PLACEHOLDER
T.K.! Goin' my way.
Here is why I have gathered all of you today.
We will commence Operation High Tension Syndrome.
Why are there no reactions?
That is an operation we have never heard of.
Yes. I just came up with it.
Yurippe, what is this operation about?
It's a simple one.
We will spend the entire day in high spirits.
That is all.
Huh?
Whatever you do, do it with high spirits.
Sprint when you're on the move.
Chug when you're drinking juice.
Shout when you speak.
Don't forget to smile.
Perform every act with high spirits, and pretend you're having a blast with your school life.
And where does this lead?
Besides, if we enjoy life here,
aren't we going to get obliterated?
No, we won't.
This is only an act we're putting on.
Acting high in spirit as the operation name suggests...
To us, it's like a penalty game.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
How unwise.
He's right. To us, this is nothing more than an ordeal.
But Tenshi, being soft-hearted, will wonder why we aren't obliterated despite having so much fun.
So what would be Tenshi's next move?
Will she do anything?
She will!
We're enjoying the school life.
It's supposed to be the condition of being obliterated.
Yet we won't be at all.
"What is going on?"
She'll get confused over the irregularity that's never happened before.
Then I'm sure she'll go and try to make contact.
You mean...
Yes! With God!
She should go inform Him that
something strange is happening.
If we follow her, we shall make our way...
...to God!
That's a crazy operation, but exactly how hard do we need to work?
The operation starts today at 9am.
We will call the operation at 9pm.
For twelve hours?!
We need to be in high spirits only in front of Tenshi, right?
You never know from where she may be watching.
So at all times.
Wait! So you're telling us to be in
high spirits for twelve hours straight?
That's right.
For your information, if this operation fails...
...we're going to fast for a week together.
Am I even capable of that?
What a fearsome operation.
By the way, I'm in charge of monitoring Tenshi, so I'm out of the operation.
Good luck everyone!
What?!
She's a devil.
Do I have to take part in this, too?
Then! Operation...
...Start!
Oh my god! What is this? It's so good!
I can't believe how good these potato chips are!
Hey, Hinata-senpai! Let's play!
A cute girl's asking you out! You lucky dog!
That does sound like I hit the jackpot, but unfortunately for you,
I'm going to be playing catch with Otonashi now!
Playing catch between guys is the way to go!
Fine! Then I'll practice for GDM!
I love playing in a band!
Going to play a loud love song or something?
Hell yeah! I'll compose the best love song and sing it out loud!
Okay, Otonashi, let's play catch!
We get to throw balls at each other!
Just thinking about it is exciting.
It gives me the chills.
Y-Yeah...
Hold on one moment!
Let me get in on that!
You're no different from usual!
I would never usually say this!
I'm saying, if you guys are going to throw,
then it could be more exciting with someone hitting!
Didn't think of that!
That sounds exciting!
That's why I said let me join!
Let me join!
Sure! I'll let you join!
Guys! Then wouldn't you want an outfielder, as well?!
Oh, that's exactly right, Matsushita Fifth!
Okay! I'm playing, too!
Would you allow me to join, too?
Look at you! You're all ready to play!
I have developed these muscles to play baseball!
You have?! Oh my god...
This is going to be one heck of a blast!
All right! Let's go to the field!
Yeah!!!
Ah! W-Wait a minute!
What are you three going to do?
Sexy.
Ooyama! If you're that hungry,
let's go to the cafeteria and chow down!
Sure! Just the way I like it!
T.K.! If you come with us, I'm sure it'll be exciting!
What do you say?!
Dive into your body!
I don't understand what you're saying, but I take it as a yes!
What about you, Shiina?!
Heck, she's not here anymore!
Okay, then it's the three of us!
We're going to eat and drink and have a blast!
It's good! It's so good! The omelet rice here is the best!
No! When it comes to cafeteria food, udon is the way to go!
It's the best stuff!
Mapo tofu, crazy night!
I finished eating it!
I want more!
Okay! I'm going to get another plate!
I'm getting one, too!
Mapo tofu, give me back!
It's already so fun; I'm shaking with joy!
Me, too!
Me, too! Me, too!
The same for me! This is what all my muscles are for!
You, too, right, Otonashi?!
Y-Yeah...
What are you planning to do?
It's her.
Baseball!
That's what defines youthful days!
Youthful days?
Right, guys?!
Youth it is!
Youth!
That's right! Youth!
Get it?
Second period is about to start.
I forgot!
But there's nothing to worry about!
Studying is part of youthful days, too!
You will be in class?
Of course!
Isn't that right, everyone?!
Yes! Studying is all about youth!
Baseball can eat shit!
Education is the way!
Indeed! These muscles are for me to better learn!
Education! Education! Education!
1858, Ansei Purge.
The elder of the Edo government, Ii Naosuke-
Yes! Ii Naosuke!
Wh-What is it?
I'm sorry. Ii Naosuke is a superhero to me, so I got excited.
What a frump hero you have.
Honno-ji...
Are we at the Honno-ji yet?!
We're past that time.
Akechi Mitsuhide!
The edict against cruelties to living things!
Give me the edict against cruelties to living things, Sensei!
What is it this time?
It is time for the edict against cruelties to living things!
That history has already been covered.
The Edo government...
Hey! You guys are too loud!
Who do you think you are?! Sogano Iruka?!
Since we're covering Japanese history.
That was supposed to be a joke?
Sensei! Please ignore them and continue with class!
Please teach me more!
I want to learn more!
Teach me! Hey, come on!
We're moving on to the next page.
In the French Revolution, as symbols
of the aristocracy, Louise XVI and Marie Antoinette-
Yes! It's Marie!
Wh-What is it?
I'm sorry. Marie is a moe heroine to me, so I'm getting all excited.
Moe?
Ah... they get executed by guillotine...
Watt's steam engine...
Are we not on Watt's steam engine, yet?!
It's already been invented.
No, the steam trains have not yet been invented.
The Second Punic War!
It is now time for the Second Punic War, Sensei!
That's been covered, too.
Poenic Government...
There was no such government.
Hey! You guys are too loud!
Who do you think you are?! Genghis Khan?!
Since we're covering world history.
This is all too crazy...
Moe moe Marie!
Time to really play baseball, guys!
Are you all ready?!
Of course! Baseball's the best!
Bring it right on!
My body's all ready for it!
We haven't cleaned yet.
That's right!
We shall get rid of our grief over death through cleaning!
Great idea!
But we won't rely on something nice, like mops.
It's the way of men to use rags!
We'll duke it out through rag cleaning!
This body of mine was practically made for rag cleaning!
The time to unleash my power has come!
They're making it harder and harder for themselves.
Ready...
...set, GO!
You cheater!
Move it!
What are they doing?
They're like that all the time.
Don't let them bother you.
I win!
No, there's still the second floor!
That was only a warmup for me!
Okay, I won't lose the next one!
It's starting to look like they're really enjoying this.
All right! That was an excellent love song, damn it!
Yeah, but it's totally a rock song!
I love Yui's lines!
I'm a woman of Naniwa, so I will protect this Naniwa.
So you live your own life.
So good!
She's going to bear the entirety of Osaka?
What an amazing woman.
We're in the middle of Operation High Tension Syndrome.
If we fail, we don't get to eat for a whole week.
I think it's great!
Isn't it?! The men and women of the world will be ecstatic over Osaka pride!
I agree!
It's a real touching love song!
You're a genius, Yui!
Hisako-senpai's wild rhythm's ingenious, too!
What's going on inside your brain?!
You're picking a fight with me, aren't you?
Well, how does going out to the field to have a concert sound, guys?!
Yay!
Crap. It was so good, I ate too much.
Yeah.
Maybe this will last us for a week since we ate this much.
The fasting Yurippe mentioned includes water.
Now that I'm full, I want to move around!
Let's go exercise this off!
Great idea!
Hey, how about learning dance from T.K.?
That's a great idea!
Hey, T.K.!
Oh my God, destruction...
It's no time for destruction!
You've got to teach us how to dance.
Let's do it somewhere open!
Let's go to the field.
Why are you guys here?
What are you doing?
Outdoor live concert, of course!
And everyone is here to enjoy that!
Let's have a blast!
We're going to play baseball here!
We're going to hit, run, play defense, and sweat the sweat of youth!
You hear that, you band lover surrounded by merry friends?!
Playing in a band is more youthful than playing baseball!
You hear that, you baseball-loving baseball maniac!?
No, no. When it comes to the debate over what's youth, it's dance!
Dancing makes you happiest.
He's right!  We're all happy!
What is this?! Damn, you guys look happy with full stomachs!
I bet everyone will be happy if this place became a dance hall!
Dance you say?! Let me dance, too!
Matsushita Fifth! I need to talk to you, who looks the happiest of all!
Baseball is the way right now!
Exactly as Takamatsu says!
I said band!
No! Dance is the way to go!
You look nothing like any kind of dancer, and you look way too happy!
Isn't that gap in character what brings excitement?!
Then let's just have a sports festival!!!
Let's just have a sports festival.
There are a lot of other students, too.
A sports festival is about the only thing that can be done with this many people.
Sports festival! Fine by me!
I smell youth from it!
Yes! This body was practically made for sports festivals!
It's going to be a good workout!
It's going to make me so happy!
We can! We can!
Are you ready, guys?!
They're showing very high spirits.
How is Tenshi looking, I wonder.
Let's ask her.
Yurippe-san!
Yes! This is Yurippe!
Hell! What are you making me do?!
I see that you're high spirited, too.
Tenshi seems to be in discussions in the Student Council room.
I think it'll be done in a bit.
Man, they're so strong.
Yeah. I'm getting seriously pumped.
Do you hear me, you guys?!
The winner of this cavalry event gets 1000 points!
We'll turn the tables with this!
Yeah!
That team's scaring me.
Which one?
Hey! Bare hands only!
Are you trying to kill people?!
Dang.
That fool.
What's that?
It's the mark of the captain.
I will stand out more than anyone and get more headbands than anyone!
Are you all ready?!
Charge!
Seeing this from the Student Council room, she must be perplexed.
She wonders why they aren't obliterated
even though they're enjoying themselves so much.
This is perfect.
It's too perfect.
Operation High Tension Syndrome.
Are you the villain?
Thanks for the high spirited comment.
She totally ruined it.
You mustn't, President!
We're still in a meeting!
I'll return soon.
And all of a sudden, it turns into the worst possible situation!
Do you know what you've done?
Take a look at this.
What is that?
ヾ(≧∇≦*)〃  CUTE!!!!  ヾ(*≧∇≦)〃
Moron.
I sense no hostility.
How am I to report this situation...
"Report"?
What? Is she...
Guys! Wake up!
We're going after her!
By the way, you guys are so weak!
What is going on?
I don't know.
But she mentioned "reporting".
You mean reporting to...
God, I'm sure.
So we hit the jackpot?
Not a single person being obliterated out of that is an irregularity that's yet to happen.
The Battlefront had an unspoken rule to not cause trouble for NPCs.
But that wasn't followed in this case.
Disregarding the outcome of the operation, we are closing on the ultimate goal of this Battlefront.
There's an entrance to the basement at a place like this?
Is this the path to God?
Password, eh? The security is equivalent to that of the Guild's.
I have no doubts.
God awaits ahead.
Charge!
I'm leaving behind anyone that falls behind!
What is this place?
It's great. It's very cute.
This is...
It's a hydroponic garden.
Yurippe, I found something like this.
Now then...
I slipped out of the meeting, the word "cute" reminded me of the turnips I was growing where the gardening club,
which was shut down, used to be, and came all the way here.
How should I report this to everyone on the Student Council?
What the hell is that?!
Oh, everyone's gathered.
What's the high security on the entrance about?!
Security?
Oh great. We were able to get in.
I didn't think it'd open by simply pressing the "open" button.
Huh?! What about the password?!
Password?
You were entering it into the number pad!
I was calculating the amount left in the club's budget.
I-It was a calculator?
As of now, the Afterlife Battlefront will...
...GO ON A WEEK OF FASTING!!!!
No way!
I'm sorry, everyone...
I've came this far alone, carrying on your wills...
But I think I'm at my limit, too...
GDM members are all down.
They're not going to die.
Yurippe-san is the best villain, after all...