Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Morning, Haruka!
Morning, Yuu-chan.
"The Other Sakura Color"
Thanks for lending me your notebook.
Math
Geez, do it yourself next time, okay?
I only copied until halfway. The rest I did all by myself.
Really?
You bet I did.
Feast your eyes.
Huh? Where'd they go?
You wrote your math answers in my classic lit notebook!
No, what have I done?!
Good morning.
Motorcycles
Bicycles
Haruka, Yuu! Mornin'!
Mornin'!
Shizuku-chan, good morning.
Good morning.
Who is this Shizuku-chan imposter?
She definitely seemed way different from usual.
Did you see that smile?
Shizuku-chan is usually more like...
G-Good morning.
Look at Kaede trying to act like all demure.
I expected it from Yuzu, but seeing you two react like that really stings.
Good melody!
Kotone-chan!
Don't jump in like that!
Hey, Kotone-chan. Shizuku-chan seems a little off today.
Do you know what's wrong?
We got in a little fight last night,
and now she's a teensy bit mad, te-he.
What kind of fight results in them acting like this?
I'm actually freeloading at Shizuku-chan's house right now.
Shizuku-chan, the bath's open now.
Did she nod off?
Time for face doodling!
No wonder she's angry!
Let me finish my story!
Sound asleep, are you?
You know, I really like living in your house.
It's a bit cramped, but it's cute and warm.
Your mom's real nice too.
And most of all,
I'm grateful for how close you live to school.
Hey, wait, just a second!
Suddenly kissing someone on the cheek is something drunk people do.
Kotone, not everybody likes being kissed.
But we're such close buddies.
Wouldn't most friends just say, "Oh, you!" and get over it?
I totally under—
Not a chance.
I wouldn't do that either.
Sakura Trick
I didn't see that coming.
Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan have a secret just like ours.
Don't you think our secret is a bit different?
Shizuku-chan was even angry today.
You don't like it either?
Stop asking me every single time; it's getting annoying.
But if you ever start disliking it, I want you to tell me.
This must be what you meant by "different"!
Stop putting words in my mouth.
I'm going on ahead.
Wait up, Yuu-chan!
Shizuku-chan.
Yuu-chan, Haruka-chan.
I told you she was angry. Just look at her eyebrows.
H-How about now?
Her mouth is seething with anger.
So Kotone told everyone.
She doesn't know when to keep her mouth shut.
I look gloomy enough on a normal day,
but I seem even more so when I get angry.
I don't want to scare people though, so I naturally put up a front and smile.
Don't worry about that stuff!
You're really cute, so just act how you want to.
Yuu-chan...
You're too close to Yuu-chan, too close to Yuu-chan...
Just look at Haruka; she doesn't hold one ounce of her emotions back.
Too close to Yuu-chan!
O-Of course, I do feel bad for hiding away and acting like this.
But she said that she liked living in my house because it was close to school.
That's basically the same as saying anyone who lived nearby would've been fine!
Doesn't that mean she'd kiss anyone who let her stay with them?
So she wasn't angry about getting a kiss on the cheek!
But it's not like I can tell anyone about what I'm thinking.
So what exactly does that make us?
Shizuku-chan, are you really fine with letting this fight with Kotone-chan go on?
Nothing will happen if you just keep running away.
That so, Sonoda?
It seems you still haven't turned your math or classic lit homework in yet.
It's time for a scolding.
Wait, Sensei! Haruka hasn't turned in her classic lit homework either!
Bring her too.
Yuu-chan, this is all because your wrote in my notebook!
Homework...
Oh yeah, we have math next.
I need to go pick up my notebook.
Did you hear that at the cafe near the station today—
Attention!
I've got all your math notebooks
here, so come'n get em!
Why does it have to be her turn to hand them back?
That's strange, there's one left over.
Whose could it be?
Buzz off, buzz off, buzz off...
buzz off
Leave the notebook here!
I bet she just wants to tease me again.
But maybe... she took it with her so we could talk alone?
Like, maybe she has a proper reason, and was actually thinking the same thing as me,
so she tried to get me alone...
No, the one who actually wants to talk...
No
...is me.
You haven't talked to me all day, so I was worried that you wouldn't follow me here.
So? I'd appreciate it if you'd give me my notebook back already.
I'm sorry.
That kiss I gave you must've freaked you out.
That's all I wanted to say.
I couldn't stand not talking to you for much longer.
Let's go back to class—
You're wrong!
I-I'm not angry that you kissed me.
Are you living with me just because my house is close to school?
Or because my mom is nice to you?
Are those the only reasons you're living with me?
It's like you don't even care I'm there at all!
sneak
sneak sneak
Why are you backing away?
Don't ask me.
Fire Hydrant
Shizuku-chan, look out!
Why did I have to get yelled at too?
I wonder if Shizuku-chan's better.
Don't change the subject.
That voice...
Shizuku-chan, are y—
Things got serious!
I've got you now.
I finally understand what made you angry.
Shall we have a do-over of last night?
Wait!
I was actually really happy when you said you liked my house for how close it was to school, so that part is fine.
What I want to do over is a different part...
You want a kiss on the lips?
It's because you're there that I love how small it is.
I love the warmth, and I love how nice your mom is.
It's because you're there that I love your house.
I-I don't think we should be watching them right now.
They'll definitely be hurt if they
find out somebody saw them.
And for some reason, I can't help but think back to when I kissed Yuu-chan.
Huh? Why did she grab my hand?
No way... don't tell me she got the urge to kiss as well?
No, Yuu-chan isn't obsessed with kissing like I am.
Then why...
This must be what you meant by "different"!
Stop putting words in my mouth. I'm going on ahead.
Which is it?!
I just got a weird idea.
Maybe I'll be able to tell if I get closer.
She closed her eyes...
Hey, Yuu-chan.
Now that Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan are doing that kind of thing,
I bet it's about time for Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan too!
That looks delectable.
Want a bite?
I won't be satisfied with just one.
I don't mind, Kaede.
Squee
Yeah, I don't think that's happening.
Hey, give me back my Pokitz! That was the last one!
Too late. It's mine now.
See, I told you!
"The Other Sakura Color"
The end
Haruka, notebook please!
Lemme copy your homework!
Again?
We've got a test next week, so do it yourself.
Pretty please?
No way.
High school isn't as forgiving as middle school.
Don't come crying to me when
you fail and get held back.
Who cares? It's just one year.
Yuu-chan, you'll be a year behind me!
I'll have to start treating you like an underclassman.
Why do you look so happy about that?!
If Yuu-chan was held back...
First-year
Second-year
Haruka!
Oh my, if it isn't my former classmate Sonoda-san.
Is that any way to address your elders?
Forgive me, Haruka-oneesama.
I just wanted to ask if you could fix my necktie.
Thud!
She called me Onee-sama! That's against the rules!
What the?
"After School with Harry-chan"
Yuu-chan would get lonely without me, and come to my class during every break.
Yuu, you need to go back to your own class soon.
No! I don't want to be separated from Haruka-oneesama!
But our school is getting shut down in three years, and we're the last incoming class,
so wouldn't she have to drop out?
Drop out
Drop out...
I wanted Yuu-chan to call me "Onee-sama"!
I wanted to fix her tie for her!
What is she talking about?!
Preparation Room
Music Room
And that covers everything that'll be on the test.
That's it for today.
Neutralization Reactions
Combination of hydrochloric acid and sodium hydroxide
Ionization
Yuu-chan will not drop out of school on my watch!
This calls for me to steel my heart and force her to study.
If Yuu-chan were to drop out,
then I'd have no reason to come to school at all!
Haruka! Lend me your notebook!
Of course!
Not!
Darn, I almost had her.
It's unfair how you keep trying to deceive me with your charm.
Do you really get that much enjoyment from toying with my heart?
I bet Shizuku-chan or Kotone-chan would lend me theirs if I asked.
Mad
After school today we're having a study session for you!
Let's begin the study session.
Let's give our all for the test!
Yeah!
Come on, Yuu-chan. Wake up.
Yuu-chan, no dozing off. Why do you think we're doing this in the first place?
math
flop
I think she's done enough.
Wake her up!
Wake up, Yuu-chan, sleep is for the weak! You don't want to drop out, do you?
'Kay...
Harupoppo, how do I do this one?
You just use the formula we learned before.
Here, on this page.
And if you use this formula there...
I get it now, thanks.
Not a problem.
Yuu-chan, how are you coming along?
Yuzu-chan, it is studying time right now!
You're mad at me?!
What can I do to keep Yuu-chan from dozing off?
Isn't that Harry-chan, the thing Yuu-chan had her eye on before?
But just what is Harry-chan?
A bear? A tanuki?
Bear
Tanuki
And what's that thing on its back?
This thing is all the rage these days, but I have no idea.
By the way, Shizuku-chan...
What's that thing you've got on your bag?
A bird? Pig? Cow?
Maybe a fox or tanuki?
Grumble
I guess that stomach growling is her answer.
Oh, so it was a tanuki!
It's a hedgehog!
Oh, a hedgehog.
I know!
Yuu-chan, rise and shine.
I drew Harry-chan everywhere
so you wouldn't fall asleep.
This should keep you focused.
Math
Really? Harry-chan? Let me see!
What is this thing? It's an abomination!
It's freaking me out.
Well, that didn't work.
No duh. I mean, this is all Yuu's fault, but still.
Why don't we start with one of her favorite subjects?
Hmm, Yuu-chan's favorite...
Me, me! I know!
Yuu-chan said that she likes gym!
And that shows up on the test where?
That's right, she likes gym!
Girls, let's go play volleyball outside.
I wanna play!
Wait—weren't we supposed to study?
Besides, isn't the baseball team
baseballing it up out there?
I think it's either them or the equestrian team.
No, they've got their own track.
Not a problem! Club activities are on hold until after exams!
We're the ones with a problem! The tests are right around the corner!
"Often" is "shiba shiba". "Understanding" is...
Commencing the "memorize chemical element names while playing volleyball" plan!
Ah, now I get it.
Haruka, nice one!
Here we go... hydrogen!
H. Water.
H2O. Carbon dioxide!
Not a clue!
Let's try again, this time with easier questions!
Yeah!
Bring it on!
Yuu-chan, make sure you give
an actual answer this time.
I'll punish you if you mess up.
Let's get it on!
Here I go!
You there!
The hell're you doing before the exams?!
We're very sorry.
I guess it wasn't such a great idea to try to study while exercising.
Let's just stick to normal studying from now on.
Good, and good for you.
No, she'll just fall asleep again.
Well, the main point is to remember things,
so how about we try doing something unforgettable while studying?
For instance?
Something embarrassing?
Are you giving yourself as an example now?
Good, and good for you.
That's definitely something unforgettable.
I need to be serious about this. Something that'll embarrass Yuu-chan...
Try translating this. You can
use a dictionary if you need to.
If you can't, it'll be what I end up doing to you.
Umm...
"The girl... hits... three times..."
And what does "her hips" mean?
Her... bu...
"Bu"?
Bu...bu...
You don't understand?
Or perhaps you want me to
teach it to your body instead?
What was that?! I'm dying of embarrassment!
Bang!
Haruka?
I wonder what Harupoppo was imagining.
But if that's what it takes to stop Yuu-chan from dropping out...
What's up with her?
Do you think she's sick?
I'm pretty sure she's still breathing.
No, that's a bit over the line. I need to think of something else embarrassing.
Why wouldn't she be?!
Ah, she stopped.
You okay? Still breathing?
Something embarrassing...
Why do you make it sound like she's on the verge of death?
When you synthesize 2H2 and O2,
what's the coefficient of the product?
Three!
Bzzt.
Please remove one article of clothing.
B-But...
This is a fair and just punishment. I'm doing this for you.
Do you need a hand from your teacher?
This is so embarrassing...
Are you too ashamed to strip alone?
I'll do it too.
Okay...
What are you making me imagine, Yuzu-chan?! You're such a pervert!
Did I offend you in a past life or something?!
It's getting pretty late.
We should be going home soon.
Come on, let's go.
Finally over. Let's buy some Pokitz on the way back.
Go on ahead, Yuu-chan and I have more work to do.
Hey, you didn't mention that before!
See ya later then.
Bye-bye.
Yakisoba-flavored
Spring
Only
Y-You haven't forgotten our secret again, right?
Where'd that come from?
W-Well, I mean...
I-I thought that if we kissed while studying, you'd be able to remember everything we went over.
What's with that reaction?!
If you'd have just studied in the first place, I wouldn't have to say all this stuff!
Stop getting farther away!
You're just doing this because you want to kiss, right?
You're wrong!
I'm not saying all this just to annoy you!
I don't want you to drop out!
I want you to study so that we can spend our entire high school lives together!
Let's start studying then.
S-Sure. I'll give you the problem,
so answer after we kiss.
Fill in the blank. "May I (go) with you?"
Ready? Here I come.
I can't answer if this never ends.
Um, is it "go"?
Yeah, that's right.
Next is correcting the bracketed word.
"I want one (more) piece of paper."
"More".
That's right.
More...
More, more!
Is she saying that to me?
Yuu-chan, don't just dawdle there. Let's go home.
Thanks.
One Week Later
English
This is one of the questions we reviewed!
I hope Yuu-chan isn't sleeping back there.
She remembers everything!
tumble
Takayama-san?!
Aw, you're adorable, Yuu-chan!
"After School with Harry-chan"
The end
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai deaeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
I'm Sonoda Yuu.
Yuu-chan's such a cutie!
Kotone-chan, why are you here?
Well, I didn't really get to say much last week.
Isn't that because you just kept repeating yourself?
But Shizuku-chan is just way too cute.
Alright, I got it already.
Angry Yuu-chan is such a cutie.
Yuu-chan
Haruka
Next time, Trick 3:
"The President is an Onee-chan"
"A Promise Made While Cleaning the Pool"
"The President is an Onee-chan",
and "A Promise Made While Cleaning the Pool".
Look forward to it, 'kay?