After I arrived in Tokyo a few days ago...
...I've been waking up to an unusual sight.
Sheesh...
Do I need to repeat myself?
Morning...
I told you to not use anything
with my name on it.
Cheapskate.
Can't you show some mercy?
NINA
It helps me with the hangovers.
No way.
Didn't I ask you if you yesterday
if you wanted some for yourself?
I was drunk, you know.
So, did you hear back?
Not yet.
It's not easy to get back a
place you just stopped renting.
- And your job?
- Same thing.
Well, I've got things to take care of on my end.
2: THREE NOCTURNAL CREATURES
This looks more like a hospital than a school.
It's private tuition after all.
80 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN ACCEPTED INTO REPUTABLE COLLEGES!!
You coming here every day?
No way! I don't have that kind of money.
ADMISSION FORM
I'll have to study a lot on my own
to get into a good university.
So you wanna go to uni?
To tell you the truth, no, not really, but...
...dropping out of educatio
nonly leads to trouble.
Yeah, it is rough.
And those who "told you so"
will relish in it.
But oh well, that's none of my business.
As long as you have time to rehearse, it's all good.
You're free in the evenings and weekends, right?
Though you'll need to get a job too.
Hold on a minute.
Form a band?
- You said so, right?
- I said no such thing.
Yes, you did.
"Please... let's flip them off together!"
Please don't do that in public.
Ouch.
I just meant we should focus
on our respective paths.
I wasn't saying that I wanted to sing.
Me with my studies, you with your music.
Oh, is that what you meant?
I thought some things didn't add up.
I should be the one saying that.
It gets really packed even this late, huh?
Spoken like a bumpkin.
Shut up.
Well, as long as you put in the effort to study,
don't you still wanna try forming a band?
You already know that's impossible.
Oh, I'm not saying you should learn an instrument.
If you ask me, you'd make a great singer, Nina.
Eh? A singer?
You've got the voice, and especially the heart for it.
Who, me?
Yep.
You know, to me a band...
Is a gathering place for people
who have a lot of things they want to say.
Folks crying out things like "I wanna be loved",
"This world sucks",
"I can't with everything anymore",
"I love myself", or "I hate myself"...
I thought you wanted to go solo.
Thought so too at first,
but I miss being in a band.
There's so much gossip, arguing,
and tension that you gotta hold in
while pretending everything's perfect.
But since you're always together,
there comes a point where you
can't keep it up and just explode.
Not a single positive, then.
Oh. Right...
But still... it's fun.
Creating something with others
that you never could on your own.
What's that?
It's nothing.
You'll probably get home faster from this station.
It's... shockingly rural for being in a city, isn't it?
That's the appeal of this area.
Your place is over there.
And there should be a super nearby. I'll show you.
Oh? Ah, thanks.
Ouch.
Is this really okay?
Don't sweat it.
Think of it as paying back my share of rent.
- But...
- I said don't sweat it.
Just leave it in the fridge for now.
Though I'll warn you, I'm not much of a chef.
At least you can cook.
Let's just say I don't hate it.
Now then, knife, knife...
It's a bit like composing a song.
You chop the veggies while the water boils.
You prepare the sauce and let it simmer.
You juggle many different things,
but you bring them all together to form a cohesive whole.
Wow, this knife sucks!
I'm sorry, I don't have any other knives...
No need to apologize for stuff like this.
But it reminds me that I'm
unable to do anything on my own.
I'll never make it living alone.
What, you think it's funny?
Nah. I'm very much the same.
All you can do is just force your way through it.
Through all the struggles, bothers, and realizations,
FLIP THEM OFF!
And keep trying 'till you get it right.
Buying actual plates would be a good start.
I'm sorry.
TO DO LIST
Right, food's ready!
Guess we'll need to add buying a lamp too.
Are we gonna just... eat like this?
So you do come from a stacked family after all.
That's something rich folks would say.
Not at all, we're actually a pretty normal home.
It's just... how to put it, a bit strict.
Like how we have family precepts.
Precepts?
Ah, like house rules?
Indeed...
Firstly: the family should always eat together.
Family precepts
Secondly: you shouldn't use your phone in the living room.
Thirdly: every Sunday the family should gather together.
You get the idea.
Here.
Eventually word got out in class about the type of household I was in
and how it prided itself in its strictness.
Right, I can see where this is going.
Because of that I couldn't go
back to school, so I had to drop out.
Wait, why?
It's not really important.
That's why?
H-how could you tell?
It's written all over your face.
She's the most popular girl at my school.
A real beauty.
All the boys were flocking at her feet.
So what, she bullied you?
Sorta...
Why?
Why would I know?
I think she just hates me...
And you didn't stand up for yourself?
That girl made sure
She had enough friends so no one could touch her.
She even had her friends ignore me and bully me.
I even had to go to the hospital once, and yet
both my teachers and parents just told me to stop being problematic-
Stop.
Eat. Before it overcooks.
Don't worry. I like my vegetables well done.
See, you really are cut out for singing.
What you just said, that's like five songs.
You know, I wanted to try out
a band where I don't do the vocals.
I'd like to focus on what I
can communicate through my guitar.
Are you sure?
Yep.
Dropping out of high school?
You'd be throwing away your future.
Even if you changed your
mind later, it'll be too late.
Then...
I just need to get into a university, right?
I'll study on my own if I must!
No. If I don't keep up with my studies,
and get into a university, then my life's over.
Over, you say...
Oh no, I don't mean it that way.
It's just that if I don't, I'll have
to admit I was always wrong.
To my bullies, teachers, and parents.
I get it.
I won't ask again then.
I'm sorry.
I already said, no need to apologize.
You've still got beer left, right?
Woah, that's heavy!
Of course, they're books.
I'll carry the big ones, you can go get the lighter ones.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Will one trip be enough?
It's alright, this is the last of the big ones.
Can you check if I forgot anything?
Sure!
Nothing left, right?
Gotta study again later.
Here!
You'll probably be needing this.
Ah. I guess so.
I don't even know how
to play it to begin with.
I guess it would be
better off in my hands.
Thank you.
Right then, I'm off.
- Eh? Are you sure you don't need my help?
- Don't worry, it's oaky.
I see.
Well, I guess there's one
last favor you could do me.
What is it?
What a big place for a city...
The Tamagawa River, you've heard of it, right?
It's bigger than I thought.
Never thought Tokyo had places like this.
Tokyo's on the other side over there.
Close, but not quite.
We're on the edge of Tokyo, huh.
Abut that favor you needed?
It's nothing special.
I just wanted to hear you sing one last time.
Any song you like.
And to wish you good luck with your studies.
I'm heading back to my old place, so...
...if you're ever free, let's
go grab a bite together.
Sure!
Good luck with your
music too, Momoka-san.
I promise I'll make a song you can be proud of.
Thanks.
And please don't forget to
keep flipping them off.
The same to you.
Ehm...
If you could raise your pinkie
rather than your middle finger...
Then I'll do the same.
Gotcha.
Right, then.
If it were up to you, would you keep going?
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés.
Even if my fingers tremble...
There's no right answers,
there's no giving in,
My whole life, I've just been me.
That's all there is to it.
No matter how much I fight from here on,
tomorrow isn't set in stone.
Oh no...
Where was I...
"Jim told her to not give up."
"Even amidst the darkness,
I'm sure a ray of hope will someday..."
Gotta buy a new lamp.
GIRLS BAND CRY.
And here's where it gets complicated: the right pronoun...
That was so fun!!
I got two at the same time!
- No way!
- I know, right?
I haven't talked to anyone.
I haven't talked to anyone all week.
Have you finished unloading?
Yeah, all done. My back's killing me.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Thanks.
We should meet
THE WEATHER
Back to studying.
FROM: MOMOKA
Have you bought a lamp yet?
I've got a spare if you need it.
Thank you! I would love to.
Can I come get it?
Good evening.
...Good evening.
Right, should be around here...
Here!
Please excuse me!
Woah, you came rushing!
Sorry to intrude.
Especially all of a sudden like this.
It's over there. Hopefully it should do the trick.
Thank you. As long as it can light up...
What? Have you settled in yet?
I wonder...
Since you came this far,
wanna go grab a bite?
I've got a job back, so I'll treat you.
Ah, yes, I'd love to!
Is she the famous Nina-chan?
Yep.
I got the lamp from Awa-san.
She's my new drummer.
I'm Awa Subaru!
Nice to meetcha!
...Uh, I'm Iseri.
Subaru, wanna join us? You'll have to pay your share, though.
Why? You cheapskate.
Hey, I'm not made of money.
All good?
Ah, actually, I'll just go home.
Come on! Nina's new to Tokyo after all.
Subaru's your age, you'll get along great.
Woah, what a big pot.
You've added too many veggies.
Cabbage loses all its flavor
if you boil it too long.
Here.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
So, what music do you like, Nina-chan?
Any favorite bands or vocaloids?
She told me she likes old Showa music,
which she got from her grandma.
Ooh? Nice! I like that too.
Any favorites?
I mean, "favorite" is a strong word...
Wait, are they playing Glarech?
Oh, true!
You listen to them?
I've been to their concerts twice,
and once at a festival too.
- Like the one in Chiba?
- The very same.
They totally sucked though.
Wow, they suck that much?
Yeah, they've amounted to nothing since.
Ever since, they haven't showed up again.
I didn't even realize they were gone...
Even if everyone loved them at first.
Nina-chan, have you ever been to a concert?
Not really...
I see.
By the way, can I add meat to the pot?
Oh, don't you like it?
Nina-chan?
Sorry, I need to...
Do you not like her?
Not really...
Then try talking to her a little.
She's trying hard to be friends with you.
Trying hard?
You mean she's being forced to get along.
I get where you're coming from, but...
She doesn't know anything about you either.
it's just... I feel like I'm being talked down to.
That's all in your head.
She goes to a prestigious acting school,
it's just her way of speaking.
She's not trying to be mean.
Yeah, what a great person she is.
She's even willing to pretend
To act nice with such an inferior like me.
You're just being biased!
No, I'm not!
No one's gonna talk to you if you keep up that attitude.
Hey!
Of course.
I'm doomed to never have any friends.
Since I'm such a pain.
Now, hold up.
I'm gonna be alone for the rest of my life.
Thanks for the food.
- Thanks for this..
- You're... welcome.
What an idiot.
She already has what she
needs more than anything.
What was I thinking?
What was I doing?
She was just trying to be nice
and trying to get to know me, that's all.
I'm stupid.
So stupid.
You idiot! Idiot!!
Dumbass! Moron! Imbecille!
I'm an idiot...
Shut up already!
- You shut up!
- What did you say?
The hell's that mean?
SHUT UP!!
Wa-wait... stop!
GO AWAY!!
I can't even fix a light on my own.
I'm doomed to stay in the dark.
I'm never getting out of this darkness...
Forever.
Come on, we really
should form that band.
Momoka-san?
Subaru...-chan?
You should hide your double key better.
And you already ruined the lamp!
I told you Nina, I love your voice.
What do you gain by lying to me?
I'm not lying.
You're a walking paradox of negativity,
But that's because you're simply
too honest with yourself.
You're a coward, but you refuse to ever give up.
You've helped me remember what I forgot,
The things I hold deeply and cherish the most.
And why I sing.
You... you don't have to feel sorry for me...
Stop laughing!
What a pain!
Ouch!
Take all that pain, and inject it all...
...into music!
Here.
NEXT: UNORTHODOX Q&A.