Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Everyone
has
their place
Everyone
has
their place
Everyone should know their place in this world. Monks are to be monks and commoners are to be commoners. Emperors are to be emperors and retainers are to be retainers. Disregarding one's place is evil.
Says
Priest
Myoue
from Toganoo
I promise no salvation in a world beyond this one.
I merely say that we ought to live this life as we are meant to be.
from Toganoo
Father...
Mother...
The Youthful Youngest Child's Problems and the Beginning and the End
He's got a weird face.
Really ugly.
And he's drooling.
The hell are you doing here?
Say what?
You've woken up?
Thanks for the food!
Dig in.
What are they doing here?
I asked my neighbor to make breakfast!
You must have been hungry.
This's great!
We should swing by tomorrow!
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Celery
Juice
Hey, that's mine!
I ain't treating you! Cough up my dough!
Hey! You!
Come on!
You're gonna pay for this.
Celery
Juice
Let's take the day off.
Yuck!
Surely a single can of juice is
nothing to get worked up about.
More importantly, why is one of us
skipping the meeting to waste time?
This is a yearly occurrence for the kiddo.
He must feel he trained in vain
with the utter lack of donations.
That's precisely the reason.
He doesn't want us to see him while he's not at full steam.
It's his own fault if he gets his hopes up and is delegated to the holding track.
Now you're being hard on him.
He always looks at me like only he is suffering.
Are we not on the same train?
Well, not really, but that annoys me even more.
He cannot return by now, just as the days of old will never return.
That reminds of a story.
There was a certain dog that kept waiting for his master.
He just kept waiting for his
master's return in the same spot.
But his master had died already.
The dog kept waiting and waiting unaware of his death,
until at long last the dog tired of waiting and died himself.
What a tragic story.
Can't you feel the tears welling up?
Did the dog have no legs?
No voice to call his master?
Ears to listen for replies?
What if he did?
Then he was a stupid dog.
Why do you say so?
Surely his master never told him to die.
He should have gotten on with life at some point.
I see. An opinion that befits you.
I have my own opinion regarding this story.
Hachiko
Was the dog truly waiting for his master?
If so, would he not have acted differently?
But if the dog was waiting precisely for what came in the end...
Silence! Don't lampoon the dog's devotion! That's depressing!
Oh my, absit omen.
Myoue!
Hey.
You floated away your stuff already?
Nah.
What about you?
You don't need that anymore?
That's why I'm floating it away.
I'm fine. I'll just buy new stuff.
I envy you.
I was thinking of taking up soccer.
Koto's really good at it.
Did you know?
No.
Myoue!
What are you doing here?!
Dodgeball.
Isn't that obvious?
Tell him we're investigating!
He's gonna give us the bead treatment if he finds out we're just playing.
We're investigating!
You're just playing.
Are you okay?
Is he dead? Myoue's dead?
The outside world doesn't make any sense either, but that's what makes it fun!
You're pulling my leg!
What a weird tale.
That's so like you, Koto.
I know she's weird.
I'm serious! Let's go there one day!
I'll take you to the outside world one day.
But...
I promise.
Looking forward to it.
Don't promise something you can't live up to.
You got in, but now you're just leeching off me!
All you're doing is screwing around, hoping something will change.
It looks to me like you just want to chill here.
What's wrong, Myoue?
Just looking at you pisses me off.
You're stupid, inconsiderate, and cheeky.
I always get the short end of the stick.
Nobody does anything but get in my way.
Just piss off already!
Myoue?
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Let me crash!
I'm sorry I just turned up,
but your boyfriend went nuts.
So you came here to get back at him?
You brought plenty of food too.
Try these.
You're a funny one, Koto.
Nobody else can piss him off like you can.
He gets pissed off all by himself just fine.
Maybe.
This is great!
He's always pissed off,
but earlier it was just...
He seemed like he was seriously angry with me.
I don't really get it.
I feel persecuted.
It's been a long time since he actually got mad.
I was getting the feeling he'd really calmed down.
He's been ditching work for a long time now.
I'm glad you came.
Help Myoue. Okay, Koto?
What are you talking about?
Please.
I'm the one in need of help here.
No sweat.
You're not making more sense than your boyfriend.
What shall we eat for dinner...
Want something in particular?
Meat or something?
Or something?
I'm sorry you had to tolerate my pastimes for such a long time.
This is the last of my selfish acts.
You should carry Priest Myoue from now on.
Take good care of things in my absence.
One day I promise I will return with the beginning and the end in tow.
I promise.
Wait for me,
Myoue.
Fine.
I guess it's your turn now.
Is she still here?
I wound up here because I read the sign wrong...
A child has to know its own
direction, even if it has no name.
If you want to take that luggage on
board, put the "fragile" sticker on it.
You read the sign wrong, so...
Never mind what you're told.
Just buy your ticket when the train stops.
I sure hope she's not trying to board the train.
Right?
Hey!
Oh, Inuyama! 'Sup?
What'cha doin' here?
Taking Myoue out for a walk?
Just kiddin'!
Come on, don't be mad, Myoue!
You waiting for some chick?
Drop it.
What are you doing here?
Just my little sociology excursion.
I'm on my way home now, though.
Did you come to welcome me, Inuyama?
That's so nice of you! Thanks!
What now?
Nothing.
How about some food?
Chapter Fifteen
Present (10)/ The Two of Them
What's for dinner?
Fish!
Come on! I want meat!
Too fast!
Want to swap seats?
No, thanks.
We'll be fine! Let me!
No!
Bishamaru
the Peerless
A fiery spirit and punch!
A breathtaking adventure!
Premiere
Hey!
A fiery spirit and punch!
A breathtaking adventure!
Can you please shut up?
I'm so gonna kill you...
You told me to shut up.
What the hell?!
Almost everything's sold out!
Seeing it makes me kind of sad.
Yeah.
Hey, did it ever occur to you to board
that train and see if it takes you home?
Oh, man! It never did!
You can be pretty smart, Myoue!
Sarcasm?
I'll try next time it turns up.
I'm fine for now.
I've got plenty to do.
Oh, really?
Can I go home now?
No!
Can't you go to the forbidden area alone?
No! You'll never hear the end of it if you don't come with me!
A and Un are waiting for us!
We promised we'd see them.
Myoue!
Yeah, yeah.
And be cool.
Of course.
I think A and Un are really cute! Aren't they?
They're the first...
relatives, or family, for me.
But they aren't human like you. You okay with that?
Sure.
Normally that'd be relevant when accepting your family...
Was there nothing easier you could've picked for a name?
Like Tarou or Jirou or something.
Sound like my grandfather.
Huh?
That isn't even true!
I think it's cool as heck.
"A" and "Un" stand for the beginning and the end.
I...
think...
just understood...
Take this!
Keep the change!
Damn! Wait, Koto!
Wait! Lemme give you a good beating!
Like hell!
Damn! Wait!
What do you think you're doing?!
What?
I think that the black rabbit you're looking for is our mother.
I'll help you looking for her.
Let's adopt him!
Heavens! What happened?
I found him.
In exchange I want you to help me too.
There's a place I've wanted to go to for ages.
Once we find our mother,
please kill me.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight