What the fuck is this?!
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
through a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Question 12
Idiots, and Clowns, and A Song for the Dead
Disaster strikes Fumizuki Academy.
Good day
He sure has some neat equipment, even though he's just Akihisa's summon.
Is it strange?
'Tis just as tall as a human too!
Hold it, guys! Isn't there something else you should be wondering about?
HEAD
I got it! I got it! Don't point two of those faces at me!
Is it strange?
Now it's too big to do any odd jobs for me.
Couldn't you sound a little more concerned?!
Morning!
Good morning!
Good morning, girls!
Slapping
I'm sorry! I didn't know what was going on.
Oh, no! I'm sorry for frightening you too.
T-That's right! How dare you surprise us like that?
I wonder if the other summons are any different.
Shall we see for ourselves?
Summon!
What is this?
It looks like they've changed to represent their master's true nature.
I see. Then my summon...
was influenced by my chivalrous spirit—
Get real, Akihisa.
Or was it my unmatched manliness, or how I excel at sports...
Perhaps 'tis headless for thou hast no brains.
You just had to say it! I was trying so hard to ignore it, but you said it anyway!
Yes, the truth is often painful.
Yuuji's summon appears much like himself, indeed.
Is it a clone?
What are you talking about? This Sakamoto Yuuji is definitely a monster!
Just look at that ugly face and disgusting appearance—
Here we come, Olympics!
Nadeshiko Japan!
You kicked it, Yuuji! You kicked my summon's head like a soccer ball!
Oh, don't get mad, Akihisa.
Don't they say "Your friend is a ball"?
Your friend is a ball
It's "The ball is your friend!"
The ball is your friend
Good Lord!
A werewolf!
W-Why did it transform? There's no full moon!
Did it see something else round?
Oh yeah, I guess it really is like a ball.
Do you two want to try too?
I guess so. Okay.
Summoned being!
Summon!
Please don't look at it!
Yeah, it sure is an obvious trait.
What?! I know I'm a little fat, but it's not that noticeable—
Stop, Himeji!
If you say any more, a certain someone who is really unnoticeable will—
Do you have something you want to say to me, Aki?
Good grief!
Your summon is like that because you're so promiscuous, Mizuki.
Minami, that's so mean of you!
But I don't have to worry about anything like that.
I'm sure I'll have a really cute summon. Watch!
Summon!
Shit!
Shit! I can't laugh now, or she'll kill me!
I can't laugh now or she'll kill me!
Hey, Aki?
What is it, Minami?
I wonder what this summon is trying to tell me.
I wonder now.
Damn! I need to mention something apart from how flat it is!
I got it!
You and that wall are so hard and so strong that—
Who are you calling hard and strong?!
The truth hurts, in many ways.
Spine
Get away from my darling, you pig!
M-Miharu...
It's a grave sin for you to bathe in her true feelings, you filthy pig!
headache
I'm going to send you back to Hell!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Shut up, you noisy brats!
You guys are...
Who were you again?
What the fuck, man?
We're Tsunemura and Natsukawa from 3-A!
Oh, the summerfags.
Summerfags? Where have I heard that word before?
Don't give us weird nicknames like that!
These two are the guys who appeared at the cultural festival.
You brats were talking so loud that we heard it all the way in our classroom and couldn't concentrate on our studies.
That's a cruel accusation.
This is the third floor, and Class F at that!
You're on another floor, in another building at that!
Indeed, one cannot imagine it was that loud.
You were just loafing around because you were bored of studying.
Then, you heard Akihisa's moronic voice, so you decided to punch him once or twice, right?
Did you just insult me in a casual way?
Don't sweat the details! You're still so annoying!
Didn't you pull off that peeping parade recently and get everyone suspended?
What are you gonna do if the academy's reputation falls and our exams are affected?!
Academy
Reputation
Exams
You heard them, Yuuji. Go apologize.
Come on, Akihisa. Apologize to the nice gentlemen already.
We were talking to both of you!
Whatever are you talking about?
Cut the crap!
Let's see how brave you really are!
Math, huh?
It's perfect! Summon!
Gender
War hammer
SPEAR
Student of 3-A
Points
Math
You're going down!
What the?!
Gender
Staff
Student of Class D
Student of Class A
Points
Math
It's my turn to beat that swine into pulp!
Gender
Points
Don't interfere!
How dare you try to hurt Yoshii?! I don't care if you're my seniors.
I will stop you!
Shimizu! But why Kubo too?
Do they not look alike?
Fallen gods.
They stray from the path of man and entice others to join them.
How fitting.
Natsukawa Shunpei
Tsunemura Yuusaku
Shimizu Miharu
Kubo Toshimitsu
Math
Damn!
Time to finish this!
That's enough!
Principal!
Save your marks for the event that's going to happen soon.
What event?
Forget about that! Get our summons back to normal first!
The school building looks like a haunted house right now!
That's a clever observation coming from an idiot like you.
We're going to have a Battle of the Grades!
A Test of Courage tournament using summons!
Battle    of    the    Grades
Test of Courage
A Test of Courage tournament?!
I bet you just messed up the summon system again, didn't you?
Perfect! I'll let you kids handle it.
Ugh!
So, the second-years or the third-years? Who will be the monsters?
Of course, we wanna do the scary part!
We ought to teach our juniors how it's done.
Fine. The third-years will be the monsters,
and the second-years will be the challengers.
Here are the rules for the Battle of the Grades and the Test of Courage tournament!
Rules
Battle of the Grades
Test of Courage Tournament
Whee! Blah, blah, blah.
The challengers will enter the haunted house in pairs.
Once inside, if they shout or make any noise higher than a particular level,
Yiiiikes!
Scream
Meter
Disqualified
they'll be disqualified.
Start
They need to pass through four checkpoints, while fighting off monsters and other summons.
Checkpoint
If they win the fight, they'll clear that checkpoint and can move to the next.
Defeated
Start
If they clear all four checkpoints, the challengers win.
But if all the challengers are defeated, the monsters win.
Yay!
It ain't fun if we just get to fight each other.
Let's decide on what we'll make you do when you lose.
Hold it right there!
This is a school event. Don't just make up your own rules!
But... come on...
Don't fret, you guys.
You can fight us one-on-one at the checkpoints.
Know what I mean?
Interesting.
We'll pulverize you!
Me?
Question 12:
Read the following passage
and answer the question.
King Xiang built fortifications
at Gai Xia, but his soldiers
were few, and supplies low.
The armies of Han and the
other states had him
completely surrounded and
greatly outnumbered them.
At night, the army of Han
would sing songs from Chu
all around the fortress, which
alarmed King Xiang.
"Has Han already taken Chu?
Why have they so many men of Chu among them?"
He awoke in the middle of the night and drank in his tent.
Give an idiom that applies to this situation.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
"Trapped like a rat"
Teacher's comment:
Correct. "Chu's song," which was
supposed to be sung by their allies,
was instead heard from the
enemy camps around them.
In other words, this meant their
allied troops surrendered
to the enemy.
Thus, we can say they were trapped
and helpless like rats.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer
"The early bird gets the worm"
Teacher's comment:
He was forestalled.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer
"The early bird gets the worm"
Teacher's comment:
He was defeated too, by the way.
That's how it is. Only one pair at a time can enter the haunted house.
I want you all to pair up, one boy with one girl.
But if the girl screams too loud, the boy will get disqualified too!
It doesn't really matter. That makes this event more exciting.
All right! Form your pairs!
So, what's the real reason?
Shouko threatened me, so I got everyone else involved too.
If you don't pair up with me, we're getting married. Immediately.
CONTRACT
Party A, Kirishima Shouko, and party B, Sakamoto Yuuji,
hereby form the following contract.
- Clause 1 -  (Purpose)
B shall be A's fiancé. B will constantly be together with A in both her private
and school life. B also consents to being monopolized by A at any time.
- Clause 2 -  (Preferential treatment)
B will treat A preferentially, such as making a team with A in school activities
A is participating in, such as "Battle of the Grades: Test of Courage Tournament."
- Clause 3 -  (Guarantee)
If B takes any action that goes against clauses 1 and 2, B shall promptly
marry A and live together with her for life.
A) Fumizuki Academy 2-A
Kirishima Shouko
B) Fumizuki Academy 2-F
Sakamoto Yuuji
What's the matter, Mizuki?
Huh? No... Um...
Himeji?
I've always been really scared of monsters.
Yoshii Family Graiv
I'm sure I'll be the first to scream really loud and just ruin our chances.
Himeji, you don't have to go in if you're so scared.
That's... That's right!
You don't have to...
Everyone has things they're bad with.
We'll make sure to do our best, so you don't have to take part, Himeji.
Okay.
Curse you, Yoshii Akihisa!
I'll be sure to cast you into Hell!
Shimizu!
What do you want?
Will you join hands with me?
I'm listening.
And so, the curtain rose on the Battle of the Grades, the Test of Courage tournament.
This is rather elaborate.
T-They're all fake, aren't they?
This isn't that scary—
Scream
Meter
Disqualified
Scream
Meter
Disqualified.
Disqualified
Bzz!
The third-years are certainly giving it their all.
This might be harder than I thought.
Dammit.
Why do I have to pair up with a guy?
Extra
It's your fault for being unpopular with the girls!
What did you say?!
Who's the loser who hit on more than 20 girls and got rejected every time?
You're wrong! I wasn't rejected! It was just a bad time—
Extra
It's just a bad time for me too!
I'm not totally unpopular!
I'm not unpopular either!
Me neither!
Extra
Scream
Meter
Me neither!
I didn't want to be like this, you know?!
Disqualified
Disqualified.
Great, Natsukawa.
This should make those second-years shit their pants!
You think so?
It's time to make those brats cry for their mommies!
M-Mikami!
Are you all right?
Thank... you!
Hey... did something flash on the screen just now?
I don't see anything.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you, Mikami.
There's no way such childish monsters—
Aaaaargh!
You've gone too far, you bastards!
Disgusting! Not just their methods, but even that picture is disgusting!
It's scarier than a monster!
I'll never be able to sleep again.
Disqualified
Our forward forces have all been annihilated!
Shit, guys!
Whatever shall we do? 'Tis impossible to defeat such a fearsome enemy!
Leave it to me!
Voyeur!
I'll come with you, Voyeur.
Let's teach the crew cut what true horror really is!
Here they come!
Get ready!
Do I really look like that?
Come on, senior! Smile!
I'm going to upload this to the Internet.
This isn't funny!
I'll remember this!
Bye-bye!
Checkpoint
There you are!
Nanami
Ichihara
Let's get to it, then.
Summon!
Gender
UNARMED
Student of 3-A
Points
PE
Voyeur, the third-years' summons look pretty tough.
Indeed, but...
Summon!
They're of no concern to us.
Ichihara Roujirou
Nanami Kenichi
Tsuchiya Kouta
Kudou Aiko
PE
Challengers
Aiko & Voyeur
Victory
Whooooaaaa!
They did it!
You two are awesome!
Yuuji, what just happened?
I couldn't see it clearly,
but I think that first faceless creature took off her clothes for an instant,
beat the crap out of those two, then put her clothes back on again.
But what cause did it have to undress?
In that instant, Voyeur started bleeding, stopped bleeding, and got a transfusion.
Good job, Voyeur!
It looks like we're set to win!
No, the third-years...
won't give up so easily.
We should be close to the next checkpoint.
Yeah.
What is it?
I am pleased to meet you.
I am from Class 3-A, and a member of the Tea Ceremony Club,
Kogure Aoi.
Are you all right, Voyeur?
It's just a flesh wound.
How cute!
But I possess one more set of clothes.
One more set?
In fact, I'm...
a member of...
the Gymnastics Club too!
Burst
Voyeur!
Scream
Meter
He won't... He won't stop bleeding!
Disqualified
We'll save you! Charge!
Charge!
Gymnastics! Gymnastics! Gymnastics! Gymnastics!
This is bad, Yuuji!
We need to grab a camera and get there right now!
Sorry, Akihisa! I couldn't see what was going on!
The sight would've been too much for Yuuji.
I think I got the gist of it, though.
I have a plan!
I don't like this.
I'm not really good at this sort of thing.
Oh?
A team of two girls, is it?
You're right! Her charms won't work on those two!
Yeah! Plus the sister is from Class A!
Well, I really dislike violence.
Well then, I'll leave the rest to you!
Understood! Summon!
Male Student of Class 3-A
Gender
UNARMED
Student of 3-A
Points
Chemistry
That appearance is really something, but those marks are nothing to worry about!
Summon!
Why does yours have cat ears, but mine is a full-fledged cat?
It must be because thou art a wolf in cat's clothing.
Wolf       in
cat's       clothing
What—
...did you say?
Got you!
Sister!
I'm not so weak that I need you to worry about me.
By the way...
Male Student of Class 3-A
Gender
UNARMED
CLAWS
Student of 3-A
Points
Chemistry
I really hate bugs.
That was easy. Let's go.
Understood.
Wait, Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
What's he doing?
Kinoshita Hideyoshi, I was waiting for you.
I don't know what he wants, but finish it quick, Hideyoshi.
I'll cut to the chase.
What do you want?
Kinoshita Hideyoshi, I...
really...
love you!
On that day...
for the first time in my life...
I heard Hideyoshi scream.
I heard Hideyoshi scream...
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem.
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby.
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you.
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N.
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go.
I've fallen in love.
I don't want any doubts in my heart.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Sparkling, glittering.
The right answer is pop!
Let's sing along!
"The Sun and the Sunflower"
Composed by Tsunemura Yuusaku
By the time I realized it, I was always chasing after you.
By the time I remembered, I was always watching out for your smile.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
If I am a sunflower,
you are the sun,
which shines upon me.
I chase after your shining brilliance
and become a big flower
to catch it all.
I don't have the words
to express these
feelings of mine clearly,
but I still want you to know.
I love you, Kinoshita.
I am really,
completely
in love with you.
"The Sun and the Sunflower"
By the time I realized it, I was always chasing after you.
By the time I remembered...
I don't have the words to express these feelings of mine clearly,
but I still want you to know.
I love you, Kinoshita.
I'm really, completely, in love with you.
Forgive me, for that unbecoming yodel.
Don't worry about it, Hideyoshi.
That's right, Hideyoshi.
There's no way anyone could take that calmly.
"The Sun and the Sunflower"
Composed by Tsunemura Yuusaku
By the time I realized it,
I was always chasing after you.
By the time I remembered,
I was always watching out
for your smile.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
If I am a sunflower,
you are the sun,
which shines upon me.
I chase after your shining brilliance
and become a big flower to catch it all.
I don't have the words to express these feelings of mine clearly,
but I still want you to know.
I love you, Kinoshita.
I am really, completely in love with you.
How... could he... read a love poem to me?!
"The Sun and the Sunflower"
Composed by Tsunemura Yuusaku
By the time I realized it,
I was always chasing after you.
By the time I remembered,
I was always watching out
for your smile.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
If I am a sunflower,
you are the sun,
which shines upon me.
I chase after your shining brilliance
and become a big flower to catch it all.
I don't have the words to express these feelings of mine clearly,
but I still want you to know.
I love you, Kinoshita.
I am really, completely in love with you.
It was
damn
disgusting.
I was stunned too.
Yeah
Well then, it's time to get our hands dirty.
Hey! You listening to this, losers?
Aaaaargh!
Those bastards...
If you're so pissed, why don't you get here and duke it out?
You say something too, Tsunemura.
Kinoshita, I really—
Hey, Yoshii! Sakamoto! Listen up!
I can't wait any more! Come at me!
I'm looking forward to it!
Those assholes!
Bring it on, you fuckers!
Question 13:
Calm down, go over
all the questions
we've covered so far,
and write how
satisfied you are
with your answers.
Mizuki Himeji's answer:
I did everything to the best
of my abilities, but
I still can't relax.
I can never really
be satisfied with
my answers,
no matter how
many times
I re-check them.
Teacher's comment:
That's just like you, Himeji. If you believe yourself to be perfect, you can either take pride in it, or you can try to prevent yourself from becoming too arrogant about it. Although these feelings seem contradictory, they are both important. There are workers who always do their work to 100%, as well as workers who will never reach 100%. Both of these attitudes are wonderful.
Yoshii Akihisa's
answer:
I always get my
name right!
Teacher's comment:
That's difficult to
get wrong in the
first place.
Question 13.
Calm down, go over all the questions we've covered so far,
and write how satisfied you are with your answers.
I always get my name right!
That's difficult to get wrong in the first place.
Next time: Idiots, and tests, and summons!
Next time:
Idiots, and Tests, and Summons!
This will be on the test.