I can't get out because there's no door...
Because there's no door...?
Yuki...
Yuki... Yuki... Yuki...
Yuki!
Yuki...
No...
Say something, Yuki...
No...!
Yuki!
Because there's no door...?
No.
There is a door...
That's...
...for Tama to select...
"This Selection..."
Taken and granted,
ideals are repetitious games that slip through
My daily life is so shot with holes
that I can barely stand
Empty theories without conclusions
Dance steps along invisible rules
The final bell holding together
the crumbling day rings
In the scene I imagine
you're there
with a smile
No forgiveness? No desires?
And still
We cry "OPEN"
A future to get back and a world to destroy
A wish to open. GOT IT?
Now cross
I wish you don't cry
The future of light and dark,
let's believe in the "future"
so that they overlap to gain color again
"No Trespassing"
We'll be in big trouble if
the person earlier finds out...
But, we need to check the place out.
Yuki...
Yuki...!
Yuki!
So... pretty...
Ru, your tears... shine like gems...
I wanted to be your LRIG.
LRIG to the greatest of Selectors...
But... my true desire was probably different.
Mayu's sorrow... dark... filth... pain...
I was born from those feelings...
But... battling alongside you...
You, Ru... came inside me...
...and spread within me...
I felt... something very beautiful,
and precious filling me...
You showed me...
...what I truly desired.
Yuki...
Thank you...
...Ru.
Stop it! I don't want to hear your thanks!
I don't like the way you're
making it sound like a farewell!
Why is she crying?
Why would parting be painful for her?
After all, for me it wasn't...
I don't give a damn about your
emotional farewells and tears.
The battle ends when an LRIG disappears.
You girls lose by default.
Say, Iona, or should I say, Yuki-san...
...are you still able to battle?
Ru and Yuki won't lose.
--Shiro!
--Tama!
This can't be...
How did she get out?
Tama...
Ru...
Use Grow...
Huh?
Make Tama and Yuki into one.
R-Ru...
You don't need to do that.
Me coming together as one
with Tama will just taint her.
Yuki, you're pretty.
Just like the snow that shines under the sun.
Pretty... Me...?
Tama, who dreams of the summer sun...
...and Yuki, who loves the winter snow.
If Tama and Yuki come together as one...
...you'll be like the snow, falling in summer.
Grow.
Level 5...
...Mayu!
Wh-Why my name...?
I really like Tama...
I really like Yuki...
And the person who created
them both is you, Mayu.
Honestly, I can't say that I like you right now.
After all, everyone went
through a lot of suffering.
And even now, everyone is in pain.
Some girls have lasting scars on
their bodies and in their minds, too.
But, you had a chance to become Mayu...
What?
The true you is next to me.
I'm sure if this wasn't how things were...
If we didn't meet like this...
...I would have really liked you, too.
Th-That...
Hearing that doesn't
make me the least bit happy!
I hate... I hate how you used past tense!
Urith! Black Desire!
Now you're talking, Mayu!
Mayu!
Ru, let's battle!
Even if Selector battles themselves are wrong...
...it still is the one and only
wish coming from Mayu!
Okay.
What a sad looking room...
Mayu! Summon Arc Energe!
Okay!
Attack with Laevateinn!
Mayu, are you okay?
Yes.
Why...?
Why are you calling her by that name?
How is that doing?
Well, aside from her lack of appetite...
So, is that girl back?
--Not that it matters to me...
--So did that eat dinner already?
What is that doing?
Make that take a bath.
Not that I care...
My name was never spoken
in such a caring tone before...
Look at yourself!
Aren't you supposed to be
the greatest Selector there is?!
Selector...
One who selects...
I... didn't select anything...
Mayu...?
It's not that I didn't
want to make a selection.
I didn't have any selections to make...!
That's right... I...
I didn't take everything away from everyone...
I gave everyone an opportunity
to make a selection.
Even if they were crying, smiling, or angry...
...at least they could select!
I was even denied that!
The only thing that connects to the outside
is the sky seen from that window.
This room was Mayu's world...
I didn't have a chance to select--
That's not true.
Why did you seal Tama away, Mayu?
Why did you only allow Yuki
to participate in battle?
That's...
Mayu hated the world outside the window...
...the world lit by light.
But in reality, she sought and longed for
the world outside more than anyone else.
That's why, just when
Mayu's life came to an end...
...she made a selection...
With that, Tama awakened...
Beyond the colors of black, and of white...
...was a world of many colors...
...where Tama, longing for light
that Mayu held, was released to.
No... No! No!
No... No...
That's not me... I wouldn't...
Come see the world outside
together with everyone.
How can you say such a thing?!
Huh?
Mayu is...
...already dead!
What? What's going on?!
Mayu!
Ruko...
Why... are you trying to
protect the LRIG I created?
No one... loved me...
No one called me by my name...
No one embraced me...
No one...
If we didn't meet like this...
...I would have really liked you, too.
If we met...
...could things have changed?
I...
...was to become an unknown
existence and perish here.
I wanted others to know...
I wanted to affect the lives of
others with the life I lived here.
Even if...
...that was hatred.
I...
I want to get to know
more about you, Mayu!
And not through hatred, or with bad feelings!
Guess what color I selected.
The color Mayu selected?
Urith at Level 5...
...can control all colors.
This move can be used only once.
If you can guess what Mayu selected...
...you win, Ru.
Get it wrong, and Mayu wins.
This card... is Mayu's heart.
The color Mayu selected...
Is it the color of dark, the hatred
she had for the outside world?
Or, is it the color of light
that sealed Tama away?
Beyond the colors of black...
...and of white...
...was a world of many colors...
That's right...
Hurry it up already!
I can't hold myself back any longer!
Now, Ru...
...what color is this card?
A world without colors.
That card...
...is non-colored.
What?
W-Wait a second!
This can't be!
Me, executed without a fight?!
Noooo...!
I have nothing in my hand, and no Arts to use.
Mayu can't do anything in the next turn.
Non-colored.
A color that erases all and
marks the end of all things.
And, it's a color that marks
the beginning of everything, too.
It can be colored any way you want.
Mayu, you're going to set the colors.
Mayu...
...can begin again?
Yup.
Mayu...
...can be embraced by someone?
Yup.
Mayu...
Ruko...
Let's take our oath
before this world disappears.
This time, let's make your wish come true, Ru.
My wish...?
It was to return the girls who became
LRIG cards back to their original selves, right?
Turn the girls who became LRIGs into humans.
What?
That would make you return back
to your original form, Mayu, but...
...it may turn Tama and Yuki into humans, too.
Ru, you're like a kid.
Huh?
Ru... you do understand, right?
Making a selection means to
select one thing, not everything.
I did make a selection.
I'm not going to make a selection
at the sacrifice of something else.
Even if that brings hardships, sorrow, or times
where I may cry, I'll still select everything.
That's the selection I made!
You really are a kid...
Look who's talking, Mayu.
I accept...
...the laws of the Selector.
Now...
...a new Eternal Girl will be born!
Looks like that building's finished.
Guess things didn't disappear
even after the pillar fit in.
Oh my, why are you so dressed up?
You have plans with the others?
Yup! We're studying for our school exam.
What about dinner?
Ah, I won't be out too late today, so--
--Ou...ch...
--Wha...?! Yikes!
Gotta hand it to piggy-Ru. That hit hard...
Well, if you're going to sleep,
sleep in bed or something.
Be careful now.
Okay! I'm off!
Have fun.
Looks like Ru-chan grew, didn't she?
Really?
Why yes.
She's grown so much.
That's it! My brain can't take this anymore!
It's only been an hour, you know?
She's right.
If you're planning to go to the same school
as Hitoe, you'll have to do your best.
Hitoe...
...gimme some of your brains!
Come on...
Say, how about we take a break?
A break...?
Let's play WIXOSS!
Trash Rhino with Tawil!
The Activation Ability on
Yuzuki's new LRIG is super!
Kazuki recommended
that I try different cards.
But, none of the LRIG cards match
me as well as Hanayo-san did...
The world of Selector battles has ended.
The girls who were sealed
into cards as LRIGs...
...were able to return to their former selves.
"Summer's Renewal Edition"
Selector battles...
What was the game all about?
"Akira's Resolute Declaration to Blue Decks!"
A game that was born from the
hatred and sorrow of a single girl.
A game of broken rules where only
sorrow lay in wait no matter the selection.
But...
...we found something within that game.
"Excuse me. We can become friends--"
We found alternatives outside the
rules from which to make a selection.
If we didn't participate in the game,
we never would have known...
...or found what was precious to us.
And, I made my selection.
So...
...I'll continue...
...my search...
Ru...
Ru!
...for a yet unseen, new selection.
Believing that...
...is my...
...Ru's selection.