This room is yours.
These coins are the
memories of the Selectors?
You are the new law.
Show us your battle.
Your battle.
Begin. Quickly.
There will be no more battles.
I'll release all the memories
and return them to their owners.
I've come here to end the Selector battles.
End the battles?
This is a place of beginnings.
An ending cannot be allowed.
We won't let it end.
We won't allow it.
My heart is being taken over by darkness...
Battle...
Everyone...  should just disappear...
Kiyoi!
You want a battle, don't you?
Then I'll defeat you and create a new law!
Open!
Grow.
Attack.
Defend.
This isn't a WIXOSS battle!
This is my battle.
Piruluk!
Leave it to me!
Burning!
I'll take the clones.
Yuzuki!
Escape!
Concentrate!
Yuki, where are you?
Right here, Tama.
Yuki! Just hang in there. I'll save you.
Tama, think back. Remember
the last time you came here.
The truth is, we aren't prisoners at all.
What we need in order to escape is...
...to choose!
I got out!
I felt it inside the door.
The last heart that Mayu left behind...
Mayu?
This isn't the real door.
An LRIG becomes the key and opens the door.
No, that's not right.
That just opens a series of endlessly
opening doors with no exit.
Where is the real door?
Nowhere.
Not right now.
This is the room of white windows.
All that's here is the
scenery beyond the window
that you can't reach.
Mayu was all alone here...
Why?
Why would you end it?
What waits for you when it's over?
Everyone gets their memories back and
returns to their old lives. That's all.
Why do you seek memories?
Memories make people suffer.
You're no different.
That's because of who I am.
Painful memories, stressful memories,
filthy memories...
I'm made up of all of them.
I'm going to take back myself.
That is my choice!
Suzu...
Chi-chan, I'm sorry.
I broke our promise.
I entrusted your memories,
and everyone else's, to Kiyoi-chan.
Because I believed that she
would be able to get them back.
I want to be with you, Chi-chan.
I want to be the closest person to you
when your memories come back.
No matter what happens, I want to
accept them, together with you.
Yeah... Thanks.
So, while we're waiting for
your memories to come back,
I thought we could eat some cookies.
I'm pretty confident about these!
They're good.
Kiyoi-chan...
Attack.
The battles will continue... forever.
I'll end them here!
I won't...
let the battles end!
Everyone!
Out of the way, wimps!
This power is great...
Sure, I can go crazier! Much crazier!
Kiyoi-chan, where are you?
Play with me!
Forever and ever!
Tentacle!
What?
We won't let you go.
You're fighting us.
Um...
What do we do?
Stop freaking out!
Blind.
Burning!
If you would destroy the law,
you must bend it to your will by force.
You can't destroy it.
I will release everything.
For my friends...
And for you!
Release everything...
Brother... will come back?
Then Sumida-san will also...
Change of plans...
We're changing our target!
O-Okay!
I betrayed ya!
I-I'm sorry!
Riru, are you okay?
Yeah.
Come get me!
Look at how desperate she is...
Humans are such strange creatures.
It hurts, run-run!
Thank you-run!
You're welcome.
Fractal Cage!
You can't do it.
It hasn't changed since the last time I came.
Confirmation. This is the room
of the beginning, correct?
I think so.
This is where the Selector
battles were born, I think.
Yuki said the real door was in here.
Inexplicable.
The only door I see is the one
that connects to the hallway.
The room of the beginning...
The real door...
Do you remember, Tama?
The last message Mayu gave
us before she disappeared.
Yeah.
When she left us,
this room was supposed to disappear,
and so were we.
Take flight, to the real sky...
But Mayu made a choice—for us, and for
black and white, to remain in this world.
Yeah...
But at the same time, that meant the
room of white windows remained, too.
Just as we exist,
this room will continue to exist, as well.
As a receptacle of human sorrow,
hatred, and despair.
No...
Because we're here?
No, that's not it.
We're not Shiro and Kuro anymore.
Mayu and Ruu gave us
new names and new lives.
We have the power to choose.
Yeah.
Don't be a keyhole. Be a key.
A key!
Ruu will find the door, I know it.
Mayu was always alone.
The outside world...
Longing, hatred...
All kinds of emotions filled her heart,
overflowed,
and were painted over...
Someone who could handle all of Mayu's
mixed-up, colorless feelings
that she couldn't tell anyone about...
Imaginary friends.
Acceptance.
This looks exactly like
the room of white windows.
There's no door.
Mayu didn't understand...
If she had painted a door,
she and everyone else
could've gone outside to play.
A door!
Ruu!
Go, Tama.
Yeah!
Happening!
Try to endure it all you want, but it's no use.
You cannot be the law.
Then why did you choose me?
You told me to find you.
Hatred, sorrow, the desire to destroy...
Is that all you are?
It's not!
You, all of you,
seek out and enjoy the battles...
But deep in your hearts, you seek salvation.
Salvation...
I want to end this.
I want to escape this darkness.
Wishes, dreams, memories...
No matter how many precious things
you steal, you'll never be fulfilled.
With each battle, the laws are warped,
and you even lose the freedom to choose.
Nobody wants this.
A small light remaining within darkness
that threatens to swallow you up...
You do know what I'm
talking about, don't you?
I...
Grow.
Peeping Analyze.
That is your choice...
They're turning into coins...
Kiyoi!
Piruluk.
It's finally time.
Yes.
We'll bring an end to all of this.
Catharthis.
The memories are returning.
All the feelings everyone had...
Yes!
I'll be heading back before you guys!
Looks like it's over.
Yeah. Finally.
Kiyoi-chan, let's play some more!
We're going to disappear, aren't we?
We were born from Suzu
and Chinatsu's memories.
We're just going to return to them.
Will Chi-chan be okay?
I wanted to see her again.
Yeah.
But I'm sure it'll be fine,
knowing the two of them.
Bye-bye, Shou-chan.
Hanna-sama, farewell.
I'm so happy for you, brother!
Complete defeat, huh?
I got you back one!
You battle junkie...
I guess this is goodbye, Kiyoi.
I don't know about that.
I can't prove it, but maybe...
So I won't say goodbye.
I see. Then neither will I.
Thanks, Kiyoi.
This was fun!
Sakaguchi...
Chi-chan?
M-My memories...
Chi-chan!
It's okay... It's okay!
I'm right here. And I always will be.
Suzu... Suzu...
Let's talk a whole bunch.
About elementary school,
about our favorite foods,
about WIXOSS...
I...
You can take your time.
Slowly...
We'll overcome it together.
Hey!
Ruu!
Hitoe!
Hanna-san!
Tama! Yuzuki!
Welcome back!
The Selector battles are over.
I'm back!
Not all of the pain is gone.
Not everything is back to the way it was.
But still...
Morikawa.
I'm so glad...
Yeah. I'm okay.
6 Months Later
Memories...
They're uncertain and nebulous things.
You just give them color in your own mind,
selecting the ones you choose
to be "happy" or "sad."
Memories change color every day in my mind.
Still...
No matter how sad those memories are...
I don't want to be rid of them.
Because they're a part of me.
Want to do a WIXOSS tournament?
Sure!
I'm in.
Sounds fun.
I'll play!
I won't lose!
Because I don't want to let all my choices,
When?
all my encounters,
be a lie.
And because I want to make the
choices I'll make in the future
with my head held high.
Open!
Light