Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Tomorrow's the start of a long break...
Don't forget that you're all students...
...and act with caution.
Precautions for
Summer Vacation
Yes, ma'am!
Students feel restless around this time of year...
...and many cause social disturbances.
I am terribly concerned.
Take extreme care to avoid causing any trouble.
Precautions for
Summer Vacation
In short...
If ya do something bad, it'll cut into my vacation, so I'm begging ya!
Sh-She's hopeless...
Ace Shooter
It's finally vacation...
When I think about how I won't have to see your face every day...
...I feel so good.
Onee-chan...
Well, even if it is a vacation,
I'll still see Sensei every day.
Why?
Do you have make-up classes or something?
We're in the same party on an MMO.
That's just... yeah.
MMO?
She plays a wizard, and I'm a tank.
So if we pair up and I pull, we can get crazy experience.
Well, I'm the only one who's actually busy.
All Sensei has to do is click AoE spells.
The other day, I pulled this huge mob...
...but Sensei had fallen asleep...
It took a whole day to make up the experience lost from death.
Um...
In Japanese, okay?
Good morning.
It sure is hot this morning.
Morning.
Your hair's pretty wild.
Hey, Onee-chan.
How about we turn on the A/C?
There you go again...
Don't be so quick to depend on that stuff.
Just use a fan or something.
Here.
A fan can make it pretty cool.
Right?
I'm hot...
You get tired from fanning yourself...
...and once you stop, you feel even hotter than before, right?
When you use a fan...
Well, I expected this.
Hang in there.
Everybody's wearing yukatas.
Well, our sashes are the pre-tied kind.
The ones you can just attach.
Even then, yukatas are really hard to put on.
Yours is a real tied-on sash, right?
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
No.
A clerk at the store tied it for me.
Tying a sash would be too difficult for me.
I see.
And Konata's wearing one, too.
Oddly enough.
Did you also get yours tied at the store?
Nope.
My dad did it for me.
Oh, really...
Come on, let's go!
How come her dad knows how to tie a sash?
Hey!
Konata-chan!
A cop?
Do you know her?
She's Yui-neesan.
Nice ta meet ya!
It's a pleasure to meet you. Hi.
Listen to your elders...
...and control yourself...
...and get home early.
Elders
No, no, no, no, no.
We're in the same year.
Don't use Konata as the standard.
We're all in the same year.
Whoa!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm amazed!
The difference in size got me.
That's okay.
Man...
Girls sure hit puberty early these days.
No.
Like I said!
Don't use Konata as the standard!
We're the normal ones!
It's a shooting game.
Yui-neesan.
Aren't you good at shooting games?
Believe it or not...
...I'm good enough to be known as Sharpshooter Yui-chan.
I can hit five bulls-eyes in three seconds.
With enough time to flash a peace sign.
Then show us.
Here.
Huh?
What?
You use rifles for shooting games?
What a surprise!
I use pistols.
Can't wait! Can't wait!
Narumi.
What are you so concentrated on over there?
Aren't you on duty?
Okay, back to patrolling.
What?
Let's try this again...
Onii-san, we can have anything over there if we hit it?
They're all okay.
All of them?
All of them.
Whoa, miss.
I'm not a prize.
Summer festivals are all about shaved ice!
It's pretty hot.
Let's have some.
Strawberry - Lemon - Melon - Blue Hawaii
Oh, yeah.
I've been wondering...
I know what strawberry, lemon and melon are...
...but what kind of fruit is a "Blue Hawaii"?
What does it taste like?
L-Like Blue Hawaii?
That's right...
That's what you would think.
So Miyuki-san...
Do you know anything about Blue Hawaii?
Blue Hawaii, is it?
Um, let's see...
Is it a song?
B-Blue...
No, that's not it.
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
I'll look it up in the near future.
I'm counting on you.
I don't believe there are any fruits or confections by that name.
Wait.
Shouldn't the person who wants to know...
...be looking it up instead of Miyuki?
Um...
About Blue Hawaii...
I think the name comes from...
...a cocktail with the same name and color.
The cocktail was named with the movie Blue Hawaii in mind.
You're right.
That was very informative.
When you learn something from Tsukasa...
...it feels like you've really failed.
I just realized that I barely have any money left.
Stuff at these stalls aren't cheap.
Use your money wisely.
For crying out loud...
But the whole festival atmosphere makes you wanna spend.
I guess.
It's like how you don't realize how expensive doujinshi is when you're at Comiket.
Afterwards, you're like, "Whoa, I spent a lot."
Seriously, nobody else understands your world!
You're all exhausted from waiting in line since morning...
...and it's really far between the west gate and east gate.
We don't know what you're talking about.
I love how cotton candy is all fluffy and sweet!
You're not a child.
Eat slower.
It's not as entertaining when two girls do it.
Don't say it.
Why haven't any of us found any romance?
Summer means festivals, which means yukatas!
If this was a dating sim,
you'd probably trigger at least one flag somewhere.
Flag?
And there'd be an event scene.
Since you'd be in yukatas.
And it's outdoor.
Okay, that's far enough.
Aren't you going to play anything, Kagami-san?
Since we're here...
Might as well scoop goldfish or something.
I haven't even made a move yet! Why are they running away?
Didn't they sense your barbaric nature and run away?
Guess we've finally got some hard proof.
Look!
There's one right there!
You're right.
Okay...
Gotta catch 'em all!
Yay!
I caught one!
That was amazing!
I'll take care of it.
I'll take good care of it.
Gyopi-chan.
Yo.
Y'all came together.
I heard there was a festival around here...
...so I figured I might as well come.
I love festivals.
Did you come with your boyfriend?
'Course not.
Ain't got one.
There really isn't a shred of romance around us.
Figured as much.
We meet again!
Looks like you're having fun with a new friend.
Hello.
So this is the one who hit puberty really early, huh?
She's our homeroom teacher.
I'm terribly sorry.
I assumed that you were a classmate.
It's all right.
This is Yui-neesan.
She's a cop.
As you can see.
Yeah...
There's a summer festival today,
so I'm on patrol here.
Man, they make us work in such hot weather.
Work?
Looks like you're just having fun.
Are you also working?
Keeping an eye on students?
Nah.
I was bored, so I figured I'd drop by.
Lucky you.
If I wasn't on duty,
then I would have come to play around.
No.
You're having plenty of fun as it is!
Are you also by yourself?
Yes, I am.
I see!
Single
Husband works far away
Actually, I would recommend balsamic vinegar...
But the normal vinegar you may have in your kitchen works fine.
Balsamic vinegar.
Balsamic vinegar!
Summer vacation is kind of boring since you usually have nothing to do.
You get used to sitting around and doing nothing.
If you're going to say that...
...don't ask me to show you my homework later.
I see.
It sure is cute.
All stout and round.
And how the outside looks like a froggie.
Yep, yep.
Depleted uranium, huh?
That's cool!
I'll get in trouble if I'm on the phone too long.
Well then, bye!
I was on the phone with Kona-chan...
...and I mentioned how much free time we have during vacation...
...but she's playing a bunch of games that have piled up, so she has no free time.
I guess some people still enjoy a full and satisfying summer vacation.
Maybe I should do something, too.
Well...
I suppose that's okay...
But do your homework!
Honestly...
Every single time...
I'll pull one.
OK.
Lolololol.
Debuff plz.
Your friend nanakon has logged on.
Sensei logged on.
Hi.
yo (^3^)/
You're on a lot more since it's vacation, huh?
Pretty much lol.
I've got some time, wanna go hunting?
I'm in the cave near chopron village.
Oh yeah, I'm coming! >w<b Time for some wiz action!
Then I'll be waiting by the gate.
So anyway, that's great and all but have you done your homework? (-_-)
Huh?
Been in your room the whole time? (-_-)
Don't forget when school starts again (¯3¯)y-~~~
Also don't stay up late or sleep in just 'cause you're on vacation.
Sensei...
Stop talking about the real world on an MMO every day...
It's like I'm getting yelled at by Kagami every day.
Yo!
Sure is hot today.
Welcome.
Come on in.
Hello.
You set up an electric fan.
Since it's hot.
Cool yourself down.
I knew it.
I knew you'd do it.
Good morning.
Kona-chan's here.
Yo.
Good morning, my foot!
Do you have any idea what time it is?
It sure is hot.
You too!?
Well, it's the normal thing to do.
It isn't.
But Kagami also did it this morning.
See.
I was seen.
Looks like Comp Festival's pretty popular.
What's that?
If you collect the forms that come in these magazines and send them in...
...you can get every single limited edition QUO card.
I'm constantly taking magazines to the register like I'm possessed.
You were saying the same thing about QUO cards the other day.
Japanese people are really weak when it comes to special gifts or limited edition stuff.
That's why it's essential to buy one for preservation, one to look at, and one extra.
Wait!
You're undeniably a special case!
There aren't many people like you.
Sometimes, I forget who I lent it to and have to buy another one.
Don't forget.
So...
I'd like to order the usual...
Homework!
Again?
I'll teach you the stuff you don't know...
...so try doing the problems yourself.
Balsamic vinegar.
Kagami.
Tell me how to do this one.
For this one...
Kagami.
I don't know how to do it from here to here.
That was close.
Kagami.
You're not even trying to think it through, are you!?
This one is...
I am thinking it through.
Really...
And I don't know any of the ones past this one.
You aren't thinking after all!
She ended up not telling me how to do them.
Hey!
I'm here to play!
Yui-neesan.
Perfect timing.
Teach me this part.
Math homework?
Let's see.
Leave it to me.
Well...
I must say, as a good police officer...
...my help would not be to your benefit, so don't depend on others!
It's such a pain when I don't understand any of the questions...
If you don't know the answer...
...just write something that sounds close.
Because you just have to turn the homework in.
I get it.
You're smart!
But this really weakens what she said before...
I doubt this will be to my benefit...
Yeah...
That's what I did!
I'm exhausted...
I'll do a little gaming for a break.
I'll do some solo hunting for thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes should be okay.
Solo hunting, right? Right?
...becomes fiction.
...what makes you strong.
This isn't...
...else.
A rare drop.
Obtained Demonic Sword Laevateinn
What's this
Laevateinn!
I've never seen anyone with this!
It's ultra rare!
Found a Laeva sword!
RLY!? ∑(@@)
Lololol gratz lolololol.
I'll be right there so show me show me! >w</
Let's celebrate. Get a bunch of clan members and go test it out o(^^)o
All-nighter for sure lololol.
I'm feeling it tonight roflcopterskates.
Okay. Come on!
OK. Come on.
Well, where should we try it out?
Everybody's pumped up.
That's right.
I'll buy a bunch of quality potions to pass out.
Let's go back to town first...
Gonna get busy!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
We're already on the fifth episode of Lucky Channel!
Let's get even crazier!
Now let me introduce...
...someone who's showing up more often in the actual show and getting full of it...
I mean...
The hardworking...
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Well...
I didn't mean to look like I was full of it...
I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
It's a pleasure!
Okay.
We're always receiving lots of postcards.
Today's is from U.S.S. Gatoh in Tokyo.
Occupation: NEET.
This guy sent in fifty by himself...
He must be one sorry guy!
Let's move onto the postcard.
Good day. Akira-san and Minoru-san.
In the actual show, Konata-chan seems to play MMOs.
Do you also play these games, Akira-san?
By the way, I live a happy life playing female characters every day.
MMOs?
Online games?
I'm sorry to say that I've never tried it.
But it's better if you haven't.
Another blunt response...
R-Really?
Too many people get addicted and give up on the real world.
I was dumb like that once.
I would log on whenever I had time...
...and stay on forever doing stuff like PKKing.
Back when I was young.
Wh-When you were young...?
Er.
There were a bunch of words I didn't get...
You're better off not knowing.
Well, only half the audience is going to get it anyway.
A-Anyway, so you've played them before?
Then do you have any online experiences you would like to share?
Yep!
You bet I do!
When I first started...
...I didn't know what to do...
...and I got lots of help from some really nice and experienced guys!
They gave me lots of expensive armor and rare items!
Akira was so touched!
R-Really...
It was really fun, so you should all play, too!
We're already out of time.
Bye-bee!
Then, we'll see you next time.
So you're popular in those kind of games, right?
Huh?
Akira-sama?
What's wrong?
Cut 12 on page 38.
Yes?
Who the hell is Yutaka!?
That's what you're mad about this time!?
I'm Akira!
Well, that's true...
Bring out whoever is responsible!
No! Uh...
D-Director?
Director!?
Ah, no. A producer would be better.
The hell is Yutaka!?
Producer would be better!
Hey! A-Akira-san!
Please calm down!
Please!
You know.
Yes?
Why don't we change Shiraishi Minoru's name...
...to something else?
Like Su-
You rocked, Kagamin!
Cut that out.
So is Tsukasa or Miyuki next?
Me.
Again!?
When did you order a song!?
They were taking too long and it'd be a waste of time.
Sorry.
I need a little more time to decide...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We can kill some time with Konata's singing.
I know this!
Didn't expect you to go with something mainstream.
Kami rules!
Sparkling!
Hikaru kumo wo tsukinuke Fly Away
光る　雲を突き抜け　Fｌｙ　Away
Piercing the shining clouds, I'm gonna fly away!
Karadajuu ni hirogaru PANORAMA
からだじゅうに　広がるパノラマ
Spreading through my body, feeling the power through my soul!
Kao wo kerareta chikyuu ga okotte
顔を　蹴られた地球が怒って
Kicked in the face... the earth is mad as a fire brigade!
Kazan wo bakuhatsusaseru
火山を爆発させる
Can't you feel it building up for her to blow?
Toketa koori no naka ni
溶けた北極の中に
If there ever were a dinosaur...
Kyouryuu ga itara tamanori shikomitai ne
恐竜がいたら　玉乗り仕込みたいね
I would wanna train it to ride a ball in a mound of icicles.
CHA - LA HEAD - CHA - LA
Nani ga okite mo kibun wa henoheno Kappa
何が起きても気分は　へのへのカッパ
Nothing can stop me now, no matter what may happen!
CHA - LA HEAD - CHA - LA
Preview
Sign: To keep our city clean, fireworks are banned
between 10 PM and 7 AM.
Well then, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
When you first start MH2...
...the condition for learning weapons is defeating five Gearnos.
So once you return to town...
...and get sent on a quest by the elder...
...even if you defeat five Gearnos...
...get loads of snow mountain grass...
...and lots of poponotan...
...when you can't go back to town...
...you realize for the first time that you can't access your supply box yourself...
...and your reward is decreased since you didn't read the instruction manual...
...and you can't save up money.
Doesn't it make you wonder about how this applies to the real world?
Next time: Summer Events!
「Summer Events」
Look forward to next time!