Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Now, it's time to begin.
Let's go!
Ngaah~
Hurry up and start already!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
So starting tomorrow you're going to have a long break.
But don't forget that you're still students.
And don't go overboard with whatever you are going to do!
Precautions for
Summer Vacation
Okay~
A lot of students get feisty during this season and wreak havoc on the public.
Sensei is very worried about this.
So please be careful and don't cause any trouble.
Precautions for
Summer Vacation
In other words, if you resort to any hijinx...
...I'll lose my summer vacation.
So seriously, stay out of trouble!
T-this is useless...
A Famous
Shooter
It's finally vacation time!
It feels great knowing I won't have to look at that face of yours everyday.
O-Onee-chan...
Well, even though it's a "break",
I'll have to see Sensei almost every day.
Huh?
Why?
Reviews or something?
We join parties together in online games.
What's up with that?
Online games?
Sensei's a wizard and I'm a tanker.
When we pair up and I lure the enemy...
We get lots of experience and money.
Err...
Well, I'm the one doing all the work because all Sensei has to do is to keep clicking on one skill.
The other day I pulled in a bunch of mobs...
But Sensei fell asleep at the keyboard.
And it took me a whole day to regain the money and items I lost from dying.
U-Um, Earth to Konata...
Could you at least speak Japanese?
Good morning.
It's so hot this morning.
Mm.
Good morning.
Your hair is all messy.
Hey, Onee-chan,
do you want to turn on the A/C?
You shouldn't rely on those kinds of things so quickly.
For the time being, why don't you settle for a fan?
Here you go.
Ah~
Even fans can cool you down.
Right?
It's hot.
It gets tiring when you fan yourself...
So when you stop, you feel even hotter.
I suppose.
Well, I knew that but...
Let's try a little harder, shall we?
I guess we all brought our yukata today.
Yep, yep.
But our obi are the easy clip-on kind.
The ones you can put on right away.
Putting on a yukata is harder than it looks.
Miyuki, your obi's the real kind you have to tie, right?
Just as I would expect from someone like you.
Actually, the person at the store put this on for me.
Tying an obi is a little difficult, even for me.
I see.
Konata, you're wearing a real one as well, surprisingly.
Yep.
Did the guy at the shop put yours on, too?
Nope, my dad tied it for me.
Is that so...
All right, let's go!
How does her dad know how to tie one?
Hey, Konata-chan!
Oh?
A police officer?
You know each other, Konata?
She's my cousin, Yui-neesan.
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Hello.
If you want to stay out of trouble...
You'd better listen to these young ladies and go home early.
Elders
No no no no...
We're fellow classmates.
Don't use Konata as a standard of comparison.
We're all classmates.
Oh really!?
I'm sorry about that.
Onee-san's surprised!
There was such a big difference, so I couldn't help it...
Don't sweat it.
But I guess kids develop really fast nowadays, don't they?
No!
Stop using Konata as a standard of comparison!
We're the normal ones here!
Ah!
It's a shooting game.
Yui-neesan, are you good at shooting?
Hmm?
I'll have you know that at the police station people call me "Yui-chan, the Sharpshooter"
I'd shoot 5 shots in 3 seconds and nail the pinhead each time.
I could make a "peace" mark on a dummy target's head.
Then show us.
Here.
E-Eh!?
You have to shoot with a rifle?
What a surprise!
Hmm?
But I use pistols.
*giddy* *giddy*
Narumi!
What the blazes are you doing?
We're on duty.
C'mon, it's patrol time.
Anyway...
Mister, can we get whatever we want back there if we hit it?
Anything you want.
Anything?
Yep, anything.
Um, Miss...
I'm not a prize!
It's not a summer festival unless we have some shaved ice.
And it's really hot.
We should get some.
You know, I've always wondered...
Strawberry - Lemon - Melon - Blue Hawaii
Strawberry...
Lemon...
Melon...
I can understand, but...
What kind of fruit is "Blue Hawaii"?
What does it taste like?
Like "B-Blue Hawaii", I guess.
Of course...
That's what a normal person would say.
Hey Miyuki-san, do you know what "Blue Hawaii" is?
"B-Blue Hawaii"?
U-Um...
I wonder if it's a song...
Blue...
No that's not it...
B-blue...
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry I'm not of any help.
I'll look it up for you.
Yeah, that would be great.
I suppose it's probably because they have something called that-
Instead of Miyuki-san...
Shouldn't you be the one looking it up...
Since you're the one who wants to know?
Um, about that "Blue Hawaii"...
Hmm?
It seems that its name came from a cocktail called "Blue Hawaii" that had the same color.
And that cocktail itself was named after a movie.
So that's how it is.
That's nice to know.
Whenever I learn something from Tsukasa, I get this sense of utter defeat...
Ah!
I just noticed that I don't have much money left!
These stands aren't cheap, so you have to wisely choose where to spend your money.
Geez.
But when you're at a festival,
you get sucked into the atmosphere and start buying everything you can get your hands on.
I guess.
It's similar to when you go to Comiket and can't stop buying Doujinshi.
And looking back, you can't believe how costly it all was.
I keep telling you, we haven't a clue about that kind of stuff!
Then you're tired from lining up early in the morning...
And because the West Wing and the East Wing are so far away from each other...
I have no freaking clue about what you're talking!
I love cotton candy because it's so soft and fluffy.
Ah!
You're not a kid anymore so take your time to eat it.
Ehehe...
Those kind of things aren't enjoyable when you do it with two girls.
Don't say that.
Why can't we have any "romance"?
We're at a summer festival wearing a yukata, right?
If this were a gal-game, then we should have triggered a flag or two...
Flag?
Followed by an event-scene afterwards.
Since we're wearing a yukata and are outdoors.
Okay okay, that's enough.
Kagami-san, aren't you going to play anything?
Well, since I'm already here, I guess I'll do some fish scooping or something.
Ah.
Wah!
I didn't even try to scoop yet, so why are you running away!?
They instinctively knew about your violent tendencies, so they ran away.
Eh!?
Looks like we finally have some solid proof of that, huh?
Yep yep.
Hey!
There's one right there.
Ah, you're right.
All right.
Gotcha! Fish was caught!
Yay!
I caught one!
That was amazing!
I'll take good care of this one.
You're such a cute little thing aren't you, Gyopi-chan!
Ah.
Hey, nice to see you all together.
I heard there was a festival in the neighborhood, so I thought I should drop by.
I love festivals, too!
Did you come with your boyfriend today?
Hahaha...
Of course not.
I don't have one!
There really isn't a speck of romance in our surroundings...
Just as expected.
Looks like we meet again!
You even got more people.
It looks like you're having fun.
Thanks!
This one's developed really quickly.
What?
This is our teacher.
I'm sorry...
I jumped to conclusions and thought you were their classmate.
No worries...
This is my cousin, Yui-neesan.
She's a police officer, as you can tell.
Yeah, I'm on duty right now patrolling the area, with the festival and all.
Even though it's so hot...
Work?
You're playing to your heart's content!
Sensei, are you here for work, too?
Like patrolling?
No, I had some free time so I kind of swung by.
I'm so jealous...
If I had that much free time, I would probably do the same.
You're having way too much fun already!
Did you come alone, too?
Yes, I did.
I see, I see.
Single
Huh?
Husband works far away
Therefore, I recommend balsamic vinegar, but...
You can substitute it with something you can have at your disposal~
Balsamic vinegar.
You're supposed to laugh here.
Balsamic vinegar...
Ahaha!
Balsamic vinegar!
Isn't it boring when there's really nothing to do during summer vacation?
I tend to start slacking off.
Fufufu.
Since you say that...
You're not going to go, "Let me see your homework, please" later on, right?
Ah!
I see.
Okay.
That AS is really cute, isn't it?
How it's short and stout, with a rounded body...
It looks like a frog from the outside, doesn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Yup.
Really, depleted uranium?
That's amazing.
Ehehe.
Oh, if I talk for too long, I'll get scolded.
Yep!
I'll see you later.
I was talking to Kona-chan about how there's so much free time during summer vacation.
But she told me she plays all the games she's been saving up, so she's not bored.
I guess some people know how to spend their summers, eh?
I should probably do something, too.
Uh, I don't mind you doing something but...
You should do your homework, too!
Geez, every single time.
I'll pull one.
OK.
Lolololol.
Debuff plz.
Your friend nanakon has logged on.
Sensei logged on.
Hi.
yo (^3^)/
You're on a lot more since it's vacation, huh?
Pretty much lol.
I've got some time, wanna go hunting?
I'm in the cave near chopron village.
Oh yeah, I'm coming! >w<b Time for some wiz action!
Then I'll be waiting by the gate.
So anyway, that's great and all but have you done your homework? (-_-)
Huh?
Been in your room the whole time? (-_-)
Don't forget when school starts again (¯3¯)y-~~~
Also don't stay up late or sleep in just 'cause you're on vacation.
Sensei, let's not talk about the real world in an MMO.
I feel like I'm being scolded by Kagami everyday.
Hey!
It's really hot today, isn't it?
Oh, welcome.
Come on in.
Hello.
Ah!
You took out the fan?
Yeah, because it's so hot.
Why don't you cool off over there?
I knew you were going to do that.
I totally knew you were going to do that.
Good morning.
Ah, Konata, you're here.
Yo!
Don't "good morning" me.
What time do you think it is?
But it's so hot...
Not you too!
It's normal for you to do stuff like that.
No, it isn't.
But Kagami, you were doing it this morning, too.
See?
He saw me...
Comp-Matsuri is really gaining in popularity.
What is that?
If you collect all the coupons in the book associated with this magazine...
...you get a limited edition Quo-card.
Is that so...
I end up bringing the books to the register as if they were compelling me to do it.
Didn't you say something about Quo-cards the other day, too?
Japanese people sure are weak to stuff like "presents" or "limited editions".
That's why you have to buy your "preservation", "observation", and "usage" copies.
Hold up!
You're just an exception!
There aren't that many people like you!
And sometimes you have to buy another copy because you forgot to whom you lent it...
Don't forget then.
Oh, I wanted to ask you a favor about this...
Ah, homework.
Again!?
I'll help you with the parts you don't understand...
So try doing it yourself once in a while.
Balsamic vinegar...
Kagami, teach me how to do this part.
Oh, this?
Kagami, I don't understand from here to here.
Whoa, that was close.
Kagami, about this section...
You aren't even trying, are you?
Yes, I am.
Oh really.
And I don't understand everything starting from here.
I knew you weren't even thinking about them at all!!
She didn't help me out in the end.
Yahoo!
I came to play!
Oh Yui-neesan, perfect timing.
Can you show me how to do this section?
Oh?
Math homework, huh...
Leave it to me.
Well, as a police officer looking out for the good of children,
I say it's not good to rely on others, so you should think about it yourself.
Eh!?
Gah...
There are so many parts I don't understand that it's annoying.
Ha ha ha.
Even if you don't understand it, you just have to make up something that looks like the answer.
Eh?
Because all you have to do is turn in the homework.
Whoa, I see, you're smart!
But now I'm starting to reconsider that statement...
If I do that, how does it benefit me?
Yeah, I used to do that all the time.
I'm tired...
I'll take a break and play an MMO for a while.
30 minutes wouldn't hurt as a break...
Just 30 minutes.
It's solo hunting, right? Right?
In the world...
I'll become strong...
For someone's hm hm hm hm hm ii...
Ah!
A rare drop!
Obtained Demonic Sword Laevateinn
What's this
Laevateinn!
I've never seen anyone with this!
It's ultra rare!
Found a Laeva sword!
RLY!? ∑(@@)
Lololol gratz lolololol.
I'll be right there so show me show me! >w</
Let's celebrate. Get a bunch of clan members and go test it out o(^^)o
All-nighter for sure lololol.
I'm feeling it tonight roflcopterskates.
Okay. Come on!
OK. Come on.
Now, where should I go to test it out?
Oh, everyone's ready to go!
Oh yeah, I should go buy some greater potions and hand them out to everyone!
I have to go back to town first, and then...
Man, I'm gonna be busy!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-Lucky!
I'm the navigator, Kogami Akira!
It's been so fast and Lucky Channel's on the 5th episode!
Let's put more energy into it than ever!
And today's topic is...
The person who's recently had more appearances in the main show...
And is letting it get to his head...
I mean...
The hardworking...
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
*clap clap*
W-Well, I'm not letting it get to my head.
I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru~
Nice to meet you~
Now, we're getting a lot of postcards each time, but...
Today it's from USS-Gato-san in Tokyo.
His occupation is NEET.
He's sent in 50 copies all by himself.
He must be a really pitiful person.
Putting that aside, here's the postcard.
Hello Akira-san, Minoru-san.
In the series, it seems that Konata-chan is enjoying MMOs, but...
Do you play these types of games, too, Akira-san?
On top of that,
I play a character that's of the opposite sex and have lots of fun all the time!
MMOs...
He must be talking about online games.
Unfortunately, I've never played one.
Yeah.
But you're better off not playing those things, anyway.
You sure made that blunt.
I-Is that so?
A lot of people get so addicted that they leave their real lives behind.
There was a period when I was pretty close to that.
Whenever I had time, I would log in and wander around busily hunting PKers.
When I was younger...
W-When you were younger...?
There was a lot of jargon in that sentence that I didn't get...
You're better off not knowing.
I'm sure there's only a limited response among our viewers right now, anyway.
E-Either way, you've played them before, right?
So, Akira-san, do you have any experiences you recall from playing such games?
Oh, yes!
Do I have memories!
When I was still a newbie, I didn't know how a lot of things worked...
And some older veterans helped me out a lot...
They bought me really expensive armor and rare items.
Akira was so moved.
I-Is that so?
It's really fun, so everyone please play one when you get the chance!
Ah, the time's up already.
Bye-ni~
I'll see you next time.
You're quite popular in those type of games, aren't you?
Huh?
Akira-sama?
What's the matter?
Page 38, Cut 12.
Yes?
Who the hell is Yutaka?
Eh!?
You're getting mad today because of that?
My name's Akira, goddammit!
W-Well, that's true, however...
Who's in charge here!?
A-Ah, you can't do that!
D-Director?
Director!!
Or would a producer be better?
Producer!!
Hey!
Akira-san, please calm down!
Please for the love of god?
Since we're gonna do it...
Yes?
Why don't we change the name of Shiraishi Minoru to something else?
Something with Su-
Kagamin, you're so cool.
That was nothing.
Who wants to go next, Tsukasa or Miyuki?
Me.
Again!?
When did you put another song in?
Tsukasa and company were taking too long, so it would have been a waste of time.
I'm sorry.
I'm choosing, so wait a little longer.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I guess Konata's singing can kill some time.
Ah!
I know this.
That's rare, you chose a pretty popular song for a change.
Kami rocks!
Power!
Hikaru kumo wo tsukinuke Fly Away
光る　雲を突き抜け　Fｌｙ　Away
Piercing the shining clouds, I'm gonna fly away!
Karadajuu ni hirogaru PANORAMA
からだじゅうに　広がるパノラマ
Spreading through my body, feeling the power through my soul!
Kao wo kerareta chikyuu ga okotte
顔を　蹴られた地球が怒って
Kicked in the face... the earth is mad as a fire brigade!
Kazan wo bakuhatsusaseru
火山を爆発させる
Can't you feel it building up for her to blow?
Toketa koori no naka ni
溶けた北極の中に
If there ever were a dinosaur...
Kyouryuu ga itara tamanori shikomitai ne
恐竜がいたら　玉乗り仕込みたいね
I would wanna train it to ride a ball in a mound of icicles.
CHA - LA HEAD - CHA - LA
Nani ga okite mo kibun wa henoheno Kappa
何が起きても気分は　へのへのカッパ
Nothing can stop me now, no matter what may happen!
CHA - LA HEAD - CHA - LA
Preview
Sign: To keep our city clean, fireworks are banned
between 10 PM and 7 AM.
And on next week's Lucky Star:
Konata here.
When I started playing Monster Hunter 2...
Because the prerequisite for a weapon's usage is getting 5 Gianosu...
I go back to the village and get a quest from the village chief.
Now I defeat 5 Gianosu...
And gather a bunch of Snow Mountain Grass...
And pick up a couple of Popo tongues.
But when I can't get back to the village...
I suddenly realize I didn't put the stuff in my storage box...
And then, I figure it was my own fault for not reading the instructions.
And thus, I have fewer rewards and no money saved up.
Did you ever think about how that compares to real life?
Next time: "Summer Staples"
「Summer Staples」
Look forward to it!