Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
15th Concert - Symphony No. 9, Opus 125
Miyuki-san!
Got any plans for the end of the year?
Izumi-san.
There's this festival and I was wondering if you'd like to go...
A festival for the end of the year?
Sounds like fun.
Yeah. It'll be lots of fun!
Is it something like a snow festival?
But I'm going to visit relatives...
Pretty sure that...
...I received a similar invitation back during summer.
Kagami-san.
I'll translate what Konata said.
She wants buddies to buy stuff for her at Comic Market.
I was totally freaked out by the site when I went.
I'm not lying.
A festival's a festival.
It's all work and no fun by yourself.
Let's Go to
the Festival
Dec     Heisei 18
Hello?
This is the Izumi residence.
Konata?
I'm writing New Year's cards right now.
Are you guys in mourning and refusing cards?
Didn't get a letter about it...
No.
Where did that come from?
Well, you know...
Weren't you absent one day this year because of a death in the family?
Um...
But don't worry about that.
Don't tell me you used yet another trick out of manga!?
Shiny shine!
I'm in the middle of cleaning right now.
I see.
Then I won't keep you.
I'll hang up.
Bye!
I wonder why...
When there's something you don't want to do, you suddenly want to clean...
...but once you start cleaning, it suddenly feels like a pain?
Konata.
Less resting, okay?
It's called Comiket?
FIRST-TIMER
I heard it was a big festival...
...but it sure starts early.
I'm so excited!
SECOND-TIMER
Looks like you haven't heard anything.
Poor thing.
REGULAR-TIMER
Nah.
She'll get used to it soon enough.
REGULAR-TIMER
Tsukasa...
Just so you know...
...this event is gonna exhaust you...
...in more than one way...
Will you be okay?
Yes!
Then I'll do my best!
Do you really understand?
Picking up more and more of her people...
Okay!
You'll soon be allowed to enter!
Onee-chan...
This place is kinda scary...
Told you...
Regular Participants
Circle Members
Industry Members
That's right.
I should explain your assignments now.
Assignments?
Here you go.
These are your shopping lists.
Once we get inside, we'll split up and go around the circles according to this map.
You two handle 1-3 in the east building.
I'll take 4-6.
But be careful!
If you don't follow the path marked in red...
...you might get stuck between rows of displays.
...and end up trapped.
And here and here...
If you're swept into the crowd there...
...you'll be stuck for over half an hour.
Why do we have to work so hard?
Just do it.
The ones marked with green can wait until afternoon.
They're stocked up...
...so there's almost no danger of them running out.
Just focus on the ones marked red before noon.
S stands for something newly published.
K stands for something already in print.
If you don't know what's what, just buy everything.
Here's your ammo.
You're going to have to pay in cash.
The coffee will be your only refreshment for a while.
Take a drink every thirty minutes.
This will be our final rendezvous point.
1 PM on the dot.
I'll wait fifteen minutes, but if you don't show up,
I'll go look for you in the medical office, so watch the clock.
That is all.
Any questions?
You only ever sound...
...intelligent and passionate when this kind of stuff is involved.
Please don't run!
Climax from the beginning!
The limit for new works is four copies per person.
Please cooperate.
Um...
Excuse me.
This is A-92, right?
Yes.
One of each new book?
That will be 1,000 yen.
Yes, what did you need?
Um...
Which of these are new...
Yes.
The new ones would be this and this.
Each one is 500 yen.
Good work!
Did you enjoy the snacks?
That's wonderful!
U-Um...
Three of each please.
Thank you for your business!
Dripping Brigade Chief...
...and Naughty Captain, correct?
Your total comes to 3,000 yen!
I'd like these.
Okay.
Your total is 4,500 yen.
Here.
Thank you very much!
Locked and loaded...
Onto the next point.
Um...
Is this the east building?
Then north should be this way...
Um...
Wa-
Excuse me!
I'm going that way!
I've pretty much covered all the big places.
Let's see...
The next place is...
Just a peek...
Gauron and Sousuke are...
This is...
Would you like that?
It'll be 500 yen.
Um...
Too intense for me!
She's here.
It's her.
Legendary Girl A!
Calm down.
She'll think we're weird if we panic.
But there's a weird jinx...
...where every circle suddenly becomes big after she buys a book!
It's impossible to stay calm!
I know!
That's why we put so much effort into this book!
So she would buy it!
You're right...
Even though it was the end of the year...
...we skipped work to do this!
This year will be our year!
May I have a look?
Yes! Go ahead!
Uh...
What do you think?
We put a lot of work into the concert scene.
Iffy.
Thankssomuch.
Don't cry!
Next summer for sure!
Um...
Excuse me.
Yes?
What's the matter?
Where is Pu-61 located?
Pu?
Wasn't Pu in the east building?
Where is the east building?
This is the west building.
If you want to go to the east building...
...get in that line there...
...and go up one floor.
How long will it take?
Let's see...
At this time, probably an hour.
[ Please wait one moment ]
Okay, I'm done.
Sorry, Kona-chan.
I just now got back from the west building.
You get completely lost after getting caught up in the crowd...
...in this event...
I had to wait in line for an hour to use the restroom.
Well...
I figured it would be a rough schedule for a first-timer...
...so let's just stroll around for the afternoon.
You're not done yet?
But you know,
it's gotten a lot better since they moved this to Ariake.
They only had two convenience stores near the site at Harumi.
Site at Harumi?
The last one at Harumi was twelve years ago, huh?
Wait.
How old were you?
Around five?
My dad took me.
We always stayed at this place called Hotel Urashima.
My first time was at the summer festival.
That was one crazy second floor.
The sweat from all the participants evaporated...
...and turned into these fluffy steam clouds.
Enough already.
Don't want to hear it.
Everything's gotten a lot easier after they moved this to Ariake...
...but maybe it's 'cause of the people mainly here for events...
...many of the younger participants think of themselves as customers, sadly enough.
This was supposed to be an event put on by all of us.
Sorry to interrupt you while you're on a roll, but you've totally lost me.
I didn't come here during summer...
...but they also have places like these, don't they?
There.
The main stuff is probably all sold out, though.
It's Nagato! Nagato!
The person behind Nagamon is here as a salesgirl!
Here.
Thank you very much.
What are you talking about?
How can you be out of Haruhi goods!?
Why did I bother coming here if the Nagato phone cards are sold out!?
Please calm down!
He's horrible.
I can't do anything about it!
Like I just said.
Like I care!
There's been a spike in people like him.
I'm never coming back to this dump!
I'm terribly sorry, sir!
Unfortunately, our limited goods...
...have already sold out!
Really!?
Really.
Well, if you're gonna show up this late.
Figured as much.
I feel for you...
...but you gotta line up early...
Fool!
Asia...
Wh-What!?
Even customers who show up late...
...must be completely satisfied!
Have you lost the true spirit?
B-But...
All we have is leftover stuff now!
Leftover, you say?
Leftover items still have value!
A value that can't be found...
...in popular items and mainstream moe!
This Comiket exists to reveal their true value!
Now that all limited goods have been eliminated,
the true battle has begun for industry booths!
B-By George...
Now!
Make a recommendation to the customer!
Dig up your true item!
Anything I can use as a weapon?
Ho-
How about this!?
No!
Gotta be this!
No, you see.
Nagato and everybody else is selling like hotcakes,
yet look at this.
Even Koizumi's sells well.
Quiet!
This one's gone unsold for three years!
And the Captain's sold out instantly!
So please, purchase this Kyon!
No, I recommend Sousuke!
No, I wanted CoCo Saikoubi-chan!
You...
...fools!
Y-You're...
President Takahashi!
Yes.
I am...
...President Takahashi!
I overheard your conversation!
Your desire to promote a new perspective of value is commendable!
That place is always pumped up.
R-Really?
However...
I see...
I cannot forgive your selfish desire to promote unpopular characters!
Well...
They're both main characters...
Onee-chan, I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy, too.
We had to help out at home as soon as we got back from Ariake...
Why do they have that event on New Year's Eve?
Kagami.
Tsukasa.
Happy New Year!
Kona-chan.
You have an awful lot of energy for someone who was at that event since morning.
Plus, it's cold so I figured you wouldn't bother.
Well, that's true,
but January 1st is a new beginning,
so I have to come charged up for the coming year.
That's admirable.
No, that's what Dad said.
Hello!
Suddenly, I'm disturbed.
Shrine maiden outfits are so invigorating!
This and that...
We're done praying.
Okay.
Good job.
Did you guys do any praying?
Oh, yeah...
You were doing some intense praying, Onee-chan.
There you go blabbing again!
It wasn't that intense.
I-I was just hoping I could be in the same class as you and Miyuki this year.
Onee-chan...
What about Kona-chan?
You know...
Kagami's actually pretty cute.
Be quiet!
You making fun of everything is why I never want to tell you!
And then there's the way you resist...
Something wrong with that!?
Onee-chan has always been the only one in a different class.
Maybe Kuroi-sensei hates me.
I'll also pray to be in the same class as Onee-chan!
Tsukasa...
No way.
Kagami needs to be in a different class.
Wh-Why?
Because you know...
That way I can borrow stuff from you when I forget mine.
And I won't get caught if I copy your homework.
And if you're in our class, my rank will go down.
Then you go be in a different class by yourself.
The other...
The other day...
Female students are so wonderful...
Sebastian was...
Are you going to draw your fortune this year?
Might as well.
Since I'm here.
Very Good
Bad
It's good to get an early start on the year.
Indeed.
And I got to see something nice.
This will be a good year.
Don't worry.
If you've already hit rock bottom...
...things can only get better.
Something good will happen.
What can I say...
It all depends on how you word it.
Thanks...
Want to tie a bad luck ward on the tree?
I'll do that.
So many!
Here, too!
Here's a spot!
So this is the power of bad luck...
Looks like it.
Whether or not something good will happen...
...depends on the amount of effort you spend.
Drawing your fortune is just a game of luck.
That's true...
Although a staff member shouldn't be saying that...
Maybe I should go for a whole set from very good to very bad.
Are they supposed to be trading cards?
Maybe you can draw a secret fortune.
What would a secret fortune be like?
Like ultra bad luck.
Why'd you go with something bad?
Nobody would want that.
You know...
Whoever collects all of them gets a special item!
No, there's no such thing.
Oh, yeah...
I just saw a huge kagami mochi...
This big!
Is that where your name came from?
Well, you're not totally wrong...
The round shape of a kagami mochi...
...is modeled after a mirror,
but it's long been said that gods rest within mirrors,
so the name is supposed to invoke the blessings of the gods.
And the round shape also signifies family happiness.
Her name has such a fantastic origin,
yet she grew up to be an awfully pragmatic person!
Would you like one?
Okay.
There sure are a lot of worshipers.
Well, it's New Year's.
Though, we aren't that well-known.
I wonder how many of them are here for the shrine maidens like Dad.
Here we go again!
There aren't that many!
Maybe...
Then once again...
Happy New Year!
Let's have another wonderful year.
Yeah.
Let's.
Hi!
Happy New Year!
How about it?
Look at this beautiful sight!
Isn't it great?
Isn't it fantastic?
Look at all the pretty flowers everywhere!
Dad.
Want some tea?
Sure.
Here.
Thanks.
Dad.
Want to play a game?
Want some zoni soup?
Dad!
NEW YEAR'S
ALLOWANCE
Kinda like that.
Apparently, he likes how I keep scurrying over until I get my money.
I'm exhausted.
Well, yeah...
You guys are really close, huh?
And I managed to get my money...
...so I'm planning on going to Gamers right now.
Really...
The fact that all of those shops are in the city is a pain.
I'm already on a tight budget.
And there's the train fee.
I wish they'd open a shop near us.
But don't a lot of stores sell online now?
So you could try that.
You don't get it...
You can get points when you order online,
but browsing through the store and making unexpected discoveries is what's really fun.
What's with you!?
You're totally ready to spend it all!
The radishes are almost completely done!
Now we'll put this completely in.
I wonder why this is called a pochi bag.
That's from the phrases pochitto (a smidge) and korepocchi (just a bit).
It refers to a bag you put small stuff in.
Pochitto would be Kansai...
...and korepocchi would be Kanto.
Happy New Year!
This is Takara.
Miyuki-san.
Happy New Year!
Anyway,
I was wondering where the name pochi bag came from...
Konata...
Pochi bag, is it?
Can't you have a little more faith in your father?
I believe it came from the phrases pochitto and korepocchi...
And couldn't you do that somewhere out of sight?
...and refers to a bag for small items.
Okay.
Time to wish everyone in the game a happy new year.
and a mess and all. In the end,
I wasn't able to buy any Haruhi goods...
;_;
Don't cry!
I wasn't able to buy any Haruhi goods...
;_;
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
;_;
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Finally got on. Been busy for a while
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Finally got on. Been busy for a while
Your friend Nanakon has logged on
It's Sensei.
Happy New Year, Sensei
Yo, Happy New Year! (^w^)/
Let's have another wonderful year
Happy New Year, Sensei
Yo, Happy New Year! (^w^)/
Let's have another wonderful year
Yep, sounds good (>w<)b
And like...
She's always online...
Doesn't she have anything else to do?
Guess that's why she doesn't have a boyfriend.
Go-
Good lucky!
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru!
We're already on the twelfth episode of Lucky Channel!
This sea is hell.
Uh.
Yeah...
As you can see,
Akira-sama was supposed to appear in the actual show this week,
but she suddenly became ill...
A cold, right?
But I put up a cardboard pop-up instead...
...so if you go look carefully...
Hey.
Akira-sama?
And so...
...it looks like Akira-sama's already tired...
...so we'll have to call it a day!
Okay, everyone.
Bye-bee!
I'm absolutely not getting full of myself.
Me?
Let you hear the new version of Take it! Sailor Uniform?
So look forward to it?
If you don't watch next week...
...I'll turn into Mars and scold you!
Fumoffu!
We got pretty into it.
That was fun.
Nobody's ordered a song!
Isn't it your turn?
Now is when you're supposed to order a song.
I didn't choose one!
Which one should I do?
I'll look, too.
There's also a menu.
Yes.
So you can also eat here.
Yep.
That song totally broke my flow.
Should have saved it for later.
What flow?
You know what I mean?
How you sometimes feel like you sing better?
No idea.
Wonder if I can sing this.
Ooi GODMAN kikoerukai
おーい　ゴッドマン　聞こえるかい
Hey, Godman? Can you hear me?
There's a tambourine here.
Ooi GODMAN tondekoi
おーい　ゴッドマン　飛んでこい
Hey, Godman? Leap forth!
We can play it!
Yuki-chan!
Try this!
Sounds nice.
Okay!
This one!
Even a hardcore anime song will work.
Just go.
Anyway, I ordered an exciting one.
You should know this one.
I do!
I'll try it.
Make-
負けー
Don't lo-
Futoshita shunkan ni-
ふとした瞬間にー
Unexpectedly, for a moment...
Preview
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Miyuki.
When something has completely outstripped the competition...
...and stands heads above the rest...
...we use the word dantotsu to describe it.
That's apparently short for danzen (on the very) top.
This word first appeared in literature...
...after the recent city election...
...where that person won by a landslide...
...on the very top.
Next time:
「Savory Day」
"Savory Day."
Look forward to next time!