Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
15th Concert - Symphony No. 9, Opus 125
Miyuki-san~
Do you have any plans for the end of the year?
Ah, Izumi-san.
There's this festival coming up so I was wondering if you wanted to come...
An end of the year festival, huh?
It sounds like fun.
Yep, it's really fun.
Is it something like a snow festival?
But I have to go back home to the countryside...
I think I recall...
...you giving me a similar invitation back during summer.
Kagami-san.
If you translate what Konata's saying,
then it's how she wants you to go buying stuff with her at the Comic Market.
I went there during the summer and was completely bewildered.
I'm not lying.
A festival is a festival.
It's too much work and boring to go by yourself.
Let's Go to
the Festival
Dec     Heisei 18
Hello.
Izumi residence.
Oh, Konata?
I'm writing New Year's cards right now,
and I was wondering if you guys are in mourning?
I didn't get a letter about it or anything, though...
We're not.
Why do you ask?
Oh, you know...
Weren't you absent once this year because you were mourning a death in the family?
Um...
Oh, yeah.
But I'm okay now.
Don't tell me you were using another cheap trick just like in manga?
*shine shine*
We're in the middle of cleaning right now.
I see.
I won't want to keep you too long, so I'll hang up now.
Okay.
See you.
Why is it...
When you're procrastinating, you really want to do some cleaning,
but when you try to start cleaning, it suddenly becomes such a pain?
Konata...
Less breaks, okay?
So it's called Comiket?
FIRST-TIMER
I heard it was a pretty big festival,
but it sure starts early in the morning, doesn't it?
I'm so excited!
SECOND-TIMER
So she hasn't told you anything?
I pity you.
REGULAR-TIMER
Oh, she'll get used to it in no time.
Tsukasa, just to tell you,
but this event is really trying...
In various ways...
Are you okay?
Yep, I'll do my best!
Do you really understand?
I'm starting to see a lot of people who would go there...
Okay, you'll be allowed to enter soon!
Onee-chan, this place is kind of scary.
That's why I told you...
Regular Participants
Circle Members
Industry Members
Oh yeah, let me tell you the objectives.
Objectives?
Here you go.
Your shopping lists.
Once we're inside, we're going to split up and go around the circles according to these maps.
Kagami and Tsukasa, you go to numbers 1-3 in the eastern wing.
I'll take 4-6.
But be careful.
If you don't follow the paths marked in red,
you might get pushed into the lines closest to the wall,
and you won't be able to move.
Especially here and here.
If you get stuck in crowds here...
...you'll lose over 30 minutes.
Why do we have to be so desperate?
Don't worry about it.
The circles marked in green can wait until the afternoon.
They have plenty in stock so there's almost no danger of them selling out.
So focus primarily on going to the ones marked in red in the morning.
The "S" is for new publications.
The "K" stands for old goods.
If you don't know what to get, anything will do.
Even if it's old!
Here's your ammo.
You're going to have to pay in cash.
This coffee will be your sole source of refreshment.
Remember to drink at least once every 30 minutes.
Our final rendezvous point is here, at 1300 hours.
I'll wait fifteen minutes,
but if you don't show,
I'll go look for you in the medic's office, so be careful.
That is all.
Any questions?
You show so much zeal and enthusiasm only at times like this...
Please do not run!
Initial climax!
We can only sell four copies per person of the new volume.
Please understand.
Um, excuse me.
This is A-92, correct?
Yes, that is correct.
You want one of each new book?
That'll be 1,000 yen.
Now then, what did you need?
Um, which ones are the new volumes you have?
Our new ones are here and here.
They're 500 yen each.
Oh, good work!
Did you enjoy the snacks?
I'm glad!
U-Um, can I get three copies of each please?
Thank you very much!
Nurunuru Brigade Chief and Naughty Captain, correct?
Your total is 3,000 yen.
I'd like these.
Okay, your total is 4,500 yen.
Here.
Thank you very much!
Done and done.
On to the next point.
Um...
Is this the east wing?
Then north is supposed to be in this direction...
Um...
Excuse me!
I'm going that way...
I've pretty much gone through all the major places.
Let's see, the next circle is...
Just a peek.
Gauron is doing... to Sousuke!
This is...!
Do you like it?
It'll be 500 yen.
U-Um...
It's too intense for me!
There she is!
It's her!
The Legendary Girl A!
Calm down.
If you panic, she'll think we're weird!
I know, but there's an urban legend...
...saying that every circle she buys from suddenly becomes popular!
How can I not be excited?
I know.
That's why we put our best effort into this book!
So she would buy it!
That's right...
We took a break from the store near the end of the year just to make this happen!
This year will be our year!
Can I take a look?
Yes, go ahead!
Go ahead!
Um, how do you like it?
We put a lot of work into the concert scenes.
Not too much.
Thanks anyway.
Don't cry!
Next summer for sure!
Um, excuse me...
Yes?
What is it?
Where is U-61?
Hmm?
Isn't U in the east wing?
Which way is the east wing?
This is the west wing.
If you want to go to the east wing,
you'll have to get in that line right there...
...and then up to the next level.
How long does that take?
Let's see...
Right now, it will probably take an hour or two.
[ Please wait one moment ]
This is it...
I'm sorry, Kona-chan.
I just got back from the west wing a few moments ago.
If you get caught in the crowd, you'll get completely lost at this event...
And I spent one hour waiting in line for the restroom.
Well, I had a feeling it would be a bit rough for someone attending for the first time.
Let's just go around together in the afternoon.
You're still not done yet?
But it's become a lot better since they moved to Ariake.
They only had two convenience stores at the site in Harumi.
The site in Harumi?
Yep.
I think the last time in Harumi was 12 years ago...
Wait, how old were you?
About five?
My dad took me.
We always spent two nights at this place called Hotel Urashima.
It was my first summer Comiket, and the second floor was amazing...
All of the attendees' sweat vaporized in the area,
and you could see the clouds go...
*moku moku*
Enough already.
I don't want to hear anymore.
Everything got a lot easier when they finally moved the event to Ariake.
Maybe it's because the event is getting bigger...
A lot of the younger participants just think of themselves as customers, sadly.
It used to be an event we all contributed to.
Sorry to interrupt your speech, but you've lost me.
We didn't come here during summer, so I didn't know such places existed.
Yeah, but the main goods are probably sold out by now.
Oh, it's Nagato, Nagato!
The person behind Nagamon is here as a salesgirl!
What are you talking about?
How can you be out of Haruhi goods!?
What's going on here!?
What do you mean you don't have any more Nagato telephone cards?
Then why the hell did I come all the way here!?
Whoa, he's horrible.
Please calm down sir!
There's nothing I can do!
Like I said earlier...
Like I care!
There've been a surge of people like him lately.
I'm never coming back here again!
I'm terribly sorry, sir!
But unfortunately our limited edition goods...
Have already sold out!
Eh?
Are you serious?
I am serious.
Well, if you've come this late...
Who?
I feel sorry for you,
but if you want it, you have to line up early morning...
Idiot!
Asia...
W-What was that for?
We have to satisfy every customer, even the ones that get left behind!
How could you forget something so basic?
B-But...
At this point, we only have the goods that wouldn't sell left!
Leftovers, you say?
Don't you know there is still value in leftovers!?
A value that doesn't exist in popular and typical moé items!
This Comiket exists for you to discover these hidden gems!
Doesn't the real battle start now,
when all the limited edition goods have sold out!?
The true battle has begun for the industry booths!
I-I see now...
Now, why don't you recommend something to this customer?
A true gem!
Something...
Anything that I can use as a weapon?
H-How about this one!?
No!
You must mean this!
No, you see,
Nagato and the others are selling like hotcakes,
so I'd go with this one.
Even Koizumi is selling.
Shut up!
This one's been leftover for three years now!
Even though the Captain sold out on the first day!
So please, buy this Kyon!
No, I recommend Sousuke!
Um, I'd rather Saikoubi Coco-chan...
You...
Fools!
Y-You are...
President Takahashi!
That's correct.
I am President Takahashi!
I overheard your story!
I commend you for your attempt...
That place always is full of tension.
...to get customers to look at new products.
I-Is that so?
However, I cannot overlook...
I-I see...
...your selfish desires to promote side characters!
No, they're both the main protagonists.
Onee-chan, I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy, too.
We had to help around the shrine as soon as we got back from Ariake.
Why do they have such an event on New Year's Eve?
Kagami.
Tsukasa.
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Kona-chan.
You've been pretty energetic for someone who's been at that event since morning.
Plus, it's so cold I thought you wouldn't bother to come.
Well, that's true...
But January 1st marks a new beginning,
so I had to come to the first shrine visit and recharge for the coming year.
Really?
How admirable.
Well, that's what my dad says anyway-
Hi there.
Something's not right!
Shrine maiden clothes are so refreshing!
Yep, yep.
This...
And that...
We're done praying.
Good job.
Did you guys pray for something, too?
Speaking of which,
You were praying really hard for something, Onee-chan.
D-Don't say something unnecessary!
I wasn't praying that hard...
I just thought it would be nice if I were in the same class as you and Miyuki this year.
Hm...
Onee-chan, what about Kona-chan?
Kagami, you're actually pretty cute.
Shut up!
I knew you were going to say that!
That's why I was reluctant to speak!
And how you deny it is just so...
So what!?
You've always been the only one in a different class, Onee-chan.
Maybe Kuroi-sensei doesn't like me...
I'll pray so that I can be in the same class as you, too, Onee-chan!
Tsukasa...
Nah, Kagami has to be in a different class.
W-Why?
Because when I forget something, I can borrow it from you,
and when I need to copy homework, I won't get caught.
Also, if you're in our class, my class rank will go down, too.
Then why don't you go to a different class by yourself?
Don't want to.
The other day...
High school students are so nice!
Sebastian was...
Do you want to draw your fortune again this year?
Might as well, since I'm already here.
Very Good
Bad
You have really good luck, right at the start of the New Year!
Yes, and I got to see something nice...
I think this is going to be a good year.
Don't worry.
If you hit rock bottom now,
there's no where but to go but up, right?
Good things will come.
How do I say this...
It all depends on how you look at it.
Thanks.
Do you want to tie it to a branch and wash it away?
Yep, I will.
It's full!
This one, too!
Ah, here's one!
This must be what they mean by really bad luck.
Seems like it.
Whether good things come or not,
depends on the person's motivation.
The lottery is just a test of your luck.
That may be true,
but that's not something a shrine maiden should say.
Maybe I'll try to complete a set from "bad luck" all the way to "good luck".
Are these trading cards?
Maybe there are secret fortunes and other things, too!
What would a secret fortune be like?
Like "super bad luck".
So it's a negative special?
Nobody would want that.
All you have to do is add special prizes for those who collect them all!
No, we don't have any.
You know, I saw a huge kagami mochi earlier.
Like this big!
Was that where your name was derived from?
Well, that's not entirely wrong, but...
The round shape of the kagami mochi is made to represent a mirror.
Old legends say that the gods reside within mirrors.
So that name is supposed to invoke the blessings of the gods.
And the round shape signifies a stable lifestyle.
Her origins are fantastically religious in nature,
and yet she grew up to be such a pragmatic person!
Would you like one?
Here.
You sure have a lot of visitors.
Well, it is New Year's.
Although this isn't a particularly well-known place...
I wonder how many of these guys came for the shrine maidens like Dad?
So that's how you start off, huh?
I swear there isn't anyone like that!
Probably...
And once again, Happy New Year!
I hope you take good care of me this year, too!
Yes, you, too.
"Hi~ Happy New Year!"
"How about it?"
"Look at this view, this scenery,
isn't it fantastic?"
"Look at the pretty flowers blooming everywhere!"
"Oh!"
Dad, want some tea?
Sure, I'll take some.
Here.
Thanks.
Dad.
Want to play a game?
Do you want some zoni soup?
Dad!
NEW YEAR'S
ALLOWANCE
Something like that...
Apparently he's really happy when I tend to him until he gives me my New Year's money.
I'm so tired.
Well, you guys are really close...
And since I safely got my New Year's money I was thinking about going to Gamers.
Really...
It's a pain that all the stores are in the city.
I'm already on a tight budget, and then I have to pay for transportation, too.
I wish they'd open a shop near us.
But don't a lot of stores sell goods online now?
Maybe you could try that?
You just don't get it...
Well, I guess you can still rack up points online...
But browsing the store and discovering new gems is half the fun!
What's wrong with you?
You're so ready to spend it all!
Hm...
Why do they call this a pochi bag?
I heard it comes from the phrases "a tiny bit" and "just a little".
It refers to a bag you put small stuff in.
I see...
"Pocchito" would be the Kansai while "korepocchi" would be from the Kanto region.
Happy New Year!
This is Takara.
Oh Miyuki-san, Happy New Year!
Anyways, I wanted to ask you about the origins of the name "pochi bag"...
Konata... why don't you trust Daddy once in a while?
Pochi bag, is it?
I believe it comes from the phrases "a tiny bit" and "just a little"...
Could you at least ask your friends when I'm not around...?
and refers to a bag you put small stuff in.
Now, time to greet all my game friends for the first time this year.
Hm...
and a mess and all. In the end,
I wasn't able to buy any Haruhi goods...
;_;
Don't cry!
I wasn't able to buy any Haruhi goods...
;_;
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
;_;
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Don't cry!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Your friend konakona has logged on
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Oh?
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Finally got on. Been busy for a while
Yeah, Happy New Year! >w<b
Congratslololo
Finally got on. Been busy for a while
Your friend Nanakon has logged on
It's Sensei.
Happy New Year, Sensei
Yo, Happy New Year! (^w^)/
Let's have another wonderful year
Happy New Year, Sensei
Yo, Happy New Year! (^w^)/
Let's have another wonderful year
Yep, sounds good (>w<)b
And like...
Sensei's always online...
Does she really not have anything else to do?
No wonder she doesn't have a boyfriend.
Lucky Channel!
Oh-Oha-lucky!
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru!
Time sure flies by!
Lucky Channel is already on its 12th episode!
This sea is hell.
Um, uh...
As you can see,
Akira-sama was supposed to appear in the actual series this week,
but she suddenly became ill and...
Yes, you caught a cold, right?
But I put up a cardboard cutout of Akira-sama as a substitute,
so if you look carefully...
Huh?
Hey...
A-Akira-sama?
As you can see, Akira-sama is really tired right now,
thus I think we should wrap it up.
Well then everyone, bye-bii!
Don't let it get to your head?
That's not true at all!
Eh?
I will?
Let you listen to the new version of Motteke Sailor Fuku?
Please look forward to it?
If you don't watch next week...
In the name of Mars, I will punish you?
Fumoffu!
You got pretty into it!
It was so much fun!
Yes.
Ah, don't put anything in, anyone!
It's your turn, right?
Now would be the time when you're supposed to queue the song.
I haven't decided!
Which should I sing?
I guess I'll look, too.
Ah, there is a menu.
Yep.
It seems you can have a whole meal here, too.
That song we just sang totally broke my flow.
I should have saved it for later.
What flow?
How do I say this...
Don't you know what I mean?
The flow of songs when you feel like you sing better?
No idea.
I wonder if I can sing this one?
Ooi GODMAN kikoerukai
おーい　ゴッドマン　聞こえるかい
Hey, Godman? Can you hear me?
Look, they have a tambourine, too.
Ooi GODMAN tondekoi
おーい　ゴッドマン　飛んでこい
Hey, Godman? Leap forth!
You can spice things up with this.
Ah! Yuki-chan, let's use this!
Ah, good idea.
All right, this is it!
Even a hardcore anime song will work, so just sing it!
Anyways, I put in a song to make things interesting.
Ah!
You guys know this one, right?
I do!
I know some of it.
Make-
負けー
Don't lo-
Oops, messed up.
Futoshita shunkan ni-
ふとした瞬間にー
Unexpectedly, for a moment...
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Miyuki here.
When something completely outclasses the competition,
and stands above the rest,
we use the word "dantotsu" to describe it.
Which is presumably short for "danzen" top.
This word first appeared in literature...
...after the recent city gubernatorial election.
And quite literally described that person who won by a landslide...
...on the very top.
Next week: "Savory Day"
「Savory Day」
Look forward to it.