Good morning, Nagi.
Good morning.
Wow, it suddenly got cold, huh?
Well, it IS the end of October.
Oh. Halloween.
Yeah. Come to think of it, you see lots of
Halloween decorations around now, huh?
Sure do. I feel like recently,
it's suddenly taken root here in Japan.
Yeah, true enough.
You're not scared?
Huh?
Nagi?
Halloween means MONSTERS, doesn't it?
That's not scary?
No, it ain't scary. Halloween's
not about real monsters.
I have a little trouble
with scary stories, but that's it.
A "little," huh?
Just a little!
You have things like that, don't you?
No, I can't think of anything.
GOOD MORNING!
Aoigaoka
High School
All right, give it your all!
G-good morning.
Yes, good morning!
Good morning.
GOOD MORNING!
Nothing gives you trouble, right?
Has trouble with
enthusiasm
Let's all do our best today!
Well, I have trouble with that, too...
GOOD MORNING!
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
THE PRESENT
Ah! Nagi-chan, Yuko-chan! Good morning!
'Morning...
Huh? The two of you look tired. What happened?
Early-morning... enthusiasm...
Nagi-chan?
Everyone has somethin' that gives them trouble.
What is THIS?!
What's the matter?
There's a creepy stuffed animal on my desk.
Whoa, what is that? It's nasty!
Right?
Oh, is it for Halloween? A trick-or-treat thingy?
A prank? Harassment? This sure seems like it.
Shouldn't you just throw it away?
But then I could be cursed!
What should I do? I can't say
it was ME who made it...
Yeah, sure enough. A curse would be scary!
What should I do? I can't say
it was ME who made it...
Right?
What should I do? I can't say
it was ME who made it...
Huh? Run, YOU made that stuffed doll?
Sorry we said such nasty things.
No, that's fine.
I heard that you like them,
so I tried hard to make one, but...
Animals are hard, huh?
It doesn't look like one, huh?
No, it's really good!
Yeah, yeah!
Especially this, um...
Ear-looking thing.
Wait, is it a horn?
And this bulging eye...
I mean, googly eye...
Oh, this mouth!
The way it opens is so distinctive, huh?
Yeah! It really looks like it!
Um, I said I like this?
What could it be?
I wonder if it looks like it...
Yeah.
A Halloween party?
Why all of a sudden?
Some things happened this morning,
and we started talking about it.
I've been interested in Halloween for a while.
Tomorrow's Saturday,
so let's all make some sweets and eat them!
I look forward to it!
What kind of sweets should we do?
Cookies or something? Or cakes?
I'll pass.
Huh?
Nagi, you don't like making sweets?
It takes precise measurements and stuff.
That's not for me.
Also, I'm on a diet.
Don't worry about it.
I'll measure out the calories for you, Nagi.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, if I only have to eat...
Okay!
What about you, Toru?
I think I'll be a little late.
Oh.
I'll come over and eat some once they're done.
Sure, okay!
Oh, then I'll show up later with Toru.
Okay.
Well, Yuko-chan, want to make them with me?
Sure. Is there anything I should bring over?
My mom makes sweets,
so I think we have just about everything.
Oh. I'm lookin' forward to it!
Okay, let's do it tomorrow!
Yeah!
Run, what are you drawing?
Look. Toru and I are exchanging diaries.
We're doing a drawing game!
What does it look like?
It's the "stuffed animal incident" again!
Is that even an animal?
It looks kinda like a bug...
Maybe it's a little difficult to tell.
Okay, here's a hint: it's often eaten.
People eat it?!
That was a big one.
It's a zebra, isn't it?
Toru, that's right!
Z...
A zebra...
Great job, Toru!
THIS is a zebra? Am I just dense?
Nagi, you're over-thinking it.
I don't mind taking it, but this thing is a bit scary.
You're not going home yet?
No, I'm going.
Come to think of it, do you want to meet before
going to Run-chan's house tomorrow?
Yeah, that would help me out.
So, the station's north exit,
near the entrance to the shopping arcade.
Okay.
Toru! Th-that!
This? I got it from Run-chan.
Yes, I know!
Then, what?
What is it supposed to be?
You can't tell, Nagi?
Why? This is really irritating!
The truth is, I got the same kind of thing.
It's so big!
How cruel.
Please, you MUST give me that!
Huh? No way. This is mine.
Don't say that!
No, no.
You're cruel!
It's not cruel at all.
Sorry for the wait.
Well, shall we go?
I'll get things ready, so wait for me, okay?
Yeah. But hurry.
By the way, Nagi...
What animal do you like?
Huh? Don't tell me you're going to put it
into that drawing exchange with Run!
No, that's not it.
I just wanted to ask.
Oh, really? Well... I like small, cute animals.
Like squirrels.
Ah. Cute, aren't they? Squirrels.
Oh, yeah. This.
I didn't say what it is, did I?
You wanna know?
I'm all ready!
Yes, I do! Come on, come on, come on!
Please, tell me!
They're cute, aren't they? Squirrels.
Come on, Toru!
Small animals.
What do you think they're talking about?
Tell me!
Beats me.
I'm home.
Yup, this is scary.
This way?
Trick or treat!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Sure enough, all these stores
are decked out for Halloween.
So, our meeting place should be around here...
We said "Trick or treat," didn't we?!
Ah. Nagi.
Candy!
Hand it over!
I told them I didn't work there, but those kids...
I don't have any candy, either.
So...
Toru, don't tell me those
are your normal clothes!
Halloween
Fair
Toru, don't tell me those
are your normal clothes!
Halloween
Fair
Huh?
We go through this shopping arcade
to go to Run's house?
Your first time?
Yeah. I think we took a different route
to get there last time.
Correct. This way is a little roundabout. Listen...
Run-chan said she'd be making sweets.
So we'll bring backup sweets.
Oh, we're here to buy them?
Wait, you're assuming she'll mess up?!
Oh, Toru-chan!
Good afternoon.
You're looking well.
Here. Take this
VINEGARED
SQUID
Here. Take this
VINEGARED
SQUID
Thank you.
Toru-chan!
See these? They're delicious.
Have some.
Thank you, ma'am.
Oh, that's right.
At the festival, Toru said the people
at the arcade give her things.
Toru-chan! Here, take this!
Thanks for coming by.
Here, take this bag now, Toru.
She ain't buyin' a thing!
Now what, all of a sudden?
We still have time,
so we're here at the bookstore.
Oh.
There's a book I've been wanting, too. Suits me.
Say, Toru? This...
Omega Bookstore
Nagi.
One Hour Later
This manga...
The girl on the cover looks like Yuko.
Hey, isn't that a MATURE manga?
Whoa, you're right. It really looks like her!
Look. This is a collection of shorts,
but all the heroines have the same kind of face.
If we showed this author a picture of Yuko,
I think he'd buy it for a lot of money.
Let's buy this.
Okay, let's make them!
Yuko-chan, want an apron?
Yeah. Let me use that.
Your mom really does make sweets, huh?
There are so many cute molds!
Is it okay for me to use ALL this?
Yeah! She said we could use anything!
Really? I can't wait.
So, what should we make first?
Um, hold on a minute.
Got it.
This! Pancakes!
Even though it's Halloween?
Yeah! Today feels like pancakes!
O-oh?
That's right! The other day,
I broke an egg one-handed!
Watch!
The other day, I broke an egg one-handed!
Run! Let's move on to the next step!
Is this about right?
Yes, I think it's good.
Well, let's cook it.
Okay.
Run!
Thank good-
Ow...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'll make it again!
I-It's okay. You don't have to rush.
I'm the one who was clumsy.
Why should YOU have to pay, too?
No, don't worry about it.
That's it! I have to become a victim, too!
What should we do?
Wanna take a bath?
Yeah.
Yuko-chan.
You're neat, Yuko-chan. So stylish.
That's not true at all.
Sure enough, is it because you have a pet?
What was it, it sounded like something else...
A tapeworm!
That again?!
Thanks to the power of tapeworm, right?
I don't have that, and it ain't a pet!
Looking like THIS in someone else's house...
I'll put a change of clothes in the living room.
I wish she'd brought them
into the washroom with her.
Dynamite!
Y-you're here?!
Such shameful behavior
in someone else's house!
I don't recall raising such a lewd daughter!
Huh? Wh-what?
What're you saying?
And what's with these outrageous breasts?!
Huh? What?!
Nagi, what's goin' on?
She's been practicing this for YOU,
Yuko, so just listen.
To what?
Note: Parody of this show's creator, bb Kuroda cc Hakuda
Girl
&
xxx
What is that manga?!
We found an EROTIC manga
with someone who looks just like you.
Huh? No! A dirty manga?
Here, have a peep.
No! Cut it out! I hate that erotic stuff!
Jeez!
What is this? Eew!
So she says, but she looks like
she'll read it all, huh?
I don't believe it!
So she says, but she looks like
she'll read it all, huh?
Yuko-chan, what's the matter?
Hey-
What's the matter, Toru?
Run-chan, not you.
It seems she's rather taken with it.
VINEGARED SQUID Sponge Cake
Wow! So many snacks!
Toru got all this from the shopping arcade.
That's great, Toru!
I'm glad. Still, I wanted everyone
to have pancakes...
Run-chan's pancakes!
But I messed up.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah. But I wanted to
eat pancakes with you all...
You can just make them next time.
Yeah. You're right.
Well, should we get started?
Okay, let's make a toast!
It's Halloween, so maybe
we should toast the ghosts!
Yeah, you're right. Wait, that makes no sense!
Hold on a minute.
Let's make them now.
Huh?
Make them again? But we don't have
any more pancake mix.
It's all right.
Wheat
Flour
Here!
We can make them with this.
Crazy Love Cake!
Everyone ready?
Yeah.
Totteoki no jikan ga yatte kimashita, Are U Ready?
That special time has come, Are U Ready?
Egg!
Totteoki no jikan ga yatte kimashita, Are U Ready?
That special time has come, Are U Ready?
Okay!
Totteoki no jikan ga yatte kimashita, Are U Ready?
That special time has come, Are U Ready?
Tokimeku yo Cook Girl
I'm so excited, Cook Girl
Jouzu ni tsukutte, egao sakasemashou
Cook it well and let's bring forth some smiling faces
Okay, I'll fry 'em.
Jouzu ni tsukutte, egao sakasemashou
Cook it well and let's bring forth some smiling faces
Okay, I'll fry 'em.
Nanoni "Danzen taberu ha" sengen to ka
But someone proclaims, "I'll definitely eat it"
Sabotcha dame (*_*) Let's make!
No slacking off (*_*) Let's make!
Watashitachi dake no special
A special just for us
Reigai nante aru wake ga nai!? Joshi wa love sweets
No way there's any exception! Love sweets are for girls
Ichinichi kurai calorie keisan, wasureta furi ni shichae!
For just one day, pretend you forgot to count your calories!
Okay, it's done.
Ichinichi kurai calorie keisan, wasureta furi ni shichae!
For just one day, pretend you forgot to count your calories!
All done!
Ichinichi kurai calorie keisan, wasureta furi ni shichae!
For just one day, pretend you forgot to count your calories!
All done!
Chotto kurai misutta tte Good, shippai wa seikou no mama
If you make a little mistake, it's still good
It looks delicious.
Chotto kurai misutta tte Good, shippai wa seikou no mama
If you make a little mistake, it's still good
We made this together. Come on, let's eat.
Chotto kurai misutta tte Good, shippai wa seikou no mama
If you make a little mistake, it's still good
We made this together. Come on, let's eat.
Chotto kurai misutta tte Good, shippai wa seikou no mama
Failure is still a success
Yeah!
Chotto kurai misutta tte Good, shippai wa seikou no mama
Failure is still a success
Yeah!
Kimochi ga daiji, sou deshou? Okoge mo ai seru kibun yo
Emotions are important, right?
Let's eat!
Kimochi ga daiji, sou deshou? Okoge mo ai seru kibun yo
Emotions are important, right?
A feeling you can even love it if burnt
It looks delicious!
Kimochi ga daiji, sou deshou? Okoge mo ai seru kibun yo
A feeling you can even love it if burnt
Crazy Love Cake!
It's delicious!
Yeah, it's great!
Lady gabu Cake!
Lady, chomp, cake!
Crazy Love Cake!
I'm glad.
Toru, you've got some on you.
Crazy Love Cake!
Here, Yuko. Say "Ahh."
C'mon, stop that.
I'm full!
Nagi, what about your diet?
D-didn't you measure the calories?!
Not to worry. I cut back on the sweet stuff.
Oh, jeez. Don't scare me like that.
Toru. We'll do the cleaning up together.
Toru, about your outfit...
It's cute, like cosplay, huh?
It's 'cuz of outfits like THIS
that kids swarm around her.
Good thing, huh, Toru?
No, they were pulling her clothes,
crying madly, that sort of thing.
Shouldn't you have done like last year
and passed out candy?
Toru likes kids, so last year-
You don't have to mention that.
What's wrong, Toru?
Toru, that's WAY unexpected!
No!
Toru likes kids.
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!
What do you think this subtitle means?
Hmm, soft drinks?
Isn't it a bit sad, feigning ignorance
when you really know?
Shut up! It was a promise.
I, Yutaka, think that it's about time
that "Yutaka" appears in the subtitle.
I don't think that idea
is going to go anywhere at all.
Next time, on A-Channel: "Carbonation"
Next
Episode!
CARBONATION
Next time, on A-Channel: "Carbonation"
Next
Episode!
CARBONATION
How about "Yutaka and Torun"?
Next
Episode!
CARBONATION
I told you, include me so it's the three of us!