Hi, everyone, we're going
to start Kaleido Star.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well, do you
have someone you like?
He makes your heart ache.
He's someone you exchange diaries
with and hold hands with.
One day, I hope I fall in love
with someone wonderful too.
I hope! I hope...
Huh? Ken, why are you crying?
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
Here, wake up, wake up!
"The Diva's Amazing Love."
Just because it's your day off,
that doesn't mean you should keep
sleeping as long as you want.
Excuse me, but I'd been working at
Theatrical Camp until yesterday.
You met Pamela, didn't you?
Was she doing all right?
Yes.
She showed me an amazing maneuver of hers.
Yeah, yeah. I remember that.
But the success rate of
that maneuver was very low,
and she was seldom allowed
to do it in a real show.
I see...
It's true. If she failed that
maneuver, it wouldn't be surprising.
Even though I actually saw that,
it was like I saw a miracle.
It just gave me chills.
Jumping straight up and grabbing
the same swing she jumped from...
I wonder if the Legendary
Great Maneuver is like that.
It seems that Kaleido Stage
wasn't a suitable place for her.
Here, it's finished. Thanks, Sora.
Being a Dorm Supervisor is not an easy job.
That's right. Please be thankful.
This is it. This is it. Is she here?
Miss Sarah!
Miss Sarah Dupont.
Aren't you here?
Please come out.
Me?
Are they mass media people?
I found her!
We're running away, Sora!
What? Why?
Wait!
What did you do, Miss Sarah?!
Oh...
What happened?
I can't run anymore.
Please run away by yourself, Sora.
So, why do I have to run away?
Miss Sarah!
Please wait! Oh!
Sarah...
I came here for you, my eternal diva.
Andy...
Miss Sarah Dupont,
so the rumor is true that you're moving
to Andy Lowe's major label, ADX?
I think I already said no.
It's true.
Andy!
What?! What?!
What are you saying?
I'm not going anywhere.
If you're worried about
Kalos, he already said okay.
What?
So, is it true you are dating?
Who knows?
Please pose for us as a pair.
Make sure we both look nice.
Ouch!
I will be nice enough to
stop right here today.
As for any other questions,
this girl will answer for me.
Uh...
So, how is it?
What is their relationship?
I don't know. I don't! I don't!
I'm sorry... I can't help you guys.
What was that?
They were talking about Miss
Sarah moving to a major label.
But she's not leaving
Kaleido Stage, I hope...
What?! Miss Sarah is crying.
I can't believe it.
It's open.
Miss Sarah...
Sora...
May I come in?
Please.
Sorry about earlier.
Oh, don't worry about it.
So, the mass media people
aren't coming here anymore?
They were here,
but they left as soon as they found out
that I wasn't interested in talking.
A picture?
Yes. From ten years ago.
Ten years ago?
That's right.
A picture of Andy, Kalos and me...
Really...
Miss Sarah, Mr. Andy and Kalos...
Ka--!
Kalos?!
You've got good, tight muscles!
You fill the spot.
You don't have a role.
Why does he look so nice?!
Back then, we were always hungry,
but our hearts were filled with dreams.
Andy was into writing music.
I was into singing,
and Kalos was aiming to be a magician.
Kalos was the most popular among us three.
And he became popular enough that he
could have his own show in Las Vegas.
But...
He injured his fingers.
Didn't they get better?
Not enough to perform magic again.
He got the insurance money from the
policy he had taken out on his fingers.
But,
Kalos used that as startup capital for
Kaleido Stage, another dream of his.
He spent everything he had.
Everything...
Isn't he extreme?
But I followed Kalos.
Kalos told me not to do it.
But it was obvious that he was just bluffing.
But Miss Sarah, weren't
you aiming to be a singer?
Yes, I was.
But, you followed Boss...
Hm?
I think I was in love.
Oh. You were in...
Love?!
You fill the spot.
I want you to do it.
If you don't like it, leave!
The image I have in mind
is completely different...
Well, of course, I'm still in love, but...
E-Even now?!
I didn't know that.
It's not like I was hiding it...
But maybe it's only natural
that other people can't tell.
But...
Then, did you give up
your dream for the Boss?
What?
No. It's not like I gave up my dream.
My dream just changed.
In those days, I wished I could
sing for everybody in the world.
But now...
I enjoy singing here.
I love everybody,
and I think this is the
place best suited for me.
Not only that,
I think the feeling that I'm needed
is something I can't replace
with anything else.
But...
I'm afraid he no longer needs me.
Ten years...
I'm sure Miss Sarah was crying back then.
Unless the Boss stops her,
I'm sure Miss Sarah will move
to Mr. Andy's recording company.
Boss... Please wait a moment!
Boss!
I have something to talk...
Excuse me!
I have something I want to talk about!!
He ignored me!
I'm so mad now!
What the hell is going on? It's you, Sora.
Mr. Policeman, which way
did the Boss's car go?
Don't tell me you're running after a car?
Oh, I see.
So, Miss Sarah is in love with Kalos.
You never can judge people
by the way they look.
That's for sure.
Anyway, Miss Sarah is facing a big decision,
so where did he go?
Oh, here he is!
That is...
Hey, that's a very expensive restaurant.
What?
Let's follow him.
Ten-four.
Really, how can he go out and have a
gourmet meal in this kind of situation?
Where's the mark?
I found him.
Good. Let's get closer.
Ten-four.
Really,
back then, all you thought of was magic.
Now, all you care about is Kaleido Stage.
I feel sorry for Sarah.
So, you're really okay about Sarah, right?
Yeah. I don't need her anymore.
He doesn't need her?
Back then, I stood no chance against you.
But, it's different now.
I can introduce Sarah to the world.
And...
Unlike you, I sincerely love Sarah.
Please give a toast to me and Sarah.
A toast?
All right.
What?!
Wait!
Sora.
Do you know her?
She is in our cast.
What are you doing?
That's my line!
Without asking how Miss Sarah feels,
why are you making decisions as you please?
It's none of your business.
Leave.
No, I won't! Please listen to my story!
Leave!
No, I will not! Please listen to me!
I refuse. Leave!
No, I won't! Please listen to my story!
These two are just alike!
I refuse. Leave!
No, I won't!
Not until you listen to my story!
Okay.
Why don't we listen to what she has to say?
What do you say, Kalos?
Thank you.
Boss, Miss Sarah loves Kaleido Stage.
She doesn't want to go.
Aren't you lying when you
say that you don't need her?
What do I gain by telling a lie like that?
I don't need Sarah.
You're terrible, saying something like that.
You asked me a question. So I
just answered with the truth.
But,
I know you needed her when you established
Kaleido Stage ten years ago.
So, even now, you must...
That is what she tells herself.
I don't recall ever saying
even a word like that to her.
So, you're really saying that you
just used Sarah for ten years?
That's right.
Boss, I thought you were a very
difficult, unreasonable, scary
and unpleasant man who doesn't
listen to others, but...
But you created such a
wonderful Kaleido Stage,
so I thought you must have a good heart.
I never knew you were so cold-hearted.
Sorry, but I have things to
take care of. I'm leaving now.
I will pick up Sarah sometime today.
All right.
Boss!
Are you really sure that it's okay with you?
Miss Sarah...
Come in.
Excuse... Oh...
Sorry. It's such a mess.
Miss Sarah...
Andy called and said he would be
here to pick me up by evening.
So, pretty soon, I'll be an
artist for the ADX label!
If I could, I'd want to have
a cheerful farewell party,
but... I can't help it.
Miss Sarah, you don't mind doing this?
I don't know.
It's a bit sudden,
so I'm really not sure right now.
But... I've known Kalos for ten years,
and he has never once lied to me.
And Kalos told me that he
didn't need me anymore.
So I think he really meant what he said.
Miss Sarah...
When you send me off, please
do it cheerfully with everyone.
I'm not good at dealing with gloomy things.
Well, I have a little more work to do.
I can ask the moving company
to take care of the big stuff,
but I'll need the nunchaku and
Chinese broadsword right away, so...
Miss Sarah's picture is
already on the ADX home page.
They're fast.
I guess there's no stopping it now.
When someone you trusted says
he doesn't need you anymore,
I think it'd be unbearable to stay.
That's true.
According to what I heard,
many recording companies have
tried to recruit her in the past.
What?
That means that the Boss never
said anything until now?
I wonder why the Boss said
something like that only now?
Maybe she suddenly lost value to him.
To tell the truth, there are
quite a lot of Sarah fans.
So I'm pretty sure it'll
damage our sales figures.
This has to be a love triangle.
I bet their relationship is too
complicated to be described in words.
That sounds good!
The love entangled during
ten years. Love! Love! Love!
Miss Sarah's growing love
for Kalos. Love! Love! Love!
Mr. Andy's love for Miss
Sarah. Love! Love! Love!
Kalos withdraws because of
his love. Love! Love! Love!
And just then, in front of Miss Sarah,
like a flash of lightning,
appears the girl, Sora!
Troubled Miss Sarah's love, love, love!
You're taking it too far.
You think?
But, don't you think that maybe
the Boss withdrew himself?
Everything would certainly make
sense if you thought of it that way.
Yeah...
I doubt we should leave
everything the way it is.
Seriously...
Here we go again. Sora's specialty.
Shall we stick our nose in?
But how?
Hm... Let me think about it a little.
The Fool...
Now there's an interesting card.
As long as you don't stick to one idea,
the possibilities will be infinite.
However...
Oh...
What?
The Fool...
That's it!
Thank you for helping me, Fool!
Do you really know what you're doing?
Shall we go?
Yes.
Miss Sarah...
Oh?
You two are the only ones to send me off?
What happened to Sora?
We have a message for you from Sora.
She says if you want to know
how the Boss feels about you,
please come to the stage.
What?! I already know that...
Well, I'm interested.
Andy.
Sora, what?!
I am the mysterious Fool, Magical Rabbit.
With my magic, I will find
out your true feelings.
Obviously, she has no clue what I meant.
Fool, find anything related to Miss Sarah.
Okay, okay, okay.
What the hell are you doing?!
Get out!
If you want me to get out,
you should tell me the truth.
What's this nonsense about
telling the truth?! I never lie!
That's enough!
No, I won't!
I will not stop until I find out
what you think of Miss Sarah.
It's none of your business!
Who cares if it's my business or not?!
I guess I won't have a chance
to sing here anymore.
Then, allow me to speak on your behalf.
"Sarah, please don't go!"
Stop it!
"I need you!"
Sora!
"I love you, Sarah!"
"Please keep singing for
Kaleido Stage, Sarah!"
I don't have any special
feelings towards Sarah!
Okay.
Ten-four.
Okay, Jonathan.
Ah-hah...
Then let me ask you this.
What?
How about the picture
sitting over there, then?
What! When did it...
Please don't underestimate the
power of the Magical Rabbit.
Why do you still keep that ten-year-old photo
from when the three of you were together?
Sora,
never tell Sarah what I'm going to say now.
It's true, ten years ago...
no, even after that, I needed Sarah.
Kaleido Stage needed Sarah's songs,
and I needed her.
Even when things didn't go well,
and when I was having hard times,
she was always beside me.
Before I knew it,
I couldn't imagine not having her beside me.
This may sound conceited,
but if I tell her that I
don't need her anymore,
she can go after her dream
without reservations.
And I knew that.
He really is conceited.
But, I didn't have the courage to
tell even a simple lie like that.
Without the courage to lose her,
I've robbed her for ten years of the
chance to make her dreams come true.
This time,
the offer came from Andy.
I know he can make her dreams come true.
I'm aware that I need Sarah now, and
even in the future, I will need her.
But, I don't want her to
know about this right now.
Such a fool...
Andy, I...
I understand.
What a farce this has been.
When you're tired of Kalos, call me anytime.
If you care about Sarah, don't
tell her what I just told you.
All right?
Too late!
What!
That's right.
I heard everything you said.
Everything?!
Microphone...
I will leave you two alone. Enjoy.
Hey!
Kalos,
you really have no clue, do you?
You have a chance to sing on the world stage.
Please don't decide my dream
without consulting me.
Right now,
I like Kaleido Stage much
more than the world stage.
Layla, Sora... And whenever
we have newcomers,
I like singing here more and more.
Besides, you're here.
Now, everyone, this is the
first show after our vacation.
So, let's brace ourselves!
Yes.
Curtain's rising!
Yes!
"Next Kaleido Star"
I came here to see your regretful face.
And so, suddenly, my junior high
school classmate came to the U.S.
But something seems wrong with her.
Not only that...
Sora, you don't mind coming
along with me, do you?
What?!
Mr. Yuri asked me out!
Er... uh... well... Oh,
dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear...
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"An Amazing Sinister Rumor."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru