So sleepy...
Geez.
You tossed your skirt in the laundry basket with a tissue still in its pocket, didn't you?
It was a disaster.
Also, make sure that you separate
your clothes based on their colours.
The dark coloured ones go in the orange basket-
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop nitpicking over every little thing!
Guys are supposed to go out with a ba-
We want a home run!
Yay, yay, yay!
Hit one now! Yay!
We want a home run!
Yay, yay, yay!
Don't worry about it!
All right!
And now... it's time for the great Minori.
Fight, captain!
My, my, thanks for cheering me on!
Kushieda...
Give me your best shot!
That refreshing smile...
Kushieda... That sparkling sweat...
First base! Yay!
Second base! Yay!
Turning at the third base, and we have a home run!
That off-pitch singing...
Home in!
Oh, Kushieda... You're as wonderful as always...
Stop it with that lewd look, you disgusting dog.
Kushieda, about the co-ed practice on the weekend...
Oh hey, Kitamura-kun. I was about to-
Hey, are you listening to me, you stupid dog?!
Stop doing that-
Hey!
Wait!
Even the Go Home Club is getting their morning run,
Taiga, stop-!
good and proper.
Take that!
Your health comes first, after all.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Your Song
A cellphone decoration?
You're really skilled with your fingers.
You could say that.
I might not look it, but I'm rather good with my hands.
What's Kushieda doing?
All right, one down!
Next up is...
What's up with that smothered voice?
Um, y-you see...
Hey, why don't I decorate yours too, Takasu-kun?
You see, I'm a part-time cellphone decorator.
D-Decorator?
I'll spell out "Ryuuji" with purple Swarovski stones on yours.
Ryuuji
She'd do that for me?
No, I-I'm all rig...
Kushieda.
Please decorate ours, too.
I see, more orders!
On this paper,
write down your name, the colour you want, and a small drawing.
To give it a lovely feel, I'll go with a large heart and the colour pink.
That's lovely!
So she's a part-time cellphone decorator...
The sparkling Kushieda and her sparkling decorations...
What a wonderful combination.
Hey, Ya-chan's not eating here since she's at the hostess club, right?
Then, can I have her side dish?
And she said "Ryuuji." She remembered my first name...
That's because I call you that all the time.
But anyway, about Ya-chan's side dish...
Oh man, I talked with her so much...
Taiga, was I able to talk naturally with...
...her?
Listen when people are talking to you!
And no, you sounded really shady!
What about dinner, is it ready yet?
That hurt, you know! It's almost done.
Today, we're having a rice bowl dish,
so as long as we have rice we'll be ok-
What the?!
What's wrong?
The rice cooker's broken.
Welcome and good evening!
What should I get?
Going all the way out to a family restaurant...
We didn't have any rice, but there was bread.
Bay while you can, mongrel.
Soon, you'll be bowing your head in gratitude.
And here you go, two servings!
Huh? But we haven't ordered anyth-
What?!
Keep this a secret.
It's an extra large serving of ice cream, the Taiga Special!
Hide it from the other customers while you eat it, okay?
Thanks as usual, Minorin.
"As usual"?
Takasu-kun doesn't like sweet things?
Then, how about some French fries?
I'll give you a huge serving! A huge serving!
No, I'm-
Minorin also works part time at places like
convenience stores and karaoke clubs, right?
Yeah! And last week, I added a shabu-shabu place to the list!
That many?!
And I'm still saving time for other things!
Being the girls' softball club captain,
I can't possibly skip club activities, after all.
Are you working so hard because you want something in particular?
Nah, I've just got the time, so I've gotta labour.
"Labour"?
Yes, the "Mysterious Files of Labour"!
TL Note: This is a pun-reference to the '96 show Ginrou Kaiki Files.
What?
The kind of labour that revives you!
But wow, you two sure are close now.
Waitress, some cold water, please.
Well, enjoy your time here.
I'm pretty sure you poking my eyes all day has impaired my eyesight.
You pitiful mongrel, drooling while checking out Minorin's uniform...
I was just thinking...
...that her smile was so bright...
S-Spare my eyes!
If I continue, my fingers will be contaminated.
Dammit...
But why is she juggling all those jobs?
She called it the "Mysterious Files of Labour", right?
Is it possible that she has a reason for earning all that money?
Something related to her home?
Maybe she's helping her sick mum?
She called it labouring.
But even so...
You should stop assuming things.
Huh?
"I'm the only one who truly understands her!"
It'll only add on to your filth level.
Ew, how gross!
Keep your distance from me, you're so disgusting!
Hey, Taiga! What's with your tone? You're so cold!
Stay away from me!
Since when have I not been cold towards you?
Now that you mention it...
Hi, Inko-chan! Sorry to make you wait, but it's dinner time!
I'll give you a huge serving! A huge serving!
-nko.
Oh, are you going for it? Inko-chan, you're going for it?
-nko, -oop!
Poop!
Man, the mornings during holidays are really refreshing!
We've gone out for breakfast.
There's sandwiches in the fridge.
- Ryuu
Right, Taiga?
I shouldn't have told you...
Did you say something?
Not bothering to prepare breakfast so you can see Minorin at the family restaurant...
It can't be helped, the rice cooker is still broken.
Then, why don't we go to an electrical appliance store first?
You even said you hate bread.
I don't mind eating bread for breakfast.
Why are you so cheerful?
Those clothes don't look good on you.
I forgot something at home-
What an annoying idiot.
I beg you, let go of me!
What you wear won't make a difference!
Hey, you there!
Aren't you Mirano-chan's son?
Oh, old man Inage?
"Mirano"?
Yeah, Yasuko's hostess name.
Mirano-chan
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Hi! Go out the station's north exit, it's 200 meters straight ahead!
I'm Vaisravana's Heaven's Mirano-chan!
How old do I look? Twenty-three?
Bingo!
This is a fortunate morning!
And now to grab a feel of Mirano-chan's DNA!
Nice and firm, being young must be nice!
Let's go.
Somehow, this old guy's pissing me off.
Hold it right there, you two!
If you haven't eaten breakfast yet, I recommend the docosahexaenoic acid and the calcium-filled taste of this Gyonisa!
Okay.
Huh?
Kushieda?
Minorin?
INAGE LIQUOR STORE
Here, carry this!
W-Why?
Another!
And some more!
It'd be better if I-
No, it's okay. Sit down and relax with some tea.
You're Mirano-chan's son, after all.
Why do I have to do this?!
I ask her for some help, but only during holidays.
Kushieda, you better work hard!
Understood!
These days, we're so busy that we've run out of workers.
You ran out of workers?
Oh yeah, do you want to work here too, young lady?
Being friends with Kushieda and all...
I'll pay you well!
Yes!
I'll work!
Along with her.
I can't keep this up!
Hey, don't cause a fuss.
It'll give Kushieda trouble.
Then, help out a little!
Little girl, I need you to go do the deliveries!
Three of those beer cases.
With pleasure!
And that's it!
Be careful on your way.
What's wrong, Taiga?
You...
You can't ride a bik-
Shut up!
So what if I can't ride a bike?!
I'll just have to deliver it like this!
That's wrong! You're doing it wrong!
You're on fire, Taiga!
She's ridiculous.
Well, if she just pushes the bike, she'll be all right, I guess.
Oh right, I was going to restock the shochu.
I'll-
I'll help, too.
I'd feel bad if I wasn't doing anything.
Then, I'll be counting on you.
Y-Yeah!
Where's the potato shochu?
It's really hard to see in this darkness.
This place isn't used that often.
They don't open up this place more than once a week or so.
If we got locked in here, it'd be horrible.
It'd almost feel like we were stranded or something!
That little runt, leaving it open like that.
Hey! There are still people in here!
S.O.S.! S.O.S.!
Calm down, Takasu-kun!
Kushieda?
It's for times like these that we have school songs!
Huh?
School songs?
This is dumb.
There's no reason for me to make an effort.
I really can't keep this up.
Keep what up?
K-Kitamura-kun! W-Why are you h-here?
Self-training.
By the way, is that your bike?
Um, yeah...
Something like that.
You can ride a bike now?
That's remarkable progress.
Um, setting that aside...
How did you know that I couldn't ride a bike?
That's because I observed you pretty closely last year.
Bikes are great. The world opens up before you.
I'll see you tomorrow, Aisaka.
He was observing me last year?
Dammit!
Opening up a world in which Kitamura-kun's not watching me...
...is meaningless!
Dammit!
Two, thr-
Aren't you lat- What happened? You look awful.
Nothing much. Where are the others?
Oh, right, where has that Kushieda run off to?
Not minding Ryuuji-kun...
That mongrel, slacking off in comfort while I'm out working!
What're you saying?
Anyway, the next delivery's three blocks away-
Ryuuji, what the hell are you up to?!
The bridge that leads to the future
That bridge is a chopstick, a chopstick
My throat's all dry.
Nobody noticed us even though we raised our voices...
At around this time, the old guy's obsessing over horse racing.
Right...
It's getting a little chilly.
I'll lend you my coat, the-
Okay, let's warm up!
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
Who's scared? Aren't you the pitcher?
He's scared! Hey!
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
Wait, you're actually scared?
Your hand's trembling.
You've got it all wrong, I'm trembling from excitement!
Here I go, you'd better be ready!
Strike!
Change-over.
We swap places now.
Oh, okay.
You see, there's no point being afraid.
That's why...
...I just need to beat up my weakness!
Kushieda...
Could it be...
Is it possible?
Hey, Takasu-kun. Can't we get out through that window?
Where is he?! Where is he?!
Where is he?!
Look, Takasu-kun.
So you're in there!
There might be more to Kushieda's cheerfulness than her simply being bright and energetic.
Watch out!
I'm sorry, Kushieda! Are you oka-
Whoa, your nose is bleeding!
Oh, it'll be okay somewhat!
Somewhat?
A nosebleed is the perspiration of your heart.
That aside, we're almost there!
Keep stacking them boxes, Takasu!
Y-Yes, sir!
I see, she was beating up her weakness, wasn't she?
We're going to get out of here!
Yeah, of course! Fight!
Huh?
When I say fight, you say...?
I-In one?
Yeah yeah, that's it!
Fight!
I-In one!
Now that I think about it,
she's always been gleaming with cheerfulness.
Even when I had just met her too.
Fight!
Even now...
In one!
She's gleaming with joy!
Found you!
Taiga, how did you get in here?!
How? I used the ladder.
Yay! We can get out now, Takasu-kun!
But...
Thanks, Taiga!
This is truly the ladder to the future!
Um, Minorin...
You get up too, Takasu-kun!
O-Okay.
Like I've been trying to say!
The ladder fell when I came in...
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira soruto de
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
The Face Back Then
Sealed deep within my heart.
A precious memory
that we can never tell.
Oh, I told Takasu all about it.
Kitamu-!