Please teach me how to battle better.
Surprise. What prompted this?
I've been thinking about a lot of things, and I realized that I needed to get stronger.
Please take me on, Master!
Puzzling.
Please!
Refusal.
Preoccupied. I do not have an abundance of time to spend on others.
I'm fine with whenever you get the chance...
No.
Then what if I pay a lesson fee?
Um... have you heard of the sweet rice cakes they sell at Monjiya?
Favorite. That shop always has a line out the door.
I'll line up and buy it for you. How does that sound?
Consideration.
If you're able to succeed...
Thank you!
Premature. It's unwise to count your chickens before they hatch.
I guess you're right.
Born into memories everything is given life
born memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Pull me from this maze of fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Dive into memories, if only I could see you
dive memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurikaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Transformation
Pure White and Pitch Black
Your next two targets are both still fresh.
Who will you go at first?
Chinatsu-chan, pick whichever strikes your fancy.
Do your worst.
They're in your hands now.
Now then,
discern which among these synergy cards
would go best with your deck.
Well, how about...
If I use these, then the effect will be doubled.
Yes... that's called a combo.
You did well to discover that.
I got praised!
Let's end today's lesson here.
Okay. Thank you very much.
If you would.
Master, I present you with my lesson fee.
Gratitude.
I'm impressed you acquired this.
I was in line forever...
Plus I got the very last ones they had. That was a close one.
Your hard work is appreciated.
That said, this was originally your own idea.
Guess so.
It's yummy!
Doubt. There is something I would like to ask.
Sure, what is it?
Up until now, you have been reluctant to battle.
Is the reason you decided to
get stronger related to Chinatsu-san?
I could see in her eyes that Chii-chan was serious about trying to throw me away.
Doubt. Even if you get stronger,
so long as Chinatsu-san continues winning,
she'll throw away her memories regardless.
I know that. But that's exactly
why I want to get stronger.
I want to protect our memories.
Yet I...
I'll be counting on you tomorrow too!
Understood.
To protect their memories, she says.
How noble of her.
The piece of the puzzle I have lost...
I'm certain you won't tell me what it was.
Foolish to even ask.
Shirai?
Shirai, it's been a while.
What's with that reaction? You're making me feel bad.
Don't tell me you forgot who I am?
Well, I have gotten taller since then.
Hey, let's go home already.
What's wrong, Shou-chan?
So this is what it's like.
That's the boy from before.
Even though I knew I'd lose my memories,
I didn't really grasp what that meant.
You're going to hit another time limit soon.
And then another—
This picture here is from my soccer team
back home in elementary school.
We won the city tournament.
The team really relied on me.
And our coach...
Shou-chan?
I don't think I...
Hey, let's battle. Come on!
Shou-chan!
Battle?
That's right.
Master, I present you with cheese tarts from Momotae.
Much appreciated.
Delight. This could not have been easy to obtain.
I managed to put in a reservation,
but it was only for one.
Abundant. Thank you.
Well?
Yeah, we're close.
So? Is it good?
Would you like a bite?
Can I? Wait, I mean—
Needless restraint.
Besides, it's difficult to eat with you staring like that.
Oh, I brought tea too.
Gratitude. That was considerate.
Suzuko.
There's one nearby.
Yes, I can feel them too.
You two are Selectors, right?
Do you seek a battle with us?
Oh, no, that's not it.
Then what?
Huh?
Is he an acquaintance?
We've met once before.
Hey again.
Hello.
Is that yours?
Oh, this belongs to a friend.
Is that friend Morikawa Chinatsu?
You know Chii-chan?
Yeah, we went to middle school together.
I see.
But I don't get why you have that.
Huh?
Morikawa carried that around everywhere.
It looked like she really treasured it.
So she did.
Dad should be back from work on time this evening,
so you two can have dinner together.
I need to get to my job.
I don't need dinner.
Huh? Your shift starts now?
Yeah. It's a new job.
Huh? What happened to your old one?
I quit.
Oh.
So, what's this new job you've got?
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
We can talk when I get back.
Chinatsu, hold on—
I'm not doing anything you need to worry about.
Wow, that really happened?
If she thinks someone's wrong, she'll stand right up
to their face even if they're older or a teacher.
Yeah, I can totally see that.
She was like that when we were kids too.
Other people might mistake that for being stubborn,
but deep down, she's actually really kind.
Hunch. Did you perhaps have feelings for her?
Of course not!
Question. If not to battle, then what business could you have with me?
I presume you didn't come here simply to reminisce.
Yeah, I've got a request for you.
A request?
Want to partner up?
Explain yourself.
I don't intend to battle.
What do you mean?
You and I will be partners,
and we'll periodically battle.
If we trade wins and losses back and forth,
then neither of us will lose any coins.
That way, we can reach the end of this ninety day battle
while maintaining the same amount of coins.
So that's what you were thinking about.
Yeah.
Well? Think it's a good idea?
Refusal. I will have to decline your offer.
Why?
Just as you have a reason not to battle,
I have a reason why I must battle.
What is it?
I have no obligation to tell you.
Additionally, your plan has a hole.
Explanation. Even if you carefully
plan the outcome of each battle,
every time one person loses, a coin will turn black and they will lose a memory.
Implication. We cannot choose
which memories we lose.
Shou-chan.
Huh? Battle mediation?
Yes. If you make a contract with the Bookmaker, he'll find you an opponent whenever you want.
Isn't it difficult to find people to battle on your own?
I guess that's true.
If you'd like, we could have a battle right now.
What?
I'll lose to you on purpose
in exchange for you signing a contract.
You will?
Yes.
Open.
I can win!
Berserk.
Turn End.
This is it!
I win! Full attack!
I feel kind of bad that you threw the game for me.
Okay, I'd like you to sign the contract for me now.
Should I really?
You're not gonna come harassing me for money after this?
We would never.
Really? Isn't this too good to be true?
What?
I'm getting freaked out, so just forget it.
Wh-What are you doing?
Spare me the crap.
I've already sacrificed for this.
Don't even think about escaping.
We aren't playing a game here.
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
..henceforth
Party A
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Contract
Satomi Kou
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Aoki Yuu
Hey, you get that contract?
Yes.
That's my Chinatsu-chan!
Oh right, Rio-chan's doing quite well too.
Thank you for your time!
S-Sure. Thank you too, Rio-chan.
Whoa, we're facing such a tiny girl?
Onii-chan, no silly mercy this time, okay?
I know.
Talk is cheap...
Don't fuck up again when you remember your sister!
I'm the one who gets her ass kicked here!
R-Right.
Let's get started right away!
Open!
Uh, Open.
I have two coins left.
If I use one and lose, it's game over.
Quit mumbling to yourself and Grow me already!
Okay. Grow.
I place two Browcra SIGNI on the field.
Turn End!
Mama, Grow!
Let's do the usual!
I play two Ferma!
Turn End!
The usual... I wonder what.
Who cares, just attack! Nothing's gonna happen in the first turn.
R-Right. Aaya, Grow.
Full attack!
Oh goodness, that one hurt.
Mama, are you okay?
That was mean! Onii-chan's such a bully!
Ah, that's his trigger word.
It's Rio's turn! Mama, Grow!
Of course, Rio-chan.
I summon Minu and Plus!
And I'll bet a coin too, Mama.
Cunning.
Here I come, Onii-chan! Attack!
Huh?
Was that her ability?
Come on, Onii-chan! It's our turn!
Right. Grow!
And then atta-ta...
Hurry up and attack, you shitty siscon!
Mama, what's a "shitty siscon"?
Rio-chan, you don't need to learn words like that.
But just so you know, it's guys like him.
A-Atta-ta-ta...ck...
Yay! You fell for it, Onii-chan!
O-Onii-chan... and that innocent smile...
Thank you!
Rio-chan, well done. Aren't you glad we won?
Yeah! Let's keep on doing it, Mama.
Is this what you want? You're gonna disappear like your sister did!
Sure!
Do you understand that? Huh?!
Please just stop...
This is the wrong brand.
Didn't I tell you that before?
So you're not even fit to be a gopher, Sumida No. 2?
Sorry.
Go get the right ones.
Yes, right away!
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Here.
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
Contract
Satomi Kou
Aoki Yuu
..henceforth
Party A
Party B
You're as exceptional as I'd hoped.
It's too bad about the other day.
Your battle with Suzuko-chan.
I don't care.
It looks like she can't do anything by herself,
but she does have something special going for her.
What do you mean by that?
Well, who can say?
But it's clear that she's different from you.
Are you saying she's stronger than me?
I didn't go that far.
But really...
You called her the chains restraining you, but aren't you the one restraining yourself?
Not to mention how you begin to lose yourself
whenever you let your guard down.
Here's your next mark.
Additionally, your plan has a hole.
Every time one person loses, a coin will turn black and they will lose a memory.
We cannot choose which memories we lose.
Morikawa.
Why are you here?
I've been looking for you, Shirai-kun.
I'm glad I found you.
I realized something.
I thought that I'd still be myself even if I lost part of my memory...
But that was wrong. I can't accept it.
So I tried to figure out a way around it,
but it looks like I can't run away.
You have something you don't want to lose.
Well then, want to do it with me?
Can't I satisfy you?
Here.
Open.
Dona, Grow.
Shou-chan, can you fight?
Yeah.
I summon Karakasa. Turn End.
Mel, Enercharge and Grow.
Here I come!
Turn End.
What? Why?! He's going to attack!
What is she trying to do?
Don't you have a memory you don't want to lose?
I'll let you win.
A trap? But I can't sense anything like that.
Dona, Grow.
Why not attack?
Dona, attack.
Ow!
You really aren't going to attack?
No.
You're almost out of coins, Chii-chan!
Shirai-kun's memories are more important.
Turn End.
Are you sure?
Mel, Enercharge and Grow.
Turn End.
Is this really okay with you?
I already said I'd let you win.
Dona, Grow!
Oddity, Snowqueen!
I also play Nurari and activate her Layer effect. Attack!
Oh, too bad.
I got a Burst.
Dona!
This is wrong! She's not planning on losing!
Shou-chan, something's coming next turn!
You should use a coin!
It can't be... Morikawa.
Whose words will you trust?
Coin Bet.
Escape!
Turn End.
Grow.
I accessorize Steak with Teaksauce. Coin Bet.
Berserk.
Cancel... Escape.
Attack.
Arts: Dust Chute.
Dona!
Now your field is wide open.
Shou...chan...
You... from the very start...
Now you have only one coin remaining.
You're out of time.
Here.
What is this?
A contract with the Bookmaker.
You...
Are you really Morikawa?
I've finally become myself.
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
Someone pulls back their tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no ga
But I can no longer remember who
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
You've gotta have fun.
If I win, I want the pieces of the puzzle.
The old you would never do this!
It has nothing to do with you!
You cannot see into the darkness.
Because of you, because of you, Aaya...
Next time: Darkness / Longing and Loss.
Darkness
Longing and Loss