I got a lead on some big business at the Big Site!
I said as much,
But those people don't seem to understand the value of money!
"I'll make my fortune through doujin!"
Despite my audacity,
I haven't drawn anything outside of class...
By the way, look at this!
You, where'd you get that from?!
HEY!
Get back here!
Wait a second!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
I was surprised when you announced you were going to draw doujinshi, Najimi.
But, I was also happy.
Even though you're being motivated by money.
That said, reference data and other additional information are essential in drawing manga.
To begin with, shouldn't you look into what's popular?
Najimi?
N-No way!
I-uh...
Um...
This is all because you told me to read it!
And even though you're the one who drew it, I'm the one who looks like a deviant here...
Young lady...
You dropped some porn.
Why did you have to go and say that so everyone would hear?!
I didn't lie, did I?
Right, it's in the basement here.
Wait a second...
I've got to prepare myself...
Huh?
Wait- Tsuyuri!
Unbelievable!
To just go on ahead, even though it's my first time in a store like this!
What'll I do...
I don't feel confident going in all by myself...
Huh?
We're going up, so...
She definitely said it was the basement, didn't she...
Oh, so girls like those two usually come to places like this?
Even though I was kinda expecting a really strong perverted atmosphere...
Ah...  Father, Mother...
Najimi learned something today!
No matter what, you should never make a judgement based on prejudice alone!
TL Note: A lot of these are actual eroge - how many can you identify? Kimi ga Nozomu Eien and Muv-Luv are the easy ones.
I really shouldn't have said that!
Najimi?
What am I doing, getting all worried?
It's okay! It's okay, Najimi!
That's right, everyone comes here with something in mind!
There's no way there'd be anyone looking at me...
There is!  He's looking at me!
What?
...Nothing.
I was seen...
By a pretty cool guy, at that!
Well, he's a stranger after all.
There's no way there'd be anyone who knows me...
Oh, if it isn't Najimi.
God, you meanie!
Right.  Here's what I recommend.
Go buy it.
They sell this kind of thing...
It's selling well!
They sure don't beat around the bush.
Justice!
Sora!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What kept you so long?
Forgive me, Sora.
When you get older, we'll be able to go in together.
We're going to go buy some painting materials...
What about you two?
I'll come with you.
How about you, Najimi?
I'll go home.
I'm a little tired.
I see.  Then we'll part ways here.
See you.
Hurry home and enjoy your first adult game!
Don't call out to me like that!
But man, I'm nervous!
Even if it's data, needing to buy something this perverted...
If I were to run into a friend with this...
Najimi!
I just ran into one, didn't I...
And then?
I came here to buy a computer, but I had no idea which one would be the best!
I get it, I get it!
I get it, so let's hurry up and say goodbye, Tomoko!
Just today...
So what'd you buy, Najimi?
Why?
What do you mean, why?  You went shopping, right?
There!
Well, yeah!
Show me, show me!
Stop right there.
W-why?
Something bad'll happen.
O-okay.
That's right, I had something to do!
What?
..That!
Crab!
Crab?
My crab... uhh.. I have to go and walk my crab!
Walk?
Your crab?
...that's right.
Really?
I want to see it!
Denied!
Wait, Najimi!
Where're you going?
I have to pay?
No!  Please stop, Master!
If you put in something like that...
If you put red bean paste into the stew...
It's dissolving, it's dissolving!
Yes!
The bath's ready!
G-got it!
This won't work.
It's too dangerous!
I guess I've got to...
You want to come here?
Now?
That's acceptable.
If it's like this I can breathe easy!
At night, I won't run into my mother or my friends,
And at this speed they shouldn't be able to...
Okay, could you stop please?
So that's how it's going to be, huh...
Let me check you out.
Well, I guess I'm okay.
So long as he doesn't ask about this bag...
This bag, I wonder what's in it.
This is a total disaster!
Would you like to see?
Sorry, it's been pretty dangerous around here lately.
Could you open it for me?
No can do!
Wait a second, you there!
What am I doing?!
This is the worst choice I could possibly think of!
Sorry!
Stop right there!
You've got to be kidding me!
Why did it end up like this?
I haven't even done anything wrong!
Wait, that's right!
I haven't done anything wrong, have I?
All I've got to do is explain, right?
Why am I getting all worried about one policeman?
He called for reinforcements?!
Ahh, Father, Mother...
Najimi might be arrested at this rate...
At least come to my interrogation...
Send me sweet things in prison...
Why'd you run away?
I, uh...
There wasn't anything in it, was there?
I left it at home!
Huh?  Najimi?
Tomoko...
What happened?
I don't feel like talking about it right now...
Wha-
Najimi, don't tell me...!
It's okay.
That bad thing you imagined didn't happen...
Though in a way, it was worse than that.
Well then, be careful going home.
Right... I'm really sorry about what happened...
But if there wasn't anything in it, why did you run away?
The contents of that package...
Can only be seen by a special kind of people!
Najimi?
Oh, there you are!
You dropped this over there.
It probably fell out of your bag.
It's great that I was able to catch up with you!
Ah...  I guess this means I'm special!
Woohoo!
I'm a pretty big fan of this game myself, you know.
Father, Mother.
I'm going to drink today. I'm going to drink till I can't drink any more!
Alcohol's for after you're 20, kids!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
If you're watching anime, make your room bright and put some distance between yourself and the television.
Depending on the show, you should consider watching it in a different room from your family.