Time      15 hours    47 minutes
So the loser delivers the declaration of war to Class D.
Sign - War Declaration
That fine with you?
Just doing Rock-Paper-Scissors is boring.
How about we add a psychological angle?
Okay then, I'll use rock.
Then if you don't use rock, I'll kill you.
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Okay, you go then.
I wouldn't go if it killed me!
It'll be all right, Akihisa.
There are a lot of pretty-boy-lovers in Class D, so you won't get beaten up.
I see. Then I guess there's nothing to worry about.
But you're ugly.
How rude. All 365 degrees—
no matter what angle you look at me from, I'm a pretty-boy.
There are five extra degrees.
So you mean only five degrees of you, right?
Puny Young Man
I hate you all!
Declaration of War!
Then I'll leave it to you!
Time      16 hours   5 minutes
I'll never get married.
Time     10 hours 30 minutes
Fumizuki Academy
According to the documentation, this afternoon Second-year Class F and Class D
Principal's Office
Head of Second-year                                         Takahashi Youko
shall begin a Summoned Being Exam War.
That's good. I love persistent idiots.
Principal                              Toudou Kaoru
I'm not quite sure that they have a winning chance this time though.
About that...
What?
Class F's Sakamoto Yuuji.
His scores have continuously dropped with every scheduled exam.
What did you say?
They think they can beat Class D just like that?
They're really underestimating their opponents.
Do they think the Summoned Being Exam War is just a game?
No, Principal.
Please look at this.
Time       14 hours   35 minutes
Second-year                            Class F
Preparing
Pack up everything that'll get in the way,
Rep                          Sakamoto Yuuji
Preparing
or else it'll be hard to move around when the enemy attacks.
We'll be able to switch setups with Class D if we win.
Shimada Minami
We'll be saying goodbye to these fruit boxes too.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi
We'll finally be able to use normal classroom equipment.
Yoshi
Let's work hard, Himeji-san.
Definitely. We can do this, Yoshii-kun.
Himeji Mizuki
Surprised Akihisa
Love Letter
That... is the love letter that was supposed to go to Yuuji.
Misunderstanding
But Yuuji is with Kirishima-san now.
So it'd obviously be hard to hand out.
None of your business
I apologize. I don't have much to do if there are subtitles.
Second-year                          Class D
The stupid Class F declared war on us.
Rep                          Hiraga Genji
Their goal is this class's setup!
Let those idiots know they belong in that classroom.
We'll begin the strategy meeting now.
You're being way too serious, Yuuji.
We have Himeji-san, so it'll be a piece of cake.
Himeji has Class A's strength.
No, you guys are too naive.
Before, Class E didn't know about Himeji Mizuki, so they lost.
But they can't pull the same trick on us.
Class D is located at the end of the new school building,
while Class F is in the old school building.
The front lines are wide and their strength is easily spread out.
It's advantageous for us, who have higher scores.
If we let Himeji enter the battle field alone,
they'll ambush her.
We'd never be able to reach their Class Rep.
Then what should we do?
We'll employ blitzkrieg tactics.
The front wave will barrage the enemy lines
and break through the enemy's defenses.
And then Himeji.
Yes.
You need to head straight into enemy territory
and strike down Class D Rep Hiraga Genji.
Yes sir.
If we don't focus our fighting capacity, we won't win.
Screw defending.
This is total war!
Break through them instantly!
We'll take down their class rep before we have to surrender.
The best defense is a good offense!
They'll use all of their power in their offense,
so they won't be able to defend.
And Sakamoto Yuuji's score is one of the lowest.
If he isn't defended, then he'll fall in one strike.
Don't give them a spare moment.
Annihilate them!
Time      15 hours   30 minutes
And so it begins.
Start
Okay, it's started!
Akihisa, you'll be the captain. Go and command the front-lines.
Eh? Me?
Yes. You are crucial to this war.
I'll help you think up strategies that only Class F can perform,
and then you can go disrupt the enemy army.
I got it.
Snake?
I got beat up!
What? You're back.
I thought I was going to die!
Five people have already been sent to the supplementary classroom.
Ninja Pervert, give me the enemy army info.
Akihisa, how is the formation of the enemy?
This person, this person, and that person are on the front lines.
And then...?
Eh? Where are the boys' pictures?
I don't have those kinds of photos.
I see. A lot of them aren't very good at math.
Then do you want me to attack them head-on?
That was the plan from the start.
We already got the math teacher, Hasegawa-sensei.
What was my sacrifice for?
Sugawa, commence with the Special Mission.
Got it.
Time      15 hours   46 minutes
All members out!
The war begins!
War Begins
Hasegawa-sense, please!
Permission granted.
Summon!
I'm heading out!
I won't lose to Class D if we're doing math.
Watch this!
Those who are dead have to take supplementary classes!
Ah! It's Iron Man!
I don't want to go through the hellish supplementary class!
That's not reviewing; it's more like torture.
It is a magnificent educational class.
I'll properly raise you to love learning!
You'll become an ideal student who looks up to Ninomiya Kinjirou!
Prepare yourself!
All right, we've penetrated the front-lines.
Class F's Shimada has made it into the new building.
Great, use this opportunity!
Capture Hasegawa-sensei!
There's an ambush by the bathroom!
Hasegawa-sensei has been captured!
They planted a trap, eh?
Then Minami-chan...
The math summoning field!
Crap!
That's the teacher for Classic Literature, Takenaka-sensei.
I'll permit Classic Literature battle.
What the heck? That's my weakest subject.
Leave this to me!
Sugawa-kun!
Buy me some time!
Okay. Let's be tenacious, Minami!
But what should we do?
So Onee-sama was here after all.
Mi-Miharu?
Miharu doesn't want to be ordered around like a puppet.
But Miharu will still fight Onee-sama!
Summon!
Those in love are doomed to fight!
Miharu is Onee-sama's soul mate after all!
I can't do Classic Literature!
I'm here!
Kinoshita!
Announcement.
Math teacher Funakoshi-sensei, there's an emergency notice for you.
It's Sugawa-kun!
Funakoshi-sensei, Yoshii Akihisa-kun is waiting for you in front of Class D.
Math Teacher Funakoshi. 45 years old. Female. Single.
No longer of child-bearing age, she's the rumored old maid
who threatens students to go out with her using test scores.
Yoshii-kun wants to break the barrier between student and teacher.
He has something very important to tell you as a man.
Please proceed to Class D immediately.
Sugawa!
It's Funakoshi-sensei!
Captain Yoshii, you're amazing!
You're such a man!
Actually sacrificing yourself for the class!
Everyone, don't let his sacrifice go to waste!
Sugawa!
You're too naive, Hiraga.
I've long prepared a back-up math teacher.
Ninja Pervert, get rid of Takenaka-sensei now!
Yes sir.
Sensei, your wig is slanted.
Ah! I suddenly have something to do, so I'll be going now!
Now!
Funakoshi-sensei, I'll leave it to you!
I won't lose!
Enemy formation has been destroyed!
Go for it, Himeji!
Yes sir! Summoned Being, Summon!
But you're too slow!
Emergency.
What's wrong, Ninja Pervert?
Enemies detected via surveillance!
We're surrounded.
I found you, Sakamoto!
He has no protection! Now's the chance!
Take a chill pill.
I'll play with you guys.
Time      16 hours  18 minutes
I've underestimated you.
No wonder you were known as the child prodigy back then.
What the hell? Didn't you have crappy scores?
Isn't that information out-of-date?
Well, I suppose the stuff that Ninja Pervert leaked out didn't have the newest scores.
All right then, my turn!
W-Why?
Sorry.
I am invincible!
Time      16 hours    25 minutes
End of War
Class F victory
TL Note: They messed up the kanji for "Curse" and "Celebrate."
Curse!
We did it, Yoshii-kun!
I didn't think Yuuji would work hard and study.
This is nothing.
Our ultimate goal is Class A.
To achieve it,
we need to take out Class B first.
Class B? Nemoto-kun's class?
After the Recovery Exam is finished,
we'll go declare war on Class B.
So, Akihisa.
There's a mission that only you can do.
You got something to say?
You've fallen for this how many times now?
Screw you!
It sure is hilarious that Class F is coming here to declare war.
Let's make them cry a bit.
Is it all right, Kyouji?
Class F defeated both Class E and D, after all.
Yuuka, are you scared of Class F?
You kidding?
No matter how much they try,
there's no way they could beat us, Class C.
Then we of Class B definitely won't be beaten.
That's true, but...
There is a reason why they are winning.
So we have to avoid the danger of a frontal assault.
Kyouji.
Look closely. I'm no idiot.
I'll have them pay me back for before.
Sign - Temporary
And that's all the battle information.
I hope everybody does their best.
We will definitely win!
Well then, disperse!
Time      17 hours    28 minutes
Disperse
Sorry for the intrusion.
Are we really not exchanging setups with Class D?
Yep. We're spreading seeds for later.
Seeds?
Just wait until they bloom.
Time      17 hours    31 minutes
What the heck?
This is terrible. Who did this?
I'm afraid that it's probably Class B.
Breaking our supplies... Are they trying to obstruct us in taking the Recovery Exam?
They have no integrity.
Pitiful.
What's wrong, Himeji-san?
No, it's nothing.
Nemoto, you...
I will never forgive you.
Bear with it. Calm down.
But!
Winning the Summoned Being Exam War will be the best payback,
but if we lose our cool, then we won't win.
That's why they did this.
Time      14 hours    51 minutes
And so, Class F and Class B began their vengeful war.
Next Day
War Begins
Battle begins!
Hit them with all you've got!
Everyone, charge!
They're coming!
What a bunch of idiots.
Proceed with the plan.
They don't have a snowball's chance in hell.
Charge!
Damn it, the difference in strength is just too great.
So we're not enough for this after all!
As expected of Class B.
Yoshii-kun!
Himeji-san, isn't it not your turn yet?
Sakamoto-kun said to use this in case of emergencies.
Yuuji did...
This is... Okay!
Everybody, listen up.
Class B Rep Nemoto has a girlfriend.
What?
It's the Class C Rep, Koyama Yuuka-san!
What?!
And I've heard that she's been making bento for him.
When the irrational fire of fury charges at the clouds,
the Esoteric Inquisition, the FFF group, will disregard the hellish supplementary class
and become heartless agents of death.
Unforgivable!
Sign - Esoteric Inquisition
How dare he enjoy such joyful times by himself!
Do you guys know the pain of being single?
Are these guys crazy?
This is too dangerous! Defend!
The fat lady is warming up!
Charge!
What's with these guys?
Are they not afraid of supplementary classes?
What's wrong?
Class F suddenly went mad!
A lot of us have been affected.
About time I use the insurance.
Time      15 hours    21 minutes
All those that are dead attend supplementary class!
Sugawa-kun, I won't let your sacrifice go to waste.
My anger seems to have calmed down a bit because of it.
So he's still pissed over the thing with Funakoshi-sensei.
Our numbers have decreased.
Let's reorganize our formation.
Those who have lost points, go take the Recovery Exam immediately.
Ah. Himeji-san!
That is... Nemoto-kun.
Why did you destroy our classroom setup?
Do you have proof that we did it?
That...
Well, we did do it.
There's some proof for you.
I won't forgive you!
Summoned Being—
Oh? That was close.
The perpetrator showing evidence of his own accord.
Very nice, right?
What...
It was an unexpected harvest.
Writing a love letter, even in these times... How cute.
Please give it back!
What is written in here?
Or should I keep it as entertainment for later?
People like you are...
Even if I didn't do this, we'd still win.
It was just insurance.
I'll give it back to you once this is over.
But only if I haven't changed my mind.
What's wrong, Akihisa? You didn't run away, did you?
Be careful, or I'll stab you with scissors.
Yuuji, I have something to say.
What?
I request that you take Himeji-san off the battlefield.
Did something happen?
I can't tell you the reason.
Then I guess we'll do what you want.
But you'll have to do the mission that Himeji was suppose to complete.
I got it.
To strike the enemy base.
Do it however you want.
Is that okay?
I'll try.
No.
I'll show you.
Good answer, Akihisa.
Time      16 hours    28 minutes
Also, Yuuji.
What?
Time      16 hours    29 minutes
Akihisa, are you really doing this?
This is the only way that I can attack Class B with my ability.
But you don't have permission to summon, right?
Don't worry. I have this.
Awaken!
Go!
This level of...
What's happening?
I'm not done yet!
You all right, Akihisa?
This is nothing.
No matter what happens, I have to complete this mission!
No matter what...
This is for Himeji-san as well!
I found him!
You think I would have no protection at all?
Your surprise attack failed.
Got you.
Ninja Pervert!
Commencing Physical Education and Health battle! Summon!
I-Impossible.
With the teacher?
In charge of supplementary classes, Iron Man Nishimura, not only can permit battles for all subjects
but is also very athletic.
Seriously...
War is over!
Winner, Class F!
What a pity, Nemoto.
Sakamoto.
Class B, I have a proposal.
Normally, Class B's setup would be exchanged with our fruit boxes,
Sign - Left: Idiots
Right: Reserve Army
but if you agree to my deal,
we'll let that go.
Deal?
Nemoto.
If you follow any of my orders while wearing this,
I won't exchange setups with you guys.
What? You kidding me?
I refuse to do such a stupid thing.
Class B as a whole accepts the deal!
Got it! Leave it to us!
We'll do our best to make him wear it!
Hey, you guys! I am not wearing that...
This... Stop! Stop!
Is this good enough, Akihisa?
No need to take off my underwear!
Himeji-san, here! This.
Thank you, Yoshii-kun!
This is great.
Um, Himeji-san...
Is that letter...
Yes, it's the chain letter from back then.
I still haven't been able to hand this letter out
and thus have given everyone a lot of trouble.
Himeji-san!
Although this letter has a lot of bad memories,
it has many joyful ones.
That alone is enough.
I feel that I shouldn't continue to rely on this letter.
I want to express my feelings through my own voice.
If I had to do it now, I couldn't.
But there's something that even I can say at the moment.
Yoshii-kun.
What is it, Himeji-san?
Can I call you Akihisa-kun?
Eh. Um... The FFF group would do some horrifying things to me...
Is it okay, Akihisa-kun?
Yeah.
Yuuji, why are you so persistent with the Summoned Being Exam War?
Do you want the setups?
I have no interest in tables.
I just want to prove that, in this world, academics isn't everything.
So, Shouko,
don't hold back.
I got it. I'll fight with all I've got.
The twelfth question. What is the name for the last scene in stories such as novels and plays that ends well?
Final Boss Battle!
You don't have enough experience points.
Next week:  Love, Courage, and Our Battle Has Only Begun!
This will be on the test.