The sport for the competition will be...
A 50 metre freestyle, one-off swimming match, as proposed by Kawashima-san!
Lucky me!
What did you write?
Vale
Tudo
If I win, I'm going to put the movie of
your imitation on display, for all to see.
If I win, Takasu-kun's spending his entire summer with me at my vacation home.
You'll be all alone for the entire summer.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
For whose sake?
If you know the answer, come up and write it on the blackboard.
I will.
Just what I'd expect from the class representative.
Oh sh-
Hey.
Idiot.
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge
Kushieda when sending
this around
Everyone in 2-C
must read this!
Exclude Ami-
tan, Taiga
First round of the Takasu Cup commencing?
Ami-tan vs the Palmtop Tiger. 500 Tirols per bet.
What the hell is this?
Will this even be a competition?
Of course Ami-tan will win at swimming! Taiga just sank, remember?
I want to be fought over as well!
What should I do?
Damn, these guys...
Ami's mine, sorry arl.
Were you trying to write "all"?
Isn't that kinda screwed up that you can't write 'all'?
>Haruta
You cheated your way into this school, didn't you? >Haruta
Isn't that kinda screwed up that you can't write 'all'?
Haruta, you...
I mean, everyone's writing all kinds of crap!
What?!
3000 Tirols!
Takasu Ryuuji
W-What's wrong, Aisaka?
If you've solved it, I'd like to see you go up and answer it...
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid, Taiga!
Dip your face under as if you're washing it!
Now, once more!
Even if you say that...
She can't even dip her face in the water?
Isn't she a little out of her depth?
I can already see how this fight is going to go...
I told you to ignore the crowd.
I know!
Well, she has to try hard for Takasu's sake too.
Who has to...!?
Did someone do something?
Kitamura-ku-
Keep working together with Takasu, and try your best!
Huh, what? Together...?
Hey! Taiga!
I absolutely will not practise during class any more.
Just doing imaginary training is enough!
Say that after you're able to dip your face into the water.
What are today's side-dishes?
Peas bound in eggs, tofu steak, and miso soup.
Also, there's spinach and deep-fried-
It's always something with beans. I want meat!
Don't be so picky.
Beans are the meat of the field.
Cheapskate.
That aside, make sure you practise properly during swimming class.
Loosen up.
I can't loosen up.
Kitamura-kun's watching, after all...
Because he's watching, you have to try your best, right?
Now, look here...
Whose fault is it to begin with that I'm working so hard,
despite the fact that everyone is misunderstanding?
Huh? "Whose?"
Well, it's to keep Kitamura from going to Kawashima's vacation home-
Ow!
Whatever. All you need to do is make my food.
Sheesh, what now?
Hey, come on and make it already.
I'm going to take in tons of nutrition and practise like crazy.
The rain's not stopping...
No pool classes today, either, I guess...
Just when I can finally dip my face into water...
Why can't we use the pool?!
Don't take it out on me.
Tickets for the public pool?
Use them.
I'm betting on Aisaka too.
Takasu went really overboard with how he was cheering for Aisaka on the piece of paper that was being sent around,
so I figured, "All right, I'm going to root for her too!"
F-For me?
Yeah!
W-Why? I can't even swim...
Aisaka is the type that shows her true strength in moments of desperation.
We don't know how this fight will go just yet!
Can't I make it like this?
W-What are you doing?!
S-Shut up!
Good luck with the practising.
Aw, man...
Idiot.
Hey, want to stop by somewhere on the way home?
How about Sudoba?
Good idea.
What the...? Why are you sitting cramped in between those?
Gloomy weirdo.
This cramped feeling calms me down.
Here we go...
My gosh! Takasu-kun's worn out as well?
Yeah, I've been like this for a while
now because of a certain someone.
Huh? Because of who? Ami-chan doesn't know!
Why, you...
The jealous Taiga is cute...
What? How is she jealous?
She simply doesn't like you.
Is Takasu-kun an idiot?
You're the idiot.
Either way, don't provoke Taiga so much.
I mean, what's with the vacation house?
You don't intend to invite me, either way.
I was serious, you know.
I'm seriously intending to win and spend the summer with Takasu-kun.
I'm really thinking about what to do after I win.
I think it'll be fun!
See, we're rather compatible, right?
N-No, we're not.
He's mad!
Why you...
Sheesh.
Keep your mocking mild, okay?
All right.
Farewell, then.
I know.
H-Huh? Know what? What do you know?
That the one who super-sized Taiga's swimsuit was...
...you!
Huh? Um, that was...
Tsk, tsk.
You don't need to hide it. It was elementary, my dear Akechi-kun.
You see, Taiga was telling me before,
"Ryuuji is always there to help."
Huh?
Cleaning, fixing buttons, ironing clothes...
Oh, that? Doing those little things...
Doing those small things is what makes it great.
Huh?
Hey, Kushie-
I believe in you, and so I'm leaving Taiga in your care.
Y-Yeah.
I'm the referee, so I can't really help you out, but...
...we're rooting for the same person!
Leave it to me!
All right.
Please, take care of tomorrow's rain.
Thank you, Teru Teru Bozu-san.
The weather seems to be holding out, but...
Look, Ryuuji. It's like I'm swimming, right?
It's about time we did some proper practice.
Man, what is this?
The match is tomorrow, you know!
What good will it do to practise the crawl stroke now?
We've got to make do with what we can!
This looks so dumb.
Yes, keep that up! Oh, try kicking your feet now.
Fine!
Huh? Hey!
T-Taiga!
That was awesome, Taiga!
Your kicking power is out of this world!
You might be able to win with this!
Win? Me?
I was just doing it like I usually do...
Well, you can't let your guard down, but-
I see.
I can win. I see.
Taiga?
Yes. I'm going to win.
Yeah! Keep that spirit up!
It doesn't seem like this will stop for a while.
And just when you finally wanted to try...
What do you want to do? Go home?
You want to keep going?
I see.
I guess we should.
We can't let Kitamura's kindness in giving us the tickets go to waste.
It's not about that!
It's not that...
The reason I'm trying so hard is-
I know, I know.
While we're at it, we'll leave that Kawashima utterly speechless.
Enough already. No matter what I say, it's pointless.
Huh? What now?
Wait, could it be about me?
Right, there won't be any food if I go away, after all.
I told you it's not about th-
But, you don't have to push yourself.
Even if you lose, it'll be settled if I go
alone to Kawashima's vacation home.
I'll ask her to leave Kitamura out of it.
I can make heaps of food and put it in the fridge,
so don't worry about unnecessary things and-
So you've finally revealed yourself?
Huh?
You wanted to go from the beginning, right?
To Ami-chan's vacation home!
Huh? What's up with that?
Well, it's none of my business where,
when, or who you pant over, or whatever.
What's your problem?!
I'm trying to look out for you!
Who asked you to do that?!
You've been really weird lately!
First with that thing with Kawashima-
Are you still thinking about that?!
What is it that you're so angry about?!
"What", you ask?
I can't stand it when someone's going off on their own,
thinking they know what's going on inside me, and acting like they understand me!
I just can't stand that!
It pisses me off!
Why won't you understand that?!
Which is it, do you want to be understood or not?
I don't know!
What?
Nobody should be able to understand how I feel.
I mean... I mean...
Even I don't know...
Huh? What?
What did you just say? Hey!
I said that I'll do what you want and not attend the competition.
It itches.
It's not my fault, right?
Huh?
Ryuu-chan?
Why is Ryuu-chan awake?
I'm home!
Didn't Taiga-chan come over?
Why? Did you two have a fight?
Taiga said she doesn't give a damn about me any more,
and pissed me off... I think.
I see.
But Ryuu-chan knows, right?
That Taiga-chan's always like that,
contradicting what she actually means.
No, it's not like she doesn't give a damn any more.
If she really hated Ryuu-chan, no matter how hungry she was,
she wouldn't eat from the same plate as you.
At least, that's what Ya-chan thinks...
Sheesh, without even removing her make-up.
Come on, pull yourself together.
You haven't eaten anything, right?
I really wanted it to be sunny, and then...
...I hoped you would seriously put up a fight today.
You see...
No matter what you think, I...
...want you to win...
Win? I...
The lunch box is innocent, so I'll be taking it with me.
But...
It was raining so much that my usual swimsuit didn't dry.
But I hope this doesn't break any school rules.
I'm getting worried.
That beautiful Ami-tan's about to swim in this pool, right?
So she can take Takasu to her vacation home, right?
Why is it always Takasu? Why?
Ow!
Why? Why? Why? Why is it always Takasu?
Quit it, you two!
It hasn't even been decided that I'm going to the vacation home yet!
As if that Tiger can win-
You don't know that until she tries!
Until she tries,
you can't be sure.
That idiot. This time it's only meat.
Hey, hey!
How long are you going to keep us waiting?
It's hot, you know!
Why isn't the Palmtop Tiger coming out?
Who cares?
Just pretend that you only came here to look at that bikini.
You're right.
Hey, we shouldn't make everyone wait this heat any longer...
What's this nonsense you're blabbering on about?
Come, let's fight this out fair and square.
Stupid Chihuahua, now re-dubbed Stupid Bikini!
Oh, yeah!
Taiga!
You're going to swim with that on?!
I thought she had armour on for a moment.
That's kinda cool.
Well then, the 50 metre freestyle, one-off swimming match!
On your marks!
Get set!
Whoa.
Hair's showing.
What?!
Cra-
I can't believe it! I can't believe it!
Whoa, now!
The Palmtop Tiger used a delayed entrance strategy coupled with dangerous psychological tactics!
Damn you, mini-tiger!
Taiga!
Oh? An accident has occurred for the tiger?
This is a golden opportunity for Ami-tan!
Damn it!
Are you okay? Did your leg cramp?
Idiot, let me go!
I can still go-!
You can't go on like this!
I'm going!
But you-!
Aren't you happy?!
Wha-?
Don't "wha" me!
Your master's working hard for your sake!
Be more happy about it, you dumbass dog!
Keep it up, Ami-chan!
The tides have turned!
All right, then! Go now!
I'll wag my tail or something for you!
And with that...
Ami-tan!
Don't push!
You idiot, that's dangerous!
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Taiga?
Takasu! Hey, Takasu! Are you all right?!
Okay, he's breathing! Aisaka, take him to the infirmary quickly!
Don't touch him!
Taiga?
But, Aisaka-
Shut up!
You're all idiots!
Why didn't you notice?
Why didn't you help him?
You all had your attention focused on the stupid bikini...
Nobody was helping Ryuuji...
Ryuuji is mine!
Nobody else touch him!
Um, you see,
I decided to come along to your vacation home too.
What?!
I lost the competition, right?
And Ryuuji's going, right?
I won't have anyone to tend to my daily needs, see?
That's why I've decided to co-
Wait a minute.
Ami-chan's getting confused by your incredibly selfish speech.
Why not bring her? The more the merrier.
Ah, I see.
Could it be that Aisaka-san's worried
about being separated from Takasu-kun?
After all, didn't you declare "Ryuuji is mine!"?
You're right, I'll admit it.
Because, I mean...
That is, in other words...
This guy's my dog, you see.
As his owner, I have to take responsibility for him.
I have to watch him so that he doesn't
get all excited in other people's places.
What? Were you expecting something else?
Not a thing. Nothing at all.
All right. Let's decide on a schedule, then.
Let me see!
You see, around this time, I am packed with my part-time jobs,
and around there I'm very busy with club activities.
Too bad we couldn't be all alone,
but there will be more opportunities.
What?
And that was how the first semester of Takasu Ryuuji's second year of high school ended,
and a "stimulating" summer break was about to begin.
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
You, who are going to the sea?
Going with Kushieda
to a vacation home...
I might be punished for achieving
this happiness, Taiga!
Kitamura-kun's thin,
hazy, black seaweed...
What?