I did it, Master Tomoka.
M-Mimi-chan, it's embarrassing when you call me that.
I won't let you pass, Nee-sama!
Oh!
I won't lose, either.
Everyone's doing well.
Yeah, it'd be perfect if we can get ten.
We're still missing those three, huh?
Hey, you know...
Since you both lost, why don't you just join the Basketball Club's practice?
Forget about it!
This is our problem!
Shut up, Nii-tan!
Can you two beat all of the others by yourselves?
N-No way.
You're all too weak.
Even if you tried ten thousand times, you two still wouldn't be able to defeat me.
Later.
We couldn't do anything.
We'll get our revenge, definitely!
Yeah.
A new menu for the S-Grade Gourmet Fair?
Yep.
We've decided to enter the Suzuran Shopping Street's contest.
We'll think up the menu ourselves!
Sounds fun!
Oh!
I'll think, too!
I'm sure we'll make a delicious menu when we pool our ideas together!
Yep!
Okay! Let's meet up at Saki's house then!
Oh!
They should all be getting here...
Why aren't you coming to practice?
That's for me to decide.
I only play basketball to beat you, Saki.
But you can't play basketball all by yourself.
Stop being so hard on yourself.
It's always like this!
We're only one year apart!
Stop acting like an older sister!
Masami...
I won't lose next time!
In basketball or in anything else!
The S-Grade Gourmet Fair, too!
I'll be helping out at Sushi Fuji this year.
Sushi Fuji vs Nagatsuka:
A duel between me and you!
Can all of you help me out?
The 6th graders are helping out at Nagatsuka.
This is a great chance to get our revenge!
But we want to get revenge on that girl first, rather than Maho.
That girl?
She's really good at basketball and she pisses us off!
But seeing a gloating Maho is pretty bad, too.
Tsuba, let's team up with Masami for now and beat Maho to a pulp!
Got it!
Thank you!
That means...
I'm sorry, Masami. I can't fight with Nee-san anymore.
I cannot betray my master.
Hey!
Mimi, Gettan, whose side are you on?
Let's decide with a vote!
Who wants to help out Masami?
Here!
That's it!
That's no fair!
Tyranny of the majority!
Will you help us out, Aoi-san?
Of course.
But before that...
If it's about going to the Basketball Club's practice, then I refuse.
We did join the club, but we get to decide whether we want to practice together with them.
I see. That's just how it is, eh?
Putting that aside...
We've been thinking.
You're only in high school, but those are magnificent.
Yeah! That's my Masami!
We all yearn for that size!
S-Stop it!
Eh? It's harder than I thought.
Isn't that because of her brassiere?
Brassiere?
Nee-sama is going to get one soon.
Stop it! If you keep on rubbing them...
I'm home!
Do we have guests over?
Oh, Nii-tan!
We're rubbing Aoi-san's breasts right now, why don't you join in?
I'm fine.
Hey! Are you idiots?!
Stop doing weird things!
Natsuhi-kun! Stop! Don't come in right now!
Oh! Nii-tan, welcome!
Natsuhi-kun? Natsuhi-kun!
We've got the cabbage and the eggs!
Cabbage!
Oh!
Shrimp, shrimp, shrimp...
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Stop that, Hina!
Got it, everyone?
Nagatsuka's going down! Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Hey!
Good.
Thanks, Father.
It's just not Sushi Fuji's fried tofu unless you make it.
Hey, can we beat Saki?
I'm only one year younger than her, but she can do anything.
She's popular, too...
She's amazing...
But...
That's why I don't want to lose. It's because she's amazing.
I...
Thank you, Father.
I didn't expect us to be right next to each other.
We'll see who sells the most, Saki!
It's a duel! A duel!
Jeez, you're all so stupid.
I'm sorry, they just won't listen to me.
Don't worry about it.
We do our thing, they do theirs. It's all good.
We just want our customers to be satisfied, right?
Right.
Thanks, everyone.
Please wait here to enter!
H-How is it?
It's good! It's perfect!
I knew it! We were gonna make something awesome!
Hmph! Ours is better!
Look!
Oh! So cute!
Yeah! That looks nice!
How's our Five-Faced Inari?
The fried tofu and the rice were all made by my father!
Wow!
This will be popular to both adults and kids!
Now's your only chance to relax.
We'll lure all of the customers and leave you empty!
Jeez.
She just yaps on and on about her sushi.
The Suzuran Shopping Street S-Grade Gourmet Fair will now begin!
I-I'm getting nervous.
Yeah, I want to sell at least one first.
Eh? I found a pair of twins who I recognize!
It's you!
From back then...
"You?"
Kinda cocky for a pair of losers.
But I guess I never told you my name.
You two were just too weak, so I never got the chance to.
Don't make those scary faces.
My name is Ashihara Rena.
I'm a 5th grader at Suzuridani Girls' Academy.
Nice to meet you.
Suzuridani?
Hey, is she the one?
Yes, the one we need to get revenge on!
Revenge?
What talk!
You two lost so badly last time.
Order something already.
We're busy now.
Hey! Stop lecturing me already!
I don't like it.
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Losers!
Hey, hey, hey!
And then...
I'm sorry.
Hey! What are you doing?
You made me drop my lollipop!
Wow, my bad.
But what a nice shot.
Stop fooling around!
My father made this fried tofu... And now...
Masami-chan, calm down!
That was an accident!
Yes, yes, an accident.
It can't be helped.
Oh, shut up!
Apologize to Masami!
Even if it was an accident, you should be more considerate!
Can't you see that Masami's sad?
Oh, what's this?
What a pain.
I don't know anything! It wasn't my fault!
Later!
Wait!
We can't serve this anymore.
My father spent so many hours on that...
We thought about this together...
Stand up, Masami!
Saki...
What do you want?
I know how you feel, but this isn't the time to feel down.
We need to make food for our customers.
You are the poster girl for Fuji Sushi, right?
But the fried tofu...
You still have the mixed sushi rice, right? Then everything's fine.
Sushi Fuji's mixed sushi rice is the best! Of course it'll sell.
And who knows that the best?
But we only have the rice...
You're right.
Hey, can all of you come over here?
What is it?
Need our help?
Yep, we need your ideas.
How can we use this mixed sushi rice to make an S-Grade gourmet?
Oh!
Food again? I'll think hard!
We can only use what we have, then.
We have eggs, shrimp, vegetable...
Hey, wait! That's for your store, right?
Stop this! Don't do this!
We aren't doing this for your sake.
Then why?
We're doing this for the customers of Sushi Fuji.
We can't make inari sushi anymore, but let's all think about something else.
Something new using the mixed sushi rice.
But what about your okonomiyaki?
We've already learned a lot by thinking about it together.
It's not important whether we sell a lot or not.
Right, everyone?
Yep!
Oh!
We can make it anytime!
We need to use the sushi rice in an authentic way...
It's easier to eat if we wrap it up like inari sushi.
How about rice balls?
But that may not look authentic anymore.
Isn't there a nice idea somewhere?
Using rice!
Stop being an idiot and think properly.
Rice? Baka?
Rice baka?
Rice burger?
Rice burger! Hina, that may work!
Nee-sama, that looks great.
I'm done!
Nagatsuka and Sushi Fuji's special collaboration menu will be on sale soon!
Please try us out!
Please!
Welcome!
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
Do your best.
Thank you very much!
Please have a look!
Seems like they're fine now.
Yeah.
Oh! The scrubbing feels so nice!
Scrub! Scrub!
Go!
Back at ya!
Saki...
Um... today...
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I guess we'll come to the Basketball Club's practice tomorrow.
Us, too?
Yeah.
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two...
We finally got all ten.
But it'll take some time for them to be a team.
Well, just getting them to come to practice is a huge step forward.
What's with you all of a sudden?
What are you saying?
I even brought you this super important letter.
Super important?
Miho-nee, this is...
Gather around, everyone!
Um, Subaru-san?
Keishin Academy Girls' Basketball Club has now officially entered the regional tournament.
So that means...
We can take part in the tournament?
Yes.
And our first round opponent will be...
Suzuridani Girls Academy!
Suzuridani... Ashihara Rena!
This is a wonderful chance.
We can get our revenge.
Masami, you two, and us.
Okay! Let's start practicing!
Let's do it, everyone!
Oh!
That Rena pisses me off!
We'll beat her to a pulp!
We must win our match against Suzuridani!
We need to have the 6th graders teach us a lot.
I'll steal my master's skill!
Let's do our best, everyone!