And that's our tentative program.
Understood.
The mission starts-
Are you going out, Kana-chan?
Good morning!
She must be going off to spend her first salary.
Not all of it.
I'll be sending some back home, and I thought of sending a present along with it, and...
A reward for yourself, right?
Yep!
You were just a trainee for the first month, and didn't get paid, right?
Isn't it nice?
Yeah.
But I was really surprised.
I heard that it was common for the salary to be delayed.
And it's normally paid in military scrip.
Here. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much!
I never thought that I would actually get paid.
Of course!
Because for that, our unit has a side-
Kanata... err... well...
There's a market in town today!
It's your first time seeing one, right?
Your first salary and first day off.
It's a variety of 'firsts' for Kana-chan, right?
Leave the job behind, and enjoy yourself thoroughly.
Okay!
Kanata's Day Off - Hair Braiding
Then, off I go!
I told you not to spill that to Kanata, didn't I?
But, if she were to just use common sense...
In such a remote region as this, not to mention the delay, they wouldn't even send salary, right?
And yet, Kanata believed it so easily.
Honesty is one of Kana-chan's better traits.
Yeah.
She wanted to start spending her money almost immediately.
Unlike the two of you, huh?
That's true!
Well then...
...shall we forget our main jobs too?
It's quite good.
Isn't it?
But, there is a problem.
There will be no further discounts.
I'm sorry. I was in a daze, and...
Looks like you're ready.
Yeah.
No problems at all.
But, a problem has just come up.
Regarding that, I do have a suggestion.
Will you take it?
Could you please tell us the details?
Yeah.
This is cute, too!
Are you guys...
...the sellers of these things?
I take it that they are to your liking?
Not too bad.
But...
...there's a slight problem.
Oh, what would that be?
With so few goods,
it'll be more work than it's worth just to sell them.
When I think of it that way, it doesn't really cover my expenses...
Therefore-
It's not my policy to give discounts.
The worth is in its flavor.
I won't say that I have lost...
I'll take them all!
Don't even try!
If you're gonna shoot, then shoot.
But, before you can do that, I'll be blowing the smoke off this.
The next hole will be through you, not your hat.
If that's the case...
Such a foolish man.
This is what you get for belittling us.
Sleep well, dear boys.
That was why I warned you.
Hey,
are you guys with them?
Th-The car!
Boss!
Give it up!
But, the souvenirs for the Big Boss-
Leave them, our lives come first!
Boss!
I never heard they were this dangerous!
I'll never return to this town again!
They left.
I see.
Well then, it's fine now, everyone!
Man, that was frightening.
Looks like we deceived them.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Not at all. Now that we've overtaken the mafia from central, our business will boom.
We give and take, right?
You'll be compensating us for this little act, won't you?
Oh my, Mikhail-san does love to joke.
No, not at all.
I wasn't joking at all!
This is a world of business, isn't it?
Shall I take that debt?
Were you the ones who crushed their car back there?
Wasn't it you?
What happened?
Well,
somebody seems to have crushed their car.
Inside it,
there are several spoils of war in mint condition, bought from the market.
I'll sell them off, and split the profits equally with you.
That concludes our business here.
Alright.
The farce is finally over...
But, I was surprised.
By what?
You were really getting in to it, Rio-senpai.
That moonshine,
if we're discovered, we won't get away with just a court martial.
We've infringed on the monopoly and tax law.
We'll probably be charged with treason.
That's right.
This may be a side-job that we've inherited from our senpai,
but Rio has never once opposed it.
I was quite surprised too.
Well, I was surprised at first.
But, when I learned that the calvados that my mother loved were made in the fortress...
Then, it may have been your mother's guidance that brought you to this unit.
Then, off I go!
Yumina onee-chan!
It's done. Look!
It looks wonderful, Seiya-san!
Mishio-san,
today is the day for first visits.
The priest will be present too.
So, at least for today-
No!
Don't trouble onee-chan, Mishio!
It's fine to fix your hair, isn't it?
No!
Definitely not!
Why?
You're always fussing about fixing it!
Shut up, Seiya!
You mustn't do that, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10 yen 25 sen
10 yen, 25 sen...
Hey girl, that was dangerous!
S-Sorry, I was in a daze...
They are a problem.
Somehow, they got wind of the deal.
Are you okay?
Yes.
More importantly, Naomi-san!
What should I do?!
This is the first time I've had money in my wallet to buy it.
If I said, "I'll take this now, please", I could buy it, right...?
Hey, if someone snatched up that dolphin, what would you do?
Did someone say they wanted it?!
Well, no. That was merely an example.
I see...
Well, I would...
I'd tell them that dolphins are scary animals that eat humans, and make them give up on it!
You're a genius!
For that, I'll hold that dolphin until you change your mind. So, rest assured.
Then, I'll just get presents for everyone first.
Well... father, mother, grandpa and grandma...
...and grandpa and grandma in Waren... great grandma.
Oh, and Granny Nanae who lives next door, too.
Amazing. They're selling so many different things!
Like this.
I'm sorry...
Mishio-chan...
Are you shopping for something?
She's looking for something like a box.
A box?
Have you seen anything like this?
Sorry.
If you're looking for it, want me to help?
What are you doing, Kanata?
I'm here to buy presents.
I thought of finding something lovely to send to my family back home.
But, I'm not in a hurry, so-
I don't need help!
What's the matter with Mishio-chan...?
T-this is a bit too...
That's a lovely shirt, isn't it?
TL Note: 夜露死苦 - Yoroshiku. Normally means "best regards, please take care of me." But this is written in ateji. It should be read as "slang". Like- Wassup!
This is cute, too.
Yumina-san?
Kanata-san.
Did you happen to see Mishio-san?
A box?
Yes. She said it was something precious.
I see.
When her mother passed away, all of their household belongings were taken.
It was apparently a memento from her mother that was taken.
Every time there's a market in town, she thinks she might find it...
I said something terrible.
I received a salary for the first time yesterday.
And I said I was sending things back to my family.
That is fine.
Now I... we are Mishio-san's family.
If she is still envious after all that, then...
...it must be due to my imperfection.
Hey, Mama. Which is more important, me or your treasure box?
You are!
Mama...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
These are Treize's famous firecrackers.
They make a powerful sound!
How about some?
Onee-chan...
Yumina onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
Mishio-chan!
The car!
I'm sorry that I'm not Yumina-san.
Onee-chan.
Yumina onee-chan!
Thanks.
Good work.
Now then...
Excuse me...
O-Oh! What's the matter?
Could... that car...
...be yours, Naomi-san?
That was you two?!
I'm sorry! Um...
There's 150 yen in here.
Compensation...
Well done, you two.
Treasure that money, okay?
I got my payment already.
N-Naomi-san... that!
美穂 - beautiful rice
If you carve that on to her seal,
like fields of abundant rice, her life should filled with happiness too.
My...
Miho, it's great that you've received such a fine name.
Did you find Mishio-san?
I was prepared to be her family and heal her heart, but...
I am still inexperienced.
No, you are doing your best.
Mishio-san!
I'm so glad you found it!
Take good care of it.
It's an irreplaceable memory of your mother-
That's not it!
Here,
I want you to have it, Yumina.
Mishio-san was taken in by the church when she lost her family.
First, her father was drafted in the army, and never returned...
What about her mother?
Mishio-san's family lived on the eastern state border, in the Vingt area.
You can't mean...
Yes.
The town that was attacked by the "invisible death reaper".
And when the both of them arrived at Seize,
her mother had already become ill, and soon after...
Mama told me...
...that she can't fix my hair anymore and she's sorry.
And then... and...
from now on, let the person who treats me most preciously braid it for me.
Yumina, braid my hair.
Humans live on...
Even if we part with those we hold dear...
...and suffer excruciatingly...
Even then, we live on.
We can live on.
That strength is extremely sad, and endearing.
I'm sorry.
Thank you...
...Onee-chan.
Everyone's already in there.
Okay. I'll go soon.
You've had a hard day.
Yeah.
I wanted to avoid washing my hair if I could.
But, things happen, huh.
Yes, yes, yes! Then, senpai,
please let me dry your hair off!
I've always wanted to touch it!
You didn't buy the dolphin after all?
I thought you would have bought that as a reward for yourself.
Rio-senpai, do you believe in fate?
Why are you bringing that up so suddenly?
Something that happened today made me think about that.
That is more than enough of a reward for me.
I don't believe in fate.
I hate things that are decided and given to you from the start.
But... yeah...
Meeting and being a part of coincidences brought forth by people,
could possibly change someone's life drastically.
If you call that fate, then...
probably...
D-flat!
It seems like you've had a lovely day as well, senpai.
Chirping Crickets
Spirits drifting in river
Next: Chirping Crickets - Spirits Drifting in the River