Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Morning, you two.
Yo.
Good morning.
You remembered to wear your winter uniform.
Come on...
It's not like I'm Tsukasa.
What?!
But the hot weather isn't over yet...
They could let us wear our summer uniforms a little longer.
And when we have to wear
summer uniforms, it gets cold sometimes...
They should just let us choose.
Right?
The switch is more to give students a change in pace.
Else there would be more slackers like you two.
Pandora's
Box
This doesn't happen in our family...
...but I've heard that some parents monitor...
...their daughters' cell phones and e-mail.
I've heard of that on occasion.
Is it like that for you?
Probably not.
Your dad's the type to smother...
...but I guess he wouldn't do anything you wouldn't like.
That might be part of it...
My dad also uses the computer.
Maybe it's 'cause he knows how
embarrassing it is when someone else looks at your D drive.
D...
What?
We've had all these classes and stuff this summer...
In the end...
I only got to have fun with the fireworks and Ariake.
So you still go to Comiket.
Comiket?!
Well, you know...
As a result, my wallet's feeling pretty lonely.
How much did you spend?
You never know when to draw the line.
If you assume each book is a thousand yen...
Around forty to fifty thousand yen total?
Why you...
There's a limit to how clueless a
person can be about the value of money!
Still, Kagami...
There's this thing called market price.
And it's pretty expensive to publish your own stuff.
That's not what I meant!
I'm talking about how you don't
feel anything after spending so much!
It may be September...
...but it's still hot.
That's right.
It seems especially hot this year.
And there's talk about global warming.
Yu-chan can't put up with too much heat...
...so she's been resting in an air-conditioned room most of the time.
That's what Tsukasa's been doing the whole time.
But she's just lazy.
Well...
Dad and I join in...
...and we all lie around looking like a 小 character.
小?
Shouldn't it be 川?
Nah.
Dad's always in the middle.
Your family never changes.
And I guess Yutaka-chan's gotten used to it.
Hey, hey!
Doing good, Yutaka?
I'm here to play!
Sis!
Oh?
Who's this?
My friend...
Minami Iwasaki-chan.
So this is the Minami-chan Yutaka's always talking about.
S-Sis!
So she has a reason for hope right next to her...
I'm a little jealous.
Man...
I'd heard all the fuss...
...but you sure are pretty.
You wowed me!
Want something to drink?
Beer then!
Huh?!
Didn't you drive here?!
Just kiddin'!
Barley tea's fine!
I see.
One absorbs from the other...
Absorption, is it...?
Oh...
[Yassai Mossai - a Japanese folk dance]
It's the Yassai Mossai?
I always get sleepy at night.
Do you have any good ideas?
Instead of forcing yourself to stay up...
...why don't you wake up early and work on it?
You'll probably feel better.
I see!
You're right!
I'll wake up early and work hard.
Huh?
Why is it the same time I always get up?
Come to think of it...
I vaguely remember turning something off at some point...
Even when I wake up early...
...I just roll over and go back to sleep.
You have no willpower...
Maybe I should just try harder...
...and work on it at night.
I doubt rubbing your eyes while nodding off...
...will improve the results.
Why don't you have someone wake you up?
Mom and the others wake up early.
Right, Mom?
Yes, yes.
I'll wake you up.
This can't fail.
Sis is amazing.
Mom!
I told you to wake me up!
I did.
You even answered me back.
I don't know anything about that.
You don't remember?
Big Sister forgot her lunch...
Thanks!
It feels kind of weird to walk
through the hallway of a different grade.
You can feel a little pressure...
I know what you mean.
Yu-chan probably drew everybody's attention.
Being the way she is...
Usually, it's just your imagination...
...but when you walk through
upperclassmen or underclassmen hallways...
...you get this feeling that everybody's looking at you, right?
I already tend to stand out 'cause I'm smaller...
...but when it's because they're
upperclassmen, the pressure is more intense.
I enjoy receiving that kind of attention.
Really...
But I don't attract much attention when I'm in the first-year's area.
They don't realize I'm an upperclassman.
Holds no power as an upperclassman.
Patty-chan.
Hi!
Hello there.
Are you heading to work?
That's right.
I signed up for too many shifts this week.
Aren't you still working?
That's right.
We're pretty popular.
The A-boys are all over us.
A-boys?
It's what you call boys who look like they totally belong in Akiba.
But Narimiya-kun was a little different.
You're getting accustomed to Japan.
A little too accustomed, don't you think?
I just had a great idea!
I'll write it down once I'm done with my bath.
H-Huh?
I can't remember...
This is what happens when I don't jot it down immediately...
And it was funny...
Hilarious, even!
Another exhausting day...
That might be a funny idea.
I'll write it down when I wake up tomorrow.
Er...
That's weird...
What was it again?
I'm positive it was a good idea.
Should have just gotten out of bed and written it down.
Man!
I even got out of bed this time!
Why do you forget dreams so quickly?
I'm positive that it was hilarious!
School Trip
Kyoto & Nara
So...
Make sure you all talk it over within your group.
Kyoto ・ Nara
Since we're going all the way to Kyoto and Nara...
...you better check up on all the hot tourist spots.
Aren't we going through all the hot spots by bus?
Those will just be the typical places...
...so they won't be that fun.
Well now...
That's a blunt way to put it...
So Iris came in here...
I will now guide you through the former capital of Nara.
Almost 1,300 years have passed since it became the capital in 710.
While in Nara...
...I hope you enjoy my historical Nara narration.
Nara!
Nara narration!
Were we supposed to laugh?
Sorry for the wait!
This is the main body...
So the little things around it are options!
You're gonna get hit by lightning.
No!
I'm all sticky...
And stinky...
I'm all stinky now!
Here, here, here.
Indeed.
What's that supposed to mean?
Please, please.
They probably want you to take their picture.
Um... Um...
Click. Click.
Okay?
This is when you can tell how much somebody's been studying.
Like you're one to talk.
Um...
Sis.
How do you say "cheese" in Indian?
You mean Hindi, right?
Um...
Uh...
Genius girl Kagami can't do any better.
Um...
I believe that Indians will understand English.
That's right!
"Say cheese!" should be fine, yeah?
Okay.
Say cheese!
You know how...
...couples pop out of nowhere during school trips?
Can't miss the school trip event.
Perhaps...
...being away from school...
...gives people a sense of freedom?
Kinda like a now or never thing.
I'm embarrassed to say that...
...I'm unable to sleep with a different pillow.
...I can't sleep peacefully without this nearby.
I'm embarrassed to say that...
...I can't sleep if I haven't turned
this on at least once during the day.
Everyone.
The bus will soon pass Kiyomizu Temple.
The hill leading to Kiyomizu Temple...
...is known as Three-year Hill.
Legend says that...
...if you trip and fall here, you'll die in three years.
Three-year Hill will become...
...your Boo-hoo Hill.
Does it count if you break down laughing?
Okay?
We'll be moving around in individual groups now.
Keep an eye out for traffic.
We'll regroup at 12:30 in front of Chion-in.
Don't be late.
Anybody who's late gets to write a
happy 20-page report when we get back.
Sure about that?
Let's give it a try.
The Dragon Slayer's probably about this heavy.
We're really high up.
You know how the saying goes,
"Like you're going to jump off Kiyomizu..."
...but if you really jumped, wouldn't you die?
Does it mean that you no longer care what happens?
You're so pragmatic, Kagami.
Look, look!
It says marriage.
This place seems to be famous for its god of marriage.
They really spell it out for you.
Look.
You can draw love fortunes.
Let's all give it a try.
Let's do it!
Guess I can't tell these apart...
Isn't that obvious?
This one!
Great fortune!
Lucky you, Kona-chan.
My.
I drew good fortune.
That's fine.
Now what did I get...
Half fortune?
What's this?
I-I guess you only get half a fortune.
Which means it's half bad.
Not like I care about love fortunes.
So cute!
That looks nice.
Nah.
Kagami would want this.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'll get one of these.
Kagami! Kagami!
You forgot this!
I'm not buying it!
Then what about this?
No!
You should be careful.
Marriage Wishes
This one says, "Konata is my wife."
Okay.
Everyone's here, right?
We'll have lunch after we've gone in the hotel.
Let's get going.
Take us there, please.
They said that Koizumi's character
song was written in an IZAM style.
Teacher!
Someone's chasing us from behind!
What?!
This is like the Hokkaido shoot all over again!
Don't ditch me!
You have to go, "***tel!"
That idiot.
He's getting assigned a 50-page report!
Driver!
Sorry, could you stop for a second?
See you later.
Hiiragi
I'd like to talk.
Please meet me in
front of the hotel
at 9pm.
-From a certain boy
Doesn't even hurt!
The Golden Pavilion Temple is golden...
...but the Silver Pavilion Temple isn't silver, huh?
They wanted to group it with the Golden Pavilion Temple...
Click.
...so they named it silver to go along with golden.
It was never silver to begin with.
Click.
I wonder if it's like Poke***...
With Sapphire and Ruby and stuff.
No comment?
Our family's shrine was on the news.
We only have one day left.
Our plan for free time is all set.
Tomorrow is the beginning of our true school trip!
Off we go to the holy land!
Right...
D-Does this count as being in front of the hotel?
Did you wait long?
So...
What did you want to talk about?
You're the only person I can talk to about this.
Please give me that doll!
Doll?
You know...
The one you bought from the Kiyomizu Temple souvenir shop!
The Yatsuhashi character.
Ya-Yatsuhashi-kun?
Yeah!
That one!
I really liked it and wanted one.
But if someone saw me buying one...
...they'd probably all make fun of me!
I'm begging you!
Thank you!
I'm eternally in your debt!
Don't tell anybody about this!
Yes, yes.
I'm reading this book about four brothers.
****** of the Dragon Kings?
I can't take it off!
That's right.
Come to think of it...
That could make a pretty good anime.
The steam within cooled off...
...and formed a vacuum.
They did an anime adaptation a while back.
If you press on the sides a little...
Really?
...that should allow air to enter and make the lid easier to remove.
I had no idea!
I think they went up to the fourth volume of the original.
In that case...
But those books are...
I'm sorry!
So sorry!
Putting on a show till the very end.
I've already looked up the directions.
Is it really okay for us to visit?
We'll just be looking from the outside, so it's okay.
There's no need to go that far just 'cause we're in Kyoto.
Tsk. Tsk. Tsk.
You don't understand an otaku's idea of romance.
I don't want to.
Not much here.
It makes it easier to concentrate on their job, so this works.
It's a pretty ordinary-looking building.
They limit their workload, so this works.
Was it really necessary to buy these in Kyoto?
That's embarrassing!
Who cares?
It's a little something for remembering this day!
Sis!
Let's take a picture together!
It's for commemorating this trip.
Since we came all the way to Kyoto.
What does this have to do with Kyoto?
Tsukasa and I made it back in one piece.
Tsukasa's already asleep, though.
I figured you'd be sulking in bed.
Why would I be doing that?
Did you put up the sticker photo?
How could I put up something so embarrassing?
Something so embarrassing....
The school trip was this week...
I sure worked hard.
Okay.
Time to spend the weekend gaming online for once.
Emergency Maintenance Notice
Due to an unexplained server error
at 8:30 PM, the server is currently
undergoing emergency maintenance.
Good lucky!
Here's another crazy episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
I'm the assistant...
Daisuke Ono.
Lucky Channel is already on the twenty-first episode!
That's right.
We're finally getting close to the end.
Well, then...
Let's get straight to this corner...
This week's...
Bend!
Who is it?
What?
I brought your water.
What is this?!
It's warm!
How am I supposed to drink this?!
I'd rather have something out of a vending machine.
Don't mess with me!
You...
Why, you...
What do you think I've had to put up with this whole time?!
All your damn selfish requests one after the next!
Mi-Minoru?
Well, I'm gonna speak my mind today!
Do you know how I felt when I was doing this corner?!
I'd have to work at CoCo**** every day!
That's better pay than my voice acting work!
Thanks to you, I'm working full-time now!
Before I come kiss your ass here...
...I'm over there frying cutlets!
Which means you're more suited for that work.
And what the hell?!
Why are you sitting there, Ono boy?!
That's my seat!
You were abandoned.
By the director and the producer.
What's that?!
They acted too quickly!
I'm a late bloomer!
I can go from here to Starga**r in no time!
You can?
Really?
Sittin' there making fun of me...
Screw working with Hine**su...
Or Lo** and Be***...
I quit.
I quit this stupid show, damn it!
Take that!
Who gives a damn about Lucky Channel?!
Shiraishi Minoru-san!
What are you doing, morons?!
What are you filming there?!
What's with the Cape of Thirty Years?!
If you wanna play with that...
...I'm gonna be thirty soon!
I'm talking about you...
Welcome to Idaho!
The belt isn't long enough, so she's holding it up from behind.
Hello.
Minoru Shiraishi here!
Yeah.
Okay!
Now please listen!
Don't wanna hear it.
The Dentistman Song!
What is this?
The sound of my drill rings through the universe!
What does that even mean?
Yeah, yeah.
Any enemy will fall after one hit!
Stop moving.
Right.
Striving to protect everyone's dreams...
Stop moving!
I head forth giving my all!
Wait, Akira-san!
Th-The enemy is the cavity monster from hell!
Sheesh.
Right.
I'll show you my Drill of Justice!
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now is the time!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Eliminate them!
T-twin drill!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Stop moving!
Shatter them!
Eradicate them!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
For I am...
I am...
I am Dentistman!
Can I let go?
Dentistman is...
Don't screw up your lines!
...is a cyborg.
He...
He will...
You can't be a hero like that.
...continue fighting to defeat the evil cavities!
You can't fight like that.
How was it?
No good.
Redo.
Yes, ma'am.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Akira Kogami!
I'm Daisuke Ono.
Okay.
That's it for the animal talk.
That was in animal, huh?
Next time:
「There Over Here」
There Over Here.
I can cross the goal line now, can't I?
Ramen set!