Yoshii Akihisa was studying.
We've gotta win the Summoned Being Tournament tomorrow.
For Himeji-san's sake, we can't afford to lose!
All right! Let's start with my relatively good subject, Japanese History!
Looks like you're working hard, Aki-kun.
Nee-san?
I've made you a late-night snack.
I really wanted to make it myself,
but I didn't have the time, so you'll have to put up with instant ramen.
Th... this is...
Good Luck!
I wrote on it with mayonnaise.
I poured my heart into those letters to help you get motivated!
R-really?
No! Take everything as a challenge!
Thanks for the meal!
Resembling all-natural super-spicy ramen,
this bright red but not at all spicy soup, mysterious ingredients,
this not quite fruit or vegetable flavor
fills my mouth with-
What the heck is this?
Good Luck!
At first I wrote the letters in ketchup...
but it dissolved.
And I had hope 'cause it was instant...
There's rice balls too!
Ah, these might taste normal!
Mmm! Wrapped in seaweed that smells like the beach,
the fresh sea salt whets my appetite,
the sweet, soft, warm texture of the freshly cooked rice gives a crunch-crunch sound as...
Nee-san,
this is not the texture of any rice I know.
Aki-kun, I know what you're trying to say.
They have a dish called "paella" in Spain, right?
Yeah, it's my favorite.
Al Dente
Delicious paella should be cooked "al dente,"
to give the rice texture.
Aki-kun, I poured my heart into making this rice, hoping you'd enjoy it.
And what do you think? Did my feelings get through?
Al Dente Love
Starting program
I tried cooking it al dente!
Rice balls don't need al dente!
Besides, how did you even pull that off with a rice cooker!?
The world remains full of mysteries.
The tangled up red string of fate
Let's force it into a butterfly knot
Kyu!
Our future together leaps for joy in my heart
Don't untie it, promise me, kay?
Strength training for my heart,
I'll build up tons of strength, just you see!
Love! These feelings aren't enough
Cry! The data's all just
Trash! Doesn't help me at all
Of course it won't
So! Whenever I'm around you
I'm around first love level...
Am I cute?
Talking like you know how I feel
Why? Why? Why?
Just a friend to chat with
But still, everyone
But still
everyone
wants to know their academic ranking in love!
Go wild!
Average score not good enough? My ever-skillful darling
What kind of crush are you really harboring?
I'll bring my level up!
High! High! High!
The tangled up red string of fate
Let's force it into a butterfly knot
Kyu!
My heart's a thumping panic, a sudden development with you
Don't look away, come with me!
Strength training for my heart
Tougher than I thought, I'm blinded again today
Idiots, Tests, and
Summoned Beasts
Festival
Idiots, Tests, and
Summoned Beasts
Day 2
_"Idiots and Fireworks and
_Summoned Being Tournaments."
Day two of Seiryousai.
These are the profits from yesterday.
With this much, we can buy some high-quality equipment!
But the new equipment comes with a catch.
We've gotta win the Summoned Being Exam Tournament.
It's going to be a random tournament of teams of two.
Our main force will be Himeji and Shimada.
Akihisa and I will be backup.
Will you be okay without us?
Hideyoshi and Ninja Pervert, I've got another mission for you two.
Got it! Leave it to us!
If we work hard and have a good tournament,
we can show off F-Class' good side too.
We've gotta win to prevent Himeji-san's transferring, too!
And so, Akihisa,
I hope you studied hard for this.
If you don't score enough on the replenishment exam before the match,
you won't stand a chance.
Don't worry!
I went over all the main points, especially for Japanese History!
I see.
You did well, Akihisa...
What's this?
Japanese History won't be in today's competition.
Seriously!?
Why didn't anyone tell me!?
We will now commence the Summoned Being Exam Tournament!
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
The curtain rises on the main event of day two of Fumizaki Academy's Seiryousai.
What are your thoughts, Takahashi-sensei?
I look forward to seeing our students giving their all.
In the blue corner...
Class 2-F, Sakamoto Yuuji and Yoshii Akihisa!
Let's do this!
Sure...
Oh come on, don't be so beat up cause your expectations were wrong.
In the red corner...
Check it out.
We're up against those kids from E-Class.
Don't lose focus and we can win.
You're right.
We've already beaten them once in a SBE War.
Class 2-B, Iwashita Ritsuko, Kikuiri Mayumi!
What the- it changed!?
We're against B-Class now!?
Hey!
What's going on here?
They're not against the E-Class team?
Well, even if you say that...
What happened?
Looks like some technical difficulties.
We don't have long! Hurry it up!
Guess we've got no choice.
Mayumi.
Right.
Let's go, Ritsuko!
This is quite the turn of events.
What do we do, Yuuji?
Naturally, we've gotta go for it!
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
What do you make of this match, Takahashi-sensei?
With B-Class against F-Class, it may be one-sided.
This is the first round, so I'm sure there will be some bad match-ups.
The subject for this match... Math!
Begin!
Summon!
Not bad.
As expected from B-Class.
However...
Summon!
Wow, Yuuji!
How did your score get so high?
Well you see...
I've been studying so that I can beat A-Class for sure this time.
A-Class?
Yuuji...
You did that much...
I was asked by Shouko.
Asked what?
Yuuji~
"Where should we hold the ceremony?"
I've got to beat A-Class no matter what, or my future will be in danger!
Yuuji... you did that much...
Our fates lie together!
Don't you pull any lame moves this time!
I hear you. I've studied for this too.
Summon!
You're really hopeless, man.
I can't help it!
Looks like they're no match for us.
Let's get this over with so we can prepare for the next match.
Ritsuko!
Mayumi!
Let's go!
Looks like you're pretty in sync.
For some girls' pretend camaraderie, I gotta give you credit.
Well then, let us
show you what true teamwork is!
Right on, Akihisa!
Yuuji!
They're all yours!
We can't both shove the work onto the other person!
That's my line, you dumbass!
I guess I should say our teamwork is about even.
All right.
Akihisa, we're going with that plan.
Plan?
You distract one of them...
And taking that opportunity...
you take care of the other one.
So I've gotta take care of both!
You leave me with no choice.
We'll combine our forces.
Because you had no choice?
I'll handle the attacking.
You act as a shield.
Then I'll be the one who gets beat up!
It hurts like hell when I get hit, dammit!
Since it's come to this, no more sneaky tactics!
We'll each take one, and have a head-on fight!
What about the plan?
Crap!
I can't hit him!
Due to Akihisa's Special Observational status,
he is used to using his Summoned Being for odd jobs,
and is skilled at making agile moves.
Now it's my turn!
Here I go!
All right! It's working!
Why?
Now!
This
is a
visualization.
Huh?
Don't we...
look like the bad guys here?
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
A rather unsightly spectacle, don't you think?
As a teacher,
I'd say I'd very much like to see the Sakamoto-Yoshii pair lose.
What? Don't!
Winner, blue corner: Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
How humiliating!
I'm ashamed we lost to a pair like them!
They're sure getting told off good.
Huzzah...
Thus the first round matches continued,
and the defeated teams left the tournament.
In the blue corner...
Class 2-F, Sakamoto Yuuji and Yoshii Akihisa!
In the red corner...
Class 2-B, Nemoto Kyouji and Class 2-C, Koyama Yuuka!
It's B-Class again, Yuuji.
This time it's those two, huh.
Yoshii? Sakamoto!?
You're our opponents...?
What's wrong, Kyouji?
It's F-Class' idiot dynamic duo.
We have this match in the bag.
I... I suppose.
The subject for this match...
English!
Begin!
Summon!
Yuuji...
What, Akihisa?
Didn't you study hard to beat A-Class?
I can't ace all subjects at once!
If both of us are this low what'll we do!?
Not to worry.
If we're up against them, I have a plan.
Ninja Pervert.
Bring me the item.
Th... that's...
Nemoto Kyouji
Picture Collection
Nemoto Kyouji, Private Picture Collection.
"Behold My Reborn Self!"
Modeled by Nemoto Kyouji, forced to cross-dress after losing the Summoned Being War,
photographed and compiled by Tsuchiya Kouta,
a highly treasured masterpiece.
We'll use this as negotiation materials.
I see.
Back then he did some terrible things to Himeji-san!
Let's negotiate to our hearts content!
Nemoto-kun! If you don't want us to spread around this Picture Collection...
Hold up, Akihisa.
Why?
Don't tell me you're letting him get away...
Your methods are too weak.
Nemoto! Take a look at this!
Th-thats...!
Fine, Sakamoto.
I forfeit.
You two can have this match.
So... please don't...
C-Class representative!
Do you want this?
Very well. It's our loss.
Winner, blue corner: Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
Please, Yuuka!
Let me explain!
Kyouji.
Let's break up.
YUUUUKAAAA!!
Despair!
And thus the matches proceeded smoothly.
You did it, Aki!
Good job, Akihisa-kun!
Onii-chan, you're amazing!
Thanks, Hazuki-chan.
What about you two?
We won too.
Piece of cake!
Good to hear.
It would be great if we could both make it to the finals.
Something's strange here.
moe
What's wrong, Sakamoto?
Our match-ups have been...
It's random, so weren't we just unlucky?
Even so this is unusual.
Hideyoshi. Ninja Pervert.
Prepare the plan.
Roger that!
Understood.
What plan?
If my hunch is correct,
we won't win our next match by playing it straight.
In the red corner...
Class 2-A, Kirishima Shouko, Kinoshita Yuuko!
Just as I thought.
So we're up against these two from A-Class.
Just as you predicted.
We're counting on you, Hideyoshi!
It worked!
Having Hideyoshi and Kinoshita-san switch places,
we're sure lucky they're twins.
Do you really think it'd go that smoothly?
Hideyoshi?
Summoned Being Test Tournament
By Hideyoshi...
you mean that idiot?
My apologies.
I slipped up.
What!?
I can easily predict what you're thinking, Yuuji.
In that case,
we'll have to use our trump card!
Trump card?
You mean you have a plan?
Sure do! Yuuji!
Just repeat what I'm about to say.
Got it! I'll leave it to you this time!
Shouko, please listen to me.
I have to win no matter what.
If I win this tournament...
I will propose to you.
I will propose to you, I-
I love you, Shouko
The fuck are you making me say dumbass!?
Neck crank!
If I win this tournament, I'll propose to you!
I love you, Shoooouukooooo!
I forfeit.
Class rep!
Fine, I'll just win by myself!
The subject for this match... Health!
Begin!
Summon!
I'm not out of plans yet!
Here we go!
I'll show you my most powerful summoning!
Summon!
Behold! Ultimate Proxy Summoning!
If you think you can take this, go for it!
Sensei, they're breaking the rules.
Oh shit!
I love you,
Shooooouukooooooooo!
We withdraw.
Class rep!
Due to the red corner's withdrawal,
winner, blue corner: Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
FFF clan now recruiting
Wages
Monthly:
(paid in kind)
But wait!
Exchange 5 AP for 1 HP!
What's more!
Percentage bonuses based on performance!!
For details,
please ask in person.
Accepting applications 24 hours a day!!
Contact Sugawa Ryou of 2-F
You little bitch!
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
It's your fault they figured out your plan!
Don't give me that shit!
You've put my life in danger!
I'm amazed you two managed to win like that.
But isn't that fine?
We've all made it to the semifinals now.
That's right.
Our two teams have made it this far,
so winning's not out of the question.
Amazing!
Hazuki's gonna cheer Onii-chan on to help him win!
Thanks, Hazuki-chan.
I'll do my best.
We will now begin the semifinals.
In the red corner...
Himeji Mizuki and Shimada Minami!
Aw man...
Well I guess that's fine.
Our goal is to have the winner be from our class.
We don't have to bust our chops to win this one.
Yeah, you're right.
We'll just lose easily so Himeji-San and Minami can save their energy...
Stupid Onii-chan!
I'm rooting for you!
Hazuki-chan...
Hazuki will cheer for you, so don't lose, please!
Sorry, Hazuki-chan...
Grown-ups have their reasons that a kid wouldn't understand...
If you win, Hazuki will give you a grown-up kiss as a reward!
Not just a kiss, I'll take a bath with you too!
A bath... together...
Hazuki will wash her tired Onii-chan's back!
You know, a match really should be fought seriously...
H... hang on...
Our goal is...
Bloody death!
BLOODY DEATH!
It would be rude to hold back after all.
Oh come on...
If you fight for real the feedback will hurt like...
Kill him!
KILL HIM!
I wonder why...
Even though we're all in F-Class... this malicious aura...
Give it up, Akihisa.
Let's just lose and get out of here.
If you lose on purpose I won't forgive you.
Shouko!?
Yuuji, you said you'd propose if you won.
If you lose on purpose we're getting married immediately.
It's the same result both ways!
W-what do we do?
We'll just have to win this and shut them up!
But how do we beat Himeji-san and Minami...
The subject for this match... Classics!
Begin!
This
is a
visualization.
Summon!
A summoned beast with only 6 points
practically isn't even part of the match!
Of course!
Let's go, Akihisa!
Yeah!
Summon!
Akihisa...
I honestly feel bad about this...
You're sure stubborn!
Stay still so I can kill you!
I'll send you to the afterlife in just one hit.
If you hit me with that much power I'll seriously die from the pain!
Akihisa!
Hold down Himeji's weapon!
I'll do something about this!
Got it! I'll give it a shot!
What are you doing!?
Let go!
Yuuji! Now!
Just make sure you don't hit me too!
Take this!
You bastaaaaard!
Winner: blue corner, Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
So it would have been the same no matter who hit me...
Death to the blasphemer!
Help! Help me...
Why only me?
Rest easy. I won't let your vain death be in vain.
You just said it was vain!
I've obtained some information.
Information?
It's just as Yuuji deduced.
I see. I thought so.
Akihisa. We're going all out for the finals.
Right!
Under the watching eyes of the entire student body, the finals have finally begun.
Somehow advancing to the finals,
we have the lowest academic rank F-Class team.
Takahashi Youko
Fukuhara Shin
Perhaps we should hereby rethink our attitude towards F-Class.
They are against a team from Class 3-A.
Class 3-A?
In the red corner...
Class 3-A, Natsukawa Shunpei, Tsunemura Yuusaku!
The Tokonatsu duo?
Akhisa-kun!
Aki!
Nice job making it to the finals.
But it ends here.
We're gonna kick your ass till you cry for mercy.
You're still wearing that?
I can't get it off!
You pervert!
You put it on me!
Senpai. You guys done with your little tricks?
Huh? Tricks?
You were the ones manipulating our tournament match-ups, weren't you?
Tch. We went out of the way to have you two lose early so you wouldn't be embarrassed.
But you just didn't know when to give up.
We're gonna pay you back for yesterday now!
Fine then. Bring it on.
Just you wait. I'll beat the crap out of you with my top subject, English.
ENGLISH
Both sides, get ready!
Japanese History
It's not English!?
Nice work, Ninja Pervert!
Not at all. Piece of cake.
Yuuji,
Considering how much crap they pulled,
I think we can get away with this little cheat.
Damn it!
Summon!
What!?
Passing scores!?
Aki would usually be around 60 points!
That's amazing, Akihisa-kun!
Let's go! No holds barred!
Shut up!
I'm your opponent!
What!?
Damn you! You little F-Class bastard...
NOW!!
Let me show you,
what battle experience means!
Be grateful for it!
So I heard you're under Special Observation or something?
I'll bet that must hurt like a bitch.
Akihisa! Damn you...
Prove you've got balls, man!
You can do it, right, partner?
Of course!
Tch! Your efforts are worthless!
I'll finish this off!
Go!
Coming through!
So he tossed his weapon?
Perfect!
I've got you now!
What!?
Akihisa!
Winner: blue corner!
What-
the fuck!?
The winner of the Summoned Being Exam Tournament has been determined:
Class 2-F, the Sakamoto-Yoshii pair!
We did it, Akihisa.
Yeah!
Dammit! There's no way we'll accept this!
What? Still not satisfied?
As if! You guys cheated like hell to win!
Just call it negligent conduct.
You guys didn't play fair either!
Fine then! We'll just tell everyone exactly what happened!
This was an unfair competition!
Damn them! They're going to reveal our cheating over the intercom!
No way! If this victory we worked for becomes invalid...
Akihisa!
That's it!
We'll be borrowing this.
Wh- what are you-
We won't let you interfere with our victory!
We've gotta win and buy new classroom equipment!
There's no way we can let Himeji-san transfer!
We did it!
Nice one, Akihisa!
Oh shit.
You punks...
Anything but there!
Are you okay, stupid Onii-chan?
Geez, there's something called "self-restraint" you know.
But they were the ones...
The funds we obtained to buy equipment,
have mostly gone to repair the damaged school building.
What?
With this, I guess tea tables are the best we can do.
Guess our priorities were backwards.
So then, will Himeji-san transfer...?
Akihisa-kun!
Himeji-san...
Where were you, Mizuki?
I met with my father.
Huh?
So he came to watch.
This looks hopeless.
My father...
said if I'm going to attend this school, I should work on not only my studies,
but also my physical strength.
Meaning...
And also...
"You have great friends."
Yeah! That's right!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
The day after a day off
should be a day off too!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
The day before a day off
should also be a day off too, yeah!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
I don't want this to end!
I want to stay like this!
I don't want to leave my room!
I don't want to believe it!
I just can't believe it!
I hate Mondays!
If I don't get up it's over.
I want to cling just a bit longer
to this irresistible drowsiness
I'm happy in my dreams.
Maybe I oughta get up, maybe it can't end like this
My dream continues into a horrifying reality.
Even if I panic now,
time won't turn back.
So I'll dive back into the world of dreams
We will now be holding the bonfire dance.
Students please gather at the school building.
There have been a lot of misunderstandings,
but they were all unfortunate coincidences!
So why don't we start over ag-
Wait!
YUUUUKAAAA!!
Yuuji.
Our promise.
Propose.
Damn it!
Testimony given under torture won't hold in court!
Um...
Akihisa-kun...
I-If you'd like...
Would you like to...
Do the folk dance with Hazuki!
Sure. Let's dance, Hazuki-chan!
What? No way...
Akihisa-kun...
Gotta feel sorry for those two.
And thus the curtain fell on Seiryousai.
Warming their cheeks by the burning flames,
holding their emotions in their heart,
the students indulged in the night of the festival.
Moon: "End"