So beat...
This school thing's pretty tough...
I can't do this...
Aokigahara
Mt. Fuji
Welcome to
Mother
Nature
Lost Inside
Brother?
Top Secret
So, what kind of depraved porno was my brother watching?
I can't believe he's looking at other women!
I call infidelity!
Even if men his age can't help their urges,
he has no excuse for straying from his sister!
I'm the leader of this project, Yagami Tsurugi.
Henceforth, we shall begin the Sasami Watch Project.
Huh?
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 4
Family Leech
Ah, um, mic test, mic test.
You sure you're capturing my beauty, Tsukuyomi?
Indeed, we're filming normally!
What... is this?
The goal of the Sasami Watch Project
is to support Sasami now that she's finally returned to society.
Support me?
To let her live as a normal girl
despite the power sleeping within her.
If we can make that life a reality,
I'd like to devote myself to helping in any way I can.
That's the reason we exist.
Tsurugi...
As such, I'd like to give Sasami a test to help her mature.
The Sasami Watch Project
aims to record the events, and laugh like hyenas as that retard falls flat on her face!
I can't believe I almost felt something...
We've already given Sasami her first task.
My superior sisters are currently recording it.
Hey Camera 2, status report on your end!
Way too close! Back it up!
Yagami Kagami on camera 2.
I am currently trailing Sasami from a distance of 30 meters.
Is that me?
Sasami shows no signs of noticing my presence.
When did she take this?
When did I go there?
Why can't I remember it?
Good work, Kagami.
Camera 3, what's the word on your end?
It's good!
Hey, I joined the school's broadcasting club!
But then,
I was super loud on a broadcast,
so the principal had a little heart—
Phone call!
Tama speaking!
Where are you right now?
So like, the sky turned all super bright, and then I was here!
And right now, these big, grey, bug eyed people holding the camera are all,
"We wish to encounter the intelligent lifeforms of Earth,"
and they're all talking like robotties!
Don't go running off with strangers!
They'll dissect you alive, or implant a chip in your brain!
Now get back to work!
Um, Ms. Tsurugi, what did you just...
Don't say a word.
Pretend you saw nothing.
Hey Camera 2, what's your status?
The heck're you doin'?!
Am I not allowed to keep one?
Ask me later! Where's Sasami?
Um...
I seem to have lost her.
Idiot!
By using electro-spiritual waves from beyond satellite orbit, I can track Sasami's location.
Located.
She is on the opposite end of this mall.
H-Hey...
Runnin' on rooftops is for ninjas only!
Teehee.
Don't "teehee" me!
You're so cute, marry me babe!
Sasami seems to be entering a drug store.
Good, she should be buying what I asked her to.
Oh?
Sasami seems to be unable to find her intended article.
Sister, just what did you ask of her?
What are you looking for?
Um, this...
A dozen Happy Family Planning Kits, then?
How could you ask a minor to purchase that?
The thought of a cute, beet-red high schooler buying a family planning kit is just adorable!
I apologize, but I don't think we carry those.
Oh, you don't...
My teacher told me that drug stores carry them.
Incidentally, what is this "Happy Family Planning Kit"?
Huh? You don't know?
The truth may be painful,
but today's youth do not stigmatize that phrase.
Opportunities for sexual harassment may be rare, but this one is a dud.
This can't be!
Just saying "Happy Family Planning Kit" out loud used to be enough to make everyone crack up!
Sasami seems to be moving on to the next item.
All Items
100 yen!
Good deals
wherever
you look!
All Items
100 yen!
Good deals
wherever
you look!
Oh, she has entered a 100 yen store.
What's she goin' there for?
Was this not a request of yours?
Nope.
Oh, she exited.
It seems she purchased something.
I shall use my X-Ray vision.
You can do that?!
A pair of sunglasses, a knit cap, and a track suit, it seems.
Who cares about that, use it on Sasami!
What's color are they?
What color is what?
The color of Sasami's panties is irrelevant.
Forget the panties, I want her nipples!
Shut up!
Oh?
What's up? Is she goin' commando?!
Sasami appears to be entering a super bathhouse.
Super Bathhouse
I wonder,
why is she bathing here instead of her home?
Maybe she doesn't want Tsukuyomi peekin' on her there?
I do no such thing.
I proudly enter with Sasami.
Huh? What was that?
Super Bathhouse
She is entering the bathhouse.
I shall pursue.
Super Bathhouse
Ticket Dispenser
Change Button
Guest Use
One student pass, please.
You carry that camera everywhere.
Women
I Transformed other humans' cognizance, so they pay it no mind.
Good job! That's my sister for ya!
I have found Sasami.
Stop it, don't film that!
Don't strip, me! Stop it!
No!
Now, time for a commercial break.
Time for a
commercial break.
It was when the moonlight glittered brilliantly,
on that quiet winter's night.
Wh— now we're here?
This is wrong, this is so wrong!
Oh, geez...
What's this doing here?
It's a sample of my prized "Sleeping Sasami" collection.
Don't you have to tell her to smile 'cause she's on Candid Camera?
Screw it, go back to Camera 2.
Kagami!
Kagami, what're you doin'?
Yoooou aaaaare beeeeiiiiiing aaaaannooooooyiiiiiing.
What're you all relaxed over, huh?
What happened to Sasami's bath scene?
Sasami did not bathe.
She changed her clothes and left.
I am tired.
It pains me to say it, but it seems I cannot go on.
Get up and chase her!
Did you forget all I've done for you?
I changed your diapers, gave you your binky, made up fun games for you, and showered you in love!
I cannot understand your speech, you sickening pervert.
Say it louder, baby!
Oh well. Tsukuyomi, we're headin' out to the field.
What's with this DVD?
I don't remember these errands at all...
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Bad...
Bad!
And here we are.
Sasami has to have come here.
And where is here?
They call this place Uzume no Ana.
Tapioca Girlfriend
They follow the subcultures behind all the latest anime, games, and comics,
and are the one-stop shop for all the merchandise you can think of!
So, it's a shop for nerds!
Don't say that out loud.
And where might Sasami be?
Third floor! Let's move.
Oh, but it says that those under 18 aren't allowed on the third floor.
Official Works
Mail Order Pickup
Original Indie Comics
Adult Merchandise
All Ages Indie Comics
Adult Indie Comics
Indie Merchandise
Official Works
Old Comics / Animated Works
New Comics / Magazines
New and Old Novels / Photobooks / How-To
All Ages / Adult
Anime / Comics / Light Novels / Games / Other
Under 18 Not Allowed
Where's Sasami?
There she is!
She's in disguise.
But my eyes cannot be fooled!
Um...
Guess it's this.
Record of Yamato War
TakeTake Roon
Kumaso
Ibuki
So...
Ibuki from Record of
Yamato War TakeTake-Roon:
Buy her limited edition figure
with removable armor!
The standard edition
can't get naked.
"Ibuki from Record of Yamato War TakeTake-Roon?"
"Buy her limited edition figure with removable armor!"
"The standard edition can't get naked."
Does it matter?
Record of Yamato War
TakeTake Roon
Ibuki
Limited Edition Cast Off
Quantities Limited
This is 30,000 yen?
So I take this to the clerk...
Oh, she's splittin'.
You make me proud, Sasami!
Welcome to my domain.
Have a taste of the dark side.
Stop, get outta there!
Cute little sisters?
Lovey Dovey <3
Love Kiss Brother
They want me to die of shame...
Huh? But she's his sister.
Why?
Oh, I get that. Totally.
Wait, what are they doing?
But that's a boy's... wha?
Kill me! Just kill me now!
Um, excuse me.
You're a high schooler, right?
Uh, well, I...
Did you come here for the voice actress show on the fourth floor?
Huh? Uh, yeah!
Sorry, it's easy to get lost.
The staircase is over here.
Let's chase him off, Ms. Tsurugi!
Cram it, retard!
I'm no grade schooler, got it?!
So shut up and sell me these!
I'm sorry miss, but I can only sell these comics to adults.
And I'm tellin' ya I am an adult!
I'll go on ahead, then!
Akihabara Shop
Event Hall
Adult Indie Works
Female Indie Works
Indie
Software
Anime / Comics /Light novels
Thank you, everyone!
It wavers, bobs around
It's like a little cloud
This is me
What're you doing?
Dance along!
This is my first love
You screwed up!
This song's red!
Huh? Oh, right...
The sun shines and I wake up
What a wonderful day
I'm kind of happy
I feel like I could fly
I'm coming to see you now
Isn't that nice?
Excuse me, let me through!
Sorry, video recording isn't allowed!
Oh, I'm not recording the singer, I'm recording Sasami...
K-Kamiomi?!
Why're you here?
Oh?
Are you not a shrine maiden from the Tsukuyomi Shrine?
Y-You're mistaken!
I've never heard of some Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Please take your leave, Kamiomi!
If someone from the Tsukuyomi Shrine is here,
then this queer event must be...
Now!
I must congratulate you.
Father...
O Daughter,
relinquish your excess burden to your father!
Sasami!
The sun shall relinquish its throne to the moon!
And a new voice shall read mankind's fortune!
What have you done, Father?
This one had plotted everything.
This one regained consciousness once its seal faded,
and contacted us proposing this ruse.
No...
Yes.
The Supreme God's power is here!
Indeed, in the palm of my hand!
Fuckin' annoying-ass walls...
Hm?
What're you up to, Tsukuyomi?
Please do what you like...
I felt a suspicious presence.
Disturbing my precious nap time is a grave sin.
'Scuse me 'scuse me 'scuse me!
I'm super sorry!
I'm running from the government!
It's all right, I'm here for you.
I won't hand over the galactic mystery of Notosmodent!
Hey, lady!
Hand those aliens to us, the Allied Earth Government!
These little guys just want to go home!
We have no choice.
Open fire!
Where the crap did this come from?
This seems to be a memory-erasing chemical.
Everyone!
Eliminate these interlopers!
All units, charge!
Now's your chance, Qupi!
I am...
free now...
That about covers it.
I beat the crap outta those Tsukuyomi Shrine guys.
Tsukuyomi called an ambulance,
and took Sasami to a hospital.
Your memories got fuzzy when you breathed that green gas in.
So we made a DVD through a Transformation to give you an outline of what happened.
Do you remember what you are,
little tumor?
You two originally shared the same body.
So you thought you were Sasami and went back home.
What... will you do to me?
You're a part of Sasami.
And I dunno what'll happen if I leave you cut off.
So I'll Transform you back to meatloaf, slap you back onto Sasami, and fuse you together.
Then we'll be back to normal.
That's ridiculous!
I'm free now!
I'm my own person!
Can you understand the agony of being trapped helplessly in someone else's body?
I was finally cut free!
And I'll live how I choose!
Oh yeah, I have power.
In this body is the Supreme God's power!
I can scorch, singe, and sear every last one of you!
By the name of the Supreme God, I command you—
Give it back.
It's too big a toy for you.
I... wha...
Now sit quietly and think about what you did.
'Cause this is me being nice.
Aw, don't worry.
I felt kinda bad for you.
I'm not the workaholic type of god,
but I can pull a miracle or two.
You awake?
What... happened to me?
Same as it ever was.
But that tumor's out of the picture.
Oh...
You two shared body and soul.
And you both wanted to live free.
You're both a pain in the ass, to boot.
But that tumor sinned.
It tried to sacrifice someone else to gain that life for itself.
You realize what a pain in the ass you are,
and try your best to catch yourself.
You don't abuse the Supreme God's power,
and you even try to reject it.
That's why someone as devilish as me thinks it's better in your hands.
Keep trying out there.
'Til the day comes where you don't have to.
Here, Meatie,
Kagami will take good care of you.
Meatie?
That is her name.
Though you say they share the same source,
calling her Sasami would be wrong.
"Meatie" makes her sound like food.
She is so cute I could just eat her up.
Even though I have no need for food due to my lack of humanity.
So, how's Tama doing?
Farewell!
There are still realms of science that mankind must never tread upon...
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Hey there!
It's everyone's most beloved character, the protagonist, Tsukuyomi Sasami!
Now you'll finally get to hear my song!
Don't touch that dial!
It's Tsukuyomi Sasami's "Osmotic Symphony"!
Even though we say our goodbyes,
I start to miss you right away
Until I board the train,
I want to listen to your voice
Why are you so enthusiastic?
Might you have a fever, Sasami?
Wait, are you even Sasami?
Who are you?
Dear me, I'm the same as ever, bro!
I love you! Smooch smooch!
I have a bad feeling about this...
I can hear your voice
like a resounding symphony
How was that?
Did I sing it well?
Um, yes!
It was perfect as a song...
Then I'll sing next time, too!
I got Uboa'd in the novels, but I'm still in the game here!
I've never been happier!
I'm gonna try hard next time, too!
Uh... you really aren't Sasami!
Who are you?
It's time for Apathetic Advice.
Ei Takeshi
Tokyo City,
Suginami Ward
Here's a letter from Mr. A in Tokyo.
Lately, I haven't been able to get motivated.
Lately, I haven't been able to get
All it does is make every day dull.
All it does is make
I feel like I've turned into a lazy procrastinator because the world is evil.
You understand me, right, Sasami?
Get a job, bum.
Next time, on Episode 5.
Next Time, on Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
I Just Haven't Tried Yet.