What's wrong?
Oh, nothing...
I just finished the book I've been
reading for a while, that's all.
I bought it at that mall.
I finished it faster than I thought I would.
What was it about?
Ummm, it's a book by a foreign author.
It takes place during the war.
It's about the journey some children and their dog
embark upon after their house burns down.
Huh?
But the ending was hard to get through.
Was it sad?
Yes, the dog, well...
I'd read the translated version before,
so I knew it was coming...
But the ending was the same in the original, too.
I see.
It was so nice out yesterday,
but now it looks like it's going to rain.
You're right.
Yuri-senpai, you always look so sad on rainy days.
It was raining the day Megu-nee died.
That was back when we were
constructing the barricades.
Kurumi, Yuki-chan, Megu-nee, and I were
expanding the safe zone down from the roof,
and we'd gotten it to the point
where we could scrape by.
That might've been why we were caught off guard.
It started to rain.
We still didn't know much about how they acted then.
So all of the sudden, we realized
they were coming into the building,
and soon, we were surrounded.
If Megu-nee hadn't protected us,
we would all be...
Yuki-chan's been this way ever since.
Are we going to be okay today?
There's been more of them lately.
You noticed that, too?
Yeah.
Back when it all began,
it was after school, so there weren't many students
still hanging around the school buildings.
But as time goes by, more and more students
that weren't on school grounds come back to school.
Almost as if they're following their old memories.
Everyone loves school.
Huh?
Isn't that what Yuki-senpai said?
All of us love school.
That's why we come to school.
I don't remember liking school that much.
But I guess so.
Let's all graduate!
Everyone write 100 pages!
I can't write that many!
But we can't stay here forever.
Even if we have water and electricity,
we'll eventually run out of food.
We have to find somewhere to go,
and figure out how we're getting there.
Are the barricades still holding up alright?
We've used all the tables and chairs we can,
and we're out of nails and boards to reinforce them with.
Don't worry.
Those barricades are strengthened by our hopes,
and Megu-nee's love for us.
They won't be broken so easily.
G'morning!
Morning, Yuki-chan.
Good morning.
You're up early.
Are you hungry?
I told you, Senpai, you can't eat Taromaru's food.
I'm not gonna eat it.
Taromaru wasn't in my bedroom when I woke up.
House of Taromaru
He slipped out of his collar,
so I thought maybe he came down here.
Huh?
Taromaru
School Living Club
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Issho ni (Hai!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Houkago nara atarimae no koto
Saa sa, atsumare!
Kossori kaeruna! (Kora!)
Bukatsu dou dane? Katsudou shichau ne!
Asonderu nja arimasen
Tadaima tte ano ko ga iu yo (Okaeri!)
Minna de ireba daijoubu (Bu!)
Everybody say: tomodachi de iyou ne
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Daisuki (Hai!)
Watachitachi wa tanoshinderu
24 jikan hashaideru
Okujou ni wa akana taiyou
Kanari sakendemita (Genki desu!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
A Rainy Day
It started raining.
Seriously?
Yeah.
See, all the sports clubs are going inside.
IMPORTANT!
Vitamins are almost out!
Taromaru!
Time for breakfast!
I wonder what Taromaru's up to.
Usually he'd come running at the smell of food.
Yeah...
Then what? What could he want more than food?
Oh! Maybe he's on a date!
With who?
He's too smart for his own good.
We made sure that collar was
on him as tight as possible...
I'm going to go look for him.
It'd be bad if he got lost in here.
I'll go too!
If he gets wet out in the rain, he could catch a cold!
Okay, let's go look for him!
What should we do if he really did
go outside the school?
He'll be fine.
He's a smart cookie.
He wouldn't leap into any dangerous situations.
You guys focus on this floor.
Okay!
Right.
I'll check the other floors.
Will you be alright on your own?
I'll be fine!
Still, it's raining...
I know, I'll be careful.
Man, this puppy is a real pain in our butts.
Hey, Taromaru!
Where'd you go?
Time to eat!
Come on out!
I don't think he'd be able to open that door to get out...
Taromaru!
Hey!
He probably wouldn't come this way.
Huh?
You cut your hair, Megu-nee!
You looked so good with it long!
Oh, really?
I had to cut it, I'm a teacher.
What's that supposed to mean?
My long hair was a little too childish.
So I figured I'd go for a more mature look.
A little too childish?
I think it looks fine on you, Ebisuzawa-san.
So what was it again?
The "School Living Club"?
Yes, that's right.
Yuri-san came up with the idea.
We'd like you to join, Ebisuzawa-san.
Sure, why not?
I feel like I'll get more worked up about this
if I have a goal to work towards.
Yes.
And it'll help cheer her up, too, seeing as
she does nothing but cry all the time.
Don't you agree, Megu-nee?
I do.
But please, Ebisuzawa-san, don't call me Megu-nee...
I know, I know.
Not Megu-nee, Sensei-nee.
Jeez!
Short hair looks good on you too, Megu-nee.
He might be little, but he's a club member, too.
So please protect him too, Sensei.
Hey, if you don't come out soon,
know who's gonna eat your food?
Yuki will!
We have lots of ping pong balls, too!
Let's play catch!
No...
Did Taromaru...
Don't tell me!
You've gotta be joking...
I've never been down these stairs before.
This is the place that manual was talking about.
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
Taromaru!
Jeez, don't scare us like that!
No...!
What do I do?
What can I...
I-I'm sorr-
Taromaru...
Think, think, think!
You're the one...!
You're the one who turned Taromaru!
Damn... Are you kidding me?
Is this where she went?!
Why?
WHY, DAMMIT?!
I'm back!
I couldn't find Taromaru.
It's already noon and Taromaru's not back?
Yes.
I just got back, too.
Where's Kurumi-chan?
She's not back yet.
She might still be looking for him.
I'll take another-
Kurumi!
Kurumi-senpai!
I screwed up.
No...
Yuki-senpai?
Where's the first-aid kit?
It should be in the teachers' room...
Okay, got it!
Miki-san, lend me a hand here!
Okay!
Megu-nee...
It was Megu-nee.
Hey, Ri-san, can I help with anything?
Let's see...
There's nothing right now.
Could you go boil some water?
Okay, I'll do that!
Are you okay?!
Sorry.
It's okay.
I've got to keep it together.
You're doing great, Senpai!
But I think you should rest a little.
No, I can't let Yuki-chan be
the only one working so hard.
I couldn't save him!
I'm sorry!
Taromaru's...
No...
Down in... the emergency evacuation area!
Megu-nee's...
Dammit!
Gardening Club
Kurumi-chan's okay, right, Megu-nee?
What's happening?
Taromaru?
Taromaru!
I finally found you!
Where the hell were you?
Open... the door.
I... love... you all.
M..Megu-nee?
Why?
Why won't you open the door?
Stop it.
Stop it!
Open the door.
PLEASE STOP!
Umm...
I read through this again.
O-oh?
Kurumi-san told us she saw Megu-nee
in the emergency evacuation area, right?
Yes, what of it?
It says there's medicine down there.
What?!
Where?!
Here.
2. Supplies
One month of supplies is prepared for the predicted
number of 15 survivors. An infinite supply of electric
power is provided by solar panels, and water via the
rainwater filtration device.
3. Relief Supplies
Supplies                      painkillers, antibiotics, first-aid kits.
Each kit                       supplies for three people.
4. Entrances
I'm going down there.
No, I'll go.
You take care of Kurumi-san and Yuki-san...
You won't make it on your own!
I'll just go take a look.
I won't go overboard.
That's what Kurumi said!
I think the only reason Kurumi-san got hurt
was because it was Megu-nee.
I'll be fine.
Please let me go.
I brought hot water!
Thank you.
Huh? Where're ya going?
The club room.
To get the shovel.
Huh?
Ri-san, are you okay?
I'll be borrowing this for a little while, Senpai.
Taromaru
I couldn't save him!
I'm sorry!
Taromaru's...
Taromaru!
Yuki
Kurumi                           Ri
It's been so long since it's rained this hard.
It's just like that one rainy day.
That one rainy day?
Brr! Cold...
Huh?
The window's broken.
Akaneiro ni kimi wa
Nani o kangaeteita no
Mabuta ippai namida o tamete
Gomakashiteita kirei da ne to
Utagai mo naku
Konna hibi ga tsuzuite ikunda tte
Zutto omotteita
Miageta sora wa tooku tooku
Bokura mitsumeteiru
Tada shizuka ni kawaranai mama
Maigo no te to te nigirishimeta
Mou samishiku wa nai yo
Owaru sekai mukou gishi eto
Bokura no yoake ga mieru kara
Mieru kara
Waratte
Next Time!
Yuki-senpai is amazing.
With Yuki-senpai, we can be happy
no matter what happens.
No matter what happens...
Scars
Next time on School-Live, episode 11:
"Scars"
We are right here.