Outou Festival
Opening Ceremony
Accepting Proposals
A culture festival, huh?
Is it already that time of year?
Tests are coming up, too.
It's a drag that there's so much to do.
This is the last culture festival in your high school career,
and that's the only sentiment you have?
Opening ceremony?
What is this?
Every year,
during the Outou Festival,
there's a time when you can show off your performance.
I just had a great idea!
TBA
Bazaar
Maze
Fortune Telling House
Tooth-brushing Exercising
The History of and How to Make Paulownia Cabinets
Now then,
our class has decided...
...to hold a fortune-telling parlor for the festival.
So everyone, please decide on the method of fortune-telling you will be doing...
...before our next homeroom.
Tooth-brushing Exercising
The History of and How to Make Paulownia Cabinets
Haunted House
You tried hard.
I was touched.
That's why...
...I was thinking about doing a cheerleading routine!
Cheerleading?
For the opening ceremony we talked about this morning.
It would be the best performance for bringing the festival to life!
Yeah, it does sound pretty crazy and fun.
Doesn't it?
We'll be the talk of the day!
By we, do you mean...
You mean we're a part of it, too?
I asked Sensei,
and was told there has to be a properly structured outline, including the performers' names.
W-What about you, Yutaka?
Me?
It might be physically tough on Yu-chan.
Maybe I'll give it a try.
Eh!?
If it's not too much trouble, I was thinking maybe I could give it a try.
Trouble?
Absolutely not!
You're more than welcome!
W-Will you be okay?
It'll probably be tough,
and I might just hold everyone else back,
but I'd like to give a try this time.
See!
Yutaka's willing to do it.
So what about you two?
If that's the case...
Well, if everyone's doing it...
I'm so glad I have such good friends!
Fortune-telling?
Can you even do any sort of fortune-telling?
Nope,
not at all.
Oh my~
Hey, weren't you the one who proposed it?
For a culture festival, fortune-telling can be pretty much whatever.
Which reminds me,
what's your class doing, Onee-chan?
Us?
Well...
We just decided to be simple and do a haunted house.
How commonplace.
We couldn't come up with any other interesting ideas...
What is it?
Nah.
I just thought it suited you well.
What are you trying to say!?
Oh no! The devil's mad now!
I knew you were gonna say that...
And so,
Patty-chan said she wanted to do a cheerleading routine.
Oh!
And I was thinking, "Maybe I'll give it a try, too!"
Ah...
What!
Why so suddenly?
I've been absent a lot,
so I've never had the chance to accomplish something with my friends.
I've been feeling a lot better these days.
What I wanted to do,
and what Patty-chan wants to do right now,
is probably not all that different.
But I still think it's going to be pretty tough...
Also,
since we don't have enough people,
Patty-chan was wondering if you would join us, Onee-chan.
So that's how it is.
You're really athletic,
so if people like you and Minami-chan are there with me,
I feel like I'll be able to hang in there until the end.
Since you seem to be really serious about this, and because Patty's also asking...
Yes, hello?
Good evening, Konata!
It's Patty, huh?
I just heard the story and was thinking about what to do...
Pin Pon Pan Pon!
Time for a quiz!
I have a certain ticket in my other hand right now.
Now, what do you think the ticket is for?
D-Don't tell me it's...
Konata.
The Gekisou was pretty moé moé, don't you think?
And don't you want to exchange a hot handshake with Haruhi?
Oh, handshake session!
I'll go! I'll go!
Must meet Aya!
By the way, Konata,
you were trying to say something earlier, weren't you?
Yu-chan.
Let's make some nice memories!
O-Okay!
And so,
this is the age of cheerleading girls.
What's that supposed to mean?
Patty wanted to do a cheerleading routine during the culture festival's opening ceremony.
Is that so.
That does fit her image.
Which is why the both of you are also on the team.
Oh,
are there any other people in your class who might be interested, Kagami?
W-Wait a sec!
Don't just go on ahead without our permission!
I-I don't think I'm suited for that kind of stuff...
What?
But we probably won't get another chance like this.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
We know everyone on the team,
and it's a festival, so it'll be more fun if we go crazy with everyone.
Really?
Yeah, you might be right!
Tsukasa, you're so easily convinced...
I'm out.
I have to prepare for my own class projects.
I just wanted to make some memories...
...with my best friends during our last culture festival together.
You always seem to pull the friendship card when there are ulterior motives!
It's clearly obvious you're putting on an act!
Yu-chan is really enthusiastic about this, too.
What?
But will she be okay?
I told her she shouldn't...
But she was really earnest about wanting to accomplish something with everyone.
I-I see.
But we're having trouble getting enough people,
so I thought I would ask you guys.
I guess I was a little too pushy about it.
And I would hate to make you guys do something you really didn't want to.
I'll just ask someone else.
Fine...
Eh, what?
Fine!
I'll do it!
Onee-chan!
Eh, are you sure?
I can't help it.
Besides, my class can just replace me with someone else,
but there are no replacements for you, right?
Kagami, you're so cute after all.
C-Cheerleading is it?
I'm not confident that I can do a good job...
Well...
Right now we're just trying to fill the gaps...
BOING
Especially in terms of volume.
If you joined us, it would help a great deal!
Is that so?
I understand.
If I can be of help.
Thank you so much Boin-
I mean, Miyuki-san.
Now that testing is over,
we're going to be focusing on preparations for the festival.
But don't slack off too much!
Geez...
They could at least cut down on the testing when we have school events.
Yo!
Hey, Konata.
What's going on with the cheerleading thing?
That's right...
Before exams started,
"The plan was approved,"
was what I heard.
I haven't heard anything since.
What!?
How carefree!
If we don't start practicing soon...
Or rather,
I think it might already be too late!
Guess we'll go ask her.
Sorry!
I haven't worked out the choreography yet!
You haven't worked out the choreography yet?
What are we supposed to do then!?
It's also taking me a while to pick the song...
It's hard finding something on Hare Hare's level.
What was that?
Anyway,
if you were troubled about it, you should have talked it over with someone.
You're the one that came up with the idea,
so you need to be more responsible about the scheduling!
I don't understand these hard Japanese words!
What are you saying after speaking it so fluently up until now!?
At least decide on some of the choreography today!
We'll work out the awkward spots as we practice!
If there's something you can't figure out,
ask someone you're comfortable talking to!
Miyuki and I will handle the practice scheduling and reserve a suitable location to practice!
We're counting on you here!
Uh...
Kagami-ya?
You were the hardest one to get on board,
but now you seem the most passionate about it.
Shut up!
What are you going to do, Miyuki-san?
I'll be doing tarot readings.
What about you, Tsukasa?
I actually haven't decided yet.
Yuki-chan, can you think of something that even I can do?
Let's see...
How about one that involves reading shapes?
T-This shape...
...means that your love fortune is looking good!
M-Most likely!
Tsukasa.
You made that up just now, didn't you?
What makes you think that?
W-Wait a second!
You expect us to learn all that!?
Is it no good?
Well, it's not a matter of good or bad...
It looks fairly difficult.
We don't have much time,
so we'll just have to simplify some of the harder parts as we go along.
Oh my...
But!
Once we overcome these obstacles,
a great sense of accomplishment awaits us!
You shouldn't be one to talk!
Ah.
We're out of gum-tape.
Guess it can't be helped.
I'll make a run to the store.
Hey, grab some sharpies while you're at it.
And some X-Acto replacement blades, too.
Cardboard!
Playboy.
Glue.
I think I heard some stuff I shouldn't have.
If there's that much stuff that needs to be bought,
stop messing around and go buy it!
What were we calling the yakisoba again?
A Fragrant Breath of Spring.
What about the Fallen Drop of Sunlight?
That's the okonomiyaki.
Man,
you have no idea what's on this menu unless you ask!
Japanese culture is so fun!
Though this project seems to be a bit slanted.
Yahoo!
What are you guys doing?
Um...
I-D Outou Festival Project
ZUKA CAFE 「WIND TROUBLE」
Elisabeth
Lucanor
Lucheni
Leon
Der Tod
Celestina
Delvalles
Joseph
Sophie
Granados
A-A Zuka Café.
W-Wh-
What's that?
Simply put,
it's a place where you can enjoy shows in the spirit of Zuka with the comforts of a café.
With girls in graceful dresses,
and beautiful male attire...
...as your designated waitresses.
Male...?
That's right!
Yu-chan and Minami-chan are the leads!
A dazzling, ever-evolving world of beauty!
When was this decided...
I was nervous about the cheerleading,
but is this going to be okay, too?
Those two are something else.
They sure are.
And they're perfectly in sync.
By the way,
I wonder if that would be considered sadistic on Miyuki-san's part,
or masochistic on Minami-chan's part?
When you put it that way,
Takara-senpai's dynamic dance moves...
...can put quite the pressure on Minami-chan.
Indeed...
Forget that and just practice.
The cheerleading costumes are complete!
They look great!
They're lovely,
but it's slightly embarrassing.
But these kind of costumes are what make the viewers happy.
Exactly.
After all, they were chosen by a person who enjoys watching this sort of stuff.
Oh, the one you mentioned last time.
The dreaded older Tamura brother.
You can look forward to some great Zuka costumes, too!
Speaking of which,
I heard you guys are going to do a cheerleading routine?
Y-Yeah.
Can I take pictures!?
Within reasonable limits.
I'll be careful...
Though the truth is,
we haven't had a successful run-through yet,
so we're a bit worried.
I'll lend you some of my power,
so do your best!
If I get too much of Nee-san's power,
I'm afraid we'll be too energetic and tire ourselves out.
And that's how it is.
We're in quite a bind right now considering how we don't have much time left.
A culture festival?
I wonder what we did for ours?
We had, what you would call,
a "manga café" in today's terms.
All the boys in our class...
...brought their manga collection to share.
Wow.
You guys were ahead of your time.
Though it may seem normal to bring manga to school, nowadays,
back in my day, they were pretty strict about it.
They only let us do it because of the festival.
Well, people do bring it to school,
but it's not like it's officially approved...
A fortune-telling parlor, is it?
Tell everyone to give me a good fortune when I come to visit.
B-But then that wouldn't be fortune-telling...
By the way,
how was it back in your day, Mom?
Each class or club would have their own activity.
A lot of classes did stuff like haunted houses,
or okonomiyaki shops.
Pretty standard stuff.
It's rather strange how...
...things haven't changed much over the years.
By the way,
was something like, "An inquiry regarding cultural objects such as Paulownia dressers,"
ever used as an activity?
What's that?
If we did something like that,
it would be so boring, don't you think?
I guess you're right...
Of course...
Okay, let's take a break!
It looks like we'll be able to put on an exciting performance!
Well, we're not finished yet,
so let's make sure we keep it up until the very end.
It's times like this,
that it's nice to have Hiiragi here to take command!
Well,
I don't want to be the only one left without memories with you guys.
SMIRK
W-What is it!?
Don't look this way!
Sixteenth
Outou Festival
now is your time to shine...
Oh, is that so?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Not at all.
It appears that today is just a rehearsal.
And it's only for students.
And?
It won't be open to the public...
...until tomorrow for people like us.
That's why I told you to check before coming here!
But,
I heard that Akira-chan would be here today.
Ah, geez!
What a waste of a train fare!
16th Outou            Festival
〇    Open to Students              November
〇    Open to General Public   November
If we still had that money,
we could have bought ourselves a hamburger steak or something fancy!
Yeah!
I think it's coming together pretty nicely!
Leave us alone.
Besides,
you're walking around dressed like that?
This way, we can advertise ourselves better.
Kona-chan's get-up is so cute!
Always gotta start with appearances, right?
I'll read lots of fortunes today!
In 5 minutes and 15 seconds,
you will buy some soft-serve ice cream.
At 5 minutes and 28 seconds, you will drop it.
At 7 minutes and 6 seconds,
I think that's foretelling, not fortune-telling.
you will hit your head on a sign.
Too exact!
You guys look great!
But we aren't going to lose either!
I cut it pretty close,
but I finished just in time!
How cute!
It's very lovely.
It's really embarrassing to walk around in this costume, though.
That's some outfit.
Oh, but it's cute!
Senpai.
Kogami Akira is about to go on stage.
Is that so?
I'll be right there.
Nice to meet you, Sensei!
I'm Kogami Akira!
I'm looking forward to today!
Sakuraba.
I am, I mean.
Today's just a rehearsal,
so just take it easy out there while we run some check-ups.
We're counting on you.
Okay, Shiraishi.
You take care of the rest.
Ah, yes.
I'm the culture festival's Executive Committee Chairman Shiraishi.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
I'm going to leave the rest up to Shiraishi,
so just let him know if you need anything.
Please.
Okay!
Hey you,
say something.
You should have just gone to the demon council.
What!
Is something... wrong?
No, it's nothing!
We were just doing some planning,
and got a little too excited!
In any case,
since you are an appreciated guest,
we'll treat you accordingly.
Then?
After this,
we're going to have you do a mic check for Misoji Misaki during Lucky Channel.
Feel free to say whatever you want after the song on stage tomorrow.
I'll do a good job then.
Then,
please get up on the stage.
Damn Shiraishi...
Lucky Channel
That's weak...
Oha-lucky!
Thank you for coming to see Akira, everyone!
I hope you have a great time today!
Longing to be in the arms of the person she loves,
when will such a day come?
As she wanders endlessly,
guided by his words from that day,
she'll go anywhere in order to find a trace.
Here is her song.
Kogami Akira-san with...
...Misoji Misaki.
Would you-
Okay, that's enough!
Hey, what the hell!
Let me sing my song!
I told you it was only a mic test today!
We don't have time!
I don't give a damn!
Ah, I don't understand these difficult Japanese words!
I'm going to kill you, bastard!
Is everybody ready?
This is our last dress-rehearsal!
This was just an idea I had on a whim,
but having the opportunity to do something with all of my friends...
...makes me really happy.
Instead of worrying about success or failure,
I think everyone should just enjoy themselves out there!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
We did it!
It's like, oh my.
Don't you think?
What's this?
You guys are still here?
We were practicing our cheerleading routine.
Is that so?
So how's it going?
Looking forward to it.
Sensei!
I'm thirsty!
I guess it's okay.
I suppose I could buy some drinks for you kids for trying so hard.
Lucky!
Is it really okay?
Don't worry about it.
It's a special occasion, so it's on me.
In return,
promise me you'll make the first event at the culture festival tomorrow a total blast!
Okay!
What's the matter, Tsukasa?
I'm not really sure how to describe it...
It feels kinda strange...
That's right.
Actually, I'm also feeling a little melancholic myself.
They say the most enjoyable part of a festival is when you're preparing for it.
That's right.
Tomorrow's the real deal.
You're right.
We'll probably never stay at school this late again.
When you put it that way, it does feel a bit lonely.
T-Tamura-san,
your face is really strained.
Yeah...
It's just,
my stomach hurts.
Tsukasa, I bet you're frozen stiff.
Speak for yourself.
What happened to your usual cool?
B-Being nervous helps you focus more!
I think I'm so nervous I can't move.
Test. Test.
And now, we will commence the Outou Festival!
The first performance today...
...was submitted by a foreign student, Patricia-san.
A cheerleading routine performed by her group of friends.
I present to you-
Mi-Mirakuru Mikurun run.
If you would please turn off your cell phones.
It's mine!
Crap!
Trouble up until the very end, huh?
I loosened up so much I almost fell!
What timing!
Wasn't that guy so lame?
They say that trouble just tends to follow certain people around.
Well, I guess that's appropriate for us.
How we can ever be completely serious, huh?
Well, then.
Anyway.
Yes!
I'm terribly sorry about that.
Okay!
Now, let's get to our momentum back.
Motteke! Sailor-fuku!
Mata anata no kimagure ga...
Your capricious nature...
Ugokidashita.
...is moving once again.
Kanashii wa...
It's so sad...
Korekkiri ne.
Put an end to it.
Mata ano ko no yume wo miteiruno desho.
Once again you see that girl in your dreams.
Tameiki de...
With a sigh...
So long in my dream...
She is an Angel.
(NO!) She is a devil.
Ah, anata ni totte wa...
Ah, as far as you're concerned...
Amai wana wo kakeru hito.
A girl who set a sweet trap for you.
Anata no ai wa Paradise.
Your love is Paradise...
Kurikaeshita wa kieta.
Repeating over and over but it's now gone.
I love you.
Kuchibiru no naka.
Within these lips.
Moshi ka, moshi ka...
Maybe, just maybe...
Ai wa moshikashite...
Love is perhaps...
Hoori nageta Boomerang.
A boomerang we throw.
Moshi ka, moshi ka...
Maybe, just maybe...
Ai wa moshikashite...
Love is perhaps...
Hoori nageta Boomerang.
A boomerang that we throw.