Outou Festival
Opening Ceremony
Accepting Proposals
A cultural festival, huh?
Guess it's that time of year.
We have tests coming up.
It's such a pain how we have to do so much in the second semester.
That's all you have to say heading into our last cultural festival of high school?
Opening ceremony?
What's this?
Every year during the Outou Festival, groups of people perform at the beginning of the day.
I just had a great idea!
TBA
Bazaar
Maze
Fortune Telling House
Tooth-brushing Exercising
The History of and How to Make Paulownia Cabinets
Now then...
Our class has decided to host a fortune telling house for the festival,
so please come up with your own method of fortune telling before our next homeroom.
Tooth-brushing Exercising
The History of and How to Make Paulownia Cabinets
Haunted House
You worked hard!
I was touched!
And so...
I'm thinking about doing a cheerleading routine!
Cheerleading?
For the opening ceremony we talked about this morning.
It would be the best performance to pump up the festival.
It does sound flashy and fun.
Doesn't it?
We'll be the talk of the town!
B-By we, you mean...
We're part of it?
I asked the teacher,
and was told that the plan must be properly developed, which requires members.
W-What about you, Yutaka?
M-Me?
It might be physically hard on Yu-chan.
Maybe I should give it a try.
I guess I might try if it isn't any trouble...
Trouble?
Absolutely not!
You're very welcome!
W-Will you be okay?
It'll probably be hard,
so I might just hold everyone back,
but I'd like to give it a try this time.
There!
Yutaka's willing to do it.
What do you two say?
In that case...
Well, if everyone's doing it...
I have wonderful friends!
Fortune telling, huh?
But do you even know how to tell fortunes?
Not a clue.
Oh my!
Hey!
Wasn't it your idea?
You can just wing it when it's for a cultural festival.
That's right...
What's your class doing, Onee-chan?
Well...
We're being generic and going the haunted house route.
A classic, huh?
We couldn't come up with any other fun ideas.
Something wrong?
Nah.
I just thought it was very appropriate...
What are you trying to say!?
The real-life demon's angry!
Knew you would say that...
And so...
Patty-chan said she wanted to do cheerleading.
So...
I thought I might work hard at it.
Why?
I'm always absent,
so I never accomplished anything with other people.
But I'm feeling better these days.
What I've been wanting to do,
and what Patty-chan wants to do right now might be the same thing, you know?
But it'll be pretty rough...
And...
We don't have enough people,
so Patty-chan was wondering if you could participate.
So that's how it goes...
You're good at sports...
If people like you and Minami-chan are there,
I might be able to hang in there til the end.
I can tell that you're really serious about this, and Patty's also asking me for help...
Yes?
Hello?
Good evening!
Konata!
It's Patty, huh?
I just heard about your idea and was thinking it over...
Time for a quiz!
I'm holding a certain ticket in my hand right now.
Well...
What do you think the ticket is for?
C-Could it be...
Konata.
You loved the Jam, didn't you?
Don't you want to exchange a hot handshake with Haruhi?
Handshake session!
I wanna go! I wanna go!
Aya in the flesh!
By the way, Konata,
weren't you about to say something?
Yu-chan.
Let's work hard to make some memories!
Which means...
This is the age of cheerleading, girls.
What kind of reasoning is that?
Patty came up with the idea of doing a cheerleading routine during the cultural festival's opening ceremony.
Sounds fitting enough.
Which is why the two of you will also be dancing.
Are there any other people in your class who can dance, Kagami?
H-Hold it right there!
Don't just go on ahead without our permission!
I-I probably can't do that stuff...
But we probably won't get another chance like this.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
We'll be doing it with people we know.
Plus, it's a festival.
It's more fun if we go crazy with everyone.
Really?
You might be right!
You're so easily convinced...
I refuse.
I have to prepare for my class project.
I just wanted to make some memories during our last cultural festival together...
You always bring up friendship out of nowhere!
It's obviously an act!
Yu-chan's really pumped up about this.
But will she be okay?
I told her she shouldn't do it...
But she was really earnest about wanting to accomplish something with everyone.
R-Really...
But you know...
She said that they don't have enough people.
That's how I got involved.
I guess I was a little forceful about it.
I shouldn't push people into this.
I'll just ask someone else.
Fine...
What?
Fine!
I'll do it!
Onee-chan!
Really?
I can't help it.
My class can just replace me with someone else,
but you guys can't do that.
Kagami sure is cute.
C-Cheerleading, is it?
I'm not confident I'd do a good job...
Well...
We're not too sure about a lot of things right now...
BOING
Especially in terms of volume.
I'd feel a lot better if you joined us!
Is that so?
I understand.
If I can be of help...
Thanks, Boin-
I mean, Miyuki-san...
Testing is over,
so we'll be focusing on preparations for the cultural festival,
but don't get too relaxed!
Honestly...
They could cut down on testing when we have school events...
Yo!
Hey, Konata.
What's going on with the cheerleading thing?
That reminds me...
Before testing started...
"They approved the plan!"
...is what I heard...
But I haven't heard anything since.
What!?
How irresponsible!
We're not gonna have enough time to practice at this rate...
Or actually...
It's already too late!
Guess we'll go ask.
Sorry!
I haven't worked out the choreography yet!
Haven't worked out the choreography?
What are we supposed to do then!?
It's also taking time to pick a song.
It's not easy to find something on Sunny Sunshiny's level.
What was that?
Anyway...
If you were having trouble,
you should have asked other people for help.
This was your idea,
so you need to be responsible for scheduling!
So many difficult Japanese words I don't know!
How can you say that when you've done perfectly fine up until now!?
At least get some of the choreography done today!
We'll work out the kinks as we practice!
Ask someone who's free if you can't figure something out!
Miyuki and I can handle general scheduling and reserve a practice location!
We're counting on you!
Kagami...
You were pretty against this idea,
but like, you're the most passionate one here.
Be quiet!
What are you going to do, Miyuki-san?
I'll be using tarot cards.
And what about you, Tsukasa?
I haven't decided yet...
Yuki-chan.
Is there something even I could do?
Let's see...
How about one that involves reading shapes?
T-This shape means that your love fortune is good...
...m-most likely!
Tsukasa.
You just made that up, didn't you?
Y-Ya think so?
W-Wait a second!
You want us to learn this!?
It's no good?
It's not an issue of quality...
It looks fairly difficult.
We don't have much time.
Shouldn't we just simplify the harder parts as we go?
Oh my...
But if we get through this, a wonderful feeling of satisfaction awaits us!
You shouldn't be saying that!
We're out of tape.
It can't be helped.
I'll make a trip to the store.
Then grab magic markers while you're at it.
And some exacto refills.
Cardboard!
Playboy.
Glue.
Something weird got mixed up in there...
And if we need to buy so much stuff,
stop playing around and go buy it!
What are we calling the yakisoba?
Breath of Fragrant Spring.
What's this Fallen Drop of Sunlight?
That's okonomiyaki.
Man...
You can't tell what's what on this menu!
Japanese culture is so fun.
This project seems to be abusing stereotypes...
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Um...
I-D Outou Festival Project
ZUKA CAFE 「WIND TROUBLE」
Elisabeth
Lucanor
Lucheni
Leon
Der Tod
Celestina
Delvalles
Joseph
Sophie
Granados
A-A Zuka café.
W-What is this?
Basically...
It's a café where you can enjoy shows in the spirit of Zuka.
With girls in shiny dresses and beautiful girls in male clothing serving as waitresses.
Two for one!
Male clothing?
That's right!
Yu-chan and Minami-chan are the leads!
In their dazzling, beautiful world!
When was this decided...
I'm also worried about the cheerleading,
but is this going to work?
Those two are something else.
You're very good, Minami-san.
They sure are.
Then let's try it again.
And they're perfectly in rhythm.
Okay!
By the way...
Wouldn't that be considered sadistic on the part of Miyuki-san,
or masochistic on the part of Minami-chan?
When you put it that way...
Takara-senpai's dynamic dance moves are probably putting pressure on Minami-chan.
Ya think so?
Just forget that and practice.
The cheerleading costumes are complete!
It looks great!
It looks wonderful,
but it's a bit embarrassing.
These kinds of costumes make the people watching it happier.
In fact, this outfit was chosen by someone who likes to watch.
The one you mentioned last time...
The dreadful, older Tamura brother.
You can expect some great Zuka costumes, too!
That's right...
You guys are doing a cheerleading routine?
Can I take pictures!?
Within reasonable limits.
I'll be careful...
Well...
We haven't done it successfully yet,
so we're pretty worried.
I'll use my power to charge you up,
so work hard!
Your power might charge us up so much we tire ourselves out.
Basically like that.
It's pretty rough considering how we have no time left.
A cultural festival, huh?
What did we do for ours?
We had what you now call, you know, a manga café.
All the boys in our class brought in their manga.
So you guys were ahead of your time.
It may seem normal to bring manga nowadays,
but back when we were in school, they were strict about it.
You could only do it during festivals.
Well, people bring it to school,
but it's not really approved...
A fortune telling house, is it?
Let everyone know to give me a good fortune if I come.
B-But that wouldn't be fortune telling...
By the way...
How was it when you were in school?
I think each class or club had their own project.
The projects were stuff like haunted houses and okonomiyaki vendors...
Mostly standard fare.
It's rather strange how it doesn't seem much has changed.
By the way,
was a study of a cultural item, such as Paulownia cabinets, ever used as a project?
What's that?
That wouldn't be any fun at all, now would it?
You're right...
Absolutely right...
Okay!
Time for a break!
It looks like we can pull off an exciting performance.
Well...
It's not complete yet...
So hang in there til the very end.
This is when it's a big help to have Hiiragi here to take command.
Well...
I don't want to be the only one left out of the memory.
SMIRK
W-What is it!?
Don't stare at me!
Sixteenth
Outou Festival
now is your time to shine...
My...
Is that so?
I'm terribly sorry about that.
No trouble at all.
It appears that today's a rehearsal,
and only students are allowed.
So?
We, the general public,
can't get in until tomorrow.
That's why I told you to check before coming here!
But...
I heard that Akira-chan would be here today.
Geez!
What a waste of train fare!
16th Outou            Festival
〇    Open to Students              November
〇    Open to General Public   November
If we still had that money,
we could have had hamburger steak or something fancy!
Yeah...
I really dig this feeling of incompleteness.
Leave us alone.
And like, you're walking around in that?
This serves as advertising.
Your costume's cute, Kona-chan!
Gotta start from the appearance.
I'll read lots of fortunes today!
In five minutes and fifteen seconds, you will buy soft-serve ice cream...
At five minutes and twenty-eight seconds, you will drop it on your leg.
Fortune telling doesn't mean to predict the future.
At seven minutes and six seconds, you will hit your head on a sign.
Word for word!?
You guys look great.
But we're just as good!
It took us until the very last second,
but we're finally done!
So cute!
You look wonderful.
It's really embarrassing to walk around in this costume...
That's some outfit...
Oh, but it's cute.
Chief.
Kogami Akira's about to go on stage.
Really...
I'll be right there.
Nice to meet you, Sensei.
I'm Kogami Akira!
I'll work hard today!
Sakuraba.
I am, I mean.
Today's like a rehearsal,
so we'll be just running some check-ups...
Countin' on you.
Hey, Shiraishi.
You handle the rest.
Yes.
I'm the cultural festival planning committee chair, Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure.
I'm letting Shiraishi handle the rest,
so let him know if you need something.
Please.
Okay!
Hey, you.
Say something.
You should have gone to the demon council.
Is something... wrong?
No, nothing's wrong!
We were going through things and got a little too excited!
Anyway...
You're an appreciated guest,
so we'll treat you accordingly.
So?
After this,
we'll need a mic check for Cape of Thirty Years on Lucky Channel.
Feel free to say whatever you want after the song on stage tomorrow.
Well, I'll do a good job of it.
Then...
Please head to the stage.
Damn Shiraishi...
Lucky Channel
Weak...
Good lucky!
Thank you for coming to see Akira, everyone!
I hope you have lots of fun today!
She longs to be in the arms of her beloved...
Will such a day ever come?
As she drifts alone,
guided by his words from that day...
She'll go anywhere in search of a trace...
Here's a song.
Kogami Akira-san with...
...Cape of Thirty Years.
Would you mi-
Okay, that's enough!
Goddamn it!
Let me sing my song!
I told you it was just a check!
We don't have time!
Like I give a damn!
So many difficult Japanese words I don't know!
I'm going to kill you, bastard!
Is everybody ready?
This is the last run through.
I came up with this idea a little spontaneously,
but the fact that I've been given a chance to do something with everyone...
...makes me really happy.
Instead of worrying about success or failure,
I just think we should have fun!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
We did it!
It's like, holy cow.
Ya think so?
What's this?
You're still here?
We were practicing our cheerleading routine.
Really.
So how's it going?
Can't wait to see it.
Sensei!
I'm thirsty!
Guess it's okay.
I suppose I can buy drinks for hardworking young people.
Lucky!
Is it really okay?
Sure thing.
This is a special case, though.
In return,
be sure to make the first event at the festival a real blast!
Okay!
What's up, Tsukasa?
How should I put it...
It kinda feels strange.
That's right.
Actually, I'm also feeling a bit melancholic.
They say you have the most fun when preparing for a festival.
That's right...
Tomorrow's the real thing.
That's right.
We may never stay at school so late again.
You feel a bit lonely when you look at it that way.
T-Tamura-san...
Your face is really strained.
Yeah...
Like...
My stomach hurts...
Tsukasa...
You're frozen stiff, aren't you?
You don't look so calm yourself.
B-Being nervous helps you concentrate!
I think I'm so nervous I can't move.
Test. Test.
Then we will now begin the Outou Festival!
The first performance today was submitted by a foreign student, Patricia-san.
A cheerleading routine performed by a group of friends.
Then let's begin...
U-Uh, sorry.
Cell phones should...
It's mine!
Crap!
Running into trouble at the very end!
That relaxed me so much I almost fell!
Great timing!
Wasn't that guy so lame?
They say that trouble tends to follow people around.
Well, I guess this is appropriate for us.
How could we ever be serious, huh?
Okay, well...
Y'know...
Yes!
Sorry about that!
I'm really sorry!
Okay!
Then, let's try that again!
Take it! Sailor Uniform!
Mata anata no kimagure ga...
Your capricious nature...
Ugokidashita.
...is moving once again.
Kanashii wa...
It's so sad...
Korekkiri ne.
Put an end to it.
Mata ano ko no yume wo miteiruno desho.
Once again you see that girl in your dreams.
Tameiki de...
With a sigh...
So long in my dream...
She is an Angel.
(NO!) She is a devil.
Ah, anata ni totte wa...
Ah, as far as you're concerned...
Amai wana wo kakeru hito.
A girl who set a sweet trap for you.
Anata no ai wa Paradise.
Your love is Paradise...
Kurikaeshita wa kieta.
Repeating over and over but it's now gone.
I love you.
Kuchibiru no naka.
Within these lips.
Moshi ka, moshi ka...
Maybe, just maybe...
Ai wa moshikashite...
Love is perhaps...
Hoori nageta Boomerang.
A boomerang we throw.
Moshi ka, moshi ka...
Maybe, just maybe...
Ai wa moshikashite...
Love is perhaps...
Hoori nageta Boomerang.
A boomerang that we throw.