I'm sorry, Homura.
I'll become a magical girl.
Madoka...
No!
I finally understand.
I've found a wish I want fulfilled.
And I'm going to trade my life for it.
Wait!
If you do that...
If you do that, I...
Why have I...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
You've always, always always, protected me, always looked out for me...
I'm really sorry for doing this.
But it's the answer I found.
Believe in me.
I won't waste everything you've done for me.
Madoka...
For you, whose karma binds all worlds together...
Any wish, no matter how absurd, can be granted.
I know.
Well, Madoka Kaname.
What do you wish for in exchange for your soul?
I...
I want to erase all witches from existence, before they're even born!
Every witch, past and future, in the universe! With my own hands!
That wish...
Granting that wish doesn't just break temporal coherence!
It violates the very laws of karma!
Do you really desire to become a goddess?
I'll become a goddess. It doesn't matter.
I don't want to let any of the magical girls who clung to hope as they battled witches cry.
I want them to smile until the end.
If there are rules against it, I'll break them. Or change them.
This is my wish.
This is my prayer.
Grant it, Incubator!
Episode 12 My best friend
Kaname, you understand how frightful of a wish that is, right?
I guess.
You'll be drawn into unending battle. In the past, in the future, throughout time.
Someday you may change your mind.
It isn't as simple as just dying.
You'll exist for all eternity as a force of nature, killing witches.
That's okay. That's what I want.
He says embracing hope is a mistake, but he's wrong.
No matter how many times he says so, I won't change my mind.
I'll insist. Forever.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Everyone has to draw a line somewhere.
You found your reason.
You decided not to run away, right?
Then there it is!
You've just gotta keep going!
Thanks, Kyoko.
I guess I should give this back to you then.
Here you go.
Don't just fulfill hopes.
Become hope itself.
All of our hopes...
I won't let them end unfulfilled or in despair.
You don't have to curse anyone.
You don't have to work dark magic on anyone.
I'll take on all of your karmic burdens.
So believe in yourselves all the way to the end!
That's enough.
It's enough.
You don't need to hold a grudge against anyone.
You don't need to curse anyone anymore.
I'll protect you before you even take that form.
Where am I?
The universe is changing to accommodate Madoka's new laws of nature.
I see...
You want to travel time again, don't you?
First, let's see the results of Madoka Kaname's existence.
This is the Soul Gem her wish brought forth.
Amazing...
Do you understand the size of the curse Madoka must bear in exchange for such a wish?
Enough hope to give birth to a new universe...
Means enough despair to bring an end to the old one.
It's only natural.
It's okay.
My wish will destroy all witches.
If it's really granted...
Even I...
Have no reason to despair!
Madoka... With this, your own life loses its beginning and its end.
No proof, no memories, remain of your time in this world.
Your existence has become that of a force of nature.
No one will recognize you, and you will recognize no one.
You will no longer be part of this universe.
What!?
Is that really what Madoka wants!?
Is this her reward!?
This can't be happening!
This is worse than dying!
It's terrible!
Terrible!
No, Homura.
I can see all of the past and future now.
Even universes which may never have happened.
Even those which may never happen.
Everyone...
Madoka...
So I understand everything now.
How hard you pushed yourself for my sake.
Everything.
Crying again and again, being hurt so much...
Yet you kept trying...
I'm so sorry I never noticed what you were doing for my sake...
By becoming who I am now, I was able to understand you.
I never knew I had such a dear friend...
So I'm happy.
Thank you, Homura.
You're my best friend.
But you have nowhere to go home to! You'll never see your loved ones again!
You'll be trapped here alone, forever!
I'm not alone.
I'll be with everyone forever.
Anywhere, anytime.
Even if you can't see me, even if you can't hear me, I'll be by your side.
Is that all you want?
Even though I'll forget you!?
Even though I'll never see your face again!?
Don't give up yet.
If you can be with me even here...
Even when you return to your world...
You may just remember me.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
Let's believe!
Madoka...
Magical girls make dreams and hopes come true!
So this little miracle could happen!
Right?
Don't leave me, Madoka!
I'm sorry. I need to go be with everyone.
Someday we'll meet again.
This is just goodbye until then.
Madoka!
Number 25, Kyosuke Kamijo.
I'll be playing...
Ave Maria.
Sorry to cause you so much trouble.
Don't worry about it. I should be apologizing to you.
I wasn't able to do anything to save you...
If I had, this future would have disappeared too.
But that's probably what you would have wanted.
Everything you wished for... Everything you worked so hard for...
I thought you cared so much about it that you absolutely wouldn't want it undone.
So...
This is fine.
Yeah. I just wanted to hear him play one more time.
I wanted to let more people hear him play the violin.
I'm satisfied just thinking of that.
I have no regrets.
Well, it hurts a little, but I can't hold it against Hitomi.
She's a great match for Kyosuke.
I know they'll be happy together.
Let's go.
Sayaka...
Where's Sayaka!?
Hey! What happened to Sayaka!?
She's gone.
She has completed the circle.
Miki... Used all her power on that attack.
That idiot...
Sacrificing herself for the guy she likes? What's wrong with her!?
Such an idiot...
We were finally friends, and then...
That's the fate of magical girls.
We know it the moment we receive this power.
We strive for hope, but disappear like that before we can curse this world.
Madoka...
Akemi?
Madoka?
Who's that?
Madoka! Madoka!
Yeah.
It looks just like her.
No, Tatsuya!
You don't pull girls' hair!
Madoka! Madoka!
Sorry, was he bothering you?
No, I came up to him.
Madoka, huh...
Here I come!
Come on!
Gotcha!
Well...
He has an imaginary friend he talks to when he's playing alone.
I guess it's pretty common at his age.
I remember having one.
Have you heard of this Madoka?
Is she an anime character or something?
I'm not really sure.
I'm not sure, maybe I've heard of her somewhere or something...
Oh, okay.
I kind of feel like I saw her with Tatsuya somewhere too.
Sometimes her name really, really sounds familiar.
Madoka...
I see.
That ribbon's really cute! I'm amazed, it looks just like something I'd pick out!
Would you like it?
It wouldn't look right on an old lady like me.
If I had a daughter, maybe I'd pick it out for her.
I see.
Your theory makes sense.
It's not a theory. It's the truth.
But there's no way to prove it.
If the laws of nature were rewritten like you say,
we'd have no way to find out.
If you're the only one who remembers it, there's no distinguishing it from a fantasy of yours.
I mean, I have no explanation for why faded Soul Gems disappear.
Your explanation of a force of nature is very interesting.
The idea of gathering humans' emotional energy like that certainly has its appeal.
If we had a neat trick like that, we Incubators might operate completely differently.
I guess that's how you are.
The Magical Beasts we fight now didn't exist in this world of witches you speak of, correct?
That seems like a much more convenient way of gathering curses.
It isn't that simple.
Our relations with you were a lot less friendly, too.
I really don't understand human values.
Even in a world without witches,
curses have not disappeared.
Something else, in a different form, aims at humanity from the shadows.
They're serious tonight.
Something really has the Magical Beasts in an uproar.
They just don't stop coming!
Complaining won't help anything.
Let's go.
Even if the world will never see an end to suffering and pain,
it's the world she strove to protect.
I remember.
I will never forget.
So I will keep fighting!
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Do your best.