My name is Jibril.
What can I do for you, new king and queen
of the Imanity, Lord Sora and Lady Shiro?
You know us?
That makes this easier, then.
Guess I'll just tell you.
I want this library.
I never wanted to become just another cog in the machine
My life had become hell because I was pretending to be average
But then God frivolously took me to a new stage
To the world of no game no life
Where I can do away with my boring everyday life
And engrave my name on the stairway to glory
I now see a destiny of flawless victory for myself
I'll change everything precisely the way I want
As an untainted blank
I no longer care about salvation in my real life
I don't know what the future holds, but if all that matters is to win
Then I'll put my strategy and talent to work and stay undefeated
I'm enjoying my new life to the fullest
Believing in myself
You want my library?
That's so very sudden.
Steph, the Flugel were god-killing warriors, right?
Th-They're supposed to be!
You caught me completely en guard—er, off guard.
Interesting
She corrected herself.
Listen, I can't tell if you're trying to be cute or imitating a famous person,
but you should drop it alread—
What?
I had thought it an avant-garde and unique way of speaking,
but somebody got there ahead of me?
Is it worth getting upset over?
Let's get back to the point.
You want my library.
Does that mean that you want to challenge me to a game, human?
Yeah, that's right.
I see.
Before the introduction of the ten pledges,
the Flugel collected severed heads.
However, now that murder is forbidden,
we value knowledge above anything else.
It's no exaggeration to say
that books containing that knowledge,
and the place where they are held, are as valuable as one's life.
Since you're telling me to bet my life,
what are you offering to bet in exchange?
More than 40,000 books from another world.
That's disgusting.
It's okay, Shiro.
In our business, that's a prize!
F-F-Forty thousand...
That's quite a prize.
Where do you have...
Inside here.
I got them to study for quiz games.
Dictionaries, medical books, philosophy books...
It's full of information from our world.
Are you telling me you're from another world?
Yes.
That's impossible.
Hey, what's she talking about?
Um...
If you were going to summon a living creature from another world,
you would need a massive amount of power to keep them here.
Even the Old Deus would find it extremely difficult.
I don't really get it, but I can prove it.
Look at this. Not sure if you can read it...
What are you saying?
I can speak every one of the over 700 languages—
A language... A language I don't know?
An encyclopedia from a world I don't know?
All that knowledge inside this little board?
40,000 books of it!
H-Hey! You're drooling! You're drooling!
Excuse me.
I see.
I am indeed interested in this thin board,
but it is a fact that I still can't trust that you're from another world.
So what do we do?
Let me check your bodies.
Check our bodies?
Why would you do that?
What are you checking, anyway?
Your erogenous zones.
Take all the time you need.
In fact, take more time than you need.
You're an awfully easy sell...
Brother... That's for adults only...
That's right!
Then just don't take off the pants.
And since I'm letting you touch my erogenous zones,
you should let me touch yours!
What are you saying? There's no way—
Sure. That's perfectly fine.
What?! It is?!
Hey...
Yes?
Do you not enjoy the way it feels to the touch?
No, it feels wonderful.
Surprisingly so.
But...
What is this? I just feel a little... betrayed.
Anticlimactic.
Is this not one of your erogenous zones?
It would tarnish my pride as a man to admit it.
And I'll add that I was hoping you'd touch me somewhere else.
But...
All of our power comes from what are called our Spirit Circuits.
Our wings, where those collect,
are a very erogenous...
Master of Touch-Type H-Games
You like that? Right here?
When you touch them so precisely like that...
What are you doing?!
Sister, I'm just touching her wings.
Right?
Right. It's super-healthy.
What are these two doing? She's a god-killing weapon!
My investigation reveals no spirits whatsoever in your bodies.
In other words, you two aren't even strictly defined as a life-form in this world,
but you have the appearance of Imanity.
So that makes us...
What?
Unknown
Unknown!
You are the unknown!
That's the source from which new knowledge is born!
There is nothing in this world as wonderful as the unknown!
Well, I guess I can assume we've proven we're not from this world?
That's right.
Please forgive me for assuming that you were mere Imanity.
Mere Imanity
Of course, I'll accept the game.
But I don't really have much that's worth 40,000 books from another world.
I told you, I want the library—
How about I bet everything I have instead?
Seriously?
Lucky me...
Acquire a Flugel
Will that be all right?
Yes, we want full rights to you, personally.
Acquire a Flugel
Thank you!
Oh, can I add in that you have to come by for tea once in a while?
I want to know more about you two.
You're talking like you've already won.
Then if we win, we can add an extra demand of our own, yes?
Yes.
You won't win, of course,
but if you do, then whatever you want is yours.
We'll play the word chain game.
But not exactly.
We'll play the Materialization Word Chain Game.
Materialization Word Chain Game?
Yes.
The rules are simple.
Just like a normal word chain game,
Use a word that's already been used
If you use a word that's already been used,
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
Use a word that's already been used
fail to answer for 30 seconds,
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
Use a word that's already been used
or cannot continue, you lose.
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Can the words be in any language?
Yes,
but fictional things that don't actually exist won't count.
Flight Stone
Materialization Word Chain Game
And remember, we're playing the Materialization Word Chain Game.
Tallow
If you say something that's here, it will disappear.
Whale
If it's not here, it will appear.
I'm sure you know what this means.
Of course,
once the game's over, everything that's happened will be undone,
so don't hesitate to show off your knowledge.
Got it.
Okay, Shiro. Come over here.
We'll do this together, like we always do.
That's fine.
You're powerless humans, so enjoy yourselves and try not to die.
What? W-Wait...
Die?
You can't directly cause a player to die,
that is, to be unable to continue.
Then I don't need to be here, do I?
That's only dangerous for—
Now, then...
Yes, let's begin the game.
Come and get us.
Listen to me!
Steph, sit!
Pet Dog for a Day
Now I can't run away!
I've had it with this!
You may have the first move.
Pick any word you like.
Let me see...
Okay, I'll start with...
Hydrogen Bomb.
Hydrogen Bomb
What's this?
Bkulians!
Self-destructing on the first move?
Hydrogen Bomb
That was Bkulians, a highest-level sealing spell.
Bkulians
Hydrogen Bomb
If I hadn't been nice enough to protect you,
the game would've ended here.
Nice enough? Gimme a break.
Bkulians!
I just took a gamble on the obvious fact that you'd think ending the game
in a single move would be terribly boring.
I see.
Still, I had predicted as much,
but it doesn't look like we'll be able to stop you from continuing the game.
I'm glad you understand.
Try not to bore me, please.
Don't worry. I won't bore you.
Bkulians
Spirit Circuits
Spirit Circuits.
Bkulians
Spirit Circuits
Well, you certainly wasted no time.
It's a word I just learned.
What? Is that a problem?
No, it limits my physical abilities a bit and prevents me from flying,
but I still have spirits in my body, so there's no problem.
If anything, it just makes me a little uneasy...
Oh, like when your cell phone can't get reception.
Cell phone? Reception?
Do they have something to do with that thin board?
Close! Close! Close! Your face is too close!
If you beat me, I'll tell you!
Brother, I think she's...
Yeah, this is getting even more fun.
Hey, Jibril. Your move.
Spirit Circuits
Th-That's right.
I'll do an easy one. Stallions.
Spirit Circuits
Stallions
Okay. Snatch.
Snatch
Stallions
Well?
Wh-Wh-Wh—
What the hell are you thinking?!
I'm getting a little tired of all this dust.
Let's have some fun.
Sea Shore
Sea shore.
It's very pretty, yes, but it's rough on someone who never leaves the house!
Sea Shore
Erect Nipples
Okay, erect nipples!
Sea Shore
Erect Nipples
I'll play along, then.
String Bikinis
Erect Nipples
String bikinis.
Jibril, you don't understand at all!
If you want bikinis, you need to get rid of the clothes first!
I see!
I'm sorry, I couldn't understand what you were getting at.
Would you two at least try to take this seriously?
String Bikinis
Whatever. Suitcases.
Suitcases
String Bikinis
Let me see, then...
Suitcases
Sea Breeze
How about "sea breeze," then?
Hey, what are you doing?!
It all worked out in the end, Jibril!
Steph's not wearing panties, so without the bikini, this would be for adults only!
But a glimpse of a bikini under a skirt is pretty good, too!
I'm glad to hear it!
And now, it'll be complete!
Sea Breeze
Every Girl's Clothes
Every girl's clothes!
No!
How do you like that, sister?
No private parts at all!
And we've still got the shoes, knee socks, and collar!
In other words, it's even more excellent than pure nudity!
Clearly suitable for all-ages!
Very healthy!
Moderately sexy, but not dirty at all!
We should call this...
The "Super Healthy Space!"
Brother, Omega Good Job!
What are you trying to do here?!
Hey, Jibril, do you get hungry?
Mantle
Mantle.
Don't worry about me.
Unlike you powerless Imanity, we don't need to eat.
Mantle
Eccentric moth comic
Eccentric moth comic.
Let's be together!
I see.
But you get tired, right?
Eccentric moth comic
The sun'll come up soon. Think you could just surrender?
Crust
Eccentric moth comic
Crust.
If you're tired, feel free to lose deliberately.
Crust
I've had more fun than I expected to get from a weak Imanity.
Timepiece
Crust
Timepiece.
Timepiece
You keep saying "weak" and whatnot, and it's getting on my nerves.
Evil creature
Timepiece
Evil monster.
Evil creature
Well, to a mighty rank 6 like you,
I'm sure those down at the bottom must look like ants.
I'm saved...
But who decided that ants are weak and powerless?
I apologize.
I hadn't considered that you
Imanity would consider yourselves anything but weak.
If you think long life and toughness gives you power,
you're the stupid one here.
You're saying I'm inferior to the Imanity?
My feelings towards you are best described as curiosity, not respect.
Don't forget that I could end this game any time I like.
Evil creature
Eye Fuel
Eye fuel.
Evil creature
Eye Fuel
And that's why you're weak.
That's what makes you an empty-headed academic.
Empty-headed academic?
Yup. Empty-headed academic. It means you don't know how things work in the real world.
Remember that.
Obviously, I know what that phrase means.
What makes you think I'm an empty-headed academic?
Instead of respecting the unknown, you're merely curious.
It's time for a lesson.
Now you'll learn
how weak you really are.
Steph, thanks for the hard work.
If you hadn't kept all the dangerous crap off of us,
we couldn't have won.
You think you've won?
So, Steph, this'll kill you a little, but tough it out, okay?
Huh?
Eye Fuel
Lithosphere
Lithosphere!
Lithosphere.
The surface of the planet.
Because you didn't understand what it meant,
I was able to erase the mantle and crust
that I had strategically named first.
You fail to fear and respect the unknown.
That's what makes you weak, Jibril!
I see.
That's why you got rid of the Spirit Circuits to cripple my wings.
It has a core temperature of 6,000 degrees,
and a surface temperature of 3,000 degrees, I suppose.
I see you're still trying to kill me.
I won't let morning come yet.
Lithosphere
Eos lumo
Eos lumo.
Oxygen
Eos lumo
Oxygen.
Oxygen
You stopped me from breathing,
but it's useless.
Oxygen
Still, I'll have a little more fun with you.
Nodes
Oxygen
Nodes.
Nodes
Damn it... Sepia.
Sepia
Nodes
You're making this easier than I thought.
Sepia
Okay, then.
Air.
Air
Sepia
Once the air comes back, I can breathe...
Why?
I was right!
Jibril doesn't know atomic theory!
You thought if you couldn't breathe, all you had to do was bring back the air,
but all I got rid of was oxygen.
The rules say that what's there disappears and what isn't there appears.
Okay, then.
Air.
The other gases disappeared and oxygen came back.
In other words, all that's here is oxygen,
a deadly poison at a far lower pressure than your own body
that your body can't absorb on its own.
But it's no different for you.
What?
Circular breathing.
This is the big difference between you and us.
Let's go, Shiro.
Air
Real Atmosphere
Real atmosphere.
Atmosphere...
The zero-pressure environment created by the disappearance of the
atmosphere will cause the air inside you to expand and burst.
You didn't know why we got rid of all the air in our bodies, did you?
Still, it is useless...
My voice?
You can't speak in a vacuum.
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
Cannot continue
Use a word that's already been used
Fail to answer for thirty seconds
If you can't answer in thirty seconds...
I lose, then.
I see.
It's a shame you're just Imanity.
This time I'll answer you
with thanks and respect.
Real Atmosphere
Empty-headed Academic
Do you understand?
This difference is a wall
that the Imanity will never be able to overcome.
You have no way to answer me.
In the end, you will lose
because of the soundless world and burning land you created.
I've won.
Empty-headed Academic
Force
Coulomb's
When Coulomb's force vanishes
and all that's left is nuclear force that draws atoms together,
the result is the astronomical phenomenon that normally
only occurs by the gravitational collapse of supermassive planets.
A hypernova, capable of destroying stars dozens of light years away.
It's got a temperature of
50 billion degrees Celsius, rivaling the dawn of creation.
Just try and survive that, Flugel!
So that was it.
He's right.
Even if I die only a fraction of a second earlier, I still lose.
That first explosion was simply
to see if he could use words his opponent didn't know.
That explosion gave him all the information he needed.
Everything that happened after that was simply a farce to keep me distracted.
The game was over after the first move, wasn't it?
People from another world— no, the Imanity...
They are a terrifying race.
I died.
Oh, welcome back.
You used me as a decoy,
and then you killed me!
You monster! Oh, the humanity!
I mean, Imanity!
Steph, beg.
Still a pet dog for the day
This is still going on?
To Sora and Shiro, "Today" means "Until they go to bed"
Well, I'm sure you have some complaints,
but if it weren't for you, we would've lost.
Thanks, Steph.
I lost completely.
No matter how well you tried to tempt me,
there was no guarantee I'd answer with "empty-headed academic."
You're insane, aren't you?
I'm challenging God.
I couldn't do that if I were sane.
Challenging God?
It was Tet who called us to this world.
The only option we have is to beat him.
So, Jibril,
in accordance with the pledges, everything you have belongs to us.
Oh, and the books on my tablet were just bait.
You can read them all you want.
You can keep using the library, too.
Oh, my dear departed master!
Artosh, the one who created us.
At last I have achieved our long-held dream of finding
someone worthy to serve as our new master.
An Imanity, who looks down on the elves, and on me,
and who will overturn everything we think we know.
My master, my lord,
I, Jibril, member of the Council of 18 Wings of the Exceed Rank 6 Flugel,
offer everything I have to you.
I will find no greater pleasure than carrying out your will.
Yeah, leave it to us.
Right, Shiro?
Yes.
Leave it to us.
Wait, how long am I supposed to keep acting like a dog?
With a loneliness
That no one else could see, I was crying all alone
We could never bring ourselves to smile
But the moment we met, we smiled
In the dead of the night,
we delved into our imagination
And shared all the feelings
we didn't know what to do with
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
We waved goodbye to sadness
And someday
We'll light up our empty hearts
By piecing together the fragments of expressions we find
Our own little world will never end
Like we're praying to the sky
Let's soar high into eternity
Sacrifice
I used to be a gamer like you. Then I took an arrow in the knee...
Stop!