(#&@irc.rizon.net presents: Ro-Kyu-Bu! SS 07
Due to complaints that our font uses shadow effects, we have removed them and instead would like to give you a feeling of nostalgia. Enjoy!)
No, you came well, young male Charles
Nice to meet you! I am the breasts of magic.
Oh...
This hurts...
There's also the me of doing the magical couch, but...
Kyou is a special fire!
No smoking.
Why?
Garts, magical magic and young male Charles!
What is cognac?
Magic, this hurts! Why?
Am I going to make cognac with a car? I don't even!
Cognac is that thing where you live in the same house and make children, right?
Hauauau, that's Vodka.
Parents? Magic, is a tragic misunderstanding taking place here??
Dear father, you are making a huge mistake!
Subaru is a large company with investors from all over the world!
Therefore, you need to take into consideration the opinion of every board member!
This is all so wrong
What a twist.
Magic was telling me about Charles so gladly
I almost though there was some sort of a metaphysical connection
Metaphysics~
I'm sorry, Charles
Maybe I should stop using shamanistic rituals for business analysis
om nom nom
W-What is it?
Dirk is right, yo, you a fine ass man
I feel that Dirk will be A-Okay in your care
Thank ya
Nigga, I say you Charles is the best coach there is!
Amirite?
Oyus
Thats rite
Oh~, Charles is a radical dude~
He sure is
Ok, alright, I see
You seem to have broken them in well
It wasn't that hard, really
I'm glad y'all could make it to my birthday today
I had a grand time playing pin the tail on Zimmerman
Anything else you guys want to do?
No, I want to go home
r u sure?
Your own ape-hoop court
tickets to watch ape-hoop live,
I can even invite former slaves to come play!
What?
Oh daddy, you're awesome!
So, Charle's, what'll it be?
That sounds cool and all, but I'm no racist
Actually,
I got an idea...
Whoah! Dirk caught in compromising positions!
She flat
That navel, though, unf~
I'd completely ravage that blonde pussy
She is the enemy and all, but damn
I bet Kobe's all over that every night
I will break that ass off
Heh, just wait Dirk
We're coming for your anus
Kobe's team will be hard to beat
And the'yre better than us in every way
If only we could get an advantage
There's gotta be something out there to help
Not enough time to do anything radical
This is all very true
I know, I know
Let's just start practicing
Hey guys, I think I know how we can get ahead
Ahead?
This mite b cool
Mike!
Mike, it's finally happening, yo!
That girl you wanna pop
O really?
Finally, we can meet each other!
I sure am tired, yo
This training menu is rough...
It's a special training menu that Charles thought of for the tournament.
What's even in this food?
LeBron, are you okay?
Oh~, I feel my muscles powerin' up
An' mah stamina increasin'
I wonder what the 5th graders are doing
I won't lose to those bustas!
Gotta werk! Get Big! Get Tough!
Take a Xanax
Charles said
Just take the food and formulas and you'll win
Oh~, I sho' feel it workin
Same here
We got this far thanks to Charles
We couldn't enter official tournaments.
And now he prepared such a fantastic stage!
We must give it our best shot and win!
Yeah!
I'm so done...I can't go on
Carry on...my wayward son
GG FAGS
LAST GAME FOR TODAY
Fuck running, we ain't a track team
Is this your special menu?
We ain't even shootin' hoops
Anne Donovan's such a bitch today
Screw you nigger! You're practicing on your own!
That's what I said!
Fuck you talking about, bitch?
At least I'm not the one taking HGH?
YOU'RE TAKING HGH?
Yeah, so what?
Everybody shut the fuck up!
Breathe...in...out
Maybe we should all start taking HGH
Huh?
W-Why?!
We're pretty weak, aren't we?
Can't even bench 300
Do you call this a team?
If you enter now, you'll just get wrecked by the 6th graders
Can we really beat them with HGH?
I can't say for sure
But we're damn well going to try
HGH, huh?
I've never taken drugs before...
I did meth with my sister once
Do needles hurt?
I can't wait to get jacked up on roids
If we want to beat the 6th graders
We'll need to supplement our HGH with protein shakes
and high-fiber diets
What are we a high school football team?
Grade schoolers are the best!
It can't be helped.
I, too, don't want to lose anymore.
This time we'll win for sure!
Thank you for waiting.
Give us the HGH, Coach!
Come on, please just do it!
HEY, now
If we start injecting and Working it with Dyrone, will we win?
You're gonna pyramid your diet so each meal
Is three pounds heavier than the last?
I'll show you the way!
Let's fight together!
HAIL!
You seem all roided up
Hell yeah
Thy are pretty good
But...
But..?
That's what makes it fun, right?
Well then, allow me to challenge you.
We won't lose.
We probably will
Let me show you how we do things in Penn State
Are you Jerry Sandusky?
And now...
Let us commence the mini-basketball tournament!
Here's the bracket! Come on!
Oh~, This is like Faith Hill!
W-wait...
So this is what
Mhm girl them booty-clappin' thighs
Oh, the bracket seems pretty interesting.
Looks like we'll meet in the semifinals.
Chris Paul! I got one thing to say to you:
We gon' crush you guys
No complaints, are there?
Sure.
However, if we win...
Then you'll be our personal slaves, like Emmett Till
Eh?
You'll order us around like slaves, am I right?
Well, whatever.
We just have to win.
Yeah!
We sure gonna kick your asses!
I'll make you swallow your words so you can break your fast,
then thank God almighty that you can eat at last!
Oh, Ok
I get it.
If the sixth graders win, you'll be able to start a plantation
Then you can rake in cash money
Kobe and the others thought of it
It's a pretty sweet deal
The slaves will have free food and shelter
Are you sure it'll be okay?
Long time no see, Charles
??????????
I've brought the slaves you requested
Perfect!
Oh yeah, how'd the vasectomy go?
Yeah, the surgery went perfectly!
I remember having sexted Anne, but...
I wanted you to think she was still fertile
Hey!
But yeah, this is great news
I'm not fully recovered yet, but I'm getting there.
Ah, nothing beats unprotected intercourse!
.....
What about the others?
Didn't make the cut, couldn't even make a basket
I'm telling ya, our bench is stacked
She the best we got
Yo what's up? Name's Mike Vick
What's good in the hood?
She used to fight dogs
But I pulled her off the street
Now she's playing hoop
Can I leave yet? I miss dogfighting
Is dat Kareem Abdul-Jabbar I see?
Yeah?
I knew it! My teammates told me about you.
There's someone taller than me in Keishin.
I'm sure you were surprised when you suddenly grew so much.
It's like the world is running away from you. It's scary.
Hm?
Airi?
I feel the same way.
I love gymnastics, but when I grew taller, I couldn't do them as well.
I started falling behind, so I wanted to try basketball.
But I'm falling behind in basketball as well.
I'm losing my confidence...
We're the same.
When I started playing basketball,
I was terrible and felt like dead weight.
I'm still far from good.
Airi-san, you too?
Yeah, but my height helped me so many times on the court.
I found something only I could do.
So, Aya-chan, you'll be fine, too.
Airi-san...
I'm really glad I could talk to you...
So, so glad.
Me too.
If I can, I'd like to talk with you even more.
Oh~, Airi's so cool!
Subaru! Airi said something that cool!
Lets Get Ready To RUUUUUUUUUUMBLEEEEEEEEEEE
Go to Court A
Alright then, Charles
I'll be waiting for you in the finals.
Don't lose before you get to us, alright?
That's my line.
See you later.
Alright, everyone, let's go!
Okay!
Just try not to suck this time
You'll be fine!
Okay!
Just maintain your rhythms to win!
Do your best, everyone!
We'll win for sure!
Yeah!
Tomo!
Kobe! Chris!
Aight!
Too fast!
Since when were they this fast?
I never knew they were this strong
Kobe!
Smell ya later!
Nice one Dirk!
Chillax guys, we still got this
LeBron!
Let's go, Sista!
Oh~, I won't lose!
Looks like a good game.
It's essentially tied.
Wait, the sixth graders are losing?
That's strange.
I thought we were up.
We can win this!
Are they worried about their score?
They keep missing their shots.
What's with them?
Hey, Charles!
You're paying too much attention to details, we're falling behind!
Screw you Anne, why don't you go back to the WNBA?
It's working!
They can't keep up with our speed at all!
I can see them clearly!
So much more juiced up
Our HGH has paid off!
We were pushed into a corner last time, but today we're in the lead!
Everything's going according to Anne's plan!
Good work.
Alright, everything's coming along nicely.
Coach, how was my shot?
Was I fast enough?
You're all fantastic! The practice helped a lot!
Can we win like this?
Let's see...
If they keep playing as before, yes.
But that won't matter at all.
We just play our basketball, right?
Exactly. That's the easiest and the hardest part.
However, you can do it now!
Believe in yourselves and believe in everyone else!
Okay!
Alright! Time for the second half, we'll win for sure!