2nd Street
“Sexual Harassment Court is Super Cool!”
“In order for the Sabbath to heal one's heart, one must work diligently on the other six days.
Even God, our creator, is no exception”
— Kirk H. Hill
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
“The Sexual Harrassment Lawsuit”(From Vol.1, Chapter 3)
Arashiyama, you have plenty of qualities that Tatsuno can't compete with.
I know that for a fact.
Darn it! My mind keeps wandering to Mr. Moriaki!
And my fantasies are starting to override my memories!
It's finally Sunday, so I shouldn't be thinking about school or teachers!
Today, I'm gonna buckle down and finish my book.
The Nara Bomber: Detective vs. Bomb
Stop right there!
Take a closer look.
You're holding a chikuwa!
Normally, nobody would mistake it for a stick of dynamite!
Except for the culprit!
This sucks! Why do I keep picturing Mr. Moriaki as the main character?!
Why...
Ow!
Hey sis, play with me!
Sis is busy right now.
Liar! You were just sitting there daydreaming!
Daydreaming is part of being a grown-up.
All right now, Yukiko. Be a good girl and play with your brother.
Unhand me, alien scum!
Takeru, play with Yukiko!
What?
Come on, you've got some two-player games, don't you?
Like “Mario Sisters” or something.
What're you doing?!
I didn't even save!
Hey, knock it off!
This is all your fault!
Ow!
Mom! Hotori's being mean!
Hotori, what did you do!?
Argh! That's it!
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
You girls are supposed to be off today.
What are you doing here?
I just get in trouble if I stay home.
I came just in case Sanada decided to stop by!
Sanada?
Tatsuno's a healthy young girl.
Hotori, on the other hand...
Anyway, get this, Tatsuno.
Lately when I think of Mr. Moriaki, I get a funny feeling right here.
Oh my! Hotori's in love too?
Tell me about it.
Just thinking about that math test makes me sick to my stomach.
I didn't mean my stomach.
I can't make head or tails out of stuff like differentials and integrals!
Iffegrals and Diffigentles?
Differentials and integrals.
I can't understand any of that complicated stuff!
I couldn't even make it past dividing with fractions!
I thought it'd work if you just flipped 'em over...
I'm still not sure I really get it.
I'm amazed you've made it to high school.
Seems like Tatsuno's not exactly suited for giving advice.
Hotori didn't even notice the subject change from love problems to math, though...
Well, don't they say that kids who have their
fractions down, make it through life just fine?
Yeah! I saw that movie too!
Even if you don't have the book smarts,
you're fine if you can just see eye to eye with people.
And coast through life that way.
Even life has its own formula, huh?
Now we're talking about the meaning of life!
Just kick reason to the curb and live like that, and you'll be fine, y'know?
Like with the perps in those cartoon detective shows.
Even if your deductive reasoning isn't good, you can guess the perp just by using the formula.
Really?! What formula?
It's whatever character the top billing voice actor plays!
Aww, I shouldn't have asked!
Now I'll know next time!
Hey Hotori, since you're free, go down to the
grocery store and get me some potatoes and onions.
But today I'm just a customer.
Then pay your bill and go home!
Tch! Fine, I'll go, so let me borrow it.
The vroom-vroom thingy.
Maruko Shopping District
Woo-hoo!
Potatoes 'n onions, potatoes 'n onions!
Potatoes...
H-HEY!!!
Potatoooes!
On...
Onio...
...ions!
Cripes!
Hey, that's dangerous, you know!
Jeez, what's your problem?
You just ignore people when they tell you to stop?
Sheesh. People like you remind me that spring time absent-mindedness is in full bloom.
YOU'RE THE DANGEROUS ONE HERE!
I just bumped into you!
Women have no idea how much this hurts!
It's your fault for jumping out in front of me anyway.
This is all your fault!
I've told you before not to ride that down this street!
Keep it up, and I'll declare this an accident-related injury!
Don't ride on the street?
So what, am I supposed to ride it inside my house then?
My mom would wring my neck!
Why you little!
You respect your mother more than the law?
This is why I hate kids.
Listen to me!
No driver's license, no license plate, no headlights,
and no blinker either!
For these reasons, you cannot ride that on this street!
You can't eat a burger without the meat, cheese, lettuce or pickles, right?
You can still have the bun.
All right, that's it.
Hmph. Fine, I won't ride it anymore.
What gives? You're awfully cooperative today.
I'm already there anyway.
Nothing's better than a bean paste bun and a glass of milk.
Oh, you running errands for the old hag?
I'll be sure to tell her you said that.
We got fresh carrots, straight from Kouchi!
Fresh outta the ground! Still got dirt on 'em! Come one, come all!
Be quiet! You're gonna make me forget what I came for!
Umm, I think it was curry ingredients or something...
Oh yeah, it was potatoes and...
Potatoes and...
...carrots please.
Thanks for shoppin'!
Oh yeah, Hotori.
Take this back with ya.
It expires tomorrow, but you could clear it by then, right?
Wow, thanks!
Heh. Drinking that might help you get a little bigger!
Got that right!
What might get bigger!?
I oughta sue for sexual harassment!
Hey Mr. Policeman, stop laughing and and reprimand him!
Yes ma'am!
I wanna live life smiling.
Perverted geezers. I won't forget this!
Don't ride that. Walk it back, please.
Headlights and a license plate, right?
And the blinkers and driver's license!
Don't try to cut corners, or I'll confiscate it!
Forget it. You're too high-strung to handle it.
Huh?
Let's ride, Tetsuo!
There's no Tetsuo he- I SAID DON'T RIDE IT!
For Pete's sake!
Someday she'll leave her nest and get married...
Then the town can extinguish that fire.
It's still raging right now, though.
I'm back!
Sanada actually came!
Huh?
Aww, back so soon?
Took you long enough.
But that cop was threatening to arrest me.
What'd you do?
I had an incomplete hamburger.
Good work. Want some coffee?
Just a cup, please. I'm gonna have some milk.
What's up, you trying to get bigger?
No point in trying now. You've already passed your growing stage.
It's no big deal if you're a little small.
That's what makes you you. You're fine just the way you-
Why does everyone have to mention my boobs?! Huh?!
That does it! I'm suing for sexual harassment!
W-wait, objection! I was talking about your height...
Yeah! Sanada's not that kind of person!
The audience may not interject with opinions!
Objection! I'll represent Mr. Sanada.
Overruled!
I'm telling you, I meant your height, not your boobs!
I told her to get potatoes and onions!
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will he held against you in a court of law, got it?
That's when you arrest someone, not when they're on trial!
Arrest... trial... who cares?
Her brain needs to develop, not her boobs!
You're in contempt of court!
“Spin city” for short.
What's the world coming to?
“Shop Girls Are Sophisticated”(From Vol.1, Chapter 8)
Maid-you!
What's that?
I just changed thank you to maid-you.
But what's that got to do with the Vulcan salute?
It's different!
Vulcans do this.
This is maid-you. The thumb makes it an M.
If we make this the shop's greeting, we'll attract more customers!
You imbecile. How would that bring in customers?
Mai... Hey, I can't do it!
Doesn't matter. Rejected.
But if we don't have a unique flair, nobody will come!
Please do
not disturb.
Meeting in
Progress
Meeting in Progress. Please do not disturb. —Seaside
Head Maid, look at this!
Your stupidity is what's keeping them away!
Our world is a mirror that reflects your true nature.
A peaceful world reflects a loving heart,
but in tough times, the seas of
adversity are caught in a whirlpool.
Another one.
Here's another arrow.
Here too.
Hey, you're from the cleaner's aren't ya?
What's going on here, guys?
Well, these arrows are posted all over town.
Ah, to tell the truth, I've been following these myself.
Is there some kind of event going on?
Hey, look!
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
It's the old hag's place.
Yo!
Great. More tough guys.
Welcome ho-
MAID-YOU!
This place has no sense of coordination.
Hey granny, what's with all the arrows?
You guys planning something?
What arrows? This is news to me.
That's my genius design!
I spent two whole days posting these around town to attract customers.
At times, like a ninja.
At others, like a shinobi.
They're the same thing.
Like that would actually get anyone to come!
It did.
Crap, it did!
Whatever, we'll just discuss the festival plans here.
Yeah, we're already here anyway.
3 waters!
3 waters, coming right up!
3 coffees, got it!
3 cutlet curries comin' up.
They're blatantly screwing it up!
Excuse me...
Hey there.
Welcome home, Ma-
Maid-you!
Um, about these arrows...
Another victim! We should change “café” to “Antlion's nest”!
Not a chance.
I figured it was you.
Hey, why'd you take them down? You stupid four-eyed cop!
Bifocop!
You can't just go around posting these things.
There were thirty of them!
I worked so hard on those! Why do you hate me so much?!
That's not why I did it.
Whenever I act out of concern for this town, I end up butting heads with you.
Do you have to be a constant obstruction in my life?!
I could say the same to you.
Terribly sorry. Our maid here is such a moron.
Please help yourself to a cold drink.
Gnaw on some ice and crawl back into your cave!
Beat it! Scram!
I've had it with you...
I told you not to mouth off...
...to the customer!
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
Got it? Don't blame me if I shoot you next time.
Stupid jerk!
Was that a Beat Takeshi impression?
Yeesh, that was terrible.
What?! I dare you to say that again!
What'd you call me!?
Crap, she's pissed!
Oh? So then you chased them around town for half an hour?
What do we do with her, Head Maid?
Considering the situation, and no valid excuse...
30 minute's pay cut.
How come?! I'm busting my hump here!
“Busting your hump” chasing middle schoolers will get you arrested.
No, before that! Like my original greeting and the flyers!
I'm trying to attract classier patrons.
I mean, look at this freak show.
Hey! What're you blaming us for?!
We're supporting your business by eating right before dinner!
Yeah! Now I won't be able to finish supper tonight!
What am I supposed to say to my family?
Jeez, bunch of family-obsessed weenies.
Well, I do understand what Arashiyama's trying to say.
The place has kind of been in a rut lately.
Our only customers are regulars from the shopping district.
We need customers who truly appreciate maids.
Why the hell are you blaming us?!
But so far, none of Arashiyama's ideas have worked.
Especially that insufferable greeting!
Fine, but we should at least try to make the store eye-catching.
Yeah, our makeshift sign isn't exactly up to snuff.
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
We ought to just have a new sign made.
Good idea!
That little crybaby that I treated like my own granddaughter is telling me how to run my store!
Cafe
Seaside
Oh, what's the matter Hotori, dear?
Cafe
Seaside
There, there, have some curry, hon.
I ended up not giving him any chocolate...
I'm such a chicken!
There, there, have some curry, hon.
I'm crying 'cause I lost my purse!
Granny, what are you wearing?! Did you finally lose it?!
Maid café's are a lucrative business these days.
Here, have some curry.
You're enjoying that, aren't you, Hotori?
I've got a proposition for you.
I'll forget about the 10 years worth of free curry if you work here for me.
What?!
That little crybaby that I treated like my own granddaughter...
I'll deal with the sign eventually,
But I'm all for making the place stand out.
Let's give it a shot.
Really?
But how do we do that?
Hmm. Well, I got a big ol' sheet upstairs...
Why don't you make a flashy banner out of it?
This is gonna be a lot of fun!
Hey, you better take this seriously.
Found it! Here we are.
There's some paint here too.
What are you going to write?
For starters, I'll write “Maid Café Seaside” in huge letters.
Can you even write the kanji for café?
I can, thank you!
Cafe
This
Here goes!
Mai
d Cafe
Seaside
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
You talk big, but it ended up like crap.
It's very “you”.
Let me borrow the paint. I'll write “sophisticated” in the blank space.
Won't we get sued by an advertising committee?
Don't worry. It's not a big deal.
Here we go!
Perfect!
Maid
Cafe
Seaside
Sophis
ticated
Nice, Tattsun!
This spontaneous outburst is apparently what her nickname for Tatsuno is.
Milk is perfect with saucy cutlet bowls.
Make sure to stretch it all the way!
Got it!
Done!
Sophisticated Maid Cafe Seaside
Granny, come check it out!
It's a work of art!
Oh, I can't wait to see it.
Ta-daa!
Naito
Dentistry
Childish Maid Cafe Seaside
Naito
Dentistry
Childish Maid Cafe Seaside
Childish...
Naito
Dentistry
Childish Maid Cafe Seaside
Damn you, Naito Dentistry!
It's like the whole world's out to get me today!
Damn you, world!
Our world is a mirror that reflects your true nature.
A peaceful world reflects a loving heart,
but in tough times, the seas of adversity are caught in a whirlpool.
Naito
Dentistry
Childish Maid Cafe Seaside
I'll tear this thing down,
and triumph over society!
You're supposed to do these things at night, Arashiyama.
Just like a ninja, or a shinobi.
Do what like a shinobi?
What, pray tell, are you doing to my sign?
We're sorry. That was very childish of us.
Naito
Dentistry
Childish Maid Cafe Seaside
Keep pulling stunts like this oughta attract some folks.
Arashiyama
So when you returned to the store, the victim was already dead, is that it?!
Suspect A is the pretty boutique owner.
Suspect B is the driver of the taxi she rode.
Suspect C is the IT exec with investments in said boutique.
The pretty lady's voice is kind of cute. Sounds like she'd be popular...
But the taxi driver's kind of shady and has a raspy voice.
The IT exec's definitely in an affair with the pretty lady.
No, wait. His voice is charming, and popular-sounding too.
Who's the highest billing voice actor of the three?
You people have to think outside the box!
Don't tell me you think Sachiko did it!
He's the culprit!
Wha... How'd you know?
He's just pretending to be dead.
But they haven't said it yet. How'd you know?
'Cause it's a rerun!
Mom! Hotori's being mean again!
Hotori, what did you do!?
Ahh, jeez!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living for rock!
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
Living lonely, blasting my music.
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Kyou mo Kare ni wa Nasake Kokurezu
and I still have yet to tell him how I feel.
Toppuu ni Inochi wo Sasage Ashikoshi wo
Putting our lives in the hands of a tornado,
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
we train our legs by playing drums.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We're the Maids, yeah!
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Chiisai no wa Zessan Eigyou Chuu
The little one's working inside, making a profit!
Thank you very maid for coming!
There's no year of the cat in the Chinese Zodiac, is there?
There are no cat constellations either.
Why isn't there one for such an ordinary animal?
Well, some folks have names like Nekodzuka or Nekozaki, though.
But what about Toshiko Tatsuno? Dragons don't even exist!
Maybe it's so ordinary they just forgot?
I smell a rat.
I bet there's an ugly truth behind the exclusion of the cat year!
Café Seaside
Next time!
3rd Street“The Cat Boy”
3rd Street: The Cat Boy.
The city'll still be turning tomorrow.