X.
Today
Study Hall
Fumizuki Academy's Academic Training Camp: Day 2, Class A-
Ehh?!
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 6
Me, a Peeping Tom and the Brotherhood of Men!
Study Hall
It's a joint camp between Class A and Class F.
Yuuji, I'm glad we can study together.
Shouko, that's not your seat!
Did we really come all the way here just to have study hall?
Aren't the teachers going to give us lectures?
Of course not.
We won't be able to understand a thing if they taught us Class A's materials.
That might be for you, but Class A and F's materials aren't really that much different to me.
Oh, that's pretty amazing.
I don't understand a thing either way.
That's a whole different kind of amazing.
The goal of this training camp is to motivate the students.
By studying in the same classroom,
Scribbling
Study Hall
Today
it's hoped that Class F's students will be inspired by Class A's diligence.
Conversely, it'll help Class A's students continue to perform for fear of becoming like Class F.
Class
Lazy
I don't know about Class A, but I'm
pretty sure that won't work for Class F.
Lazy
Oh, Rep, I didn't know you were here!
Maybe I'll study over here too.
Kudou Aiko!
Hello, hello.
I heard you guys tried to peep
into the girls' bath last night.
You could've just asked if you
wanted to see that badly.
If you'd like, I can show you my underwear.
Huh? What's wrong, Muttsurini?
Your love for erotica is usually pretty obvious,
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
but you seem to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Even my heart is beating fast.
Your love for erotica is usually
pretty obvious, but you seem
to be calm.
Even my heart is beating fast.
Don't be fooled, Akihisa.
She's wearing shorts underneath.
What?!
That's so cruel, Kudou-san!
That's so cruel, Kudou!
I want my innocence back!
My bad, Yoshii-kun.
Let me show you something interesting instead.
What is it?
A compact recorder.
Huh? What's wrong, Muttsurini?
Here's the interesting part.
Kudou-san! I want your love. My heart is beating fast.
Kudou!
I want your love.
My
heart is beating fast.
Huh?
That's extremely interesting!
It's a very interesting line indeed.
Mizuki, give me a hand.
Sure.
Of course.
Akihisa!
Run quick, before they come back with their torture gear.
Wait, Hideyoshi!
Wait, Hideyoshi! I didn't do anything wrong, did I?
I didn't do anything wrong, did I?
Hey, Akihisa.
Wait, Hideyoshi! I didn't do anything wrong, did I?
What is it, Yuuji?
Kudou might be the one responsible for the eavesdropping.
You're right!
Her skills are amazing.
Akihisa, figure out if she's really the culprit.
Got it.
So, Kudou-san...
What is it, Yoshii-kun?
Are you...
She won't tell the truth if I just flat-out ask her!
What's wrong?
Um... well... that is... you're not really...
Um... well... that is...
you're not really...
What about me?
Um... well... that is...
you're not really...
I have no idea how to ask!
All I know is that the culprit has a burn mark.
Let's see... Let's see...
I'd be really grateful if you could show me your ass!
Not bad, Akihisa.
I expected no less from him.
You sure are daring, Akihisa.
I'd be really grateful if you could show me your ass!
I'd be really grateful
if you could show me your ass!
This is embarrassing.
It's even the unprocessed recording.
Please, Kudou-san! Delete what I just said!
Please, Kudou-san!
Delete what I just said!
Show me your ass!
I wonder what that was.
Yes, I wonder.
Could it be that some fool has gone and said something he shouldn't have?
This is quite the problem.
Someone like that needs to be disciplined severely, doesn't he?
This is a misunderstanding!
This is a
misunderstanding!
All I did, was just
All I did, was just...
try to clear some stuff up
love ass
and nothing else!
Don't do that, Kudou-san!
Kudou Aiko!
Stop messing around.
Muttsurini!
Muttsurini
I'll counter her.
Leave it to me!
Oh, you're helping me out!
All right!
Listen, both of you, this is
just a misunderstanding.
I was just trying to say I wanted to clear some stuff up!
love ass!
love
ass
I mean, it was a misunderstanding!
I mean Yuuji's.
I mean
Yuuji's
Whoa, Muttsurini!
Kudou Aiko, you're still so naive!
Not too bad, Muttsurini-kun.
Yoshii.
I won't give you Yuuji.
I don't want him!
Aki, do you like Sakamoto's ass that much?
Isn't mine any good?
I more or less knew already, but it's still shocking to hear it so plainly.
Everyone, this is all a misunderstanding! I don't have such a creepy—
Ass
Yuuji
Don't mock same gender love!
Miharu! Why are you here?
Darling!
I slipped out of Class D because I wanted to see you so much!
Sugawa Barrier!
You are disgusting!
Hugging you is like hugging a greased boar!
Don't be so mean, Darling!
Miharu loves you so much!
Wait, stop it!
I'm not interested in girls!
Excuse me, this is study hall.
Could you be a little quieter?
S-Sorry, Kubo-kun.
Also, I'm not fond of statements
that mock same gender love.
It just means that one thinks
a little differently than others.
If these practically normal people are looked upon with revulsion, I think society is in dire need of reform.
Exactly, gender doesn't matter!
I don't swing that way!
"Gender doesn't matter", huh?
For some reason, I'm getting the chills.
Gender doesn't matter?
Why're you taking turns staring at Yuuji and me?
You've got the wrong idea!
You know that I love Hideyoshi!
Love
Hideyoshi
Wait a second!
Akihisa, I'm not sure how to respond.
Don't misunderstand, Hideyoshi! You know...
I love your ass.
I love
your ass
Wait, it's just getting worse!
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Yuuji and I are taking turns touching asses...
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo
Taking
turns
Kubo-kun, show me your ass!
Kubo-kun
Kubo-kun, I love you!
I'm troubled, Yoshii-kun.
There's a proper order to things.
The problem is more fundamental
than just the "proper order".
I think Kudou-san is probably
the person blackmailing us.
Judging from how she uses that
recorder, I'd say it's pretty likely.
Should we try and capture her?
I wouldn't recommend it.
We'll only get one chance.
If we're wrong, the real culprit will know we're
on to her and disappear without a trace.
Evidence will be destroyed and
there will be more blackmailing.
The situation will become even worse.
We can't afford making a risky move
until we're absolutely sure it's her.
Confirming the presence of a burn
mark would be a good start.
Maybe we should risk pissing
her off and flip up her skirt.
She's wearing shorts.
That's right.
Peeping into the girls' bath
is the only way to check.
Now we're back to this again.
What should we do though? Getting through
security without a plan is gonna be tough.
There's not really much we can
plan; there's only one path.
Women's large bath
Men's large bath
Locker room
Hallway to
men's bath
women's bath
Stairs
Boiler room
Women's large bath
Men's large bath
Locker room
Women's large bath
Men's large bath
Locker room
Hallway to
men's bath
women's bath
Stairs
Boiler room
Women's large bath
Men's large bath
Locker room
Boiler room
Hallway to
men's bath
women's bath
Stairs
Women's large bath
Locker room
Hallway to
men's bath
women's bath
Stairs
Boiler room
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Japanese
Math
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Social Studies
Science
PE
Social Studies
Math
Japanese
Locker room
Hallway to
men's bath
women's bath
Stairs
Boiler room
A head-on assault is the only solution.
Actually, there is another way.
If a straightforward attack is our only choice, we
need to gather numbers in order to be successful.
So, we should get some allies?
Yes.
Then let's do it right away—
What did you want to talk about?
Sugawa-kun... everyone!
Thank you for coming, my fellow Class F brothers.
I have a proposal for you all.
A proposal?
What is it? I'm tired.
I just want to lay around in my room.
Guys, are you interested in
peeping in on the girls' bath?
Tell us more!
Last night, we tried to sneak a look at the girls' bath,
but we were stopped by the teachers' ambush.
So?
Tonight, we'll launch a second assault.
I want you guys to eliminate
the security of the girls' bath.
The reward will be the chance
to catch a glimpse of Agharta!
Agharta
Deal!
Muttsurini, what time is it?
Class
Enter bath
Girls
Begun
10 Elapsed. 20:10
2010 hours, ten minutes have passed since
the beginning of the girls' bath hours.
Passed
The timing's perfect.
We'll divide the unit up into four teams.
I'll lead Team A,
Akihisa will lead Team B,
B!
Hideyoshi will lead Team C,
C!
and Muttsurini will lead Team D, so follow your leaders.
D!
Roger!
Do you understand?! We have
one goal and one goal only:
to reach Agharta!
No matter what happens along the way, imbue your limbs with spirit,
and charge headlong toward your target!
Even gods and demons are mortal; kill all enemies in sight!
Even gods
and demons
are
mortal
Kill all
enemies
in
sight
Think of this as our final turning point in life!
20:14
Hallway in front of girls' bath
I think we really showed them yesterday.
They probably got the point and won't try anything—
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts are attacking in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
The perverts
are attacking
in formation!
Hallway to women's bath
Chemistry
Summoned Being: Summon!
Perverts
I will not let you pass!
Summon!
Kinoshita's Team C has engaged Fuse-sensei!
We'll pass by while Hideyoshi's team is distracting him!
Everyone, don't fall behind!
All right!
Everyone, engage the enemy!
X
Sex
Position
Points
Flask
Chemistry teacher
Chemistry
Kinoshita
Hideyoshi
Class F Student
Hallway to women's bath
Perverts
Now's our chance! Let's go!
Wait, Yoshii-kun!
Pervert
We'll cut through like this!
Yeah!
That's as far as you go, you disgusting pigs.
Men are forbidden beyond this
point. Go back to your sty!
Yoshii, we're outnumbered and outgunned!
Please, Shimizu-san.
Make way for us!
You're going to indulge yourself with a
glimpse of my darling's flat chest, aren't you?
Flat
chest
Absolutely disgusting!
That's not it!
My goal isn't Minami's flat chest!
Flat
chest
You're lying!
Flat
chest
I'll punish you filthy pigs who are enamored
by my darling's beautiful flat chest!
Flat
chest
Flat chest
Trust me, a flat chest is just a flat chest!
Right now, I have more important business than Minami's washboard che— My right elbow!
Flat
chest
I was listening and you just wouldn't shut up!
Looks like you still need more punishment.
Hey there, Yoshii-kun.
What did you come here to see?
I wouldn't mind if you came to spy on me.
I won't forgive infidelity.
Even Kirishima-san is here?
We didn't account for this!
Yoshii-kun, is this your objective?
There's still one hidden camera
left in the changing room.
It's not mine. I just happened across it.
Kudou-san?
Let's get started, shall we?
Muttsurini-kun.
Showdown!
Summon!
We're counting on you, Muttsurini!
I'll take this one!
Educational Guidance!
I knew you'd come, you seasoned idiots!
I-Iron Man?!
We have to go through him unarmed?
That's simply impossible!
I'll carefully guide you today.
Prepare yourself, Yoshii!
Is this the end?!
Don't give up, Yoshii!
Sugawa-kun!
Let go of my leg, Sugawa!
You can't be defeated here!
Only you... the Punishment Inspector, has a
Summoned Being that can defeat Iron Man!
So I beg you, run from this place,
and live on!
Don't get in the way of my guidance.
Sugawa-kun? Sugawa-kun!
Summon!
Support Yoshii's advance!
We'll open up a way out!
Just run through and don't turn back!
You guys!
Yoshii is our only hope! Protect him at all costs!
Yoshii!
Perverts
Hallway to women's bath
Okay, guys, I'll leave this to you.
I will definitely survive and achieve our goal!
I'm sorry, everyone!
I'm sorry!
I swear...
I swear I'll reach Agharta!
Yoshii Akihisa-kun of Class F, please come to the guidance office immediately.
Well, no surprises there.
Man, it's morning already.
I didn't sleep much with all those
supplementary lessons Iron Man gave me.
A dream?!
Damn.
Like hell I'd do that!
Take this!
What's wrong? Did Yuuji creep
into someone else's bed again?
Again?
It's a bad habit of his.
He came into my futon when dawn was breaking.
Unforgivable!
I won't forgive you for fooling with my innocence!
Oh yeah, Kudou-san told me
something strange yesterday.
Strange?
"There's still one hidden camera
left in the changing room."
What?
Perhaps she really is the culprit.
No, I don't think we can count on that as proof.
The perpetrator wouldn't incriminate themselves like that, would they?
We'll just have to verify it ourselves.
If what she says is true then we owe her one.
Why?
If we get our hands on that camera,
we'd be able to see the girls changing.
We might be able to spot the culprit.
I see.
I'm confident I can find that camera in a matter of seconds.
Can we even be sure the camera's actually there?
The girls found one the day before yesterday.
As a master in the art of spying, I doubt the culprit
would've let their equipment be discovered so easily.
There was a reason for it.
Exactly, the first camera was just a bait
intended to divert the girls' focus on to us.
The other camera remaining in the changing room, the one Kudou discovered, is the real one.
So we just need to take out that camera, right?
That won't be possible.
The changing room is locked when not in use.
But nothing else has worked so far.
Stairs
Bath
Hallway
Akihisa, why exactly did we lose yesterday?
Reason?
I guess because half of the girls
were there to defend against us.
Then we just need to get some new recruits.
We'll ask the other classes for help.
The other classes?
It's for more than just increasing our numbers.
Hmm?
Protection
It's for our own protection.
Protection?
Real
culprit
Even if we succeed in spying on the girls, we'll be in deep trouble unless we find the real culprit blackmailing us.
Oh, it'll be harder to single out one man in the crowd!
Culprit
Mastermind
Our name is mud right now though.
Fumizuki Academy is a pretty high-profile school, so
they'll either have to punish everyone or cover it up.
Punish All
Cover-up
All we need to do is gather enough people
so it'd be hard to punish us all, right?
You're a pro when it comes to these dirty tactics!
Oh please, I'm just resourceful.
We need to gather forces during the day!
Today
Study Hall
We'll approach Kubo for Class A.
Akihisa, go convince him.
You're the best man for the job.
We're counting on you.
Sure, but why me?
Use this to protect yourself if something happens.
Eh?
Hey Kubo-kun, got a minute?
Of course, come and sit right here.
I'm fine here.
I guess that's fine too...
I've got a favor to ask of you. I want to—
I'll do it!
So fast!
Oh, sorry.
I got overexcited.
Let's hear it.
Oh, okay.
I need you to help peep in the girls'—
I refuse!
So fast!
Why?!
I'm disappointed, Yoshii-kun.
There are ground rules for human interactions.
Whole societies are founded on such principles.
Today you'll be breaking those rules.
Are you really okay with that?
In the first place, trying to peep
at girls' naked bodies is disgusting!
Sorry, I failed.
Oh...
Well, at least you're okay.
I don't see how it was dangerous.
Since we've struck-out with Class A, I guess
we'll just need to try the other classes.
You're up to no good again, aren't you?
N-No way, of course I'm not.
Well, I can't really be bothered
to reprimand you right now.
I can't believe you'd try to peep at us girls.
I'd be compared with the other girls during bath time.
I can't wear pads and there's
nothing I can do to give them a lift.
I wasn't expecting someone to peep at me, so I didn't have a chance to diet!
You're so mean, Akihisa-kun!
I told you, what I want to see are the girls' asses.
is Yuuji's ass.
I didn't say that!
Training Camp
D-Day
Night
Third Day
Again, it's the night before D-Day-
Not again...
So only Class D and E are going to help us, huh?
I'm on bad terms with Class B's Nemoto Kyouji, and Class C's rep is that Koyama Yuuka.
The guys of her class wouldn't dare go against her.
It can't be worse than yesterday.
The girls can only send out half their forces.
We'll be able to pull it off if we
can hold the teachers down.
I've informed the two classes of the
operation start time and insertion point.
Good, preparation is vital here.
Bad news!
The enemy has ambushed us by the canteen!
What?!
Our forces have been divided and are scattered throughout each floor!
They made the first move...
Our movements were read by the enemy.
Was it Shouko?!
She really can't forgive you for trying to peep.
We have to act now!
We'll rally the troops.
Now, let's roll out!
I won't let you peep!
Damn, why are the girls here?!
Like I know! Just fight back!
Concentrate our forces and break through!
Follow my lead!
Got it!
Yuuji, the enemy's forces are
highly concentrated at the front!
They'll have planted traps on the
ground where their forces are thin!
We'll have to outwit them!
Yuuji, I've been waiting.
Shouko?!
She outwitted my counterplan!
I told you, I won't forgive infidelity.
I'll teach your body a lesson.
You guys really need a lot of guidance.
It's the second year Head Teacher, Takahashi-sensei!
Yuuji, order a retreat—
Sorry, but that's not going to happen.
Kudou-san and Ooshima-sensei!
You didn't learn your lesson.
Why didn't you just ask me if
you wanted to see so badly?
We have no choice but to fight!
Summon!
Go!
It's fast!
OUCHHHHHHHH!
Overall Scores
What the heck?!
OVER 7000 POINTS?!
That's overpowered!
So, what do we do now?
Isn't it obvious?
We're gonna put everything we have on the line!
Yuuji!
Everyone, listen!
No more plans, no more strategies!
Do what you think is right!
Believe in yourself!
You guys can do it!
Feel with your heart, think with your
head, and do what you think is right!
You hear me? I'm counting on
each and every one of you!
Ready?! LET'S GO!
We're terribly sorry!
The two of you won't bow down?
Is that the pride of a leader?
You're wrong.
We already knew.
Yes, it's just as he said.
We already knew that we didn't need to bow down and beg.
Are you expecting reinforcements?
You think you know everything?
That's not what...
we meant at all.
Yes, they knew perfectly well that begging would have granted them no reprieve.
Thus ends the third night of the camp,
with Akihisa and Co. still not knowing the identity of the blackmailer.
Can Akihisa and Yuuji change their fa—
Arghh!
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Question 6
Write about what
you did on your
second day of
training camp.
Himeji Mizuki's Diary
Today I focused on physics,
which I'm a bit weak in.
It was different because
I got to study with some of
the students from Class A.
I felt my time was well
spent.
Teacher's Comment
I'm glad you gained something from studying
with Class A. It may become your new class
depending on the results of the next placement
exam, so it's a good idea to mix with them.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Diary
To summarize: I did things
and then slept
Teacher's Comment
That's not an appropriate
summary.
Yoshii Akihisa's Diary
I did stuff.
Teacher's Comment
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
This bold act of laziness
has momentarily left me
speechless.
Question 7
Answer the following question.
What do we call an act of
inflicting physical and/or
mental pain upon others in
order to make them
compliant?
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
Torture, examples of which include:
ishidaki, whipping, burning, ebiseme
binding, tsurizeme binding, crucifixion,
hanging from the ceiling, etc.
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Just as I'd expect of you, Kirishima. Nowadays, torture is prohibited by
international laws, such as the Convention Against Torture. As I'm sure you're
aware, you should respect human rights and refrain from acts of torture in your
school life.
Sakamoto Yuuji's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 7:
What do we call an act of inflicting physical and/or mental pain upon others in order to make them compliant?
I'm sorry, Shouko!
I won't pry too deeply into this.
Next episode: Me, a Peeping Tom, and the Distant Utopia.
Me, a Peeping Tom, and the Distant Utopia!
This will be on your test.