We're leaving now.
I'm so sleepy again today...
You sure are.
Tooru, you don't seem sleepy at all.
I'm a morning person.
That must be nice. I'm jealous.
I'm just so bad with mornings...
Caw____Caw
That's...
What's wrong, Run-chan?
There's something strange about those birds.
I wonder what happened?
Hey, Tooru.
Those birds keep going in circles. Are they okay?
Run-chan. That's a weather vane.
Worried...
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
Kilogram
Her silky long hair!
Her cute, thin, hourglass waist!
Her arms as long as a giraffe's neck!
Huh? Are they arguing?
She must have more good points than that!
Her slender legs!
Better points!
Her voluptuous E-cups!
More!
Her skin that's white as tofu!
More more more more more more more more!
What's wrong, you two?
We're naming your good qualities!
H-How'd you get on that topic?
Pores so small you'd need a microscope to see!
A tiny face like a water flea's!
Seems like you're only describing her appearance.
I wish they'd name some more internal good qualities.
More!
Umm...
Her figure is to die for!
W-What's wrong, Tooru?
Run-chan...
Run-chan keeps giving Yuuko all the praise.
I got so caught up in the moment that I shot myself in the foot.
That's not true.
Tooru, I'm sure you have good qualities, too!
Like?
Huh?
Um, that is...
That's right!
There are people who are "moé" for f-flat chests.
You know, slender is in style!
That's your target audience, Tooru!
W-What?
S-Stop it!
What's so great about a nice body?
You look like a model, Yuuko-chan!
Oh shoot!
I forgot!
My goal for this year:
lose two or three kilograms by summer, and look like a model!
No, wait. I still have time.
Summer doesn't really start until August.
The high school girl's summer has yet to begin!
One more month.
One more month to do something about this!
Hey...
"Today: School-wide Campus Cleaning"
"The pool"
Nagi, you idiot.
I forgot something else.
A high school girl's summer starts today!
Making us change into swimsuits just to clean the pool...
It's so inconvenient.
But it sounds like fun to do the cleaning in swimsuits!
Right? Don't you agree, Nagi-chan?
What's wrong, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing at all.
It's tight...
Don't tell me I gained weight?
No, it couldn't possibly...
Did our swimsuits shrink?
Mine feels a bit tight.
We're still growing!
In various places.
S-Stop it, gosh.
I see!
My swimsuit shrunk!
Don't you think Nagi's acting strange today?
Huh? She's the same as always.
board: "Campus Cleaning"
Responsibility:
Grounds
No~
Tooru-san!
Making progress?
Ah.
You're Yutaka's friend.
Call me Miho.
Actually, just like Yutaka,
I'm a fan of yours.
Fan?
Anyway,
I never got the chance to ask, but
there's something I've been wondering about.
So soft!
Is this natural? Do you style it?
It's natural...
Toooooruuun!
No fair, Miporin!
Miporin, you're bothering Toorun, too!
But I don't always cling to her like you do.
It's not fair that you can touch her!
Yutaka's gonna touch her, too!
Grab!
Oh, you...
Toorun! Toorun!
By the way,
you two seem like good friends. Were you in the same middle school?
Yep.
We've sort of been stuck together.
She keeps checking the time.
Okay! Three minutes is up.
Hm?
Move away from Tooru-san immediately, Yutaka.
What, already?
Miporin, you're so mean!
I'm used to her,
so if Yutaka bothers you again, you can ask me for advice.
Speaking of middle school,
they used to call Miporin "Remote Control".
Lame nickname, isn't it?
You realize where that came from, right?
Nope!
Yutaka!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
So long as you understand.
Miporin, I'm so sorry.
But Toorun's hair.
Yutaka never had a chance to touch it.
Tooru-san, I'll carry that trash bag for you.
Ah! Yutaka will carry it!
Well then, it's all yours.
Wait up! This is heavy...
Miporin!
"Remote Control."
So heavy...
The brilliant rays of sunlight!
At the poolside!
Feels like a resort?
Not in the least.
It's way too hot.
The inside of a pool is sure hot.
Well, yeah.
The heat from the sun has nowhere to escape to.
In any case, let's get this over with!
Yahoo!
Watch out!
*stop*
What's she up to?
Dunno.
Yuuko-chan, Nagi-chan!
This place is all slippery!
You're right.
That's dangerous!
What if you fell and hit your head?
It's fine, I won't!
Here I go!
Gosh.
Nagi, you tell her too-
Nagi!
What?
Yuuko-chan! Gotcha!
You're soaked!
I see.
So that's how it's gonna be.
Run!
Got you!
Hey!
Take that!
Water sprays into the air, going splish-splash.
Why you-
Like summer's never gonna end, at the poolside.
Ouch!
The sky sparkles and shines.
All the girls have sweat on their skin.
Strip down to swimsuit? Can't decide.
I want us all to play innocently,
too fond of being wet, just like children.
The paradise we dreamed of is like a resort if I'm with you.
That secret, stretched a bit too far.
Suddenly, I fall on my rear, slip!
I'm such a klutz every day.
Crying and laughing all the while,
even if we tease, we're still friends.
This exciting and beloved moment is a treasure for us all.
Onto that girl's smooth skin,
I splash some water, just to try it out.
Come on, come on, come on!
She flicks back, plish plish.
I want to embrace that girl while she's still soaking wet.
Um, Toorun, what are you looking at?
Gotcha!
Paradise.
This is not paradise at all.
Had to stay
because they
didn't finish
I'm back.
I'm beat.
I should have put on more sunscreen.
It'll be fine.
I got a ton of exercise today.
I'm sure it went down.
Rather,
I may have reached my goal of three kilograms already!
Show me what I want, scale!
1 kg gained
Come to think of it,
since I'm wearing clothes, I should just subtract one kilogram.
Oh look, it hasn't changed!
Such a letdown after all my nervousness.
"The Basics of Dieting"
I guess I should plan out my month.
To start with, limit your food intake and exercise a lot.
Don't eat everything on your plate.
Eat dinner early and make it small.
Cook something with lots of vegetables and that's low in fat.
Make sure to exercise daily.
Jogging, jumping rope, and stretching are effective.
Wow, sadistic.
Thanks for the meal.
Better not tell anyone I started a diet.
I bet they'd make a fuss.
If Run found out...
It's bad for your health, so stop it!
Yuuko would...
You're fine the way you are!
You're just right.
Sounds like something she'd say.
Tooru would...
Ahh.
munch
crunch
Mmm. Delicious.
Want some? You can have all you want.
Just imagining it is making me hungry.
Nagi.
I totally spaced out!
Tooru's kinda sharp, so I'd better watch out.
Hey, what's up?
Diet.
What are-
Hey.
You're on a diet, aren't you?
W-What are you talking about?
Where are Run and Yuuko?
They just went to the bathroom.
How did you know?
This spring, didn't you say,
"If I diet, I can lose three kilograms by summer, no problem"?
You were reminded of it yesterday, weren't you?
You could have just forgotten a trivial thing like that.
Are you going to tell the others?
Don't plan to.
Don't tell me you want a bribe to keep quiet?
Not really.
Whah are you dohing?
They're not here.
For all the sweets you eat, you sure are skinny, Tooru.
It's probably because I run around so much.
In exchange, not much growth's going on here.
I see.
They say if you shake it, you lose it.
In that case, I can't jog or jump rope or I'll lose my breasts!
All right!
If you're that concerned,
why don't you ask Yuuko?
Maybe she actually goes to a lot of trouble.
There must be something.
Some secret to her nice body.
I see.
You're right!
Okay!
They're not here, either.
Maybe we just missed them somewhere.
Tooru, you're sweating!
These are tears of sadness at being unable to see Run-chan.
Don't bluff like that.
All the walking made you hot, didn't it?
No, it didn't.
Besides, it's summer already. Why the long sleeves?
I want to avoid exposing my arms.
Gosh, you'll get heatstroke, so take it off!
Are you that against it?
Okay! Turn to page 52 in your textbooks.
Huh? Am I doing anything to maintain my figure?
N-No particular reason.
Just felt like asking.
Hmm...
Let's see...
I eat my favorite foods as much as I want,
and sleep a lot, I guess.
Really, I don't do anything.
What are you, the ultimate model?
Don't kid me!
You're utterly useless!
Huh?
W-What?
Maintaining her figure?
You mean a diet?
Oh, you were talking about a diet?
Nagi, did you start a diet?
Well...
Yeah, but...
I guess the cat's out of the bag.
Run, have you ever dieted?
Never stuck to one.
Don't like limiting what I eat.
Neither have you, right, Yuuko-chan?
No, I haven't. Why?
Because you have pets, right?
Pets?
What do you mean?
What was it again? Sounded like an office supply...
Tapeworms!
You use the power of the tapeworms!
I don't have any, and they aren't pets!
Computer.
Huh?
You can look up some good diets online.
Oh, I see.
Why'd we come to the library?
Couldn't you use the classroom's?
Looking this up on the classroom computer is kinda...
There sure are many kinds of diets.
It says, "I lost 60 kg after taking this!"
That's way too much.
It sounds fake.
If I lost that much, my weight would go negative,
and then I could fly!
Sure.
You'd become incorporeal.
Thanks for the food.
Nagi-chan, you're done already?
Yeah.
Eating less is fundamental to a diet.
Don't push yourself, Nagi.
I'll be fine.
I can handle this much.
You're pushing yourself.
Forget what just happened!
You didn't hear that!
I can't do that. I definitely heard it.
Forget it!
Man, I still get hungry by this time of day.
Um, hey, Nagi.
Jumping right into a tough diet is bad for you, so you should stop.
Take it slowly.
In fact, just make it your goal for next year instead.
She's right, Nagi-chan!
Just take it easy.
I guess you're right.
I can't push myself.
I'll stop rushing and go at my own pace.
Right, right!
Oh yeah!
Want to go for ice cream?
I like the sound of that!
Now wait just a minute here!
Isn't ice cream a bit out of place in this conversation?
I want chocolate chip and strawberry!
Vanilla, and cheese, and yogurt.
They're all white!
Like I said-
I'm thinking of getting mint and raspberry.
What about you, Nagi?
Rum raisin.
Guess I won't be dieting any time soon.
Come on, let's go!
Nagi!
Ah, hold on-
You're fine just the way you are!
Huh?
Nagi, you're just right the way you are.
You're plenty cute!
What kind of embarrassing line is that?
Geez!
Wait up, Yuuko!
Come on, hurry up!
I said wait up!
Take a look!
Brand new socks!
Fluorescent yellow!
Those will stand out.
Aren't they something?
Good morning!
Morning!
Tooru!
Why are you wearing loose socks?
In this day and age...
Uh-uh, these are new knee-socks.
They just fall down easily.
How skinny are you?
Even though they have stoppers, they keep slipping.
Want some sock glue?
Sure.
I wish I was just a bit chubbier.
I just heard something I can't let slide!
I said nothing.
Okay. Done.
Thank you.
I wish I was chubbier.
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
It's really summer now!
Summer means the pool, and the beach!
We're at the beach!
And the beach means swimsuits everywhere!
Can't get enough!
Are you really a high school girl?
I'm sure you're all dying to see Yutaka in a swimsuit!
I don't think so.
Next time on A-Channel!
"Beach"!
But Yutaka's only dying to see Toorun in a swimsuit!
Ah, me too, me too!
What, no comeback?
See you next week!