Hey, did you watch TV yesterday?
Watch what?
Isn't it obvious? "The News Crew Saw it!
The Startling Truth Behind 'Hassie, '
the Giant Eel of Lake Hamana."
Oh, I watched that, too!
There's no way something like that exists.
"Upon seeing its true nature, the ghost
proved to be a beckoning flower,"
is that what you're saying, Hotaro?
You're such a wet blanket.
Have you no sense of adventure?
Am I right, Chi-chan?
I am curious as to the truth of
whether it really exists or not.
Well, it doesn't matter
if it exists or not,
but today, I hope that it does.
Wouldn't that be more fun?
All ghosts are just beckoning flowers.
That sounds like you, Hotaro.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Classic Lit Club of Kamiyama
High School consists of four members.
Upon Seeing the True Nature
The reason
why we are being bounced around on this bus
Oh, can I have some of those, too?
has to do, of course, with where this bus is going.
Its last stop is at Zaizen Village,
famous for its mountain
climbing and hot springs.
We are headed there, not for the mountains,
but for the hot springs.
It's a fitting activity for one who lives by the principle
that during summer vacation, one should vacate.
And yet...
Thank you so much for what you
did regarding my uncle, Oreki-san.
And, since it's the break, let's all
go to the hot springs together.
Let's go to the hot springs!
I want to go
Yeah, okay...
There should be a van coming
to pick us up any minute now.
Wow, what a great view.
Um, Oreki-san? Are you all right?
Carsick.
Leave it to Hotaro to find something
so small to complain about.
It was just an hour and a half.
What a sad sack.
I have to say, Mayaka,
I'm impressed you got us rooms.
I have some relatives who run a tourist
inn, but they're renovating it right now,
and can't take in any customers,
so they're letting us stay for free.
We're here, Oreki-san.
Ah, we're here, we're here!
Oreki! Snap to it,
or we'll leave you behind!
We've finally made it to our inn!
Thank you for coming! Welcome to Seizanso!
Seizanso
This is the older sister, Zenna Rie,
and her younger sister, Zenna Kayo.
Hello.
They're now in 6th grade
and 4th grade, right?
They've grown even tall...
Hyah!
Sis!
Your rooms are on the
second floor, at the end.
Wow! Hotaro, hurry, hurry!
This is a room with quite
a nice view, huh?
This isn't so bad, once in a while.
Though, even if it's a lot to ask,
coming alone would have held more charm.
You, traveling alone?
Ha! That's a laugh.
Don't forget that it's because
Chitanda-san planned this trip
and Mayaka had the connections
that we're even here.
Hmph.
Time to eat!
We're having dinner.
You heard them. Let's go.
Cheese?
Stew... gratin... cheese fondue...
Cold shabu-shabu?
Ready, everyone?
Thank you for this meal.
There's dessert afterward, too.
Is it cheesecake?
How did you know?!
I could smell it.
That's amazing.
It is?
It's just like Maya-neechan said, huh?
What did you tell them, Ibara?
Let's all set off fireworks tomorrow!
That sounds nice.
I know! Dad bought some for us yesterday...
Whoa, what are you doing?
S-Sorry, Sis.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Did you burn yourself?
I'm fine.
Jeez, be more careful, okay?
That was filling. Hm?
Has Satoshi gone to the baths already?
This is a hot springs inn
that we've come to, so...
Oh...
If I may ask, Oreki-san,
where are you going?
Same place as you.
Where's Ibara?
The children took her away somewhere.
Forgive me for asking out of the blue,
but Oreki-san, what is your sister like?
That really is out of the blue.
Come to mention it, Chitanda,
you're an only child, aren't you?
My sister, huh?
She's a real character,
in more ways than one,
and she's also brilliant,
in more ways than one.
I don't think I could
outshine her in any area.
Oh...
Then again, I've never
wanted to outshine her.
So, what suddenly makes
you ask about my sister?
Seeing the Zenna sisters?
As a matter of fact,
I've always wanted siblings.
An older sister or a younger brother.
Don't you think it would be great to have someone
nearby with whom you can always feel at home?
No, I don't.
I suspect that the nice young lady
is a bit too good-natured.
Isn't she dreaming a little too much?
Siblings aren't actually all that terrific.
This doesn't appear to have mixed bathing.
Of course it doesn't!
Hm?
Satoshi's here?
Dad! Grandpa! Hurry up!
Sheesh!
Oh, this is bigger than I expected.
Hey, Hotaro! You're here!
Wow, this hot water is great!
It penetrates right through your body!
It could be dangerous if too much
water mixed in with your blood!
That's a silly thing to say.
Although, it is nice to have some
evidence that you are relaxing.
Hmph.
Is that Chitanda?
Oreki! What happened?! Is he okay?
He got dizzy from the baths.
Huh?
Have you ever heard of
anything so pathetic?
He wasn't even in there
half as long as I was,
but before I knew it, he had fainted.
I-I don't believe you...
Ugh... Sorry to put you out, both of you.
You are quite welcome.
Oreki, you are simply destined never
to be able to enjoy an event, huh?
Absolutely right.
Maybe I had some leftover carsickness, too.
I feel sick.
Is that Chitanda?
Oreki-san, are you all right?
Not really.
You're still so hot, huh?
Do you want me to wring you out a towel?
No... I don't want one!
Ah, I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry for casting a damper
on such a nice outing.
Not at all.
The rest of us are talking about
telling ghost stories now.
If you start feeling any better,
please come and join us, okay?
All right, take care.
Yeah.
It's still not even 8:00?
Taiko drums?
Actually, we could have gotten by
without having to build another hall.
Is the next room open, too?
There's a secret.
A secret?
Long ago, there was this brooding
old guest who stayed here.
He was put in Room 7 of the main hall.
He said he didn't want to
eat, and he didn't need a futon,
and to just stay away from him.
But he paid in advance,
and he came at a busy time,
so they said that he was a perfect fit.
However, that evening,
there was a terrible scream!
A scream?
There in Room 7 was the shadowy figure of a person,
dimly visible with a rope around his neck,
slowly swaying back and forth,
the story goes.
Word was that this man had taken money
from the company he worked for.
That's what I was waiting for!
Cut that out!
Ever since that happened,
guests that have stayed in Room 7
say that there's something in the room...
that there are shadows
that appear during the night.
Then, the ninth guest that stayed there...
What happened to them?
Sometime during the night,
they suddenly got sick and died!
Oh, no!
That's more like it!
I said knock it off!
So, Grandma called in an exorcist,
and then also had this second hall built
to keep any bad rumors from spreading.
Where is this Room 7?
Look, it's the room you can see
through the window, straight ahead.
We live down on the first floor,
and make sure not to go to
the second floor very much.
Y-You're kidding, right? It's a joke!
Listen, you can't tell anyone this story!
How quaint. Truly. Hmm?
Risshu ('Dawn of Autumn')
The time of the first stirrings of autumn
Hyouka
It's morning, huh?
The Fuji Room
Ah, good morning.
Good morning. Where are Chitanda and Ibara?
I saw it.
What did you see?
Last night, after midnight,
a warm breeze woke me up,
and when I rolled over,
I saw the silhouette of a hanging man
in the room across the way,
slowly swinging back and forth!
It's pretty rare to see Ibara so shaken up.
Tough luck for Satoshi,
missing a sight like this.
Thanks for breakfast.
How were the open-air baths?
They were extremely refreshing.
Terrific!
Hm?
Rie
And I hope your futon was nice and fluffy.
Yes, I slept quite well.
It doesn't look like there's one for Kayo.
I didn't realize that you couldn't handle
a story like that, Maya-neechan.
I'm not afraid of ghosts. But when
I saw what I did point-blank...
There's a limit to how
creeped-out I can stand being!
Maya-neechan, you saw it?
I saw it! I totally saw it!
I really saw it!
Sis, you told them the story?
Dad said never to tell anyone!
Oh, buzz off. Who cares?
It's Maya-neechan, after all.
What's the matter?
Well, um...
what do you think about
what Mayaka-san says?
About seeing the silhouette
of a hanging man?
Well, you can't dismiss that it's an old staple,
something obligatory, and that's why it lives on.
So then, Oreki-san, do you think that
what Mayaka-san says is true?
No, I don't.
Then maybe I was mistaken.
Hm? What do you mean?
I saw it, too... the silhouette
of a hanging man.
Mayaka-san had woken up,
so I woke up, too.
When I did, I saw it
suspended in the darkness.
Ho...
I thought that my mind could
be playing tricks on me,
but Mayaka-san saw the
same thing, too, so...
You must have mistook what you saw.
Like in that saying yesterday...
"Upon seeing the ghost's true nature..."
It was a beckoning flower? Hm...
If that's true, then what
did we see that fooled us?
Yeah!
If you're right, then tell us
what we did see that fooled us.
Why do I have to...
Oreki-san!
Let's investigate this together!
I am so curious!
I'm sorry, Chi-chan!
I promised Rie that I would look over
her summer vacation homework.
Leave it to us! We will be sure to
find out the truth behind this!
Right, Oreki-san?
She's asking me "right"?
In any case, what has to be done is at
least close by. Pardon the intrusion.
So then, you saw this shadow
directly across from your room?
Yes, that's right.
How big?
It wasn't too big, and it
wasn't too little, I'd say.
Shape?
I don't exactly remember.
Color?
I don't know. It was in shadow.
Shadow, huh? So you're saying
that it was lit from behind,
so it looked like the
silhouette of a person.
I believe so, yes.
Backlit, huh?
The only source of light at night
would have been the moon.
I think so, too. The moon was pretty
bright last night. Would that mean...
Oh!
Chitanda, what time did you finish
your ghost stories and go to sleep?
Let's see, it was 10:00.
And the shutters at that time?
I believe they were closed.
Hm.
As long as those shutters were closed,
there could be no shadow.
Now we're running into a problem.
At this point, we'll need to
check out Room 7 in the main hall.
This is nice and mysterious! I really
am glad we went on this outing!
I'd have been glad if we hadn't.
No Admittance
Say!
Y-Yes, what is it?
Would you?
Huh?
I suck with kids.
Oh, okay.
Kayo-san, can we have a moment?
We'd like to go into the main hall.
The main hall? But why?
We are investigating the
hanging-man shadow.
We'd like you to show us Room 7.
I'm sorry, I can't right now.
My sister would get mad at me.
Then, at least tell us one thing.
Is that room still a guest room?
No. Only the baths and the dining room
in the main hall are used by guests.
So, the room is vacant?
The whole second floor
is used for storage now.
May I go now?
Thank you. You've been very helpful...
She hates me, huh?
It doesn't matter, does it?
She's probably just scared of big men.
She's so cute!
Will not being able to see
Room 7 pose a problem?
Not so much a problem as a hassle.
We can't inspect the scene, after all.
Oh, my! I remember having these!
Rie
Hm?
Morning radio calisthenics.
I went to these, up until
the year before last.
Until her second year of
middle school? Really?
Let's check around the
other side, as well.
Did it rain last night?
Yes, a small shower.
In order for there to be a shadow seen,
both the east and west side shutters
would have to have been open.
Excuse me...
Lunch is ready.
Thank you for lunch!
It sure must be nice,
having a sister, all right.
Oh, yeah? Chitanda-san,
do you wish you had a sister?
Yes, a little.
So, did you find out anything?
No...
We're still just getting started.
I have a theory, though.
Yeah? Let's hear it.
Huh? Hm...
Now, see here.
What exactly are you talking about?
Don't go shutting me out.
Nobody's shutting you out. Where is it you're
always disappearing to? We never see you.
You don't get it, do you?
It's good manners to go and visit
the hot springs again and again.
Oh, is that a fact?
Ta-da! How do you like my yukata?
Wow, that's so neat!
Isn't that nice?
I finally had one bought for me
at the start of summer vacation.
You've said you wanted one
for a long time, huh?
Mm-hm!
Nice taste, huh?
What's wrong with it?
That sash.
I'll bet it's an imitation.
What do you mean, it's a mutant?
Not "mutation," imitation.
The bow is a separate piece,
clipped onto the sash.
I don't acknowledge that
as being a yukata.
That's ridiculous.
Is something the matter?
I wonder if I might have fallen under
the hanged shadow's curse, too.
Let's go to the same hot
spring as yesterday.
Okay.
The hanged shadow...
It's a product of Ibara and
Chitanda's false impression.
A beckoning flower.
But still, there's one piece missing.
Let's go back together, okay?
Satoshi's here.
You were just there sitting next to
us while eating, weren't you?
When did you manage to get here?
Oh, if you slide down the
cliff behind Seizanso,
it leads right behind here.
Sliding down a cliff, just to take a
shortcut? That's just like Satoshi.
I don't have an explanation
that will satisfy Chitanda.
The source of the shadow isn't too hard.
The question is, how did
it come to be there?
Hotaro, don't tell me you're dizzy again.
Say, was there some kind of
big event last night?
Yeah, Hotaro, you fainted.
No, not me!
Yeah, we all told ghost stories.
I was surrounded by more
girls than I could handle.
No, something more official.
Now that you mention it,
there was a summer festival.
You heard the taiko drums, right?
Taiko drums...
That's it! A summer festival!
That explains it.
So? Does that mean something?
So about the hanged shadow...
It was probably a yukata,
hanging on a hanger.
Huh?
Why would there be a yukata hanging there?
What's more, it's strange that
both shutters would be open,
to show us the yukata's shadow.
It wasn't done to show you.
Then...?
It was hung up to dry.
The yukata was wet.
The reason the shutters were open
was to let the breeze through,
to dry it quicker.
Why?
Because it rained.
Not that. Why was it in Room 7?
To prevent anyone from seeing
it being hung up to dry.
But we saw it.
Not you.
They were trying to hide
it from the family.
But why?
The one who hung up the yukata was Kayo.
Kayo was envious of Rie's yukata,
and wanted to wear it.
But I doubt Rie would lend it to her.
Why not? They're sisters.
Didn't you notice? Rie is the kind of
girl who clearly marks which cup,
which radio calisthenics card,
and which ball are hers.
She couldn't ask Rie to lend her
her yukata if she's like that.
Rie
Oh...
But Kayo still wanted to wear it.
So she snuck it out,
and wore it to the summer festival
yesterday. That was at 8:00.
Kayo-san went to the summer festival?
I saw someone leaving the house
at 8:00 last night.
Kayo wasn't there when you were
telling ghost stories, right?
You're right; Kayo-san was not there.
But then, Kayo ran into some bad luck
while she was enjoying the festival.
It started raining.
The rain let up quickly,
but the yukata was wet.
Kayo remembered we would be
setting off fireworks the next day.
Rie would undoubtedly want
to wear the yukata for that.
If the yukata wasn't dry by tomorrow,
Rie would blame her for it.
The family would see it on
the main hall's first floor.
The other hall was out of the question.
She can't use the dryer
in the middle of the night.
That's why Kayo waited until
everyone was asleep,
and dried the yukata in the most distant
room on the main hall's second floor.
But Kayo's run of bad luck would continue.
Moonlight shone in through the open window,
revealing the hanged shadow.
Then the last bit of bad luck came
when we started investigating
the hanging shadow.
Kayo had to have been agonizing.
No doubt that was Kayo's shadow
I saw between the sliding doors.
Kayo-san...
She put the yukata back
early in the morning.
Unlike Rie, Kayo went to radio
calisthenics every morning.
It would have been easy to return it.
So that's it.
I'm not going tell Ibara about this.
I'm sure there could be some
family issues at work here.
If that's true...
it would mean that the two
of them don't get along.
I mean, a sister who won't
lend you her yukata...
Isn't that what siblings do?
I...
wanted a sibling. An older
sister I could respect,
or an adorable younger brother.
I wonder if the sibling
that Chitanda desired
was a "beckoning flower."
It's so hot...
Ready?
Mm-hm.
Well, maybe they're not all
"beckoning flowers," either.
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Let's Go To the Screening!"
Let's Go To the Screening!