From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
It can no longer be overlooked that bears have crossed the Severance Barrier which must not be breached.
Izumino Sumika-san became the ultimate sacrifice, and at the present moment,
Akae Katyusha-san, Yurikawa Konomi-san,
and several other students have fallen out of contact.
Hakonaka Yuriika
LILY
This is the greatest crisis we have faced since the Day of Severance.
Fortunately, the bear that had infiltrated our school was shot to death last eve,
but you mustn't let down your guards.
Do you understand? The friends sitting by your side are your key to survival.
Stay together at all times, even on school grounds.
You must protect one another.
I will protect you myself.
Kureha?
I'm sorry.
But why? Just yesterday...
That wasn't my intention...
I understand, Tsubaki-san.
Yurizono Mitsuko
LILY
Rejection? Well, no matter.
I love that part of you as well.
The fun has yet to begin, Tsubaki Kureha.
I'll shower you with my love before eating you from head to toe.
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Well? Have you calmed down some?
Tsubaki Kureha
LILY
Yes.
Liar.
You're terrible at lying.
That all-too-serious part of you is just like Reia.
Reia... you mean my mother?
That's right.
You resemble her quite a bit.
There's no doubt you're her daughter.
Don't push yourself too hard, Kureha-chan.
The more you attempt to conceal the pain of loss in your heart, the greater it grows.
I understand that fact very well.
That day, I lost Reia.
And you, your mother.
My irreplaceable and once-in-a-lifetime friend.
That's why I was overjoyed when you came to this academy
and started to remake that garden.
A place replete with my memories of Reia.
I detest bears.
They are certainly detestable.
Bears stole from us our most precious person.
There's another.
What?
There's another bear.
But Yurizono-san eradicated the bear that attacked Izumino-san.
You're mistaken!
I saw them!
There's another bear! It must be hiding somewhere in this school!
I really must appreciate how well this school system was made.
My role is simply to sit and wait for the right time.
Yurizono-san.
In today's you-know-what, I'll take over as the leader in Yurikawa Konomi-san's place.
Oniyama Eriko
LILY
How commendable of you, Oniyama-san.
Friendship in a class begins with awareness of one's role.
I really admire your leadership.
Strong people are beautiful.
Y-Yurizono-san?
Call me Mitsuko.
Lily dark!
You're a good girl, aren't you?
Hurry... hurry and bring me Tsubaki Kureha to eat.
Yurigasaki Lulu
LILY
Yurishiro Ginko
Growl?
Another bear is about.
Beware
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will exterminate the bears!
She's like, totally revved up to shoot bears!
Just when I thought we'd finally gotten one step ahead of that mean-old Yurizono Mitsuko!
Now we can't even get close to her!
Who could've expected that there'd be a rival bear
who knew our identities at school?
Deliciousmell, growl.
It's all in one ear and out the other with you, Ginko.
I bet Tsubaki Kureha is one delicious girl.
The Pope at the time,
taking the name of Pope Urban II, called together the kings and nobles of western Europe to form an army
and started the First Crusade in 1096.
This was the beginning of a long-lasting series of wars.
Flashback
You can have mine, Miss Scatterbrain.
And if anyone asks you if this will be on the test...
It won't!
No, it most certainly will! Don't test me!
Sumika... every class without you feels like an eternity.
Due to this Crusade, the people of western Europe...
Is this how you'll be forgotten?
With small events and happenings fading from memory...
And one day, I'll forget my love as well,
and become invisible...
Your mother's garden?
Flashback
Slightly over half a year ago
HISTORY
Yeah. Back when she was a student here,
she made it with her precious friend.
So that was her love.
I want to fill it with flowers once more.
Of course you wouldn't back down, Kureha-chan.
Yeah.
You precious mother's garden
is your love now, Kureha-chan.
My love?
Yes, love.
That's why I won't back down either, Kureha-chan.
Not on my precious love.
I won't forget.
I'll never forget.
Sumika, I won't back down on love either.
We must remain invisible at all costs.
Let us now begin the Ritual of Exclusion.
Ritual of Exclusion
EXCLUSION
Friends are important above all else, don't you think?
We, in this classroom right now, are all friends.
Don't you think that those who deny
our feelings are the scum of the earth?
Those who stray from us are irredeemable.
People who don't stain themselves our color are nothing but trouble, right?
We have a word for people who can't read the mood.
Evil.
Can't read the mood = Evil
EXCLUSION
Izumino Sumika-san was killed by a bear because of that.
But that was entirely her fault.
For she was evil.
We must proceed to select the next evil to exclude.
Let's search evil!
Invisible Storm
EXCLUSION
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
She's been selected. The time has come!
She is mine.
I will eat Tsubaki Kureha!
Slurp.
Grind grind grind grind...
Beware
Kureha, did you play nicely with your friend today?
Really? I'm glad for you.
You must really care for her, Kureha.
Kureha, did you know?
So long as you don't forget love,
you will never be alone.
Don't forget that.
Yes. As long as I don't forget love,
I'm not alone.
Beware
Flashback
Currently, a heavy wind and flooding advisory has been released for the greater metropolitan area.
This is an exceedingly dangerous rainstorm.
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Evacuation warnings have been issued for several areas.
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
Flood
Watch
[Heavy Wind and Flood Advisory] Special Report on Greater Metropolitan Area
Evacuation
Warning
We advise everyone in the affected areas to...
Oh no, the garden!
Advisory
Heavy winds and flooding
Kureha-chan.
Aren't you cold?
I'm just fine, Kureha-chan.
Thanks, Sumika.
Thank you for being my friend.
Sure, and thank you, too.
I...
won't back down on love.
To live is to constantly forget and back down.
It is to leave behind.
That which does not renew itself is destined to perish.
We beasts do not live in the past.
All we have is the present—our immediate feelings.
What compels us each and every moment.
That is everything.
The order of this closed-off world is kept by the invisibles.
Grind grind grind grind...
Ginko, did you know?
I'll never be able to forget the day I met you.
You're the one who found my love and brought it to me.
That's why no matter what happens to me, I won't back down on love.
The time of judgement has come.
Growl growl.
restricted number
Yes?
Is your love true?
It's true.
This is a challenge from the Severance Barrier.
Tsubaki Kureha, if your love is true, then come to the rooftop at once.
The bears are awaiting you.
Entrust your body to the bears,
and your love shall be approved.
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will exterminate the bears!
I've been waiting for you, Tsubaki Kureha.
Yurizono-san? Why are you here?
To eat you, of course.
I'll tell you something interesting.
The one who ate your beloved Izumino Sumika was me, Yurizono Mitsuko.
I am a bear.
What are you saying?
I'm sure it's hard to believe, but I'm a bear.
Perhaps it would be more accurate to say I'm a bear taking the form of a human.
A bear in the form of a human?
Yes, and so was the bear I killed, Yurikawa Konomi.
Yurikawa-san?
But, wasn't she—
My friend? I suppose she might've been.
At least while she obeyed me.
Hey, did you know that there's only one thing to take into consideration when making friends?
Whether that girl is just the slightest bit inferior to you.
Then you'll have no problem controlling her.
Your face says that you can't
believe me, but I'm not surprised.
I'll show you proof that I'm a bear.
Those are Sumika's...
That's right. Do you believe me now?
That girl was certainly an oddball.
The entire time she was being eaten,
nothing but words of worry for you left her lips.
"I'm sorry, Kureha-chan!"
"Your love... I couldn't repair your mother's garden!"
"Even after I promised to not back down!"
"Kureha-chan, forgive me."
"I'm so sorry."
You aren't able to shoot me.
That's exactly why I love you.
Yes, glare at me more with those eyes burning in fury.
I can feel it; your blood is boiling!
You reek an irresistible scent.
Come on, get more angry.
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will... exterminate the bears!
Didn't I just tell you?
You can't kill me!
No... it can't be...
You can't hit.
You can't hit me!
Don't worry! Because I ate her, I'll take Sumika's place
and give you all my love!
I want to eat!
I want to eat that girl right now!
Enter!
The Lily Court is now in session.
Lily Court in Session
TRIAL
Your Honor, hurry with the Lily Approval.
I want to save Tsubaki Kureha, growl!
Save Tsubaki Kureha? Such nonsense.
You two are bears!
We eat people.
If we didn't, we wouldn't be able to protect Ginko's love!
So you choose to admit your own guilt.
Very cool.
Objection!
Eating people is no crime of bears!
Shiny shine!
Please give your judgement before it's too late!
I see. That is sexy.
Shabadadu.
I ask of you, bearfendants.
Will you become invisible?
Or will you eat humans?
We will eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily, Approved!
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily Approved!
Don't back down!
Where am I?
Kureha, don't back down on love.
Only love can change this world.
My... love.
Yes, your love.
Love.
Lick.
What is this? Their tongues feel a bit rough,
but they're warm and gentle!
I've felt this sensation before...
It's time, Kureha.
I can do it!
Bestow upon me the promised kiss!
I... killed her. Yurizono-san...
But... but that...
A bear can't be a person...
So what'd you call me out here for?
You two aren't qualified to take part in the Ritual of Exclusion yet.
As long as you don't mix in with the
Invisible Storm, we won't be your friends.
That's unnecessary, growl.
Growl... instead of that, we'll tell you
something interesting, Oniyama-san.
Something interesting?
Say, where do you think your friends that are missing went?
Missing... you mean like Akae-san?
There.
Huh?
Wh-What is that?
The leftovers after eating Amae Katyusha are buried there.
Akae Katyusha
LILY
Aren't we kind?
Wh-What does that mean?
You ate... Akae-san?
Why would you tell me that?
Grind grind grind.
Growl.
Because in just a moment...
Shock!
Bear Shock!
We're going to eat you.
Slurp.
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger