Quiz Trial 7
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
A Corpse By Evening
Championship Round
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
|̶|̶|̶|̶ |̶|̶|̶|̶ |||
Wall Newspaper Club
Gathering news
Fortunetelling Club
Fortunes of every kind
Each reading 20 minutes
The Fortunetelling Club has already
lost its Wheel of Fortune.... Jumonji
It will be returned after
the culture festival is over.
Getting Around at Kanyasai
"Correct" "Incorrect"
"Incorrect"
"Correct"
"Correct" "Incorrect"
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
Hyouka
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
Manga Club collection on sale
100 reviews of manga through the ages!
Must see! Showdown underway
Battle of the Maidens of Manga
A heated debate on manga theory
173 copies remaining
"A Corpse By Evening"
Kaburaya Middle School Bulletin
"Body Talk"
Town News Magazine
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having
antennas is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Wild Fire