Hey, guys! You got time on your hands?!
Yeah!
Quiz Trial 7
Do you want to
be the quiz king of Kamiyama?!
Yeah!
Quiz Trial 7
Let's at least get
you through the preliminary round!
Yeah!
Quiz Trial 7
Quiz... Trial...
Seven!
Yeah!
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
A Corpse By Evening
Question number one!
The term "adamant" refers to diamond,
while the term "beryl" refers to emerald.
Is this true? Or is this false?
I suppose that's a decent first question.
The answer is...
true!
I'll show them who the true database is.
Our numbers are gradually
getting squeezed down!
Will this be the final question
of the preliminary round?
Here comes question number seven!
The word darui [listless] derives
from the English word "dull."
Is this true? Or is this false?
Huh?
Which is it?
Hm, it seems like it ought
to be derived from it, but...
Well, Mayaka?
Huh?
What do you think?
Hm...
True, maybe?
The answer is...
You don't have to build it up!
False!
That completes the preliminaries!
Yahoo!
Congratulations to those
who answered correctly.
The championship round will
be held on this platform.
Come on up!
Championship Round
Yo!
Fukube, that's an interesting outfit.
Here's our first finalist!
Who is he, again?
Please tell us your name and class.
Y-Yeah, well...
I'm Shimizu Noriko, Class 3-E.
You didn't even notice me here, huh?
The winner will be the first
one to score seven points.
I was too focused on the quiz.
Ah, I remember now.
How do you feel about your chances?
So, Tani-kun, how's the Go Club?
Yes, well, I am a little nervous.
Hm? The Go Club?
All right, let's introduce our
second finalist. Name and class?
I've got a funny story about that.
Goto Naoki, Class 2-C. I'll do my best.
Wanna hear it?
Okay then, our third finalist...
Yeah, coming!
Come on, let's go.
Wow! He has a giant Saturn
on top of his head!
Your name and class, please?
I'm Fukube Satoshi, of
the Classic Lit Club!
Huh?
The Classic Lit Club!
Wow, we have a Classic Lit Club!
From your outfit, I'd say you have
lots of odd club activities, huh?
Oh, yeah! Yes, odd club activities!
After all, our goals are not well-defined.
Huh? Is that right?!
We knew that creating an anthology
was one of our activities,
so we did make one. And if I do
say so myself, it came out awesome!
We put our all into it.
We put our all into it, all right...
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
|̶|̶|̶|̶
|̶|̶|̶|̶ |||
copy-number-wise.
In fact, we uncovered an important
secret about the Kanyasai!
Oh, what is that?
The origins of the Kanyasai name.
"Kamiyama High School Culture Festival" did
not simply get compressed down to "Kanyasai."
The Classic Lit Club has...
learned the truth!
Then what is the origin?
To find out...
Please buy one!
For just ¥200, the 45-year-old secret
of Kamiyama High School's
culture festival can be yours!
Our anthology, Hyouka, is selling fast
in the Earth Science Prep Room, on the
4th floor of the auxiliary building.
Pitch successful. I don't care
if I win at this point.
Oreki-san!
How did it go?
According to Tanabe-san,
having them placed at other clubs'
locations will be fine.
So, I tried to go discuss it with
Irisu-san, but I never made it there.
Yeah, I get the picture.
I don't know what to do.
Satoshi's plug was pretty interesting.
Hm? Plug?
That's it! As I recall, the Wall Newspaper
Club is putting out an extra.
I'll go ask them if they will
cover the Classic Lit Club.
Always on the go, huh?
Hm?
Wall Newspaper Club
Gathering news
Excuse me!
Did you need something?
Hello, Togaito-san.
Could I ask you to cover
the Classic Lit Club?
Huh?
I'm not sure I understand what you mean.
I beg your pardon. I came to ask
if you would be good enough
to include an article promoting the
Classic Lit Club in the wall newspaper.
Hm... well, um...
I'm not in the club anymore.
I'm a 3rd-year, so I've retired.
Oh, excuse me. Then would you mind
introducing me to your juniors?
That would be fine, but I don't
think it will do any good.
They're running a one-page
extra in two hours,
so their lineup is already
set up in advance.
And it's impossible for
them to run anything?
I wouldn't say it's impossible.
There's some room available on the page
if you can wait until
after noon on Day Two.
There are over 50 organizations
with booths at Kanyasai,
and they give priority to
those who merit attention.
And forgive me for saying so,
but the Classic Lit Club is only
publishing an anthology, right?
B-But the anthology contains...
Each club is serious about what it does.
If there's a story that will
garner everyone's attention,
I'll ask them myself to run
an article about it, okay?
A story, you say?
Very well. Please excuse me
for taking up your time.
If you have any interesting
stories come up, drop by again.
I may be able to help you.
Eru...
Kaho-san!
Long time no see.
Is Uncle Jumonji doing well
after everything that happened?
100 percent. But never mind him,
how are you? You seem unusually down.
I've got a lot going on.
Hm?
Come on in.
Fortunetelling Club
Fortunes of every kind Each reading 20 minutes
If you like, I can read your fortune.
This is always so amazing.
Let's see... All right,
let's do tarot cards, please.
Oh, I'm afraid I can't.
Huh? Why is that?
Eru, you enjoy these, don't you?
The Fortunetelling Club has already
lost its Wheel of Fortune.... Jumonji
What is this?
I'm doing this all by myself,
so I'm away from here quite a bit.
After stepping out for
a moment and coming back,
my Wheel of Fortune card
was gone from my tarot deck.
And that card had been left in its place.
"Jumonji"? Kaho-san, why is your
last name written on here?
Yes, why indeed?
Have you located the card that disappeared?
This was left here, too. I
think it will be coming back.
It will be returned after the culture festival is over.
For a thief, they certainly
are strange, huh?
Here, I think I'll show you one last thing.
Getting Around at Kanyasai
Is there
something special about that guidebook?
Its pages are the same as
the others going around.
It was left here together with that card...
opened to the last page,
with all the club comments.
Does all of this mean anything?
Who knows? As long as I get my
Wheel of Fortune back safely,
that's good enough for me.
And now, at last, it's our climax!
Shimizu-san and Goto-san
both have five points.
Meanwhile,
Tani-san and Fukube-san have six points,
and both of them are out to clinch this!
Who will end up taking it all?
Let's hear you all cheer them on!
All right, now for our next question.
Here it comes!
The formula to determine
the surface area of a sphere...
is 4πr².
Oho, that was quick!
I have not yet finished the question;
are you sure about this?
Yes.
All right then Shimizu-san,
your answer, please.
⁴⁄₃πr ³.
Correct
Incorrect
Correct!
Correct
Hooray!
The formula to determine the
surface area of a sphere is 4πr².
Please give the formula
to determine its volume.
The answer is ⁴⁄₃πr ³. Nicely done!
Shimizu-san is also now one step away,
as we have three contestants
with six points each!
We have a spectacular dead heat
going on. Goto-san, hang in there.
All right, now for our next question.
Here it comes!
Kamiyama High School's student
council president's full name...
is what?
Huh?
Yes, Shimizu-san?
Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Correct
Incorrect
You don't need to build it up anymore.
Correct
Incorrect
Correct!
The Quiz Trial 7 champion is
Shimizu Noriko, from Class 3-E!
Hey, Fukube!
Hm? Hey, so close, huh? Both of us.
The Quiz Trial 7 champion is
Shimizu Noriko, from Class 3-E!
Yep. I guess it's a draw.
So? What did you want?
Congratulations!
To continue that funny story about the Go Club.
Thank you very much.
Some of our go stones were stolen.
All right, the club president
will present you with your prize.
Oh, yeah? Not lost, but stolen?
Shimizu-san, please come forward.
There was a confession note
stuck in the go stone bowl,
that said "We've taken some
go stones from the Go Club."
Thank you for giving us such
a well-fought battle today.
It's not like we use all of them,
So they could take ten away,
And we wouldn't notice it.
What would they steal them for?
All right, ladies and gentlemen, the Quiz Club's...
Why, to play Five-in-a-Row, of course.
Quiz Trial 7...
Some other club is goofing with you.
Is now concluded! Thank you, everyone!
See you around.
Oh, hey, hold on!
I can't let this end in a tie between us.
Let's settle this! Where are
you competing next?
The Cooking Club, tomorrow.
Okay! We'll settle this
score for good there.
I can't wait.
Shimizu-san, how do you feel?
So tacky.
I'm not interested in
competing with Tani-kun.
I wonder if Hotaro is hard at work.
You open?
Y-Yes, we're open.
Is this what has the origins
of Kanyasai's name in it?
Mind if I thumb through it?
Yes, I do. It's only ¥200; please buy one.
We've got so many of them here, it hurts.
Senpai, your barn door is open.
Huh? Ah!
Aw, it's torn off.
Now what am I gonna do?
Here, please try this.
Hm? Oh! I'm surprised you
have one of these! Thanks!
For you. Take it.
An air gun?
It's a water pistol.
We're roasting sweet potatoes
in the Gardening Club.
Using a bucket to put out the
fire is so primitive, you know?
Then, you need this, don't you?
That's just my sidearm.
My main weapon is right here.
It's an AK.
'Zat so?
Later, man! Thank you!
A Glock 17, huh?
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
This collection was doomed from the start.
Nobody's coming, are they?
We should start making up posters now,
inviting customers in here, I tell you.
Mm-hm. But we all decided that
we would proceed like this.
Why are they looking at me?
Manga Club collection on sale
100 reviews of manga through the ages!
100 manga reviews?
Who's gonna read something
as stuffy as that?
Um, Kochi-san, that's enough.
I mean, there's no point
in reviewing anything.
It's a waste of time. Am I right?
Y-Yeah, well...
I wonder if Fuku-chan will believe me.
I really was trying to behave myself.
What do you mean, it is
a waste of time, Senpai?
It's a question that has everything
to do with the reader.
The reader?
That's right.
All manga starts out being
equally entertaining.
No matter who the writer is?
That's right.
Then, how do you decide whether
or not one is interesting?
Don't you know, Ibara?
It's up to the reader.
Ultimately, it depends on
whether the reader's antenna
for picking up on entertainment
stands high or low, that's all.
Then what you're saying is that those
who have their antennas low
can't pick up on what's interesting?
That's right.
Which is why I'm saying
that reviews do no good.
We should just read whatever we like,
and have a good laugh over it.
Every manga is the same? That's something
you'll never convince me of.
I won't back down.
Okay, Senpai, by that reasoning,
there would be no such thing as a
so-called masterpiece, would there?
No, there are masterpieces.
How would you define them?
Those that go on for many years, that manage to
hold lots of readers after they sift through them,
are the ones that are masterpieces.
You're wrong.
Hm?
Masterpieces are the ones that are
created masterpieces from the start.
Those that have not stood the test of time?
Now you're just being
subjective, aren't you?
You're wrong!
How so?
It's a question of experience.
Senpai, you've just never been
bowled over by anything
where you've had to say,
"This is incredible!"
Oh, yeah?
Well, aren't you the sassy one?
There's definitely a difference between
the talent and skill of different artists!
Senpai,
did you read the manga that was sold at the
school's culture festival last year that was called
A Corpse By Evening?
Haven't heard of it.
Then, I'll bring it tomorrow.
If it still doesn't convince you,
then I don't have anything left to say.
I've just ensured that I won't be able
to leave copies of Hyouka here.
Thank you very much.
What is this?
Welcome!
Battle of the Maidens of Manga A
heated debate on manga theory
Battle of the Maidens?
Excuse me.
Yes?
What is this?
It's over now. They will
go at it again tomorrow,
so by all means, come by.
Oh.
So, what did you think? About my plug?
Do you think it helped at all?
Yeah, I suppose.
173 copies remaining
We sold 14 copies.
Huh? Really?
Publicity works better than I expected.
We're off to a good start, huh?
I think I'll give it another shot tomorrow.
I should do pretty well
at the cooking contest.
You mean the three-man team one?
Huh?!
Three-man teams? Really?
He's on the executive committee, and he
doesn't have a handle on the events?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to increase
our number of outlets,
nor was I able to get us covered
by the wall newspaper.
Don't worry about it.
Although, there is something
I'm curious about.
Curious?
Nevermind.
I guess I'm not curious after all.
I'm positively thrilled to hear it.
Look, it says nothing
about three-man teams.
No mistake about it. I heard one
of the Cooking Club girls say so.
Aw, I misunderstood.
I thought I could enter on my own.
Come to think of it, Mayaka,
how did the Manga Club go?
Nothing happened!
Mayaka, Chitanda-san,
would you mind entering the
Cooking Club contest with me?
I can talk to my president
to see if she'll let me out.
If it will mean publicity,
I'd definitely like to enter.
All right! Now at least there's some hope.
How badly did you want to enter this?
I'm fairly proud of my cooking.
There's no way I was going
to miss a contest this fun.
Attention all students,
as well as all of our visitors,
this announcement marks the end
of the first day of our Kanyasai.
Those students still in the school,
Um, Oreki-san,
please lock your doors and make sure
all fires are out before leaving.
Did you, by any chance...
Oh, no.
Uh...
Ah! Nevermind, it's nothing.
Where is it?
Not here.
Where could it have gone?
A Corpse By Evening
Kaburaya Middle School Bulletin
Body Talk
I guess I'll bring this, instead.
No, no way.
Town News Magazine
It isn't anywhere.
How come?
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "Wild Fire."
Wild Fire