Mochizou!
If you've got time to laze around, come help out in the kitchen!
'Kay.
We're off!
Whoa! Hot!
Ah!
What's up?
It's Mochizou.
What?
Wanna go to the pool?
Hey, Tamako!
Huh? What?
What are you inviting a guy for?
You want him to see us in our swimsuits?!
Right. I guess not.
You're so lewd, Tamako.
I'll pass.
Oh, okay. Bye!
Do your homework.
That hurt!
As the heat of summer grows, our hearts sizzle with excitement.
But where do this girl's feelings lie?
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Shiori's late.
I'm here!
Sorry to make you wait.
Did you oversleep?
No, I forgot my swimsuit.
I thought about coming without it, but I decided to go back.
Yeah, I don't blame you.
No point going to the pool without a swimsuit.
Episode 5
We Spent The Night Together
Right! Left!
Right!
Hey! Keep your back straight!
So Tamako can't swim?
You can do it, Tamako!
I don't think I can!
Okay, I'm letting go now. Try swimming on your own.
Huh? Midori!
C'mon! We're going on a school trip to the beach in two days!
Give it your best shot!
Tamako...
I don't believe it.
She hasn't moved an inch.
How was that?
I think I made it pretty far this time!
How far did you get in swim class back in elementary school?
Rank thirteen!
"Can keep one's face underwater for ten seconds."
Oh, right. You were the only one who couldn't pass the underwater rock-paper-scissors challenge for rank twelve.
But it's scary.
I can't breathe underwater.
That's why you're supposed to come up for air.
You're saying the same thing Mochizou did.
Ooji? When did he say that?
I forgot.
I don't even want to remember.
Um...
Out of the way, Tamako.
O-Okay.
Kanna?
She went underwater...
Kanna?!
I'm gonna drown!
Floats like wood, sinks like a hammer...
Ow! What was that for?!
Don't space out while eating.
I was thinking about something important!
Something important?
What is it?
Nothing.
I bet it's just Tamako.
Oh.
Th-That's not it!
I'm done eating!
Sheesh.
Man, I really should've gone.
They went to the town pool, right?
Ah, Mochizou!
O-Oh, Tamako.
So you're here.
Yup.
Hey, wanna play in the pool together?
Uh...
N-No thanks.
It's not like I came here just to hang out with you, anyway.
Oh, I see.
I'm sure I'd just blurt out something stupid.
My boy.
Wh-What are you doing here?!
I have a name, you know.
I am Dela Mochidis Gusting,
a proud retainer to the royal—
I know all too well!
Don't just barge into my room!
You were the one who invited me in!
See? You put a welcoming chime on that door.
What?!
That chime signifies that a welcoming party is to be held here.
It's been a little over six months since my arrival,
so I suspect it may be a little late for a party.
If you insist, however, I'm willing to participate.
This is Japan, and here we call that a wind chime.
Nobody's throwing any kind of party.
What? How misleading!
Who's misleading who here?
Well, whatever.
What's on your mind?
Huh?
You seem troubled.
Ack.
When did you get here?
"Hey, wanna play in the pool together?"
"N-No thanks."
"It's not like I came here just to hang out with you, anyway."
Around then.
You heard all that?!
With how you carried on, how could I not?
I don't need advice from a bird.
Leave me alone!
Are you in love?
I can read you like a book, my boy.
Shut up!
Who is this lass for whom you yearn?
Come on, say it.
Is it Shiori?
I'm afraid you can't have her.
It's not!
The florist, then?
You'd best not.
That one's way out of your league.
Listen to me! You've got it all wrong!
Could it be my girl?
N-No way.
My boy,
I really can read you like a book.
Just go away already!
My girl, eh?
You're telling me that you live so close, yet you still haven't told her how you feel?
And you call yourself a man?
Shut up!
I tried to tell her last year, and the year before that!
But Tamako just doesn't reali—
So it really was her.
Shaddup!
Well, that settles it.
You need love advice, and I happen to be an expert. Fate must have brought us together on this day.
What's more, that very girl has courted me in the past as well.
Tamako courted you?
Rest assured, I am a bird of noble birth.
I politely refused her proposal,
though she seemed quite heartbroken.
That is why I understand her feelings like the back of my own wing.
Pull the other one.
If you think I'm lying, then so be it.
I merely offered my assistance to you as a fellow man.
Fare thee well.
Wait.
You're getting quite tan, Anko.
What?!
But I've been using sunscreen!
You come too, Anko!
You'll be fine as long as you come up for air.
Oh, she's sleeptalking.
Put a bedsheet over her.
Okay.
Like this! Get it?
Now you try it!
This angle is the key!
If you do this, women will swoon at your feet!
Oh, come on.
Like I could.
Long-distance swimming?
I guess the ocean's nothing like our swimming pool.
I'm getting excited.
Cheer up.
You only need to get through the swimming.
The rest is all fun and games.
You're right!
Oh, and I brought these for tonight.
Mochi?
Yup! That's right.
We can roast them over the campfire.
I've got enough for everyone.
They look great.
Here you go.
Trust you to think of that, Tamako.
Mochi's a bit heavy for summer, though.
No way! They're great during summer too.
Don't you often see them on shaved ice along with green tea and red beans?
Aren't those rice dumplings?
You can use mochi too.
Wouldn't it get all frozen and hard?
You could heat it up first.
But then it'd melt the ice.
That still sounds tasty in its own right.
You're right. There's more to mochi than meets the eye.
You said it.
Whoa!
Hey! How long do you intend to keep me stuffed in here?!
Stay inside, will ya?!
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Rest assured.
Just leave it to me, and you'll find your love requited in no time!
More to the point, I hope you weren't lying about bringing me to the beach in here.
Attention, please! Line up according to your roll numbers and take your seats.
All right, just stay quiet.
Hey, come on!
Let me out!
Oh!
Wow!
Double bunks! Nice!
Huh?
Kanna?
She's totally getting into it, isn't she?
But we don't go swimming until tomorrow.
I love long-distance swimming.
Hey, you okay?
Ugh, my head's spinning.
I feel sick.
Look, it's the sea.
Oh, it is indeed.
The salty breeze brings back memories...
This is the first time I've seen a bird get motion sickness.
Ugh...
Are you going to puke now?
It's no good.
I will visit the sea when I feel better.
My boy,
did you ready a letter?
A letter?
Oh, right. I wrote one, yeah.
Very well. Read it out loud.
Here?!
E-Er...
I have something I want to tell you.
Could we meet outside tonight?
What's with that insipid letter?
Well, no matter.
I hope you've practiced the courting ritual.
Like this! This angle!
Give it a rest already.
Dela?
Tokiwa!
Why is Dela here?
Ah, a friend of my girl.
Actually, this boy here asked me to help with his court—
No particular reason!
What's this?
It's nothing, really.
Hey, hurry up and deliver it!
Good heavens. What a troublesome lad.
I wrote this because you said you'd deliver it for me!
Boys aren't allowed in the girls' lodge!
Just go already.
Huh?
Now, where could my girl be?
Hey, my girl!
Oh. Midori, there you are!
Over here!
Hey, my girl!
What?
I could've sworn I heard Dela's voice just then.
R-Really? I didn't hear a thing.
Tokiwa.
What's her problem?
Tamako Market
When I close my eyes like this and listen to the sound of the waves, it brings back memories of my homeland.
My prince, I will definitely...
Hm?
Uh...
Who might you be?
I bet you could weld something in this heat.
Is it ready yet, Tamako?
Just a little longer.
It looks great.
Does it?
Seriously, what's with you?
Nothing.
I'm just worried you might be bothering Tamako.
It's got nothing to do with you.
It does too.
Why don't you just quit following Tamako everywhere she goes?
I haven't been doing that in the first place.
You have!
Look, I'll be honest. Tamako isn't interested in you at all.
Don't bother asking her out. You're wasting your time.
A-Asking her out?!
I wasn't even going to—
Then what were you doing?
How do I say this...
I can't leave her alone.
I'm worried about her.
Yeah. I'm just worried.
I mean, she's kind of an airhead and a bit of a ditz, isn't she?
That's why.
Really? I don't agree.
Doesn't matter. That's how it is.
I've known her since we were toddlers.
Only 'cause your dads both run mochi stores!
I've spoken to her loads more.
I talk to her as much as you!
And I know her much better than you do.
Oh, really? Did you know she can swim 25 meters now?
Are you serious? That's awesome!
Er...
I'll give you that one, but did you know she used to wear glasses?
What?
Didn't think so!
Before she switched to contacts, she used to wear these huge full-rim glasses!
Of course I knew.
I've been with her since fourth grade.
Oh, yeah...
But I'm Mochizou, you know?
The mochi she loves so much is part of my name.
My boy!
Save me!
What are you doing?!
Begone!
How dare you bare your fangs at nobility, you wretched—
What the hell's wrong with you?!
Shoo! Scram!
Also, getting Dela to ask her out for you is just pathetic.
What? No! This is—
Either way, Tamako is my friend.
I'm the one who's going to protect her!
What I say to Tamako is none of your goddamn business!
Fighting, are we?
N-No, we're not.
This isn't a fight!
That's good.
I felt as though you were giving off the same scent, so to speak.
A muddled aroma with hints of instability, but one that should clear up soon enough.
The two of you are birds of a feather.
Like I care.
Huh? Dela?!
What are you doing here?
A man needs no reason to travel.
In other news, I've grown quite peckish, my girl.
We brought mochi.
Excellent!
Go forth, my girl.
Sure.
C'mon, you two. Let's go.
What are you standing around for?! Let's get moving!
Sorry. There's something I need to do.
Really?
Oh, what a marvelous sun!
Could my prince be gazing out at this very same sun?
Wait for me, my prince.
I will soon find you your bride.
Will I be okay?
Don't give up, Tamako!
You practiced hard! You can do this!
I-I guess...
Okay! I hope those of you who can't swim have put on your floaters!
If you're in trouble, call for help!
So the guys are done already...
They look a bit worse for wear.
Long-distance swimming sure is scary.
Tamako!
Oh man!
He looks ready to collapse!
Let's go, Tamako.
O-Okay.
Hang in there.
You can swim 25 meters now, right?
Yup!
What's wrong with that?!
Hang in there, Tamako!
You can do it, Tamako!
It looks more like you're floating than swimming, Kanna.
I'm good at long-distance swimming.
Oh, really?
Usagiyama Academy, High School Division
You did it! We're halfway there!
Huh? Is that Mochizou?
Looks like it.
I wish I was finished already...
Anyway. Let's go, Midori.
Hey, what do you think about Ooji?
Huh?
What do I think?
Usagiyama Academy, High School Division
Yeah...
He's my childhood friend.
Usagiyama Academy, High School Division
A comrade-in-mochi, even.
That's what I thought!
Usagiyama Academy, High School Division
What about me?
You?
Well...
I love you!
Thanks.
Nooooooo!
Dela?!
Good grief!
I never realized that we nobles had so many people out to get—
Everyone wants a piece of Dela!
Yeah, a literal piece...
Tamako...
Hey, Tamako!
The fireworks display's starting soon.
Everyone's gone outside already!
You said you were looking forward to it—
Yep! I'm wide awake!
She must be exhausted.
Huh? Kanna?!
What? Am I adrift?
You're gonna drown.
I hear fireworks, Shiori, Kanna!
She woke up.
Let's go! Don't get too comfy there, you two!
Tamako's amazing, isn't she?
Yeah.
What? Why?
No reason in particular.
I'm just saying that if you want to tell Tamako something, you can go ahead and tell her.
Nah, I'll pass.
Why?
It's none of your business.
That's true, but...
Wow, look!
They're huge!
Quick, let's watch from over there!
They'll look even bigger!
Wait, Tamako!
Go with them, Tokiwa.
Huh?
What's the point in sitting here with me?
Relax.
I'm not going to ask her out anym—
N-No...
Not that I was going to do it in the first place.
Why not?
There'd be no point.
No, I mean...
I didn't really have anything to tell her in the first place...
Ah, there you are!
Midori!
We found a great spot over there!
No one else is there yet!
I hear ya.
Let's go, Ooji.
Huh? I-I'm fine here.
Come on, Mochizou!
Hear that? Tamako's calling for you.
Shaddup.
I'm with Tamaya Fireworks!
Oh hey, that's the name of our shop!
I'm with Tamaya!
Tamaya!
You're welcome to try our mochi!
Tamaya...
...has delicious mochi!
Easily amused, are we?
Tamaya!
You're welcome to try "Ricecake Oh! Zee" too!
Hey!
This is fun, isn't it?
Fireworks of love, fireworks of the heart,
midsummer's night dreams, and feelings that erupt in splendor.
May none of them burst and fade away.
Dela?!
Looks like he's...
...in a lot of trouble.
I'll save him!
How's your homework coming?
Gimme a break! I've been doing it!
I sure hope so.
Don't come crying to me when you need help.
Since when have I ever done that?
We're off!
Whoa! Another hot one!
Heh!
Three idiots.
Heh.
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Smooth rice dumplings are just the thing for summer!
Tamako here.
They're great with icy, sweetened water too!
"All of the dumpling,
Contains the sugar that we,
Used as we made it."
Episode 6    I Felt Shivers Down My Spine Too
That was apparently a haiku by someone named Takahama Kyoshi.
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?