Wow!
Amazing!
There's snow everywhere! Everywhere!
It's so beautiful!
The scenery isn't bad,
but aren't these clothes a bit... you know?
I know they're rentals, but...
It's okay.
It'd be a waste if we didn't try to have fun on this trip!
Come on, everyone!
One, two...
I guess I'm just a natural skier.
Haruta, you're too cocky.
Oh, I'm getting it!
Pizza... Pizza...
I haven't skied since middle school, but I guess I still have it.
Minori-chan, you're pretty good.
You're really a sports genius!
Really?
You know, you're pretty good too.
I'm just average.
Okay, I'm moving forward. Now what?
Lean sideways according to the slope.
S-Sideways...
This isn't fun at all.
Move! Move!
Move!
My silky love
nijuuyon jikan zutto
24時間ずっと
Every hour of the day
My silky love
kimi no koto omou tabi
キミのこと想うたび
whenever I think of you
My silky love
modokashii kono kimochi
もどかしいこの気持ち
these impatient feelings
My silky love
tada afurekaetteku
ただ溢れかえってく
simply overflow.
suki to ieba kantan na no ni
スキと言えば簡単なのに
Even though it's easy to say "I love you"
kimi ga mae ni kichau to
キミが前に来ちゃうと
when you stand in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
個性がそびえ　私のコトを邪魔してる
my personality stands up and gets in my way.
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
いつもならば強気でイケる
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku na no ni
そんな性格なのに
that's just how I am.
donna ganbatte mite mo kabe wa kuzusenai
どんな頑張ってみても　壁は崩せない
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us.
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
察して欲しい…　この気持ちを
I want you to realise… my feelings.
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
だから私は　いつもキミに
So I always send a gaze
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
大好きだよと送る視線
of "I really love you" your way
saidai no yuuki de
最大の勇気で!
with all of my courage!
yaburesou na shiruku no haato
破れそうなシルクノハート
My flimsy silky heart.
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
キミに逢って気づいた　やっと
After meeting you, I finally realised
ai ni wa bukiyou dattan datte
愛には不器用だったんだって
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love.
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
忘れかけた恋の傷跡
The scars from love that I'd almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashita no kyun to
急に疼きだしたの　キュンと
have started to ache all of a sudden.
itsuka wa watashi rashiku suki to
いつかは私らしくスキと
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
言わなきゃ…今より弱くなっちゃうよ
I must say "I love you", or else I'll become even weaker.
Sheesh, getting run over by a sled hurts.
Wait, why do you have a sled?
No Matter What
It's not like I wanted to use it...
Could it be that you can't ski?
What are you so smug about?
I thought I was the only one in our class who couldn't ski.
I see, so you can't either.
It's the end of the world, right?
Ah, skiing is so boring.
What's so great about wearing two long planks and sliding on snow?
That's what I was wondering too...
Why don't you ask Kitamura to teach you how to ski?
How the hell is he supposed to teach me when I have a sled?
Besides, you're not getting Minorin to teach you.
Sheesh, you're putting all my effort to waste.
Hey, hey, hey!
The lift is for two, right?
I want to share one with Maruo!
Okay, but shouldn't you share one with Kashii?
Nanako and I want to take pictures of each other while we're on it.
Right?
What are they doing?
What is it?
Normally you'd say,
"Why is that gal girl acting so friendly with Kitamura?"
and then get pissed, right?
You...
Did something happen between you and Kitamura?
N-Not really...
Are you sure nothing happened?
Nothing! It's nothing, but...
Well, maybe something did...
Which one is it?
I just didn't tell you about it.
I had tea with Kitamura-kun after I bumped into him on New Year's,
then we went to visit a shrine for a New Year's prayer.
That's about it.
So something like that happened...
Why didn't you tell me about it?
You were in bed with the flu, so you didn't need the extra trouble!
And why do I need an excuse anyway?!
I don't have to report every single thing to you!
Hey, why are you so mad?
Why the hell do you always screw things up?!
Why do you always have to get in my way?!
You're really, really annoying-
You're the one who's screwing things up.
You play weird tricks so you can hang around Kitamura.
I'm not playing tricks!
You did, there's no doubt!
It's none of your business!
We just want our friend to be happy!
Right, Haruta?
Yes!
Wait, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry, but I think your tricks are disgusting, and it pisses me off.
Huh?
I don't give a damn if an idiot like you gets pissed off.
Hey, you guys...
All right, let's be nice to each other.
We're on a field trip, after all.
Come on, stop fighting.
Just do it for me.
What's the point of doing it for you?
I don't get you guys.
Anyway, just calm down!
Calm down!
Oh, gosh...
Yuusaku, are you thickheaded by nature,
or are you doing it on purpose?
What do you mean?
If you want to say something, just say it.
Oh my, I can't believe you're such an airhead.
He's nearly violent...
I can't believe the first day ended like this.
Confirming Kushieda's real feelings?
The field trip will be over before I even talk to her.
What's up with you?
Everyone is so weird today.
Look at them, they look so lethargic.
Taka-chan?
I'm going to use the toilet.
Kitamura didn't mention anything about visiting the shrine with Taiga to me.
I honestly don't get what's going on in their minds.
Sighing get!
K-Kushieda!
Going to the toilet?
Nope, I saw you leave the dining hall all alone.
I have a secret.
S-Secret?
Actually, I've been waiting for a chance like this.
M-Me too-
Noto-kun and Maya-chan were fighting, right?
I want to relieve the tension between them.
We're on a field trip, after all...
I don't want people to be fighting.
So-
Huh, what's wrong?
N-Nothing.
I just thought the exact same thing.
Do you have any ideas?
Well, the problem is that Maya-chan wants to be around Kitamura-kun, or something.
That's one view of the problem.
Y-Yeah...
Takasu-kun, do you know why Noto-kun wants to stop Maya-chan's love?
It's because he misunderstood and thinks that Taiga likes Kitamura-kun,
and he wants to help Taiga, so...
It's not really a misunderstanding.
I'm sure there are things about Taiga that you don't know.
That's impossible!
There's nothing I don't know.
I know everything about Taiga.
What's that?
Oh, this?
Taiga gave it to me.
She said it's a treasure, so I'm going to really cherish it.
Cute, right?
Oh, I'm talking about the hair clip, not myself.
It's no use, Taiga.
It's no use no matter how hard I try...
This is what they call reality.
Kushieda can't accept my feelings.
Regardless of what happened on Christmas Eve, or of my one-sided feelings,
she pretends that it never happened.
Takasu, are you all right?
Are you okay?
We're worried about you, Takasu!
We're really worried!
Takasu, are you really asleep?
Let's find out!
Wait, Kitamura, what are you doing?!
Why are you taking your clothes off all of a sudden?
You're only undressing your bottom part! How perverted are you?!
That's not all, you're waving it on top of Takasu's face...
I can't hold it anymore. There's some mysterious gas in my butt...
You assholes!
So did something happen?
B-By Kushieda, you mean that Kushieda?
Are there any other Kushiedas?
That's right, it's Kushieda Minori!
I've been in love with that weird girl for over a year!
I'm sorry!
But I was rejected on Christmas Eve before I could...
I-I see.
But why did Kushieda reject you?
Beats me.
I want to know too.
If I were a girl, I would definitely go out with Taka-chan!
No, going out with you would be bad.
All right, let's go.
Where?
To find out.
Wait, wait, wait! Stop!
It's all right, Taka-chan.
Yeah, it's like what happened in Chushingura.
You're Asano Takumi-no-kami, and we're the Akou Ronin.
Yeah, and Kushieda is Kira.
Oh, Kira is so cool!
I even rented the DVDs...
I'm sure Kitamura is using me as an excuse to take revenge on the girls.
We're coming, girls!
We're going to-
Huh? No one's here.
The door was unlocked too.
Also, why is it so messy?
Takasu, control yourself!
You can't tidy it up!
I found a navy blue camisole!
I found a wet towel...
Hey, stop!
Takasu-
I never knew you had a...
No, that's not it.
It's not what you think.
I can't tolerate an odd number of socks, so I'm pairing them up to make them even.
Why Taiga of all people?
Oh, whoops.
How could she wipe the tatami with that?
Hey, don't wipe your hair with that!
Calm down, Takasu!
Huh?
The door's open.
Did Taiga come back first?
As I thought, no one's here.
I'm begging you, don't talk!
Please!
This is the only time I've ever begged you!
That felt great.
Nanako, you love taking baths, don't you?
By the way, Ami-chan, your curves are great! You're amazing!
Really?
I never wanted to be an actress.
Where did Taiga go?
She came back to the room first, right?
Kushieda, that's impossible.
Don't tell me Taiga went to the guys' room by herself.
She might be together with Maruo and...
No way, you're overthinking it.
Wouldn't it be possible for Yuusaku to walk in on her and Takasu-kun doing stuff?
Having fun...
If that were real, I would totally hate it!
Besides, I wonder what's going on in Taiga's mind.
Is she really interested in Maruo?
Kushieda, what do you think?
Between Takasu-kun and Maruo, which one do you think is Taiga's favourite?
Well, it'd be troublesome for me to answer.
Just ask Taiga herself when she comes back.
Why would she tell us?
Kushieda, you've been pretty quiet since we got back.
Really?
Maybe I'm tired from skiing.
I've been sleepy since we got back.
Don't count on getting any sleep tonight.
We're going to have a girl talk.
I wonder if Takasu-kun could get Taiga.
That would make all these problems disappear.
And so, Minori-chan was dragged into her sea of thought.
What do you mean, Ami-chan?
This is relevant to my interests!
Oh, you heard me?
I'm sorry, Minori-chan.
I said something I shouldn't have because you were spacing out.
Come on, don't just stare at each other.
Hurry up and tell us, Ami-chan!
Now that Maya-chan has said that, what should I do, Minori-chan?
Should I tell them?
Tell them what?
You should know...
How you rejected Takasu-kun before he could confess on Christmas Eve.
Did you forget?
What?!
Really? Did Takasu-kun confess to you?
Wait, Ami-chan, how do you know about it?
Huh, how do I know?
It sure is mysterious.
Amin, why did you bring that up?
Because you're always spacing out.
I'm just saying it to spite you because it seems you don't really care.
Takasu-kun is interested in you, not Taiga,
but you rejected him.
I think you're just pretending to be an airhead so you can just forget about it.
You're probably thinking "Let's just be friends forever".
When did you see me pretending that nothing has happened?
Did you really see it?
What do you know about me?
Can you look into my heart?
Besides, this has nothing to do with you.
I see, so it has nothing to do with me...
Oh, I see!
So your sense of guilt is nothing too, right?
I thought you at least had some feelings for Takasu-kun.
I thought you rejected him because you thought you'd feel guilty about someone.
But now I see.
You rejected him simply because you don't like him.
I'll tell him about it tomorrow, then.
Don't you think it'd be kinder to just end it now,
than to leave him half-dead?
Do whatever you want.
Then, should I go now?
I said, do what you want!
You're really good at faking.
Cut it out!
Ami-chan, what's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Why are we all arguing on a field trip?
Yeah, you went a bit overboard.
Just apologise, and let it be.
I'm sorry, Minori-chan.
I said too much.
Just forget it, okay?
All right, now it's over.
I've already forgotten about it.
Oh yeah, Taiga isn't back yet.
Yeah, you're right.
Where did she go?
L-Let's look for her together!
Come on, Kushieda, you too!
I think we just witnessed something that we shouldn't have.
Yeah, and Kushieda was a bit...
Am I the only one who doesn't get what they were arguing about?
Which country was Ami-chan talking about?
Hey, Taka-chan, what's going on?
I want to know too!
Anyway, we neither saw nor heard anything.
Got it?
This really...
...sucks.
What are you doing?
I'm tired, so I'm taking a break.
Hey...
There's something I have to apologise for.
It might be my fault that Minori-chan rejected you.
I said something sarcastic to Minori-chan when you weren't around.
I don't even know why I said it.
What do you mean?
You know, I had an argument with Minori-chan yesterday.
I just felt pissed off whenever I saw her face...
...because she never looked directly into my eyes.
No matter how hard I pushed her, I couldn't find out how she really feels.
That pissed me off.
I hate you because you're an idiot.
Not again...
I hate myself because I'm an idiot too.
I felt really guilty, and I exploded.
There were a lot of misunderstandings, and now it's like this...
Stupid Chi', move!
Seriously, I told you to move.
How many times are you going to do that?!
Are you retarded?
I apologised already!
I'll buy you some ice cream when we get back to the dorm!
No! It's too cold!
Amin, I'm sorry for not stopping.
What are you sorry about?
You did it on purpose, right?
There's no doubt that you did it on purpose.
No, no... I really couldn't stop-
You did it on purpose!
You still haven't forgotten about what happened yesterday, right?
You came to mess things up because I was having a chat with Takasu-kun, right?
Huh?
By "what happened yesterday", you mean the thing you started?
Just when I forgot about it you went and brought it up again.
Both of you, stop...
What do you mean you forgot about it?
You've been ignoring me all morning.
Your egotistical gaze pisses me off, you brainless Hercules.
Who's egotistical?
You're just pissed off because you're jealous!
You bitch!
No hitting the face, Hercules!
I thought you didn't want to be an actress!
Taiga!
I've always hated people like you!
You seriously piss me off!
Hey, this doesn't look good.
Oh, a follow-up on yesterday's argument?
You idiots!
Don't just stand there and watch, come with me!
I hate you!
Kawashima, calm down.
H-Hey!
Takasu, are you okay?
What the heck is going on?
Both of you, stop!
What's wrong?
Huh? Ami-chan!
Both of you, cut it out!
Hey!
What's wrong with you two?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Kushieda, you're not yourself.
Huh?
Taiga...
Taiga?
Hey, Taiga?
Taiga's not here...
All of the ski resort's staff are out looking for her.
If they can't find her, they're going to call the police.
Takasu!
Get a grip on yourself, they'll definitely find her!
Taiga...
What a terrible snowstorm.
Kushieda?
Those clothes...
I'm going to look for her.
Are you stupid?
This time, it might be you who'll-
But I can't just stay here!
I'll be right back.
I'll come back when I've checked the places we've been to.
But...
I'll go too.
You too?!
Shit...
I'll go with you guys.
Ami, tell the teacher we're going out to look for her.
Wai-
Taiga!
Aisaka!
Takasu-kun, Kitamura-kun!
This way!
There are some skid marks down here.
Be careful.
That's...
What's wrong?
Did you see something?
Probably.
Hurry and get some adults over here.
No, I'll go.
Ta-
Again...
I left her alone again.
She has always been by my side, but I never noticed.
Damn it.
That clumsy girl...
I'll never let go of you when I catch you this time!
nemurenai yoru ni wa
眠れない夜には
On the nights I can’t sleep
hitori de tameiki
ひとりでため息
I sigh alone.
minna wa dou na no
みんなはどうなの？
How is everyone?
nandaka sabishii
なんだか寂しい
I feel a little lonely.
Taiga?
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
広い大地に　ひと粒の種
Within the vast world,
a single seed
Taiga!
Hang in there, Taiga!
It hurts...
nekko nobashite
根っこのばして
extended its roots
I fell down.
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
まだ青い　実をつけた
and put out a fruit
that was still unripe.
It hurts...
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish
would turn orange soon
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
Ryuuji?
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
Kitamura-kun?
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams
just swell-
I thought you were Ryuuji.
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
Ryuuji would definitely save me at a time like this.
orenji itsuka
オレンジ　いつか
I wonder if someday the orange
amaku naru kana
甘くなるかな
will become sweet?
sore tomo shibonjau no
それともしぼんじゃうの？
Or will it wither away?
Sorry...
watashi no mirai shiritakunakute
私の未来知りたくなくて
I don't want to know
about my future,
I'm sorry...
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
Kitamura-kun, you know...
suppai
すっぱい…
It's sour...
The God of Broken Hearts' blessing didn't work.
suki da kedo nakeru yo
好きだけど泣けるよ
I love it, but I feel like crying.
My wish didn't come true.
Please take these feelings away from me...
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish would
turn orange soon
Make me stronger.
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
I'm no good right now...
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
No matter what I do,
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams
just swell-
I can't stop...
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
...loving Ryuuji.
orenji kyou mo
オレンジ　今日も
Today, I tried eating an orange
tabete mita kedo
食べてみたけど
mada suppakute naita
まだすっぱくて　 泣いた
but it was so sour I cried.
watashi mitai de nokosenai kara
私みたいで残せないから
I couldn't leave it behind like I have been,
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
suki da yo
好きだよ
I love it.
suppai
すっぱい
It's Sour.
nakeru yo
泣けるよ
I feel like crying.
suki da yo suki da yo
好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it... I love it.
Next Episode Preview
The Scene With You
Taiga likes me?
Why did she pick me?
You're such a player!
I'm afraid that's not true, sorry.