They're sho pretty!
Erika Shower!
Stop it, Erika!
Give us a break!
Take that! And that! And that!
Let's all work together and get Erika, everyone!
Right!
Sawai!
Yes?
Come and help us get Erika, Sawai!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
I can't think of any new designs...
Me neither...
We've been drawing pretty much
non-stop since yesterday, after all...
I can't go on anymore...
Me neither...
What should we do, President?
Hmm...
To be honest, I'm kinda running out of ideas too...
I've got it!
Let's go for a walk! It'll be a nice change of pace!
We can't!
Why not?
You said you wanted us to light some fireworks together this evening.
You're the one who said we should get the designs done during the day, Erika.
Right... I did...
Grr...
It'd be nice if designs would just
flow through my mind like water...
Oh!
Speaking of water, there's this pond behind the villa.
I think there was a rare flower growing there!
What was it called, again?
Let's see. It was a water...
Water ca...
You mean a water canna?!
Right, that.
Is it really that rare of a flower?
It is! It hardly ever grows, and has
the most beautiful purple flowers...
Ahem.
W-Well, a little walk couldn't hurt, could it?
All right!
Yay!
Naomi, what was with that lifeless high five?
I can't wait to see it!
Be Brave!
Making Friends is Truly Amazing!
The air out here is really nice!
Yeah, it's really clean and refreshing.
A change of pace really is important every now and again, huh?
Y-Yeah, you're right...
We're nearly there now, so let's keep on moving!
Ahhh, it's a spider!
Look out!
Sawai, are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
Thank goodness.
Sorry about this.
You'll be all right over here.
She's so cool!
You're so brave, Itsuki!
Will you please walk in front of me?
Sure, fine by me.
Don't worry! Everything's okay now!
Now let's get back in the adventurous mood and keep walking!
Okay!
Naomi?
Oh, it's nothing. Sorry...
It feels nice when the water splashes, doesn't it?
Naomi, Itsuki was really cool back there, wasn't she?
Yeah!
It's not far, right?
Just a little further!
Tsubomi, the thing is, I've always really
admired the student council president.
She's cool, athletic, and great at studying.
I've always considered her to be special, on a higher level than someone like me.
I know how you feel, Naomi!
When I first transferred here, I didn't know Itsuki was a girl,
so I, um... developed a bit of a crush on her...
We're lucky to have you leading the pack, Itsuki!
Jeez, Erika, what are you saying?
Must be nice...
Naomi?
Oh, nothing.
I just don't know what I should do to become friends with the student council president.
Her joining the same club as me,
and us all going to camp together...
I never dreamed something like this would happen.
Naomi...
Say... Tsubomi, how did you manage to become friends with the student council president?
Huh?! Well, um...
It's kinda hard to explain, really.
I guess it must be.
I just wish I could make friends with her as easily as everyone else has.
But I don't know what I should do.
It's so beautiful!
Not bad, Erika!
It's not bad at all, is it?
Hey, a water canna!
Wow, it's so pretty!
Well then, I think it's finally time to eat!
It looks delicious!
Your mom's a good cook, Erika!
She really is!
These sandwiches are delicious!
That was delicious!
Thanks! I'm sure Mom'll be glad you like 'em!
Hm?
Erika, can I have a word?
I see... So Naomi's worried about that, huh?
This is as good a chance as she'll get, so it'd be nice if she could become friends with Itsuki...
What should we do to help her?
Just leave it to me!
It's time for the Heart-Pounding Whirlwind Seating Arrangement Changing Event!
Huh?
E-Erika!
Um... I-I...
So, uh... what do we...
All right, now it's time to start the Exciting Conversation Event!
Um... err...
Come on, you two! Get talking, get talking!
Come on, quickly! Quickly!
E-E-Erika, you idiot!
Huh?
Sawai!
Jeez, Erika, you're so pushy.
Sorry...
At last, it is complete!
My new finisher!
Big Bang Kumojacky Summer Wave Crasher Special!
Sasorina! Kobraja!
Let's show those Precure the results of our training!
Hm? What's this?
"Training possesses not a shred of beauty. It doesn't suit me in the slightest.
But make sure you work hard nonetheless.
Adieu!"
What?!
Oh, so that's where you were, Sasorina?
Hey. Sasorina!
Why are you spacing out like that?
Wait, I remember!
So that's why?
Hmph! Well, that's fine.
I shall walk this path alone!
That's what being a man is all about!
Say your prayers, Precure!
I'm such a wimp, aren't I?
Erika gave me the perfect opportunity, and I just...
It seems I've found a sad little runt!
Who are you?!
The Flower of your Heart has withered, so I shall take it!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
What?
A Desertrian!
Green teaaaa!
Ichuki!
Potpourri?!
We have to shtop the Desertrian before it comes any closher!
Right!
Sheed of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
Green tea!
So the third Precure makes her entrance, huh?
Go get her!
This third Precure isn't bad at all!
Did we keep you waiting?
We're sorry for being so late!
Blossom? Marine?!
All right, this is where the battle really begins!
So you two finally bothered to show up.
Desertrian! Crush them into dust!
Green tea tea tea tea!
Greeeeeeen teeaaaaaa!
I just want to be friends with
the student council president!
I just want to be friends!
But I'm just too nervous to be able to talk to her!
I can't even make eye contact with her!
Why is it when I look at her face, I can never find the words I want to say?!
I just want to make friends with her like everyone else has!
Blossom! Marine!
The student council president!
I just want to be friends with
the student council president!
I want to be her friend!
Just how should I...
respond to Naomi's feelings?
How ridiculous.
You want to be friends?
Such a ludicrous reason for the
Flower of your Heart to wither so.
There is but one way to make a true friend!
And that is to let your burning fists do the talking!
So cease your whining and plunge headlong at her!
Get her, Desertrian!
Green tea!
She may not know how she should become friends with the girl she most admires,
but that doesn't mean you can just
ridicule the pain a girl feels in her heart!
Using her heart to create a
Desertrian like that is just cruel!
I just want us to be friends!
Making friends is really simple, you know!
You already want to be friends with her, after all!
Marine's right!
If you both feel that way, then you
and Itsuki are already friends, Naomi!
Right, Sunshine?
Yeah!
We're friends!
You and I are already friends!
I-I'm so happy!
Desertrian!
You cannot become stronger with such a half-hearted attempt at friendship!
Kumojacky!
Hm?
Everyone has their own ideal of what friendship means to them!
But you force your beliefs on others and
belittle those who think differently from you.
That darkness in your heart...
shall be illuminated by my light!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Tch... But this is where the real fight begins!
Behold, my new finisher!
Big Bang Kumojacky Summer Wave Crasher Special!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
What?!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Tch...
Hmph.
You've gotten stronger, haven't you?
All the better to keep me entertained.
If we have this many to choose from, everything should go perfectly!
So I think that wraps up our
designing for the school festival!
Right then, it's finally time to play with some fireworks!
Let's hurry and change into our yukata!
Right!
Thank goodness you've finally woken up.
President!
We found you lying unconscious in the woods.
Are you all right?
You did?
How strange. Did I not get enough sleep or something?
Don't worry, though. I'm all right now.
That's good.
Looks like you'll be able to enjoy the fireworks with us, Naomi.
Well then, I'll help you change into your yukata.
Thanks.
President?
What is it, Naomi?
Um... well...
Will you please become my friend?!
Let's be good friends, Naomi!
Let's!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Come on, you two! Hurry up!
Otherwise there'll be none left!
Sorry!
Are you all right, Itsuki?
Yes, thanks to you.
You finally called me by my name.
Yeah...
Hey, come on already!
Coming!
In the language of flowers, a strawberry flower means "love and respect."
Friendship is such a beautiful thing!
The very spirit of youth!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Enraptured by the scent of lavender and the sweet tones of the cello...
...in a nostalgic memory of the one she loves!
Such is the story of Cure Flower's first love!
Tsubomi's grandpa and grandma first met in a really romantic way, didn't they?
Your first love being a hot guy you met in Kamakura... Sigh.
First love, huh? I wonder what
my grandpa was like back then?
HeartCatch Precure:
Grandpa was a Hottie?!
Cure Flower's First Love!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!