Homura, I'm sorry.
I will become a Puella Magi.
Madoka... that's...
I finally understand.
I found a wish I want to get fulfilled.
So I'll use this life for that.
Don't... Then I... I...
Then what for...?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I think I turned out this way because you protected me and looked over me all this time.
I'm really sorry.
This is the answer I found.
Believe in me.
I won't let all your work go to waste.
Madoka...
You're shouldering the destinies of countless worlds,
and you're the focal point of all the fate lines.
No matter how impossible your wish is, it could probably be fulfilled.
That's right.
Now, Madoka Kaname. What do you wish for so much that you'll pay for it with your soul?
I...
I want to erase every witch before they are born!
Every witch from every world, from the past and the future. With my own hands.
That wish... If your wish is fulfilled, it'll surpass even space-time interference!
It's a treason against the wish itself!
Do you really want to become a god?
I don't care what I become.
I don't want to let all those girls cry.
All those Puella Magi who believed in their hope and fought against witches.
I want them to live on with smiles on their faces.
I will destroy the rules that prevent that. I will change them.
This is my prayer. This is my wish.
Fulfill it, Incubator!
Final Episode       You were my best friend
Kaname, do you understand how scary that is?
I think so.
You will have to fight forever in every world, past and future.
Will you be able to stay yourself through that?
Dying would be easier.
You will be locked in space and destroying witches for all eternity.
That's fine. That's what I'm going to do.
If someone tells me that it's wrong to hope,
I will tell them they're wrong every time.
I could tell them that countless times.
That's fine, isn't it? You'll never know until you give it a try.
You found your reason to fight, right?
You decided by yourself that you won't run away, didn't you?
Then it's okay, isn't it? All that's left is to strike at full force.
Thank you, Kyoko.
Then I should give back what I've been taking care of until now.
Here.
You're not just granting hope. You're becoming hope itself.
The hope for all of us.
I won't let your prayers end in despair.
You won't curse anyone! You won't torment anyone!
I'll take all the misfortune!
So please, believe in yourselves to the very end!
It's okay. It's okay now.
You don't have to hate anyone anymore.
You don't have to curse anyone anymore.
I will stop you before it comes to that!
Where...
According to Madoka's new laws, space is getting reorganized.
I see... Your magic went beyond the time.
Shall we look together for
what's at the end of the being called Madoka Kaname?
That's the Soul Gem her wish created.
That's...
Does the amount of despair she has to shoulder as payment measure up to the hope she creates?
The amount of hope equal to creating a new universe was reached,
but that also means despair equal to ending a universe.
Of course.
It's fine.
My wish is to erase every witch.
If that's fulfilled...
I have no reason to feel despair!
Madoka, now your life has no beginning and no end anymore.
There is no proof or memory left of your existence in this world.
Your existence shifted to another plane and became a mere concept.
No one can become aware of you and you can't interact with anyone.
You ceased to be a person in this space.
What's this?
You mean this is the end Madoka wished for?!
Will she be erased like this, too?!
Are you kidding me?!
This is worse than death!
Worse!
That's not it, Homura.
Now I can see everything in both the past and the future.
The worlds that might have existed, and the worlds that might come to exist. All of them.
Madoka...
So I understand everything.
How much you struggled in all those timelines for my sake.
You cried so many times... You were hurt so many times...
For my sake...
I'm sorry I didn't realize it at all.
I'm sorry.
I had to change like this before I finally got to know the real you.
To think that I had such a great friend all this time.
I'm really happy.
Thank you, Homura.
You were my best friend!
But you won't have any home to return to,
you can't see your loved ones anymore,
and you'll be locked up in this place for eternity?
I'm not alone.
You're all with me forever.
The way I am now, I'll always be everywhere.
Even though you can't see or hear me, I'll be with you, Homura.
Madoka... do you mind?
That I'll forget you?
That I won't ever feel you again?
It's too early to give up.
You came all the way here with me,
so maybe you won't forget me even when you return to our world.
It's fine. I'm sure it'll be fine.
Believe in me.
Madoka...
You know, Puella Magi fulfill hopes and dreams!
I'm sure there will be a true miracle soon. There has to be.
Madoka, don't go!
Sorry, but I have to go meet everyone.
I'm sure I'll meet you again, too.
Until then, wait just a little longer.
Madoka!
I'm number 25, Kyosuke Kamijo. I'll be performing Ave Maria.
I... caused you a lot of trouble.
No, I have to apologize, too.
To save you I had to erase it all.
And this future will disappear, too.
But that probably isn't how you wanted it to be...
I don't think everything you did and worked for was meaningless.
So...
It's fine.
I just wanted to hear him perform once more.
I wanted many, many people to hear him play.
Thank you for reminding me of that.
I have no more regrets.
I feel kinda bad about it, but, well... It ended up being Hitomi.
She's very nice to Kyosuke... I'm sure she'll make him happy...
Then... let's go?
Sayaka?
Sayaka? What happened to Sayaka?
She went away... Led astray by her denial of change.
She used all her energy in that last attack.
What an idiot... What's the point of disappearing for the sake of the guy she loved?
That idiot... We finally became friends...
That's the fate of Puella Magi.
You should have learned that when you acquired these powers.
Our hope will bring misfortune to this world, and we must disappear before that happens.
Madoka...
Akemi?
Madoka?
Who's that?
Madoka! Madoka!
That's right. It looks just like her.
Don't do that, Tatsuya!
You mustn't pull a girl's hair!
Madoka! Madoka! Madoka!
Excuse me, are you all right?
I'm fine, sorry for disturbing.
Madoka, right?
Yeah!
I'm going!
Come!
She's like his imaginary friend when he's playing alone.
It's usual for children.
I remember her, too.
Madoka? You know her, too? Is she a character from an anime or something?
I just... I recall hearing that name.
I might've seen her together with Tatsuya once.
Sometimes it gives me a really nostalgic feeling.
Madoka...
I see...
That ribbon is so cute!
Wow! That's the exact kind I like!
Let me give it to you.
It wouldn't fit an old lady like me.
If I had a daughter, I'd get one for her.
I see. What you say is one conceivable hypothesis indeed.
It's not a hypothesis. It's the truth.
But you have no way of proving it.
If the rules of the universe changed as you say, then we have no way to prove it.
Also, since you're the only one who remembers it,
you can't distinguish it from something that you've imagined.
It's true that not even we can explain why exhausted Soul Gems disappear,
so the concept of these "witches" you speak of is really fascinating.
It certainly is an excellent way to gather the emotional energy of humans.
If such an easy way existed, us Incubators would have quite a different plan.
That's right... That's how you are.
There weren't any demons like the ones we fight here in that world with witches, right?
Isn't this a faster way to gather curses?
It wasn't that simple. Our relations with you weren't the best, either.
I don't understand why humans act the way they do.
Even though witches aren't born in this world, it doesn't mean that there are no curses.
The distortions of this world change form and attack people from the darkness.
Tonight the miasma is thick... The demons show up one after another.
There's no end to them, no matter how many we defeat.
No use complaining.
Let's get going.
In this world that can't be saved, all the sorrow and hatred continue on.
Yet, this world is a place she tried to protect.
I remember that. I won't forget that no matter what.
So I'll fight on.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Keep it up!