Kaoru...
We're in the same class again this year, eh?
I'm glad.
Yeah.
I'm happy about it as long as you are, Ritsu.
Oh yeah, where'd he go off to?
Hey there! Well don't you just look chipper?
Aren't you just thrilled about being in Class 10 with all the troublemakers?
What's up?
Nothin'.
He isn't used to being separated from all his friends in class.
It's the first time for him.
Oh...
Um... There's a petal in your hair...
That's okay. I'll get it myself.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Nishimi!
I'm so glad we're in the same class again!
Oh, are we?
Y-You're cruel...
There's no way you didn't notice.
Oh, that's right.
You helped him get the ticket for the sleeper, too, didn't you?
I-I'm so sorry!
He said to keep it a secret from you...
I actually had a nice trip because of it.
Thanks.
It's finally over!
We should've decided the class rep by drawing lots in the first place.
No kiddin'!
Hey, I heard there's already been a fight in Class 10!
I'm just glad I wasn't put in there!
So, is that the best the Boxing Club got to offer?!
I thought you had a little more spirit than that.
Sen!
Hi, Richie!
Don't give me that!
Why are you fighting on the first day of the new year?!
Just gettin' a little exercise...
That was fun. Been too long since I had a fight.
Hey, Sen! Are you listening to me?!
Hey!
W-What?!
W-Wait a minute!
Don't go!
What d'you want?
You're gonna just go in with that banged-up face?!
Is it that bad?
Ritsu.
Sorry, but would you take this guy to the infirmary and patch him up?
All right, go! Go!
Ritsu, he's in your hands.
Sure...
It still hurts a little,
but I should get over it eventually.
The pain will go away and I should be able to smile and relax again.
I'm going to submit it to the public exhibition this year.
It's the one Sentaro modeled for.
Um...
Uh...
Oh, no, that's okay.
You don't have to force yourself to give me feedback.
S-Sorry.
I don't know much about art...
Oh?
That's a strange thing for you to say.
After all, painting and jazz are relatively close cousins, aren't they?
A painting is created on a place called the canvas,
while jazz is created during a time called the performance.
It's like etching your living self into that place and time...
Or something like that.
I don't remember who said it first.
Junichi was talking about it when I went down to the shop.
Fukahori
Yurika
Everything he says is just so interesting.
I feel like I could talk to him about anything.
Well...
I went to Tokyo during spring break...
And I dropped by Brother Jun's place, but he wasn't there.
Oh, that's too bad...
Apparently, he hadn't been back for a long time,
so there were letters just bursting out of his mail slot.
Someone said he might be staying over somewhere else...
Oh...
One of those letters may have been pretty important.
I wonder where he went?
Aren't you done yet?
Just put a little spit on cuts like these and they heal up fine.
What'll you do if it gets infected?
C'mon, close your eyes.
W-What?
Ri'ko...
I'm glad you're in the same class as Richie.
From now on, would you look after him more instead of me?
Um, well, I'd better get going...
Richie!
Glad I caught up with you before you left...
Are those tears?
This glob looks like a tear...
That's the tear of a broken heart.
In Greek mythology, the god Apollo
fell in love with Daphne, the daughter of a river god.
He became obsessed and chased her everywhere, but she just wouldn't stop running.
At long last, she gave Apollo the ultimate rejection
by turning herself into a bay laurel tree.
What unbearable heartbreak!
Such sadness!
He was so sick with grief that he fashioned a wreath out of the laurels!
Wha...
Who's he?
This is Matsuoka Seiji, a second-year.
He's the Great Hope of East High's Art Club.
Oh, stop it!
You're embarrassing me!
Kawabuchi Sentaro...
We're both in Class 10, huh?
Pleasure to meet you!
Richie...
Do you remember that guy from last year?
Nope...
I'm gettin' the chills...
Oh, that's right, Sentaro...
Are you free on our next day off?
I want to get you a gift as a thank you for doing me a favor.
Hey!
Wait up!
Idiot! Apollo, my ass!
Like this guy would ever wear a wreath of laurels!
Ritsu, do you have detention?
Yeah.
I forgot to do my math homework.
That's unusual for someone as level-headed as you.
Who said I was level-headed?
I'm careless as can be.
I get more absent-minded in the spring. I better snap out of it...
This song...
It's from "The Sound of Music."
I love this song.
Yeah, I figured you'd like that movie, Ritsu.
Oh, no, I didn't see it.
I wanted to, but before I knew it, it'd already stopped playing.
I bet it was good, huh?
How could I miss it?
I guess I thought I'd be able to see it anytime...
I'm pretty dumb, huh?
What is that again?
"My Favorite Things."
Yeah, that's it!
No, better not... I had my chance...
Oh yeah, there was somethin' I wanted your advice on, Richie.
About my date...
With Yurika?
Y-Yeah...
Well then, let me give some perfect advice to a romantic novice like you.
Don't go.
That's all.
Huh?! What the hell?!
If it's just the two of you, you're guaranteed to freeze up and blow it.
D-Don't you make fun of me!
I can handle a date. Piece of cake!
Oh, sure!
You really think you can mind your P's and Q's in front of such a refined lady and behave like an adult?!
P-P's and Q's?!
You know what it means?
You don't, do you?
But for your own sake, you'd better not go.
P's and...
Jeez, what a pain...
I wish everyone would just stop falling in love...
That dope! Fine then, don't blame me for what happens!
Sentaro,
don't hold back. Tell me if you see something you want.
Oh, nah.
I never get expensive stuff like this.
Even this jacket is a hand-me-down from Brother Jun...
Oh, really?
And from then on, all we talked about was Brother Jun...
When Brother Jun was in high school, nobody was cooler!
He was good at fightin', real smart too...
Oh, really?!
We had a good time talkin' about 'im,
but now all I got left is a feelin' of emptiness in the pit of my stomach.
What are you doing, Sen?
Did your date go well?
C-Course it did!
That's right.
A date is a piece of cake for you, huh?
Y-Yeah, that's right...
What a liar.
It didn't go well at all, did it?
Just like I said...
Sen...
Stay away from her from now on.
What's up with that all of a sudden?
Are you really that dense?
Any way you look at it, you and a refined girl like that just don't work out.
She's just completely out of your league—
Crap.
I went too far...
Hi, Kawabuchi.
What?
I heard you went on a date with Yurika?
She said she had a great time.
H-Hey, really?!
Did she say anythin' else?!
You wanna know?
Uh-huh! She said you were just so handsome,
and that maybe she'll even hold your hand next time!
Really?!
Oh, Richie, you're here, huh?
Hey, you wanna try playin' "My Favorite Things" with me again?
What's this? I thought he'd be mad at me for what I said at lunch,
but he seems to be in a great mood.
Hey, what's that?
I thought only jazz was allowed in here...
Oh, that kid with the mushroom cut, Matsuoka, forced it on me.
I couldn't refuse, so I just carried it here.
Huh...
W-What's that mean?
Good for you,
making a nice friend that lends you records...
Hey, Sen...
Would you come upstairs a second?
S-Sure.
What, did a new record come in?
Just come up here...
'Kay...
Is he actually gonna listen to that record?
What am I so anxious about?
Kawabuchi...
Did you listen to the record I gave you yesterday?
Nah,
I can't get into music that has girls squealin' over it...
Isn't that the purpose of makin' music?
Don't you wanna become popular?
Don't really care about that...
Anyway, I'm not interested.
Well, I wanna be popular.
My dream is to become a star!
Hah? A star?
Seiji
Wait a sec!
Are those the boxers of somebody who's aiming to be a star?!
Oh, these?
I've got a lot of brothers,
so if I don't stake my claim, they'll disappear in no time.
And we're poor, so we can't afford to buy new ones very often.
Amongst all my brothers,
I'm called the "good-for-nothing."
Honestly, singing is the only thing I'm good at...
I wanna prove that I can become somebody who's able to support his family.
To me, this band is the first step.
So...
Kawabuchi, I need your talent.
A-Awesome!
That was wonderful, Maruo! Much better than I expected!
I lost...
All right, now all we need is a drummer.
Seiji, are you at least gonna tell me who you have in mind?
Oh, you'll find out soon enough.
It'll be a surprise.
Hey, Ri'ko!
Yeah?
No school tomorrow, so if you're free, wanna go to the beach?
Ma told me to take the munchkins.
But lookin' after them alone is a tough job,
so I thought I'd ask you along to help out.
Well, if you're busy...
Richie!
Hold it right there.
You free tomorrow?
What d'you say we have us a clammin' contest at the beach?!
Huh? Clammin'?
Say, Sentaro...
I like clamming, but...
Ritsu...
What is it?
Some kind of competition?
Oh, Kaoru! Clamming means digging up clams at the beach.
Oh! It's confusing when this guy calls it a contest or whatever...
Are you going too, Ritsu?
I guess...
Great!
Then the threesome's set!
This is gonna be fun!
I'll need to mentally prepare myself this time.
If those two have a romantic moment,
I'll casually get out of the way and just pray for Ritsu's happiness.
Or that's the idea at least...
Well, maybe that's a non-issue.
I got a hamaguri clam!
That's a short-necked clam.
Hi.
Fancy meeting you here, Kawabuchi!
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you.
What cute little girls and boys.
Y'know, there's a place over there where you can find a bunch of razor clams.
Razors?!
You must be Ritsuko.
I've heard about you from Yurika.
She said you were exceptionally cute!
Hey! Where are the razor clams?!
Oh, they're right over here.
Follow me.
What's with that guy? Sweet-talking everyone...
Don't criticize the guy when you don't know 'im.
Bro, you come, too!
Sure.
Nifty, right?!
Who wants to try it?!
Me!
Me, me!
Salt!
Looks like they're having a good time over there.
Should we join them?
I'll pass.
For some reason, that Matsuoka character rubs me the wrong way...
What's wrong, Taiichi?!
Oh, no! I'll be back in a bit!
Crab!
You were just surprised that the crab pinched you, right?
Thank goodness that's all it was!
Hey, Seiji!
Don't tell me your drummer is Kawabuchi!
Please, anybody but him!
I-I'm against it, too!
He isn't as scary as you think he is.
All I have to do is set him free from what's tying him down
and then everything should work out the way I want it to.
Hey, Richie!
Catchin' any short-necks?
Better not underestimate me!
I'm good at this kind of simple task.
Well, I ain't gonna lose to you!
All right!
Clammin' contest!
What do I get if I win?!
How about the record that Ritsu's dad gave you?!
Forget about it! 'Cause I'm gonna win anyway!
What about the Beatles record?
Kawabuchi, did you listen to it?
Yeah, I heard it.
Wasn't bad...
Did it stir up your interest?!
I wouldn't go that far.
But still...
I'm thinkin' I'll help you out with
that band you're gonna have for the school festival.
Really?!
You'll join my rock band?!
Yeah...
Yay!
Richie, don't worry.
I'm so happy!
I'm just gonna be away 'til the festival's over with.
We're just gonna be apart for a little while, Nishimi.
Let's send each other letters, okay?
Bullshit!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Richie, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't wanna listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
Kaoru! Wait!
Kaoru!
I know.
I acted like an angry little kid.
But being separated from him scares the hell out of me...
I abandoned him without even thinking.
Ever since I came here, I'd forgotten
that I'm not any good at getting along with other people...
It's better this way.
After all, I've made it this far, all on my own.
No problems...
None at all.
Good evening...
Tsutomu, hey!
Look at the end of the bar!
It can't be.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change