Cure Blossom... Cure Marine...
While they collect the Heart Seeds in
hope of reviving the Great Heart Tree,
we of the Desert Apostles strive to make the human heart wither, and reduce the whole world to desert.
The Precure pose a great threat to us.
Fear not, Professor Sabark!
Next time, we shall defeat those rookie Precure!
If it was Cure Moonlight you were dealing
with, then I would understand your failures.
But how many times must you fall to those "rookie" Precure?
I'm terribly sorry, sir!
Professor Sabark, allow me to dispose of the Precures.
As you wish.
However, make sure that you also dispose of all the Heart Seeds they have gathered.
Understood.
Hold on just a second! I'll be the one to defeat those Precure!
Well then...
You can accompany me as my subordinate.
Your subordinate?!
Don't joke around like that!
Well fine! As a special treat, I'll follow your instructions just this once!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Erika, you're heavy!
You can do your homework at night!
Hey, let's go for a stroll!
Can't you solve that using the formula we learned today?
You're as amazing as ever, Erika!
Then let's go on that stroll!
You need a change of pace!
Shall we go, then?
Chypre, Coffret, you're coming too!
I never knew a place this beautiful was right nearby.
And it was here that Chypre and
Coffret came crashing into my life!
"Crashing"?
What?! What on earth?!
It was really shocking!
Really!
I feel so excluded...
Our meeting might've been somewhat mundane, but that doesn't mean we're not best friends!
Best friends!
If you keep saying we're best friends, you're gonna make me blush!
But we are best friends!
It's so pretty...
The Desert Apostles are trying to turn the entire world into a desert, right?
That's right!
And to stop that, we need to revive the Great Heart Tree!
That is the duty of the Precure!
We'll protect the Flowers of everyone's Hearts from the Desert Apostles,
and ensure that they all bloom into beautiful flowers!
And once we gather a whole bunch of Heart Seeds, we can revive the Great Heart Tree, right?
And that's not all!
A most amazing miracle will occur.
Whoa, what's this amazing miracle?!
Will it, like, go baaaang and
defeat all the Desert Apostles?!
That's a secret!
A secret, huh? Well, I guess that's fine...
Well then, just how many times are we going to have to defeat the Desert Apostles?
Th-That's also a secret!
W-Well, I guess that's fine...
The Desert Apostles sure are causing us a lot of trouble...
Though we'll defeat them no matter how many times they appear!
How very rude.
Haven't we been kinda busy lately?
Huh? Well, a lot of Desertrians
have been popping up as of late...
But I really enjoy becoming a Precure!
Well, I enjoy it too, but...
When you're feeling blue, you need the Heart Perfume!
We'll use a Blue Seed!
The Blessed Perfume of Blue Light!
A spray makes my mood clear up!
What a lovely fragrance!
Makes me feel like a clear, sunny blue sky.
The blue seed's perfume has the ability to make your mood clear right up!
Many hardships still lie ahead of you!
But if your hearts trust each other, you can overcome any obstacle!
Tsubomi, Erika!
Sayaka!
Wow, that's a cute doll!
It is, isn't it?
Sayaka, do you like this hill as well?
Yep!
Whenever something good happens to me, I come here!
Something good? What happened?
The girls' soccer team has finally
been accepted as an official club!
That's great news!
Yeah, it is! I followed your example and advertised for new members!
Quit that!
The Flower of her Heart shouldn't be shining like that, you damn Precures!
Sasorina.
Who is she?
A girl the Precures saved before, Ueshima Sayaka.
Oh, the girl whose Flower of the Heart you failed to steal.
Wha—
She's perfect.
Let us taint the Precures' name beyond repair.
Huh?
The Biggest Predicament Yet!
Dark Precure Makes Her Entrance!
Erika, would you mind if we watered the
flowerbed before the Fashion Club meeting?
Sure, that's fine!
Today marks the official start of the girls' soccer team!
And so, as we head toward our tournament debut, I'd like to get straight into training!
Right!
Well then, we'll be your practice partners!
We're the girls' soccer team from Desert Junior High!
Who are they?
I've never heard of them before.
And you really don't look like you're in junior high.
Quit yer yappin'!
We're challenging you to a match!
Well, we were kinda out of luck without practice partners...
so we accept your challenge!
Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
We'll show you our desert-parched soccer!
Snacky! Cover her in sand!
This is against the rules!
Over here, over here!
Okay!
Desert Sliding Corps!
Captain, shoot!
You're...
A Precure.
Sayaka!
Get a hold of yourself!
Who could've done this?!
It was...
a Precure.
There's no way a Precure would—
At any rate, we need to call a teacher!
Right!
We really hate pretty flowers!
Just watch, you little humans!
This is the truth behind your beloved Precure!
It's good that nobody was badly hurt.
But just what happened?
Are there other Precure besides us?
Could this mean that Cure Moonlight is still alive?!
Moonlight?!
But why would she do something like that?
I guess you're right...
I can hear the voices of the flowers!
The flowers are calling out for help!
This is cruel!
Was it you who did this to the flowers?!
You're...
From our dreams!
I was created to destroy the Precure...
I am Dark Precure.
Was it you that hurt these flowers and Sayaka?
I did it to teach you just how
pointless being a Precure truly is.
My goal is simple.
Defeat you Precures, and ensure this world
becomes a desert, just as Professor Sabark wishes.
Yet you two have no goal at all!
The likes of you...
have no chance of defeating me.
Relinquish all your Heart Seeds!
We don't have any Heart Seeds with us!
And we'd never hand them to you even if we did!
Then I suppose I'll have to offer both of these as a trade.
Tsubomi! Erika! Don't come after us!
I shall await you at that water tower.
Chypre! Coffret!
What she said just now really shocked me.
About us being Precures despite having no goal?
Yeah...
What the heck are you saying?!
We do have a goal, don't we?!
Right! To make the Flowers of everyone's Hearts bloom into beautiful flowers!
And to gather the Heart Seeds so we can revive the Great Heart Tree!
That's right! And that's all we need!
That's why we become Precures and fight!
Yeah!
But really, what are we going to do?
If we're going to save Chypre and Coffret, we don't have any choice but to hand over the Heart Seeds.
But she isn't just going to give those two back if we just hand it over!
And with them captured, we can't even transform...
What are we going to do?!
Can you keep it down?
We're very sorry!
You two get along pretty well together, don't you?
Uh, yeah.
You know what the geranium means in the language of flowers, I take it?
Yes!
If I recall correctly, it means "true friendship."
That's just like us, isn't it?
I wonder.
I don't think you understand what that really means.
Huh?
Hey, wait a second!
What exactly are you getting at?
You should work that out for yourself.
What true friendship really means...
I guess it means... having trusting hearts?
But if your hearts trust each other, you can overcome any obstacle!
Chypre and Coffret have always believed in us and encouraged us to press onward!
And they've risked their lives to protect us!
Now it's our turn to protect them!
Yeah! Even if we're beaten and broken...
...protecting such trusting hearts is why we Precure exist!
Chypre!
Coffret!
Stay away, Tsubomi!
You too, Erika!
I commend you for showing up.
You've brought the Heart Seeds?
They're right here!
Then we'll trade...
...is what I'd like to say, but it's such a pain.
If I defeat you and take them, then both my problems will be solved.
So they were planning to deceive us!
We'll have to save Chypre and Coffret before they can steal the Heart Seeds!
They're really underestimating us if they think they can fight us unarmed!
Get them!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
Now, defeat them, and take the Heart Seeds!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
It's over.
I still don't know who you are, but thank you very much!
Please... Please save them!
Who are you?!
It's that hottie again!
You're...
Not this again!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
Tsubomi, let's go!
All right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Let's go, Marine!
Gotcha!
Had enough yet?!
Precure are the greatest!
There's a lot more where that came from!
Go get them!
Let's go for a finisher!
Sounds good!
Precure Grand Explosion!
How could this happeeeeeeeeen?!
And now we'll take down Dark Precure!
It's foolish for rookie Precure like
you to even attempt to defeat me.
We aren't down for the count yet!
We're not gonna lose to the likes of you!
I know we can win!
As long as our hearts trust each other, we can overcome any obstacle!
What trifling nonsense.
Trusting in each other will not allow you to defeat me.
Giving it your all will not allow you to defeat me.
No matter what you try, it shall all end in ruin.
Just like it did for Cure Moonlight.
Don't look down on Cure Moonlight like that!
An impostor like you could never understand!
Once I destroy you two, I'll become the real thing.
The wishes that Cure Moonlight entrusted to us
have always remained within my heart.
That's why there's no way...
that we'll ever accept defeat!
Marine, let's do this together!
Okay!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
It's the end for you.
Blossom!
Marine!
Fear not. I shall ease your pain.
Dark Power, Gather!
Dark Tact!
So that's what happened...
How intriguing.
We're saved...
But... why would Dark Precure just suddenly...
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
We have to train!
This is kinda sudden!
Now that Dark Precure has appeared, we need to become stronger!
All right, sounds good to me!
But what should we do?
We must learn kung-fu!
Kung-fu?!
Now, Erika! Don't think, feel!
Train your body and mind, and reach new heights!
Let's kung-fu!
Hah! Tah! Achoooooo!
Ts-Tsubomi's on fire!
HeartCatch Precure:
Achoo!
Power up with Kung-Fu!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!