What? How to lose weight?
I wouldn't know, since I really haven't done any dieting.
No way! How come? You're so thin!
Let's do this.
Yeah.
I guess I'm just genetically predisposed to not getting fat.
Wow... predisposed...
I'm so jealous...
Kawashima's sure become the center of attention among the girls.
Yeah.
If you push yourself too hard, you'll just be piling up stress.
Maintaining a good balance between just eating what you want and eating healthily is probably the best.
Now that I just can't ignore!
What's going on?!
What are you-?!
H-Hey! Let me go!
What's going on?
Take that! And that! And some of this!
Teacher! Kawashima-san's hiding the flab in her gut!
It is customary to bring only up to 300 yen worth of meat for trips!
Is this only 300 yen worth of excess flab?! Bananas like these don't fit in the meat category!
This here is from meat buns! Here is the expensive ice cream! And here's the American dark cherry!
Take this! Divine fist of convenience stores!
HIGH!
CALO!
RIEES~!
I dedicate this to the tears of the dieting warriors that have vanished along with the stardust.
Bye then.
We sure did it, the divine fist of convenience stores!
My, my, she was quite an admirable foe.
Those bastards!
A-Are you okay, Ami-chan?
That was really mean of them.
You poor thing.
Ah- Um...
That was the first of many storms to come.
I see...
Coming out of nowhere, those two were so mean~!
If you go about it like that, Ami ends up like this, huh?
Huh?
True Colors
That felt so good! As expected of Minorin, your performance was superb!
Girls are way too scary.
As a dieting warrior, I wasn't able to hold myself back.
As long as you face the fat head on, you will obtain the grace of the god of weight loss.
I'm sure she will understand this some day too.
Is that really how it works?
What's that guy doing here?
Oh, right.
Ryuuji, want me to make some salad for dinner tonight?
You, make salad?
I learned how in elementary school.
I can even make dressing on my own.
First you buy the lettuce, right? Then you separate the leaves, and then slice them up, right?
And then you put it on a plate. Pow, and it's done!
You didn't wash the lettuce, you didn't put it under running water.
And where did the dressing go?
Shut up about the trivial things, you nosy sister-in-law.
Sister-in-la-!
Takasu-kun!
What's wrong, Kawashima?
Please, can I stay with you for a moment?
That's... the guy from earlier.
Hey, Kawashi-
You're...
Hey, how long do you intend to cling to him?
Completely ignoring that I'm here, sticking closely to him, clinging onto him...!
Wait, Taiga! Now is not a-!
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
You lewd exhibitionist woman!
Hey, Kawashima, who was that?
It's... not someone you know, is it?
Ah, yeah. When you're a model, things like this happen sometimes...
It's like getting entangled with your fans, or well...
And here I went and even changed schools...
Huh?
Hey, you're going home now, right?
Well, uh, yeah.
Can you shelter me in your house for a little while? Meeting him again would be scary...
So that's how it is.
If that's the case, then just leave it to me.
What?
Between a drafty, wooden, rented house and an autolocked, high-security, expensive apartment, which would you prefer?
The expensive apartment!
It's decided, then.
Come to my place.
Why? Wait a minute, why does Ami-chan have to go to your place?
It's okay, I won't force you.
But keep in mind that Ryuuji's place is so vulnerable that even I could easily sneak in.
Wha-?
Fine then, it's none of my business anyway.
W-Wait! Aisaka-san!
I'm telling you to wait already!
Oh well, whatever.
Here you go.
Way too sweet!
This is the honey-preserved kumquats that Ryuuji has been making in large quantities.
I tried mixing it with soda.
Isn't it too thick?
Sheesh, making me drink this, who's the dieting warrior, huh?
It's like your brain is the same size as you are.
Man, you sure do change when you're like that.
It makes me want to show the people in our class how you really are.
Like I would ever show my true self to anyone.
I see, I see.
Now, when you drink honey-preserved kumquats, your throat becomes nice and clear.
Huh?
You don't intend to show your true self?
Well then,
let's have you show off the fake you instead...
Thoroughly.
What?
Hey, good morning.
Good morning...
Kawashima, you look worn out.
Yeah, I couldn't shake off yesterday's exhaustion...
Right, you went through a scary situation there.
Not that.
For roughly five hours in Aisaka Taiga's apartment... no, six hours...
Did Taiga do something to you?
Jackson.
Uganda.
U... ganda?
Falcon...
Akechi Mitsuhide...
Matsumoto Seichou...
Oda Nobunaga singing French songs with enthusiasm...
Dazai Osamu cheering on Japan...
Huh?
Susano-o, Amaterasu, Uzume, Quetzalcóatl, Matthew, Judas!
H-Hey, are you okay, Kawashima?
Oh yes, I made her do it, a medley of 150 different imitations!
It was an incredible blast!
I can't even begin to guess how to imitate Akechi Mitsuhide.
I told her I'd throw her out if she didn't do what I told her to.
Then she started to frantically do my every bidding.
So cruel.
No, I'm thankful, Aisaka!
Kitamura?
K-Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, I have a favor to ask of you!
Ami-chan, you don't look so good.
Are you sure you shouldn't go to the infirmary?
I'm fine, really.
H-Hey.
Come, stupid chihuahua. It's feeding time.
"Stupid chihuahua"?
Yes, you. Putting on a sweet and innocent act, yelping all the time, and you're always in heat.
Either way, just come along.
Like I ever would.
Why should I come with you, huh?! I got plans with my frie-
Michael Jackson guiding a bus.
Mona Lisa attacking a corner at 200 kilometers an hour.
A happy 'The Thinker'.
I've already made copies of the pictures I took. There's a chance they might carelessly get spread around.
Wa- Stop that!
Okay, fine! I just have to come along, right?! Damn you!
Um, Ami-chan?
I-I'm sorry!
I forgot I was going to eat lunch with Aisaka-san today.
I'm really sorry!
Hey, you! Wait up!
Thank you for this meal!
Thank you for this meal.
What's this supposed to be?
If she keeps interacting with people just using her facade, Ami won't make any real friends.
So I'm asking you two, who know her true colors already, to take care of her.
Even if you say that... I wouldn't mind,
but no matter how you look at it, the chemistry between Taiga and Kawashima's not really...
Aisaka!
Please! You're one of my very few female friends that I can ask favors of!
Like I sai-
WHAT?
Oh! Thank you, Aisaka!
That Kitamura... pushing the trouble onto us and running off to the student council on his own...
W-Wow! Kushieda's lunchbox is amazing!
It might look large, but this lunchbox is super low on calories.
Look, these are king trumpet mushrooms, this here's konjac, and this is thread-konjac rice!
Sheesh, why do I have to do this?
Hey, Ami. I'll share some konbu with you.
I don't want the damn thing.
Aw, is that so...
How nice.
What?
Uh, no, um... Right, lunch, gotta eat my lunchbox.
Huh? Why does Takasu-kun's lunchbox have the same side-dishes as Aisaka-san's?
Hey, why?
Well, you see... this is...
Now there's no problem, right?
My lunchbox is a omelette and fried food-lunchbox, while Ryuuji's is a just a rice lunchbox.
Ah! My side-dishes!
Here. Like this, Takasu-kun has a meatball-lunchbox.
Huh?
Oh. Thanks.
But why do you let Aisaka-san do just as she pleases so often?
Do I really?
You see, Ryuuji was my dog in his previous life.
A dog's happiness is measured by how useful he is to his master.
Yes! These two are meant for one another, you see!
No, no way.
Jeez, why do you do this, Minorin?
Sorry, I was kidding, just kidding!
Jeez.
Hey!
Everyone, please listen to me for a moment!
Today we're having the customary neighborhood volunteer cleaning rally that the student council organizes every month,
but this time we're a bit short on hands.
Could any brave heroes that would like to participate please come forward?
I'm sorry, Kitamura. Today Super Kanoya has a special sale-
Oh, Takasu! You'll come along?!
Huh?
Go change and meet up in the school yard.
Sheesh, why do I have to?
Look, I'm taking responsibility and coming along to participate with you.
That's what you're saying, but you just wanted to spend some more time with Kitamura, didn't you?
You could say that.
How honest of you.
Takasu-kun!
I'm participating too. I just transferred, so I want to get more familiar with the school.
Huh?
Minorin.
As a dieting warrior, I just can't help but want to cheer on girls that are desperately working up a sweat, trying to lose weight.
I never said that I wanted to lose some weight or anything like that.
Let's do our best together, Takasu-kun!
Uh, yeah, okay.
All right, you punks! Put some heart into it, and let's move out!
Don't even dare to skip out on this, you bunch of scum!
Whoa there, calm down.
Are your work gloves on?!
Got your trash bag?!
Confirmed your assigned cleaning area?!
Yeah!
Don't take the town lightly.
With that level of guts you'll get tossed off this trip, you maggots!
Put some spunk into that reply, you cowards!
YEAH!
That's our president for sure.
All right, I'll explain the program. First-
Kitamura eventually ended up going along with the student council.
Sorry, the council staff is going a different way!
So why did I even-
Hey, doesn't this piece of trash look just like Aisaka-san?
I mean, look at it, it's so helplessly small!
Well, this piece of trash here looks just like Kawashima-san.
It's just as sodden, sloppy and flabby as you.
Let's go the other way, Minorin.
Oh, we're going? Fine by me.
Let's get away from here.
Yeah! The trash is awaiting us!
Those two just bailed, didn't they?
The ones left behind should get along well, right?
Um...
Picking up trash can be pretty fun too.
Or maybe it's because I'm together with Takasu-kun?
Kawashima, look, I...
Hey, let's go that way next.
Watch ou-!
Hey, are you oka-?
Oh man, that's so filthy! What is this?!
What the hell is this?!
K-Kawashima...?
Wow, that scared me. Jeez, my shoe's all drench-
NO!
Ew, ew, ew! Get it away!
Kawashima!
Don't move, now!
Aah! It's climbing upwards!
Don't kick my face!
Ew! Ew!
Damn it!
Okay, salvaged!
Right, it's all okay now.
Look, the frog's gone home to frogtown. See?
I don't want to frigging do this anymore!
Huh?
K-Kawashima?
Just kidding!
Did I fool you?
It's starting to rain.
Ew, I'll get wet.
We've got to seek shelter from the rain. Right, Takas-?
Hey.
It's enough already, stop keeping that up.
Huh?
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
The one who doesn't get it is me.
Why did you even bother coming out here to do this troublesome work?
You don't... get it? I see...
So this approach doesn't work on Takasu-kun...
I've known about the act for a while now, you know.
You should be more, uh...
With a face like that-
You see, I...
I can't get by without this facade.
Huh?
You really don't understand my feelings, do you?
Well, frankly...
That's okay.
I mean, I'm an airhead after all!
Kawashima?
What's wrong? Hey, Kawashima!
Hey, what's up all of the sudden? If we're going to take shelter, we sho-
What are you doi-?
That's yesterday's...
Why is he here?
Um, well, to be honest...
that guy's a stalker.
Sta- Why didn't you say anything?!
It...
It's frustrating.
Frustrating?
I don't want to admit it...
That my life is being thrown into disorder by guys like him.
I moved away because of him.
Huh?
I didn't want to cause trouble for my parents.
So I moved here on my own to be in the care of my relatives.
Taking a short break from my modeling job, yet...
Now I've been chased down all the way over to this town...!
Hey! Hey! Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hey!
That's strange, we were told they went this way...
I don't care anymore, let's just go home, Minorin.
Whoa!
Cute, mini-sized monster spotted!
Wow! So cute! Lucky me!
"Monster"?
Taiga!
Watch ou-!
I don't recall having to be referred to as a 'monster' by suspicious people like you.
What is she doing? He's a stalker!
And besides, with whose permission are you taking pictures in the first place?
You're being really disgusting here!
Why can't I? It's not like it's the end of the world...
Of course you can't.
I'll destroy that camera along with its owner!
Why are you running away, huh?!
I told you to stop running!
W-Wait, Taiga!
That idiot...
Why?
Huh?
Why isn't she scared?
I mean, that guy's a pervert!
Kawashima?
Why did I...
Why did I take a break from work, move out, even change schools, all because of that bastard?
Getting all nervous, piling up stress, eating tons of candy...
This means that...
Ami-chan's losing to that worthless bastard...
and also to Aisaka Taiga...
Huh?
Takasu-kun.
It's like you were saying earlier.
That I should stop putting on this facade.
You told me I should do that, didn't you?
Um, well, yes...
I got it now.
I got it.
I'm quitting the 'Ami-chan' act.
I'll quit it, I'll quit it, I'll quit it, I'll quit it, I'll quit it, I'll quit it! And then!
Ka-Kawashima?
And then I'll live on with this ill-natured look!
I don't intend to continue being defeated either!
Hey!
Kawashima...
After that, Kawashima was amazing.
She ran through the town with a form that would've put even the track club to shame.
And then she recklessly smashed the frightened stalker's camera to pieces.
The stalker was completely frightened by the extreme change.
And then...
You liar! With this demonic appearance...
You're not the Ami-chan that I know!
You're not an angel! Your personality is horrible!
What of it?
Ami-chan's cute either way.
Who cares about personalities?
Kawashima! Hey, are you all right?
Hey! Kawashima!
I did it, Takasu-kun.
I see.
But...
That was so scary...
Here, this'll warm you up.
This... is honey-preserved kumquats.
I'm amazed you knew that. Taiga loves it.
"Taiga"? You call her by her first name, don't you?
You're still suspicious of that?
She's great, isn't she?
Self-centered, always in a mess, and yet not even attempting to hide it...
And even so, she has friends, she's got Takasu-kun...
What would Takasu-kun do if I showed him the real me?
Huh?
Would you fall in love with me?
K-K-K-Kawashima...
Would you?
W-Wait just a moment...
I...
Taiga? Were they there?
Taiga?
Next Episode Preview
Pool Opening Day
"Water-proof, water-repellent design."
"Delicate gradation."
"One-touch installation is possible."
How about this one, Taiga?!
Fake breast special force.