Who is the next target?
Frank Claude.
We finally figured out his location.
Do you intend to use that unknown group again?
I believe it was already decided that we would dispatch them.
You are going to make a show of it, aren't you?
In order to announce our existence, it is a necessary measure.
Their power shall become a conflagration and shall burn hell to nothing.
We shall construct our world there.
You're injured?
It's only a scratch.
I will... kill.
I will kill... so I can live!
karuma nando mo onaji koto wo kurikaeshi no naka wo
Karma, in the midst of ever-repeating events
ochite itta
it fell...
karuma kono karada wa rasen no you
Karma; this body is like a spiral
umare kawatte mo nao mayoi tsuzuketeru
Even if it's reborn, yet it continues to wander
yasuraka ni... owari ni shiyou
Tenderly... bring it to an end
onore no aza de
With my own birthmark
Awaken
I'll be killed...
If I don't run, I'll be killed.
I can't run from those black eyes.
What should I do?
If I can't run away, I have to kill.
I have to kill, or I will be killed!
Where am I?
What is this?
What was I...?
Who am I?
I don't know my name.
What...?
Japanese?
Vacation luggage...
This is me...
I am a Japanese tourist, and...
Why? Why can't I remember?
They might be nearby... the people who attacked me!
Don't go around by yourself, Clo.
You'll negate the meaning of having a bodyguard in the first place.
Do you want to ride in my car?
Oh dear.
Don't worry.  I'm only going to take a look at the situation.
I can't leave all of it in that man's hands.
Right about now, that snake of a man is playing with an extraordinary toy.
Geez, he makes me want to puke.
However, his contributions to the organization are great.
That doll is McGuire's favorite, after all.
We'll use anything for the sake of our objective.
That's Inferno's motto.
I know.
However, Clo, you cross too many lines.
If something happens, contact me.
I'm depending on you, Lizzy.
If it weren't for that driving...
Situational decision rate, 074
Atavism numbers 087
To have reached these numbers only a few minutes after awakening...
I believe I said it before.
He's an outstanding talent.
I'm going to descend into hell, aren't I?
No... I've probably already fallen.
What was that sensory ability just now?
It is the core nature of the animal.
What you might call wild instincts hidden behind the veil of reason.
However, not yet. Not yet.
He has yet to reach the level I'm looking for.
It's your turn, Phantom.
However, don't overdue it.
Yes, Master.
If you don't want to die...
Those eyes...!
...come at me seriously.
Danger to the spirit, danger to life, and danger to existence...
The only way of dealing with that is to use the survival instincts within you.
The ones who rely on morality and kindness,
thinking that their own safety is guaranteed,
are weak humans who have given up living.
I absolutely loathe this world where traits like that have become the norm.
Well, if it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
If I had known you would be coming here...
What is the situation?
I believe we will get results in a moment.
Will you observe?
Yes.
Then, right this way.
Who is it?
Why am I being targeted?!
I don't even know the reason.
I don't even know where this is.
I don't even know who I am.
I can't get away.
There is nowhere for you to go.
I can't get away...
You and I...
...have to kill...
...or I'll be killed!
It's about to start.
Start?
Look closely.
Why?!
Come at me seriously, if you don't want to die.
There is nothing.
Past or future.
Not even life.
Even so, I...
...don't want to die!
Where should I go?
Even though I don't know where I came from...
Even though I don't have any memories...
What should I do to become free?
How is freedom gained through killing?
Tell me... I beg you!
Where is this?!
I... Who am I?!
Zwei.
Who are you?
I am Ein; you are Zwei.
Zwei...?
That is your name.
From now on, your name is Zwei.
Zwei?
What is that?
What do you mean-
You are me.
I am you.
What do you think?
Is he not a wonderful human resource?
Even so, those were perfect results.
This boy has not had any training; he also has no tactical knowledge.
He took those actions entirely based on the instincts he was born with.
What's more, he momentarily surpassed Ein.
Pathetic, Phantom.
My apologies.
He's a genius.
He has talents which only manifested when his life was in great danger.
He is most certainly a human born to be integrated into Inferno.
Even so, would he desire that?
There is no egg that would reject surpassing the world.
Nor is it possible that there would be a seed that did not desire to blossom.
It isn't a matter of will.
Brainwashing... Your specialty, huh?
It's perfect.
By using drugs and hypnotism, we seal only the memories that involve his own identity.
Please understand, Ms. McCunnen.
This is merciful.
He encountered an extremely unfortunate sight.
Ordinarily, he would have been a witness who would have been disposed of.
However, I myself desire to bestow upon him a life where he can blossom.
A lone, Japanese tourist, eh?
This could be troublesome.
It is no longer possible for anyone to discover his footprints.
His secrecy is complete.
Fine.
Scythe Master, I'll leave this boy to you.
Thank you.
Ein and Zwei...
How about you think about the names of your students a bit more?
I wonder just how much longer you will be able to give me orders like that, little girl?
I am the number one woman, Ein.
You are the number two man, Zwei.
We are...
What are you doing?
That's enough, Ein.
Return to your post.
Yes Master.
We are ghosts who cannot exist anywhere. We are now phantoms.
Welcome home, Master!
Hi, where are the others?
Yes, they are all resting.
During the middle of the day?
What's going on?
You are...!
Phantom.
Phantom... Inferno's greatest assassin.
The title of the organization's top sniper.
My greatest masterpiece.
And, he as well.
That's overdoing it...
I see...
That's the end of his organization.
This means that two of the five organizations in Las Vegas have now been crushed.
Gentlemen, from now on...
We will create the next era.
We will create Inferno's era.
Ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
Phantoms who are no one.
yami ni iraretara massakasama ni
If stays in darkness, it turns upside down
ashi wo jama ni shi fukaku nikushimi wa tawawa ni
The foot is caught deeply; Hate is looming
kyoushitsu wa hana to sabi midare minoru yume no kashi
The classroom is flowers and rust; ripening dreams of pastries
nou dake se dake harawata
only the brain, only the back; guts
te wo kake yo
offer your hand
mei wo made
hold the command
souhaku ni hiraku yubi
Fingers that open palely
mamieru mae ni
Before facing it
moshi mo omae ga
If you
nousatsu sanagara mayoi netami
are bewitched and jealous
uchikudaku koto dekiyou ka
can you break it
monzetsu se yo
Faint in agony
tada kudasuru toki ha
But when you drop off
risei wo tori
and acquire reason
chi wo haki doku ni mamire
Blood is smeared by poisoned vomit
naraku e no mukawan
Head to hell
soko de shika mienai
Only there you can see
ten wo aogi yaketadare teyuku asu wo warae yo
Face the sky and laugh at the burnt sky
Training
Next episode preview
You are...
...someone whose existence is only tolerated because of your ability to kill people.
This series is fiction.
All names and character who incidently share the name with a real life person are just by coincidence.
Note:
Ein (One), Zwei (Two): Those are german words for the number 1 (Eins, one) and 2 (Zwei, two),
but could also describe the rank (1 > 2)