Tsukuyomi Juju
Oh? Lady Juju, what are you looking at?
Dear Mom,
I received some postcards from Sasami.
They appear to be photographs of where they traveled.
That looks fun!
Or does it now?
Good question.
This is... the inn where Sasami's staying!
Paparin's here!
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 11
Love is just an urban legend
I'm hungry...
I was sharing her senses so it felt like I ate,
but that was Tama. I haven't eaten anything.
I'm gonna dig in!
Oh right. I've gotta take a bath by myself.
Now I have joined with the flow of natural energy under this island,
and prepared my body to be a suitable host for Kuzuryuu.
I only need to gather enough energy to revive—
Edogawa, you're taking a bath this early, too?
You've already foiled my plot?
But you're too late! I can start the ceremony whenever I want!
Huh, what?
Oh, shut up.
What other explanation is there?
She's my enemy!
She's trying to get to me let my guard down and sabotage my plan!
It's gone now, isn't it?
What does that matter?
In my eyes, it doesn't.
Tsurugi
Oh, hey!
Tsurugi joined the tele-divine channel.
Sasami
Hey, Tsurugi.
Tsurugi
Why the hell are you naked?!
Don't start the H-scenes while I'm asleep!
Tsurugi
I won't be able to unlock all of the CG scenes!
This isn't a game...
Huh? Why you? Where's Tama?
Tsurugi
Huh? Ah, I see.
You called me?
Tama joined the tele-divine channel.
Tsurugi
S'okay, I figured it out.
Go back to sleep.
Okay! Wake me up when it's time for breakfast!
Tama left the tele-divine channel.
Um, Edogawa...
This opportunity doesn't present itself all of the time, so how about we wash each other's backs?
What?!
Jou
Is this some kinda trap?
What should I do?
Sasami's Yagami Tama now.
If I touch her carelessly, she could eat me!
Nothing happened yesterday when you touched her.
Babysitter
You're overthinking, milady.
Foxie
Then what's this about washing each other's backs?
Jou
What is she up to?
Uh guys, I think you're in the wrong channel.
Who're you in the first place?
Oh my god, this is bad!
Foxie
I've written in the wrong channel!
Babysitter
Let's delete the logs and pop off!
Jou
Jou left the tele-divine channel.
Foxie left the tele-divine channel.
Babysitter left the tele-divine channel.
I don't get it.
I'm going back to sleep.
Um...
This is bad...
Washing each other's backs, was it?
Very well then! Let's do this!
I've got the power to eat my opponents too.
We're on equal grounds!
Let's wash each other's backs! Eat or get eaten!
You really shouldn't get so worked up about it.
Sasami's starting to become a little more sociable. Good for her.
What's this ruckus so early in the morning?
Kagamin joined the tele-divine channel.
Kagamin
Fight me!
Get ready to get washed.
She made the first move!
Edogawa, you're so pretty... Pop idols could hide in your shadow.
Who cares about looks?
What matters is one's superiority. The amount of power one can wield.
But I'm pretty weak.
Sasami
My hair's a mess too.
My boobs aren't big either.
Edogawa,
I'm jealous of you.
So, you're gonna act humble now?
I don't like that.
You threw away your blessing and yet, you complain that you don't have enough.
I don't really get it,
but I guess I should only complain after I'd given it my all.
I'm sure you've done your fair share of hard work.
That's right.
Just to overcome you guys, I've been through the hell that'll make one's blood freeze.
That's amazing, Edogawa.
Seriously, you're so awesome.
So lively this early in the morning.
Sasami
Morning, Kagami!
Guess what! I might be able to make a friend!
Kagamin
How wonderful.
This is the first time I've had a real
conversation with someone from class.
I'm so happy!
How wonderful.
I think I'm becoming more gregarious.
Thanks, Kagami!
Would you consider her your first friend?
Kagamin
Sasami
Oh please...
You're the first, Kagami.
I'm just a stepping stone, a mere practice doll, am I not?
Kagamin
But I won't walk all over you with my pessimism.
I'm just a nuisance, so I should part.
Kagami? Kagami?
Kagami?
Sasami
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
Even though you act a little slavish, you should at least have some pride, or even fake it.
The mere sight of you pisses me off.
You're my arch-nemesis, so don't make such a pathetic face!
Thanks... You're so kind, Edogawa.
W-Who did you call kind?!
I'm a full-fledged villain!
I'd like to exchange phone numbers if that's fine with you.
Huh? Why?
You don't have to if you don't wanna...
Uh... Am I being annoying?
Fine, I can grant you that much.
Thanks, Edogawa!
I really wanna get along with you.
This photo seems really happy.
Yes. She should enjoy her youth while I shoulder the power of Amaterasu.
Uh?
There are no bikini babes swarming here,
but at least I can relax, unlike on those cramped beaches.
Tsukuyomi should've come too.
Sasami
I knew you'd challenge me, Sasami!
You attack when my defenses are the lowest, wearing my bikini!
You're a worthy arch-nemesis!
Challenge? Just beach volleyball!
You're probing for a vulnerability and once you find it, you'll crush it.
But alas! Edogawa Jou has no blind spots!
Ah, Kagami!
I mean, my dear sister!
Can I call her too?
How much of a coward do you have to be to call in reinforcements?
Very well! I'll crush you both!
Hey, Kagami! Wanna play beach volleyball?
I'll pass. I do not want to be in the way.
You wouldn't be!
I'm sure it'd be fun!
I'll pass.
I want to focus on building this sand castle.
Okay... Well then, see you later!
Its defenses are still unsatisfactory.
What kind of a trip is this exactly?
You are asking the wrong person.
Indoor
dried kelp
Top quality
Sasami, I wanted to see you so much!
Now that I'm here you've got nothing to worry about!
Top quality
Indoor
dried kelp
I'll take care of your meals, baths
Restarurant
Bath
and everything else you wouldn't say in public.
On his lap!
I'm sitting on Paparin's lap!
Sasami
C'mon, Tama!
Not "Paparin", say "Brother"!
And I never hug him, nor am I nice to him.
At least try to pretend to be me!
Huh? But you always do it like this!
I love you, Brother!
Sasami
Oh well. She's a kid, after all.
Ah, you woke up finally, Tsukuyomi?
Let's go to the summer festival!
Treat us to lots of octopus balls and cotton candy!
There is a summer festival?
Yeah, it's regularly held.
Gods live in everything in this country.
Eating and having fun is worshiping at its best!
Let's walk around and get our fill!
You'll be my purse!
Oh right, we should invite Edogawa to the festival too.
What is the meaning of this?
Just what is she planning?
Babysitter
Oh, calm down.
Edogawa!
What did you call me here for?
The ritual is in its last stages.
Oh, I see.
If you put a crack in my carefully designed equations now, everything will collapse.
You didn't act until now because you wanted to maximize my losses!
You're a worthy arch-nemesis, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
Uh, I'm kinda confused...
You've got that eighth-grader syndrome?
Eight-grader...?
Isn't it embarrassing to go on about arch-
nemeses in high school? Dunno.
Are you gonna bring up your previous life, abilities, or the organization next?
Are you telling me you already know about the organization?
What about it?
How much do you know?!
Anywho, Edogawa!
Do you wanna go to the festival together?
Awashima, explain what's going on here!
Babysitter
You're so on edge.
I don't think she has an ulterior motive.
Foxie
She's honestly trying to get along with you.
We're ready!
Okay, I get it.
You wanna get along with me, right?
Yeah.
I finally get it. Sorry.
I had to be careful, since I'm a leader of people.
Then will you become frie—
You want to become my servant, right?
That's quite an interesting way to interpret it.
Uh well...
You're my arch-nemesis, so I overcomplicated it a little.
You kept flattering me because you
wanted to become my servant, right?
Um...
Milady, are enemies and servants the only way you can group people together?
What? You don't get that?
Sasami wants a more equal, kind, and deep relationship.
I see.
I get it now.
Everything has become crystal-clear!
You approached me when my body was virile.
That means you fell in love with me!
This is getting better and better!
Huh?!
Everything has fallen into place.
It's a bit of a nuisance, but being loved doesn't feel all that bad.
Slow down, milady! Your distance from the truth is widening with each passing moment.
Oh shut up!
You love me, don't you?
Yeah, I love you, Edogawa! So be my friend—
Not "Edogawa"! If you really love me, you should call me something else!
Lady Jou! My mistress! Whatever!
Then can I just call you Jou?
Kagamin
That's stupid.
Kagami, where're you going?
Let's go to the festival together!
Kagamin
If I'm there, you'll end up relying on me.
Sasami
Huh?
You finally found a friend all on your own.
Kagamin
Get along with her.
Kagami?
I wish you happiness, Sasami.
Kagami!
What's gotten into you?
Didn't you see? Kagami!
Kagami!
What's going on? Explain!
You're becoming my servant, right?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa!
I've gotta go!
I'll call you later!
Hey! Wait, Sasami!
Very well! Then don't come!
Sasami
Hurry, Tama!
There!
Kagami...
Don't look at me, please.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Kagami?
I'm weird.
I should be happy. I should be supporting you.
But when I see you trying to get along with Edogawa, I...
I don't understand myself.
Someone important to me is making a new friend.
Her wish is fulfilled and she's happy.
I can't support you!
I must be broken somewhere.
I'm a robot, so when I'm broken, I mustn't be around people!
Kagami...
Kagami, you're no robot.
You don't have to support me.
Just stay by my side.
You're human, Kagami.
You're a girl more human than anyone else.
That's why you got hurt.
I hurt you accidentally.
I should be the one apologizing.
Don't cry, Kagami.
I'm sorry...
You should worry more about Edogawa than me.
You're so stupid.
Foolish.
Trust me.
Sasami
No matter how much I change,
whoever I encounter,
however the world changes,
I'll always love you, Kagami!
It's so incredibly difficult without you by my side.
You're making a new friend,
and I can't help but feel that it's because I'm lacking as a person,
and when I think so I just get so restless...
I want to disappear...
I've encountered this ineffable feeling. I must be broken.
I'm happy you're feeling like that because of me.
I'm really happy you were hurt by what I did.
You're so mean.
They all seem so happy.
It would be lovely if this moment lasted forever.
Right, Lady Juju?
Wait, is that...
Tsukuyomi shrine work log.
Log keeper: Micchan.
Today was my birthday.
The head of the family gave me a collar. Is that supposed to be a present?
When I considered that he'd want me to put it on, I thought "What is this guy even thinking?"
but looking closely, the collar had the name of the head of the family carved in it.
I noticed that he was completely naked, pretending to be a dog.
This triggered an indescribable emotion which took complete control over me, leaving my mind totally blank.
Next thing I remember, the head of the family...
I'm terribly sorry!
Where is he?!
So late!
What's Sasami doing?!
She said she'd call me later!
You told her she didn't have to come.
You're feeling lonely after all, milady?
I-It's not like I'm lonely or anything!
I just want to get over with our final battle already!
Yes, of course.
So good!
What's that, Tama? What happened to acting like Sasami?
She's worn out spiritually, so she's taking a rest.
Oh Kagami, buy that for me!
I treated you because I thought you were Sasami!
C'mon, buy that for me!
My dear sister!
Stop doing that!
Why?
Fireworks.
Isn't it pretty?
It's really pretty,
Brother.
Sasami@Unmotivated
Good night.
The long-awaited miraculous showtime is finally here!
Today we get to enjoy the beautiful voice of everyone's super-idol, Sasami!
Sasami! Sasami! Sasami!
C'mon, sing! Then take your clothes off!
Good luck, Mamarin!
Huh, what? What's going on?
I told you I won't sing!
That won't do it this time.
Important people are really upset, so get over it and sing!
You could put some effort into it, too.
Okay, I'll do it then! But sing along with me!
You smile at me with a disappointed look.
Hey, let's go home together.
I can hear your voice.
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony.
Light shines down like love.
Let's hold hands forever.
I can feel our osmotic pressure,
and I don't want it to stop.
This was tough... I'm not putting forth any effort from tomorrow, okay?
You did really well!
Preview
Unmotivated@Drama
It's time for the Unmotivated@Drama.
In the previous episodes:
stuff happened.
How will the fate of the two unfold now?
We've gone through stuff, haven't we?
Yeah, we have.
To be continued.
About the next episode.
Stuff happens.
After a sudden plot twist, how will the fate of the two unfold?
Be sure to tune in.
Next episode: finale
Next episode, the finale.
No efforts      tomorrow
No effort tomorrow.