I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but a sudden situation changed everything.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
Was the encounter that led me along this magical
path just a coincidence, or was it fate?
I'm not quite sure right now, but...
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
The Lost Logia is around here, correct?
Its manifestation is a blue jewel...
...generally called a "Jewel Seed."
That's right.
I'll have it soon enough.
A Rival!? Another Magical Girl!
Come on, Yuuno... c'mere, c'mere!
Good, good.
You're so smart, Yuuno.
Nanoha, are you ready yet?
Ah... sorry! Just a little longer!
Huh? Are you two going somewhere today?
Yeah, to the Tsukimuras' house.
Suzuka-chan apparently invited Nanoha over.
Ahh... I see.
So then... I suppose you're going
over too, to see Shinobu-san.
Well... I thought Nanoha might need
someone to walk her over, so...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Well then, shall we get going?
If we leave now, we should be able to catch the bus.
Okay!
Yuuno-kun, come here!
Well... have a nice time.
Yep.
We're off!
Today, we made plans to have a
tea party at Suzuka-chan's house.
I'll be spending the entire day with
Suzuka-chan and Alisa-chan.
And Onii-chan is coming along to see
Suzuka-chan's older sister, Shinobu-san.
Oh, it's nothing. Really.
Is that so?
Kyouya-sama, Miss Nanoha, welcome.
Thank you for the invitation.
Good afternoon!
This is Noel-san, the head maid
of the Tsukimura family.
She's a little reserved,
but she's beautiful and really cool!
Please come in.
Right this way.
Nanoha-chan! Kyouya-san!
Suzuka-chan.
Nanoha-chan, welcome!
This is Farin-san. She's Suzuka-chan's personal maid,
and she's like a cheerful and kind older sister.
Kyouya... hello.
Yeah.
Onii-chan and Shinobu-san have been
classmates since high school.
And they're still really close to each other even now.
Let me prepare you both some tea.
What type would you like?
You can decide for me.
And how about you, Miss Nanoha?
I'll leave it up to you, too!
Understood.
Farin.
Yes. Coming, Onee-sama.
Well then... Kyouya and I will be up in my room...
All right. I'll bring the tea up to you when it's ready.
Good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
Suzuka's cute sister and Nanoha's brother really
seem to be deeply in love, don't they?
Yes.
Ever since Onee-chan's gotten to know
Kyouya-san, she's seemed very happy.
As for my older brother... who knows?
But comparing him to the way he used to be,
I guess you could say he's lightened up a bit.
He smiles a lot more now.
I see.
Before I forget, thanks for inviting me here today.
Not at all. It's my pleasure, and thank you for coming.
You seem pretty lively today.
Nanoha-chan, you've looked a little down recently, so...
If you're worried about something, I was wondering
if maybe you could talk to us about it?
At least, that's what the two of
us were talking about earlier.
Suzuka-chan... Alisa-chan...
Yuuno-kun!
Ai, stop that.
Here I am!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've brought you some strawberry milk
tea and cream cheese cookies!
Farin, watch out!
Safe...
Suzuka-chan! Nanoha-chan! I'm sorry!
There she goes again...
She's quite a handful at times.
But anyway, your house sure is a cat heaven, isn't it?
But it's okay, since the kittens are so cute.
Yeah!
But some kittens are already promised to
people, so I'll have to part with them...
I see...
I guess that's kind of sad, huh?
Still, I'm happy the kittens will be
able to grow up big and healthy.
Yeah.
You're so cute...
There, there.
Nanoha...
Yeah, it's really close.
What should we do?
Umm...
Uhh...
I know!
Yuuno-kun?
Huh? Is something wrong with Yuuno-kun?
Yeah, I think he found something.
I-I'll go look for him.
Should we go with you?
I'll be fine. We'll be right back, so just wait here.
It's been activated!
Since there's a good chance of someone seeing
us, we'll need to put up a barrier this time!
A barrier...?
The same kind of space I made when I first met you.
It combines magical space and reality to
slightly delay time outside of the barrier.
It's one of the few types of magic I'm good at.
I can't make it all that wide, but...
If I only need to cover this general
area, I should be able to manage.
Th... Th... Th...
That's...
P-Probably...
That kitten's feelings of wanting to become
big... were literally granted?
I... I see...
But it'll still get dangerous at this rate, so if
we don't change it back to normal soon...
Y-You're right.
It'd probably be a big problem for
Suzuka-chan if it stayed that size.
It doesn't look like it'll come after us,
so if we just seal it now, nice and quickly...
Well then... Raising Heart!
Bardiche. Photon Lancer - Electricity.
Photon Lancer. Full auto fire.
Wh...?!
Magical light...
That can't be...
Raising Heart! Please!
Stand by, Ready. Set up.
Flier Fin.
Wide Area Protection.
A mage...
I'm a little less surprised every
time I see what she can do...
It might just be that there's nothing
more I can teach Nanoha...
Another mage, the same as myself.
Another person searching for the Lost Logia.
There's no doubt about it now...
She comes from my world.
And this girl... she knows the true
identity of the Jewel Seeds...
Another intelligent device, just like my Bardiche.
Bardiche...?
The Lost Logia... or rather, Jewel Seed...
Scythe Form. Set up.
I'm terribly sorry, but I will be the one to claim it.
Evasion.
Flier Fin.
Arc Saber.
Protection.
Nanoha!
Why...?
Why are you doing this so suddenly?
Even if I answer...
It'll probably mean nothing to you.
Device Form.
Shooting Mode.
Divine Buster, Stand by.
Photon Lancer, Get set.
I'm sure she's around the same age as me...
She has such beautiful eyes and hair...
But... this girl is...
I'm sorry...
Fire.
Nanoha!
Sealing Form, Set up.
Capture!
Order?
Lost Logia... Jewel Seed Serial XIV.
Seal.
Yes, sir.
Sealing.
Captured.
When I woke up, the evening twilight
had already stained the sky.
Yuuno-kun went and got my brother and everyone else.
I lied a little and said I tripped and fainted
while I was searching for Yuuno-kun.
I made everyone worry...
and I'm so sorry for doing that.
That staff, those clothes, and how she used magic...
She's probably...
No, I'm sure of it. She's someone from my world.
Yeah...
I wonder if... we'll run into her again while
gathering the remaining Jewel Seeds?
Strangely, that thought doesn't really scare me...
But... I'm sad, and filled with
so many confusing feelings...
There was a bit of interference,
but everything turned out all right.
Jewel Seed... Serial XIV...
I wonder how many she has?
It'll be all right. I won't stray from my path.
Wait for me, Mother...
I'll return to you soon...
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Sometimes students and
employees need breaks!
And with that said,
we've arrived here!
We're at our local
Ocean's Roar Hot Springs!
Just when we started to relax,
who's this causing trouble?
And what's the goal of that
mysterious magical girl?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Five: This is a Town
of Hot Water, and the Ocean's Roar Hot Springs!
I, Lyrical Magical,
will do my best!