Reiji-san.
Forgive me for getting here so late.
You're...
...Uncle Daisuke's...
Umm, mom.
Is it about your father?
Some people have been saying things about Father and Uncle Daisuke.
I figured that one day the time would come when we had to talk about it.
Although it came faster than I expected.
Your father's death is a lie.
He's still alive.
We could never even imagine the cruel and unrelenting world he lives in.
Can you...
...accept that?
At first I thought of living together with him.
I didn't care if I were to lose my life over it.
But now I think this is for the best.
By leaving me behind,
he could keep our memories.
He can keep the one thing we cherished as support in his heart.
He longed for where I stood and remain,
but he could never reach this place with me.
Staying far away from each other was our only option.
We could only return to each other in our dreams.
If I had been selfish,
I'd have ruined his wishes.
I'm living the life he yearned for in his dreams in his stead.
Love isn't all about being together.
Mom...
Daisuke-san is your father's son from his previous wife.
He could endure all his hardships because his little sister lived happily in his place.
He told me so himself.
I...
...have something I need to tell him.
I give up...
I guess it's in the blood.
Damn.
I have no chance of finding them even if I turn every stone.
Fujieda-san?
Yes.
Elen rescued me.
I'm back home now.
Thank god.
Reiji-san.
Elen and Cal-san are trying to kill each other.
I overheard them talking on the phone.
They meet at 3 AM.
They were talking about a place both of them know well.
...both of them know well?
Also...
Cal-san is suffering.
She had no one to talk to.
Reiji-san, please help them both.
Leave it to me.
Everything will be fine.
I'll work something out.
Fujieda-san.
I'm sorry about everything that has happened.
It's all my fault.
It's okay.
I don't mind at all.
By tomorrow I won't remember anything.
So you can come back here any time you wish.
I love how you laugh.
If you can feel happy like I saw you can, it's fine for you to be here.
Thank you, I'm really grateful to you.
Fujieda-san, I...
I'll be waiting.
I'll keep waiting for the time when your burdens are gone and you can return to me.
That's why...
...this isn't farewell.
I'll see you soon.
Yeah.
See you soon.
Listen up, don't underestimate them because they're just kids.
Are you going to kill them?
I'll be there shortly.
I won't let Mio-san stand in harm's way any more.
I promise you that.
Do you think that's what Mio wants?
This is the promise I made to Brother Daisuke.
How selfish.
You people are always like this.
Shiga-san.
The one who shot Daisuke-san...
What is...
Huh?
...the meaning of all this?
No meaning whatsoever.
I'm just doing it because I want to.
That's all.
What will you leave behind once you're dead?
Nothing at all.
He will be dead,
my flames will have died,
and everything will be over.
That's all.
Is that really all you ever wanted?
Yes, it is!
What else would there be?
Besides, what about yourselves?
What did you ever accomplish when you were alive?
What did you leave behind when you died?
Nothing!
All of you died like trash!
Indeed.
And so will you one day.
You will disappear without proof you ever lived or a reason why you were born.
Don't screw with me.
I'm different from you people.
I'm the invincible Phantom!
I finally found...
...something I can do better than anyone else.
A way of life where no one dares to look down on me.
This is my everything.
I steal...
I bring ruin...
I don't want it to be the other way around again.
I knew you'd be here.
Do you really think this is for the best?
Yes.
You won't be able to shoot Cal.
No, I'll be the one to kill her.
I will burden myself with all her agony and wrath.
I will probably be the saddest person alive when she dies,
but I can be the one to mourn for her.
That's why I will kill her.
I refuse.
You will lose.
I don't want to lose you.
Elen...
I don't want you to do it all by yourself.
You're gentle.
You won't be able to shoot her.
I'll stay here as well.
Together we can beat her.
Please understand, this is my karma.
If I don't put an end to this,
I will be forever imprisoned by my past.
I'll never be free.
Elen, leave ahead of me.
I'll catch up with you later.
Where should I go without you?
I don't even know where I come from.
I can't remember anything.
What should I do to free myself?
What is freedom if it's obtained through killing others?
Tell me...
...please...
Let's look for it...
...together.
To find it I will definitely return to you.
Reiji...
Elen won't be coming.
Why are you...
Because it's my responsibility.
To protect her?
No.
Cal.
It is to kill you.
Many people have been sacrificed before today.
I lied to countless people,
used them, and killed them...
...for the sole purpose of staying alive.
How dare you say such shameless words...
You're right, Cal.
You bear righteous hatred.
You don't need to point your gun at anybody else.
Punish me with that gun of yours.
Don't leave it to someone else.
Do it on your own.
If you're stronger,
retribution will be brought down upon me.
Very well.
I won't let you get in their way.
Fire at will!
If you really want to resolve everything,
let this decide.
That's...
Oh, so you recognize it?
This is the fate we share.
This has cast light on my path until today.
It was always there to tell me whom to hate or whom to kill.
The duel is with handguns.
We draw when the song ends.
Ready?
The only one who's heard this song and not been killed...
...is you, Reiji.
What? Were you sleeping?
I had a dream...
...of when we were still in L.A..
Oh? What about?
What would have happened to us if we had been separated after our hideout was blown?
That sounds stupid.
You wouldn't make such a mistake.
It's impossible for us to be separated.
If it did happen, I'd look for you.
To the end of the world.
No way it could happen...
I really am stupid beyond salvation.
I say such things...
It's alright.
Once in a while.
Isn't it fine this way?
At least it would be...
...if I could find the unlikely salvation I dream of.
Is this where Judy Devens died?
How can you be so strong?
I can only answer you this way.
I see.
I guess...
I did manage to have you for myself in the end.
Then I'm fine.
I don't need anything else.
Is that the reason you threw your life away?
What do you mean?
Is there any more reason than that?
Do you think we could have lived a different life?
Met under different circumstances and lived somewhere far away?
Yeah, we just...
...took a wrong turn somewhere.
I'm sure of it.
I'm glad I met you, Reiji.
That's all...
...I need.
I'm happy...
Cal!
Phantom... you monster!
Sheesh, I fail to understand your lot.
I was expecting you to be smarter than this, Mr. Shiga.
Why didn't you leave everything to us?
You bastard! Were you just watching from the sidelines until now?
The stage has reached the epilogue at last.
Unrefined extras aren't welcome.
If you don't mind, vacate the premises and watch from the side.
Consider it an honor; this public performance will be my masterpiece.
The concerto of the ultimate phantoms.
Well then,
who will answer the curtain call, I wonder.
I...
...will kill.
To keep on living,
I will kill.
Even though I've made lots of mistakes...
...and failed to keep many promises in my life,
there is one promise I must keep no matter what.