Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room bright,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Have you ever had times when you
didn't know what you wanted to do?
That's exactly the way I am right now.
I worked hard, trying to
get into Kaleido Stage.
Then I worked hard so that I'd
be acknowledged by everyone,
and I worked hard trying
to catch up with Miss Layla.
But, I wonder what I'm working hard for now?
No... Not good. Not good.
I can't become a star with my
feelings all wishy-washy like this.
I can't! I can't!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
That's right.
This is my duel with fate!
Demon Spiral!
Her movements are too irregular;
it's impossible to follow.
Amazing... Can he grab her?
Not good. She doesn't have enough height.
A devil's maneuver?
That certainly might be
appropriate for a partner of mine.
Then...
It seems this has been decided.
"Amazing Angelic Counterattack."
Even for someone like Sora,
it must be quite a shock this time.
I can't even say anything to her.
Let's leave her alone right now.
Sora...
Demon Spiral...
May had a shoulder injury,
but she used that to invent a new maneuver.
And she got the Phoenix Ticket.
I...
Sora...
Miss Layla...
To tell you the truth, I didn't
think May would go that far either.
I was actually moved by the fact
that she invented a new maneuver
by taking advantage of her injuries.
I'm sorry.
Three years ago,
before Yuri and I participated
in the Circus Festival,
Kalos told us this:
Listen very carefully, both of you.
If you cannot win, don't come back here.
If you cannot win in the Circus Festival,
you two have nowhere to come back to.
The Boss told you something like that?
That was why I didn't
have any choice but to win.
But you won your duel with fate.
You really are amazing.
What are you going to do now?
I will try to improve my skills
so that I can keep up with May.
Sora, are you thinking you lost to May
because you didn't have enough skills?
What?
If I thought you didn't have enough skills,
I never would have recommended you.
You lost because the festival meant
only that much to you. Am I right?
No, I never thought that way.
To me, it was something I needed
to enter and win by all means.
To me, it was worth that much.
But, for you, it was not worth that much.
Sora, I will ask you one more time.
Do you seriously want to participate in
the Circus Festival no matter what happens?
Yes!
Once you make up your mind and decide
to seriously follow through,
you never give up.
I know that better than anyone else.
But here you are, right now,
having given up on everything.
That's proof that you
weren't serious about it.
I think I told you after the Salome show.
I can't feel enough of that edge
from you right now to be scared of you.
You've lost track of what's important.
I wanted you to enter to the festival.
Miss Layla!
I can't believe what I did...
I...
I betrayed Miss Layla's expectations.
Sora, Sora, take the tape off!
I want to do something.
I have to do something.
What can I do? Tell me, Fool!
I don't know the answer either.
You're no help.
Aren't you supposed to be on my side?
Can't you give me some
clever advice or something?
I am the spirit of the stage.
I'm neither enemy nor ally.
One more time, I want
to have one more chance.
Oh, I can't believe
I feel this way at this point.
I'm really pathetic.
The only thing I can tell you is this.
The deadline for Circus Festival
entries hasn't passed yet.
Sagittarius is still not able to
find its way out from the darkness.
But, nearby Sagittarius,
I can see another arrow;
an arrow shining, as if it's guiding
her way out from the darkness.
Another arrow?
Phoenix Tickets are the "seed" right
which were given to those two who won.
Two...
Two!
There's one more ticket!
There is! There is! There is!
--There's another ticket!
--I can't breathe! I'm gonna wee!
Yuri is studying in Paris
right now, you know.
The Circus Festival will be
held in Paris too. It's perfect!
Take me to Paris, quick!
Paris?
Yuri hasn't even registered for the festival!
He might not have any
intention of being in it.
First of all, it's impossible
to go to Paris by cab.
Impossible or not,
there's nothing to do but ask!
I realized that I can't just keep
moping about how I lost to May.
I just have to acknowledge
my defeat and do what I can now.
I'll end up being absent from Kids'
Stage, but Marion's accepted it,
so things should be okay.
Don't you think Sora's
back to her usual self?
If it's true, we can't stop her now.
Sora!
Rosetta!
This is the guide book for Paris
which I used to use a long time ago.
There's some French phrases
too, although it's not much.
Thank you. This will help.
Also, a winter coat. It's cold over there.
Rosetta, thank you.
Bye!
Go, Sora!
Paris... It must be nice.
The clown I admire, Mr. Charlie, is there.
Oh! So Anna, you're rarin' to go too?
Well, if you put it like
that, I'm parin' to go!
Je... Je...
Je t'aime.
That's...
The God of Death, Leon!
The God of Death's come back.
I'll finish checking in.
Amazing.
Leon, I've not seen you for a long time.
Emma...
So you remember me? I'm glad.
Are you his new partner?
That's right. I am Leon's partner, May Wong.
Poor you.
Once the Circus Festival is
over, you'll be discarded too.
Hey! Just who are you?!
Hey, please don't put us
on the same floor as Leon.
He'll make my performers nervous.
If you can't arrange
this, I'll change hotels!
Please wait for a moment...
There is a message for
Mr. Ken Robbins from Kaleido Stage.
What? For me?
"I will create a chance for you to show off."
So, did you hear it too?
The whisper of the God of Death?
I will create a perfect chance
for you to show off in today's show.
"The whisper of the God of Death"?
Were you also Leon's partner?
Partner? Nobody can be Leon's partner.
Nobody but her.
Her?
Sora's in Paris?
Er... The drama school where Yuri is...
I can't read French!
Where? Where? Where is he?
Yuri!
I see. I'll try to look for her too.
Goodbye.
Well, okay, but... where should I look?
Er... Me-Merci.
My money's all gone after
I took the cab. Well, but...
Yuri is here.
Non.
What? He is not here?
Mais, c'est bien ici le... Conservatoire...
Excuse...
Oh, what shall I do...
If you're looking for Yuri,
he wasn't in class today.
What?
So, he is here, isn't he?
Yes.
You liar!
Excuse me, but do you know where Yuri is now?
He's, how should I put it,
he marches to his own beat,
or shall I say, he's difficult to approach...
But anyway, I don't really know.
Don't you know where he lives either?
Well...
Sorry.
Bye.
So, there is no clue. What shall I do?
The Circus Festival...
I'm sure... I'm sure Yuri will
come here too. I'm sure! I'm sure!
Oh... So, this is the hall.
Wow, they're performing! Oh...
Merci, merci.
Oh, I know! If I make some money here,
I can look for Yuri, and I can eat something!
I'm not at a dead end yet. I'm not! I'm not!
Hey, they're getting fired up.
Oh, Mute and Alice.
She is something of a performer.
She's amazing. But I've
never seen her before.
She's pretty good. Who is she?
Ta-da!
Huh?
Super!
Brava!
Oh... Merci! Merci! Merci!
Wow, now I can eat something with this.
Hey, are you all right?
Did you hurt yourself?
Oh... I understand what
he is saying. I'm lucky.
What?! What did you say? Hey!
Really... I thought you
hurt yourself. I was worried.
Whoever would have
thought she was just hungry?
I'm sorry! I haven't eaten
anything since I got to Paris, you see.
Then it's impressive that you
can manage maneuvers like that.
I wanted to enter the Circus
Festival no matter what, you see...
Are you going to participate in the festival?
I want to!
Mute and Alice, you too?
Yeah.
We want to win in the festival
and get the world's attention,
and organize a performance team with
these guys right here, and travel around.
That is our dream.
Everyone's dreams rest
heavily on Mute's shoulders.
Well, I guess.
Wow!
Didn't you also come here to
make your dream come true, Sora?
Don't give up that dream.
An angel always keeps
an eye on us somewhere.
An angel...
My angel...
Sora!
Yes!
Huh?
What do you know, it's Sora.
Yuri!
Yuri... Don't tell me he's the Yuri Killian.
Does she know Yuri Killian
who won the last time?
Who on Earth is she?
Yuri!
Oh, I'm glad. I finally found you.
I was sure you would come here.
Whoever thought I would
see you in a place like this?
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Yes!
An angel always keeps an eye on you.
Miss Layla, I will never give up on
participating in this Circus Festival.
Hmm... It's such a different
atmosphere from America or Japan.
It's calm, isn't it?
Yes.
It looks like you've
completely adjusted to Paris.
You think so?
Yes.
Well... To tell you the truth,
I came to Paris because
I wanted to ask you a favor.
A favor? What kind?
You have Phoenix Tickets, don't you?
Yes, I do. Why?
Using those tickets,
I want you to participate in
the Circus Festival with me.
That is a big favor.
Please, Yuri!
You're the only hope left for me!
Sora, I didn't happen to
be there just by coincidence.
I went there looking for
you after Layla asked me.
What? Miss Layla?
And I've heard the gist of
what happened at Kaleido Stage.
Then...
But I think this is too tough for you.
Why?
Sora, you really don't know
what kind of place this festival is.
This is the place that can
make your dreams come true.
But at the same time, it's also a place
where you destroy the dreams of others.
I already know that.
And I also know that victory
means beating everybody else.
But, I have to win here.
Here, there's no such thing as
fair play, friendship, or consideration.
If you let your guard down,
someone will get the jump on you.
Do you know this is that kind of world?
Yes, I do.
Then, for example, if a friend of yours,
let's say Ken,
suddenly collapsed just before you perform,
and you received a call saying that he
was in the hospital and wanting to see you...
What would you do?
At that time...
It's possible that the call was a
lie made up by another performer.
Yes, that's true...
Sorry. I think that question
was a little mean.
All right.
Yuri...
Let's participate in the festival together.
I will submit an entry application tomorrow.
Thank you!
So this is where you live.
Wow... Did you paint all these, Yuri?
Yeah.
What with spending all my time commuting
back and forth between here and school,
maybe I started wanting some company.
I just casually picked up a brush,
and then I was completely into it.
Everyone is smiling.
When I was at Kaleido Stage,
I don't think I looked at
the audience's faces much.
When I started painting,
I realized how wonderful smiling faces were.
Is this the picture you're painting now?
Yeah. When I tried to capture the
essence of the smile, it became an angel.
Angel...
It's May. I'd like to start
training soon, if that's all right.
All right.
So, this is it.
Leon Oswald, eh?
In order to beat Leon and May's Demon Spiral,
I suppose we need a maneuver on par with it?
Shall we try an angel's maneuver?
An angel's maneuver?
That's right. To counter
their demon maneuver.
Yes.
Sora?
We will help your practice.
Mute and Alice?
It must be hard because
you don't have too much time.
And we also can learn something if we
get to watch the previous winner's practice.
What do you want to do, Sora?
Since they offered us a hand,
I think we should accept their offer.
That's what she says.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Even among those
people who enter the festival,
there are nice people like Mute and Alice.
Good! Then, go higher like that!
No! Not good at all.
Okay!
Do it like you're flying
upwards on your own power!
Yes!
I won't lose to May! I'll definitely win!
In order to meet Miss Layla's expectations.
Demon Spiral!
That speed is your limit?
No! I can go faster!
Then speed up to your limit!
Yes!
That's right. Do it more slowly.
Like an angel's wings...
Yes!
So, this is a winning candidate's maneuver...
I'm going to win no matter what!
The one to win will be...
me!
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (Here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
Perhaps a match with you
is my unavoidable destiny.
And so, it's showtime!
What? Mr. Yuri and Mr. Leon know each other?
Wait! What happened between them?
How would I know something like that?
What I saw during the
battle was betrayal and despair.
Something I believed in is
shattering! Shattering! Shattering!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Cruel Amazing Festival."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...