Oh, okay...
Please! Please marry me!
I have no choice.
If you're going to say it like that, I'll do it.
Takasu Ryuuji's Dog House
Ryu-chan look, look.
Taiga-chan has given birth to so many babies.
They're your children.
A dream, huh...
Even though it's finally summer vacation.
Because of that ridiculous DVD I borrowed,
I had such a strange dream.
Even if it was just a dream, it was terrible.
That kind of future.
Oh, Taiga.
I had a terrible dream.
Huh?
I saw you as a dog, a dog as my husband.
Anyway, it was a terrible dream.
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
You who said let's go to the beach
A warning dream?
That's right.
If you don't find some kind of counter-measure,
that wretched kind of future is waiting for us.
That dream is a warning to us.
And so, in order to change the future,
I think one of us should support the other with all their might on tomorrow's trip.
I understand that but...
Why badminton?
That's why...
To decide it of course, which of us is getting supported.
Listen, be sure to leave the stove off.
Stir the rice bran mix once a day.
Be sure to change Inko-chan's water once in the morning and once at night.
And lastly, read the list I left for you today.
Okay, I'll be going now.
Go? Where to?
Haven't I told you?
We're going on a trip.
See you later, Yacchan.
Ah, it looks like we're going to have good weather today~
Well, I'll be counting on you.
For "that" strategy.
Hey, are you sure?
Okay, okay, it's your win.
Just get this dog away from me!
If it weren't for that stupid dog helping you,
that would've been my victory!
That's because you were trying to beat me at something which was your specialty.
It's divine punishment.
Man, nothing good ever happens when you're mixed up with dogs.
But, will it work well?
I told you, just leave it to me.
After this trip, your relation with Minorin will be...
Huh?
What? What's wrong?
Good morning! Both of you have arrived on time.
Hahaha! Fantastic! That's fantastic!
What's up?
You guys look down.
Let out your voice!
What's that?
What?
Well, the weather's perfect for the trip, isn't it?
You must not look!
Um, yeah...
By the way, Ami isn't here yet, huh?
There's still time left before she's late though.
I have a great idea!
What the hell's up with those guys?
No one's coming after all.
H-Hey...
You're two minutes late, Ami.
Good morning! Ami.
You're late, stupid Chihuahua.
H-Ha ha...
W-Where's everybody?
Hey! Don't run away, stupid Chihuahua!
Ami, we're over here.
Wow, this is really delicious. The plum inside is uber-delicious!
As expected of Takasu.
You want to marry into my family?
No, I won't.
My, you're mean.
By the way,
I don't see Aisaka-san anywhere.
Is she late?
Takasu-kun, contact h-...
OUCH!
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh my, so you were awake, stupid Chihuahua.
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes wide open.
I told you not to fight at least until we get there...
By the way, what are you doing for summer vacation, Kawashima?
Me? Always working.
Oh, so you've resumed your job.
How about you, Minorin?
Club. Part-time. Club. Part-time...
How about you, Taiga?
Well, I...
What's up, Taiga?
...made this.
J-Just now, I heard "senpai" in a strange voice.
Is this...
Yeah.
I've compiled new ghost voices from the "Moon Of Temptation" CD.
I knew it!
No! I was called!
Aisaka, do you like that kind of horror stuff?
Y-Yeah... probably...
Hm... That's surprising.
It's also surprising that Kushieda can't handle those kind of things.
Yeah, I'm scared. Uber-scared.
You see, Minorin is...
...really scared of horror movies, spirits and occult-related things.
That's why we're going to scare her to death.
And while she's terrified, you will rescue her while saying,
"I will protect Kushieda!"
This strategy is called, "Scare Minorin, Her Knight in Shining Armor Appears!"
Anyway, scary things are definitely prohibited!
Wow!
It's the sea!
Damn, how long do we have to walk?
You can see it already, can't you?
Huh?
Let's walk to the back.
Just keep going, and we can look out from the veranda.
Wow!
Is this Ami's villa? We're going to stay here?
That's right, Minori-chan.
Superb! I'm really moved!
But first, we'll have to clean it.
It hasn't been used since last year.
Since last year?!
My, this is going to be a vicious battle.
Hee... A beautiful sea is in front of us like this, cleaning can be done later.
Yeah, I agree. Cleaning can be done later.
I'm going too.
I'm going too, how about you, Takasu-kun?
Here I go!
Why am I cleaning alone?
That feels good.
Hey, hey.
Yeah, what's wrong?
That thing, doesn't it look like a human's head?
Whoa! A floating corpse!
What should I do? I found a floating corpse!
Looks like they're having fun.
Those guys.
You really did come, Yuusaku.
Of course I'd come.
If Takasu comes, I, as his best friend, must come too.
Is it okay?
The things with the student council.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Takasu, Ami said to buy groceries for dinner.
Apparently, there's a motorcycle in the garage.
Motorcycle?
In that case, take Taiga with you.
Together with Aisaka?
I'm not going. I'm afraid of motorcycles.
What?!
Be careful.
Yeah, I know.
See you later.
Ah... And just a perfect chance for you two to be alone together.
I have my reasons.
Before those two return,
I'll have to find places suitable for "that" plan, right?
You're just embarrassed, if only you were more hon-...
I said I have my reasons!
Man, even if you say places that can be used, but...
This place is...
A bathroom, huh. If this place is not cleaned...
Eh?
W-Who's there?
I'm sorry, I didn't realise that there was someone here.
Takasu-kun?
I'm leaving now.
You're really brave, aren't you?
To enter while a lady's in the middle of a shower.
It's not like it was on purpose.
That's fine.
If it's now, I'll keep it a secret from the others.
You, what're you....
Hey, don't you wanna do it?
Do what?
Cleaning the bathroom.
Huh?
No way, what were you expecting?
What's with the face? What a masterpiece!
Hm...
Taiga...
Huh?
The stupid Chihuahua is...
...acting like she's taking a shower...
...playing with a man's pure heart...
...so, are you finished investigating the 2nd floor?
You're useless!
That's why you got tricked by the likes of the stupid Chihuahua.
That's enough, I'll do it.
And, I have a thing or two to say to her on the way.
Hey, stupid Chi...
That stupid Chihuahua was really taking a shower this time...
The stupid Chihuahua was like...
The stupid Chihuahua was like... Bom!
The stupid Chihuahua was like... Bom! Bom!
The stupid Chihuahua was like... Bom! Bom! and Boooom!
Don't say unnecessary things!
I'm back.
You bought quite a lot.
What about Kitamura?
He's pulling the motorcycle around.
I-Is that so....
I'll carry them.
N-No, that's fine.
You did the shopping after all.
Is that so?
W-What's wrong?
J-Just now, there was something touching my neck.
Must've been your imagination.
I-I guess you're right...
Yeah, you're...
Just now, there definitely was something touching me.
Slimy, like a seaweed.
I knew it! I smelled seaweed. It's seaweed.
It seems the seaweed has some unsettled things with me.
Sea otter?!
Is that why it wants to kill me?!
The pet you raised was the sea otter that died by drowning?!
I've been cursed by the sea otter and the seaweed!
No way! I can't eat spicy food, so no!
Well, I can eat spicy food, so yes!
If it's not sweet, I can't eat it!
Hey, Ryuji!
I know, I'll make your portion sweeter than the others.
Aisaka-san's getting special treatment again...
If you do it like that, you'll be hated by all the girls you know, including Minori.
Did you call me?
You're almost done? You're really skilled at this, aren't you?
Yeah, I just have to add the roux.
Come on, you guys should also prepare the table...
Oh, it's already time for dinner?
As long as it's something like making a salad, I can help.
Y-You...
Hey, Taiga!
Yuusaku, are you insane?!
Oh, sorry. I heard Takasu's voice, so...
I forgot there are girls here too.
Are you stupid?!
Taiga, get a hold of yourself!
Sorry. Sorry.
Hey, hey!
Why you narcissistic boy! Give me some nude poses!
Oh, stop it.
What are you doing with that sort of pose, pretending to be modest!
Just now, something black flashed past me.
It was probably the spirit of the seaweed.
S-Sea... weed...
Kushieda!
Yuusaku, you're the worst!
Sorry.
Enough, just go!
Be careful, everyone.
There's an evil spirit lurking in this place.
Is there anything I can do?
Just make my curry really spicy.
Got it.
Wow! It looks delicious.
Just as Kushieda requested, I made it as spicy as possible.
Okay! Let's eat.
Itadakimasu.
This is good.
It is delicious.
It's not as spicy as I thought it would be.
Is that so?
Taiga, want to try a bite?
Yeah, it's true.
Huh?
Minori?
Spicy!
My nose!
It's hot! It hurts!
Thanks for the meal!
Are you guys all right?
Takasu-kun, you're the best!
Super-spicy! Super-delicious!
Indeed. There's a strange attraction to it.
I feel kind of strange.
Well, if you want more, there are seconds...
I want more!
Ugh, I thought I was gonna die.
Okay, I'll do the dishes.
Um, me too...
What is it?
I wonder if it's because I ate spicy stuff.
I want some stomach medicine.
Stomachache?
But if I remember correctly, the medicine is...
Aisaka, are you feeling sick?
If you want some medicine, it's in my room.
Want to go together?
T-That is...
Then I'll leave it to you.
W-Wait...
It's a chance to be alone together, right?
What's wrong?
Nope, nothing.
Well, I'm counting on you.
Hey, hey.
Whoa!
Ami-chan also has a tummy-ache.
Huh?
As if.
What was that all about?
Nothing, that's because you spaced out.
It's never boring around you.
Is that a compliment?
Strangely, yes.
What's with that?
Anyway, if you'd like, would you come with me to the beac-...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Fetch me the glass over there please.
Yeah, I'll do it.
Sorry, what did you say?
Nothing.
Is the water enough?
Yeah.
So, how is it? Does it look like it's working?
Probably...
Oh good, is that so?
Looking at Aisaka's painful face makes me hurt too.
Oh yeah, if it hurts, do you want to lie down?
Your cleaning technique is great, isn't it?
Well that's because I'm always doing a lot of part-time work.
Takasu-kun too, your curry was splendid.
No, that's not...
Oh, that's right.
For helping me, I'll give you something good.
It's a secret from the others, okay?
Takasu-kun, is green tea good?
Yeah, it's delicious.
The azuki bean flavoured is not that good.
The stars are beautiful, aren't they?
It's beautiful.
We're alone.
It's a chance.
K-Kushieda, do you have a boyfriend?
That seaweed spirit from before, I wonder if it's still around here.
Takasu-kun, have you seen ghosts before?
No, nope.
I believe ghosts exist.
But, I haven't seen them myself,
and I also don't believe stories from people who said they've seen them.
And I also, in the same way, believe that,
someday I will fall in love, get married, and be happy.
But in reality, I haven't felt that way about anyone yet.
For in this world, the people that are naturally loved, are still very far away from me.
That's because I can't see it.
Really, I know that ghosts don't exist.
And that I won't be able to see one during my whole life, so I've given up...
So, the answer to that question is no.
How about you, Takasu-kun? Are you a person that can see ghosts?
I, might want to see one.
That's why I visited places with spirits.
And also watched horror DVDs.
I think, those people that are sensitive to spirits... would they be surprised upon seeing a ghost for the first time?
People who've tried to erase its existence because they think it's impossible,
and people who've worked hard to finally be able to see it,
I think people like that exist.
That's why, if you've decided that you won't be able to see it for your whole life, I think that's fine too.
Huh? What's that? A UFO?
Man-made satellite perhaps?
Man-made satellite...
What... I thought it was a UFO.
I, I think it would be good if you were able to see ghosts one day.
A ghost that you want to see probably exists somewhere.
That's why a lot of strange things happened today.
It's appealing to me. That spirit of seaweed.
What's with that, suddenly.
Can I see it someday?
Huh?
Nope, nothing.
Wahahahahaha.
Strange girl.
Huh?
Hey, Ryuji.
It looks like my stomach is feeling better now.
Okay, then?
I'm full, I'm full.
Why me too?
Hey, what should we do for tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
It's about that strategy.
You haven't had any progress at all.
What about you?
This time, I'm playing the support role.
Geeze! At any rate, I'm tired.
Being with Kitamura-kun for a whole day, I only thought of how much happiness it would bring.
I was so nervous all day, I felt like I was dying.
That's true.
When I'm with you though, I feel completely fine.
What's with that? How rude!
It's idiotic, even though we're in this huge room, we're sticking close together.
Feels like a habit coming from living in a small apartment.
Why you...
Ryuji, I think, that dream might unexpectedly be...
Hm, what's wrong?
Nope, nothing. Let's sleep.
Oh, okay. Good night.
Huh? Did I leave my bag in a place like this?
W-What... the hell... is this...?
And there's something slimy too.
Ryuji!
What do you think of this?
I had put that in my bag before, but when I touched it a moment ago, it was warm...
It felt like someone was in here until just a moment ago...
There's something strange in my room too.
On my pillow, there's something long like hair...
W-What was that?
N-No, it's gotta be...
This... this is a dream, right?
Th-That's right. It must be a dream.
Living in a dog house, giving birth to dogs, this must be the continuation of the dream.
T-Then, if we close our eyes, we'll wake up, right?
We'll wake up, we'll wake up!
Right?
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
Fireworks
Scary! Scary! Scary!
Horror is scary, ghosts are scary, monsters are scary!
Stay calm, Kushieda.
But, the most scary things might be UFOs.