It's great!
Hooray!
Vous haven't lost votre touch since passing le thé lesson.
Thanks!
There's naught but for me to
advance toward princesshood!
It's really snowing out there.
What is it?
They're so cute!
They're budding in this weather?
Yeah!
They're called snowdrops.
In flower language...
they mean "hope."
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Like a Flower,
With Strength, Grace, and Beauty!
Only the Castle of Flowers remains.
Hope Kingdom will soon be...
Worry not.
Do you mean...
What now?
Girls, something is wrong with the Castle of Flowers!
Please, come quickly!
The Castle of Flowers?
That's the final one.
All right.
Let's go!
Be careful.
Royal Majesty!
It's not covered in thorns?
But it seems le castle hasn't awakened.
What could that mean?
Princess...
Princess... princess!
Is that bird...
It couldn't be!
Princess...
Princess!
W-Wait!
Haruharu?
Princess...
Princess!
Wait!
Haruka!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Huh? What's this?
These clothes make me look like the...
Princess of Flowers!
Welcome to my castle,
Princess of Flowers.
I'm the... Princess of Flowers?
Of course you are!
And you've finally arrived...
to meet your prince!
Now let us be off, Princess!
I'm a... princess...
How lovely!
So splendid!
Princess!
Did you sleep well?
Please, relax with some tea.
Oh, let me do it!
I'm great at pouring tea!
We can't have you getting burned.
Don't worry, I took lessons!
Lessons?
A princess has no need for those.
I don't need lessons?
Wait...
When did I ever take lessons?
Now, eat up.
As long as you're smiling, all is well.
Yummy!
A princess's smile is truly splendid!
What's going on?
Dyspear!
Cure Flora's dream has come true within these walls.
Come true?
What do you mean?
She has forgotten you all and fallen into
the abyss of the happiness she so desired.
Impossible!
She will never wake from her dream... for all eternity!
Dystroyvil.
You girls shall also...
Meet your end here.
What a huge garden!
It is simply splendid!
As gorgeous as flowers may be...
none could hope to rival your beauty.
G-Goodness!
P-Pardon, but may I plant some flower seeds here as well?
To celebrate our visit...
But of course!
Here are your flower seeds!
Thank you!
Huh?
What pretty flowers! Thank you, Princess!
Princess?
Why?
Hm?
Why did it bloom so quickly?
What a silly question!
As long as a flower blooms, all is well, no?
Seeds blossom in a flash and never wilt for all eternity.
This is a land of abundant bliss, after all!
Abundant bliss?
But of course!
Splendid balls at lavish castles!
Exquisite teas surrounded by unwilting gardens!
What else could one desire?
This world is the dream you longed for!
I longed... for this?
Flowers...
bloom just like this?
No.
This is no flower.
Flowers aren't beautiful for their blossoms.
Flowers are beautiful...
because they're planted beneath soil and sprout toward the sunlight.
They withstand the cold and spread their leaves...
ever striving to one day bloom into a beautiful blossom!
They fight the odds on their own strength!
On their own strength...
What do you have to complain about?
Wasn't it your dream to become a princess?
My dream...
Become a princess and live happily ever after.
That's your dream!
And your dream came true!
It didn't!
This isn't the princess I dreamt of!
A dream that comes true with no effort...
isn't worth dreaming!
Lady Dyspear's plan has failed.
But I can't say I didn't expect this.
Close!
I'll crush your dream...
with my own two fists!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
What?
Flora!
Don't look away!
Dystroyvil!
You had the chance to live happily ever after!
That world had nothing to be happy about!
I want to do things myself!
That's what all those lessons were for!
Because it will lead me to my dream...
to becoming a true princess!
What a load!
What is your dream?
What is a real princess?!
Having all the Keys still hasn't made you a Grand Princess!
So what will? How long will it take?!
That's right... your dream leads
to something that doesn't exist!
It's an endless dream!
One you'll never stop chasing!
It's... endless?
Endless...
Yes...
My dream... has no end!
My dream... is to be like a flower blooming upon the land,
growing with strength, grace, and beauty!
Someone who can endure any hardship or sorrow...
and always, no matter what...
stand with strength, grace, and beauty.
That's the princess I want to be!
Lily!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Girls!
Cherry Blossom!
Dance, O cherry blossoms!
Precure!
Cherry Blossom Turbulence!
Dystroy!
Are you okay?
Flora!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Bloom with pride,
O radiant flowers!
It's Hope Kingdom!
It's our homeland!
Flora!
Stand with strength, grace, and beauty...
To accomplish one's goals with one's own strength...
That is the path to becoming a princess.
I guess the lessons we took were to help us do that.
Excellent!
There's nothing left for moi to teach vous.
Vous have become splendid princesses.
All that remains...
is to open that gate of despair...
and free the citizens of this land.
The only ones who can open it...
are Grand Princesses.
Grand Princesses...
Don't worry.
Vous are almost...
Not bad, Precures.
Very well, I'll let you have Hope Kingdom once again.
But despair...
cannot be stopped.
Dyspear!
Where did she go?
She couldn't have...
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Dyspear is flooding the town with despair!
As well as the students?
Wait a sec, what's that huge thing?!
Is it... Lock?!
Could he have revived by consuming despair?
Don't worry, we'll protect everyone at school!
Go! Princess Precure:
Encroaching Despair!
The Cornered Princesses!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hyougo Prefecture - Sayuki (Age 12)
Niigata Prefecture - Miu (Age 6)