Tsukuyomi Shrine Activity Log.
Scribe
Mickie
(Alias)
Scribe, Mickie.
The head's vocabulary has expanded with "I say work's for chumps,"
"people don't gotta work,"
and other such variations.
That's not bad in itself,
but he looks at me like he's a genius whenever he says something,
so after I eventually hit him out of annoyance, I blacked out,
and when I woke up hours later,
I saw the head prostrating himself stark naked,
and instead of calling me Mickie,
Master
he called me "Master."
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 9
It's Not That I Can't
I'm an assassin from the corrupt occult society, Arahabaki,
a spirit living inside this Killing Stone golem!
And a fair skinned, golden haired nine tailed fox!
Nine tailed fox?
This country knows me as the playfully chaotic Tamamo-no-Mae!
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey there,
haven't you ever wanted to change the past?
The past?
I don't remember anything like this happening!
Then maybe...
My mom wouldn't have been caught so easily...
I've been waiting for this moment!
I possessed you here as a child,
and hid myself for a mere ten years!
All while waiting for you to wish to change the past!
What do you mean?
I programmed myself to awaken if you wished to change the past!
I'd latch on to the Supreme God's Power and force the past to Transform to my benefit!
Transform the past?
Yes, Transform history!
That is my ability!
But I'd need an extraordinary amount of power.
It's impossible without absorbing the Supreme God's Power!
Transforming history...
Changing the past is taboo!
You can't do it!
But this is your desire.
Tsukuyomi Sasami,
you bear regrets!
To regret is to mourn a failure in the past.
And the regret of the Supreme God can distort space and time, making it easy to tamper with the past!
No...
True, I have regrets...
I betrayed my mother.
I broke our promise,
and I made it so she couldn't even rest in peace.
Originally, this Killing Stone never appeared in this time or place.
Do you know what that means?
The Transformation has already begun!
The moment of your regret will be your end!
No...
And I'll kill Tsukuyomi Juju here and now!
Once I do, her daughter will inherit the Supreme God's Power!
And that daughter, Tsukuyomi Sasami, will be in the palm of my hand!
And that is my goal!
To cripple my mortal enemies, the Tsukuyomi Shrine,
and make the Supreme God's Power my own!
The corrupt occult society Arahabaki shall continue to grow!
And Madam will be saved as well.
Madam?
And Arahabaki shall rule this world,
this planet,
and everything else in it!
You're a fool.
Controlling a single country...
drained my mother to death!
And just living on with my puny body is all I can handle!
And you want the world?
What a joke!
You're pathetic!
You're only talking so big because you're resorting to something as underhanded as changing the past!
You can't do anything!
You think you can rule the world?!
Is your speech over?
Now, feel free to die, Tsukuyomi Juju!
It's curtains for the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
And the stage is set for Arahabaki!
Huh?
I remember this!
It's the day Mom died.
That's enough now.
Tsurugi!
What's happening here?
I came to the past,
got put in someone else's body,
and then history changed!
This is no time to tarry about.
M-Mom?
Yes, that is I.
Your mother who couldn't bear to witness your foolishness,
and so returned from the underworld.
Finally caught up to ya.
Huh? Caught up?
Remember when she force-fed that medicine to you?
She was sharp enough to hide a divine idol within you.
That gave her a lifeline to get out of the underworld.
There's one of those inside me?
Is that why I got so fat?
I had only intended it to be a blister in size,
but it seems I tuned it improperly.
If the Supreme God's Power can't fix it, it's kind of a problem!
Let's put aside our little spat for now.
We gotta join forces and stop Tamamo-no-mae's schemes!
I cannot abide world domination.
Altering the past is deplorable enough.
Now's a good time for a parent-teacher conference.
Tamamo-no-mae used your regret to trigger your powers.
So all we gotta do to stop her is erase your regrets.
But how?
Leap through time, and find a hint from the past!
We can do that?
We're already in a different time, aren't we?
Looks like she wasn't counting on your mom's spirit coming back.
So her ability malfunctioned,
meaning we've got a chance to turn the tables.
So let's go back a bit.
And I'm out!
What?
Have I lost yet again?
Now strip, Tsukuyomi!
But I don't have anything under this!
Could you not remove your bag?
I absolutely can't relinquish it!
But to remove my last strip of underwear...
I know, Paparin!
If you give up your bag,
but put your undies over your face instead,
it'll be super peachy!
Why didn't I think of that?
You're a genius, Tama!
Yay, I'm a genius!
How does that solve anything?
Where are we?
Whoops, got the time wrong.
Your life seems to be quite happy.
Yeah, it's always a lot of fun!
Sasami,
I think she was being sarcastic.
Oh, really?
Next up!
And this is... when?
This is...
just after Brother and I escaped from the shrine.
I was feeling crushed by the guilt of running away...
How long were you there?!
Your brother is always by your side!
Please gaze upon me, and feel as though there are thirty people with you!
Shut it, you roach!
Get out!
Brother was a pervert,
so I never had the time to get sad.
He saved me.
Look, Mommy!
What is this?
A Mother's Day present!
I hear there's a day for that!
Do not draw, Sasami.
Creative activity is wicked.
Humans imbue desires into their creations.
And the desires of one who bears the Supreme God's power can change the world.
If you have enough time to play, then train!
You good-for-nothing!
I...
was really sad back then.
It could not be helped.
That too was part of your training to become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Hey!
Mommy
I knew you liked it!
I was training my ability to suppress my emotions.
It is true that creation is dangerous,
and it is a mother's duty to scold her child!
Mom...
Mom... looks so happy.
All people find joy in giving life.
So, you wished for my birth...
Of course.
Ooh, lookie!
That looks pretty neat!
Wait!
What does the next Tsukuyomi priestess want with scum like me?
"Take your training seriously!"
"Never go to the city!"
I'm sick of hearing you preach, sister!
Ruza...
I...
like you!
Huh?
Die!
I never knew Mom got so into it!
Do not look!
Stop it!
Avert your eyes from the mistakes of my youth!
After destruction comes creation.
We are chased to the brink of death,
and we gaze into the abyss of destruction.
That is what gives us strength.
I was so earnest back then.
That's some crazy training.
You humans are really something.
This is also a duty of a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Mom...
I will ask once more, Sasami.
I won't go back no matter how many times you ask.
You are the current Tsukuyomi priestess.
That duty has been passed down to you whether you accept it or abandon it, so do the right thing.
Today, the boundaries between worlds have been replaced with chaos,
so we cannot entrust the future of this country to the whims of our flighty gods.
Moreover, it must be humans that protect and control.
But still...
our gods are perfect for that role.
They're weak, helpless, and prone to failure,
but all the same, they overcome it and grow up.
So, aren't they getting stronger?
Staying under the covers in your room is no way to live.
You've got to go to school, in public, and even if you're hurt,
you'll get stronger, and you'll grow up!
So let's put some faith in our gods!
Let's send them into the real world!
We're just fill-ins who were lent our power from the Supreme God.
It's not ours to begin with.
It's rude to want to protect it.
Saying we need to for the sake of the world and its people...
just isn't true.
Our days as guardians are over.
I'll believe in the gods.
That's why...
I won't try anymore!
We don't have to try anymore.
I'm still a child, so I've always been told what to do.
That's why I'll lend you the Supreme God's power.
And I'll grow up while you have it.
I'll grow strong enough to bear the Supreme God's power.
So that is how you think.
Because I died early,
you were forced to be a priestess long before you were ready.
So you behaved like a child.
You never tried because you never had determination,
and I despised you for it.
But...
you contemplated, struggled, and came to your own conclusion.
It is one that nobody in the history of our shrine came to.
I have remembered our true duty.
You have made your mother proud.
You resisted me out of the strength of your conviction.
I will call you a traitor no more.
It seems that I was the wrong, foolish one.
You weren't wrong or nothin'.
You two just tried too hard.
You spent all this time passing down that pain in the ass duty...
so, good job.
Now take a rest.
Is this... Ninigi's descent?
What will you choose?
This is when I tired of my powers, left them for others, and started this whole mess.
You can start over from here if you'd like.
I got enough rest.
You all let me get much more than I needed.
And in exchange,
I let humanity ruin itself.
I should never have done that.
The sun can't just give up and stop shining.
It's out of the question.
I do not know whether the history humanity built was for better or for worse.
Many of you suffered and died.
This country, too, is as turbulent as a storm.
All because I was lazy.
That is my regret.
Answer me honestly.
Was I wrong?
Did I fail?
I thought about it so much,
but I can't say for certain.
Should I have tried a bit harder?
You worked hard for a long time.
And you came back after a short rest.
You pass the torch when you're tired.
I think that's the best way to do it.
You weren't wrong.
Let's not regret our pasts, God.
We'll work hard until the sun rises.
We'll be under moonlight, though.
You're right.
Now, feel free to die, Tsukuyomi Juju!
It's curtains for the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
And the stage is set for Arahabaki!
Unfortunately,
I have a promise that I must keep.
I will not allow myself to be killed!
What are—
You activated your abilities using our desires to change the past as a trigger.
But I bear regret no more!
No!
How did you hide your spirit within Tsukuyomi Sasami?!
A novice like her should be completely incapable of it!
How could such a powerful spirit—
Sorry kid, but I just used you to fix some family bonds!
Tsurugi?
You don't find people who can go back in time every day, so I made the most of it.
Prepare yourself!
I was manipulated?
I, the fair skinned, golden haired fox that brought about chaos and revolution the world over?!
I can finally accomplish the true goal of the duty we accepted long ago!
I'll tear you limb from limb!
I'll pulverize you and feast on your flesh!
I will protect them until the sunrise.
The Three Treasures entrusted to me...
they are our pride!
There ya go.
I'll leave the rest to you.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Sasami.
Want me to help?
Oh, no.
Sasami, you go inside and warm yourself up.
Don't worry, let me help a little.
Then I'll go get another shovel,
and we'll shovel snow together, and then the neighbors will be all,
"Oh my, you siblings get along well."
"Siblings? No, we're newlyweds!"
Speak a language I can understand!
Good afternoon,
Tsukuyomi Sasami.
H-Hello...
um...
have we met somewhere?
Tsukuyomi            Kamiomi
Sasami
Well, you're a celebrity.
You show up out of the blue after months of absence,
and you're the teacher's sister to boot.
Of course I'm curious.
Everyone's dying to know more about you.
I'm Konohanasakuya Academy's student council president.
Talk to me if you have any problems.
Let's be friends.
Uh, sure.
Oh, good for you, Sasami.
You've made another friend.
If I may so request,
please get along with her.
However...
if you're planning to use Sasami for some nefarious plot,
and she ends up hurt,
I'll have no mercy, friend or no.
Oh, are you an Emishi?
Perhaps a Tsuchigumo?
No, maybe a Kumaso?
I'm far different from what you imagine.
I see. This gets more interesting by the minute.
You two are rather fun.
U-Um!
What's your name?
Jou.
Edogawa Jou.
Strange name, isn't it?
See you soon, Sasami.
Somebody looked spooked.
It's not often you take matters into your own hands.
Did you not hear?
I'm dying to know about her.
I'd prefer you to keep that curiosity in check.
That girl...
has lost the Supreme God's power.
No way!
I could feel the strength of her divinity all the way from here!
It's like looking at the ruins of the Sun Goddess.
She only has the divinity left of the skin she shed.
I was hoping to suck up the Supreme God's power,
but this calls for a change in plans.
But I think we'll have some fun soon...
Her second year...
no, spring will be exciting.
You are our master.
Should you wish for, say, destruction,
we'd gladly follow your orders.
Yes, I'm counting on it.
Everything is for my happiness.
Rather,
everything is for my own gain.
With the combined powers of the corrupt occult society Arahabaki,
we'll take those shameless, cocksure gods of the country and the world
and spit right in their faces.
As you wish,
Madam.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
What, is this an ending?
So there was an alternate world built in a place like this...
This pocket universe is outside the Supreme God's jurisdiction!
We, the corrupt occult society Arahabaki, shall fortify our residence here
and take the first step to complete world domination!
Madam, if you get this worked up so soon, you'll drive the viewers away.
Oh, come on.
This is how you're supposed to start off.
Though I suppose there's no tact in invading without a declaration of war...
Let us do the honorable thing and follow this world's rules.
But how should we?
Anything goes!
I, Edogawa Jou, shall flail about!
It seems we're supposed to sing into this mic.
How does that work?
No matter.
The power of Arahabaki filled polytheism with the contradiction of monotheism!
To its inheritor, almost nothing is impossible!
I can HEEEEEEAR your vooooooice
Woo hoo hoo!
Yeah!
eeeeeverywheeeeeere like a resounding symfoNYYYYY
You can do it, Madam!
The light shiiiiines the COLOOOR OF LOOOOOVE
Whoo!
Great!
Let's hold hands foreveeer
I want to feeeeeel the ozmosis groooooow
So good!
What was that?
Excellent work, Madam!
It seems it's getting to be that time, so let's return home and warm ourselves up!
I feel like I was used.
Next Episode
It's time for Pooped Pro Wrestling.
Pooped@Pro Wrestling
Tsukuyomi Sasami here, live from the ring.
In the red corner, Great Giveacrap.
In the blue corner, Lazy the Kid.
In the black corner, Apathetic Animal.
Yellow's got The Sunny Slacker.
Pink's got Triple Zs.
When these five get in the ring...
Next time, on Episode 10.
Next Time, on Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy.