Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
I'll dispense you with the face of mask
kamen no kao de tebanasu no da
We meet only to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume nomama tabitatou
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru utakanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
Those who have defeated two teams here will cross these bridges next.
The first teams to make it across will be permitted inside the third wall.
Chaika.
Yes.
Begin!
The Bells of Contention
Chaika!
N-No worry!
No fear!
Grab on!
Come on!
Sheesh... I was afraid the bridges would collapse under your weight, Nikolai.
Don't say that.
But what is this? They're mocking us.
Someone out there is getting a kick out of this.
I'll make Hartgen pay for this when I get my hands on him.
Stop!
What?
You two have violated the rules.
Your right to participate will be revoked.
Violated the rules?!
Rules in a killing match?
It's not a free-for-all?
Enough jokes! You two have lied about your identities!
We know you're with the Kliemann Organization.
Keep walking that way.
They're not going to just let us leave?
What are they making us do?
I don't know, but it doesn't matter.
It got us into the castle.
Does this really go all the way to the top of the castle?
Yes. According to Chaika's magic probe,
it's likely the remains are on the highest level.
Come forth, strained atmosphere!
The Tense Air!
Victory!
Come this way.
What is this?
You two have violated the rules.
Huh?!
We know that you and your companions were snooping in the castle last night.
Toru...
Go. Your battlefield lies ahead.
In here, what sort of arena?
I don't know...
But our only option is to go forward.
Yes.
Toru...
What?
Niva's true identity, Father's fortune.
But Father's goal, do what?
Accomplish what?
If he left behind a Gundo that powerful,
Emperor Gaz may have wanted
to bring war to this world, even after his death.
Maybe he thought the Gundo just needed to get to someone who wanted to start a war, like Hartgen.
If that's the case, then his goal has been realized.
Want war... Toru same?
Huh?
War is fine with me!
Why don't we let her bring back the age of war?
I...
Chaika, how do you feel?
What if that is what the emperor wants?
Not want war.
I see. That's what you think?
Yes.
I'll keep your words in mind.
Come forth, silence which speaks not.
The Silencer!
Come forth, crusher of air!
Most of the guards are currently acting as security for the tournament.
Now's our chance.
You're from the Kliemann Organization!
I am a retainer to King Hartgen...
Or, I used to be.
What is King Hartgen trying to do?
You may think I'm talking nonsense,
but the king wants to become the second Emperor Gaz.
It was as if the king was possessed by Gaz after he killed him.
He investigated, in depth, how Gaz was trying to seize the continent,
and what sort of army he was trying to raise.
Eventually, it led him to gather soldiers for this martial arts tournament.
King Hartgen intends to start a war.
The king changed completely after the war ended.
And when that person arrived at the castle, it only spurred him on.
What person?
Chaika.
Your Majesty!
Welcome back!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Your Majesty?
"There is no value in peace.
Song and verse offer no comfort.
My soul is only satisfied by the roar of the battlefield and the smell of blood", he said.
It was then that Chaika appeared before him.
If you give me the remains of the emperor,
I will bring change to your days of monotony.
Gather strong men to this castle.
They will be the face of your power.
That girl proposed that he hold a martial arts tournament
with Emperor Gaz's remains offered to the winner.
At first, no one believed the king would listen to her.
But, against our expectations, he began to do just as Chaika said.
Every retainer who objected to his will has ended up as I have.
He got rid of them?
Uh-huh.
Some were even killed.
I cannot remain in the castle any longer.
Please stop the king.
So the black Chaika was pulling the strings behind the scenes.
I'll stay in the castle.
Would you two go back to our meeting point for now?
I want to find out where Vivi and Captain Nikolai are, too.
Right.
Chaika.
The plan is going perfectly.
Soon, all the remains will be together.
I'm glad, Father.
It's all thanks to you, Chaika.
You gave me a reason to live again.
They don't have a clue. Poor things.
I smell corpses.
What is this?
Why are there so many...?
Chaikas?
They want to fight?
Fredrica, count to three and shut the door!
Got it!
One...
Two...
Three!
Whoops! Did I get her?
They're puppets.
Oh, good. That wasn't yours.
Let's hurry.
Uh-huh.
We've been waiting for you.
Shock! Chaikas...?
Three of them?
So, we finally meet.
I can't forgive people who do bad things.
Yes, this is where you will atone.
What are they going to make us do?
Nikolai...
Uh-huh...
Gillette-sama?
Captain...
Is that you, Captain?
Are you ready?
Chief Konrad.
Prime Minister Berman and Minister Moscaetz of the Alliance of the Six Nations
have independently dispatched the floating fortress Cima to the Principality of Hartgen.
That one is only half Chaika.
And she won't even acknowledge that she is Chaika.
She didn't even attempt to gather the remains.
What a bore.
Gillette-sama...
Is this really the captain?!
It is Gillette-sama!
Why are you fighting us?!
Because that is my job!
Vivi, fight him for real!
Otherwise, we'll be killed!
Have you forgotten?! We're your subordinates!
What are you talking about?!
You really don't remember us?!
Do you know how worried we all were?!
Vivi! This isn't him!
Stop, Captain!
I don't... I don't know you!
That's not true! You're Gillette-sama!
Try to remember, Gillette-sama!
Gillette-sama...
Vivi?
Yes.
Gillette-sama!
Captain!
How boring.
What a farce.
To say I misjudged him is an understatement.
And he was supposed to make her atone for her sins.
We have to stop the bleeding!
Gillette-sama... I'm sorry.
No. I should be the one to apologize.
We'll talk later.
We have to get out of here, Vivi!
Yes!
Brother Shin...
So you're here, Akari.
Did you come to find the remains?
Too bad. They're no longer here.
You think I'll believe what you say?
Fredrica!
We've sealed the dragoon's power.
What now?
Which do you two think will win?
I think it'll be the red one.
Then I'll say the white one.
Always wait for this chance.
Will take all remains now!
Can't!
No!
Proposal. Gather remains, then father's funeral, together.
Refuse. Absolutely refuse your proposal!
Objective, different!
Objective, different?
Explain objective!
Revenge.
Uh-huh?
No matter! No need explain!
Will take all remains! That is all!
Chaika, we have to take her on. Be ready.
Right.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear. Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy thee.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
The Burster!
Sorry.
No need concern!
Come forth, strained atmosphere!
The Tense Air!
Will defeat!
David!
Come forth, to strike and crush!
Damn...
The Slugger!
Ow...
Declare loss.
Hey, come on!
We can keep going! Don't give up!
Fine.
I also have
something to protect.
Don't...
I quit.
I lose.
Hey!
Dear Sister, what shall we do with the red one?
Just leave her.
Yes. She's no longer needed.
What are they gonna make us do next?
Chaika, have your Gundo ready.
Right.
How's it going here?
Just as I expected.
So the one who gathered the most remains won, then?
Shin!
Yes.
Toru!
Isn't this the one I gave you a long time ago?
You're still using it?
You never change, Toru.
You're still not cut out to be a saboteur.
Because you're so quick to act on your emotions!
Toru!
Hand over all of the remains that you have.
Do that and we'll give her back.
Toru,
you've lost.
Just as we planned, right, Father?
Yes, that's right, my most beloved daughter.
Akari...
Toru!
The sky is overcast
The bell rings to signal the beginning
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
noroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
The time has come to break a curse
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
kono inochi kono ai mo
This life and this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
The white Chaika and the red Chaika
have worked so hard to gather the remains.
And they had no idea it was all for me. Poor things.
Next time: "The Throne That Invites War".
The Throne That Invites War