MISSION 75
"IT'S JUST WHITE DAY."
[whimsical music playing]
[Hitohito moaning]
[Hitohito sighing]
[Hitohito] Hmm?
[Komi] It's friendship chocolate.
[narrator] Tadano is thinking about
what happened that Valentine's Day.
He thinks about it 100 times a day.
[Hitohito gasping]
MARCH 8
[Hitohito] It's already March.
I've gotta think about
what to give Komi for White Day.
Huh.
"Happy Valentine's, Tadano."
Hmm.
SNIFF
[Hitohito gasping]
It's not what you think!
What are you saying?
[door sliding closed]
[Hitomi] Hmm?
[Hitohito] All right, then.
What should I get for her in return?
I hear that people often give candy
or marshmallows.
Hmm.
Whoa! Each of those things
has a different meaning.
Candy means you like them,
marshmallows mean you hate them,
and cookies means you're friends.
Hmm.
[narrator] He's even more worried now.
[Hitohito inhaling]
[Hitohito]
Maybe I should try asking Hitomi.
Nah.
Yeah, but...
Nah... Yeah--
You're ruining my concentration!
Um, actually,
I'm having a hard time deciding
what to get a friend for White Day.
This is about White Day?
Are you talking about those chocolates
you got from your guy friend?
Yes! That's right!
Yes, that's it!
What's gotten into you?
Well, if you wanna give him something
for the chocolates he gave you,
how about giving him some food?
Chocolate would be good too.
Huh.
I wanted to get something more,
I'm just not sure what I should get him.
Do you like him?
[Hitohito] N-no!
[Hitomi gasping] Judging from his reaction
and the fact that the shadow back there
was about 165 centimeters tall
and had a silhouette with long hair,
and the fact that those footsteps I heard
had a short stride...
Hitohito?
So did you get some?
[Hitohito] What...
what are you talking about?
You've left me no choice.
I'll help you decide what to get.
[Hitohito gasping]
[both sighing]
NO CUSHION FOR ME...
So first, was that chocolate
"friendship chocolate"
or "true-love chocolate"?
Just friendship chocolate,
at least I think.
Wait. You think?
[Hitohito] Well, that's what they said.
Huh. Maybe they just said that
to avoid feeling embarrassed.
Maybe. I guess so.
[gasping] No, no, no, no, no, no!
I don't even think that's possible!
[Hitomi] Hmm.
If those were true-love chocolates,
they'd probably like it if you gave them
something they could keep for a long time.
- [Hitohito] I see.
- Do you like this guy?
[Hitohito] Huh?
I said it's not like that!
Pick one. You like them or hate them.
Which is it?
[gasping] In that case, I... Well...
We're talking about Katai, right?
I guess I like him, more or less. Why?
- [seething] That's not what I mean!
- What are you trying to get at?
[Hitohito gasping]
Picture them, brother.
Picture that person in your mind.
Hitohito, do you like or not?
[Hitohito] Uh...
Uh...
[Hitohito shuddering]
I guess I'm interested in them.
- [Hitomi] Huh?
- [Hitohito] What are you upset about?
[Hitomi] I understand the situation now.
[Hitohito] Huh?
Let's go to the department store!
[Hitohito gasping] Great idea!
[opening theme music playing]
[Hitomi] I just watched a news show
about which sweets look best
on social media.
Great idea!
But, you know, Hitohito,
as long as it's from someone you like,
it doesn't matter what it is.
Don't you think? [chuckling]
[Hitohito] Great idea!
[narrator] All his mom knows
is that Tadano got chocolates from a guy.
Friday the 13th. White Day is on Saturday.
In other words,
White Day falls on a weekend.
All the guys who receive chocolates
are nervous today.
Conversely, the girls are relieved.
Their work is done.
Meanwhile,
the guys who didn't get any chocolate
are in the process of getting enlightened.
Komi!
I got this for you for White Day--
[squealing] Komi!
I got this for you for White Day!
You can lick me wherever you want, okay?
[Yamai giggling menacingly]
Huh? [gasping]
Oh. Thanks, Katai!
[Ayami chuckling menacingly]
[narrator] The strain of anxiety.
[Makoto] N-Next I've got
to give my gift to my mentor!
- [Komi gasping]
- [Makoto chuckling menacingly]
[Komi shuddering]
[Komi grunting]
[Makoto]
The only thing I have on my mentor
is the fact
that I have more muscle than her.
[Komi shuddering]
[Makoto] I... I hope she likes it!
[narrator] And speaking of Tadano...
Oh, by the way,
would you like
to go out to eat after school?
It'll be my treat.
[Komi gasping]
Huh, Katai?
[narrator] Tadano chickened out.
Since Tadano was too nervous
to give his present to Komi,
he started to have thoughts like,
"Today is bad luck."
So, in the end,
he didn't give her the gift.
- [Komi gasping]
- [Makoto gasping]
[Makoto] A date?
You're talking about a date, right?
[narrator]
Friday the 13th went by without incident.
[narrator] Since Tadano chickened out
and failed to give his gift to Komi,
he was left with only one choice.
And that was to go
to Komi's house on White Day
and deliver his gift to her there.
[intense music playing]
You should go before it gets too late.
[Hitohito] Okay.
I'm going now.
[Hitohito shuddering]
[dramatic music playing]
[Hitohito] I didn't think
I'd be so nervous.
I came all the way to her house.
I... I hope she doesn't get the wrong idea.
All I'm gonna do is give it to her
really quick at the front door.
It's gonna be fine.
Or maybe it's not gonna be fine!
[Aoyama] He looks suspicious.
[Hitohito] But, I bet
she was even more nervous than I am now.
KOMI
[Hitohito sighing, grunting]
[Hitohito breathing deeply]
[doorbell ringing]
[Hitohito gasping]
I rang the bell. I want to run away!
- [Shosuke] Yes?
- [Hitohito gasping] There... there it is!
Uh, um...
Komi, uh... Is... is Shoko at home right now?
I, uh... I'm her friend from school.
Oh and, uh, my name is Tadano.
[Hitohito shuddering]
- [Hitohito] He hung up!
- [door opening]
[Hitohito gasping]
W-what is it, Tadano?
[Hitohito] Hello. Is Shoko at home?
[narrator] Tadano gave a serious reply.
Shoko's out running an errand right now.
I'm so sorry
that she's not here to see you.
[Hitohito] Huh? Oh, then I'll come back--
- Come on in. You can wait inside.
- [Hitohito gasping]
- [Hitohito] Uh... Well, uh...
[Hitohito shuddering]
I'll bring you some hot tea.
Make yourself at home.
Oh, thank you. Don't worry about me.
[Hitohito grunting]
[Hitohito] Mmm.
What am I supposed to do?
Excuse me...
It's her dad?
[intense music playing]
[Hitohito] Oh, thank you so much.
- [Masayoshi] Hmm.
- [Hitohito] He's sitting down?
So I have, uh...
[Hitohito chuckling nervously]
[Hitohito] What was that?
He's gonna drink tea here?
[Masayoshi] Hmm.
[narrator] Tadano couldn't take it
and started to talk.
[Hitohito] My name is Hitohito Tadano.
I'm in class with Sho--
That is, I meant to say your daughter.
I study hard every day.
And... and your daughter gave me some
friendship chocolates for Valentine's Day.
[Hitohito gasping] So I've come here today
to give her something in return?
[Hitohito shuddering]
[Komi gasping, shrieking]
[Komi screaming, straining]
PUSH
[narrator] Tadano is in a panic.
[Komi exhaling]
[narrator] She left her closet door
half open, she didn't make her bed.
- It's, uh...
- [Komi panicking, gasping]
It's not that messy.
[Komi panting, shrieking]
[Komi panting]
WHEW
[narrator] Komi is catching her breath.
Tadano is concerned.
Komi is calming down.
Tadano fixes his posture.
But she can't stay calm.
Tadano drinks the same tea
that Komi's father drank.
Tadano is having a hard time
starting the conversation.
Komi clearly remembers
that today is White Day.
[Hitohito shuddering]
- [Hitohito] Uh, I forgot.
- [Komi gasping]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Thank you for your Valentine's Day gift.
Here's something for you
in return for the chocolates.
[Komi gasping]
[emotional music playing]
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] Go ahead. You can open it.
It's hand cream.
[Komi gasping]
[Hitohito] I know
it's not the right season for it,
but I thought it just smelled so good
I had to get it for you.
[Komi grunting]
Anyway, I'm just glad that you like it.
Uh, well,
that's, uh, a piece of, uh, candy.
[Komi gasping]
[both grunting]
So, um, sorry.
I'm gonna go home now.
I don't wanna bother you
any longer, you know?
Especially since it's a weekend!
[Hitohito chuckling nervously]
[Komi grunting]
[Komi sniffing]
[Komi sighing]
[narrator] It smelled good.
- [Maeda] Sato, can you hold this for me?
- Yeah, sure!
[Hitohito sighing]
Komi?
Is it okay to use this towel
to wipe off the desks?
Huh?
[indistinct chatter]
Uh, Komi?
Die!
ROLL
Let's play Eraser Drop!
[Hitohito] Huh? Why?
[narrator] Eraser Drop.
An eraser is a physical object
created by humans
who leveraged
their entire body of knowledge
built over the history of humankind...
You flick your eraser, and if your
opponent's eraser drops to the floor,
you win.
[Makeru] It's my turn to take the stage.
[narrator] They're using Tadano's desk
as the battlefield.
- And set!
- [announcer] Round one.
Fight!
BEAM
Victory goes to who makes the first move!
Whoa! She's squishing down on the eraser,
which makes the eraser stick to the desk!
The "Barricade" move!
[Chushaku] If you do this,
other players will badmouth you.
[music stops]
[Makeru grunting]
[Najimi] You can go next, Komi.
PLINK
[Najimi] Stalling!
She didn't move her eraser so
her opponents would make a mistake first?
Great move!
A perfect fit for your eraser unit!
[narrator] Actually,
her hand just slipped.
Well, it's my turn now.
- [Najimi roaring]
- [intense music playing]
[music fades]
[narrator] Out of bounds.
Najimi disqualified.
[Makeru] Now, it's my turn.
- [Makeru roaring]
- [intense music playing]
Her eraser's barricaded!
She flicked it too hard!
[narrator] Out of bounds.
Makeru Yadano disqualified.
[music stops]
Tadano, it's your turn.
[Hitohito groaning]
FANTASTIC ERASER MOON
[Hitohito sighing]
- ZAFU II
- KOMI'S ERASER
- [Tadano roaring]
- [intense music playing]
[Komi gasping]
[music stops]
[narrator] Hitohito Tadano
has been disqualified.
As a result, Komi wins.
All right! Next game!
[Nakanaka] The time has come.
I know you want to see my awesome skills!
[announcer] New challenger, Nakanaka!
- [Yamai] Don't worry about a thing, Komi!
- [Nakanaka] You!
[announcer] New challenger, Yamai.
I'll defend your eraser to the death.
Even if I have to sacrifice my own life!
Ha! That's redundant.
Like saying my headache hurts.
- Huh?
- Ah?
Najimi, the phoenix, that's me!
[announcer] Round two.
Fight!
[all roaring]
Oh look.
Hey, what's going on?
They're playing Eraser Drop!
I wanna play too!
Huh? They're not playing the game right.
I thought players
are supposed to take turns?
- [boy] I wanna play too!
- I wanna play!
The three of us reserve the third battle.
[all exclaiming]
[Hitohito] Why does everyone wanna play
Eraser Drop so bad?
[announcer] Witness this fierce battle
that turns
all other Eraser Drop battles into dust!
They've taken the concept
of taking turns and...
[Hitohito] And that's good?
All right!
Round two, battle three,
will take place on this desk over here!
- The come-back match is over here!
- [Hitohito] A tournament?
[Makoto] I ended up joining a game somehow
without knowing how to play!
What am I gonna do?
I've never played Eraser Drop before!
Why are there so many people here?
[Makoto grunting]
[Naruse grunting]
I'll show you
what a real eraser battle looks like.
[Makoto snarling, roaring]
[intense music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[Naruse groaning]
[Chushaku] It's okay.
Hey! Look at that desk over there!
[Nakanaka groaning]
Nakanaka is starting to get worn out!
She overexerted her finger!
[Mono] She has a weak constitution!
Huh? Huh?
[Najimi cackling]
[Taisei] They powered up their finger!
That's cheating! That's cheating, Najimi!
Winning is all that matters! Let's go!
[Najimi screaming]
Now's her chance!
[all] It's Komi's turn!
FLICK
[dramatic music playing]
[all] She did it! Woo-hoo!
WOOO!
[crowd cheering]
[Hitohito grunting]
- Does this look right?
- You can do it!
- [boy] Wow!
- Yes.
[Yuji] I knew it.
Hey! Is it finally my turn to battle now?
[Ushiroda] Uh, hey! You can't do that!
This is so tough.
[Makeru seething]
Yeah!
[Toshio roaring]
Yay! On to round three!
[Onemine chuckling] Okay. That was fun.
I'm coming back!
- [boy] I'm playing next!
- [girl] No, I am!
[girl 2] I am!
[Hitohito chuckling]
Komi, so about round two. Uh...
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] Huh?
Komi?
[Komi gasping]
Hey, uh, are you okay?
Gosh, are you feeling sick?
"Sorry. I'm okay. I'm fine."
I see.
[rain pattering]
All right, Tadano.
I'm double-booked. Gotta go. Bye!
Uh, hey, you!
Comrade, we shall meet
on the battlefield another day.
Well, I... I thank you so much
for all the fun I had today.
- Bye-bye Komi!
- Komi, give me a goodbye kiss!
WHACK
- See you later! Sleep well, Ren.
- [Agari laughing]
Uh...
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] I see it started raining.
Do you have an umbrella?
"I have a folding umbrella."
Oh, good.
I brought mine too.
[Komi] I'm sad.
[Komi sighing]
[Komi] The c-closing ceremony
celebrating the end of school
is only a few days away.
We'll be put in new classes next week.
I just feel sad that our time together
might be coming to an end.
I know how you feel.
[dramatic music playing]
[inaudible]
[Hitohito] This year, it went by so fast.
[Hitohito] First,
we made friends with Najimi
who says crazy things sometimes,
but I also feel Najimi was the reason
we were all able to become friends.
They took the lead.
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] After that
we made friends with Agari.
Going out to eat
with her was an adventure.
I hope we can go out to eat
with Agari again someday.
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] Yamai and Nakanaka
always act like they're fighting,
but I think
they actually get along pretty well.
[Komi grunting emphatically]
Onemine and Otori are so stable.
Being around them
just somehow puts you at ease.
I feel like both of them
are really dependable people.
[Komi grunting]
I'm glad you made friends
with Kato and Sasaki on our school trip.
They seem nice.
[Komi grunting]
Somehow that trip made me happy too.
It's too bad we only got to help Sato
clean our classroom before school
just this last month.
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] I feel bad that she was
doing that all alone the whole year.
[Komi grunting]
I also wanna try going out
with Maeda and Ushiroda someday.
[Komi grunting]
There was the school athletic festival,
a cultural festival.
We went shopping, to the water park.
We had that great Christmas party
and snowball fight!
And went to a shrine on New Year's
to get our fortunes.
[Komi grunting]
[rain intensifying]
[Hitohito] The rain isn't stopping.
[Komi grunting]
[Hitohito] But it's going to stop someday.
Uh, I was going
to use the rain stopping as symbolism
and try to come up
with something witty to say,
but it was too hard.
[Komi gasping]
We've got a problem.
[Komi grunting]
[both sighing]
You forgot your eraser unit!
- Huh? What? You two haven't gone home yet?
- [both shuddering]
[Najimi] Let's go home together!
You can share your umbrella.
Huh? Weren't you going somewhere?
- [Najimi] Hmm?
- [Hitohito] You wanted to leave early.
[ending theme music playing]
Hey. How about we invite everyone out
after the closing ceremony?
Great idea!
Hey, Komi! You can invite everyone for us!
[Komi gasping]
Oh, boy.
You don't have to force yourself.
[Komi shuddering]
[inaudible]
NOD
NUMBER 6
FEBRUARY TO MARCH
NUMBER 7 APRIL
SECOND YEAR STUDENTS
KOMI
[music fades]
Hello there, Komi. Good morning!
[Komi gasping]
GOOD MORNING
Huh?
[indistinct chatter]
[birds chirping]
[Komi inhaling deeply]
I...
I am looking forward to...
to the upcoming n-n-new school year...
[Komi breathing heavily]
with you.
[narrator] When a person
has extreme social anxiety,
they struggle to communicate with others.