Meet Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
Her debut single as Full Moon, "Myself"
has just been released.
She was going to gather gossip
from her classmates and
see how they felt about the song,
but no one was talking about it!
She was really disappointed.
But thanks to my help
she's been able to become friends
with her classmates,
and her single's become
the talk of the class.
She was really happy
about that!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Mitsuki, who's coming
from your house?
My grandmother was
supposed to come,
but she caught a cold and
she's been in bed since this morning.
So nobody's going to come.
Oh, really.
Who?
What?
That can't be.
It's...Oji?!
What?
Don't you remember?
"Route L"?
Oji!
Who is that?
He's really handsome!
Dr. Wakaoji...
Dr. Wakaoji really stands out
when you see him in a place like this.
Couldn't stand out more.
Boy, it stinks of make-up in here.
Mitsuki.
Doctor...
What are you doing here?
Today, when I made a house call
at your grandmother's,
I heard that it's your class
visitation day.
She let me come in her place.
Thank you.
Who's that?
Your father, Mitsuki?
How could you not tell us that
your father was so good looking?
No...that's not it.
No?
Dr. Wakaoji is my father's friend.
Oh, I see.
I guess me playing the role of
your father maybe annoying to you...
No way!
Don't be silly.
I think you're standing out
a little too much though.
Huh?
He looked this way!
Oji!
ALWAYS BE CHEERFUL,
AND GIVE A SPIRITED GREETING.
Dr. Wakaoji, I heard stories but,
you're really popular, aren't you?
Oh no, that's an old story.
I was kind of proud today.
Next up is the song we're
highlighting this month.
It's looking to become
a runaway hit!
It's "Myself" by Full Moon.
Why do I like you so much?
My tears are falling...
She said it's a big hit!
See? Just like I said.
Huh? Shhh!
Yes! This is Wakaoji.
Ah, what? Just when Mitsuki's song
was playing.
He got a phone call.
It can't be helped.
Yes...yes...
Yes, the academic conference
at the Tauji Hotel tomorrow.
Mitsuki, play the CD.
Okay.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Doctor?
Do you want to listen to music?
See, this.
Oh, sorry, this car doesn't
have a CD player.
Well... take this home!
And please listen to it at your house.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Sorry...
I...uh...don't listen to things
like this much.
I'm an old man now, you know.
Don't say that, listen to it and see.
I think it's a good song.
Really...
Mitsuki, so you like that
song that much?
Y-Yeah.
If I were to become a singer,
this is the kind of song
I'd like to be able to sing.
That's why I want you to hear it,
to see what you think.
I see Mitsuki, you want to be a singer.
That's right, you've always said that.
Yes.
By the way,
about your class visitation today.
I've never done that before
and I was really nervous.
Humph!
Uh...
Mitsuki? What's wrong?
Nothing.
I wonder what happened.
Stupid.
Thank you for taking the trouble
to come to school today.
Mitsuki!
Sorry, did I say something bad?
No...nothing.
Ah...okay...
Hey, if there's something you want
to say to me, won't you say it?
There's nothing.
Ah...okay...
That's right, he's cold.
No reason to talk to him!
Doctor, you're good looking,
tall and intelligent, and...
perfect. I have no complaints.
Mitsuki...
An old man like me can't understand
the feelings of a young girl!
Grandmother, I brought you
some porridge.
Oh, thank you.
You must be hungry, Gran-
That's...the radio in Ms. Tanaka's room!
Mitsuki...
Y-Yes?
It's noisy. Please go and turn it off.
Y-Yes.
Whew, I got nervous...
Ms. Tanaka?
Mitsuki?
Your earphone's unplugged.
Huh?!
We can hear everything.
Oh my...
Sorry, sorry.
Mitsuki, you have work today!
Yep.
Yaaay, we're going out, we're going out!
That physician... Is he coming
to pick you up?
No, I haven't contacted him.
Sorry, I...uh...don't listen
to things like this much.
What?! What does that mean?
Meroko, you're staying home.
Are you serious?
I don't want to... It's boring.
I don't feel Mitsuki
is this kind of type...
Hm? "Normally quiet children
tend to..." What's this?
Special Feature,
"A Father's Words to His Daughter."
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
I could cry!
What?! It can't be...not that...
No...not Mitsuki. Not that!
For future reference...just in case...
Ah! No!
For future reference...
Ah! I'm bored!
I can't take it anymore.
Thanks for the great work today!
Good job, everybody...
Okay, pull out, pull out.
Good work.
You've gotten pretty used
to interviews, haven't you?
Way to go.
Yes.
Hey, what do you think this is?
What is it?
It means we've got
a runaway hit!
I see, it's selling.
What happened?
Aren't you happy?
Huh? No, that's not it.
You look kind of down.
No, I'm okay.
I see! So it's selling.
Well, I'm going this way.
Be careful on your way home.
Okay, thanks for everything!
You're thinking about it,
aren't you?
About what?
What do you mean, what?
It's written on your face.
"I'm lonely because the physician and
my grandmother won't listen to my song."
"I'm depressed."
What? Really!
Stupid, that's not what I meant.
It's a big hit, right?
Yeah...but I...want the people close to me
to be happy for me.
I auditioned with my father's song,
I succeeded, and became a singer.
But Dr. Wakaoji,
who once also pursued music,
won't listen to it.
Somehow it feels like my father
doesn't acknowledge it either...
I think it's good.
You have a nice voice and
you worked so hard to write the lyrics.
That's true but...
I assure you.
W-What is it?
Takuto, you don't know much about music,
so you can say that so easily.
Uh...I'm sorry I said too much.
Um...
I'm going home.
- I...
- Huh?
I...used to be a musician, long ago.
What?!
Daddy, over there.
Wait for me.
Takuto...
What did you just say?
Long ago, I used to be a musician.
Huh? Long ago?
When I was a human, I sang songs, too.
What? Takuto, you were a human?!
Hmph!
I wasn't born a Death Spirit.
What?! No way, really?!
Well, what about Meroko?
Was Meroko a human, too?
I don't really know,
but it seems so...
Is that so?
Sorry, I...said that you don't know
anything about music.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
Let's go!
What? Where?
You want him to hear
your song, don't you?
Dr. Wakaoji is out at
an academic conference today.
Yes, yes...
She says he's at a conference.
Now that I think of it...
Yes, the academic conference
at the Tauji Hotel tomorrow...
Okay, on to the Tauji Hotel!
Ah...wait!
Hm? I'm wrong?!
Yes, I'm sure he said that he had
something special to take care of
so he was looking for someone
to go in his place.
There's no sight of him.
No...
I think it would annoy him if
I burst in on him at a place like this.
You won't know
unless you do it, right?!
But...if he listens to it and
says that he really hates it.
What will I do?
Oh, Come on!
Stop being wishy washy.
Take the bull by its horns!
Be more confident.
Yes, that's right!
Meroko!
What are you doing?!
Well, you two always go out together.
It's boring all alone.
Yeah, but...
No problem.
That old lady hasn't recovered from her cold
and she's been in bed all day,
so we won't be found out.
That's it.
Which way are you going?
Uh...to Dr. Wakaoji.
I'm very sorry, but we're asking
unauthorized parties
to please refrain from
entering the conference area.
Sheesh!
To get stuck at a place like this.
And we came this far...
I know! I'll make Dr. Wakaoji
listen to the CD!
Huh? Wait!
Meroko! Not again!
Well, we want him to hear it, right?
Meroko!
Where are you going?
Takuto, what should I do?
This should work.
Where did that Meroko go?
I can't believe her.
It's Meroko!
I never heard you say
anything about that!
No, I'm sure of it!
Hey, porter.
There's strange...er, nice music
in the academic conference room.
Let's go see.
Yeah!
Here's our chance!
It's nice to have background music
like this once in a while.
I wonder where he is?
I don't see him anywhere.
Hurry, let's go confirm it.
Yeah.
I wonder what that was
just now.
It's probably
a complimentary service.
Umm, excuse me,
is Dr. Wakaoji here?
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji?
He didn't come today...
What?!
Where did he go?
How about it?
It went perfectly today, right?!
Huh? Yeah. If that physician
had been here.
What? He isn't here?
Owww.
Huh?
Do you know where he is?
Yep.
Umm...
This is...
Does it look familiar?
Yeah.
It seems like I've been here
once before.
I see...
What is...this feeling?
Oh!
Dr. Wakaoji!
It's been 10 years since
you passed away.
Your daughter is already 12 years old.
She's becoming a teen from head to toe,
and she's started to look like Hazuki...
This is where...Mother and Father...
I think all this time I've been running away
from your death.
Every time I see Mitsuki,
who's starting to look like Hazuki,
I feel like I'm called back
to those days.
And it really pains me.
But, Mitsuki is beginning to walk
toward the future.
It seems I can't dwell on the past anymore.
I have to get over your deaths.
I've sealed music away for a long time.
What?!
I...uh...don't listen to things like this much.
I'm an old man, you know.
Those words that time...
I see Mitsuki, you want to be a singer.
That's right, you've always said that.
You've always said that.
I thought I'd never listen
to music again...
Your daughter says
she wants to be a singer...
There's no doubt
that she's your daughter.
I'll watch your daughter grow up,
in your place.
Please cheer her on with me.
He's coming this way.
Huh?
I-It can't be...
Dr. Wakaoji...Thank you.
Father, Mother...I've made my debut.
Please cheer me on.
I'll work very hard.
Is Dr. Wakaoji here?
Oh! Mitsuki.
Doctor, uh...
Sorry!
I have an urgent patient.
I'll be back soon!
Aww...you're always busy.
I wonder if he sits here...
Doctor...
You bought it.
Sorry...
I made you wait.
What?
Mitsuki...
I guess she went home.
She must have...
Thank you for coming
to my classroom visitation.
I was kind of embarrassed
but, in truth, I was really happy.
Please continue to be my surrogate father
from now on. Yours, Mitsuki.
I wonder if the doctor read my card.
What are you doing Meroko?
Laughing like that all by yourself!?!
But Takuto,
how can you not be happy?
We're at a TV station...TV!
Everywhere you look,
there's famous people!
Darn it, you know we're
here as her chaperones.
But look, even Mitsuki's...
Ahh...both of you are so starstruck!
Are you sure this is going to be okay?
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Rules of Show Business"
- Don't miss it!