Testing, testing.
Mic check, mic check.
Bring those things over here.
- Okay!
Then, we'll start the introduction
music as we hit the lights.
- Okay.
It's been a while since
you performed, huh?
Yes.
Let's do our best!
Yes!
Well, thank you for waiting.
We are now opening the doors.
Seats are all reserved,
so please don't run.
All right everyone,
let's work hard today too!
- All right!
Please show the tickets
to the attendants.
Was that the right thing to do?
Here, thank you very much!
What the heck is this?!
Looks like my power is back.
This was the right thing to do.
Besides...
I remember her with no problem.
But...
What are you doing here?
Meroko!
Today's the fated day!
This is no time to be daydreaming.
There's no stopping now
that we've made it here.
We have to work hard
for Mitsuki today!
That's right.
I must do what I can today.
You don't have to tell me.
We'll prevent her from dying,
no matter what!
Yes, that's the spirit!
But we don't know where
other Death Spirits may come from.
Just make sure not to
leave Mitsuki's side.
I'll go check around.
Okay.
Later.
Takuto...
In every case,
we Death Spirits were destined to
be separated from Mitsuki today.
But we're trying to change that,
so it wouldn't surprise me if
we lose something else instead.
So we must not let Mitsuki die,
no matter what!
It's beautiful.
When we tested it on stage,
it looked so pretty shining in the light.
Oh, Meroko!
Look, look!
Isn't this pretty?
I'll be singing in this dress!
Meroko, what's wrong?
Nothing. It's wonderful!
It's so beautiful!
It'll look really good on Full Moon.
Yes!
Man, I wish I could've worn this when
we were at the studio rehearsal.
What's gonna happen?
What's coming?
It doesn't matter what comes!
I won't give Mitsuki's life to
anyone no matter what!
Hello Takuto.
How are you?
Hi!
Izumi...
Wow...
Don't look so scary.
Is it you?
What are you talking about?
Is it you who's going
to take Mitsuki's life?
No way. There's no reason for me
to do such a thing.
I can't get Mero to turn to me
even if I did that.
What is it?
Izumi, do you really like Meroko?
Why are you asking?
If you really like her, then why do you
do things that make her suffer?
I know...
What you want to say is, that in true love
you should care for each other, right?
But I know that's just an illusion.
So I'm just testing her.
Besides, whatever you try to do,
Mikki's life will end today.
Even if you don't do it,
someone else will come to do it anyway.
Fate won't change.
The result is the same.
There's no point in trying.
Izumi...
What is it?
Why do you think we
became Death Spirits?
It's a punishment for being careless
with our own lives.
Right. You must be right.
I didn't finish my life properly.
But I am so disgusted now
for being forced to see
the death of someone
that I care about.
That's the punishment.
We became Death Spirits to suffer.
Maybe you're right.
But I will prevent that destiny.
Nothing will start unless I move.
You are an optimist.
It's just that you're too pessimistic.
You think so?
See you.
Izumi!
What?
Meroko is a good person.
I already know that.
Not only Meroko. There are people
that you can actually trust.
There's no need to test them.
I think I got enough pictures
from this area.
Then, let's head on in.
It's so amazing that this girl became
such a popular idol, isn't it?
Totally!
I was like "huh?" back when she said
she was going to debut as a singer.
When I first saw the huge billboard of her,
I thought, "What?!"
Where is Mitsuki?
With her grandmother, I think.
There are so many people here.
I wonder if Mitsuki was able
to find her friends.
She should be fine.
Oh, Ma'am, this way, this way!
Hello there!
I'll have two pamphlets, two necklaces
and two pen-lights as well, please.
Sure!
You really seem to know
what you're doing.
Oh, yes, of course!
I used to always come to shows
without your knowledge!
Is that so?
Well, not always.
It was just once in a while!
Just once in a while.
I really don't come to
shows that often.
Wow!
So many people came for me.
Meroko...
How does it look around the area?
Not much going on.
How about here?
Did anyone come?
No problem here.
No one has come here.
Okay.
Takuto?
Did something happen?
What happened? What do you mean?
You're acting a bit strange.
What are you saying?
Takuto is always like this.
It's starting!
Hello everybody!
Welcome to Full Moon's "Live"!
Before Full Moon comes out in
just a little bit, let's get pumped!
- Yeah!
Without further ado,
I'll introduce you to a wonderful guest!
She rushed over here for Full Moon!
Madoka Wakamatsu!
The song is, of course,
"Eternal Snow"!
How long has it been ever since
I fell in love with you?
My feelings just keep
getting stronger...
She's so lively.
She's a clumsy one, but looks like
she's found her own way to live her life.
Yes.
Even if Madoka says all those things,
I think she likes Full Moon.
I think she gets the motivation
to work hard from Full Moon.
No, Madoka is someone who could sing
very well even if Full Moon didn't exist.
Just look at her singing so happily.
Hold me tight.
If loving someone was
going to feel like this,
I wish I never found out
about love.
I won't lose to her!
Because I'm singing the songs I love
so much, I'll sing happily like Madoka.
So I won't lose fighting
against my fate!
Mitsuki...
That's right!
We will support you too,
so defeat fate with your singing!
Thank you, Meroko.
Mitsuki...
Dr. Herberd.
We've been looking forward
to your visit.
Today is the day, Mr. Wakaoji.
Yes.
Today is the day.
Everything will finish today.
If Mitsuki is fine
after midnight tonight,
that means that we were able
to change her fate.
I will protect her till then,
no matter what.
So, Keichi, you must
succeed in the surgery.
Yes.
All right.
I'm counting on you.
Takuto!
After everything is finished
and tomorrow comes,
let's jam together again.
Yeah!
Okay, let's go!
Let me carry your luggage.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for
a lovely performance!
By the way, what kind of artist
is Full Moon in your eyes, Madoka?
For me, she's someone
who's destined to be my rival!
I see.
If I remember it correctly,
you were supposed to release a song
at the same time as Full Moon, right?
Yes! I actually kind of
got depressed then, but...
Oh, you did, Madoka?
I think people see me as someone
who says whatever comes to my mind,
but I am really a pretty
sensitive person.
Huh?
Just listen to her.
She's clearly gotten over it well.
Well, that aside,
we will be looking forward to
everything you do in the future!
- Izumi,
- Yes, of course!
- we're not going back yet?
- That was Wakamatsu Madoka,
- No.
- everyone!
- Why? Tell me why?
- Thank you!
Shut up, it's none
of your business.
So, Mitsuki, it's almost time to go.
Okay!
Takuto, please turn me
into Full Moon.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am!
I really want to sing now!
I want to sing to the entire world.
Got it.
N-No way!
She can't transform?
What happened, Meroko?
Takuto's power isn't working!
What?
What about the concert?
Full Moon, long time no see.
Congratulations on your first live show.
Unfortunately,
I can't make it today,
but I will definitely come and
support you next time, so keep it up.
I look forward to seeing you again.
So long.
All right, that was
a video letter from Miss Komaki!
Now, Full Moon will finally
come out on stage soon!
Takuto...
My power isn't enough.
The effect of the Flower of Forgetfulness
probably hasn't kicked in yet,
but once it starts working...
Damn it! Why can't I use my power
at such a critical moment?!
Just start working now!
That's okay if I can't transform
into Full Moon.
- What?
I'll sing... just as my
12-year-old self.
But then...
I was able to become a singer
because Takuto allowed me
to transform into Full Moon.
I was able to live a completely different
life from the one I used to live.
So that's already more than enough.
When is Full Moon coming out?
She's so late.
She's coming now!
Please!
What should we do?
We'll take care of things here,
so please take care of the stage.
All right!
Mitsuki, you...
It's okay.
I can't project my voice as much,
but my desire to sing is all the same.
No!
Mitsuki, that's impossible.
Yeah, the audience is waiting for
Full Moon to come on stage now.
Ms. Oshige!
Where's Full Moon?
Okay. I'll fill the time.
Hey everybody!
I don't think you're loud enough!
You've got to call Full Moon
in a much louder voice!
- Full Moon!
But...
No one will understand that
you are Full Moon.
Everyone will be confused.
But...
Damn it! It's my fault.
- Meroko?
- You...
Here, Takuto.
What? What's this?
I'm giving you my power.
But if you do that...
Don't worry about me.
Please transform Mitsuki into Full Moon.
This is the last time
she can sing as Full Moon.
Meroko...
- Full Moon, Full Moon, Full Moon!
This ring will lead
my power to you, Takuto.
We are going to join our power.
Thank you, Meroko.
You better be really grateful
for a young lady's hair.
I've given you my treasure.
Okay?
Meroko...
Let's go, Mitsuki!
But...
It's fine!
I won't lose.
I won't forget about you
no matter what, either!
- Full Moon, Full Moon!
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep getting stronger.
They're silent like the snow,
but they keep building up.
Hold me tight. If loving someone
was going to feel like this,
I wish I never found out about love.
I love you, my tears won't stop.
If this is how it's going to be,
I wish I had never met you.
- If the snow falls forever,
- I... I...
- will I be able to let go
- Who am I?
- of these thoughts of you?
- Your name is Takuto.
Takuto? Why am I here?
Because...
Because you're going to
make new memories.
New memories...
I love you.
The feeling of love fills my heart...
I want to scream in the winter sky
that I want to see you right now.
This is my first listen,
but her song is really good.
Yeah.
It's a really good song.
Hey, what's her name?
She's Full Moon.
No, she's Mitsuki.
Mitsuki?
Yes. She's the girl you threw
everything away to protect.
I protected her?
Here, this is her last song.
We have to listen.
Yeah.
Next time on the final episode of Full Moon:
"Looking for the Full Moon."
- Look forward to it!