SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
Are you prepared, my darlings?
Prepare to advance, forward!
Advancing!
Where're our allies?
Left, forty!
Prepare the main cannon!
Distance, 400!
Load shell!
HEAT Round!
Roger!
Olga!
Leave it to me!
I've been staring at this scope for three days.
I refuse to die until I can take a shower.
Main cannon, ready!
Fire!
Direct hit!
Anna, signal the trailing forces!
One enemy unit destroyed, follow our lead!
Roger!
Filicia, cover Anna.
R-Roger!
It's flashing, but it's not lightning. So don't worry.
I know!
Th-Three o'clock-!
Oh no...
Lieutenant Anna!
Ka...mi...ya...
Hi...go...ya...
CHIRPING CRICKETS
SPIRITS DOWN THE RIVER
Hey Noel, nothing will get clean if you don't put effort in it!
Okay.
It's so hot!
This building is so cold in the winter, but it's great in summer.
Hm? Weren't Rio and Felicia in charge of laundry today?
They seemed busy so they asked me to switch.
Whose is that?
It's Felicia's.
She said she wasn't hungry, so we could eat it if we wanted.
It's mine then!
What're you doing? Preparing dinner?
Wait, what are you doing? You'll get in trouble for playing with food.
I'm not playing with it.
Obon is today, isn't it?
What? What's Obon?
Fiesta des Lumières.
What?
Fi...?
Fiesta des Lumières is a special Southern Helvetian event.
Derived from a local religion that believes the souls of the dead return to the present world for a short time in summer.
To symbolize sending them back to Heaven,
lanterns are sent down the river.
In other provinces, the same kind of festival is also known as "Obon".
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh? So it's the same thing!
Souls of the dead return? Wait, what are you saying?!
Ghosts are coming back, is that it?!
More or less.
Lanterns? That sounds incredibly wonderful!
We only make fires in my hometown.
That's wrong!
The dead go to Heaven and stay there forever!
Any left wandering on the surface are evil.
What? That's not true.
But the church-
We're home!
Hey, lend us a hand!
When did you two go shopping?
Ah, that's...
It looked delicious, so I bought it.
These as well.
Is this how I do it?
That's no good, Father.
It's like this.
It's done!
Is that your father and mother?
I see, it's well made.
What? Even the church acknowledges it?
That Fi-something...
Yeah.
I bet the main church would have a problem,
but we're in the countryside, so...
That's so lax.
In my hometown, we make horses and cows out of cucumbers and eggplants,
for our ancestors to ride upon.
Afterwards, we dance to impart some solace to the returning ancestors.
Really?
Are you making it as well?
Yeah, but I only watched last year.
It's our job to maintain good relations with the local residents.
If you don't think about the weird things, it's only a pretty festival.
Right, Filicia?
Filicia!
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
My hand just slipped.
But it sure is rare for the Captain to be clumsy.
That's Kanata's domain.
What?
It's been quite hot for the last few days, right?
I haven't been sleeping well.
I'll take a short break.
Filicia...
She's acting a little weird, isn't she?
She didn't finish her meal and used the food budget to buy watermelons.
She must have a lot of things on her mind.
I'm going to check on her...
Stop!
Everyone has very private matters.
Please leave her alone.
Noel?
Do you know, Rio?
I've read the record.
I was actually there.
So...
Filicia...
Grip it firmly, that's right.
Now, now...
And then, a monster looking like the Captain jumps out...
It's hard to believe that this ocean was full of life a long time ago.
Have you heard that the world is ending slowly,
and that humans are going to become extinct?
Those... are just rumors.
But, if those rumors are true,
then just what are we fighting for?
I'm... still alive...
Ideographs?
I'm sorry,
I wish I could read your last words...
This equipment...
Is this from the old era?
Captain...
Lieutenant Olga...
Martina...
Anna...
Why am I the only survivor?
Why...
...are you crying?
I see.
So there are still people living in this world.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because we lost...
...to them.
I'm truly sorry we couldn't protect you.
The world has ended.
No...
You're all remnants.
The final breaths of humanity's struggle for survival.
Humanity...
...can never restore the world's prosperity as it once was.
Don't just decide that!
It's the truth.
You should simply put an end to everything.
Struggling for life within the despair of an apocalyptic world must be lonesome.
No. No way!
Why?
Are you saying life still has meaning in this world?
That's...
Help...
I'm over here! I'm still alive!
Please! Help me!
You're...
I apologize.
If only our unit had arrived half a day earlier, this wouldn't have happened.
Your highness, Princess Iliya...
But I wasn't expecting this.
What?
You totally ignored the Fiesta des Lumières last year, Rio.
Why the change of heart?
That's...
It's a nice color, isn't it?
It's from Treize. I bought it the other day.
Wow!
It's so pretty!
Right?
Indeed, she was everything to me.
I wanted to protect the country and its people like she did.
But, sometimes I think...
Is there a meaning to any of it?
So if she ever came back,
I wanted her to tell me the answer.
But I'm more worried about you.
Everyone's worrying about you.
True, I guess I did made things a little awkward.
I've failed as a captain.
It's not just them!
Even I- Um...
What is it?
Anyway! Don't shoulder everything yourself!
I can at least listen to you!
Thank you, Rio.
Then I'll take you up on your offer and tell you.
What is it?
To be honest...
I'm afraid I gained weight this summer.
At this rate, I won't be able to wear my winter uniform.
I heard that eating only watermelons can help lose weight, so I'm trying that.
Hm? What's wrong, Rio?
You're still playing dumb?!
Because you were on the front lines at Vingt-
Ah! You must be thinking I was recalling that time?
You... You're not?
It's beautiful.
Let's do it too.
You made one too, Kureha?
N-Not that I believe in "spirits" or anything...
This is a mission, I tell you.
Um, who did you make yours for, Filicia?
My old comrades,
and a nameless soldier.
He was a savior who made me realize what's important.
Is that person the reason why...
Filicia, if anything's bothering you, I...
Well, I might not be of help...
But!
It seems I've made you worry, haven't I?
I'm sorry.
But, I'm fine.
That's depressing.
I want to worry, too!
You've always worried about me, Filicia.
I've made you worry about me.
I want to worry about you, too!
Because, I like you, Filicia!
And I love you too, Kana.
You just need to stay as you are.
Please.
Filicia...
You're always telling us,
to not be afraid to share our feelings.
I believe that's an amazing thing.
Captain...
Filicia...
Me, too...
You all... are so adorable.
Please come again next year, my ancestors.
Dad... Mom...
Mother... Sister...
That girl...
Rio, you were asking about the meaning in this world, right?
Yeah.
Being the only survivor, I've always thought about it.
Why I was the only one left alive,
Listen now, be careful not to fall over.
and what meaning there was to it.
And I've realized,
that for us, this world must have no meaning in it.
But isn't that wonderful?
Because it means we can find that meaning ourselves.
And I've already discovered the reason I'm here.
And after that, the Priest...
And then?
He sucked, so he asked Yumina...
I don't ever want those kids to experience the same thing I did.
That's true.
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
PHONE DUTY - WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY
Next episode: Phone Duty - We Have an Emergency
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.