Makise... Kurisu?!
I did knock, for what it's worth.
How did you discern our location!?
I asked Mr. Hashida.
He called it a "laboratory,"
so I was expecting something a little more grand than this...
Daru, did you betray me?
You were deceived by the wiles of a 3D woman...
I'll never forgive you! Ever!
You... You...
Bitch!
Can you do anything about him?
Just consider him confused by certain current events.
This is an emergency.
The Organization has finally sent an agent of theirs to the lab!
What?
Then is this, too, the choice of Steins;Gate?
Steins;Gate?
Something Okarin made up.
It doesn't really mean anything.
I'm sure.
He's mixing up his German and English.
Take off your shoes!
I'm sorry.
I've been in America for too long.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Makise Kurisu.
You can't even shake hands?
Japanese men don't know how to do anything.
You're freaking out too much.
It's because I can feel murderous intent seeping from your every pore.
Is this what they call the "martial arts"?
Where are you going?
Honestly, I came here to see if your claim that I'd been stabbed was real,
or just an excuse for sexual harassment.
But it seems something more important has appeared.
This.
Parallel World
Paranoia
There's no damage to the stalk.
It's not some kind of trick.
She may attempt to trigger some sort of explosive.
Don't let her out of your sight for a second.
No, she won't.
Got any tweezers?
No!
I see.
It's mushy inside.
It tastes...
Nothing.
Ew!
You zombie!
If you're hungry, say so.
I'll give you a banana.
I'm fine.
Who'd eat a pervert's banana, anyways?
Pervert?
You poked at me, attempting to touch me out of nowhere.
Miss Makise? Miss Makise?
Yes?
Could you say, "Who'd eat a pervert's banana, anyways?"
once more, do you think?
If possible, with an upset expression.
Upset?
Yes.
Why are you blushing?
Did you imagine something?
Out with it, genius girl.
Let's hear what the genius imagined!
It seems you're both perverts.
Oh, my...
It's not a compliment.
I would say the person with the perverted imagination is the pervert.
You perverted genius girl!
Who's the pervert?
Okay...
To be honest, we're at the point where
I could sue you for sexual harassment right this minute, but I'll let it slide for now.
For now?
So, tell me the details.
This banana has something to do with that microwave, right?
It's top secret!
Future Gadget #8, the Phone Microwave,
is my lab's secret weapon.
But Miss Makise might be able to explain how this strange device works.
But...
You need to understand, we'll never figure this out on our own.
But this is the Future Gadget Lab's...
You!
Cristina, you said?
No, I never said that.
I'll tell you the secrets of the Phone Microwave,
but on two conditions!
One, you must become a member of the Future Gadget Lab.
You want me to join your lab?
But I'm returning to America in August...
It can be just until then.
And one more condition.
There's more?
Forget about any acts of sexual harassment I've committed.
That's it.
Okarin, you're a petty person.
A very petty person.
And I love that. Love it!
Shut up!
Well?
I think the conditions are very favorable...
Favorable to you.
Jeez...
You're making my brain send out too much norepinephrine.
What will you do, Cristina?
There's no "-tina"!
Sorry, "The Zombie."
Say it right, Hououin Pervert-Kyouma!
What?
Perverted Genius Girl!
Perverts glaring at one another... Win!
Shut up, pervert!
Oh, fine.
All right.
I accept.
So, no more "Pervert."
I'll stop calling you one too.
Very well.
Then, from now on, you're Lab Member 004!
Cristina!
No "-tina"!
Juicy Karaage Number One... Wow!
I'm back!
Do you think it's a teleporter?
It's dangerous to jump to conclusions.
Then, what do you think it is?
If nothing else,
it didn't teleport the single banana or the banana bunch.
One, two, three, four...
A guest?
Hello there.
I'm Makise Kurisu.
I'm sorry for just showing up out of the blue.
I'm Shiina Mayuri.
It seems I'm a lab member now as well.
A lab member?
Yes...
A female lab member!
Is that rare?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
You're the first female lab member since Mayushii!
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, nice to meet you.
What?
What happened?
There was an electrical discharge.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Give me the details.
Um... Well...
Some kind of lightning shot out from the microwave.
When?
Yesterday, around noon.
You saw the alert about the satellite crash and ran out,
and I connected my phone to it.
Then, when I sent that message,
your phone was hooked up to the Phone Microwave?
The one about Miss Makise being stabbed?
That was a week ago, wasn't it?
No, that was yesterday!
Where is it? Where is it?
Why isn't it here?!
When this happened, what was the microwave doing?
I was running a systems test...
so I think it was during the reverse spin testing.
We should try to recreate the situation.
Mayuri, bring me the Juicy Karaage Number One!
Okay!
Want some, anyone?
I can give each of you one.
Do we need to put something in there?
I want to see
what happens to its contents when it rotates backwards.
Daru.
Assistant, send a message to my phone.
Since when did I become your assistant?
And I don't know your number anyways.
Useless assistant.
Daru, your phone's fine.
What should the subject be?
Let me see.
"Cristina is a pervert."
I told you that's off-limits.
Then we'll split the difference and go with "Okarin is a pervert"...
What?
Mr. Hashida, good job!
All right, sending.
Now, we wait for the message to reach the phone...
I bet it's ready now!
Wait!
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Gotta turn on the fan!
What is this?
The EM waves, maybe?
Don't be stupid.
A microwave's EM waves couldn't split a desk just like that.
They're all black!
And I just bought them, too!
What'll we do about the hole in the floor?
If Mr. Braun finds that, we'll be in serious trouble.
Well?
It's here.
7/24, 17:30.
It went back to the past...
Did you find something?
Yes. It's all coming together!
I can see it...
The one answer this all points to!
Really?
The banana, split off from the bunch, returned to it!
The message traveled five days into the past.
No way. You can't mean...
That's right!
The Phone Microwave is...
...a time machine!
Thirteen messages?
The lightning...
Oh, right.
I dubbed her the "Shining Finger."
But this many?
"Message me now."
"Are you asleep?"
"How long are you going to sleep?"
Daru?
Wanna go for a walk?
What's wrong?
The damage is pretty bad.
I worked all night, with nothing to show for it.
I regret even trying.
Why aren't they turning into gel-banas anymore?
Hell if I know.
That was the only time we were able to send a message.
Shouldn't we call Miss Makise back?
You know that's not going to happen.
No way.
A time machine?
She never came back.
What was that?
What is this?
The LHC.
The Large Hadron Collider,
SERN's particle accelerator.
Feels nice, just looking at it...
SERN maintains an exclusive monopoly on time machines.
John Titor...
Oh, the one you were talking about.
@channel can't get enough of the guy.
What is SERN?
Titor was explaining that they completed a time machine by 2034!
I have no idea what you're talking about...
Just tell me!
What is SERN?
Calm down.
It's the acronym for the European Organization in Nuclear Research and Particle Physics.
Its H.Q. is just outside Geneva.
As the name suggests, its main work is in particle physics.
It also has some of the world's best facilities for it:
the Low Energy Antiproton Ring,
the Proton Synchrotron Booster,
the Large Electron–Positron Collider...
and the last boss,
the world's biggest particle accelerator,
the Large Hadron Collider~
There were rumors that the LHC could generate a miniature black hole.
A black hole...
Daru.
'Sup?
Didn't one proposed time travel method
utilize a miniature black hole?
Yeah, it did.
But you attended Miss Makise's lecture, didn't you?
She said creating a black hole was impossible.
But if the LHC exists,
then it's possible...
It is!
No, it isn't.
SERN's publicly denied it.
But they say, "where there's smoke, there's fire."
It's me.
No Cell Phones
That's right. I know.
El Psy Congroo.
Who, exactly, are you fighting?
There's only one thing for us to do now.
Go to Faris'!
No!
You're a supah hakah, right?
You should smile smugly!
It's "hacker," not "hakah," all right?
You understand the rest?
Not a bit.
Hack into SERN.
That's it.
Okarin... This is a joke, right?
You need to find out what evil they're up to
and find hints about the time machine.
Whether we make the Phone Microwave into a real time machine
or let it rest forever in the lab storeroom is up to your skills.
Don't blame me for whatever happens!
Two orders of beef bowl.
800 yen total.
Okarin!
Slacking off again?
Yeah, the shop's boring.
Nothing to do.
You're more of a bicycle shop now.
Anyways, what are you guys doing on the second floor?
Future Gadget Lab, right?
Where did you learn that name?
Future Gadget Lab
If you know that much, then fine.
We're fighting against an organization
that rules the world from the shadows.
Just now, we're hacking into that organization.
So, is SERN that organization?
How did you know?
I'm sorry.
Actually, I overheard you guys.
I said I was bored.
So, I accidentally...
You were spying on us?
I could hear you...
But don't worry.
I'm good at keeping my mouth shut.
Again?
What? A message that someone died?
Someone died?
N-No... I was just kidding.
This girl's obsessed with some old PC
called an IBN 5100.
An IBN?
You know it?
Um... Yeah.
You heard it too?
No, I saw it on the Internet.
You know, that guy who claimed to be a time traveler?
John Titor, was it?
Titor?
It was on @channel.
The IBN 5100 was built before the widespread use of the BASIC language,
so it can read IBN's proprietary programming language or something...
Really?!
Yeah.
Come to think of it, the Titor who appeared in 2000 also...
You all seem to have fixed ideas about the nature of time.
031 Name: Mr. Anonymous [sage]
John Titor took a dump in space,
and now the world is in danger...
032 Name: KuriGohan and Kamehameha [sage]
This is getting more disappointing
None of this is really concrete
I realize you're doing your best to sound realistic,
but you can't fool me.
Time isn't a single line, moving from past to future.
Let's say I were to go back in time and kill someone we'll call "A."
This alters something called the divergence number,
and the world line moves to a world without A.
When there's a world line shift, people's memories are altered.
In other words, memories of the world line where A existed are deleted,
and replaced with memories of a world line where A doesn't exist.
I'm more interested in how SERN,
214 Name: KuriGohan and Kamehameha [sage]
a research organization, ends up as the planetary ruler
It's a question I've been asking for a while now.
a research organization, ends up as the planetary ruler.
Don't believe what SERN says.
343 Name: Anonymous [sage]
And this results in a dystopia?
They've already succeeded in
creating a miniature black hole.
357 Name: Anonymous [sage]
What's a dystopia?
It would be easiest to describe a dystopia as the revival of communism,
and the world's reversion to the 18th century's living standards.
By 2036, SERN holds most of the world's science and technology.
472 Name: Anonymous [sage]
Guess what I had for dinner tomorrow!
473 Name: Anonymous [sage]
I want to know the future!
And you need the IBN 5100 to change this future?
That's correct.
I need the IBN 5100's abilities to stop their plans.
The John Titor who appeared in 2000 said the same thing.
558 Name: Hououin Kyouma [sage]
The John Titor who appeared in 2000
said the same thing...
559 Name: Anonymous [sage]
Dude, just shut up already.
The "me" who appeared ten years ago?
As I've said, I've unfortunately never been to the year 2000.
But, it's possible you saw me in a different world line.
Interesting.
I'd like to talk to you in detail.
*In 2015, WW3 occurs.
*In 2036, Earth is polluted by nuclear warfare.
*I've travelled from 2036 to acquire an IBN 5100.
*The IBN 5100 has a hidden function.
*Only a few IBN engineers know of it.
This is my address.
If you contact me, I'll answer.
I've almost got it.
If I can just access the SQL table list, figuring out the password should be easy.
Good morning!
Mayuri?
What brings you here so early?
I heard you've been up two nights in a row, so I brought snacks.
Here you go.
Canned fishcake stew!
Great!
Bring me another sometime, Mayuri.
Mayushii doesn't have enough pocket money to treat you too often.
I need to buy my Rai-Net sausage, as well!
Upa again?
So I want you to enjoy this!
There's some for Daru and Kurisu too.
That's not it!
He's not listening at all.
I told him to take a break, though.
His supah hakah's soul is burning bright!
Don't say "hakah"!
But it's not good to nose around in the secrets of others, isn't it?
This is to reveal SERN's plots.
Even so...
I'm sure Kurisu left because she was mad.
No, that had nothing to do with the hacking.
My assistant ran off on her own.
I wonder if she'll come back...
Huh?
What?
I'll trade you a mandarin for a beef strip.
I'd rather have a quail egg, then.
No.
I like quail eggs almost as much as I like beef strips.
Mayushii likes quail eggs too!
Then I'll give you a fish sausage instead.
I guess I like fish sausages more than mandarins.
Okay, then negotiations have concluded.
Then here's my beef strip...
I ate it already.
When did you...
It was good.
I got it!
I got it! I got it! I got it! I got it! I got it!
Now give up, and show me everything.
I got it!
ID get!
You did it?
Mission complete!
Wow!
I don't understand, but wow.
Well, the hacking's complete,
but there are limits to what I can see without being an admin.
It's like I can only see the boobs.
You're so naughty, Daru.
What did you get?
So far, just some e-mails.
English?
Let's get Dr. Excite in here.
No way, that's a pain.
It says "Hi, Paul!"
We don't need your acting.
No?
"The LHC is working well."
"It's as fickle as a cat, but for the past month,"
"...it's been working surprisingly well."
What's he talking about?
Anyways, does anything here mention a time machine?
The phrase "time machine" doesn't show up,
but in the last month, the word "Z-program" has been used over a hundred times.
Let's see...
"Z-Program Experiment Report 137."
"The miniature black hole mission has already been established,"
"...so I'll skip that report."
Miniature black hole...
Looks correct.
They announced publically that those experiments were a failure.
What else does it say?
"Experiment result..."
"Human is dead,"
"...mismatch."
Human is dead?
Someone...
...died.