[NARRATOR]
Alchemy...
the science of understanding, deconstructing,
and reconstructing
matter; however,
it is not an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange--
the basis of all alchemy...
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[NARRATOR] On their
journey to Resembool,
Ed and Al encountered former
State Alchemist Dr. Tim Marcoh,
who admitted to possession
of an incomplete
Philosopher's Stone...
Moved by Ed's determination,
Marcoh gave the
brothers the location
of his hidden
research materials.
After Ed's automail
had been repaired,
he and Al immediately
left for the first branch
of the National
Central Library,
where they hoped to
find Dr. Marcoh's research
into the secrets of
the Philosopher's Stone.
Augghh!!!
[ED] Dr. Marcoh's research...!
It's all gone!
[LUST]
In the end,
burning the entire
place down was easier.
[GLUTTONY] Oh, is that what
you were doing in Central?
[LUST]
Yes...
The Fullmetal boy found out
about Marcoh's research...
Something had to
be done about it.
[LUST] With that
issue taken care of,
I thought I would
come to see how things
are progressing in
East City... Is he here?
[LUST]
Gluttony?
[GLUTTONY] I smell 'im...
I can smell him!
[GLUTTONY]
The scar-faced Ishvalan.
He's close. I can taste
his stink--like blood!
[GLUTTONY] I still
get to eat him, right?
[LUST] Oh yes, down to
the last strand of hair.
[explosion]
[HAWKEYE]
Scar hasn't been sighted...
Not once since that incident
with the Elric brothers.
[HAVOC] Maybe he's not
even in East City anymore.
[ROY] I hope you're
wrong about that.
[HAVOC] Huh?
[ROY] This case
has obviously gotten
to be too much for
Central to handle...
If I can close it quickly
enough, I'll be golden.
[ROY] I've got a
ladder to climb,
and this is how it's done...
I need every mark in my
favor that I can get...
At least until I've assumed
the office of Fuhrer, that is.
[HAWKEYE] You may
not want to display
your ambitions
quite so nakedly, Sir.
[ROY]
Yeah...
I'll be sure to remember
that in the future.
[SOLDIER 1]
Reporting in, sir!
We've just received word
of an explosion
occurring on the Marl River.
[ROY]
What?
[MP A]
Was it a gas explosion?
[MP B]
With everything else
that's been going on
around here, who knows?
[HAWKEYE]
There's no mistaking it.
This was definitely
Scar's jacket.
[ROY] Have you
found the body?
[HAVOC] Not yet,
but we're still searching.
[HAWKEYE] Either way,
he can't be in good shape
after losing
this much blood.
[ROY] Yeah... But we
do this by the book.
We need to find hard
proof that he's dead...
All right,
Lieutenant Havoc.
[HAVOC]
Yes, Sir?
[ROY] You and your men
will work day and night
to clear out
this debris...
I want his body found...
Don't take so much as a
coffee break until that's done,
do you understand?
[HAVOC]
Come on Colonel,
can't you cut
us some slack...?
At this rate, you're
gonna work us all to death.
[ROY]
Shut up!
[ROY] I don't get to relax
until I've seen his body.
That means you
don't get to either.
[HAVOC] I guess
we'll get to work then.
[LUST]
Looks like he got away.
[GLUTTONY]
I didn't get my snack.
[LUST]
Yes, I know...
Maybe next time... Though...
I think we can safely assume
that Scar will be out
of the game for awhile.
[LUST] I suppose I'll be
heading back to Central again...
I need to report to Father
about everything
that's happened here.
[ED] There's nothing
left here but ashes.
Everything's gone.
[ROSS]
Major Armstrong!
[ARMSTRONG] Oh,
Second Lieutenant Ross
and Sergeant Brosh...
To what do we
owe this pleasure?
[ROSS]
You have been ordered
to report back to
the Command Center, sir.
[BROSH] We'll be
taking over supervision
of Edward Elric and his
brother, effective immediately.
[ARMSTRONG]
Very well. He's yours.
[ED]
What is this?
Just when I think I'm home free,
they saddle me
with more bodyguards?
This is getting old!
[ROSS]
All might not be lost...
There's a woman who
was well acquainted
with the materials
in the first branch.
[ROSS]
Unfortunately...
she wasn't working
there anymore.
[ED] That sounds
incredibly helpful.
[AL]
Something wrong?
[BROSH]
Oh... it's nothing...
Although, if you
don't mind me asking...
why are you wearing
a suit of armor?
[AL] It's a hobby!
[ED] It's a hobby!
[BROSH]
A hobby?!
What kind of freaky
hobby is that, Lieutenant?
[ROSS]
Who are these boys anyway?
[ED]
So... What d'ya say, Al?
It's a lovely view, isn't it?
[AL] Oh yeah,
yeah, it's gorgeous.
[ED]
Oh, wow...
there's gotta be
a million of 'em!
[BROSH] Is there really
someone living in this place?
[ROSS]
Miss Sheska... Are you here?
Miss Sheska...?
[SHESKA muffled]
Is someone there?
Please help me!
[AL]
Umm... Brother...
There's somebody under there!
[ED] Start digging!
We're coming!
[SHESKA]
Thank you! I'm so sorry!
I got myself trapped under
a whole mountain of books!
[SHESKA] I thought I was
going to suffocate under there.
[SHESKA]
Thank you so much!
[ED]
So, uh, are you Sheska?
[SHESKA]
Yes.
[ED] And you worked
at the library?
[SHESKA]
Oh, the library...!
The word itself
is so beautiful...!
[SHESKA] I've loved books
my whole entire life...
ever since I first
learned to read as a girl...
that job... was heaven!
[SHESKA]
But I forgot
that I was supposed
to be working,
and all I ever did was read...
So they fired me.
[SHESKA]
If I don't find another job,
I'll never be
able to move my poor,
elderly mother into
a better hospital...
But I'm hopeless...!
The only thing I can
do well is read...!
I'll never find another
job as long as I live!
[SHESKA] I'm useless!
Good-for-nothing!
More pathetic
than pond scum!
[ED]
Excuse me...
there was one thing
we wanted to ask you.
[SHESKA]
Yes?
[ED] Do you remember
seeing any research
belonging to someone
named Tim Marcoh?
[SHESKA]
Let's see. Tim Marcoh...
Where do I know that name...?
Oh! Yes, of course.
I remember now!
[ED]
Really?
[SHESKA] Oh yes,
I'm absolutely positive.
There were some
handwritten notes
stuffed into a bookcase
where they didn't belong.
[ED] The notes really
were there after all!
[ED] Which means
they burned up
along with everything
else in the library...
[SHESKA] Did you
want to read them?
Is that why you're asking?
[ED] Yeah, but
it's too late now.
They're nothing but ashes.
[AL]
Sorry to bother you.
[SHESKA] I remember
everything that was in them.
Would that help at all?
[ED and AL]
Huh?!
[SHESKA]
It's just how I am...
I'm able to remember the content
of any book I've ever read.
[SHESKA]
It'll take awhile,
but I could write
them out for you.
[ED]
Thank you bookworm...!
You're my hero!
[SHESKA]
You're... welcome?
Here you are!
Complete copies of
all Tim Marcoh's notes!
[SHESKA] Sorry, I know five
days is a long time to wait,
but there was quite
a lot to write down.
[AL]
Unbelievable!
There are some amazing
people in this world!
[ED] These are really
Dr. Marcoh's research notes?
[SHESKA]
They sure are.
Come and take
a look at them.
[SHESKA]
"Written by Tim Marcoh...
One Thousand Easy Recipes"
[ROSS] Six cups
of rice, one carrot,
two onions, salt...
[ROSS] Oh great.
Does this mean we came
all this way for a cook book?
[BROSH] Miss, which part
of this made you think
it was an
important document?
[SHESKA] Is it not what
you're looking for...?
All I did was copy
down what I remember.
[BROSH] Wonderful--so this
was just a wild goose chase?
[ED] Sheska...
are you absolutely sure
this is a flawless
reproduction of the notes?
[SHESKA]
Oh yes.
I'm one hundred
percent certain!
[ED]
Then thank you very much...
You're incredible!
[ED] All right. Let's get
these back to the library.
[AL] They should have
related materials there.
[ED] Oh... I almost
forgot Sheska's fee.
[ED]
Lieutenant... Here...
This is my
registration number
and the pocket watch for ID.
[ED]
Withdraw that amount
from my annual research grants
and make sure
Sheska gets it, okay?
[ROSS] Right... I'll get
on that right away, sir.
I assume that I can
just take this note down
to the State Alchemist office?
[ED]
That should work.
[ED] Well... Sheska,
you're a life saver!
Bye!
[ROSS] From his
research grants, huh?
[Shocked cries]
[SHESKA] Did he miss a
decimal point somewhere?!
Wow!
[ROSS] How does
a boy like that
have this kind of
money to throw around?
[BROSH]
I-I don't understand...
These are cookbooks.
What could they possibly
have to do with alchemy?
[ED] Alchemy's a
powerful art...
It can be incredibly
dangerous if misused...
In order to
prevent that...
[ED] Alchemic research
is always encrypted.
[ED] These are designed
to look like recipes
to the average person,
but they're actually
advanced alchemical notes...
Only the alchemist who
originally wrote them
can understand.
[BROSH] If they're
so heavily encrypted,
then how are you going to
be able to decipher them?
[ED] It's not
going to be easy...
We'll have to use all
our alchemical knowledge.
[BROSH] Wow, sir...
That sounds really complicated.
[ED] Al, there's a section
in here on green tea!
[AL]
Green tea?
Are you thinking what I am?
[ED]
Uh-huh...
t might be a reference
to the Green Lion of
metallurgic alchemy...
Do we have copies
available of Flamel's Codex
or Lambspring's Concerning
the Philosopher's Stone?
[AL]
Of course.
[ED] Alright...
take a look at this here...
[ED]
And here too, you see?
[AL]
Yeah, you're right...
And maybe here, too.
[ED] Great... We've got
a place to start...
Let's do this!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ED]
Why does this encryption
have to be so damn
hard to figure out?
[AL] Brother...
Maybe we should ask
Dr. Marcoh about this directly.
[ED] No way...!
That'd be admitting defeat!
[AL] So this is
a contest now?
[SHESKA]
Excuse me...
[ED]
Sheska!
[SHESKA] Thanks to
the money you gave me,
Edward, I was able
to move my mother
to a better hospital...
I really appreciate it.
[ED] Aw, it was no
big deal, really.
[SHESKA] Have you had any
luck deciphering it so far?
[AL] Have you found
another job yet?
[SHESKA] Anyway... you
two made me feel better.
It was nice to know
that even a pathetic mess
like me can help
out sometimes.
[SHESKA] So thanks
for that as well.
[AL] You're not
a pathetic mess.
[AL] I think that
the kind of dedication
you show to reading is a
talent all on its own...
And besides that, your
memory is incredible...
You should have
more faith in yourself.
[SHESKA]
Thank you, Al.
[yawn]
[HUGHES]
Yo!
[ED] Lieutenant
Colonel Hughes.
[HUGHES] Major Armstrong
told me you two were here.
[HUGHES]
What gives, Ed?
I told you to
give me a shout
the next time you
made it to Central.
[ED] Oh... something
urgent came up, sorry.
[HUGHES]
It's just as well.
I've been busy too.
[BROSH] They talk
to Colonel Hughes
like he's an old friend!
[ROSS] Just how high
up are these boys?
[HUGHES] We've had a lot of
cases to deal with lately...
And we're still
working on getting
the Tucker Chimera
situation settled.
[HUGHES]
Sorry...
I guess that brings up some
unpleasant memories, huh?
[HUGHES]
Anyway...
[HUGHES] As if things weren't
bad enough for us already...
The first branch
had to burn down
in the middle of all this.
[ED] That's been
a problem, huh?
[HUGHES]
A big one...
All our case
records were stored
in the stacks
at that location;
trying to work without 'em...
hasn't been a picnic,
let me tell ya.
[HUGHES]
What?
[ED and AL]
Uhhh...
[SHESKA]
Huh??
[ED]
Hey, Lt. Colonel,
I think I've got
exactly the person
you guys are looking for.
[SHESKA]
Well, I have read
the military's
criminal case records,
and I do
remember them all.
[HUGHES] That's all I needed
to hear, lady, you're hired.
My office pays well,
so don't worry.
[SHESKA] Oh, I--
You're saying you want me...
Oh!
Thanks so much!
[SHESKA]
I'll have faith,
just like you told me to...
Thank you! Thank you!
[HUGHES] Come on now,
right to work!
[ED] She may not be
thanking us for long.
[ED] How did you
put it again, Al...?
"I think dedication is
a talent all on its own."
[ED] Very smooth,
little brother.
Very smooth...
[AL] Well, it's
something I always think
whenever I see a
certain someone I know.
[ED]
In that case,
a certain someone
should hurry
and get back to work,
or you're gonna
have to come up
with a new
motivational phrase.
[snores]
[BROSH]
I'm awake!
[ROSS]
The library's closing.
[BROSH] They've been
at it for ten days now.
[BROSH] I'm impressed
they're still going
after all this time.
[ED]
To hell with it!
[BROSH] What did you
guys do to this place?
[ROSS] Don't get angry
because you can't crack it.
Throwing things won't help.
[AL]
We did crack it.
We cracked the code
and decrypted the notes.
[BROSH]
Really? You did?
But that's a good
thing, isn't it?
[ED] There's nothing good
about this, damn it...!
This is the devil's research...
It should have been destroyed.
Doctor Marcoh...
was right. It's evil.
[BROSH]
What's so evil about it?
[ED] The main ingredient
for a Philosopher's Stone...
[ED]
Is human life!
[ED] In order to manufacture
even a single stone,
you have to make
multiple human sacrifices.
[BROSH] How could the
military authorize research
into something so horrible?!
[ROSS] I can't
believe it. How awful.
[ED]
Do us a favor...
Don't speak to
anyone about this.
[BROSH]
But, sir...
[ED]
Please!
[ED] Just pretend you
never heard any of it.
[ARMSTRONG]
What's this now?
[ARMSTRONG] The Elric
brothers are holed up
in their room again tonight?
[ROSS] Yes... they haven't
been eating, either.
[ARMSTRONG] The fatigue
must be catching up to them...
They seem to have
devoted all their energy
to these notes.
[ROSS] They worked
so hard to decipher
those notes only
to find out that.
[BROSH] It disturbs me too,
just thinking about it.
I bet I'd act the same way!
[ARMSTRONG]
What was that?
[BROSH and ROSS]
Oh! It was nothing, sir!
[ARMSTRONG] Your behavior
is most suspicious!
[AL]
Brother...
You should really
get something to eat.
[ED]
No thanks.
Pretty awful, huh?
[ED] You know,
Al... it's like...
[ED] We try so hard
to grasp the truth,
but it always slips away.
[ED] And now that we
finally have caught it...
it turns out the truth
is too dangerous to hold.
[ED] I'm starting
to think this
is God's special way
of torturing people
who've committed taboos.
I wonder... If it'll be
like this all our lives?
[ED]
You know, Al...
There's something
I've been wanting
to tell you for awhile.
[ED] But I guess I've
been too afraid to say it.
[AL]
What?
[ED]
I...
[loud knocking]
[ARMSTRONG] Elric brothers,
I know you're in there...!
Open up...!
This is the Major!
[AL]
What do we do?
[ED] We ignore him,
that's what.
[ARMSTRONG] I know what
it said, Edward Elric.
[ARMSTRONG]
How tragic!
To think the legend of
the Philosopher's Stone
is built on such
a terrible secret!
[ROSS] We're...
we're really sorry.
[BROSH]
It's hard to stay quiet
when someone
like him asks you...
[ARMSTRONG]
Imagine the military
being behind
something like that...
Often the truth
is more cruel
than we'd bargained for.
[ED]
The truth!
[AL]
What is it, Brother?
[ED] Do you remember
what Dr. Marcoh
said at the station?
[AL]
Huh?
[MARCOH]
Look closely...
maybe you'll
find the truth
hidden within the truth...
[ED]
I didn't have a clue
what he was talking
about then, but now...
[ED] It's the same as
with alchemical notes...
What you can see...
on the surface is only
a portion of the truth.
[ED] There's still
more to find here.
There has to be...
[ARMSTROMG]
Currently there are
four operational
alchemy laboratories
in Central that have
connections to the government...
We can narrow it
down even further.
Marcoh worked in
the third laboratory.
We should start with that one.
It's the most suspect.
[ED] Al and I've been to all
the laboratories in the city...
None were doing any
remarkable research.
[ED]
Here.
[ED] What's this
building used for?
[ROSS] It was designed
for the fifth laboratory,
but it isn't currently in use...
The building isn't
structurally sound,
so it's been
classified off-limits.
[ED]
It's there.
[BROSH] Huh...? How can
you be so sure that's it?
[ED] There's a
prison right next door.
[BROSH]
Okay, so?
[ED] What was the
main ingredient
for a Philosopher's Stone?
[BROSH] You said it
needed live humans--
[ED] There'd be plenty
of condemned criminals
in the prison.
Officially, they'd be
recorded as executed.
[ROSS] They're using the
prisoners to make the stone.
[ED] Don't look
at me like that.
I don't like talking about
this anymore than you.
[AL] Prisons from
other jurisdictions
could be used too...
I wonder if the
government is involved?
[ROSS] Why do
I have the feeling
that we're getting involved
in something really
dangerous here?
[AL] That's why we
told you to pretend
like you'd never
heard anything!
[ARMSTROMG]
This has the potential
of becoming a political
nightmare before long...
I'll look into what we've
talked about tonight.
[ARMSTRONG]
In the meantime, officers...
speak of this to no one.
[BROSH and ROSS]
Sir!
[ARMSTRONG]
And you, Elric brothers,
behave yourselves!
[ARMSTRONG]
I know you two boys...
You were thinking
about sneaking
into this building and
taking a look around,
weren't you? Admit it!
[ED and AL]
We weren't!
We weren't! We promise!
[ED]
Yeah, sure we weren't.
Hmm...
A guard posted at an
unused building. Interesting.
[AL]
That is suspicious.
How do we get in?
[ED] We could make
our own entrance.
[AL]
They'd notice the light
from the transmutic reaction.
[ED]
Well, in that case...
[AL]
And... Up!
[ED] They're not taking
any chances, are they?
[ED]
Al... you need to wait here.
[AL]
You're fine on your own?
[ED] Whether I'm
fine on my own
or not isn't the issue.
You're too big to
get through here.
[AL] It's not like
I asked to get this big.
[48]
Sixty-six?
[66]
What is it, Forty-eight?
[48] It looks as
if we've got guests.
[66] Some daredevil idiots
came to visit, did they?
[ED]
Damn...
It's even tighter in
here than I thought.
[ED] I couldn't
get through this far
if I was regular sized...
Lucky I've got a small body.
[ED]
Oh no!!
I just called myself a
tiny little pipsqueak!
[ED]
There are lights on.
"Not currently in use."
Who are they
trying to fool?
[ED]
This is it all right.
[AL] Ed's taking
a long time.
[clang]
[NARRATOR]
There were once two men
who knew more of bloody
blades than human sympathy...
They snuffed out life, laughing
as their weapons flew...
Now, they guard the
darkness, hollow shells
of the villains
they once were....
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Eight.
"The Fifth Laboratory."
There are those
who find pleasure
only in battle, who feel
alive only during a fight...
They are coming soon...
with blood on their hands.