When I was young,
I was surrounded by the love of
my mother, father, and grandma.
I was so happy.
I wanted it to stay that way forever and ever.
I am but a mirror that reflects you.
Cure Blossom Mirage.
So please,
don't hate me.
And please, don't get rid of me!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Precures,
Transform into Super Silhouettes!
You won't ever be able to change.
Not until you can bid farewell to your shy, withdrawn self.
I will...
I will change!
Blossom's sure taking her time.
What will happen to her if she doesn't pass the trial?
She'll just remain as she always was.
The HeartCatch Mirage's trial is simply to be shown yourself as you truly are.
Everyone is afraid to know their true self.
It can be saddening to realize just how weak, petty, and shallow we can be.
But we are all capable of changing.
Rather than trying to escape the reality of who we are, we can try to understand ourselves.
Sometimes, that means accepting facets
of ourselves that we'd rather didn't exist.
But you have to ask yourself,
"What is it I want to do?"
"What is it I should be doing?"
It's something that we all worry about and stress over.
But from that despair we find our light,
and that gives us the hope we need.
Now it's Tsubomi's turn to face it.
Only she is capable of defeating her own demons.
If Tsubomi's heart is to grow stronger, then that is something she must do for herself.
I'm still so worried about her!
Yeah!
Blossom's such a coward, and so unreliable, and...
She kept on calling herself the
weakest Precure ever at first, and...
And... And she...
She's so withdrawn!
She's so useless without us to help her!
We'll just have to hope she pulls through.
Our beloved Blossom.
Blossom! Don't give up, you got that?!
We're right here cheering you on!
You can do it!
Oh desert seed, the Desert Devil...
Before the HeartCatch Mirage can unleash its true power,
I bid you to destroy it.
Cure Flower,
I'll be taking back the power the HeartCatch Mirage stole from me fifty years ago.
But knowing you, you'll surely notice my presence nearby.
Girls, the Desert Devil's on its way here!
What?!
But Blossom hasn't finished the final trial yet.
We are shy and withdrawn,
always relying on others to save us.
That's how we truly are!
I...
It's true that I was like that in the past!
But I really have changed since then!
No, you haven't changed at all.
I have changed!
And becoming a Precure cannot change what lies within.
It's gigantic!
The Desert Devil is trying to
destroy the HeartCatch Mirage.
How are we meant to fight that thing?
We can handle this!
We'll just beat that thing up before Blossom gets back!
Let's go, Coffret!
Aye aye!
We'd better go as well.
Marine Impact!
All right!
Don't give in, girls.
You can do it.
You don't have to look at me.
You can run away from me if you wish.
And then, you won't have to face your own weakness.
You can stay as you are. You don't have to change.
That way you don't have to admit your
weakness is your own fault, and you can keep
relying on other people!
Just stop this pointless attempt at fighting me,
and accept that you are incapable of changing!
I...
It's all right.
Mom, Dad, and all our friends will still love us just the way we are.
Even if you don't transform, and even if you don't fight,
they'll still love you just the same.
Okay?
I can't do that.
All this time, I just despised the
fact I was so shy and withdrawn.
All I was doing was hating myself.
But then I met everyone.
Make sure to protect the Precure Palace while we fight, you two!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
My friends, who are so strong and kind...
I love them all so very much!
It's because they're there that I can give my all!
I feel...
that I have changed, even if only a little!
I feel like I've gained the strength to create a new me!
You're the me who hadn't quite found that resolution.
The me who was scared to become a new person.
But I can change.
I will change!
You don't need your shy, withdrawn old self anymore, do you?
I thought the final trial was meant to power us up.h
Complaining won't get you anywhere.
It looks like we'll need to combine our
powers if we're going to beat this thing.
We'll just have to hang on till Blossom gets back!
Coffret, let's give this another try!
Roger!
We'd better get out there too, Chypre!
Got it!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
The feelings that got me here all seemed so half-hearted
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late.
But there's no turning back now
Aww, it's fine!
Now that we're all back together again, let's take down this Desert Devil!
I just have to trust in all my hard work, and take the first step
Okay!
Now's the time to take the plunge, ready, go!
Flowers, glitter bright!
So no matter how afraid we feel
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
We'll never give up, cause even though you can't see it
We've found a treasure more precious than any other
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
In the boundless skies of my heart
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
This melody takes flight
Flowers, dance for me!
My heart goes on, and I won't let a moment go to waste
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
And though my tears fall, slowly the seed shall bloom into a beautiful flower
Let's use a Fortissimo!
Okay!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Must be nice doing a Fortissimo with Moonlight.
We can do one too!
You wanna do a Fortissimo?
Let's do it!
All right then! Let's go!
In the sunny skies of my heart
Yeah!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
I soar into a higher octave
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
My heart goes on, and when it resounds with all of my friends
Those distant dreams can one day become reality
By love's gentle touch, and the light of the stars, we're all shining here together
HeartCatch Mirage!
Now's our chance to try out their new power!
Here's the Powerup Sheed!
Let's do this, you guys!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world!
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
There's something I realized while we were facing the final trial.
If we are to defeat the Desert Apostles, the four of us merely combining our powers won't be enough.
We each have to grow as people so we're able to stand on our own two feet.
Only then can we truly combine our powers effectively.
That's why we each had to face our true selves, right?
And it wasn't just a matter of fighting against ourselves.
We had to be able to accept the parts of ourselves we don't like so that we can change them too!
Right?
You don't need your shy, withdrawn old self anymore, do you?
That's not true.
If I'm going to truly be myself, then I need to accept my slightly cowardly side.
That's why I love my shy, withdrawn side too!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
To counter the threat of the HeartCatch Mirage, the Desert Apostles have let loose our strongest foe yet!
The fearsome devil that lurks in the darkness, Bossnacky!
If he's after us, then we're finished!
Don't give up yet!
Cure Marine'll beat him with a Blue Forte Wave!
Sorry, but I kinda lost my Marine Tact.
Whaaaaat?!
HeartCatch Precure:
Erika's in Trouble!
Someone Stole Her Marine Tact!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!