In this ever-changing world
What should we come up with?
I'm turning off the AC.
Okay, let's start.
Okay.
Playback.
Seriously!
The song gets harder when you make
the melody using a Vocaloid.
I really like this melody line you wrote,
so maybe we should
find a vocalist who can sing it.
I told you no.
I see.
Then I suppose that's it.
We'll just have to continue
making music on our own.
I'll go take the trash out.
Rupa.
Yes?
Are you wanting to try?
Look at this.
BENI-SHOUGA
WE MAKE MUSIC.
22,738 FOLLOWERS
If you're serious about pursuing
your dream...
BUDOKAN, HERE WE COME!
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
BATH HOUSE
How's your voice?
Much better.
Doesn't sound like it.
You two, come in the sauna,
it's good for your throat.
You won't last
if you wreck your voice every time.
For sure. Ow...
Does it hurt?
When this pain feels like home,
it makes the performance feel real.
Ow!
Still, that was a crazy show.
It was fun though.
Nina really let loose.
You went pretty hard too.
Pleia on the drums!
I'm Pleia!
Zing!
I can't use my real name!
Personas are important.
Pleia the high school girl!
I'm getting out now.
She's really obsessed with it.
- You mean, Nina?
- Yeah.
Is that bad?
It's not that.
Momoka!
Huh?
I'll read some of the reactions
to our show.
"Momoka really is Diamond Dust."
"Her new band's way more rock
than the current Diamond Dust."
Wow, they say you're cute, Nina.
Well, thanks.
Anyway, the audience likes
the old Diamond Dust better.
So?
What?!
You want to make a post trashing
the current Diamond Dust as posers?
That they should support us
because we are more authentic?
You don't want to?
Are you serious?
Do you know how many followers they have?
Just look.
20,000.
It went up.
And how many do we have?
500.
There you go.
So what do we do?
Nothing.
Just do what we've been doing,
practice when we can,
make songs, and do shows...
And then what?
What's the goal for our band?
Aren't you going to go to college?
I'm asking about your goals.
What a pain.
Don't ruin my mood when
I just got done taking a relaxing bath.
But I kinda want to know too.
I mean, you used to be a professional.
It's a little strange that someone like
that would be in a band with us amateurs.
Do you have something in mind?
No, not really.
So no goal either?
Nope.
I'm so ticked off.
I'm so ticked off!
You're getting rice everywhere.
What's her deal?! Every time I try to have
a serious discussion with her...
You like to charge at people too much.
It's like you're a bull.
Moo.
There's no way
she'll open up like that.
Then what do I do?
Make a situation
where she can open up
and let her do it gradually.
Liar.
I'm not lying about this!
But I wonder how she actually feels.
What is it that you want to do
with this band anyway?
- I mean...
- You want to beat Diamond Dust?
That's a high bar.
They're pros that have
an agency behind them.
What do you want to do?
I'm home.
Band. Goal.
How to become a professional band.
HOW TO START A BAND
Professional?
Yes.
You starting to feel ambitious?
It's not like we've had any offers.
I'm just curious.
It used to be that scouts
would come out to the venues
or you would send in audition tapes,
but these days directly contacting
bands popular online is the norm.
Is a talent agency that important?
Yeah.
You can release songs online,
but when it comes to collaborations
and promotions...
I suppose you should strive to reach
the indie band days of Diamond Dust.
They had about 10,000 followers
back when they were still a local band.
That's how they got noticed by agencies.
So it just comes down to numbers.
I mean, yeah.
Followers represent crowd potential.
When it's high,
interested parties approach you.
471 FOLLOWERS
It went down?
...not to hear
Look, it's passing us by
The city flows down a whirlpool of truth
Where should we float to?
If we can smile when we arrive
Then let's hold hands
It's not a dream
"I don't want to risk losing
what we have."
"I'd rather stay where I am than suffer."
There's nothing wrong with thinking that.
But in that case,
you need to take that down.
It's absurd.
Rupa, do you think it'll work out?
There's no way to know.
Close friends can end up
fighting and split up.
While incompatible members
somehow stay together.
But I think the three of them
are a good fit for you.
Why?
Just a feeling.
Anything else you want to do?
Considering we need to clean up,
we should call it a day.
That's true.
That okay, Nina?
Nina?
Um...
Can we start thinking about
outfits for our next shows?
I mean, sure.
You chose them for our last performance.
Yes, but I'm thinking about
something cuter for next time.
Cuter?
Also, can I upload the picture I took
of you earlier to social media?
Oh, nice!
You're glowing.
It will attract lots of followers...
Of course not!
I thought since you seemed into it...
Post your own picture!
Sorry.
I thought maybe fans
would like this better.
What if my grandma sees?!
You want to gain followers that badly?
It's important to draw a crowd.
Then we can try wearing
high school uniforms.
Call ourselves
the Shinkawasaki Girls' School.
It'd be a scam
if you wore one though, Momoka.
Just let her have this.
I'll kick you.
But if that will get us followers...
Are you serious?
Wouldn't that be the same
as the current Diamond Dust?
I know that.
But it's hard to reach their level
of success without going pro.
And for that, we need a strong fan base.
Since when is that our goal?
Because we won't be able to beat
Diamond Dust otherwise!
Like I said, when did it become
about beating them?
I keep telling you.
I don't hold a grudge against them.
It's me who doesn't want to lose.
Like I care.
Don't put your personal vendettas on us.
I know.
But I really don't want to lose.
Look, I get where you're coming from.
Good evening!
But suddenly wanting to go pro?
I know things won't immediately
work out if we go pro.
Nor do I think we'll beat Diamond Dust.
But I hate admitting defeat
and giving up from the start.
Because we're not wrong.
Medium bowl, no onions, please.
One medium bowl for me, please.
Okay, two medium bowls...
What?
Nice to meet you.
Girls Band Cry.
You two play music?
Let me introduce myself.
Hi. I'm Rupa.
And this is Tomo Ebizuka.
We've been making songs
together for a while.
I've seen this before.
People were buzzing about it.
The faces were hidden,
so it was you two, huh?
So cute.
Thank you.
Did you come to us because...?
A battle of the bands?
No.
To complain?
I know, we're the 10,000th customer!
No.
You're kinda slow.
We're here to scout you.
- The power level detector.
- No.
We're scouting you!
Scout?
Who is?
Scouting who?
You're poaching her?
No!
We're asking if all three of you
want to work with us!
- No way.
- Way.
We went to see your last live show.
No way.
The two of us talked it over,
and we decided we want to play with you.
No way!
Vocabularily stunted.
But we don't draw a crowd,
and our fan base is still small.
We're the same.
The same boat, huh?
But we still had a few agencies
reach out to us.
Wow.
Yes, but as we talked,
none of them really matched
with what we were looking for.
They just latch on
to what sells right now.
That's going a bit far.
At the very least,
they weren't a good fit with Tomo.
So that's why you approached us?
Yes, after seeing your show,
we realized you only sing what you want.
That you'd voice your opinions.
Really?
Were we wrong?
No, that's how I sang.
Nina really knows how to let off steam.
Come in.
- Excuse us.
Hold on, I'll turn the light on.
Okay.
This way?
Ow.
Don't wander around.
Excuse me.
Huh?
What's this?
- It's a lizard!
- Gecko!
I see your goal is to play at the Budokan.
Budokan?
W-What?
There's nothing wrong with that,
is there?
Nothing wrong at all.
It's really amazing actually.
It never even crossed my mind.
Yeah.
Is the Budokan big?
You don't know?
I mean, I've heard of it
and seen it on TV.
A country bumpkin...
Tomo's from Sendai though.
Sendai city?
I'm from Kumamoto!
What? Sendai in Miyagi!
Oh.
Do you guys want to go check it out?
What?
Why did we have to come here this late?
It's important to close the distance.
BUDOKAN
If we could sing here...
If we could sing here
then we'll be able to feel
that we weren't wrong.
We could say we aren't losing
to Diamond Dust.
I'm sure.
Budokan, here we come!
So, what are we going to do?
Let's call Momoka!
- Are you stupid?
- Why?
Momoka said she wanted
a bass and keyboard player!
But their dream is the Budokan.
It means wanting to go pro.
Do you think Momoka would agree to that?
Then what should we do?
Good question.
I think I'll tell her after all.
An opening.
Is that all you can think of?
Morality Monster.
But there's no other way.
What?
Is there?
You won't call me a liar?
Huh?
I'll tell you if you don't call me a liar.
Look forward and take a step
They're good.
There's proper top-end isolation,
and effective rests.
Right?
And they're bass and keyboard players.
Seems perfect to try making
one song together at least.
What do you think?
What are they saying?
They're really up for it!
They want to try jamming
together this Sunday.
Are you free?
Probably.
I'll send you the details later.
Liar!
It's a strategy!
- Which is it?
- Well, she's in and she's out.
What's that mean?
Just from what I could tell.
I think there are two different Momokas.
When she's making music,
she's serious and dedicated,
wanting to create something great.
She wants to see if her songs
can resonate with people.
But when she drifts away from music,
she comes to her senses.
Realizing she stepped down
from music once already.
I think she's wondering if there's
any point in taking this so seriously.
I see.
Who cares.
Can we play together or not?
I don't know.
But I feel like she'll give in
if it looks like we'll be a good band.
She's a musician through and through.
I see.
I understand.
Do we have to get ready now?
So annoying.
Huh? What do you mean?
Just do as I tell you.
DAYS LATER
Are you ready?
It's nice to play in a studio.
There's something weird
with this cable.
Granny?
Wait, this picture!
Is it real?
How did you get a picture with her?
Are you a fan?
Yes, Tomo watches it about
three times whenever it's on TV.
She always cries at the end.
You don't need to mention that.
Still, getting a picture like this...
Tendo Awa is famous for being
distant with her fans.
Awa?
Yes.
Okay, I need details.
Yo.
What?
You're late.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the bass player, Rupa.
This is Tomo, she plays keyboard.
You're from the beef bowl...
Thank you for your patronage.
Order something other than
a medium bowl and beer sometime!
Good to have you.
I'm Kawaragi, I play guitar.
Former Diamond Dust member
Momoka Kawaragi!
We'll get back to you later.
So what are we playing?
Can we play the song from our last show?
Sure, but can the two of them play it?
Yes, we listened and practiced a bit
before you arrived.
I'll be changing it up a little.
Is that okay?
One second.
I guess we'll give it a try.
Okay.
Okay, ready.
One, two, three, four.
Wow.
What is this?
The city flows down a whirlpool of truth
Where should we float to?
In this ever-changing world
What should we come up with?
Um, Momoka.
The two of them are actually wondering
if we want to be in a band together.
I want to try.
You weren't wrong.
Your songs are just as good!
I want to prove it to everyone!
A festival?
The first step is getting attention there.
There's an amateur section.
We apply, get selected,
play on stage, and make waves.
Then an agency would reach out?
Yes.
Music producers flock to festivals.
They'll come to look.
For a diamond in the rough.
We'd play here?
Diamond Dust.
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
I laughed, thinking it a dream
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
I can't even say that I'm lonely
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
Is incapable of making anyone happy
But still, I feel a growing hope
Moving past all of the lies
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
I don't care if I'm still the same today
I just want to sing with you
My emotions stir so often
I've been hated
But I'm going to keep walking
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
Even if I'm alone
I believe in myself
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing
Next episode, "I'll Give It a Name"