To people who are wondering why these episodes do not have the OP & ED:
These releases use ordered chapters to seamlessly include the OP and ED from separate files to the episodes. you can find the OP & ED from the 01-05 batch torrent from our the site: http://underwater.nyaatorrents.org
You're awake?
Let me out.
Name
What're you gonna do after you get out?
I'll go join up with Master.
Scythe betrayed the organization and ran.
He abandoned you.
It's not over yet.
I'll join up with Master.
If I'm unable to join up with him, I'll assist in his escape.
If I stir things up, I can split the organization's pursuers.
Stop the car.
No. If you want to continue the mission, then stay with me.
Scythe is on the run right now but he's still protected by Phantom.
The fear of Phantom is always with Scythe.
So the organization can't be careless in dealing with him.
If you get caught now, it won't work in his favor, either.
You've changed, Zwei.
Changed?
Yes. It's as if you're a different person from yesterday.
That's right. You're no longer Zwei.
You're Reiji Azuma, so...
You were listening?
You have a place to go back to. You have your true self.
But... I have nothing.
I am Ein. All I have is that number.
The only place I can go back to is by Master's side.
That's not...
I have nothing...
except the name Ein that Master gave me.
Ein...
That's who I am. I am no one but... Phantom.
That's not true.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Drink it. It'll help.
Didn't you think that I'd be gone when you came back?
You're reckless but not a fool.
The hijacked delivery vehicle was found. They said it was empty.
So we let them get away clean.
Scythe is your dog, so you settle this.
Yes, I understand.
You know this song?
Ah, sorry. Was it too loud?
What's this song called?
Hmm, what was it called?
I don't remember the title, but I often heard it in town.
Does everyone in Japan listen to songs like that?
Everyone has different tastes in music.
Japan is no different from LA.
Tell me about Japan.
What?
You got your memories back, right?
The memories from your life as Reiji Azuma...
Yeah...
It's me. We got the stuff as planned.
Have a safe trip.
You kidding me? The escape route. The transportation...
You're taking care of everything for us.
Once we're settled, I'll contact you.
I hope we can continue to have a good relationship.
She can't be trusted.
If we let our guard down, she could sell out the Godo Family itself.
So what? We're using that woman. That's all, right?
But it's risky.
Don't get cold feet now, Shiga. Be resolved.
I'm gonna rise to the top.
Reiji Azuma... You should go back.
Go back?
Yes.
Where are you saying I should go back to?
You know what I've been doing these past 6 months, don't you?
There's no way I can go back now.
But you have a past. You exist in this world as Reiji Azuma.
You, too. You're here and...
You have something I don't have.
You have something that can prove who you are.
Is whether you have it or not that important?
Yes. That proves you are you. But I don't have anything like that.
What're you doing, Reiji?!
Do you know what you've just done? That was your...
That was just paper.
The only thing allows me to be who I am is my past memories.
And you also...
You told me before about your dream. Your memories about colors...
Dazzling brightness and strong wind...
That's the memory of your homeland, right?
That's a vague memory. There's no guarantee that it's my homeland.
But it's your memory. You do have a past.
You have a real name that's not some number like Ein.
Why? Why do you care about me? You won't gain anything.
I don't want you to die. I don't want to see you die without trying to help you.
It's for no one. This is my own will.
Sticking to that is proof of who I am.
I don't need a stamp and pieces of paper... to prove it.
Driver's license, please.
Where did you come from?
From LA. We're visiting my friend.
Wallace Yang. 20 years old. You look younger than that.
Yeah, people often tell me that.
Who's that?
My younger sister.
Doesn't she look pale?
Yeah, we've been on the road for a long time. She got carsick.
Okay. You can go.
You've gotten better.
Hm? You mean the acting from earlier?
What're you saying? You're the one who taught me.
What're you gonna do now?
We'll keep moving, stopping from time to time to let you rest.
And when your wound heals, we'll go somewhere far away.
A far away place? Where?
All the way...
There's no way...
I told you... that I decided it of my own free will.
I'll go buy something to eat.
Ein...?! Ein?!
I never felt fear up until yesterday...
but I can't... My finger doesn't move.
Reiji... Shoot me. Take away my pain.
You're too selfish. What's the matter, Ein?
You used to be a lot stronger than I am.
That's not true. I was...
just for Master... Just for that...
Even if I turn the organization against me, as long as I have Master's orders...
But...
What am I... living for now?
I'm pursued by the organization so I just run. I can't even pull the trigger.
If I had died there yesterday... I could've at least died as Ein.
Don't say that. Did we fight all this time to die?
No. We fought in order to live.
I don't want you to die... for something stupid like this...
I want you to live.
That's all, and yet...
I'm pursued by Inferno.
If pursuers come here now,
which do you point your gun at, the organization or me?
Of course, I'll shoot at the organization.
I'll pull the trigger of my own free will.
Why? Why are you trying so hard to survive?
Are you telling me to live like that, too?
You don't want to?
But I m nobody now. I have nothing.
I have no reason to live nor a role.
Ein...
No, let's stop using Ein. Ein is just a number. It's not a name.
You need a new name.
Name?
A name that's not Phantom or some number...
A name for you to live as yourself...
Eren... It's Eren.
I'll call you Eren from now on.
Why Eren?
What does it matter? I decided that name.
It's a name for you to live as yourself, not as a killer or a puppet.
Eren...
Eren... It feels kinda strange.
Really?
Eren. Let's search for the past you lost.
If you find your real name, you can find plenty of reasons to live.
You'll want to live even if it has to be by hurting someone.
It may be still tough right now... but let's go... together.
Your favorite pet...
What're we gonna do if he keeps this up and takes Scythe's side?
Kill him.
I'll go get a car and cash.
I'll be back in an hour. How's your wound doing?
It's fine if I don't push myself.
Be careful, Eren.
Yes, Reiji.
Eren... The name Reiji gave me...
With this name, I'll...
It's not like you, Ein.
Overcome pain with your inner strength.
Master...
This is the last stop, Zwei. Did you enjoy your childish honeymoon?
Lizzie...
Looks like you were manipulated by Scythe, huh?
I have nothing to do with Scythe.
I wonder.
I'll have a long talk with you about it. However, I got some news earlier.
The subordinate I had following Phantom was killed.
Phantom went back to Scythe.
That's a lie!
Eren...
Why don't you spit it out already! Where is Scythe headed?!
I don't know... We were...
It looks like he really doesn't know anything as I suspected.
Leave the rest to me. You can go now.
You're stubborn, I'll give you that.
The microphone is turned off. It's okay to say anything.
Saving Ein and escaping together... Was that your decision?
You're such a fool. You helped the traitor.
You're considered suspect.
Going back to Japan is the last thing you should be worried about now.
But you still have one great option left.
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back...
What... is it?
You know how to use this, right?
I will kill Scythe.
Next episode
Finale
Eren... I'll make you smile someday.
I'll get back your natural smile.