High ranking positions in an aristocratic
republic are naturally dominated by aristocrats.
At the time, Rome was divided into two social classes;
patricians consisting of aristocrats, and plebs consisting of commoners and farmers.
I'm already bored to death.
The two consuls, dictators, and all 300 senatus members were aristocrats.
The senatus was the highest legislative
consultative body, and their office terms were...
Was that from Class-A?
Their teacher is Omichi, right?
Yes, probably.
It's definitely Class-A.
I wonder what's going on.
Omichi probably lost it again.
Is that Chitanda?
Okay, let's continue with our class.
Where was I?
The senatus part?
The senatus was the highest
legislative consultative body, and...
退屈な窓辺に吹き込む風に
The wind blew into the boring classroom
顔を顰めたのは照れくささの裏返し
That grimace on my face hides my tiny bit of joy
lce Cream
曖昧に頷く　手のひらの現在
I just nod my way through the life designed for me
描いてる自分は少し大げさで
Maybe I'm a little too pretentious
何か変わりそうな気がしているよ
It feels like something is about to change
心に呼びかける君のせいだね
You're probably to blame, for calling out to my heart
曇り空覗いた予感
It's as if I saw a glimpse of color through the clouds
手を伸ばそういつよりも力強い勇気で
Let's reach out with more courage than usual
光も影もまだ遠くて
Light and shadow are still so far beyond our reach
それでも僕らは優しさの理由が知りたい
But we still want to know the source of your kindness
今は誰の名前でもない
Your name doesn't define you
輝きの彼方へ 全部過去になる前に
Let's go find what lies beyond the light
見つけに行こう
Before everything turns into the past
Committing a Deadly Sin
Geography Prep Room
You were the one who suggested it in the first place!
Mayaka. Calm down.
Stay out of this, Chii.
I know you have some excuse!
Let's hear it! What happened?
I know! Mayaka—
Any decent human being would've notified me.
Would you like a cookie?
If you would have just contacted me, it wouldn't have been a problem that you wanted to cancel our plans.
You have a cell phone, don't you?
Uh, should I go buy some milk?
I wouldn't be mad if it was a favor I asked...
What's that look for? Pay attention!
Don't you know your place?
Chitanda Eru never knows when to give up.
Don't think you can get away with nothing but an apology.
I mean, you notice all these little things,
but you don't have a shred of kindness when it comes to things that matter!
You intentionally neglected to contact me because you knew what would happen, didn't you?
It was raining, the wind was blowing, lightning struck, and to top it all off there was hail!
Well, you wouldn't have noticed me there even if you did come!
Did you know I was wearing a nice dress?
It's ruined now!
This all happened because you—
Are you tired yet?
I am.
Take a break.
I will.
I wasn't trying to save you!
You get really mad, don't you?
Thanks to me, you just got a lot off your shoulders!
I wouldn't have been stressed in the first place if you treated me better.
Oh, come on. You should learn from Chitanda.
I've never seen her get angry.
There's no need to single me out. I've never seen you or Oreki furious either.
Fuku gets mad.
Satoshi gets mad.
Really?
Yeah.
I can't let it all out like Mayaka,
but I do sometimes.
I can't imagine you ever getting like that.
Hey, I'm a human being. I get mad too.
You just keep it in and never show your emotion to anyone.
He's not very scary even when he is mad though.
I'm not scary?
That's a downer.
I'm a little curious...
Maybe.
Eh?
Chitanda might plot something just to see him angry.
I'll look forward to it.
Do you get mad too, Oreki?
Oreki? No way!
Because he's a gentleman?
No, it's because he's a pathetic excuse of a human being who can't even get mad.
Hey, that was uncalled for.
Oh, see? I just got mad.
Houtarou's emotional deficiency aside,
Chitanda's ability to keep herself from getting mad is really something else.
I hope you can cultivate your ability to remain calm by learning from her.
Still, it's not something you can learn.
I can't act like her.
That's not praise, is it?
I'd say it's praise.
We're just making an analysis. I'm not saying it's good or bad.
Hold on!
Being unable to get mad is one thing.
Not getting angry can be advantageous.
Wrath is a deadly sin.
Mayaka should take it easy.
A sin?
The Seven Deadly Sins, right?
Correct.
She knows her stuff.
It's well-known, so you must have heard of it too.
Oh, right. Even I know that.
I thought there were 108 sins.
Those are kleshas.
If you say so.
Anyway,
there's wrath, pride, gluttony, greed...
...envy, lust, and sloth.
That's it.
Sloth, huh?
Why are you looking at me?
You're perfect then, Chii.
You're always serious and you don't eat all that much.
Oh no, I...
She can't possibly be greedy, and she's a hard worker.
Um...
And uh, she's not perverted either.
It's impossible to tell if she gets envious though.
They aren't praising her. They're totally mocking her now.
Let's stop this!
And I eat lots when I'm hungry!
She doesn't look like the jealous type.
Of course you would.
She's practically Saint Eru.
Chitandael sounds like an angel's name!
Uriel, Gabriel, and Chitandael, huh?
Please stop it!
She got mad.
Actually, we got scolded.
Sorry, Chii.
Whatever!
Look, you made her mad.
You were totally on the same boat.
I think getting mad is a good thing.
I mean, the same goes for other deadly sins.
I think pride and greed are important too.
How so?
Someone without pride might be a person lacking confidence.
Someone not considered greedy might have a hard time providing for his family.
If no one in the world one got envious,
then new technologies would never be invented.
I didn't mean it to be deep or anything...
I see, that's an interesting view.
You're saying it's all about moderation?
I just don't think the deadly sins can be directly implemented to our daily lives.
Then you don't think getting mad is a bad thing either?
Yes. If you can't get mad at anything, then you probably wouldn't find anything interesting either.
I can get mad, damn it.
If that's what you think, why don't you ever get angry?
Because it's tiresome.
I don't want to do something that's tiresome.
Chi-Chitanda got corrupted by Houtarou!
How could this have happened?
Kamiyama High is haunted by a monster!
A monster named Energy Conservation!
Wake up, Chii! Chii!
I'm sitting right here.
I'm just kidding.
She was kidding? And here I was, thinking that I've found my soulmate.
I'm sorry for being inconsiderate.
It's not that I don't get angry.
I get mad, too.
Let's see, for example...
I'll be annoyed if you waste food!
A drop of sweat fell for each grain of rice!
That's a farmer's daughter for you.
Speaking of getting mad, weren't you the one who got mad in Omichi's class during fifth period?
That's right!
How did I forget?
I've been meaning to ask you about that incident!
Time to go home.
Something strange happened?
Yes.
In math class during fith period,
I got mad.
Really? You got mad?
But it's sad. I don't know why I got mad.
Of course, I didn't have to get mad, but
something bad happened so I had to get mad.
Sad to say, it's bad because I don't know why I had to be mad.
What?
What I mean is... it's sad, bad, had to be mad...
In any case,
I'm curious!
Shousho
The term before Taisho
lce Cream
Our fifth period today was math.
Omichi was teaching the class,
but I think Oreki and Fukube know very well what he's like.
Allow me to explain from the beginning.
Let's see...
He came into the room almost exactly when the period started.
He stopped for a second and looked at the class sign before coming inside.
Yes. That happens all the time.
First, he solved a quadratic equation—
What? Oh, the equation was simple, but
there was a range given to the value of x .
Range
Then he asked Kawasaki and told him to draw the equation'S area in a diagram.
Kawasaki was clearly at a loss.
That's right. We didn't learn anything about calculating area yet.
Kawasaki said he didn't know.
So the teacher got mad and started yelling at us.
Tamura, a student who's good at math, was picked next.
However, he couldn't answer the question either.
That's when I realized that he didn't comprehend our progress as a class.
Others noticed as well, and it stirred up the class a little.
When that further frustrated him, our teacher harshly criticized us.
Yes. He was tapping at the blackboard between his words.
I think there were some of us in class who could've solved the problem,
but everyone just looked down.
He picked Tamura again, and made him stand up this time, and started screaming again.
That was when I stood up.
I asked him to double check our class progress.
Yes. That was when I got mad.
What happened then?
He flipped the textbook and mumbled, "Oh, that's right."
and made Tamura sit down.
Afterwards, he acted like nothing happened.
That's the type of teacher Omichi was?
Yep.
Did you get to experience his painful teaching after midterms?
You must have seen that type of teacher in elementary and junior high schools.
He's not a bad teacher by any means.
Besides, it's not Omichi's fault you failed.
Figure out a way to pass final exams.
That's what happened. What do you think?
Was there anything strange about it?
Huh?
Oh! What I wanted to ask was why the teacher made the mistake.
He didn't make many mistakes.
Yeah.
Omichi is tough on students, but he's also tough on himself.
I don't know why he would make such a mistake.
I don't know either.
Oreki!
I just don't know why he made that mistake.
Go ask him to cut his head open for you.
I only wish I could.
I see. That's too bad.
Give it up.
I'm curious!
Please help us figure it out!
Why do I have to?
I know you'll make sense of things just by thinking about it.
Don't make it sound like I'm a kid who just has to try.
Chii, don't expect too much from him.
He was a grasshopper in his previous life.
You can tell what people's previous lives were?
Great! That's the way, Ibara!
But I'm still wondering about the teacher right now.
Damn it, how bothersome.
I'm curious!
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
The
Calamity
in
Summer
He always writes a note after class.
What do you think it's for?
He was marking down how far the class progressed?
I think so.
He even checks the class sign before coming in.
It's a perfect system.What could have gone wrong?
If he makes himself memos, he must've wrote something like "July 1st for Class-A" on page 15.
Otherwise, he can't tell where they left off last time.
Maybe he mixed it up with another day?
Then he'd go too far back and never forward.
Use your brain.
She's got a point.
Can I ask you something that's been bothering me?
Sure.
I understand why you would be mad about that.
But I don't think most people would tell him off.
Why did you do that?
I was mad, but I don't think it was because he said something terrible.
Was it because people who could've solved it, didn't?
No.
Nobody would've wanted to answer the question in that situation.
Was it because nobody else corrected him?
No.
Was it because you pitied this Tamura guy?
I did feel bad for him,
but I don't think that would've angered me.
I mean, it's normal to scold students who don't remember what happened in the previous class.
Then again, now that you asked me why I got mad...
It's not easy to analyze yourself.
I guess so.
What makes Chitanda mad or happy...
I still know too little about her to know that.
What do you think, Oreki?
It's certain that Omichi noted class progress in his textbook, but he still got it wrong.
If he's gone too far, then the note was placed on the page after the correct one.
Your class still didn't learn the quadratic equation for area, right?
Y-Yes.
What if it did?
What do you mean?
Omichi teaches math every year.
Class 1-A last year must have learned it already.
Unfortunately, if you're saying he mixed up the year, it's not possible.
What do you mean?
New teacher editions of our textbooks get distributed every year.
It would be problematic if the textbooks were inconsistent, right?
Omichi uses the fourth edition textbook.
I didn't know that.
The useless information in your head never fails to amaze me.
I'm a database, after all.
Maybe he makes a lot of notes and mixed things up.
But that's not going to satisfy Chitanda.
Man, I don't understand how to calculate areas.
Drawing x and y on a diagram is tough enough for me.
I'll be doomed if he ever picks me.
Wait a minute.
Class-D is already on the area chapter?
Yeah.
Satoshi's class is already on the area chapter,
but Chitanda and my class aren't yet.
I see.
That's your "Eureka!" look.
Yep.
Chitanda.
Yes?
You're certain the page after the correct page was marked?
Yes. I think so.
In addition, it was written this year, and he made a note to remind him of how far the class has progressed.
Yes.
What if the note wasn't for your class?
What if it was the note about Satoshi's class?
My class?
Omichi handles four classes— A, B, C, and D.
Maybe he didn't check class A or B, but it doesn't have to be D.
What's so special about Class-D anyway?
It wouldn't be surprising to mistake Class-D for Class-A.
There's no way you can mix up C and A.
Huh?
He's being dumb again.
You can't mix up A and D either.
Omichi is a math teacher.
So?
The likelihood of a math teacher mixing up A and D is higher.
Huh?
Especially if Omichi wrote something like, "July 1st A on page 10."
Illustration: Oreki Houtarou
and "July 1st D on page 15."
What about it?
Illustration: Oreki Houtarou
How could you get that wrong?
When you mix up A and D, you end up with what happened today.
Illustration: Oreki Houtarou
Hmm?
Yes, but how?
Illustration: Oreki Houtarou
Math teachers would write like this.
Oh! Lower-case A and D!
That's possible.
I've been penalized in English class before for not writing them clearly enough to distinguish.
Oh, you too?
Well, it was N and H for me.
You're right. That's likely.
It's finally over.
A and D. I can't blame him for making that mistake.
I may have said things he didn't deserve.
I feel bad about it.
What?
That makes no sense!
It's Omichi's fault, so he totally deserved it!
I mean, you're so...
Calm down. It's almost late.
Let's get going.
What? But Fuku—
Come on, the problem has been solved.
That's not what I meant!
Fuku!
Chitanda wanted to know why she got mad,
because it was out of character for her.
She said it's not bad to get mad.
Perhaps she'd rather avoid it herself.
That's why she wanted to know.
Even Omichi may have his reasons.
Maybe she wanted to think she got mad because of her own mistake.
That's the kind of person Chitanda Eru is.
No. What do I know about her?
I may be able to predict her actions,
but if I thought I could read her mind...
Then I'd be committing a deadly sin.
That's what they call "pride."
Don't go overboard. Don't go overboard.
I mean, who knows how many times Chitanda has surprised me today?
Oreki.
Aren't you going home?
Yeah. I am.
Oreki.
Thank you so much.
You're always helping me out.
I'm definitely not enjoying it.
What are you two doing?
Aren't you going home?
Yes. We're coming.
Let's go.
Okay.
I guess I can finish this tomorrow.
Oreki!
It may be true for you, but think about it.
And so, my high school life was consumed by another day.
Pride is enough of a deadly sin for me.
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね　見つけてね
Please come and find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
芽生えてた温もり　暖かくて戸惑う
I'm at a loss to this warmth growing inside me
こんな気持ちをまだ　あなたは分からないの
You're still oblivious to my feelings
その視線には意味なんて別にないはず
I'm sure your gaze doesn't mean anything
だって友達にしてるのと同じ
Because you look the same way at your friends
明け方に消えてく　小さな願い星
The tiny wishing stars disappear into the dawn
夜の間だけの魔法
This magic only works at night
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
Next week: Identity Revealed.
Identity Revealed