(Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.)
Well, well, well. Have
you ever kept a secret?
I know that keeping a secret
is not a nice thing to do.
But, I'm not allowed to speak
the truth no matter what.
I have to do this for myself
and for people who I care about
and for something I want to protect.
Miss Layla, I completely
understand how you feel.
I completely understand.
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
It started raining hard. Let's go, Sora.
Okay.
Thanks to all you guys,
the number of visitors at our
park is increasing drastically.
This is my way of showing gratitude.
Please enjoy as much as you like.
Let's eat!
Who knew the owner was such a nice person?
You never can judge people
by the way they look.
I think he wants to say
"build up your stamina, and do a good job."
As I thought, you're sharp, Rosetta.
That's tough.
By the way, I don't see the Masked Star.
Eep!
If I remember right,
I think she was saying that she was
going to sickle and chain class.
Sickle and chain?
I see... That's too bad.
"The Amazing Resolve Beneath the Mask."
You received a bouquet.
I wonder if it's from a fan who doesn't
know you're supposed to be in London now?
It's from Yuri.
What?
Are you enjoying hide-and-seek?
Miss Layla, please hurry.
If you miss the six o'clock flight,
you'll not make tomorrow afternoon's filming.
I understand. Thank you.
I think you already looked
at the mail I sent you.
The Masked Star  shown
in the picture is Layla.
Layla is in the middle of
a movie shoot in London.
That is not possible.
Are you sure?
I heard the attendance at Kaleido
Stage is dropping these days,
and the operation is getting tough.
But I would suggest  that
you not stoop so low.
Well, sooner or later, you
will find out the truth.
Soon, the airplane will arrive
at Heathrow Airport in London.
Cut!
It was wonderful, Layla.
I want to check the cut you shot right now.
Father...
Are you in London for business?
Yes.
Since I had been thinking about showing
up at your movie shoot at least once,
this was perfect.
Maybe you're worried that
your darling only daughter
might have been mistreated by me?
I don't mind that at all.
Please train her without hesitation.
Father...
Then enjoy.
There's some guy talking nonsense,
saying that you're appearing
in an amusement park show.
Who'd say something like that?
Could it be...? Yuri Killian?
When the nonsense rumors start,
they're proof that you're a star.
You don't need to worry about those.
Is Mr. Dio off today?
He's got Theatrical Camp's
daytime performance.
When you have a roof,
I guess it doesn't matter
whether it rains or shines.
If it keeps raining like
this all day long, perhaps,
we're going to have a long-deserved day off.
Nope.
We're going to have a review meeting
and rehearsal for a new performance.
Yuck! You're a demon for stage.
I understand...
We'll discuss the schedule in detail later.
Rosetta...
Aren't you squeezing your
schedule too much because of us?
I'm doing all of this because I want to.
So don't worry.
I can handle both schedules well.
Thank you.
You want to buy 2,000
admission tickets per day?
I'm thinking about  giving away those tickets
as presents to the
audience at Kaleido Stage.
So for the time being,
I want to buy 2,000 tickets
a day for three months,
which brings us to a
total of 180,000 tickets.
And I want to purchase
those tickets all at once.
180,000 tickets...
It looks like this  month
will be a rainy month.
As an owner whose business
is affected by the weather,
this deal is a dream come true, but...
Kaleido Stage and my park are
business rivals, so to speak.
Will this deal come with a catch?
Yes.
But it's a simple one.
I want you to cancel the
Freedom Lights' performance.
They're our park's cash cow now.
There's no way I can just give them up.
Even without that Masked Star?
What?!
She may not come here anymore.
Don't worry.
It's nice to hear the movie
shoot is going smoothly.
The success of this movie
will decide your future.
It's very important.
That's why I selected the
project very carefully,
and gathered the best staff.
Yes, I know.
By the end of next week,
we'll finally shoot the big climax scene.
I wish you success.
Thank you.
She's not there.
What?!
The Masked Star is not there?!
It was just like Yuri told me.
Fired?!
Wait a minute!
That is different from
the contract we signed.
That's my line!
Listen,
the fact that the Masked
Star is not a formal member
is a serious breach of contract!
Really... I'm glad Yuri Killian told me this.
What?
Yuri did?
Nothing.
Get out of here.
Mr. Yuri...
Damn that Yuri...
I can't believe he's sunk so low!
I heard that Kaleido Stage is
losing a lot of its audience.
So I'm afraid that the presence of
Freedom Lights is getting in his way.
Just because we're getting in his way...
But, because of this, I
understand something well.
What?
We're still missing something.
Then what are we going to do now?
Are we going back to the life
of working part-time again?
I wonder if we still can make it to that one.
"That one"?
Vancouver World Performance Festival?
Yes.
Around the year before last, I
participated in their exhibition.
Oh, I know. If we get a good reputation,
Marine Park's owner  may
reconsider firing us.
Not good.
The prescreening deadline
has already passed.
Oh...
But with your talents,
I think they can waive
the prescreening process.
I'll talk to them and see what they can do.
What?!
What?
Please!
Okay!
Rosetta, you're amazing!
Really.
You're a big shot!
I don't want to make an enemy of you.
Okay. Let's call everyone and practice.
The reversed Magician:
the enemy's trap.
What?!
You don't need to  permit
their participation!
I can't believe they'd apply for a festival
in which I'm participating
as special advisor.
Oh, wait...
Maybe they're not aware that I'm involved.
Fine. Give them permission.
In short, you're saying that Marine Park's
show was cancelled because of Yuri.
Yes. Probably...
And I researched a little.
Yesterday, Freedom Lights entered
Vancouver's Performance Festival.
Isn't that the festival in which my father
is supposed to participate as a judge?
Yes. Yuri Killian is also
involved as a special advisor.
I have a hunch this will be bad.
I already cancelled the flights between
San Francisco and Los Angeles.
Thank you for everything.
You're welcome.  I'm on
your side, Miss Layla.
Thank you.
I hope filming goes well.
By the way, when is the Vancouver festival?
It's this weekend.
This weekend...
We'll finally shoot the big climax scene.
You were the best partner.
Thanks.
I don't want to lose.
Today, there was a new movement.
A local popular performance team called
"Z" suddenly entered the festival.
"Z," if I remember correctly,
is an amateur street
performance team. Right?
Yes. It seems an amateur team's
participation is very rare.
Also, I'm concerned that
their scheduled performance
is similar to Freedom Lights' performance.
Cut!
What's wrong, Layla?
Is something on your mind?
Sorry, would you mind if I
ask you to do one more take?
Let's take a quick break.
When I called their office,
they said that their performance
will not be affected
even if the number of registrants
changes on the day of performance.
What's this?
"Z"?
An acrobatic Performance Team from Vancouver.
The contents of their show
are exactly the same as ours.
What?
Do you want to back out?
Please don't give me that scary glare.
Because I'm part of this festival's staff.
What?
"Z" is a group of local street
performers here in Vancouver.
I scouted them out and suggested
that they participate in this.
I want to give an opportunity
to a talented group of people.
If you have confidence  in your performance,
you should have no problems.
Moreover, your opponents are amateurs.
I know you will never lose to amateurs.
The following is a local street
performance team from Vancouver, "Z"!
Wow...
They're popular.
This is...
It's the same as ours.
Did they copy us?
Not only that, they improved it a
little and made it more dynamic.
I will announce to the mass media
that Freedom Lights copied Z's
performance without permission.
Then their lives will be over.
It sounds like fun. I don't mind doing it.
If everything goes well,
I will welcome all of you to Kaleido
Stage under special conditions.
Sorry, but we don't want to be restricted.
They're getting wonderful cheers...
We can't afford to be beat by those guys!
Now what are we gonna do?
All right, I understand.
I will postpone the shoot until next week.
In return, I expect the best
performance out of you.
Now, the following is
Freedom Lights from L.A.!
The Masked Star...
Do you know what you're doing?
Yuri, thank you for the flowers.
Don't get in my way!
Miss Layla!
Well... What shall we do about the festival?
Layla Hamilton is not a
professional performer now.
Therefore, they're disqualified.
Layla!
Why are you here?
Today is supposed to be the
day for the climax shoot.
I asked them to postpone the shoot.
What?
I'm aware that I'm selfish.
But I couldn't just stand by and do nothing.
Why? I don't understand what
on earth you're thinking.
Sorry, I told myself that I
would never disappoint you.
But...
This time, I couldn't help myself.
That's just how much my
friends here mean to me.
Miss Layla...
And...
I realized that I still have
something left to do on stage.
I want to perform a perfect...
a perfect performance that
makes me fully satisfied.
I want to receive applause that
makes my whole body tremble.
And right now, I have a partner
who can make it possible.
Miss Layla!
I've not finished my last show.
In any case, make sure to
finish the movie shoot.
After that, do whatever you want.
Father.
How was my performance today?
Don't you need to run after your father?
It's all right.
It's a path we had to
go down someday anyway.
Miss Layla...
What?
Hmm? What? What?
Can you see me?
"Next Kaleido Star"
What? That's impossible. There is
no way you can do that maneuver.
And so, surprisingly, even
Miss Layla can see Fool!
This means...
The legendary great maneuver...
It sounds wonderful.
But, what kind of maneuver is it?
Finally, breaking free of the past,
Kalos ends his silence and
begins to take action!
The legendary great maneuver;
the details are...
The details are! The details are!
Next time on Kaleido Star, "The
Legendary Amazing Maneuver."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing