I have a memory that I have concealed.
No, it was actually something I didn't realize I had concealed.
I found it!
It's a book on magic!
This corner is the magic books section, huh?
But is this really the best way to find it?
We have no choice but to go through everything.
Yeah, we have to work hard to find a way to get everyone back home.
We need to do it for our beloved Negi-kun as well!
Right?
No, it might be that it was a feeling that I didn't realize before.
And it's probably because I didn't want to admit to it.
You should move up further Yue; you can get more of the books that way.
And that feeling was...
Yue?!
Are you all right, Yue-san?
Negi-sensei.
There was an emotion that affected Yue's heart. That was...
By Takahata.
By Chamo.
Master, Master.
Let me sleep a bit longer, Chachamaru.
I'm exhausted...
We have a problem, master. Please wake up.
What is the meaning of this, Chachamaru?!
It was already like this by the time my system turned on.
We've been transported to the magic world.
To be brought all the way here, that bastard Takamichi...
Let's go, Chachamaru!
La Lac Spiritus!
That can't be done, master.
Due to your condition you have yet to fully recover your magic powers, Master.
Magic can't be used.
It can't be helped.
Chachamaru, I'll stay. You fly out of here.
I deeply apologize.
I forgot to recharge. I won't be able to fly for today.
So you are telling me...
That we're stuck here for now?
Affirmative.
5 points.
I didn't say anything?
Maybe it's my imagination.
I have this feeling I should go rescue a survivor... or something.
Is that so?
5 points.
The trial is next Wednesday, isn't it?
We need to do our best.
Ah, what a relief!
It was good that Negi-kun was there in time to save you.
I'm actually ashamed of that.
Let's hurry home and read through this material.
Okay!
What's wrong, Yue?
Looks like I hurt my arm earlier.
Are you all right, Yue-Yue?
I'll be fine- this is nothing.
Let me carry it for you.
Negi-sensei...
You shouldn't push yourself.
When we get back, why don't you have Ako-san look at it?
Ah, okay...
Yue, do you like him?
Eh? N-No, it's not that I like him...
It's just that... well...
But you've been like that lately, haven't you?
Ah.
What kind of juice is that?
This is "karei" flavored.
Curry juice?
Note: Curry = "kare-"/"karee"
Jou-chan, lemme take a sip of that.
What does it taste like, Chamo-kun?
I can't quite explain it...
You want to give it a try, Aniki?
Okay...
What is this flavor?
I recognize the taste, but I can't recall the name...
Note: As noted earlier, Curry = "kare-"/"karee", but spicy = "karai," which, when said informally (as in, in the guy-ish manner), is pronounced "kare-"/"karee".
For curry, it doesn't taste spicy at all.
You've got it all wrong.
I didn't say "kare-" as in "curry".
I meant "karei," as in "flounder".
Huh?!
Japanese culture is amazing!
They even have fish juice?
I don't think it's even part of Japanese culture.
Well, shall we get going?
Alright!
Negi-sensei...
You're head-over-heels.
Right now you are in love.
Your eyes are different when you look at Negi-chan, mya!
T-That's not it!
I don't have any particular feelings towards Negi-sensei...
Oh hey, that straw...
... is an indirect kiss with Negi-san.
I-I-Indirect kiss?!
You could call an indirect kiss a smooch on the elbow or on the knee.
Indirect... kiss.
It's nothing you should be embarrassed about, mya.
Didn't you have a flat-out direct kiss with him when you made a provisional contract with him?
I-I-I had no choice when that happened!
Besides I wasn't the only one; everyone else in class did it, too!
Nope, you're wrong.
The one that the class kissed was not Negi-san, but a Chupacabra.
But when he was in human form, you personally kissed him yourself.
In fact, you were the last person to kiss him when he was in his human form.
In a good way!
In a good way!?
From that time on, and above all else,
You've been...
In love with...
Negi-san!
In a good way…?
Just like this...
Love Jui...
Note: "Koi" means "carp", but it can also mean "love".
How do I feel about Negi-sensei... ?
Note: Garfish in Japanese is said "kisu", but that can also mean "kiss". Hence the "kiss me" pun.
Check it out! I got a ton!
Why don't we do sukiyaki tonight?
Yuuna, you really like green onions don't you?
Note: Green onions = "negi"
Like green onions!?
Hey, don't you think it’s a bit chilly today?
You're right. Maybe I should wear some more layers?
Note: wearing layers of clothing = "kasanegi"
Wear more layers... !!
Chizu-nee, what are you listening to?
Tchaikovsky.
It's a recording by the New York Philaharmonic Orchestra in Carnegie Hall.
CarNEGIe Hall?!
I can't say it.
I get nervous whenever I hear anything related to Negi-sensei.
Let's try this one out!
Minamoto no Yoshitsune...
Note: A popular figure in Japanese myth/lore
Night on the Galactic Railroad.
Note: A famous classic novel by Kenji Miyazawa
What was all that about?
Minamoto no YoshitsuNE-
Note: These are the Japanese pronunciations of the two lines. (Can you see the emphasis?)
GInga tetsudou no yoru!
Ah, geez! Desu!
Huh?
Geez! Geez!
I've finally calmed down...
Negi-sensei...
Why am I hiding like this?
It's not like I'm going to do anything bad.
A four-leaf clover?
There was something about this in the materials I read last time.
According to the legend, with this you are able to evade tricks from evil fairies.
Oh! This would be perfect to give to Negi-sensei to protect him from evil fairies or other creatures.
What should I do?
My heart is pounding like crazy.
Negi!
Asuna-san!
Where did you go?
Today you promised you were going to help us capture the Bonge Bonge didn't you?
Huh? I did?
Geez, you forgot!
Asuna, when you say that, aren't you just volunteering people to help without asking?
But still, if he didn't refuse, isn't it the same as promising to do so?
Another heavy-handed move, huh.
And I was looking all over for you, too.
We thought you got caught up in something bad, so we were worried.
I'm sorry!
It's okay now, you two...
because we're all alive and kickin'!
Right, Negi-kun?
Here! This protective charm is for you, Negi-sensei!
Thank you very much, Yue-san.
I-I can't do something like that!
Give us a hand when you're done with lunch, alright?
Sure, okay.
Negi-sensei is alone now.
This is my chance!
But, what should I say if I want to give it to him?
Negi-sensei!
While we were out walking around, we came across some beautiful flowers, de gozaru.
Don't you think they're cute?
We brought this for you, sensei!
Ah! Thank you very much!
That's it!
I can give it to him if I do it that way!
Negi-sensei!
I made a fresh batch of steamed buns!
Would you like to try one?
Wow, that looks good!
Don't be shy; help yourself!
That's where you were, Negi-bozu.
Why don't you help me with some techniques, aru?
Wah! W-Wait a minute, Kuu Fei-san... !
Negi-sensei!
We made ourselves a new cheerleading uniform!
Look, look! Isn't it cute?
What do you think, Negi-kun?
You all look wonderful!
Yay!
Negi-kun's rather popular isn't he?
It gets pretty hard when you've got so many rivals.
Calling them "rivals" is kind of...
Really, it's none of my business if people want to be friendly...
with Negi-sensei...
What are you saying? That's pretty heartless.
It'd be mean if we didn't cheer Nodoka on, right?
Since Negi-kun is so popular, it puts Nodoka in a bit of a pinch.
I guess...
That's right...
Nodoka's got her eyes set on Negi-sensei.
Nodoka is my best friend.
That's why I...
shouldn't be falling for Negi-sensei...
Ah! It's a ramen place!
Ah, I'm hungry.
But I don't have any money.
Daddy!
Treat me to ramen!
I really wanna eat with Daddy!
Oh, that makes me feel warm and fuzzy.
Okay! I'll get whatever you want.
Hey, welcome!
2 bowls of ramen.
This is a nice place you got.
Okay! Coming right up!
It's really good.
He says it's good.
How's school been for you?
Been able to make friends?
Yeah!
Really? If you get bullied, let Daddy know right away.
Yup! Thank you, Daddy!
Here ya go!
Wow, this looks good!
Itadakimasu!
I'm so hungry...
Master, would you like one?
Don't give me that crap!
Note: These are sound effects of her powering down, and the sound of a plug... being plugged in and out.
Shobon.
Shakii.
You're rather interesting aren't you.
Much obliged.
Excellent work.
Now then, one more.
This isn't cormorant fishing!
Note: Cormorant fishing = method of fishing involving use of a cormorant bird to catch fish which is then reeled back so the fisherman can grab the bird's catch.
This is the set of profiles the bad guys had.
If we can find something similar between them,
we can figure out why they are after these girls.
Kaede-san was first, right?
Then Yuuna-san, right?
Then Chiu-Chiu-san, right?
Don't call me Chiu-Chiu!
I just did an analysis and other than being in the same year,
there's no real connection between everyone.
I got it!
The names fit together like shiritori.
Note: Shiritori = Japanese children's game where you have to take the last kana in a word to make another word.
Shiritori?
Well, here take a look at it.
Ma"na",
"Na"tsu"mi",
"Mi"yaki"e",
Note: She's misconstruing it, as you can see.
"E"incho
See? It's a riddle!
How is it one?!
Besides, my name isn't even Eincho.
Since its in England, it's in English...
How about angel?
Note: Angel = "einjoru" (she's making the "ru" pretty silent)
It's Yukihiro Ayaka.
There isn't a word like Eincho in English anyway.
Neither is Miyakie.
That's right.
At least Natsumi should be swapped with Makie.
Ah, it's a text from Chizu-nee.
Huh?
Natsuma?!
Hey, that's cute.
Murakami Natsuma.
That isn't cute at all!
Nodoka is my best friend.
Nodoka likes Negi-sensei.
So I probably just like him because Nodoka likes him as well.
That's probably it.
It's a bit tough to read through all this, huh.
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry Yue-Yue.
I zoned out, so I missed that.
What'd you say?
Oh, it's nothing.
Besides, I don't exactly have a reason to like him like Nodoka does.
Nodoka.
Yes, Yue-Yue?
Umm, well...
Nodoka, why is it that you like Negi-sensei?
Eh? "W-why," you say?
Negi-sensei is cute, honest, smart, and he can use magic.
Even though I'm older than him, he is so mature and, and...
But...
But?
You don't need a reason.
Eh?
If there is someone that you like,
I don't think you need to have a reason to like them.
My gosh...
Even without a reason, I do like Negi-sensei.
That isn't right.
Something like that isn't right.
Wouldn't that mean that it would be fine for me to like Negi-sensei as well?
Yue-Yue, what's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
You've been acting weird lately. Is there something bothering you?
It's nothing!
Yue-Yue, we're best friends, right?
We can talk about anything. You know I'm always here for you.
Leave me alone.
Eh?
This has nothing to do with you, Nodoka.
Leave me alone!
Yue-Yue... I'm sorry...
Wait!
Why am I such an idiot?
I didn't want to hurt my best friend, but still I... I...
Yue!
The patient is a 15 year-old girl.
She was found collapsed in a corridor.
Vitals are 54, 31.
Pulse...
is now 20!
We'll need to take a blood count, analyze her biochemistry, blood agents, and urinalysis.
After that, I need a CT on her abdomen and all directional photographs of her cervical vertebrae.
Sen... sei...
Exactly what happened?
World...
delicacies...
-noodles.
The other patient is showing the same abnormalities.
Umm...
how are my vitals?
He's dead.
What is the matter?
Nekane-san...
Something troubling you?
It's not something you can tell someone, is it?
That's painful to deal with.
It's even more painful when it’s a secret you can't even share with someone important to you.
Nekane-san, do you have a painful secret that you keep inside you as well?
Yes.
I wonder if you would be able to understand my pain.
"The king has donkey ears."
Note: This is a phrase based on the story of King Midas when he angered the dogs and gets donkey ears for his troubles.
What?
In that story, in the end everyone laughed.
But if no one laughed,
if you yelled out loud, wouldn't that be refreshing?
Why don't you give it a shot?
Don't worry.
No one will hear you from here.
But...
I won't listen.
You see,
I come here sometimes to shout.
Really?
It's very refreshing.
I...
... I...
... I
I'm sorry, Nodoka.
I... like Negi-sensei!
I like him!
I love him!
I really like him!
Love, love, love!
I really love Negi-sensei!
No matter what anyone says, I love him!
Master...
The batteries have been recharged.
Really?!
I'm not fully recharged, so I cannot take you with me.
However, I will go seek help.
No other way, I guess.
Proceed.
Yes, master.
Nodoka.
I'm sorry about what happened earlier.
Umm... Well... That is...
There are times when I am in a bad mood.
Yue-Yue...
Just kidding!
Ah, that reminds me.
Is that a four-leaf clover?
Supposedly this makes you immune to fairy trickery.
Nodoka, give this to Negi-sensei.
For me to give... to Negi-sensei?
It should increase the good feelings between you two.
From now on, that memory will be kept hidden.
This pure memory is a...
Se-cr-et.
On the other hand, we continue on with the attempts to halt the situation in the magic world.
Well then, what will happen...
The steamed bun was first invented by Zhuge Liang during the Three Kingdoms period.
During a rough storm that kept him from crossing a river,
he threw nikuman into the raging waters and was able to pass!
As expected of the steamed bun!
Next time... "Aiya? It seems like something is going to happen!"
"This may surely bring an end to the world!" by Lingshen.
Oh! Will this be the nikuman's debut appearance?
Achou!
How was it?
Is help on the way?
No.
No?
Wasn't that the reason you went?
Instead, I came back with supplies.
Why, you!
Well whatever, I'm starving. Hand that over!