Hey, did you see it on TV yesterday?
See what?
You have to ask?
"Exposed! The Amazing Truth About Lake Hamana's Giant Eel 'Hassie'!"
Oh, I saw that too!
As if there'd be anything like that.
"All ghosts are, when the fog lifts, is withered grass in the wind", right?
You're so boring.
He's about as romantic as a pinch of salt, right, Chi?
I must know the truth of its existence! I can't stop thinking about it!
Well, whether it exists or not, I just hope it's there today.
That'd be a lot more interesting, right?
Either way, it's just withered grass in the wind, isn't it?
That's so much like you.
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
When the Fog Lifts
The Kamiyama High School Classics Club is four strong.
So why are we letting this old bus shake our brains out?
Can I have some?
As you might imagine, it's more about the destination than the journey.
The Zaizen village is famous as a hiking spot and for its hot springs,
and we're going there for the latter.
My lifestyle dictates that I rest during summer break, and yet...
Thank you very much for helping find out what happened to my uncle!
Now that we finally have the time, let's all go to the hot springs!
C'mon, let's go!
O... kay...
They should be here for us with a van...
The scenery is really nice!
Um... Oreki?
Are you all right?
I feel sick...
I can't imagine anyone else getting motion sick so easily.
We were only on the road for an hour and a half. You're pathetic.
By the way, Mayaka, how'd you find us a place to stay so easily?
My relatives run an inn in this area,
but they can't take guests now because they're renovating, so we get to use it for free.
We're there, Oreki.
All right! We made it!
Oreki! Hurry up or you'll be left behind!
Greetings, dear inn! Well met!
Welcome to the Blue Mountain Inn!
Blue Mountain Inn
This one's Zenna Rie,
and this is her little sister, Zenna Kayo.
Hi there!
They're in sixth and fourth grade now.
You got taller ag—
Your rooms are at the end of the second floor!
Whoa! Hurry up, Houtarou!
The view's not half bad from here.
I guess it's okay to do things like this every now and then.
Though, if I were up to me, I'd rather come alone.
You? Traveling alone?
No way.
Don't forget, the only reason we're here in the first place
is because Chitanda planned it out and Mayaka used her connections.
Come and eat!
Dinner is ready.
You heard it.
Let's go!
Cheese?
Stew. Gratin. Cheese fondue.
Meat salad?
One, two...
Let's eat!
Save some room for dessert!
Is it cheesecake?
How did you know?
From the smell.
Amazing!
Is it?
He's just like Mayaka said!
What did you tell them, Ibara?
Let's all light fireworks tomorrow!
Sounds good!
I know, right? Dad bought some yest—
Aww, what're you doing?
S-Sorry!
Here.
Thank you!
It didn't burn you?
It's okay.
Can't you be more careful?
I couldn't eat another bite...
Satoshi went to take a bath already?
Well, I guess we did come all the way to the hot springs.
Where are you off to, Oreki?
Same place as you.
Where's Ibara?
She went off with the girls.
This is a bit random, but what's your sister like?
That really is random.
That reminds me, aren't you an only child?
As for my sister...
There's a fine line between genius and madness, and that describes her pretty well.
I don't think there's anything I could beat her at.
Though, the thought of competing never even crossed my mind.
But why ask me about her all of a sudden?
Did seeing the Zenna sisters remind you?
Actually,
I always wanted to have an older sister or a younger brother.
Wouldn't it be wonderful to have someone good-natured always close by?
I beg to differ.
Milady is far too good for this world, I fear.
If she pulled her head out of the clouds for one moment,
she'd realize brothers and sisters aren't all they're cracked up to be.
Oh, this place doesn't have mixed bathing?
Why would it?
Satoshi, huh?
Dad, Grandpa, hurry up!
Whoa,
it's a lot bigger than I expected.
Hey, Houtarou! Welcome to my domain!
This water is great! It washes you right through to your bones!
I'd rather not have bathwater mixing with my blood!
That's not even funny.
Well, at least you're relaxing.
Chitanda?
Oreki!
What happened? Are you all right?
He just got dizzy from the heat.
He's really outdone himself this time, I know.
He hadn't been in for half the time I had,
but before I knew it he'd almost passed out.
You're hopeless.
Sorry about that, guys...
Don't worry about it.
I guess not being able to enjoy anything exciting is just your lot in life.
That's so true.
Maybe it had something to do with my motion sickness earlier.
I feel sick.
Chitanda?
Are you all right, Oreki?
Not really...
You're still burning up.
Should I bring you a wet towel?
No...
No thanks!
Um, I should sleep.
Sorry to spoil your club trip.
Please don't say that.
We were thinking about getting together to tell ghost stories.
If you feel better, you should drop by.
Anyway, take care of yourself.
Thanks...
It's not even eight o'clock yet.
Drums?
Actually, we didn't really need to build a second wing.
The other room's open too?
There's a secret behind it.
A secret?
A gloomy customer turned up once, a long time ago.
He stayed in room seven in the original wing.
He required neither food nor room service,
and told all the staff to stay away.
But he paid in advance during a busy time, so it was convenient for them to let him stay.
However, that very night they heard a terrifying scream.
A scream?
In room seven lay the grisly sight of a corpse hanging from the rafters,
swaying with macabre grace.
Apparently, the mysterious guest had stolen money from his employer and fled.
I knew it!
Shut up!
Since then, many people who stayed in room seven
reported feeling as though something was there with them, like a lurking shadow.
Then, the ninth person to stay there...
What happened to him?
He suddenly took ill and died in the middle of the night!
No way!
Now you're talking!
Oh, shut up!
They called an exorcist and built the new wing of the building we're using now.
They had to stop the rumors from spreading.
So where's room seven?
It's over there in the old wing, right across from the window.
That room.
We live on the first floor there, and only go to the second floor when we have to.
Of course!
But listen, you gotta keep this a secret!
So old-style. So very old-style.
When the first winds of autumn begin their journey.
Beginning of Autumn
Hyouka
Oh well...
Oh, good morning!
Morning. Where are the girls?
I saw it...
Saw what?
The creepy warm wind woke me up at night...
And when I tried to fall asleep again...
I saw the shadow of a hanging man
swinging in the window of the room across from me!
It's not often you see Ibara panic like this.
It's a shame Satoshi missed it.
Thanks for the meal!
How was the bath?
It felt really good!
That's good to hear.
Rie
The mattresses were soft and fluffy too, right?
Yeah, I slept like a baby!
I see there isn't one with Kayo's name.
Rie
I didn't know you got scared so easily by ghost stories, Maya!
Ghosts don't scare me, okay?
But I really saw that thing! I can't handle something that creepy!
Maya... you really saw it?
I did, I did, I totally did!
Rie, did you tell them that story? Dad said not to tell anyone!
Oh shut up! It's just Maya, after all.
What's wrong?
Um... What do you think of Mayaka's story?
About the hanging man's shadow?
Well, I guess ghosts could be kept in this world by their unfinished business...
So you think Mayaka's story could be true?
I don't.
Then could my eyes have been playing tricks on me?
How do you mean?
I saw it too.
The hanging man's shadow.
Mayaka was moving about and she woke me up.
I saw it swinging in the darkness.
Oh.
I thought it was just my imagination,
but if Mayaka saw the same thing as well...
You just saw what you wanted to see.
Like we said yesterday, "all ghosts are, when the fog lifts..."
"...is withered grass in the wind"?
But if that's the case... What did I see?
That's right.
If it wasn't a ghost, what did we see?
How would I—
Oreki!
Let's find out together!
I can't stop thinking about it!
I'm sorry, but I promised Rie I'd help her with her summer homework!
Leave it to us! We'll find the truth for sure!
Is that okay, Oreki?
It's not okay at all.
Anyway, what I have to do, I do quickly.
Excuse me!
Well then. You said you saw the shadow in the room across from yours?
Yes.
How big was it?
I wouldn't say it was particularly big or small.
What shape?
I don't really remember.
What color?
I don't know. It was a shadow...
A shadow, huh?
So you saw someone's shadow, lit from behind.
I think so.
Lit from behind, huh...
At night, the Moon would be the most likely light source.
That sounds right.
The Moon was quite bright last night.
But why does that—
Chitanda, around when did you finish telling ghost stories and go to bed?
Um, about ten o'clock.
Was the window open?
It was closed, I think.
There's no way you could see a shadow through the storm shutters.
This is getting complicated.
I guess we should go check out room seven for ourselves.
That's wonderful! So mysterious!
I'm glad we came on this trip!
I could've lived without it.
No entry
Hey!
Wh-What is it?
Please.
I can't handle kids.
Of course.
Kayo, do you have a moment?
We'd like to go to the old wing.
The old wing? Why?
We're investigating that hanging shadow,
so we wanted to take a look at room seven.
Sorry, you can't go there now.
Rie would get mad at me.
Then just tell us one thing.
Do people still stay in that room?
No. In the old wing only the bath and the dining room are open to guests.
Then it's empty?
The second floor rooms are all used for storage.
Can I go?
Thanks! You really helped...
She hates me.
Don't worry about it.
Talking to a big guy like you must be scary for her.
It's pretty cute.
Is it a problem if we can't look at room seven?
Not really, but it makes things more difficult,
since we can't investigate the scene.
Ah, this brings back memories.
Rie
Reminds me of morning exercises on the radio.
I did them until a couple of years ago.
Until the middle of junior high? Seriously?
Let's check the back of the building too.
Did it rain last night?
Yeah, a little.
You'd need the shutters on both the east and west side to be open to see a shadow lit from behind.
Um...
Lunch is ready.
Thanks for the meal!
It really is great having a sister, isn't it?
Oh? You want a sister of your own, Chitanda?
Kind of.
Did you find anything out?
No, not yet.
We just investigated the scene.
I have a theory, though.
Oh? What is it?
So, um...
what exactly are you talking about?
I don't like being out of the loop.
Since when have you tried to be in the loop?
You've hardly been around.
You don't get it, do you?
What's the point of hot springs if you don't use them?
I guess...
Ta-da!
Well? How's my yukata?
It's pretty!
It's nice!
I finally got one at the start of summer break!
You've wanted one for ages, right?
I guess it's good for what it is.
What's wrong with it?
Take a look at the sash.
It's an imitation.
It doesn't look different to me.
Not "mutation". Imitation.
The bow is pre-made, so they just add it on.
I wouldn't consider that a real yukata.
That's stupid.
What's the matter?
Oh? So now I'm also being haunted by the hanging man's shadow?
Let's go to the hot spring we went to yesterday.
Okay!
The hanging man's shadow
is simply the product of Ibara and Chitanda's imagination.
It's just withered grass in the wind.
But there's still something missing.
Let's go back together afterward, okay?
Satoshi, huh?
You were sitting at the lunch table when we left!
How did you get here already?
If you slide down the cliff behind the inn, you end up right here at the hot springs.
He slid down the cliff just to take a shortcut?
That's exactly the kind of thing he'd do.
I can't think of an explanation that'd satisfy Chitanda.
Figuring out where the shadow came from was the easy part.
The question is, why would they do that?
What's up, Houtarou? Did the heat overload your brain again?
Did anything noteworthy happen last night?
Well, you passed out in the bath, for one.
Not that!
We told ghost stories.
I had more girls around me than I knew what to do with!
No, something more official!
Oh right, there was a summer festival.
Couldn't you hear the drums?
Drums?
I see!
The summer festival!
So that's it.
Why do you ask?
The hanging man's shadow...
I think it was a yukata hung up by the window.
Why would someone hang up a yukata there?
And why would they open the shutters just to show it to us? It doesn't make sense!
They didn't do that to show it to you.
Then?
She was drying it.
Her wet yukata.
She opened the shutters to let the wind through so it'd dry faster.
But why?
It rained.
That's not what I meant. Why room seven?
So that no one would see her drying it.
But we saw it.
No,
she wanted to hide it from her family.
Why?
Kayo was drying the yukata.
She was envious of Rie's yukata and wanted to try it on.
But Rie wouldn't lend it to her.
Why not? They're sisters!
Didn't you notice?
Her mug, her exercise stamp sheet, her ball...
Rie makes it clear what's hers.
She couldn't ask Rie to lend it to her.
But...
But Kayo wanted to try it on,
so she nicked it to wear to the summer festival last night.
It was at eight o'clock.
Kayo went to the festival?
I saw someone leave the house at eight last night.
Kayo wasn't there when you were telling ghost stories, was she?
No, she wasn't.
Then, as Kayo was having fun at the festival, disaster struck.
It rained.
It didn't rain for long, but the yukata was soaked.
Then she remembered tomorrow's fireworks.
Rie would definitely want to wear her yukata then.
And if she couldn't get it dry by then, Rie would kill her.
If she hung it up on the first floor of the old wing, her family would find it.
The new wing would be out of question,
and there's no way she could use the dryers unnoticed.
So she waited until everyone fell asleep,
and hung the yukata in the room at the end of the old wing's second floor.
But further misfortune would befall her.
The moonlight shone through the open windows and revealed the hanging man's shadow.
And her final piece of bad luck was that we started investigating that shadow.
She must've felt like she was walking on hot coals.
I bet that shadow back then was Kayo as well.
Kayo...
She returned the yukata early in the morning.
Unlike Rie, Kayo does morning exercises every day.
Returning it would have been simple.
I see.
Let's keep this a secret from Ibara.
Families are complicated, after all.
But then...
Those two don't get along very well.
They're sisters, but they can't even lend their clothes to each other...
That's pretty normal for siblings.
I always wanted one of my own.
An older sister I could respect, or a cute little brother.
I guess the brother or sister that Chitanda wished she could have
was, in the end, just withered grass in the wind.
It's still boiling...
You okay?
Or maybe there's more to it than that.
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: To the Preview!
To the Preview!