Where could that Perfume be?
If we still can't find it,
someone else may have.
That's it!
Kirara's on the cover!
She's cute!
The Hottest Designs are Here! Top 50 Tops of the Summer!
What Comes Out On Bottom?
We Test the Best Undies to Beat the Heat!
Like a Resort in your Very Own Home!
How to Flip Your Room!
No Allowance? No Problem!
Get Bang for Your Buck with Petit Price Jewelry!
The Newest and Cutest Sneakers of 2015 S/S
Amanogawa Kirara
She's been a fashion model since elementary school!
She lives the life that every girl dreams of!
I love her!
Oh, that's Amanogawa, one of our new students.
Huh?
Kirara's a Noble Academy student?!
L-Look at that!
It's the Princess Perfume!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
"Every girl needs her perfume."
No wonder we couldn't find it.
What do we do?
Make her into a Precure.
Huh?
The aura emanating from her photo alone is proof that she can become a Precure!
Blouse (Milky Farm)
3,980 yen / Milky Farm™
Dreamy Shore, Capris
(Fairy Drop)
6,990 yen / Fairy Drop™,
Rest: Personal
Kirara's popularity has been exploding
among teens, and our editors scored an
exclusive interview with her! We go
behind the glamour to bring you the real
side of the most buzzed-about teen model
in the biz!
—How is your life at school?
Kirara: Hmmmmmmm... okay, I guess? The rules are
kind of a drag, but I'm holding up. The uniforms are cute,
but I'd like to show my own style with them. Oh,
but the sweats they make us wear are total lamesville
(laughs). I still get a lot of work, though, so it doesn't
feel like a whole lot's changed.
—What do you think of the latest fashion trends?
Kirara: You hear people saying "normcore" a lot lately,
right? I mean, I think it's convenient since a lot of
simple, cute, yet affordable clothes have come out
because of it, but it defeats the purpose of fashion if
everyone just wears the same thing. Clothing brings
out people's personality, and sometimes even lets
people dress the opposite of who they are. I think
that's really cool. That's why I'm always pushing my
own style as well as trying to learn about other
new ideas. Fashion's kind of an adventure like that.
—Any dreams for the future?
Honestly, I want to keep being a model. It'd be
amazing if I could appear in a fashion show in
Paris or something. I don't know what might
happen or what interests I could have in the
future, but nothing's more fun than modeling
to me. Getting to do something so fun as a job
is just a dream come true! That's why I'm
aiming to become the next top model.
If something's that's fun yesterday is still fun
today, of course it'll be fun tomorrow!
Kirara could be a Precure?!
That's simply fantastic!
Starstruck!
Kirara is Cure Twinkle?
What are you doing?
You scared me!
I'm nervous! Who wouldn't be?
Oh, found her!
Bonjour, Amanogawa.
The academy's princess?
Bonjour. Whatcha need?
Pardon the intrusion, but I'm Kaidou Minami, second year.
B-Bonjour!
And she is—
I know her.
The girl who was late to orientation, right?
That was a laugh.
I'm Haruno... Haruka...
Haruno Haruka?
You've got two "Harus" in there.
I'm calling you Haruharu.
Haruharuuuu.
H-Haruharu?
Haruharu.
There's something we'd like to ask you.
Could you spare a moment?
I'm thinking right now, so no can do.
Ah. Then, perhaps during lun—
Can't do that, either.
Then perhaps...
Do you ever lay off?
My apologies.
W-We'll come back after school!
Yeah, sure.
Um, is Amanogawa still...
No clue.
Didn't she go home?
Really?
Then, perhaps her dorm...
She has work, so she's always the first one out the door.
We've tried asking her to hang out, but she's always turned us down.
Really?
Well, I hear she shows up a lot in Dreamy Shore City after school.
In the city?
Dreamy 5          Dreamy Hill bound
This is my first time going to Dreamy Shore City!
I'm so excited!
I've been too busy to visit for a while myself.
Then let's see the sights while searching for Amanogawa!
Whoah!
Good day.
I'm not your mommy!
How splendid!
That smells ni—whoah!
Welcome!
Wow!
Today's
Special
Dreamy Shore's famous marble doughnuts!
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Berry Chocolate
Marble
Cruller
Caramel Cream
Something the matter?
I've never really had these before...
Really?
This is yummy!
I've had better.
It's scrumptious.
Glad you're happy.
Is that...
Perfect smile! I love it!
It's her!
It's the Perfume!
Bloody Precures...
I'm gonna stop 'em from getting a
third one if it's the last thing I do...
Break time!
I think we can get a word in now!
What the?!
Dyspairvil!
Close!
Found ya!
Hold the phone.
What's the big idea?
You! Hand over the Perfume!
Perfume? You mean this?
Haruka!
Minami!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
Oh, more weirdos.
Precures... about time!
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
We'll use a pincer attack!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
I ain't givin' up!
Um, can we have a moment?
Wh-What?
We are the Princess Precures.
That Perfume you have is a treasure that we need to do battle.
Oh, is it?
I found it in my dressing room, so I
figured it was a present from someone.
This world is in danger due to some very bad people.
So we need you to joi—
'Kay, here you go.
Huh?
That thing'll come again if I hold on to that, right?
I'm too busy for those kinds of fans.
Well, see ya.
Whaaaaaa?!
We've got the Perfume back, but I still feel like we lost!
That said...
I still think Amanogawa should be a Precure!
It's a feeling I can't really explain!
Haruno...
A fashion show?
Can we go to this?
It's huge!
Thank goodness the dorm gave us permission to go!
Excursion Request Form
Mrs. Shirogane!
Please approve us!
Just return before lights out.
It's all thanks to you!
I'll stick with you until you're convinced.
Ten minutes 'til showtime!
Good luck!
This... is cute...
The Starry Sky Fashion Show is about to begin!
It's Amanogawa.
Splendid...
We'll now take a 15-minute break.
Oh, Haruharu?
Amanogawa!
You came to this?
Yeah!
I also...
brought a care package!
Marble doughnuts!
Can I?
Thank you! I love these!
Let's share them.
Yummy!
Now I can get through the second half no sweat!
Good to hear!
I've been preparing for today.
I'm thinking right now, so no can do.
So that's what you were busy with.
You really thought it out!
I guess.
I need to make tonight's show a success
so I can move on to an even bigger stage!
You're already planning your next show?
Of course!
Time waits for no woman. I can't get left behind!
The model Amanogawa Kirara still has a bright future ahead!
That's a wonderful dream!
I'm sure you can make it happen!
Of course.
Sounds like you've got a dream too, Haruharu.
I do.
Oh. What is it?
My dream is to be a pri—
Kirara, you're on in five!
Gotcha!
Sorry, I've gotta go back.
Thanks for the food!
Sure! Thanks for the tea!
She's amazing.
Amanogawa is way closer to her dream than I am.
I'm up next.
Nope, I'm stealing the show!
Lemme see that dream of yours!
I'm the winner!
I'll toss that dream into the cage of despair!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Another one?
A Dyspairvil!
Here, of all places?
'Sup. Hand over the Perfume.
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
They're here too?
Here's the Perfume!
That parrot talked?!
Oh yeah, parrots do that.
But I think I saw this poodle at the dorm...
I'm not a poodle, I'm the Royal Fairy, Perf!
The poodle talked?!
Whatever. Doesn't matter which o' you sods has it,
I'm takin' it!
You won't get the Perfume!
Dyspairvil!
Dys! Spair!
Heh.
You tossers thought I'd lose forever?
Hey, how about you beat it?
Huh?
I ain't got business with you.
Well I do.
You ruined my show!
Stuff your show!
Dyspairvil!
What?
Dyspair—
Dyspairvil!
Don't push your luck!
Hurry up and escape!
Isn't there a way for me to beat them up?
Dyspairvil!
You makin' an arse of me?
Yeah, because you're in the way of my dream.
Dream?
No matter what dream you got...
it ain't worth squat!
It's worth everything!
One day, I, Amanogawa Kirara...
will outshine...
every star in the sky!
Wh-What?
It really is the Dress Up Key!
Why do you have that?
Combined with this Perfume, you'll be able to beat him!
Then give it!
Huh?
Hurry!
Sure!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Th-The third Precure?!
Amanogawa!
Cure Twinkle...
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
Vil!
What're you doing?!
Here I go.
Viiiiiiil!
Do whatever it takes to defeat the Precure!
Sorry, but that's not happening.
Now! Unleash the Precure's power!
I know. I saw you do it before.
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Another bloody loss?!
I ain't standin' for it!
Amazing!
She's strong.
Sweet!
You're not done! Use the Dress Up Key on the ca—
Yeah, I get the idea.
Open!
The door to your dream!
It's back to normal.
Guess the show's still over, though.
Amanogawa!
Haruharu! And the Council Pres too?
So you two were the Precures.
I see, so that's what you came to me for.
Yeah!
That makes three Princess Precures.
Amanogawa! I'm so glad we'll get to fight together!
Huh? I'm not doing that again.
Huh?
Uh...
Er...
Um...
I just wanted to give that guy some payback for ruining my show.
Don't hold it against me, 'kay?
My schedule's packed for tomorrow, anyway.
I've got no time to Precure around.
Here ya go.
I bid ya adieu!
Whaaaaa?!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Amanogawa, be a Precure!
Well, how about you try my schedule on for size?
Go! Princess Precure:
Go, trio!
We're the Princess Precures!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Aomori Prefecture Kazuki (Age 6)
Kanagawa Prefecture Arisa (Age 12)