Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Have
you ever skated before?
Skating on the ice smoothly,
skate and turn... Isn't it so cool?
This time, I'm making the
first attempt of my life, but...
Oh my! It's super difficult.
Since I'm very good at in-line skating,
I thought I would be all right.
But I just keep falling
down and running into things,
and it seems I keep saying
things like "Ouch!"
But, unless I'm able to do this,
I'm gonna be beat by May.
I can't back down now, either!
I can't! I can't!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Anyone who stands on the
top will aim to be a real star.
But nobody has reached that top yet.
A real star...
That's right.
They say that the hearts of all people
who see that performance will be one.
But even I don't know what
kind of performance that is.
Sora, surpass me.
What? I can't...
You can.
And please be a star.
Show me you can be a real Kaleido Star.
When you become a real star,
I'm sure Kaleido Stage will
spread its wings wide again too.
Miss Layla entrusted me with Kaleido Stage,
and I still can't meet her
expectations at all, and yet...
Not only that, because of me...
Ultimately, it means Layla Hamilton
was also a lukewarm performer like that.
For him to say that about Miss Layla...
Anyway, I will work hard in order to be
acknowledged by Mr. Leon as his partner.
That's the only thing I can do.
I swear one day I'll make him take back
what he said about Miss Layla.
"Amazing Match on Ice."
These are my thoughts, such as
they are, after observing you all this time.
Maybe I've depressed you, talking about
this at length first thing in the morning, but...
Sora!
Yes.
Oh, good morning, Ken.
Good morning.
That is, were you listening
to what I was saying...?
Huh? Were you saying something?
Oh, well... If you're not concerned...
I guess it... might be fine...
Really? Then, bye.
You don't have much presence...
But in a sense, that could
also make you a gag character.
Hey, Ken.
What?
Do you want to pair with me?
No.
Have you seen May?
It seems she didn't come to the
meeting for the town girls' roles.
Oh, really?
It's a minor part,
but I thought she'd be all excited because
she's been granted special
permission to perform.
Well, May might not be that kind of person.
Then she could be in the middle of
special training under a mysterious master.
Who knows?
Then she ran away with
someone tall, dark and handsome?
No, she's not that kind of person either...
And I don't know what you're talking about.
Then I wonder what happened to her?
Well...
Leon!
Who's that?
She's a newcomer, isn't she?
She just called him by his first name.
May...
May, all cast members who play
town girls are in the meeting room and--
It's got nothing to do with me!
She's at it again.
Leon, come with me right now.
What? Right now?
I'll show you what I'm
like when I really shine.
What's she trying to do this time?
Who knows?
She said she'd show him how
she looks when she really shines...
But why ice skating?
Isn't that May?
Yes, it is.
Long time no see.
So, May is good at skating. I didn't know.
The way she skates, she's
more than "good at skating."
The ice fairy May Wong is back.
It's Mina Murray.
May's playing the role of
Dracula's leading lady, Mina Murray.
But, if I remember right,
isn't Mina Murray supposed to
do a Screw Spin using a trapeze?
Yes.
Even if she is good at skating,
it has nothing to do with the role.
But...
It's true, she's really shining.
You're the best, May!
Beautiful!
So, this is how May really shines.
Mia, change the script.
Yes. How?
Dracula will be done on ice.
What?
On skates?
Then you're saying that you're going
to choose me as your partner. Right?
Are you telling me that I should be satisfied
with the way you performed right now?
What don't you like?!
The performance I did right now was perfect!
You may be satisfied, but I was bored.
It didn't excite me at all.
I just like the idea of skating.
So in the end, we're going without
Mina Murray and now he wants it on skates?
This is deviating further and
further from my original image.
There, there...
Skating...
All right! I'm going to
challenge you at skating!
What?
'Cause in order to play Mina Murray,
I have to master skating, right?
Are you stupid?
Do you think you'll be
able to skate better than me?
Uh, well...
Unless I try it, I won't know.
Also, I want to give it a try.
She's not bad.
After all, she's good at in-line skating.
What? What?!
I can't turn!
Oh, my goodness.
This could be pretty difficult...
This could... This could...
Her performance level dropped
way too much all of a sudden.
That's not like you.
But I have to get used to it first...
Straighten your back.
Yes!
Put your feet sideways.
Open your legs.
--Oh! I'm going to fall.
--Keep your back straight.
Huh?
I'm not falling.
Unlike in-line skates, on ice
skates you slip less if you slant them.
I see...
Hold that pose.
I'm skating?
It seems you have talent.
So I think you'll improve quickly.
Really?
Who's that?
I have no idea.
My name's Meryl. I work here.
You must be from Kaleido Stage, right?
Yes, my name is Sora Naegino.
Are you competing with May for a role?
What? Do you know May?
Yes.
I saw her skating for the first time in
a while, but her skating is not rusty at all.
That girl could shine even on the
international stage. It's such a waste.
Shine on the international stage?
That's right.
When May came to this skating rink,
she was only three or four years old.
Once I saw her,
I knew May had the talent
to compete on the world level.
If she kept practicing regularly,
I thought even getting a
gold medal could be a reality.
But...
She had another dream...
A big dream.
Amazing...
Miss Layla is amazing.
One day, I want to appear on
the Kaleido Stage with Miss Layla.
One day...
Her desire was very strong.
No matter how hard I tried to persuade
her, she didn't listen to me in the end.
May was that enthralled by Miss Layla?
What's he saying is wrong?
What's missing?
Doesn't Leon like me?!
May told me clearly.
"I like skating, but I
like Kaleido Stage more."
I want to be a Kaleido Star,
a real Kaleido Star, like Miss Layla.
Sorry. I'm very sorry, Meryl.
I probably won't ever wear these shoes again.
After three years, once
I finish school, I will audition.
And, one day, I'll definitely stand
on the same stage as Miss Layla.
When that happens, please come to see me.
May's the same as me.
She's been inspired by Miss Layla's
performance on Kaleido Stage like I was.
Yet, Miss Layla retired.
So she must hate me because I performed
the legendary great maneuver with her.
If you want to make friends with her,
you have only one way to do it.
How?
Take a bath together immediately, and...
Would you mind not joking like
that when I'm seriously distressed?
Joking? I'm not joking.
I seriously want you, May and I...
Sora? I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
In order not to disappoint May,
I have to work hard and beat her.
Isn't that right, Miss Layla?
According to my dad, the rink will
be ready for skating after three days.
Then, Leon actually skates,
and he is supposed to set the
contents of the show in stone.
So three days from now will be
their last chance to pass the test?
Yes.
In three days?! Don't be rash!
Please!
Please teach me to skate in three days.
I have to beat May. By all means.
You sound serious.
Okay. I'll teach you.
I guess I have no choice but
to ask Meryl to help me after all.
Meryl!
Oh, May.
Meryl is somewhere around the rink.
What?
Not like that. Do it stronger.
Yes.
Meryl!
What is this?!
Why are you teaching Sora?
Is something wrong?
I asked her.
Because I want the skill to
compete with you on equal terms.
May. If you let your guard down,
you will be surpassed by Sora.
Surpassed by Sora? Me?!
That's right.
Sora is gifted.
She could be better than you.
And I'm the one teaching her, after all.
Nonsense! I can't lose at skating.
And I'll never lose to somebody
like Sora. I will never lose! Never!
No, do it more boldly!
Yes!
They're amazing, huh?
May's amazing. But I'm sure
I'm going to catch up with her.
For May and for Miss Layla!
Sora, you have a weakness.
You're probably not aware of it, but...
Sora's so amazing. She's
improving so quickly.
She could come from behind and win.
How is your physical condition?
Right now I'm in top condition.
I see. In that case, that's fine.
Sora has a weakness.
But she doesn't have enough
time to overcome it in two days.
I don't think I should say
anything unnecessary right now.
It all finally happens tomorrow.
I'm sure Sora can pull it off.
Oh, please let him decide
to let Sora play Mina Murray.
In only three days, she's gotten this good.
How is that possible...?
In order to be accepted by Leon,
technique itself is not good enough.
I can't say Sora's performance is perfect,
but there's a possibility that she could win.
I will not... I will not let it happen.
I will not be beaten by you.
I've not seen this kind of
desperation in May for a long time.
Wow! You're pretty good, Sora.
She is something else.
Go, Sora!
In only three days, what could have changed?
The composure she had at
that time is completely gone?
Because of Sora?
Interesting.
If you want to be my partner, come up here.
Yes!
I can't believe he jumped over there.
It's a superhuman feat.
Will Sora be okay?
What is he thinking?
In terms of the degree
of perfection, May is better.
Sora's performance looks like
she just learned how to skate.
When it comes to perfection,
it's not worth talking about.
But...
She possesses something.
I don't know what it is...
But I definitely felt it then.
Something strange... Something.
What the hell is it?
I will not be beaten by her!
I will not lose! Never!
At the same time?
Sora!
They can't reach...
I lost.
I couldn't be acknowledged by Mr. Leon.
Sorry, Miss Layla. Sorry, Mia.
She lost...
Why did he pick May?
Sora...
Does this mean May won Leon's heart?
Leon...
You're going to play Mina Murray.
Yes.
It won't do me any good
to keep moping about this.
The thing I have to do now is
to make Dracula the best show.
Niagara Diving!
I can hear it.
I can hear the applause they're giving us.
May, you found a good rival.
Grand Screw Jump!
Here!
Sora, you have a mysterious power.
Somehow, people around you are
influenced by you, and start shining.
But, in order for you to shine,
you have to overcome your weakness.
The fight between you two is just beginning.
But I'm looking forward to finding out
which one of you becomes a real star.
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (Here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
Master Sora, please train me rigorously.
And so, to my surprise,
Rosetta declared to Kalos that,
unless she can master the trapeze
in three days, she'll quit.
It will be a crash course!
Oh, dear. It seems she caught Sora's disease.
But since she's calling me her teacher,
there's no choice. I have
to do it. I have to! I have to!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Rosetta of Sweat and Tears."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...