The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
Bullying?
And really stereotypical stuff, too.
Turning right!
Now then, let's have a chat about those human
experiments you're involved with.
It was me.
I know it.
They know where I was heading.
I've found you, my love!
I don't need any excuses.
Or would you rather be
the material yourself?
Give it up.
Maybe you don't need a head.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Tarou Tanaka
It's always the important
stuff you lose, isn't it?
Like a brand new umbrella.
You never lose your crappy old one.
Kanra
I don't mind losing an umbrella,
but a winning lottery ticket...
You put them somewhere important
but then forget.
Tarou Tanaka
When you look for them,
you end up finding all these other things.
Kanra
Maybe we just think the things we lose are
more important than we would otherwise.
Setton
'Evening.
Looking for something?
Sometimes, I think...
When I'm asleep, maybe I'm awake there.
Sometimes, I feel that since
my memories got hazy,
my sense of passing time
has gotten hazy, as well.
How long has it been?
Since I stopped seeing myself
whole, even in dreams?
Here and there...
In the there, but not here,
what types of things do I see?
What am I looking at?
In the dream I have over and over,
I try to find out.
But the dream's always the same.
Ephemeral Dream
Celty!
It's amazing!
Last night, you said you didn't
have work today, right?
I just did the calculations.
It's your first day off in 265 days!
The look on your face is unhappy.
He reads expressions on
the face I don't have.
I heard that humans have dreams in order
to organize their memories. Is this true?
Well, that's certainly a sudden question.
Why do people dream?
Put simply: no one knows.
Medicine has a long way
to go in lots of areas,
especially concerning what
happens up here.
Everyone knows that you have dreams
during REM, rapid eye movement...
He's a doctor.
An underground doctor, to be precise.
But to be honest, I don't really
know what he does.
He's letting me live here, and it's thanks to him
that I can continue my job as a transporter.
Well, I guess the issue is that no one
really knows what "memories" are.
You listening?
I feel grateful for him.
And lately, I've thought that what
I feel for him is probably love.
But...
You seem to think your memories are
in your head, but we don't know that.
Of course they are!
Anyway, first let's change.
We can go somewhere.
I'll take the day off, too.
See? I'll turn off the phone.
I'll pull the interweb feed too!
I won't check my emails at all!
The whole day is ours!
Where shall we go?
Take your horse to the sea?
Or a hot spring?
I don't want to go anywhere.
Why?
If we're taking the day off, I'd like to cook for you, thanking you for all you've done for me.
Home cooking!
What do you want?
Let's look for a recipe.
I'm so moved, Celty!
I wonder what I'd like...
OK, thanks so much, man.
I overslept this morning, so it really helps.
No problem, young man.
I figured you'd eventually get
tired from the trip to Tokyo.
Times like this are your hunter chance!
Shoulder to shoulder with the lovely
lady next to you, sharing textbooks!
So what's up? You going
without the necktie?
Or did you just forget?
You OK?
You didn't forget your wallet, did you?
No way...
It's yummy!
It's Russian sushi!
Simon, you seen Yumacchi?
Oh, Karisawa!
Want sushi?
I have not seen him.
No luck, huh?
Big trouble today.
The owner got sick.
Dengeki Bunko's accel World comes out today.
But he is OK now!
The two of us went to buy it,
then got some tea and split up.
He took medicine.
But he could not go to get fish.
But one of the café maids came after me,
saying Yumacchi forgot his cell.
So we have no ingredients.
We are looking for them now.
What?
Don't attract customers then!
Hello?
Excuse me!
What are you looking for?
I said it's Yumacchi's...
Who are you?
Lost objects
Lost objects?
Write what you're looking for here!
Tell me.
Are you doing this all day?
I am asking everyone!
My phone!
Welcome back!
What am I looking for?
It's enough that Kazutawno's safe.
I promised Karisawa and Yumasaki
I'd stop looking into this.
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals...
They say they're secretly hooked up with the Awakusu
or the North American Nebra, Inc.
But I'm not gonna find anything by standing here.
Did you see Karisawa?
I have not.
I see...
Now, how about some Russian sushi?
Celty! Let's use a kitchen knife, OK?
This is great!
Great!
Good stuff.
Wait. Why are you crying?
Crying?
I'm just so happy.
It's truly wonderful.
These super-sweet sautéed and
simmered veggies,
the bitterness of the miso soup...
Something's wrong.
No. Your cooking is avant-garde!
Just like you!
That's not a compliment!
I get it. I screwed it up again.
Fine!
Don't force yourself to eat it!
I'm not forcing myself.
It's so good...
I said, "Don't eat it!"
What are you doing?
How's this thing work, anyway?
Listen, you've got a talent
for cooking. I know it.
Who cares if you don't have "watermelon cells"?
What? Watermelons?
I mean a sense of taste.
The brain doesn't have tastes that
aren't recorded in your DNA.
But you don't have to eat, and it looks like
the brain has nothing to do with it.
Cheer up.
Want to play a game?
Don't treat me like a kid!
That pisses me off more than anything.
I'm not.
You do teach me a lot of things,
but some of the hazy memories I have
date back a hundred years ago.
And my head has more...
Do you need memories from
hundreds of years ago?
What do you mean?
It's like I'm always saying.
You're fine the way you are.
What do you know?
I feel like I'm going to
forget my own face!
Wait! I'm sorry!
Celty!
You're back!
You need to keep your phone on, Doctor.
We have a patient in a critical condition, and we couldn't reach you.
Sonohara, is something wrong?
They're not here.
They're not?
What?
What did you lose this time, Mikado?
Sonohara's shoes are gone.
Again?
Man, people need to get a life.
I've got a good idea who's doing this stuff.
Kida...
OK!
Wait, Kida!
Kida was kinda scary.
He's not normally like this.
You think?
He ran off. That guy...
When I was a kid, I used to
lose things all the time.
I'd always cry, "I can't
find it! I can't find it!"
And my mom would help me look.
Your mom's nice.
Yeah.
My mom and dad both.
It's OK.
I'll just go home.
Thank you, Ryuugamine,
for looking with me.
Give up on whoever it is, Kida.
No. She went home.
No, I don't.
Me?
I'm still looking, of course.
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
There they are!
What am I doing?
Weird, huh?
I can't remember at all.
Empty lots are weird, aren't they?
Once everything's gone, you can't
remember what was there.
Used to be something here, right?
For Sale
Something pretty big.
What am I doing?
I get mad when Shinra tells me
to stop looking for my head.
But doing a job, making friends...
Is it like I think I'm human?
Didn't you want to talk to
me about something?
I remember!
It was a long, thin, blue building, wasn't it?
Oh, that old, crappy one!
There was an elderly lady who sold
cigarettes on the first floor.
Nice work, transporter.
But I'm sure I can sense
my head in this town.
Hello, how are you?
Me?
I am searching for beautiful Japanese.
Tell me what it is you are
looking for in your heart.
Um... Can I see that?
OK!
I love you
Hanejima Yuuhei
My cat that ran away
A job
Yumacchi - I'll wait for you on
the first floor of Tora no Ana
I wonder if she met him.
Head
I looked for a lot of things today.
And I found some, and I didn't find some.
His bag was gone, so I thought
he was at work.
But...
Something felt unusual.
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals Kanto-area Laboratory
Fireworks?
Yeah. They were going nuts.
It took several people to put him down.
All for fireworks?
Man, your staff is harsh.
It causes problems.
He was talking nonsense.
Said his girlfriend was kidnapped,
and she could only remember this place.
Demanded to know what we did to her.
That's not nonsense. It's the truth.
Can you make it
so he won't remember anything about us
when he wakes up, Doctor?
There's no easy way to erase
memories like that.
And I'll remember this kid.
We'll send him back.
Dunno whether to his
house or not, though.
Doctor... The chief and
I, we both trust you.
You're keeping our big secret, after all.
That's right. You're living with quite
a strange houseguest, aren't you?
At that point,
I had forgotten...
About my head...
And the memories of hundreds of years
of being a Dullahan inside it.
I wasn't thinking of anything,
just... just...
Hey, would you come with me?
If I ask for two plates,
the restaurant won't complain.
I know a good place.
Please, Celty!
I don't like eating alone.
What is this bizarre dish?
Fried chicken sushi, cheese sushi, mabo
sushi, prosciutto sushi,
and this is sour cream sushi!
Those things shouldn't be
made into sushi!
What?
It's a special set!
It's a great deal!
And a fortune cookie for dessert? Sheesh.
It's got a fortune inside, you see.
I'll open it.
This is yours.
Lost and Found Object
Let me see.
This means you'll find what
you're looking for.
I don't know if I like you
quite that happy...
Unrequited Love
I'm so happy, Shinra!
What's yours?
It didn't have one.
I can't cry.
When I'm sad here,
does my head weep there?
Connections
Thank you.
I hope not.
I hope it's smiling.
What's wrong?
You're still scared...
No one's here.
We're alone.
Do you think you can remember anything?
You don't have to.
I told you.
I don't need your past or your future.
Just you, as you are now.
You and I, right now, are eternity.
I love you, Celty.
That night, for the first time in a long while,
I had a dream of when I was whole.
I am here
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Love and Cherish
My love is different.
It isn't like the love that only seeks and asks.
It's a more perfect thing.
Next time:
Love and Cherish.
I'm what Seiji needs.