She's so magnificent...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Oh, she's adorable!
Tralalala!
She sounds so elegant.
She was!
And the melody she played was simply splendid!
Haruka, you're interested in violins now?
Yeah!
Violins...
are so princessy!
Minamin, do you play?
Yes.
I'd love to listen!
My violin's currently out for repairs.
But I'm picking it up on Sunday, so you can tag along.
Thanks!
On a Blue Note
The Black Princess Appears!
You play wonderfully.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Nishikido also gives violin lessons.
He taught me to play as well.
You can make violins and play them? That's amazing!
What about you, Haruka? You like violins, no?
I do!
The other day, I met a magnificent violinist.
Her song still gives me shivers!
It seems it struck a chord.
A chord?
A player's heart is resonated by their violin.
A heart filled with joy will play a cheerful tune,
while a heart clouded in sorrow will play somber refrain.
And on occasion...
it can strike a chord deep within a listener's heart.
I want to learn to play the violin!
But do you have a violin?
Uh...
Okay, maybe not right away, but one day!
You should play as soon as the mood strikes you.
That's the quickest way to improve.
Feel free to have whichever one you like.
Huh?!
These all belong to me, after all.
But I...
Don't be shy.
Think of it as my gift to celebrate your first step on the road toward mastering the violin.
Thank you very much!
Good for you, Haruka!
Yeah!
Now, which will you choose?
Let's see...
This one!
Oh...
Wasn't that...
Why that one?
I just... felt it call out to me.
It looked so brilliant to me!
That's the first violin I ever made.
You told me before that you
put your dreams into making it.
I couldn't take something so valuable!
I don't mind.
I'm sure it'd be happier being played than being left on that table.
Take it.
Thank you so much!
I'll treat it well!
Dreamy 6                             Noble Academy bound
Bonjour, tout le monde!
Bonjour!
Teach me to play the violin!
Le violon?
D'accord!
Prince Kanata was taught by none other than moi, so worry not!
You taught Kanata?!
Oui!
His play was beautiful indeed...
I'll do my best!
Now, let's commençons le lesson!
Let's start with the scales.
Minamin, set the stage!
If you'd please!
It sounds beautiful!
I'll go next.
How was that?
You can play violin?
I've played a few times before.
Now then, Princesse Haruka.
Okay!
Play like she did...
Noooooon!
Tu will start with the absolute basics...
Okay...
I'm sure you can do it!
You've already learned ballet and tennis.
Thanks.
This song...
Haruka?
Haruharu?
Is that who Haruka was talking about?
Excuse me!
You're a magnificent violinist!
I started practicing so I could play as well as you!
But... it's not going so well.
Close your eyes.
Now close your heart... and play.
My heart?
Close my heart and play...
I did it!
Violins aren't meant to be played with heart.
Play with refinement, majesty, and elegance.
With refinement, majesty, and elegance...
Who was she?
She's definitely no ordinary musician.
At this rate, I shall meet Close's fate.
There must be something...
Who goes?
Beautiful...
Huh?
Commoners meet naught but doom!
Silence.
What do you make of the Princess Precures,
Twilight?
Those imposters are princesses in name only...
Mother.
Mother?
Tree updo!
Dreamy 5          Dreamy Shore bound
Who was she?
She was scary...
How?
She helped me play violin,
so I'm sure she's a good person.
But there's something odd about her.
Her song was certainly beautiful, but...
Close your heart...
Play with refinement, majesty, and elegance...
You've certainly gotten a lot better...
but the tone just doesn't sound like you.
If I can't feel your heart in it,
then it can't strike a chord in mine.
A third rate violinist playing a third rate violin...
can't hope to do any better.
Shut!
If you're with one of Dysdark's men...
Then you must be on their side.
Hey!
I know I'm not great,
but Mr. Nishikido's violin is splendid!
A pity.
What are you...
Impudence!
This dazzling figure before you...
is the daughter of the great witch Dyspear and the rightful heir to her throne!
She is none other than Princess Twilight!
Princess Twilight?
Dyspear's...
Daughter?!
The princess... of Dysdark?
Princess Precures, I refuse to
accept your claims of nobility.
No amount of endeavor can make one a princess.
I suggest you learn your place.
A black Key!
Is that a Dress Up Key?
No, not quite!
Then what...
The power... it flows within me!
What in the world...
Mr. Nishikido, run away!
Now, show me your dream.
Passing the wonders of the violin on to a new generation.
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
This one looks way more evil than the others!
This is Princess Twilight's power!
Mr. Nishikido...
Yui, get to somewhere safe!
Be careful.
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Your charade is over.
Now begone.
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil...
Dyspairviiiiiiiil!
It's nothing like the Dyspairvils we fought before!
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
Go!
Dyspairvil!
Flora!
Dyspairvil...
Why?
You taught me to play violin!
Only on a lark.
Hearing a false princess eke out a cacophony on that crudely cobbled violin...
was such a delight.
That violin was built with a splendid dream!
Dreams are but illusions to sate the pitiful masses.
With refinement, majesty, and elegance...
A true princess like myself wants for nothing, and so needs not dream.
You're but a false princess clinging to her dream...
and an eyesore.
Dyspairvil!
Are you okay?
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Sadly for you, it doesn't matter how strong you become.
We're not losing to someone
who makes fun of our dreams!
Yeah!
Dreams aren't illusions!
So we'll fight!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
To defend everyone's dreams!
Dyspairvil!
Rose!
Dance, O roses!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
Dyspairvil!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Even with the power that Princess Twilight bestowed upon me...
There's no need to rush.
Please wait!
A black... princess...
Open!
The door to your dream!
Haruka, try once more.
But this time, play from your heart.
Yeah, try thinking about flowers while playing.
Oh, imagining flowers? I'll try it!
I'll keep practicing!
This violin could use one more dream... my own!
'Kay, a black princess?
No more slackin' off, 'kay?
She's so beautiful!
Just as the sun sets upon the land and dusk engulfs the sky...
I'll use this black key to drown the world in despair.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Hooray, I get to see my family again!
Indeed, today is Noble Academy's Family Day!
My little sister's coming too!
You have a sister?
Yeah! She's cute and we love each other!
But your sister seems angry...
Whaaaa?!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Form of Love!
The Haruno Family Dream!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Tokyo - Uta (Age 5)
Aichi Prefecture - Kanami (Age 4)