It's been a few days since I came to Tokyo...
And this is the sight I wake up to.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Morning.
I wrote my name on that.
Cheapass.
What's the harm?
FATHER'S FARM YOGHURT DRINK (NINA)
I've got a hangover. Let's go halfsies.
Not happening.
I asked you so many times if you wanted to buy your own
at the convenience store last night.
I was drunk.
So did you manage to get in touch?
Not yet.
It's tricky to move back into a place you've just left.
- What about your job?
- Also TBC.
I have to head out today, you know.
Three Creatures of the Night
TL note: reference to a song by
Yura Yura Teikoku https://youtu.be/n_dk8ChdCA8
This looks more like a hospital than a school.
It's a prep school.
Do you have class every day?
No way. I don't have that kind of money.
ADMISSION FORM
I have to study hard and get into a good university.
Oh, you want to go to uni?
I don't care about uni all that much,
but life as a high school dropout will be tough.
Yeah, that's true.
Shallow folk will look down on you for it.
Well, whatever. I won't pry.
All's good as long as you can practice in your spare time.
You'll be free on weeknights and Saturdays, right?
Then we just have to think about what shifts you take.
Hang on a minute.
A band?
- Isn't that what you said?
- I never said that.
Sure you did.
"Let's flip 'em off together."
Don't go flipping everyone off like that.
Ouch.
I didn't mean I was going to sing.
I was talking about our respective lives.
Studies for me, music for you.
What, really?
No wonder something felt off about it.
I was just as surprised.
It's pretty busy at this hour, huh?
Spoken like a real bumpkin.
Shut up.
But hey, studying is all well and good...
But don't you want to try being in a band, too?
I could never.
Look, I won't ask you to play an instrument.
I think you'd make a good vocalist.
Huh? Vocalist?
You've got a great voice, and more importantly
you've got the heart.
Who, me?
Yeah.
The way I see it,
bands are where people with pent up feelings get together.
Like, "I wanna fall in love!"
Or "fuck this world!"
Or "the feels, man!"
Or "fuck those self-centered pricks!"
Weren't you going to go solo?
That was the plan, but I do love being in a band.
When other people are around, there's gossip,
there's backbiting, things get awkward,
you know that speaking up will ruin everything
but you're always together so the stress builds,
you start to hate sharing the space,
and eventually you explode-
None of that sounds very appealing.
Huh? Oh, you're right.
But it's all good fun.
What you can't do alone, you can do with others.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I reckon this station is closest to your place.
It doesn't really feel like the big city here.
That's what makes this area great.
Your place is that way,
but there's a supermarket over there. I'll show you.
Huh? Okay.
Ow.
Are you sure about this?
Totally.
I am older than you after all. Consider it my rent for the night.
- But...
- Just forget about it.
Can you put the rest in the fridge?
I'll warn you though, it's not like I'm a master.
But you can cook.
I kinda enjoy it.
Let's see, where's the knife...
It's sort of like writing a song.
Boil the water while you cut up the ingredients.
Make the sauce while the water boils.
You do a bunch of things at the same time,
you put it all together, and you end up with a complete dish.
Whoa, this thing's blunt!
Sorry I don't have a better knife.
That's nothing to apologize for.
It makes me realize that I can't do anything.
Yet here I am, trying to live alone.
What's so funny?
Nothing. Just thinking I used to be the same way.
You've just gotta tackle it head on.
"Crap", "I screwed up", "is that right?"
Flip 'em off!
Rinse and repeat until you learn.
And you could start by getting some plates to serve this on.
Sorry.
Things to get:
- Plates
- Ladle
- Tension rod
- Colander
Thanks for waiting.
You should buy a light too.
Are we really eating this?
You really are a princess, huh?
You sound like a rich girl.
No way, not at all. My family's totally normal.
Though they can be a bit eccentric...
Like, we have these family rules.
Family rules?
Oh, like household traditions?
That's right.
1. Dinner is to be eaten at home, with the whole family.
Family rules
2. No smartphones in the living room.
3. There will be a family meeting every Sunday evening.
Like that.
Yikes.
My parents seem to think that's what a good family is like.
We were kinda famous at school.
I think I getcha.
But then I stopped going to school, and ultimately dropped out.
Why?
Why does it matter?
Is that why?
How did you know?!
You've got no poker face.
She's the most popular girl in school. She's pretty.
She jumps from one boys school hottie to the next.
And what, she bullied you?
Yeah.
Why?
I don't know.
I guess she didn't like me.
Did you get her back?
Girls like that only mess with you
once they're sure they've got numbers on their side,
so you can't fight back.
They'll get their friends to ignore you and hurt you.
I had to get taken to the hospital,
but school, and even my parents, told me not to make a fuss.
Stop.
The hotpot's boiling over.
It's fine. I like my veggies mushy.
I really do think you should sing.
I could write like five songs based on what you just said.
I've always wanted to be in a band without being the vocalist.
I want to know what it's like to just focus on the guitar.
Are you serious?
Sure am.
Quitting school means
y'got fewer options in the future.
Even if yer figure out what yer wanna do with yer life,
it'll be too late fer regrets.
Then...
I just need to go to university, right?
As long as I study and get into university...!
No. If I don't get into university
and end up as just a high school dropout, it'll all be over.
Over, you say?
Oh, I didn't mean it like that.
It's just, if things don't change, it'll be my loss.
I'll have lost to the bullies, my parents, and my teachers.
Fine.
I won't ask you again.
Sorry.
Again, it's nothing to apologize over.
We had more beer, didn't we?
Ugh, it's so heavy!
That one's filled with books.
I'll take the heavy ones, so you get the others.
It's alright. Is one trip going to be enough?
Yeah, this is the last of the big boxes.
Can you check inside?
Sure.
There's nothing else left, is there?
I've really got to study.
Here.
You're going to need this.
Ah, I suppose so.
I can't play it, anyway.
I guess I should take it then.
Thanks.
Okay, I'm off.
- Shouldn't I come with you?
- I'll be fine.
Alright.
Could you do me one last favor?
What is it?
I wasn't expecting a place like this here.
It's the Tama river. I'm sure you've heard of it.
It's more open than I thought it'd be.
I didn't think Tokyo had anywhere like this.
Tokyo is on the other side.
You were close, though.
Talk about splitting hairs...
Do you have any requests?
Anything's fine.
I just want to hear you one more time.
Sing whatever you want.
Oh, and good luck with your studies.
I'll just be moving back into the house I took you to last time,
so let's go for dinner again when you're free.
Yeah.
Good luck with your music, too.
I'll write some killer songs that you'll really love.
Yeah.
Give them the finger and show them who's boss.
You too.
Actually,
when you feel like giving them the finger,
try giving them a pinky instead.
I'll do it too.
Gotcha.
Here goes.
How would you move forward?
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial cliches
Whether my fingers tremble or not
There's no right answer
There's no losing
I've been me all my life
That's all there is
No matter how much I fight
There's no tomorrow
Crap.
Uhh...
"'You can't give up,' said Jim."
"'The light of hope will eventually shine in the darkness.'"
I'll have to go shopping.
Girls Band Cry.
Here's the key point.
The possible pronouns that could be used here are...
Dodgeball was so much fun!
I hit two people!
- Whoa, you rock!
- I know, right?
I haven't spoken to anyone.
I haven't said a word to anyone all week.
Are you done moving?
Yep, all done. My back is killing me.
Take it easy!
Thanks.
It's been a wh...
UPDATE ON TOMORROW'S WEATHER
I should hit the books.
1 NEW MESSAGE FROM MOMOKA-SAN
Bought a light yet?
Someone gave me one they weren't using today, want it?
Thanks! Yes please!
CAN I COME PICK IT UP RIGHT NOW?
Good evening!
Good evening.
Uhh, I think it was this way...
I found it.
Hello?
Oh, that was quick.
I'm coming in.
Sorry for the short notice.
It's that one there.
Looks like it should do, right?
Thank you very much. As long as it's bright, it's fine.
How's things? Have you gotten used to life here?
Good question.
Since you're here, how about we go for dinner?
I've started working, so I'll treat you.
Sure, I'll go.
So this is Nina-chan?
Yep.
This is Awa-san. She gave me the light.
She's going to be my drummer.
I'm Awa Subaru.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, I'm Iseri.
You wanna come eat with us, Subaru?
I'm not treating you though.
What? How stingy.
I'm not made of money.
Is that alright?
Ah, it's alright, I'll just go home.
Oh, come on. Nina's new to Tokyo.
You two are the same age, y'know.
This is more like hotpot than shabu-shabu.
You put in too many vegetables.
If you overcook cabbage, it loses its texture and tastes gross.
Here.
Dig in.
Thanks.
What kind of music do you like, Nina-chan?
Like, your favorite bands or Vocaloid songs.
Her grandma got her into Showa music.
Not bad. I listen to that stuff sometimes, too.
Which artists do you like?
Uh, I wouldn't say I'm that into it...
Oh, isn't this GureRuchi?
TL note: seems to be a fictional band
You're right.
Wait, you listen to GureRuchi?
I've been to one of their concerts,
and seen them at a festival once.
- You mean the festival last year in Chiba?
- That's the one.
That was a real mess.
It was?
They'll never get invited again.
They haven't held any proper concerts since.
I wasn't really paying attention,
but now that you mention it...
They had a good debut, though.
Do you go to any concerts, Nina-chan?
Not really.
I see.
The pot's emptying out, so how about we add the meat now?
Are you not a fan of meat?
Nina-chan?
Pardon me, nature calls.
Not your type?
It's not like that.
Then talk a bit more.
We worked hard to set this up.
What do you mean, you worked hard?
Is she forcing herself to make conversation?
Everyone's like that at first.
You don't know anything about each other.
She's kind of patronizing.
It irritates me.
You've got the wrong impression.
She said something about going to an acting school,
so that's normal for her.
She doesn't mean anything by it.
You're such a softie.
She's basically screaming
"look at what a good girl I am,
making friends with such an antisocial girl."
What's with that cynicism?
I'm not being cynical!
If you see everyone like that,
you'll never speak with anyone.
Hey!
You're right.
I doubt I'll ever have any friends.
I'm a difficult girl.
Now see here...
I'm sure I'll die alone.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the light.
You're...welcome...?
Sheesh, what an idiot.
She's already got what really matters.
What am I doing?
What the heck am I doing?
She was kind enough to reach out to me,
she was kind enough to be considerate of me...
I'm such an idiot...
I'm so stupid...
Am I fucking dumb?!
Stupid! Fucking! Idiot!
I'm so dumb...
Shut up!
You shut up!
What?!
The hell does that mean?
Shut the hell up!
H-Hey, watch it!
Shut up!
Get fucked!
I can't even plug in the light on my own.
I'll spend my whole life in darkness.
I'll be gloomy forever...
and ever...
You'd be wise to join my band.
Momoka-san?
Subaru-chan?
Find a better place to hide the key.
The light's in pieces.
I told you, I love your voice.
Why are you lying?
I'm not lying.
You get all twisted up, and you complicate things,
but that's because you can't lie to yourself.
You're so fragile, but you'd rather die than change.
Just like that song of mine that I'd forgotten.
The song I love so much
and hold so dear.
I don't...I don't need that!
What's so funny?!
You're such a pain in the ass!
Ow!
Just cram all that frustration
into your songs.
FATHER'S FARM YOGHURT DRINK
Come on.
Next episode:
"Stupid Q&A".
TL note: reference to a song by Eastern Youth https://youtu.be/NL5D6-7C9hg