Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
I will act as a married woman.
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who are you talking about?
You'd get somewhere with a single-lens
reflex camera and a telephoto lens.
It is you, Big Sister!
Nice to meet you. I'm Sakura Usuda.
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Yamaji? Yamaji?
You called, Miss Yoko?
I invited my classmates to visit tomorrow.
We will be playing in the garden.
That's wonderful!
Start preparations immediately.
Of course, Miss Yoko.
Welcome to my home!
Shall we play house?
That sounds delightful.
Yes.
I will act as a married woman.
I will be the wife of a chairman.
And I, the wife of a real estate magnate.
Today, I will go to the beauty salon and nail salon.
Meanwhile, I will have my pet trimmed.
Perhaps we will have foie gras sauté
with caviar this evening.
A tradesman will be visiting today.
"Actually, This Is What I Live For"
And that's just one of the heartwarming
memories from when Miss Yoko was younger.
Stop talking about things from the past.
You're a rich girl through and through.
Sounds just like you.
But, has Miss Sonobe...
...always been like that?
Yes. She said she was already
well into adulthood by then.
What were you like when you were little, Futaba?
Hm, when I was little...
"Futaba's Memories"
I'm home!
Welcome home, Futaba.
What's for snack?
Is bread okay?
Yup!
Yummy!
I was an energetic girl who ate a lot.
You've been like this since then...
What about you, Hayama?
Well, I...
Teru, what's wrong?
Santa... presents!
What about presents?
I told Santa I wanted a white tiger,
but he tried to pass it off with this.
And if I couldn't get a white tiger, I would have
conceded to my second choice of a puma,
third choice of a snow leopard,
or fourth choice of a saber-toothed cat.
That's terrible. He's cutting corners.
He should quit, huh?
Teru, cheer up.
Okay... but it's probably my fault.
Santa didn't get me what I wanted,
because I was a bad girl.
I'll be a good girl and study hard.
Yeah... even if it's just for show.
"One Moment Please"
And that's when you awakened!
What do you mean?
It seems your sister has always been kind.
Yeah, I'm jealous, since I'm an only child.
Teru!
Oh, Big Sis.
Can I have lunch with you all today?
Oh, we have already finished our--
I'm having bitter melon today.
Stir fried?
Nope, it's raw.
You still jealous?
Oh, yeah. It comes out tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow?
"This Month's Grand Prix Grand Prize" "Tama (1 years old)"
You see, Teru has...
No way. My kitty is just as cute.
"Tama (1 years old)" "Haru (5 years old)" "Jump!"
"Please" "Yomogi (2 years old)"
No way. My kitty is just as cute.
My kitty is a hundred times cuter!
Its coat is silky, and it has cute eyes!
"Bel Hayama (1 years old)"
What?!
Morning!
Hm? What are you looking at, Nishiyama?
Nishiyama?!
Al... ways... always... !
You're always, always--
"Collection of Popular Cats"
That won't do.
None of these kittens have done anything wrong.
Oh, is that...?
There's a picture of my kitty in here!
There's so many of them,
and they all look the same...
What?!
It's obvious! She shines differently than the others!
"Bel Hayama (1 years old)"
Get your eyes checked!
Ugh, what a doting parent.
Hayama.
So it really was your cat.
She's a cute one. Mine is cuter, though.
Why, thank you. The kitten you
got from me is cute, too.
Not as cute my mine, though.
My cat is cute, but yours is also...
And yours is also...
Well, well...
Well, well, well...
Well, well, well, well...
I don't get it!
My, that's amazing, Hayama.
It's so lovely. It would not be as lonely
living on my own if I had a pet.
But my apartment does not allow...
You need to find another place, huh.
I do not have the means for that.
Oh, but you do have a dog.
Huh?
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who are you talking about?
Oh, no. To think of Yamaji
as a dog is quite unpleasant.
Miss Yoko.
Throw this and say, "fetch."
Fetch!
Here.
That's creepy!
What?!
I won't lose. No, I won't!
I can do it, too!
I'll take a cute picture that's magazine-worthy!
Hey, wait!
Let me take your picture!
Come back!
Nishiyama?
I respect animal photographers.
You'd get somewhere with a single-lens
reflex camera and a telephoto lens.
Wait, are you really thinking to buy them?!
You actually own that stuff?
Hayama, so photography's a hobby of yours?
Oh, it's not my hobby. It's my duty.
Duty?!
Do you have other hobbies?
Mm, not really. Maybe reading.
Like international guides to torture?
I finished reading most
of those in middle school.
Is that so?
Is eating your hobby, Futaba?
It's not a hobby. Humans need
to eat, right? That's why I eat.
Humans...
Why do you have a look of pity in your eyes?!
What's your hobby then?
Why are you asking so nicely now?
My hobby?
I like cooking.
You're kidding. That'd be
the lamest joke of your life.
Wha--
You mean you like to eat cooked meals?
Or that you like eating a ton of it?
No, I like actually making it!
I like eating, so I can actually cook!
Even though I eat bread for lunch.
You can tell us your real hobby now.
You don't believe me!
I really do like cooking! I'll eat something
at a restaurant and try making it at home.
So it really is eating.
--Well, I guess my hobby would be eating out then.
--E-Er...
I have a request.
I have always wanted to try this...
On the way home, while talking with friends.
I can't believe you've never eaten here.
Since Futaba said her hobby is
eating out... if you are willing...
Actually, this is what I live for!
Th-This...
It has been my dream to eat this.
What a humble dream.
Let us talk endlessly about vague
and silly things while eating this!
Go ahead!
What should I say?
Anything is fine. I do not mind if you talk
about food or animals as you normally do--
Those aren't silly!
How is it? Is it good?
I feel like there is something missing.
It would be much better with mayonnaise.
So you still need some, huh?
Miss Yoko?
This might not be the right place to ask
you this, and it's not a silly question,
but I feel like it's okay to ask now.
Futaba?
What are your parents doing right now?
I do not know.
My mother passed away when
I was young, but my father...
Your dad?
When my father lost everything and
decided to start over, he said this:
All right! Daddy's going to do something big!
From then on, he has been
sending money regularly,
but I do not know where
he is or what he is doing.
You've had it hard, Miss Yoko.
--A little late to say it now, though.
--So that's why you're living on your own.
Yes.
If you ever need anything, just ask.
We want to help!
Thank you for making my dream come true.
You're over exaggerating.
Keep on inviting us!
For when it's related to food, right?
Big Sister?
I knew it! It is you, Big Sister!
Miss Yoko, you have a brother?
Oh, no. Yu is--
Nice to meet you. I'm Yu Takezono;
Yoko and I are promised to each other.
What?!
Promised to each other?
Sounds like something rich people do.
You have the wrong idea. I have known Yu
since we were young. It is nothing formal.
I'm serious about it, though!
Yes, yes.
Ah, okay.
I see now.
I have money, so you will
not have a difficult life.
Money?
Oh! I need to go to cram school.
Big Sister, I'll see you again, right?
Yes.
Please continue to get along with Yoko.
We will.
Yup.
If you will excuse me!
It has been a long time, Young Master Takezono.
You worked at Big Sister's place.
You're Yamaji, right?
What are you doing?
I have something to deliver to Miss Yoko.
Are you still pretending to be her servant?
Can you stop? You're getting in my way.
Stalker.
He's just a child. A child...
Hey, hey, about that boy from yesterday...
You mean Yu?
He seemed pretty attached to you.
Yeah.
It has been a while since I have
seen him, but I am glad he is well.
He seems like a reliable boy.
There's a difference with the rich ones.
Oh, yeah. I can't walk home with you guys today.
Oh?
What are you doing?
My cousin's staying with us for a week.
I need to go pick her up.
Your cousin?
My, I would like to meet her.
Really? I could really use some help.
Help?
"West Park"
Sakura!
Oh, Futaba.
Sorry, were you waiting?
Geez, you're late!
I'll introduce you. These are
my friends, Miss Yoko and Hayama.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
She's my cousin, Sakura.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sakura Usuda.
My, you are adorable.
Yes, I know.
What?
Sorry, she's a little weird.
D-Do not worry. She really is adorable.
By the way, why does she have so much luggage?
It's a week's worth of clothes and other things.
This amount of luggage is normal for a girl.
So this is what you meant by needing help.
Thanks for helping!
You summoned me?
I told you, that's creepy!
I don't think I'm extraordinary,
but I'm pretty up there.
I see...
That's why I've planned out my life.
"Sakura's Life"
In the summer when I'm fourteen, I'll be
scouted in Harajuku and debut as an idol.
After being in some movies and commercials,
I'll get married at twenty-three.
I'll give birth to a boy at age twenty-five.
At twenty-eight, I'll debut as a model
in the young missus' magazine.
At fifty, I'll move overseas
and live a carefree life.
That's how I've been thinking of it.
You never know what life will bring.
That's depressing.
This person is a kind of handsome.
I accept many types of people.
He's actually...
...more of a stalker who
pretends to be a part-timer.
Ugh, that's the worst.
I don't need you in my life.
I'm not even in your life, huh.
Big Sister!
Oh?
Yu!
I'm so glad I ran into you.
Here! It's wagyu beef I received as a gift.
Wagyu beef?
We can't finish it all, so I
wanted to give some to you.
It's yummy!
Yu!
--Usuda! What are you doing here?
--Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
--What? You two know each other?
--The meat's sweet juice floods your mouth!
--Yeah, we're in the same class.
--Right now, he's the top candidate to be my darling.
--The meat's sweet juice floods your mouth!
--Don't decide that on your own!
--Aw, you're just embarrassed.
--The meat's sweet juice floods your mouth!
--I am not.
--It will be so wonderful!
--Why not? You two'd make a good couple.
--You think so, too?
--Wagyu beef...
--No! Yoko is my betrothed!
What do you mean, "betrothed"?
That is...
Is it over for me? Do I still have a chance?
Well, it's a promise they made as kids, nothing
formal. And Miss Yoko isn't serious about it.
Right, Miss Yoko?
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
--Miss Yoko...
--See you, Big Sister!
--Wait, Yu!
--Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef. Meat...
--Er...
--Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef. Meat!
--What should we do?
Miss Yoko!
Miss Yoko. How was yesterday's meat?
No fair. The marbled wagyu beef
was probably delicious. I'm jealou--
Huh?
You bully! Shame on you.
What?!
My first meat in a long while...
It is fine. I can cook this!
You just need to fry the meat.
The outside was crunchy
while the inside was rare.
Ah...
You messed up cooking it, huh?
Hey, you still have meat left, right?
Yes, but...
All right. I'll cook it for you.
What?
I told you. Cooking is my hobby.
It's good quality meat, so the trick
is to not cook it too long.
Here it is.
Oh, this is it!
Ouch.
You really didn't believe that I could cook?
If I only ate and couldn't cook,
it'd be pretty bad.
I'm sure most people think you only eat.
No way!
Well, anyway, let's eat while it's hot!
Let's eat!
Delicious!
It's tender and juicy!
Ah, this is what meat is supposed to taste like.
The Japanese style radish sauce was good, too.
I don't make things that I have to
splurge on and can't eat them normally.
In other words, Mom's cooking is my specialty!
Momma!
Be in awe and worship me.
A mom's cooking?
My mom also...
She often made a dish of veal
spareribs simmered with chickpeas.
Veal...
It was very delicious...
...but today's meal was just as good!
Thank you for the meal.
It has been a long time since I have
eaten at home with others.
Miss Yoko...
How about seconds? I'll fry up all the meat!
Futaba.
Eating delicious food makes people happy, right?
It puts you in a pleasantly good mood.
So you should keep eating yummy things, Hayama.
What are you implying?
I will learn to cook delicious dishes as well.
And I will invite you both over!
I gladly accept!
What will you make?
I will poeler straight-from-the-bakery bread crusts
topped with fresh-squeezed mayonnaise.
Then on a whim, the chef will
flambé it with a special balsamic?
Make it on the crunchy side with the works!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life
is so entertainin-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
I'll do it! I'll sell delicious steak
for cheaper than this place!
And so, the cooking showdown began.
Futaba went about to find ingredients.
I think something like that will happen next.
"This will not happen."
My, that would be good.
A cooking story needs a taste tester!
"Nishikawa is waiting for an offer to be the taste tester."
"Next time: Your Birthmarks Have Faded"