I have always thought this way...
That there would be an occurrence which would make me special.
That one day I will find that I possess a talent.
Since a long time ago, one thing I had in mind was...
being a knight and protecting the princess from misfortunes.
But...
I guess it's too late to become one now.
I wonder what I should do?
That place was my favorite place.
A quiet and abandoned place where nobody would come is a perfect place for reading.
However, there was a passenger today.
N-No trains will come to this station.
Eh?
Sorry, it's nothing.
W-Well then...
That was the first day I met her.
That was... a chance meeting of less than 45 seconds.
Ahh, I have no idea!
Time for some data collection.
Oh, it's Kei.
Merry Christmas, Onii-chan.
Don't forget the party okay!
It can't be helped...
Guess I'll go and show my face.
Okay, cut!
Did you get a good picture, Kyousuke?
I don't just take good pictures.
Actually, it would be great if the snow was falling.
Nope, no can do. It would be hard to connect the "cuts".
Oh well, it's for library use anyways.
Shall we go get a bite to eat?
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Ah, I just thought I should shoot some people on the street too.
Must have been a pretty girl, right?
Again? You did it again?!
Ah, that hurt!
Ouch, ouch!
I'm home!
Ah, welcome home, Kei-senpai!
Sorry, Mizuki. The cake shop got these all mixed up.
Huh, where is Onii-chan?
He's not here yet.
Really? Does he even plan on coming?
I even told him that if he doesn't come this time I won't go easy on him!
Hiro-sempai always seems to be busy, right?
Even though he doesn't go to club activities or cram school.
He must be doing other things.
Mizuki, help me arrange these.
Okay!
But he is a really weird guy.
Recently I thought he was thinking about something deeply when he suddenly got up in a rush to draw.
Just like a mangaka before a deadline, right?
What's the matter, Kei-senpai?
Ahh, it's nothing.
I'll try sending mail one more time.
Merry Christmas, Onee-chan.
Chihiro...
Maybe I came by at the wrong time.
So the inside looks like this...
Too bad for you...
Mass has already ended.
Ah, I'm not here for that.  I'm just here for some data collection.
You are?
There is someone I must meet.
A promise or something?
Well then, I'm off.
Ah, please wait.
What is it?
Merry Christmas.
It's so cold.
You're late! Where are you?
Crap, Kei is getting angry.
Thief!
Wait!
Hey you, did you see a bike go by?
You mean just now?
Do you know where it went?
That way.
Thank you! I'll be borrowing this.
Hey, wait!
That's my bicycle!
You bicycle thief!
Hello?
Hello your head!
I hope you didn't forget about the party yet again, Onii-chan!
I didn't forget! I'm just not going to it, that's all.
What's that?! What's with the sudden change of attitude?!
I don't have my dress for the ball!
What, are you the Snow Princess or something?
I actually meant Cinderella.
They are both the same!
Now's not the time for that!
Eh?
Did you suddenly get a extra job or something?
That's right, I'm really busy right now!
We'll do it next time, okay?
Do it next time? Eh? W-Wait!
Stupid Onii-chan! Go die!!
I-I'm dying!!
Uhh, my bicycle...
Hey, you. Are you still alive?
Is this 911?
Looks like I have to come along too when the ambulance arrives.
Give me a break...
You're still alive, right?
Don't tell me you're...
Huh? What was I doing?
You're asking me?
Ah, I just remembered!
W-Wait a second!
We have to make sure you're all right.
That was a handbag snatcher!
My important bag got stolen!
What if you hurt your head?
Wait here until the ambulance arrives.
No, that bag was expensive! Both my wallet and cell phone were in it!
I'm definitely going to catch him!
Hey, wait!
Being at the park at night is kind of relaxing, right?
How about the handbag snatcher?
Didn't you say, "I'm definitely going to catch him?"
I got tired of running so much.
You give up too quickly.
It's fine, it's fine.
There was no money in my wallet anyway.
The cell phone only had my aunt's number in it.
And it's almost time to get a new bag too.
I don't really care now.
That's completely different than earlier.
More importantly, are you sure you're all right?
Are you hurt anywhere or feel nauseous?
Nope, nothing.
There might be some internal bleeding, you know.
You did faint.
I didn't faint.
You must have completely lost consciousness.
You're lying. I don't remember anything about it.
Of course not, you fainted.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
For what?
For worrying about me. Thank you.
W-What are you saying?
You're so kind.
Shut up.
In any case, you should go to the hospital.
Okay, I'll think about it.
It's snowing. There's snow!
It's so amazing!
Snow!
Don't you think it feels kind of nice?
Being together with someone during a white Christmas.
I-I have no idea.
Jeez, you're so heartless.
During this time, it's lonely when you are alone, right?
That doesn't matter.
Since I'll keep living even if I'm alone.
I... don't really want to be alone.
I haven't asked your name, right? I'm Miyamura Miyako.
I'm Hirono Hiro.
Hirono Hiro... so it's Hiro Hiro.
A strange little name.
Speak for yourself, Miyamura Miyako, so it's Miya Miya.
Ah, I guess it's the same.
You sure notice some good things.
You're so smart!
Hey, Hirono-kun.
W-What?
No one is at my house today.
You must have thought something naughty just now.
Idiot. What are you saying?
But the the house key was inside that bag.
So?
Therefore, I can't go inside even if I go home.
So, I have to stay outside for today.
And for a girl like me, it's dangerous staying outside, so...
Don't tell me you're going to say that you should "stay with me".
Like they say, since you started it, you should finish it.
Come on, let's go!
Hey, wait a second!
Looks like Christmas this year...
I haven't said I will...
hasn't ended yet.
At the end of the class,
future career survey forms were handed out.
A future career that is tangible and not the dreams that you imagine when you're still young.
I wanted to be a knight who protects the princess from misfortune.
The time to write it in the career survey form has long already passed.
I guess it's too late to become one now.
I wonder what I should do?
So why me?
I wanted to hear it from an adult.
I was just thinking that Himura-san might have some good advice.
I'm sorry, but I'm neither a priest nor a counselor.
But you are always here, so it's not a surprise when people start to consult with you.
I'm just here waiting for someone.
A promise or something?
You have something that you like?
Something that I like? I guess reading.
I like novels and stuff.
Then just go on with that.
You can go to a liberal arts university and go into publishing, or write a novel yourself.
But isn't getting a job on something because you like it too simplistic?
Well, it's far better than getting a job on something that you hate.
Stop worrying; instead, start thinking about it.
End of advice.
This is what you call an adult opinion.
Adult opinion...
I get it, but at the same time I don't.
Whichever it is, it just means that I have to think about it myself.
That's easier said than done.
Hey!
Hello.
Did I disturb you?
No.
Umm, can I ask you something weird?
Are you the same person from before?
Y-Yeah.
I see.
Sorry, I guess we met before, right?
Well, we literally only met.
Looks like it.
Umm...!
Yes?
Do you always come here?
Yeah, now and then.
It's a quiet and nice place.
You can say that again.
It's a perfect place for reading.
Also, it can be a grand make-believe standby...
Eh?
since you can walk down the railroad tracks.
No one will be angry here.
I see. That's interesting.
Chihiro.
My name is Chihiro.
Shindou Chihiro.
It is written as senjin meaning lions drop their cubs down a cliff, but pronounced as Chihiro.
I'm Asou Renji.
Asou-san, right?
Yeah.
Chihiro, you are early.
Early?
Yeah, since last time you were here before me too.
That's because I don't go to school.
You don't go to school?
Right.
I see.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going back now.
Eh? Why?
I just don't feel right because my being here might be bothering you,
since this is Asou-san's place after all...
No, it's not like that.
That's completely untrue.
Actually, I've thought the same thing too,
that because of me, Chihiro is feeling uncomfortable.
No, it's not like that.
Please don't worry about it.
I am the same too, so please don't worry about me.
I'll accompany you home.
Is your home nearby?
I'm fine. I just want to stay here a little bit longer.
It's getting dark now.
I want to stay.
I see.
Umm...
Can I... come here again?
Of course!
Thank you.
Well then, see you.
Eh?
What's the matter?
Nothing...
See you, too.
See you then.
What were you looking at?
I wasn't particularly looking at anything.
How about the sky?
That's right, I guess I was watching the sky.
Are you all right?
What do you mean, "Are you all right?"
Ah, I mean since you look different than yesterday.
Yesterday?
Wait, don't tell me you're Asou-san?!
Eh? Yeah, that's right.
Huh?
What?
Yesterday, I slept again...
What was yesterday?
I slept again...
Huh? Hey, what's the matter, Chihiro?
It's not like that. This is... this is different.
I'm just... I wonder why...
Even if you ask me why...
No, that's not it. This is different.
A-Are you all right?
I'm all right. I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Umm, why did Asou-san come here again today?
Well, that's because... I just felt like it.
I see. I'm sorry.
I was so happy that I misunderstood you.
Huh?
I'm sorry. Please just forget about it.
Did she mean she was happy because she met me?
But we only met once; she cried and hugged me...
No way I guess...
Asou-san...
Huh?
That pocket is...
Ah, this is a novel that I'm reading right now.
So you like to read novels?
Yeah, it's like an addiction.
I always have a few of them in my pocket.
Without them, I feel like I'm missing something to the point that I become restless.
Just like a cat's whiskers, right?
Eh?
Ah, I see.
It's cute.
What Chihiro has there is like a cat's whiskers too?
Something like that.
Without this I can't keep on living.
Just like me.
I agree.
Asou-san, I have a favor to ask of you. Is that okay?
What is it?
Will you become my friend?
Y-Your friend?
You don't want to?
N-No! Of course I do!
Will you become my friend too?
Yes!
See you.
Yes.
Asou-san said that and went home.
I was so happy.
Asou-san promised yesterday's me and met with today's me.
He also promised to today's me to meet with tomorrow's me again.
And he also became friends with someone like me.
I shouldn't let my feelings go because of something like this.
Kei-oneechan.
The two have met again,
and the time of hesitation starts to move.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Upon A Time.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?