Did you hate me...
Did you hate me so much?
The origin shot.
It causes the target's prana to go out of control,
ripping apart their body.
What?
Time Alter:
Double Accel!
The origin shot isn't working.
No...
I understand.
He's using Command Seals as his prana source.
When the bullet connects,
the prana contained within the Command Seal vanishes.
Since he doesn't use his own Magic Circuits,
the bullets won't work.
But if I can hit him...
It's still strong enough to kill him.
Don't think you'll escape next time.
Now that I know you're moving at double speed,
I can adjust my defenses to compensate.
He's fast!
Am I the one to blame
for your madness?
My...
Time Alter:
Double Accel!
His advantage at close range is enormous.
The Calico is gone.
The Contender needs reloading.
However...
Avalon...
He recovers quickly enough to instantly regenerate a demolished heart?
I'll have to destroy his brain, then.
But...
I can't use my right arm.
Avalon's healing powers will work on self-inflicted wounds...
I have a knife and two grenades left.
I have twelve Black Keys.
And eight spare Command Seals.
Time Alter:
Triple Accel!
Square Accel!
I will win the Holy Grail,
no matter what.
If I do not,
there will be nothing I can offer
to you as recompense.
Even after all of this...
You would still wield your blade
for such a reason?
What a difficult person...
This is...
I knew you'd come.
I believed you would reach this place.
Iri.
This is where your wish will be granted...
Inside the Grail you sought.
That is the Grail.
It has yet to take form,
but the vessel is more than filled.
All you need do now is offer your prayer.
Only then will it be able to go outside.
Now, please...
Give it a shape.
Kiritsugu,
you are worthy to give it form.
Who are you?
I am Irisviel.
No...
If the Grail is prepared,
then she is already...
Answer me!
Yes.
I will not deny that this is a mask.
Unless I use a pre-existing personality as a shell,
I cannot communicate with others.
However,
her personality, which I recorded, is inarguably real.
So I have inherited her last wish.
Are you the will of the Holy Grail?
Yes.
That interpretation is correct.
I have a will... A wish.
The will to be born into the world.
Impossible.
In that case,
how does the Grail intend to grant my wish?
That is something, Kiritsugu,
that you should know better than anyone.
What?
You learned how to save the world a long time ago.
So I will do as you did,
to carry out your will,
and to answer your prayer.
What are you talking about?
You already know the answer to that.
The only way
is to look within and ask yourself.
Where am I?
Three hundred in one ship.
Two hundred in another.
What?
Five hundred total passengers and crew,
plus Emiya Kiritsugu.
Let's posit that these five hundred and one are humanity's last survivors.
Giant holes simultaneously open up in both ships' hulls.
Kiritsugu alone has the ability to repair a ship.
Now then,
which ship would you fix?
Obviously,
the one with three hundred people.
After you made that decision,
the remaining two hundred apprehended you.
They demanded that you
fix their ship first.
So what will you do?
Then, I'd...
Kill all two hundred.
That is correct.
That is what Emiya Kiritsugu would do.
Next,
the surviving three hundred abandon their damaged craft,
divide themselves between two new ships, and continue the journey.
Two hundred on one.
And one hundred on the other.
But again,
more holes open at the bottom of both ships
Wait.
The hundred in the smaller ship kidnap you,
demanding that you fix their ship first.
Now, what will you do?
You already know.
But...
Yes,
you made the right decision.
Impossible...
That's impossible!
How can that be the right decision?
Two hundred survived...
But three hundred died to ensure it!
The scales are tipped the wrong way!
No, your calculations were correct.
You chose to save the many and sacrifice the few.
Isn't that right, Emiya Kiritsugu?
You have always chosen to kill those on the lighter side of the scales.
Even if it meant leaving a long trail of bodies behind you.
If it saved lives,
those lives had more worth.
This is what you wanted to show me?
Yes.
This is your truth.
The answer that lies within Emiya Kiritsugu.
In other words,
the wish that the Grail should grant.
No...
This isn't what I wanted!
I wanted another way.
That's why I said
a miracle was my only hope!
Your wish can never include
a method you yourself don't know.
If you wish to save the world,
it must be done in a way that you comprehend.
Shut up!
How the hell
can you call that a miracle?!
It is a miracle.
The deed that you
tried and failed to do on your own
can be accomplished on a scale beyond the power of any man.
What else could you call it
but a miracle?
Dad...
Natalia!
Emiya Kiritsugu,
you truly are Angra Mainyu.
The one worthy to bear all the evil in the world.
Now,
the last question.
Three remain.
Will you save two?
Or choose one?
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
You're finally back!
You understand, right?
This is the Holy Grail granting your wish.
All you need to do now is offer your prayer.
To bring back your wife.
To take back your daughter.
I won't be able to go looking for walnuts with you anymore.
It's okay.
I'm happy,
as long as you and Mother are with me.
Thank you..
Daddy...
loves you, too, Ilya.
If nothing else,
I swear that to be true.
Goodbye,
Ilya.
Ilya!
Ilya, Ilya, Ilya...
Why?!
Why did you do this?!
My love, you killed our Ilya!
M-My love...
Wh-Why?
Why do you refuse us?
Refuse us...
and the grail?
Six billion people...
I curse you,
Emiya...
Kiritsugu.
Against two members of my family...
Angra Mainyu curses you...
I...
Suffer...
...until the day you die.
I will kill you...
You will...
...regret this!
And I will...
save the world.
I'll never forgive—
What a boring conclusion.
Why did you refuse it?
You saw it, too?
I thought you sacrificed everything you had
to make it this far.
How can you deny the worth of something
you worked so hard to attain?
It's so foolish, I cannot understand it.
Its cost is greater
than any benefit it offers.
That's all.
That thing
is no omnipotent wish-granter.
Then give it to me!
You may not need it,
but I do!
If it...
If it can create something like that,
then it can answer my every doubt.
It longs for its own life!
For its own birth!
Please don't kill it!
That's—
You're just too stupid
for me to understand.
Irisviel...
You're late, Saber.
How could you keep me waiting,
while you played with your old rabid dog?
Archer...
Look at that expression.
Like that of a ravenous dog.
Get out of the way...
The Holy Grail belongs to me!
Saber,
even delusional and crawling along the ground,
you are still beautiful.
Lay down your blade and be my wife.
A Grail that grants miracles?
Why fixate on something so implausible?
Abandon your foolish ideals and vows.
From now on, seek only me, and be mine alone.
If you do,
I swear, as king of all the world,
that I shall give you every pleasure there is to feel.
You...
You would steal the Holy Grail from me?
For such nonsense?!
I was not asking your opinion.
This is simply my decision!
Now, let us hear your response.
I refuse! Never—
You are too embarrassed to accept?
That's fine...
You may give the wrong answer as many times as you like.
If you would learn the joy of serving me,
you must first learn pain.
Kiritsugu...
Then you have finally made your decision.
By my name, Emiya Kiritsugu,
I order you with my Command Seal...
Give me the Holy Grail.
Saber, use your Noble Phantasm
to destroy the Grail.
Impossible...
What are you doing, Saber?!
No!
By my third Command Seal,
I order you again...
Why, Kiritsugu?
You, of all people...
Why?!
Curse you...
You dare interfere with my wedding ceremony, mongrel?!
Saber, destroy...
Stop!
the Grail.
Episode 24:
The Last Command Seal
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
I remember that face...
With tears in his eyes,
and joy filling his heart...
It was a man.
The man was grateful to someone or something.
"Thank you," he said.
Next Time:
Fate/Zero