"Me, Pool, A Paradise of Swimsuits, and—"
[*The staff ate these food deliciously later.]
[Akihisa vision/point of view]
[Boy's Changing Room -> Girl's Changing Room -> Hideyoshi's Changing Room]
[Question 4 List the following chemical symbols based on the amount of atoms present from least to most then provide the name of the element.]
[Himeji Mizuki's answer:  ; Teachers comment: Correct.  Ga and Po are hardly ever used so I thought it would be difficult but it was to be expected of Himeji-san]
[Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:  H an o en ga i op (he simply reads the symbols as is and roughly means 'a perverted favor, blush'; Teacher's comment:  Although the answer is like this, it's irritating that it's in the correct order other than sodium.]
[What are you talking about?]
[My life ends here but I have no regrets or complaints.]
[Women's bath - Men's Bath - Hideyoshi's bath]
[So the world already approves.]
[butt?]
Summer.
Summer at Fumizuki Academy
is a season of playing in the water under vibrant sunshine.
It's also a season of nosebleeds.
Oh, Yuuji!
What?
They turned off the gas, so there's no hot water.
Say something sooner!
I'm sorry. When you get in the shower, start farther from the heart with your extremities
and then gradually move closer.
I didn't ask you how to take a cold shower!
What are you flipping out about?
I know! Why don't you take a cold shower to calm yourself down?
I'm flipping out because of the shower, jackass!
Seriously, there's no gas and no food.
How the hell are you still alive?
That's a little bit rude. There's food.
At least, things with lots of calories!
Sorry, oil isn't my cup of tea.
Look, your fridge is completely empty.
That's harsh. It isn't empty!
That's it, I'll just use this to help cool off.
Hey, Yuuji, what do you want to eat?
There's cola, coffee, ramen, and cold sesame noodles.
You son of a bitch! Were you planning on having me eat the disposable chopsticks?!
Were you planning on doing that?
It's closer to real food than the inorganic plastic bags.
I won't let you eat chopsticks.
I'd have to eat the ramen with my fingers if I did.
I bought you some stuff.
Diet cola, konjac jelly, agar—
Aren't these calorie-free?!
I chose these because they wouldn't make you fat.
You've seen how I eat! How would I get fat?
You mean eating only sugar and fat?
Those are all I eat, okay?!
Now I'm pissed!
What? You wanna go?
Yeah. We both knew it would come to this.
So be it, this is just what I wanted.
Ah! My eyes! They hurt!
Not bad...
Same to you.
But now I'm serious.
I won't hold back.
That fight was pointless.
I guess...
Ah, now I have sticky stuff all over me. I need to take a shower.
Yuuji, you take one first.
I'd never take one here, even if it killed me.
Then what are you going to do?
Go somewhere that has hot water.
I see. So you snuck in to take a shower,
and went swimming in your shorts and underwear?
Anything else you'd like to add?!
It's his fault!
It's all because Yuuji didn't bring anything good to eat.
More like because you didn't pay for gas!
Just having water is good!
You have times when you don't even get water?
That's enough, I understand now.
You do? I'm right, right?
I now know how stupid you two are!
As punishment, you two will clean the pool next weekend!
Yes, sir.
That sucks.
Thinking about having to clean that huge pool by ourselves makes me depressed.
Don't think about it like that.
If we clean the pool, he said we can use it whenever we want.
Ninja Pervert should come help too.
Pass.
I'm taking Himeji and Shimada too.
I'll bring the brushes and detergent.
It seems like it'll be fun.
Can I come and help clean too?
Of course!
Hey, what are you guys talking about?
Seems like you're all excited.
Next weekend, the pool is all ours.
You two should come too!
The pool... That means swimsuits...
The pool... So we'll be wearing swimsuits...
Also, Hideyoshi will show off a swimsuit for Akihisa.
That's sly, Kinoshita! You're so brave!
That's right, Kinoshita-kun is just too sneaky!
What are you guys talking about?
So what do you guys say?
We're going!
I need to prepare.
Yeah, being prepared is important!
I need to diet...
All right, now all that's left is telling Shouko.
You're telling her?
Aw, you're finally growing up.
Akihisa, what do you think will happen to me if Shouko finds out afterwards?
I'm sorry.
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning, Yoshii-kun.
It's great outside today.
I've even prepared a special new swimsuit for today!
Eh? What's it like?
Trunks.
Isn't that what men wear?!
I'm disappointed in you.
That's cruel, Hideyoshi... Do you hate me?!
What are you going on about?
Morning, stupid onii-chan!
Hazuki-chan.
She insisted on coming, no matter what I said.
Now everyone's here.
So let's get into our swimsuits and meet up by the pool.
Okay!
Hey, hey, this is the guy's side.
You and Hideyoshi need to go to the other side.
I'm just playing.
I'm not.
All right, Hazuki, Kinoshita, stop playing around.
Even you?! No! No freaking way am I going into the girls' changing room!
If you dare expose yourself to Yuuji...
How did it turn out like this?!
It's fine, Hideyoshi. Look.
So Hideyoshi's a gender...
Sorry for the wait, everyone!
Hey, Hazuki-chan—
This is illegal, right?
Who's going to get me a lawyer?
Don't get so excited over an elementary kid's swimsuit.
What the hell, Hazuki!
Give it back! If I don't have those, my...
Oh, the breasts moved.
Don't screw around! These were expensive!
Is that the so-called NuBra?
You saw nothing! You saw absolutely nothing!
Nothing, I saw nothing!
Someone... Someone hurry and press the button!
I was prepared... Stupid Hazuki.
What are you looking at? Something wrong?
No way! You look great!
Really?
Yep. Your chest, bust, and breasts are all very slim—
My big toe!
Did you just call me flat-chested three times in a row?
Hey, don't get so angry!
Despite what he's saying, Yuuji actually had quite a reaction to you wearing a swimsuit.
Aki, you suck!
Wouldn't it be better if you were honest?
Okay, Minami has small boobs.
Careful, or I'll gouge your eyes out.
Ah! My eyes! My eyes!
Yuuji, you aren't allowed to look at other girls.
Onee-san, you're so pretty.
Thank you for the compliment.
Come on, Yuuji also has something to say to Kirishima-san, right?
Shouko...
Get me a tissue. The tears won't stop.
Say what you think of her swimsuit!
I've lost my vision, what the hell am I supposed to do?
Yuuji is such a troublesome guy. Right, Ninja Pervert?
Eh?
Ninja Pervert!
Sorry, I'll be going on ahead...
Damn it! Who... Who did this to Ninja Pervert?!
Sorry! I got held up by the strap on the back!
Profuse bleeding!
Is this a biological weapon?
Yoshii-kun!
What's wrong?
God, how do you decide those who receive and those who don't? Why is it that I don't qualify?
What's wrong with Minami-chan?
If onee-chan is in shock, she'll lapse into speaking German.
What? What's happened?
Yuuji, you can't look.
Is everyone here?
No, Hideyoshi hasn't come out yet.
What kind of swimsuit is it?
Trunks.
Oh, right.
Sorry for the wait!
Sign: Stopped
Ah, there isn't any blood left.
It's stopped.
Everyone's here now!
Kinoshita, how long do you plan on getting in our way?
That's way too sneaky! You get us to lower our guard and then stab us in the back!
Onee-chan, you're very cute!
I'm a guy...
But that swimsuit is for girls.
What?
I told the store clerk that I wanted normal trunks!
If they don't know you, anybody would give you a girl's swimsuit.
Yuuji, are your eyes okay?
Yeah. Don't worry, my vision's slowly returning.
There are too many things here that you mustn't see.
Just get it over with and kill me, okay?! Hurry!
There!
Shouko-san. S-Shouko.
Yoshii-kun, you're really good at swimming.
Himeji-san, you're not going to swim?
Actually, I don't know how to swim.
The most I can do is float on the surface.
Want me to teach you? I'm pretty good.
Really? Thank you so much!
Usually it's the other way around, the Class A Himeji-san teaching the Class F Minami in academics.
It feels just like Minami is the A and Himeji-san is the F!
It's probably a B if they're lifted!
By the way, Yuuji, I'm a C.
What are you talking about?
Onii-chan!
Let's play Water Demon!
Water Demon?
You mean like playing hide and seek in water?
No, I mean the game where the person who is the demon hunts down the others who aren't.
And then, if the demon pulls the others into the water and drowns them, he wins!
Holy crap, that does sounds demonic!
But Hazuki-chan, this game is too dangerous. We can't play it.
Oh, we can't play it?
Look, Kirishima-san.
What?
I want you and Yuuji to play Water Demon.
The rules are simple. Pull Yuuji into the water by force.
And then after he drowns, perform CPR, and then you win.
What the hell? Someone! Someone save me!
See? It's dangerous, right?
Yeah.
It was you, wasn't it?!
Yuuji sure is hard to handle.
Let me go! Do you hate me or something?!
Eh? Rep?
Aiko.
Kudo-san from Class A? Why are you here?
Because I'm in the swim club.
The others came too.
Onee-sama!
If you were coming to play at the pool, why didn't you call me?!
Why are you here too!
I have a special information network designed specifically to keep harmful pests away from onee-sama!
Then I'm going to go change, too!
By the way, if you're going to peek, then don't get caught.
She's inviting us to do it.
I'm not a man if I don't go.
Yoshii-kun, if you're going to do it, be prepared for the consequences.
You want to go home alive, Aki?
I have a bad feeling...
There's no other choice, I can only rely on Ninja Pervert's camera.
Damn it!
Ah, I'm hungry now that we're done swimming.
Speaking of which, I have something good.
Since it didn't go well and I couldn't make enough for everybody, I didn't bring it up,
but I actually made three waffles this morning.
Begin!
Fastest Swimmer Competition!
The swimming battle of life and death!
The rules are simple.
Swim to the other side of the pool and back.
The first one to return to make it back is the winner!
Himeji has made three killer waffles,
and there are only four competitors.
That means only the winner will be exempt from eating the waffles of doom and survive.
Pay attention! We're starting!
On your marks...
Ninja Pervert should be weak from his hemorrhaging.
I should be able to beat Hideyoshi in stamina.
Get set...
That means only one person stands between me and victory!
Start!
Go die!
You fox!
You'll eat those words!
Not bad, Akihisa!
I won't lose to the likes of you!
It's all right if you guys want to fight it out,
but the two people in front of you are already turning around.
Crap! We'll lose if this continues!
We can't let them get what they want!
I'll go block Ninja Pervert. Akihisa, you get rid of Hideyoshi!
Okay!
Hideyoshi, you're not passing through here!
Huh, what's this?
Aki!
Yoshii-kun, what are you doing?
What is... this?
Don't tell me this is...
W-What?
Yoshii-kun!
Aki!
Kinoshita, hurry up and cover your chest!
Why? I'm a guy!
My life ends here, but I have no regrets or complaints.
It seems like it'll be tough to clean this up.
That sure was fun.
Yup.
But I feel rather tired.
It's more anemia than fatigue.
That's right! Let's go take a bath!
Okay!
Hey, hey. This is the men's bath.
You and Hideyoshi need go to the other side.
I'm just playing!
I'm not.
All right, Hazuki, Kinoshita, stop playing around.
Again? Why is it like this?
No way I'm going to go over to the girls' bath all alone!
Don't worry, Hideyoshi. Look.
Sign: Men's bath
Sign: Women's bath
Sign: Hideyoshi's bath
So the world already approves.
Ah, the water sure is nice.
It's warm...
What is it, Ninja Pervert?
The girls' bath is over there.
What?
What are you doing?!
It's legal, it's legal!
Onee-sama, let's wash each other!
Whatever happens in a bath is legal!
Whatever happens? What are you planning on doing?
Sign: Attack Strength
Eh? Oh... It's not necessarily good to have big ones.
My shoulders are always sore. It's quite tiring.
All the big boobs say so!
Akihisa, pass the shampoo!
Here.
Isn't this the soap I bought?
It can make bubbles too, so there's no need to buy something else.
I'm an idiot for even asking.
Hey, Shouko! Lend me your shampoo!
Thank you!
Yuuji, lend me your soap.
Catch!
It's like they're already married.
Don't say too much, Himeji!
It'll be troublesome if she takes it seriously. She's an idiot.
No! No!
Onee-sama, it's illegal to wear a bath towel in a bath!
Hurry up and take off this unromantic cloth so you can legally...
Why are you bullying the weak?
Hey, did you know?
Public baths are connected!
I wonder what you'd see if you dove into it...
Hot!
That's the hot water vent!
Pour cold water on yourself first!
Ah! Eyes! My eyes!
Sucks to be you!
Damn it! How dare she trick us!
Unforgivable!
If this is how it'll be, I'll stop holding back with my peeking techniques!
This Black Golden Bracelet allows summoning of Summoned Beings
without a teacher's presence.
Awaken!
Summoned Being, summon!
Okay, go!
Ah!
It's stupid onii-chan's Summoned Being!
Can you see?
Although the Summoned Being can, I don't feel happy at all!
Alternative method!
Oh, nice! If we have the Summoned Being use the camera...
Summoned Being,
summon!
We're not going to let you do whatever you want!
With your Summoned Being, there's no way you can pierce this defensive line!
I'll show you!
Go!
Ow!
Those who receive zeros go to supplementary classes!
Why the hell is Iron Man here?!
What the hell were you doing in there?
What an unlucky fellow.
I won.
Question 7:  Based on Japan's civil laws, what is the legal marriageable age?
As long as there's love, a difference in age doesn't matter.
Thank you for your hopes and dreams.
Next week:  Me, Shouko, and Kisaragi Grand Park.
This will be on the test.