I will make your wish come true.
Even if it meant hurting someone.
Even if it meant hurting myself.
So please, when your wish comes true...
...I wish for you...
...to smile.
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
You're kidding me?
Iona's playing WIXOSS too?
Hey, WIXOSS is fun, really!
"What We're Into"
I even bought a starting deck.
Ah, but isn't this stuff only
for the guys or something?
"Daikichi Apartments"
Welcome back Ru-chan.
Grandma!
"Kominato"
I'm back, Grandma!
--Long time no see, Bro!
--Hey, Ruko.
Grandma!
C'mon, at least put your bag away.
It looks like it's going to be
an apartment. Grandma wins.
I though it was going to be a business.
Now I have to clean the bath for one week...
They're both the same
in that it's just a big pillar.
Big pillar?
When that's finished, it means that a
big pillar is going to fit in that alley, right?
Pillar?
Oh.
See, if a pillar goes there...
I feel like this city is
going to just disappear.
All right! Grandma, that stage
you custom made was really hard.
I guess it's about time for a meal.
I'll help too.
You just came home,
so get yourself relaxed there.
That's right. You just left
your bag there too... Ah! No!
Heh, you deserved that.
Wha?! It stinks here! Bro!
Take your socks off before you get in there!
Take this!
No! I'm going to catch athlete's foot
all over! I'll help you after all, Grandma!
It's so lively with your brother around.
But, I don't like the place stinking.
Seeing me all the way out here,
you really do like me, don't you?
That's not it! My favorite milk tea is at
the vending machine around here, that's it.
Ruko, don't make Grandma too worried, you hear?
Worried?
Grandma was telling me that you haven't
made friends yet after moving to this school.
I don't really need any friends.
Well, you're pretty bold,
so I'm not worried that much,
but Grandma is worried about you all the time.
Take this.
What's that?
Just take it.
My work buddy told me these
cards are a hit with the girls now.
I've seen some in my class playing this.
Use this to get in with everyone!
I'm making Grandma worried?
Well, see ya.
Wasn't it cold out there?
Coldy-coldy. Warmy-warmy.
Um, ah, I'm going to go and study now.
"Ruko"
I didn't really care too much for friends,
but making Grandma worried is...
The card called an LRIG is
the player's avatar... Is it this?
She's so cute! Um, on the
player's turn, this card...
Her voice is so cute too... Wait, what?!
Ouch...
Ru-chan? Is something the matter?
Grandma.
Did you fall down, Ru-chan?
You... don't hear that voice?
Voice?
Am I the only one who can hear her?
I'm fine, so you can go now.
I have to get back to my studying.
--Grandma, you can take a bath first, okay?
--Ru-chan?
It's cold, so make sure you
keep yourself warm in there.
Okay, okay.
Good night.
No! It's disappearing!
Don't make it disappear!
It's all because of that strange voice of yours.
Who are you?
--Why is a card able to speak?
--Battle!
Battle? You mean you want to have a card battle?
You can't eat right? You're made out of paper.
If you eat, the noodles will just make you wet.
Battle!
Well, even if you tell that to me...
It's a bit hard to ask here.
Wait a minute. Their cards don't
talk like you, right? I wonder why?
Found you!
Huh?
You're a Selector, right?
Selector?
Hey! Found your LRIG!
You can hear her voice?
Of course!
I have an LRIG too, you know?
It's Hanayo-san!
Come at me!
Come at me?
Perfect! No one's around!
Your card, Hanayo-san,
isn't like my card at all.
She doesn't purr like a cat,
and speaks normally.
Ruko-san, was it?
So you can hear Hanayo-san's voice too.
Huh? You can't hear her?
Well, I'm not a Selector after all. I have
Yuzuki speak in place of Hanayo-san instead.
Selector?
Let me explain.
Selectors are WIXOSS players who
are striving to be the "Eternal Girl."
Eternal?
If you win in battle,
the Selector can become their ideal self.
That form is what an "Eternal Girl" is.
You mean their wishes come true?
Well, something like that.
To be specific, that's a bit wrong there.
You become a person who can make the
most outrageous wishes or dreams come true.
Make wishes come true?
To have any dreams and wishes
be fulfilled is just a fantasy.
But, these cards can make that happen.
For that, you need to continue winning in battle.
Yet, not everyone has a deck which
has LRIGs with a mind of their own.
Only the chosen girls, the Selectors, have them.
Recently, famous people such as
female celebrities and sports players
"Everyone's playing this during their breaks"
made announcements that they're playing WIXOSS.
They're just looking for Selectors,
letting others know they own an LRIG too.
But, don't forget this.
If you lose 3 times in battle,
you lose your right to be a Selector.
Your right?
The moment you lose your
3rd battle, we disappear.
Your wishes won't come true,
and the world of WIXOSS, where you
battle to be the Eternal Girl, will close.
Thanks, Hanayo-san!
Okay then! Ruko, let's battle!
But, I don't have any wishes now, and...
That's okay! As long as we can battle,
it doesn't matter if you have a wish or not.
Battle! Battle! Battle!
See? She wants to fight too,
so come on, just one battle.
Okay, I guess so.
Great!
Yuzuki, isn't it too sudden to battle
when she doesn't know the rules?
No mercy! I'm gonna win this
before she gets to know the rules!
Open!
What is this place?
Um...
Battle!
Battle?
Yuzuki-san, Hanayo-san.
Great! I get to go first!
Okay then! It's your turn now, Ruko!
What do you mean by "turn"?
Can you hear me?
Kazuki!
It's just like the rules. Summon a SIGNI,
call out the name of your LRIG, and then attack.
Hey! Kazuki! Why are you on Ruko's side?!
He can't hear your voice from the outside.
Call her name.
Name? Uh...
T-Tama.
Why "Tama"?
Well, she makes sounds like the
cat I used to own with Grandma.
Tama!
Okay, I'll give it a try! Level 1, Grow,
summoning a SIGNI! Tama, attack!
Tama!
It's gone... It's really gone! Is it okay?!
Relax, it's only a game.
It'll recover at the next battle.
Recover? I see.
See what you've done, Kazuki?! I could've
won this easy if she didn't know the rules!
Can you hear me too, Yuzuki?
I don't think this is fair after all.
Aren't the battles supposed
to be fair and square?
It should be even more so, especially if
this is a battle to make your wish come true.
Level 3, Grow!
Battle! Fun!
T-Tama?
More! Battle!
Why? Why is she so strong even though
she's just started? If this keeps up...
Hey, Yuzuki! You want to
be beat here or something?!
Hanayo-san.
Get a hold of yourself! You said that
you wanted to make Kazuki your own...
Noooooo! D-Don't say that!
Hanayo-san! Hanayo-san!
Both of you! Get back here!
What are you kids doing? Lunch is over!
Hurry and get back to class!
Yes!
Um, wait a moment. What happens to that battle?
If an external influence terminates the battle,
losses are not counted. It's a no-gamer.
Thank goodness.
Um, about that earlier...
Ah! Let's go, Kazuki!
Okay, um, laters!
Well, that was weird, wasn't it, Tama?
Hmm?
She's been sleeping all
the way since. She's so cute!
So cute, but...
They use up their powers in battle.
When the battle ends, they usually just sleep.
It's the same with Hanayo-san too.
Yuzuki-san?
Um? Isn't Kazuki-kun around?
Just because we're twins,
we're not always together.
Um, can you not say anything about that earlier?
What do you mean?
Stop playing dumb!
I really don't know what you mean.
Um, do you want to come over to my house?
Ru-chan's friend?
H-Hello.
Can we play at home?
Yes, yes. Oh, Grandma's got
something to do, so I'm stepping out.
You can take the rice crackers too.
"Ruko"
I see. So you really didn't hear me.
I guess not.
Well, there goes all that worrying.
The thing you didn't want me
to know is your wish, right?
Yeah.
A wish that I want to come true.
A wish that can't be fulfilled
just by doing your best or anything.
Yuzuki-san.
But, since I encountered
WIXOSS and Hanayo-san,
I now know things like miracles can happen.
If so, I want to believe.
With the miracle granted from WIXOSS,
I want to be the Eternal Girl,
and have another miracle fulfilled.
A miracle granted by the cards...
Well then. Let's battle again.
I'll lose to you, Yuzuki-san.
I'm not interested in this
Eternal Girl thing anyways.
That's not necessary.
I mean, if Kazuki ends up hating me for that,
then that already defeats the purpose of my wish.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Excuse me here.
Grandma!
Well, you young girls would like
these instead of rice crackers, right?
Cake!
Tarts, macarons, bavarois... Grandma,
there's so much we can't eat all of them.
Thank you very much!
So good! Tastes so good! All of them!
That's good. Ru-chan,
you have such a wonderful friend.
Now I'm recharged. Well, see you again.
Okay, see you.
I don't know WIXOSS
too well yet, and it's a bit scary,
but I owe it all to you for making Grandma happy.
Ru-chan, dinner is ready.
Coming! Um, I want to show
you something, Grandma.
What's that?
I made one more new friend.
Her name is Tama.
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
Me...
I can't lose!
Tama!
Please battle with me!
Urazoe Iona?
P-Please!
"That Poisonous Meeting."