Hey!
Let me see it!
Wait-
Jesus Christ...
Why the heck do you have this?
You didn't have to hide it...
If you really wanted to...
Well, I have to apologize!
What I actually wanted was
Hideyoshi's picture, not your-
Can't breathe!
This is the last straw!
Feel my wrath!
This is your payback for always being a bitch to me!
Teacher!
I request a mock-ESB!
Permission to summon, please!
All right.
Approved!
Summoning Being...
Summon!
Huh?
Summon! Summon! Summon!
That's odd...
What's going on?
Summon! Summon! Summon!
Summon! Summon!!!!!!!!!
Approval denied!
What the...
I can't control the ESB field!
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Disaster always strikes unannounced.
Who is it?
The password?
I lust.
Good.
Do you have it?
Where's the cash?
Hell yeah, Hideyoshi in a waitress outfit!
Makes me glad to be alive...
That's not all.
This is a picture of him changing.
It'll cost you double, though.
Can't you cut me a deal?
I'm already living off salt water this week.
Buy one, get one free.
God...
Damn.
This is so much work...
Another layer of security?
The pass is...
Shit!
Fuck...
I almost pissed my pants.
Looks like we have a problem here.
Excuse me.
Director.
There seems to be a problem with the summoning system.
Yeah.
I can see that.
Even here?
What's going on?
Do you ever shut up?
Get away.
Ow! Holy shit!
Stop it!
Yoshii.
What the hell did you do this time?
Why am I always the number one suspect?
What did you do, Akihisa?
You'd better fess up.
We won't get mad.
You guys too?
Well, your Being's the only one that's acting up.
Huh?
How?
Maybe the system is unstable...
I'll try to summon mine.
Summon!
A grown-up version, huh?
Please don't look at it!
Eye
Yuuji, no looking.
I wonder if that's what Himeji will look like in a few years...
She's so... well-developed.
Hey, I'm going to be too...
Summon!
Look at that.
She's just like her master, completely undev-
Holy shit, a Frankensteiner!
Wait a minute!
Maybe I can get a nude shot if I do this.
No, please don't!
You're brilliant, Voyeur!
Please don't!
Stop it!!!
Skeletal frame.
Well, it sounded like a good idea.
Maybe if I back up some more...
This is pretty cool.
I think I'll summon mine as well.
Summon!
Don't do that...
Don't, Mr. Wolf!
A babe!
Please stop.
I knew it, Hideyoshi!
I wasn't mistaken about you!
This is obviously a mistake!
There's an error in the system!
Then...
I guess I'll try too.
Summon!
Fabulous...
I'll do it too...
Summon!
They look so cute together.
What about you, Voyeur?
Summon.
Yuji
You're so stubborn...
Don't you...
Hang-
want me?
Kouta
Don't think so
highly of yourself...
You said you wouldn't do a thing to me.
I love you.
You liar.
Wait a minute!
No! It's malfunctioning...!
Don't do it!
Traitor.
What does yours look like, Yoshii?
Come on, show us!
All right, I'll give it a shot.
Summon!
This is dumb...
Why is mine the odd one out?
Oh, they're back to normal.
What's going on?
They're going out of control!
Where are they going?
What's going on?
The teacher's Beings were being held near the core,
so they've completely frozen. They can't be summoned.
Meanwhile, the students' Beings are out of control.
I can't access the server room's security system.
Server Room
UPS
Power
Core
Security
Doors
This means that we can't open the
doors. There's no way to fix the core.
Couldn't we turn off the power to the system?
It'll keep running for at least a month with the UPS.
That would mean...
that we'd have to bruteforce our way in.
We're holding a presentation about the security system tomorrow.
We can't do that if there's a hole in the wall.
Then what should we do?
Oh, I know.
Why don't we put the idiot to work for a bit?
Berserk
Counter-Measure Headquarters
Exam Summoning System
Berserk
Counter-Measure Headquarters
I'm supposed to fix what, now?
The Beings of Punishment Inspectors run under a different system,
so they're not affected by the
malfunction like the other students'.
I see.
So that's why Akihisa's Being was acting differently from ours.
But I couldn't summon it properly.
That's because you tried to summon it in a corrupted Instructor Field.
But you have your own field, right?
Oh yeah!
I have this iron bracelet.
Go into the server room with your Being and connect the cable.
After that, I'll shut off the security system from the terminal and open the doors.
Heh. This plan wouldn't work without a Being that can manipulate physical space.
My Being can't go through walls, though...
There's an AC vent that's used for system cooling.
Your Being should be small enough to pass through.
How is he supposed to control it without being able to see where it's going?
Here.
A video camera and a transmitter.
If you give these to your Being, you'll be able to see the inside of the vent.
You're so smart, Voyeur!
I'm surprised you have those on you.
What do you use them for?
Don't treat him like that!
He's actually a great guy!
He's just a little, well, really perverse!
I haven't even said anything...
Well, Akihisa's his VIP customer.
The iron bracelet can only create a short-range summoning field.
You'll have to control your Being from right outside the server room.
We'll direct you from here.
So that's the entrance.
Awaken!
Summon!
Go!
The Being has entered the vent.
Course clear.
Keep going forward, Akihisa.
Roger that!
Are you certain about this?
He's under special observation...
In other words, he's a problem child.
We don't have a choice.
He's the only one who can use the iron bracelet.
Turn right at 3 meters ahead.
Turn left at the first cross road.
This is a friggin' maze.
Why is it so confusing?
It's another brand of security.
Shit, I'm feeling numb!
I'm losing points!
What the hell?
There's a poison swamp.
Why the hell would you do that!?
It's another brand of security.
We'll avoid the danger zones.
Turn right at the next corner.
I can see a light.
You're almost there.
Keep going straight.
Huh?
What are those?
Summoned Beings?!
Berserk Beings have appeared!
Incoming attack!
Make it stop, Yuuji!
I can't.
I can't control him!
No...
No!
This can't be happening!
Stop this, please!
Stop it!
Yuuji! Hideyoshi! Minori! Himeji! Dad!
Stop!
Make it stop!
Those who were KIA must receive supplementary lessons.
This can't be!
Berserk and Maze and
Beings Instrumentality Project
Are you okay, Yoshii?
I've seen Hell.
How was the lesson?
We'll resume the mission.
Please take the recovery exam and replenish your points.
He'll have to get a really high
score to survive those attacks...
Yoshii.
Would you like me to help you study?
A private lesson with you!?
Really?
You sure pick up stuff like that quickly, eh?
It's useless unless it shows immediate results.
Well, then I have a great idea.
Points
I see.
He can get easy points with these easy problems.
It's kinda cheating, though.
Wow.
Akihisa's power level is off the charts!
You're doing great, Yoshii.
Keep it up, Aki.
What did you get wrong, Akihisa?
The Taika Reform was in 645!
How could you possibly forget that after what happened a little while ago!?
That's why I got confused!
Well, anyway, he's leveled up quite a bit, hasn't he?
He should be able to deal with the enemy attacks now.
Resume mission.
All right.
Summon!
I am so gonna beat it this time.
All right.
Take a left at that crossroad.
Roger that.
The poison swamp.
I guess it hurts no matter how high your level is.
Look, I'm not a lab rat!
Take a right when you reach the end.
Okay.
Be careful, Akihisa.
If you touch it...
Yoshii?
Aki?
I can't breathe!
I told you to watch out!
It's a bad habit of mine...
That's...
All right! I'm not gonna lose again!
Victory is mine!
Don't let your guard down!
Tsuchiya's coming.
Worry not!
The subject is history!
He's only good at health, so
there's no way he can beat me!
Danger
There stood a poison swamp.
Those who were KIA must receive supplementary lessons!
That isn't fair!
The Beings lost on their own!
Resistance is futile!
I made it.
There should be a disconnected cable.
Connect it.
Roger.
There it is.
Minami?
Aki!
Run!
But...
Now!
If you don't...
My...
Himeji...
Wooden Horse!
Minami!
Yoshii!
Aki!
God dammit!
Something's approaching!
Phase synchronization detected in the field!
A Being is approaching!
Sissy!
Miharu?
It might be just your Being, but I won't let anyone else have it either!
I won't allow it to touch anyone's except mine!
Now's my chance!
Supplementary lessons!
No!!
Yay!
I'm sorry, Himeji.
I did it!
Yoshii! You won't make it!
Run!
But...
I've come this far.
There's no turning back.
Yoshii!
I'm...
so close...
This isn't going to work.
We should pull him back!
I don't think teachers should be forcing students to do-
Not yet!
I'm still alive.
You don't have enough points left!
The difference in strength is too big!
But...
That doesn't mean...
Strength?
That's it!
Difference in points doesn't always equal a difference in strength.
Remember how my Being got stronger!
Himeji, take the recovery exam!
Please!
I see what you mean.
Ms. Takahashi!
I'd like to take the test!
If your points increase, his
chances will be less than zero.
Please grade this!
Yoshii...
Mizuki Himeji.
0 points.
You did good, kid.
The system is beginning to recover.
Looks like the problem's solved for now.
My first kiss had the flavor of strawberry milk.
The sun sets as I push my bike home.
My mind blanks out as I sink into delusion.
Life spins me around and watches me fall.
Every day is a day to remember.
Let's hold hands until we touch the sky.
I get the feeling our future is promising.
Tomorrow will bring the sun and smiles.
Yoshii!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
That was nothing.
Those who were KIA must receive supplementary lessons!
Well...
I'll see you later.
Yeah...
Himeji...
What are you looking so blue for?
Oww!
What the hell was that for?
My points!
Don't whine about a couple of points.
Go take your supplementary lessons.
Yoshii.
Yeah.
It was a pretty big gamble letting the class F kids handle this,
but I'm glad it worked out in the end.
I didn't see it as a gamble.
You'll understand one day.
How to deal with idiots, that is.
Miss, me too...
Question 9:
We use the unit "cup" to measure the bust size of women.
Describe the size of a basic A cup.
Minami Shimada.
No comment.
Next episode: Kiss and Bust and Ponytail.
This will be on your test.