Let me tell you a story about my past.
It was back when I was in sixth grade.
One of the girls in my class brought a box
with around seven or eight hamsters to me.
She'd carelessly let them breed, and couldn't keep them all,
so she didn't know what to do.
I took them home, filled a large jar with water, and dropped them all in it.
When I returned to my room after dinner three hours later, I was fascinated by what I saw.
One of the hamsters had managed to stay alive
by standing on the lifeless corpses of the others.
It honestly gave me goosebumps.
I decided to keep that one, naming it "Spice."
What I saw reminded me of
the short story, "The Spider's Thread."
Have you heard of it?
A sinner named Kandata is a cold-blooded criminal who has been sent to the depths of Hell,
but he has performed a single act of compassion in his life: sparing a spider's life.
Moved by it, Buddha lowers a
silvery spider thread from Paradise.
Kandata begins to climb it, but he kicks off all the other sinners who try to follow him.
At that moment...
The thread snaps, casting him
back down to the depths of Hell.
You might not believe this, but I'll tell you anyway.
Actually, you might understand.
Ever since I met Spice,
every now and then, I've seen a spider's thread before me.
I've killed everyone whom I saw with one dangling above their heads.
But this one time, a boy foiled my plans.
And then, a spider thread appeared above his head too.
Yashiro!
I know what lies in your future!
But the boy didn't die.
I named him "Spice" and decided to observe him.
That's you, Satoru.
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
I stopped and looked back at the never-ending days with a sigh
Finally I realized my memories would fade into nothing
And a small part of my heart has been grieving since
I can't let it slip away again
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
Or I'll never be able to tell you on that day
That I regret everything that's happened around me since
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
Each day tears another hole in me
It has to be you
ERASED
That'll be 987 yen.
Thank you. Come again.
Come to think of it, didn't Satoru mention this once?
You can actually take a direct train to Ueno.
It's true.
Just where was he goin' with that?
Heisei 15
Heisei 15
TUE
WED
THU
Fight! Wonder Guy
TV
Theme Song
B Side
The Wandering Man
Good morning, Satoru.
Funabashi General Hospital
Yeah, this is a miracle.
It's hard to believe you've spent the last fifteen years in a coma.
Fif... teen... years...?
Wow, you can speak already?
Looks like you'll be able to start rehab soon.
Mom apparently dedicated four hours to looking after my body every single day for the last fifteen years.
And for the last three years, she's been using what's called an EMS device to prepare for the day I came to.
She kept my joints and muscles in shape.
I was 139cm tall back in fifth grade,
but now I'm 169cm tall.
Dr. Kitamura kept alternating between "This is all thanks to your mother" and "I can't believe this" over and over.
All right, Satoru.
I think it's about time.
Please answer this question.
What's the last thing you remember from fifteen years ago?
The last thing I remember...
Huh?
What?
What happened, again?
Those memories were locked up behind a thick, imposing door.
Want to see?
You're taking it in stride, huh?
I mean, your face must look a lot different from when you were eleven.
But well, considering how your memories are all jumbled up,
maybe you're still having trouble zeroing in on your own identity.
At first, I accepted his words at face value,
but the term "Heisei era,"
which I should never have seen before,
Heisei 15
seemed somehow familiar.
"Perseverance."
"Cardiometer."
"Destitute."
"Arbitration."
I can read all of these words.
Just when did I learn them?
What is with me?
Good morning, Satoru.
Morning.
You have visitors.
Long time no see, Satoru.
You seem well.
Kobayashi Kenya and Sugita Hiromi were two classmates I was particularly close to.
Kenya had become a lawyer, and Hiromi a doctor.
I had fun talking to them about the most pointless things.
Kenya looked like he wanted to ask me something, but I think Mom had told him to tread carefully.
So we ended up just chatting that day.
Laters.
Laters!
There were a lot of questions I wanted to ask them too,
Fujinuma Satoru
but it seemed like Mom was trying to avoid having me bring up my past.
Believing that I would wake up someday,
Mom's been living solely for my sake for fifteen whole years.
If she doesn't want me to remember, then maybe I don't have to.
Are you okay?
Shall we call it a day?
Satoru!
Congratulations, Kayo.
Future
Episode 11
I got married. I'm Sugita Kayo now.
Oh, so Hiromi's the father?
Yeah.
I knew he wanted to say something to me.
I guess it was about you and the child.
Probably.
Oh, yeah. Looks like the baby inherited Hiromi's long eyelashes.
Yeah, though it's a boy.
His name's Mirai.
Mirai... "Future," huh?
That's a great name.
Satoru...
Honestly, we didn't know if it was right for us to find happiness by ourselves.
I mean, it could've been our fault that you ended up in a coma.
It kind of felt...
like we were leaving you behind.
Kayo, I hold my fate in my own hands.
You don't have to feel guilty about anything.
I'm sure I am who I am right now as a result of my own choices.
For a guy who spent fifteen years in a coma,
you've still got the gift of gab.
But you know what, Satoru?
Back then, I could only ever picture a life of solitude for myself,
but now I have a family to call my own.
And it's all because you were there for me.
Thank you.
"Thank you," huh?
What did I do?
There, there!
Hungry, are we?
There, there.
Satoru?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Sorry for springing all this on you at once.
Must've worn you out.
Bye. I'll come visit you again.
Sure. Laters.
Oh, you're back already?
Yeah.
Hinazuki dropped by earlier.
Yeah, I ran into her too.
Her baby's adorable, isn't he?
Say, Mom...
What is it?
They're here again?
Who is?
Gossip magazine photographers.
They want to cover your story now that
you've awoken from a fifteen-year coma.
Oh, right.
You were about to say something, weren't you?
Nah.
It's nothing.
Come in.
Hello.
Thank you for doing this.
Dr. Kitamura, when will I be able to walk again?
I couldn't say. It's all up to you.
Then please double my rehab regimen going forward.
I want to walk outdoors as soon as possible.
O-Oh...
I'll consider it.
Excuse me.
Yes. Thank you, Director.
He's steadily recovering.
He could regain his memories any time now.
No.
Like I said the other day, I'll have to turn you down.
My patient isn't some guinea pig—
Goodbye.
Fujinuma Satoru
That's great, Satoru!
Your limbs have gotten a lot stronger.
Congrats, Satoru!
You're amazing, Mr. Fujinuma!
I can't believe you actually went the distance!
Great job hanging in there.
Satoru.
Kenya's here to see you.
Hey, Kenya.
Fujinuma Satoru
Sorry for coming so late.
Nah. Thanks for coming.
Hello, Satoru.
Nice to meet you.
I used to work with your mother.
You met me several times before you started grade school.
Come on, that was over twenty years ago!
There's no way he'd remember.
Bye. I'll come again.
Take care.
We've waited fifteen long years.
What's the point of rushing now?
Let's take it slow and steady.
Right.
Hello.
Oh...
So you've got surgery in two weeks, Kumi.
My sister's giving me this "bone marrow" thing.
They say that'll cure me.
But I'm scared.
Is it true you were asleep for fifteen years?
You've been here around three months, huh?
Yep.
I've been doing my best so I'd look good in front of you.
If you're gone, I'll lose all motivation.
Courage...
Want me to teach you how to muster up courage?
Picture the smiles of the people you care about.
With a smile on your own face, of course.
"A nomad in time.
Man who wakes up after
fifteen-year coma still likes little girls.
Adult in body, child at heart.
He gets discharged soon!"
How's that for a story?
Nice.
Sneak photography of civilians on
hospital grounds, libel, and trespassing.
More than enough to get you punished by law.
Get out of here right now.
That flower was really pretty.
Oh, Mr. Nishizono!
Hello!
Hey, Kumi.
Fujinuma Satoru...
Y-Yes?
It's me. Did you forget?
Well, I guess I've changed a lot myself.
Look. I was your homeroom teacher in fifth grade...
Yashiro Gaku.
Fujinuma Satoru
I go by Nishizono now.
I also changed my first name to Manabu.
Why did you change your name?
I got married five years ago and was adopted into my wife's family as a son-in-law.
My father-in-law had been a city councilor for ages,
but he passed away three years ago.
I inherited his constituency and became a councilor myself.
That's when I switched to the more common reading of my name.
So you're a politician now?
Yeah, but I'm still in my first year.
Well, I think you'll make a fine politician, Mr. Yashiro.
I met Kumi at a charity event for leukemia.
And I happened to know one of this hospital's directors, so I referred her here.
Is that so?
I found out that you'd regained consciousness much earlier,
but it took me this long to come visit you.
You came all the way to see me today?
I'd been eagerly waiting for you to wake for fifteen years.
Thank you.
Hey, we went through a lot together.
Sorry, I...
Yeah, I heard.
You haven't regained all your memories yet, right?
Don't worry. You can regain them one step at a time.
Hey.
Oh, Mr. Yashiro.
Are you going to see Kumi too?
Yes. I heard that her surgery's the day after tomorrow,
so today's the last day she can have visitors.
Yeah. I just saw her myself.
That said, she was fast asleep,
so there wasn't much conversation to be made.
Oh...
Maybe I should come back later, then.
Since you're here, mind chatting for a bit?
Sure, but we don't want the paparazzi interrupting us.
Why don't we go someplace quieter?
I found the perfect spot, actually.
Freight Elevator
You didn't know about this elevator, did you?
This is an adventure of sorts.
Freight Elevator
Press the roof button for me, would you?
That's a shame.
On a clear day, we'd get to see a beautiful sunset from here right about now.
Still, there won't be any creepy photographers up here either.
This place is technically off-limits, so keep this a secret.
Reminds me of how you, Kenya, Hiromi,
and the rest kept going to this "secret base" of yours.
Yashiro.
I've...
regained my memories!
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory