Morning, huh...?
Yeah...
And we didn't sleep a wink...
Not after seeing that...
What's on the agenda today for Operation
Scare Minorin, Cue the White Knight?
How can we expect to carry out our plan
when we're scared stiff ourselves?
Shut your trap.
We have to, or else our
future's set in stone.
Well yeah, but...
What do we even do?
What would freak Minorin out?
You want to scare Kushieda?
Ki—
Y-You're up early, Kitamura.
What kind of mischief are you up
to first thing in the morning?
M-Mischief?
Wait, were you two responsible for
Kushieda's meltdown yesterday?
I'm right.
Honestly...
Why would you do that?
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Uh, about that...
It's our gift to her.
Your gift?
Mi-Minorin actually loves scary stuff
more than anything in the world.
And since she loves being
shocked and scared,
we wanted to make this
summer memorable for her...
Hey, Kitamura...
I see.
No wonder her eyes sparkled
like she wanted more!
Okay!
Count me in!
Let us work together and scare
the bejeezus out of Kushieda!
Uh, well...
I know! Let's get Ami in on this.
Dumb-chi, too?
She should be familiar with the area.
All right!
Strike while the iron's hot!
Uh, but won't Kawashima refuse?
Leave it to me!
I promise I'll convince her to help!
No need to worry!
Wh-What do we do, Ryuji?
What do we do?
There's nothing we can do...
Seaweed...
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Fireworks
What's this?
I was gonna make breakfast,
but someone beat me to the punch.
Morning, Takasu-kun.
H-Hey.
What are you making?
Um, boxed lunches.
Since we're spending all
day down at the beach.
You mean you woke up
early to make lunches?
This won't do!
Chef, allow me to assist
you in your endeavors!
I am at your command!
R-Right...
Could you slice the onions, then?
Yessir! Happy to slice and dice!
What's on the menu, chef?
Egg salad and tuna salad sandwiches...
And stew using the leftover curry
from yesterday, I guess.
Ooh! That sounds fantastic!
You've got a good grip.
Ooh, was that a compliment?
Yay.
And the way you washed
those dishes... You're good.
Well, both of my parents work.
And I used to make lunches when
my little brother was home.
You have a little brother?
The hard-working baseball
player, Watson-kun!
- Ow, that stings!
- Whoa! You okay?
Silly me.
Takasu-kun?
Oh, I-I need to peel the apples.
You're really good at cooking, Takasu-kun.
Last night's curry was stupendous.
I didn't do anything special...
I think it's wonderful
how responsible you are.
Our other classmates never
get to see this side of you.
Makes me feel kinda special.
The lucky girl you marry someday
will be very happy.
Kyushyieda!
Yes, Tak-yasu-kyun!?
A-About yesterday...
Oh yeah, that...
Could you keep it a secret?
I've never talked about that
stuff with anyone before.
How do I put this...?
I let my guard down.
Said too much.
But I'm glad it was to you, Takasu-kun.
Thanks for listening.
Shoot!
You klutz!
But that was cute!
D-Don't call me cute.
Just kidding.
Anyway, chef.
What's next?
Oh, right...
Mix it all up?
Mix everything together?
Whoa!
The sun is burning bright!
You small-town angel!
Minorin's so excited.
Now we just have to stick to the plan.
Huh? Where's Kawashima?
She's helping out, right?
Yeah, Ami will lead us to a nearby
cavern, where we can set up.
So everything's riding on her...
Why isn't she here?
No idea.
I'll get her.
Taiga, hold on to this for me.
Huh?
H-Hey!
Here, I'll carry it. Seems
a bit heavy for you.
I-It's okay.
I'm good.
Kawashima, you there?
Yes.
We're leaving.
Man...
What's the holdup?
Admiring my reflection.
Care to join me?
Seriously?
Wow...
Isn't this crazy?
How's my cleavage?
Not bad, I guess?
That's all you have to say?
Oh right, you saw me
in a bikini at school.
That's not the point...
But this part comes off.
See?
Put it back on! Put it back on!
What?
No, you put it on for me.
Not happening!
You're so heartless.
Don't be that way. I won't help.
D-Don't say that...
Hey.
Why do you want to entertain Minori-chan?
What?
Wh-Why...?
Tell me, or I'm not helping.
You've got five seconds.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Sure about this?
Two.
One.
Zero.
No longer helping.
Taiga!
Bring it on!
C'mon!
- Boom! Blam! Kaboom!
- Cold!
- What are they doing?
- C'mon, why not?
Can't be bothered.
But you're the only one who knows
the interior of the cavern.
I drew you a map.
Sorry, but you'll have to do
this on your own, Yusaku.
Hey...
No complaints, right?
This was your choice, after all.
Sorry, Takasu.
Ami suddenly...
It's fine.
I'll come with you.
It'll be tough alone.
But it'd look suspicious if we both left.
Don't worry.
I'll manage.
I've come up with three award-winning ideas.
Kushieda will be half-crazed
with fear, guaranteed.
R-Really...?
Hey! Kushieda! Aisaka!
What is it!?
I need to use the bathroom!
Man, this is so good!
Takasu-kun is a genius in the kitchen!
Well, you helped.
She did?
You betcha!
This girl did the mixin' for
your egg salad sandwich!
Oh? Eating without me?
Jeez, Kitamura-kun!
What's wrong with you!?
Don't announce to a bunch of girls
that you're going to the bathroom!
Oops, sorry.
- Plus, you took forever! Where did you...
- We're all set.
- Oh, does that mean he was...?
- Okay.
Hey, what's up?
What're you talking about?
Oh, Kushieda.
Actually...
Hey, Minori-chan...
There's a beautiful cavern down by the cove.
A cavern, you say!?
It's my special place.
Ooh, special!
Wanna stroll down there?
Ooh, a stroll!
Sounds great!
Let's do it!
Can't wait!
Oof!
Ooh, so this is it.
Amin's special path...
Danger
S-Sure looks inviting...
Doesn't it?
Okay, let's go inside.
B-But doesn't it feel like
something might pop out?
Wow, maybe we'll encounter
an unidentified creature?
That's fine, as long as it's alive...
Great idea.
We should try to capture it alive!
- Yeah, now I'm pumped!
- Guess we were right to accept his help.
- Here's to an intense summer memory!
- Such beautiful manipulation...
Okay!
Kitamura Exploration Party, advance!
We're going to find the
two-headed golden cobra!
It's so dark, and narrow, and scary!
I believe I've heard that line before.
This passage is bigger than I expected.
Near the entrance, sure.
Hey, don't get distracted.
This isn't your typical test of courage.
Understand?
R-Right...
There's a step down here, so be careful.
This is the first gateway.
What?
Fried tofu.
Nice...
Kitamura's certainly book smart...
But he's a moron.
D-Don't badmouth Kitamura-kun!
Hey, isn't it kinda cold?
We're pretty far in.
No, that wasn't what I meant...
What's wrong?
I smell ketchup.
Hey, what are you doing?
Shriek
Here.
Is that...written in blood?
Shriek...
So this was the second one...
Yup, total imbecile.
I...I said not to badmouth him!
Don't sigh, either!
What?
This is...
Hey! What's up?
Ta-Ta-Ta-Takasu-kun!
Th-That's...
No, uh...
A woman's hair!
The curse of a heartsick woman
who wandered in here post-breakup,
only to meet an unnatural death!
No! Lemme out!
Please let me out!
- Minorin, calm down!
- No! Lemme out!
- Set up some tricks of your own, huh?
- Please let me out!
- But I didn't...
- The curse!
- My last one's fifty meters ahead.
- The horror!
It's a real doozy!
O-Okay...
Come on, Kushieda!
Pull yourself together!
Kitamura-kun sure can do anything.
- Minorin's terrified.
- Deep breaths. In and out.
- It wasn't Kitamura.
- Begin by stretching!
It wasn't me, either.
- Th-That means...
- One, two, three, four!
This isn't a prank.
- It's real, just like the stuff last night...
- Five, six, seven, eight!
- Minorin!
- One, two, three, four!
It'd be bad to get separated,
so let's hold hands.
Yeah? Okay! Hold on real tight!
Good!
Now we're warmed up.
Let's proceed!
- What a waste of time...
- Kitamura Exploration Party! Tally ho!
I'm gonna take a shortcut outta here.
H-Hey, Kawashima!
Where are you going?
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun?
Do we have to keep going?
The exit is this way.
Right, Ami?
What happened to Ami and Takasu?
Ryuji?
Wait up, Kawashima!
Do you even know where you're going?
Of course.
Are you that worried about getting
separated from the others?
I just...don't like dark places...
Really now...?
Then what would you do if I ditched you?
Scared?
Worried about getting separated
from me now?
Lonely?
Want to stay real close to me?
H-Hey...
Do you need me?
Th-This isn't the time for that!
Why, in a hurry to get back to Minori-chan?
Seriously!
I don't think she's a good match for you.
What?
I-I don't think...
Your perfect match would be...
Wh-What?
Huh?
What?
Where...are we?
No way! We're lost?
C'mon, stop messing around.
I wouldn't joke about this!
Wh-What'll we do?
H-Hey...
I-It's okay!
I'm sure the others will
come looking for us!
Don't be scared!
I'm here!
Sorry.
There's no need for you to apologize!
That stuff about being lost...was a lie.
As if I'd ever get lost!
You-fool-ish-boy.
That hurts!
Gross, Takasu-kun.
Your hand's so slimy.
This isn't the time to be laughing!
But you were acting like a kid!
I-I was really scared!
Takasu-kun...
You're pretty lame.
There you go again...
Still...
It's not a turn-off.
You know how I said that you and
Minori-chan don't make a good match?
I meant it.
Because...
You're like the moon.
What's that mean?
Minori-chan's like the sun.
Get too close, and you'll get burned.
I mean, you wouldn't be able to
whack her with tofu, would you?
Adoration never leads to
a balanced relationship.
What you really need...
is someone like me.
That was...
Kushieda's voice!
Wait! Takasu-kun!
Sorry, I'm...
It's okay.
Let's hurry!
R-Right!
Kushieda!
Ryuji!
Takasu! Ami!
You guys okay?
Kitamura!
Where's Kushieda?
What happened?
Well...
Kushieda was taken by something...
T-Taken by what!?
I don't know...
But there's something here...
And it took Kushieda?
Huh? Batteries running low?
Takasu, lend me yours.
Sure.
What's this sound?
A voice?
Kushieda! I'm coming!
H-Hey!
Kitamura!
Ki-Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun!
- Kitamura-kun! Kitamura-kun!
- Wh-What's going on!?
Don't stray too far!
Try to stay calm!
I don't care anymore.
If that's what you want...
It's on!
What!?
Taiga!?
Tai—!
Stop! Stop!
Kitamura-kun! There's been an accident!
We have to rescue Taiga!
On it!
You okay, Aisaka?
K-Kita...
Kitamura-kun...
Kitamura!?
You're late, Watson-kun.
Ku...
Kushieda?
Yes.
I am Kushieda Minori,
also known as Minorin.
I am the culprit!
And...
he was my accomplice!
The hair in Takasu's room.
The crumpled dress in Taiga's.
And everything else, was all our doing!
So sorry.
I mean, you guys were really
failing at scaring me,
so I got the urge to show
you how it's done.
That was how you scare someone.
So you knew it was us?
Pretty obvious, the way you
two kept sneaking around.
So I recruited Kitamura-kun to
my side and set you up.
It was so much fun.
Thanks.
You're not mad?
Not at all!
I love scary stuff!
Think of Brer Rabbit and the briar patch.
If I say I'm scared of ghosts and occult stuff,
somebody's bound to try to scare me.
It lets me sit back and enjoy.
Okay, confession time's done.
It's lit!
Isn't it pretty?
This was one crazy day.
Honestly...
What a pain...
About what you were saying before...
I didn't get a chance to give
you a proper answer.
I'd feel lonely if you weren't around.
But this isn't about how I would feel.
It's about whether you would
be lonely, isn't it?
I've never given it so much as a thought.
Think about it, then.
Seriously.
But won't it hurt?
If you start to feel pain, express it.
After all, we're...
On equal ground?
Hey...
Sometimes, Takasu-kun...
You're way too nice.
'Sup, Takasu-kun!?
This is our last night here.
Are you enjoying yourself?
Kushieda...
Um...
Th-Thanks.
I was completely fooled,
and utterly petrified...
But being with you is fun,
no matter what's going on.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
I had a blast.
The curry was wonderful too.
You even listened to my weird
spiel without laughing.
You understood me.
Sorry for scaring you.
I wanted to show you a ghost
and kinda went overboard.
Show me a ghost?
Uh-huh.
You said you wanted to see one.
Oh...
Tell me, why were you trying to scare me?
W-Well, just because...
Taiga told me you didn't like that stuff.
So you wanted to tease me?
I don't believe it.
You'd never do anything to
make someone feel bad.
You're always thinking about
how to make people happy.
So why would you do this?
I want to know the answer.
It's a mystery to me.
I wanted to show you...a ghost.
I wanted to make you believe
that ghosts exist.
You can't give up on something
just because you can't see it.
That's how I feel.
I see.
Then next time, let's look for UFOs.
A real one, not just a satellite.
And after UFOs, we can find...
Oh, a tsuchinoko would be good!
If I find the things I want to see...
If my world truly can change...
Then...
Kushieda!
A UFO...
went kaboom.
It's like a dream come true...
I saw one!
I actually saw one!
Is a galactic war breaking out!?
We must defend Earth!
Trip's not over until we're home.
Don't relax just yet!
Maybe I'll head to my parents' place.
See you later!
Want to drop by the supermarket
and do some shopping?
I'm exhausted, so don't
go all housewife on me.
Yes, ma'am...
It's just...there's a special sale today...
Seriously, shut up.
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning Love
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
The Culture Festival.
Chills from a band performance...
Thrills from a cosplay cafe...
Friendships renewed over the campfire...
And leg-spreading at the wrestling show!
What are you up to?