Over a century ago, mankind suddenly faced a new enemy.
The difference of power between mankind and their newfound enemy was overwhelming.
Soon, mankind found itself driven to the brink of extinction.
The surviving humans built three Walls:
the Maria, the Rose, and the Sina.
Within these Walls, they enjoyed a century of peace.
However...
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
That Day
Fall of Shiganshina (pt 2)
Until that time a wretched soul and parted.
From God was I, and wholly avaricious.
Now, as thou seest, I here am punished for it.
What avarice doth is here made manifest.
In the purgation of these souls converted,
and no more bitter pain the Mountain hath.
Stop! Let go!
What more, O Avarice, canst thou do to us,
since thou my blood so to thyself hast drawn,
it careth not for its own proper flesh?
What more, O Avarice—
Eren? What?
We were so close to saving Mom!
Why the hell did you do that?!
We could've saved Mom!
Cut it out.
Eren!
Eren...
You couldn't help your mother because you lacked the strength.
But I...
I couldn't face that Titan
because I lacked the courage!
I'm sorry.
It's happening again.
Hurry to the inner gate!
Use all the ferries to evacuate Shiganshina!
Hurry up! Otherwise you'll be eaten!
Places like Shiganshina are small, enclosed towns projecting from the main Walls intended as bait to attract the Titans,
thereby reducing the costs and manpower required for defense.
As a result of this design,
the people of Shiganshina could only escape
the onslaught of the Titans through a single gate.
We'll be okay, right?
Toss all luggage! We'll fit as many people as we can on board!
Armin, sit down.
But Eren and Mikasa aren't here yet.
There they are!
Eren...
Now is not the time to talk to them.
Poor souls. From the looks of it, they saw hell.
Don't just stand there! Hurry up!
What are you waiting for?!
Hurry up! They're coming!
This can't be happening.
God, please save us.
Hey, what the hell are you guys doing?!
This ship is full! We're leaving!
Please, let us on! At least my child!
I'm sorry, but we can't do that!
Go!
Let him on!
Let us get on!
You fool! What are you aiming at?!
B-But we can't accurately hit moving targets with these!
Who the hell cares?! Hurry up and load the next round!
It's hopeless!
The gate is closing!
No... They're leaving us behind!
Hey!
Don't close it yet! Just wait a little longer!
We've still got people out there!
If they break through this gate, we'll lose far more than just this district!
Mankind will be pushed back to the next Wall!
That doesn't make it okay to just leave them for dead!
Hurry up and close it!
The Titans are coming!
Hurry up and close the gate!
Stop!
Hey!
What the hell...
is that?
Fire!
What...
No effect!
Shit! Run!
Hurry!
The Titans are coming!
Close the gate!
Hurry! Close the gate!
The gate...
Currently Disclosable Information
Map of human activity [1/2]
This map, copied from the source material,
illustrates the size of the human activity area.
No information is available regarding areas beyond Wall Maria.
Currently Disclosable Information
Map of human activity [2/2]
The altitude of the human activity area
increases near the center.
This area is rich in water, minerals,
natural gas, and other resources.
Within a few hours after the fall of Shiganshina in Wall Maria's southern district,
the news had spread across the human territories like wildfire.
Is it true that Shiganshina has been invaded by the Titans?
South of Wall Rose
Trost District
Unbelievable. How could a Wall that lasted over a century crumble so quickly?
Believe it or not...
A ferry carrying refugees has already moored here!
We have reports that at least 500 people are on board.
The question is whether Shiganshina is all we've lost.
But there's no way they could breach Wall Maria.
Anyway, let's contact the Central and wait for orders.
We can't handle such an emergency on our own.
E-Excuse me!
We've just received word!
Wall Maria has fallen, and the Titans have advanced inside!
This is the end.
It's over.
The Titans will devour us all.
It's over?
I'll never be able to go home again.
Why?!
Why did I waste our final moments together on a petty argument?!
Now Mom's gone...
She's gone forever!
Why?
...because you lacked strength.
I... We humans are weak.
In our weakness, can we do nothing but cry?
I'll erase them from this world.
Eren?
What's is it, Eren?
I'm going to exterminate them.
Every single fucking one of them!
Eren...
That year, the Central Government decided to withdraw all human activity to inside Wall Rose.
The Titans devoured 10,000 people.
Eren... Carla... Mikasa...
I pray for your safety.
Eren...
Eren!
Dad! Please stop, Dad!
What are you trying to do?!
Just give me your arm!
No!
You've lost it ever since Mom died!
Let me go, Dad!
It's for your own good!
What are you talking about?!
Don't forget the key!
You must make it there!
But until you do—
Eren, are you okay?
You were crying out in your sleep.
I feel like I just saw my Dad.
Not possible. It was just a dream.
Was it?
Let's go.
They're handing out rations.
This place used to be a food storehouse.
All the refugees who came by ferry are gathered here.
Hey, no cutting in line!
Shut up!
I haven't eaten anything since yesterday!
We will still struggle for our survival.
Eren! Mikasa!
Armin?
Look! I made it!
Grandpa got these for us kids!
Thanks.
What's his deal?
That's just how it is.
There's probably not enough food for everyone.
This is an entire day's worth.
There are just too many refugees.
Plus, food has always been in short supply,
and you know how people look down on those from the outskirts.
Why do we have to give our food to outsiders?
I mean, the Titans broke through the Wall anyway.
They should've eaten more of them.
Eren!
This just makes the food shortage even worse.
What the hell are you doing, you brat?!
You don't know shit.
You've never seen it happen with your own eyes!
The way the Titans eat people...
Shut up!
We're sorry!
He's just upset because he's hungry.
That's why he's being such a brat.
We're really sorry!
Whatever.
We're the only reason you're not already dead.
You kids should learn to be more grateful.
Yes, sir!
Damn it...
I'd rather die than leech off scum like him.
I'm going back inside Wall Maria to kill off all the Titans.
Eren, you're not serious, right?
Dead serious!
I'm not like those people who act tough while they hide behind the Walls!
I don't need this crap!
Eren, you'll starve!
Doesn't it piss you off?
We can't retaliate against the Titans while living off the pity of others!
It's impossible!
Nothing can defeat them.
Our only choice is to live inside these Walls.
If you do anything rash, you'll die just like my parents did!
So that's why you're sucking up to these people?!
Aren't you ashamed?!
Right now... Right now that's all we can do!
That's just an excuse!
Just keep on living like livestock, you pathetic weakling!
Mikasa?
If Armin's a weakling, then so are you and I.
We couldn't even escape the Titans or flee the city on our own.
Even the food we're eating came from someone else.
There's absolutely no chance weaklings like us could defeat even one Titan.
What's important is surviving, just like your mother said.
Mikasa?
Eat. Eat, and survive.
I won't let you starve to death.
A few days later, the refugees were all sent to cultivate land and to secure food.
But even that couldn't avert a food shortage.
In the following year of 846,
the Central Government ordered many refugees to participate in a campaign to retake Wall Maria.
Two hundred and fifty thousand people...
Nearly a fifth of the entire population.
However, only about a hundred survived.
Their sacrifice alleviated the food shortage for those who survived, at least a bit.
It's all because of the Titans.
If only we could defeat them,
we could regain our place in this world.
Armin, I'm enlisting for military training next year.
I'll gain the strength to fight them.
Me too.
Armin?!
Me too!
I'm going too.
Mikasa? You don't have to!
Didn't you say the most important thing was to survive?
Correct. To ensure your survival, I'm coming.
All right. The three of us.
You are now officially members of the 104th Cadet Corps!
Unfortunately for you, I, Keith Shardis, will be your instructor.
I'm not here to welcome you!
Right now, all of you are merely livestock, fit only as Titan feed.
You're even lower than livestock!
For the next three years, we will train you useless shitrags.
I'll teach you how to fight the Titans!
When you face a Titan in three years, will you still be just food?
Or will you become a glorious Wall to protect your King?
Or even a mighty champion of mankind who will destroy the Titans?
The choice is in your hands.
Yeah, that's what I'll be.
I'll kill every fucking one of them.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
A failure as a soldier...
Eren vows revenge against the Titans and starts his training,
but his continued failure at even the most basic exercises forces him to face a harsh reality.
A Dull Light in Despair
Restoration of Mankind (pt 1)