Why are you asking about the Dollars?
Don't tell me you want
to join them. Do you?
What the hell does that mean?!
Why does some other
body have my head?!
Maybe there was a fresh corpse
or something it found?
This'll be fun! This'll be fun! This'll be fun!
What do you think will happen
if the police see that thing?
I don't care if they're alive or dead.
If necessary, eliminate them right away!
Things are a bit tight this month.
Now I need a sponge for the kitchen...
Thank you!
The black bike!
It should be right around that corner...
I'm sorry!
Are you OK?
You're...
Save me!
Please!
The black bike!
Wow, so cool!
Get a photo! We've gotta get a photo!
Oh, man. This is so cool!
Never Before
Seen
So, the beautiful girl you ran
into on a street corner
lost her memories and a bad guy
on a bike is chasing her, too.
And now that I'm here,
she's tired and asleep.
You expect me to believe this
rather-difficult-to-swallow story?
It's true, man!
The only way it'd be better is if
you were also almost late for school.
Oh, and if she were a
transfer student, too. How marvelous!
And she's a queen and your childhood friend,
to boot. That would be perfect!
Did you get how I'm being sarcastic here?
Yes, I think we all did.
She has no memories and says she doesn't
want me to go to the police.
I don't know what to do.
You'll just have to watch her for a while.
For now, wait till tomorrow and
then hear what she has to say.
OK.
OK, see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Thanks for coming so late.
The person on the black bike
may know my face now.
The urban legend of the black bike...
If they're going to come after me,
how can I possibly fight them?
I disliked the ordinary.
I wanted to live a different life
than those of others.
That might be why I'm
letting her stay here.
There's one thing Kida-kun doesn't
know about - her scar.
It was like someone sawed it off
and then sewed it back on.
This is the school store.
We are sold out of
jumbo melon bread.
We will not take reservations
for tomorrow.
Hey, Mikado!
How's your apartment's sleeping beauty?
We do not take reservations.
Kida-kun, quiet!
What? You have a beautiful
girl in your apartment?
Aren't you a bit young for that?
You see, he was turning a corner,
when he ran into a beautiful girl
with amnesia being chased
by a bad guy, and now
she's living with him.
What?
Kirigamine's just making shit up?
It's Ryuugamine...
Someone buy these meal tickets off me.
See? No one believes you. It's fine.
So how is she?
She was asleep when I left.
That's one sleepy babe.
Anyway, let me get to the point.
The point?
This is why I'm going so far as to eat in
fourth period, to free up my lunch.
The "Is He in the Dollars" poll?
Right now, it's kind of big in our class.
The Dollars are shrouded in mystery.
So you vote on the guy at school who makes
you think, "Like, doesn't he look like a Dollar?"
Wow. Some people are
getting a lot of votes.
A person can vote for as many
people as they want.
Huh? This Takiguchi guy, from
1-D, only has one vote.
You saw that?
That was none other than my vote.
I'm in his gym class,
and I'm sure that he's part of the Dollars.
Why do you think so?
Intuition.
And so, I'm going to make sure.
Hey, wait!
Excuse me!
Is Takiguchi Ryou-kun here?
He's not here.
He in the cafeteria?
Probably the roof, don't you think?
He goes there a lot during lunchtime.
Maybe he's smoking up there.
Shouldn't we go back?
There might be scary people up there.
I'm kidding.
Kids only smoke on the roof
in crappy old manga.
But...
Are we just going to say,
"Are you in the Dollars?"
He won't tell us the truth...
Leave it to me.
I've got an idea.
He's smoking...
Hey, Takiguchi.
Hi.
Oh, you're writing a song.
Yeah, I am.
What's up?
You need something?
Something I want to ask you.
Go ahead.
Are you part of the Dollars?
Kida-kun, what are you-
Yeah, I am.
Thought so.
I was sure of it.
See?
My intuition's perfect.
Oh, this guy's an old friend of mine.
I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
So you're the famous Ryuugamine Mikado.
Famous?
The name's famous.
Want some?
Oh, thanks.
Thank you.
Um, Takiguchi-kun?
Why did you join the Dollars?
I can't tell you exactly why...
About six months ago, I got an e-mail
from someone I didn't know.
He said that there were no rules or
restrictions in the Dollars.
At first, I thought there was no such thing,
but it might be fun to join if there were.
I don't like giving orders or
taking them, you know?
So, what are they like?
I dunno. Probably the best word to describe
them is "colorless and invisible."
"Colorless and invisible"?
They don't try enlisting more people
to wear their colors
to fight for power like the
Yellow Scarves or Blue Square.
Blue Square?
They were a color gang that was big
when I was in middle school.
I don't know the details, but they
did some crimes and fell apart.
Kida-kun?
Then you like the Dollars?
Yeah.
So do you meet the other members?
I only know them by their online nicks.
But I've met a bunch at my job or in town.
Sometimes it just felt like
they might be, and they were.
Like, what kind of person?
Why not just ask them,
like you asked me?
I think most would admit it.
Oh, crap.
I'm heading back!
Once I knew Takiguchi-kun was a Dollars member,
I figured I'd never tell anyone.
Mikado!
I know. I won't tell anyone.
I'm sure he wouldn't want people
to make a big deal out of it.
I figure it's something only those
who ask him need to know.
Stand up.
Bow.
That ends the Representative's Meeting.
I wonder if Kida-kun's still busy with
the Public Morals Committee.
I think he'll be done soon.
Yagiri Seiji-kun's stalker, Harima Mika-san,
has been missing since the day before school.
Have you heard anything about
Harima-san since then?
No. Nothing.
Ryuugamine!
Kida asked you to head
home without him.
Did something happen with him?
They're having a big argument
at the Public Morals Committee.
See you.
Um, you want to go, then?
I wonder what he's arguing about.
Probably what kinds of clothes or hairstyles
are allowed or something.
Mikado!
Make sure you talk to that pretty girl!
Introduce me soon!
Peace.
See you!
Th-The "pretty girl" is a French girl
we met at Russian Sushi,
and um... sh-sh-she has a nose piercing.
I'm sure he's arguing about that...
I've actually known about
you for a long time.
When we turned in our forms
to officially join the school,
there was a list of names at the desk.
I saw a name and thought it was cool,
and it turned out, the person with
it was standing right next to me...
And then I ended up being
class reps with him...
Wait a second! Isn't this just like Harima
Mika-san and Yagiri Seiji-kun?
Oh, man. Is she a stalker?
Wait. If she's hot, it's OK, right?
No way. This is really bad.
It might go like...
I want you!
She might stab me!
Fire Truck
Or maybe set me on fire!
Fire!
Wait. Maybe she'll take
my parents hostage...
Dad               Mom
But if she's got a nice personality,
then maybe it's OK...
Wait. If she's stalking me,
she can't have a nice personality!
I'm kidding.
You wouldn't want someone like me
hanging out with you all the time.
No...
Don't worry.
I'm not a stalker!
No, um... Well...
I'm sorry...
No. I'm the one who teased you,
so don't apologize.
Um...                    Um...
Um, well...
I-I look forward to our relationship
from now on.
Me, too.
Takeshi, that's the guy!
Who's "the guy"?
It's not me, right?
I mean you!
Don't ignore me!
Uh, who are you?
I had to buy a new cell phone
because of your friend!
Umm... I don't know what you're talking about.
I hear you're boys with the guy who
broke my girlfriend's cell phone.
I don't think we're really friends.
So, what are you?
His dad?!
His co-guarantor?!
I think you picked those
two deliberately...
You think you can lecture me?
Know your place, damn it!
You're taking advantage of the fact
that I don't hit girls?
What a wonderful girl you are.
I'd make you my girlfriend,
but you're not my type. Sorry.
Hit the bricks!
How awful!
See ya around!
Now then, Ryuugamine Mikado-kun,
I was hiding outside the gate to find you.
I'd like to talk to you.
By the way, why is the black biker here?
She's looking for her...
Oh, I forgot!
M-My apologies.
I'm in a bit of a hurry...
See you around, Sonohara-san.
This is surreal...
But they're going to follow me home.
Then...
Save me!
U-Uh... Well...
If you need something, I'll listen here.
I can talk to you after
the black biker does.
Hello?
Oh, hi there.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
What?
Oh, so we can communicate.
Ah, who are you?
I'm looking for a relative's
missing daughter.
I found her yesterday, but for
some reason, she ran away.
Y-You're an awful liar.
I-I'm sorry. I don't believe you.
How much do you know about me?
Um, you're an urban legend.
You ride a bike without engine
sounds or headlights.
And...
You have no head.
Do you believe that?
Uh, will you show me what's
inside your helmet?
I was amazed I was able to ask that.
Do you swear you won't scream?
I felt that I'd always been waiting
for a moment like this to occur.
I don't know how to describe what I felt...
I just found myself saying,
"I knew it! I knew it!" again and again.
Th-Thank you.
After that, she told me the real reason she was
searching for the person from yesterday.
That she was a Dullahan named Celty,
that she'd come to Japan
seeking her stolen head,
that the person with the stitches
on her neck looked just like her.
Normally, I'd never have believed it,
but oddly enough, I felt like I could.
Are you a friend of hers?
No. I just met her yesterday.
I asked her a lot of things,
but she said she'd lost her memories.
Celty-san?
Would you let me see her?
She's scared of you, probably
because you chased after her.
I want to meet her, no matter what.
Would you try to fix the
misunderstanding?
All right.
Nothing like fruit milk in the afternoon.
I think this is a sure sign she's
turning into the sparky heroine.
Nah. The heroine's gotta be Himegami!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
That bastard... He...
He hit the car with a rock!
Calm down, Togusa!
You'll pay for that!
The lights are red! Red! Red!
Wait here a moment.
I'll explain the situation.
I wouldn't want her thinking
I betrayed her, should she see you first.
Understood.
He's pretty careful.
I had never heard your name before.
Didn't take you for a foreigner...
Liar.
Throw another rock at my
horse and you'll pay.
So, it's a horse.
But you know...
Isn't he taking a bit too long?
A cleaning company at a run-down
apartment building like this?
No way...
I told you,
tell us where the girl you
were hiding went.
This hair in your futon's
from a girl, isn't it?
Please! I don't know!
Please don't hurt me-
You've seen our faces, you know.
We can kill you here if we want.
Someone's coming!
I-I'm saved...
You don't need to follow them.
I know where they're from.
I've seen that van before.
They're probably from
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals?
Yup.
A pharmaceutical giant that's been losing money,
about to be bought out by a foreign company.
The missing girl with the head,
the Dullahan,
the missing girls,
Harima Mika,
Yagiri Seiji,
human trafficking,
and the Dollars.
What is he doing?
I didn't want normalcy.
Honestly, I only half believed it.
Please help me a little.
I wanted to try living differently
from most people.
I have all the pawns I need.
So...
I was right!
I...
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Storm and
Stress
I didn't want normalcy.
I wanted to try living differently from most people.
I never thought it would affect so many others...
Next time:
Storm and Stress.