What's the matter?
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Tansan
Run!
What's up?
So, as I was saying yesterday...
Right?
Run, you dropped your notebook.
-Many names-
What's up?
I-I'm sorry!
I will erase this from my memory... So please don't kill me!
I'm sorry!
What are you talking about?
But isn't that the notebook you use to
curse people you bear a grudge against?
No, it's not.
This is an exchange notebook with Tooru.
That's Tooru's page.
Huh?
Then why are there so many names?
-More names-
This is a memory test.
We are seeing how many names we can write down of the people we have met.
Why are you guys doing this...?
But still, she has an excellent memory.
I don't think I can win against her.
Furthermore, halfway through, all
the names are written in katakana...
Is Tooru a returnee student or something?
Nope.
She said from there onwards are
characters from the manga she read.
Ah, no wonder it has weird names.
Justine?
Michele Richard.
Jules Auguste Guillaume.
Marie Francoise Victoire!
Dobochi Hekenovich!
Count Francoise Polignac!
Michelle Bonn Parnasse!
O'Brien Butkovich!
Alessandro Gullickson!
Paul Linares!
Andrews Banderas!
Gladios Andretti!
What?
Salvador Andrea!
Heisel Poncho!
Yuuko.
Velazquez!
What's the matter?
So, what did Tooru say?
"There's something I want to show you all, so come to my house," she said.
I wonder what it is.
But it's my first time going to Tooru's house, so I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
I wonder what kind of place she lives in...
You'll find out soon.
It's here.
Tooru sure lives in a nice apartment.
Let's go.
Tooru didn't have to leave early just to clean up...
Maybe there's something that we shouldn't see.
What's the matter?
It feels like I'm treading on bamboo sticks here. It feels great!
Quit acting like an old lady and let's go!
Tooru, we're here!
It's not locked, so just come in.
Okay!
Sorry for intruding.
Tooru.
I'm coming in.
This is so messy.
Is Tooru the kind of person that can't clean up?
Nope.
It's always more on the tidy side than anything.
Which means...
A messy room.
The actual person is missing.
And locked from the inside.
This is a closed-space murder!
The front door was open.
The room is not really dirty.
If you look closely, the trash is scattered all over.
So the trash is walking by itself.
It's impossible for it to grow arms and legs.
Ah, it's a human!
I see!
Should we tidy it up for now?
Yes.
What Run-chan's thinking is probably wrong.
Sorry for not cleaning up.
This little guy wreaked havoc in the room.
Little guy?
It's so cute!
Where'd this cat come from?
I picked it up this morning.
It seems like someone abandoned it.
Oranges
I see!
Cats also have arms and legs.
I don't understand your reasoning, Run.
Cats are anthropomorphised, too.
What are you talking about?
And then I think it turns into Tooru.
That's...
I feel like I can agree with that.
Right?
What does that mean?
See ya.
See you tomorrow.
Take care of the cat!
Goodbye.
It's cold, isn't it?
Are you okay, Tooru?
Yes.
I know, why don't we go eat something on our way home?
Hmm, I'd like something sweet.
Then shall we go to a family restaurant?
We can go through the shopping district.
The shopping district?
Can we make a stop somewhere, then?
I remember it was around here.
Where are you going?
To buy a collar.
Ah, I see.
I also want some cat toys and other things.
Toys?
If that's so, I know a place!
Toys
I'm sure they sell them here.
Adult
Toys
You're not wrong but...
You're wrong!
Adult
Toys
Welcome!
It's a white cat.
Which colour would match?
Red... Blue.
She's very serious.
You really care about that cat.
I also really care about you, Run-chan.
I know.
That tickles.
Welcome to Goonies.
Sorry for the wait.
Please have a seat here.
Tooru, take the booth side.
No, you take it, Run-chan.
Why don't we just sit together?
Oh yeah, about our cat...
I can't control myself at the drink bar.
How many did you mix in?
Five flavours in one, a deliciously mixed juice!
We still haven't decided on a name for the cat.
I can't think of a good one.
What about candy or juice?
You like them, don't you, Tooru?
That sounds good.
What I have in here are...
cola, cider, lemonade, ginger ale, melon soda.
If you put them all together, that makes Tansan!
TL Note: Tansan 炭酸 means "carbonic acid"
We're back!
Are you doing well?
From now on, your name is Tansan.
This cat is very well-behaved.
There are times where he goes wild, though.
Tansan, the collar looks good on you.
So cute!
Do you want some food?
I'll go get something to eat.
We also got some toys, so let's play after eating.
Run-chan, we need to talk.
In the end, Run-chan spent the whole time with him.
Good morning, Tansan.
It's already this late?
I need to get changed.
Don't do that, or you'll get hair on my uniform.
I don't have time to play around.
It'll be a cold day from this morning onwards.
There's a high possibility of snow.
Please be careful when going out.
It can't be helped.
Well, I'm off.
Good morning, Tooru.
It's even colder today.
There was a snow forecast for today, Run-chan.
What?! Wait a minute!
What's wrong?
Tada!
I brought some syrup.
For the snow?
Yes.
Good morning, Yuuko-chan.
Good morning.
Its been cold today since the morning.
Yeah.
Good morning...
Good mor-
Nagi, what's up with those clothes?
The forecast said it was going to snow, so I prepared for it.
You look like an assassin; that's so cool!
Won't you get mistaken for a pervert?
Geez.
Why am I supposed to come to school when it's this cold?
It's natural, because we're students.
Don't you think that when autumn is over,
it should be winter break until spring?
You hate winter, don't you?
And during the summer, you kept saying that it was hot.
As it is, on days it snows, I don't think I have the strength to keep on living...
What are you so gloomy about?
Snow is full of fun things!
Huh?
You can make a snowman, make kamakuras,
TL Note: A kamakura is like an igloo.
and have snowball fights!
You too, Nagi. Pray for it to snow!
Weren't you listening to what I was saying?!
Eh?
period
First
Second
Third
Fourth
It won't fall... It won't...
You still haven't given up, have you?
I've half-given up, though.
Give up fully.
Ah! It's snowing!
Awesome!
Wow!
I wonder if it will pile up enough?
It really is snowing.
The weather sure changes quickly.
Run, isn't that great... Huh?
She's gone!
It's here!
Lunch! Lunch!
Eat your bentou, not the snow!
Seems like it's going to pile up.
It's really coming down.
If it piles up a lot, then I'd like to try that.
I'll be buried and disappear below it!
Just like in a manga.
If I jump from here, I wonder if I could do it?
Huh? No that's...
Then from the roof!
I think it's impossible...
Wow!
It's really piled up high! Amazing!
Okay, let's go!
Go!
Yay~!
Run-chan.
Did she die?
She's eating it!
Run-chan, don't!
Hey everyone, jump in!
Geez, stop being so sudden.
What are you trying to do so suddenly?
That's dangerous!
Huh? What is it?
Yuuko-chan, you did a strange pose.
Way to go, Yuuko.
Geez!
The snow is...
The snow is warm, isn't it?
Nagi?
Are you all right, Nagi?
She looks cold.
I know!
I'll make Nagi-chan warm!
What are you doing, Run-chan?
I thought of building a kamakura for Nagi-chan.
Ah. It's warm, isn't it?
I'll help!
Okay, Nagi-chan.
It's ready!
It looks cramped.
Nagi, is it warm?
Yes... More than outside.
I'm glad.
Your guard is down, Yuuko-chan.
I'm coming too!
Now you've done it!
tenki yohou yuki no maaku de watashi no kokoro odoru
When there's a snow mark on the weather forecast, my heart dances.
samusa nante kankeinai no yo
It has nothing to do with the cold.
hora inotte
Come on and pray.
miageta sora ni
Look up into the sky
yuki fureba Lucky  kimagure ni Snow Man
How lucky if snow falls. Whimsically make a snow man.
ashiato tsukete
Leave your footprints.
omoikiri Diving katadotte
Follow after me and dive with all your might.
I Wish I Wish Snow Day   Happy Happy Snow Day
motto motto furitsumore
I hope more and more falls and piles up.
Lucky Lucky Snow Day
zutto zutto furitsuzuke
Continue falling forever and ever.
Happy Happy Snow
motto furitsumore
I hope more and more falls and piles up.
Happy Happy Snow Day
We played outside that much, but somehow I didn't catch a cold.
I caught a cold
-Yuuko-
"I caught a cold." From Yuuko.
Why did you catch one?
I got a 38° fever
-Tooru-
"I got a 38° fever." From Tooru.
"It seems like I caught a cold." From Run.
I might have caught a cold too.
Sending Message
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Come here.
It's warm.
It's cold.
Okay everyone, let's do our best shovelling snow!
Yes...
Preview
It's almost time to bid farewell to everyone, isn't it?
Eh? Already?!
Isn't it too soon?
Wait, it's already winter?!
It came fast, huh?
What did we do last winter, anyway?
Well, we were getting ready for the high school entrance exam...
That's right, we spent a lot ot time studying, didn't we?
Although Yutaka was always the one teaching Mipo-rin!
Don't lie!
Next time!
Birthday
Next time, on A Channel, Birthday.
Everyone, do your best at studying for your exams!
What month do you think it is?