Well?
Y-yeah...it looks good...
...I think.
A-ah...um...
Whatever, I don't care.
Assassination
Hey, hurry up!
We don't have all the time in the world, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, it's this way. Did you even look at the map?
Yeah, I saw.
Ah! Wait for me, I want to look in that store!
All right.
Give me your wallet.
Eh?
Thanks for waiting.
Nice to meet you.
Are you going to carry that thing around all day?
Yup...I am.
Hey, why don't you come with us?
Let's go ove-
I'll buy you another one.
Idiot.
You're too kind.
It's fine. It's my fault, anyway.
Please, help yourself.
Okay.
Hmm, delicious!
Are you students?
Ah, yes.
Today's a weekday.
You're playing hooky.
It's our school's anniversary today
and we didn't want to go to the school's party, so...
I understand.
I skipped school, too.
Right?
Sorry.
You have ice cream on your mouth.
Y-Yeah.
You're so careless,
Wallace.
Let's head back.
Have you memorized the mall interior?
It's drilled into my head.
How many security cameras are on Main Street?
Sixty-eight.
There are blind spots, but too many to carry the mission out there.
Watch it when socializing.
Sorry.
Let's head back and plan the mission.
Our supplies will arrive soon, so...
Roger.
Zwei.
Your acting...
...stinks.
Having gained Zwei, Phanton can now pursue missions more efficiently.
They're the ideal pair.
Those brats appear dull but,
I commend you for expanding our territory to the
east coast five months earlier than planned.
I'm honored.
But...isn't it risky? To repeatedly use Phantom like this.
You're right.
It'd be wise to tread with caution and wait.
With all due respect...
Place your trust in Phantom and me,
and allow us to carry out the mission.
In order to guarantee its success, I'll be going myself.
Oh? You're pretty excited.
Okay. I'll leave it to your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
The fake name given to me was...Wallace Yang.
A student living in Los Angeles.
It was the name of the first man I killed.
Ever since I killed him,
I've been working full-time...
The work of assassination.
Together with her...
I...
Don Lucio...
Dallas Mafia's boss.
He tends to stay inside his mansion, which has strict security.
But tomorrow, there'll be an opening.
He'll be purchasing a birthday present for his granddaughter at that mall.
That'll be...
A present.
Tomorrow, the target will arrive around three o'clock in the afternoon.
We'll find the best location before then.
Where do you think the best location is?
You tell me.
Another test?
Master told me to ask.
We'll mingle with the shoppers and approach the target.
People won't suspect us.
But we can't shoot him inside the mall.
Why?
It's too open.
There'll probably be a lot of guards, too.
They'll have gained control of the security cameras as well.
We should attack from somewhere unexpected when there's only a few guards.
Where's that?
We have one chance.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
That's...
That's enough.
You're correct.
Let's go back now.
Okay.
What's up?
I've found the target, but
I'm being trailed.
Two of them are following.
Help me fool them.
Elevator Nine's fountain.
Hurry.
How long do you think you've made me wait?
Jeez! I've already looked at everything myself!
Sorry.
I don't want any excuses!
So, what're you going to do about wasting my time today?
Well...
Depending on your answer, I might go home.
I know.
I'll pay for everything you buy today.
Dinner, too?
That's fine.
I already know all the stores.
Now I'm going to be poor.
It's your fault, Wallace.
Didn't I just apologize?
The target is at the antique store in the mall's southern section.
His car will be picking him up at the southern entrance.
Are we leaving now?
Thank you very much.
I think this looks cute on you.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'll attack.
Back me up.
Got it.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
Well, let's end this party.
Well done, both of you.
What's wrong?
Nothing much.
No, it's nothing.
Nothing...
I am honored that you took a detour to come and greet me.
It's natural for a superior to show appreciation to her subordinate.
You did a good job. I appreciate it.
I thank you for your praise.
That boy...changed...
Are you satisfied?
Yeah, I guess...
Is something wrong?
No,
where are those two?
I ordered them to return by passenger flight after destroying the equipment.
Do you want to go?
Not really.
Maybe she's tired from waiting?
It's you...
Vacation?
We took one here.
We're headed back now.
I see.
Did you have a good time?
Yeah.
That's good.
I see.
It'd be nice if we saw each other again.
See ya.
Yes.
That was...
...good acting.
Two dogs sitting, waiting for an order.
That's...
...what we are.
That...
...again.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Never mind.
What Master said was right...
He went through a path that took me two years,
in only three months.
He is...
...the old me.
Another me...
I'm...
...afraid.
I feel like...
I might see the truth...of who I really am...
Your eyes are...
...scary.
Moment
We suppress our emotions and pull the trigger.
We take away the happiness of others.