Get up already.
You stayed up late again, didn't you?
The lights were on.
I confirmed this up to 2:30 AM.
Rice is... rice is... dripping out of...
Ryuuji's ears... sparkling, white rice...
If it's about breakfast, I brought it already.
I'll warm it up for you, so go wash your face.
Breakfast...
All right, now for the dishes and laundry...
This place really is barren.
A cardboard box?
What's this?
A picture album?
This is...
Just what are you looking at?
T-Taiga, this is...!
Yeah, that's right! They're pictures of
Kitamura-kun! You got a problem with that?
Even if you have a problem, there's no way in hell I'm going to listen to it.
This... is supposed to be Kitamura?
I-I-I can't help it! I always end up shaking!
When I try to take pictures of Kitamura-kun, I...
Want me to take one?
Huh?
A picture... of him.
I won't say I'm good at it, but anything is better tha-
Wait a minute!
H-How many are you willing to take?
The Face Back Then
What kind of picture shall I get?
An extremely concentrated face? In the middle of softball practice?
Oh, can't forget to take one of him eating lunch!
Like I said, I'll take as many as you want.
You say "As many as you want", but there's a limit, isn't there?!
Okay, then take an infinite amount.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning. You're late today.
Yeah, it's because I went to student council first.
I see.
Mornin'!
That's so old. Just way too old, Taiga.
Uh, tha-that was wrong! Um, uh...!
Aisaka.
Mornin'!
I'll go on ahead then.
M-Mornin'?
Hey, did you get that?
Get what?
Him saying "Mornin'!", of course!
That came out of nowhere. How was I supposed to get that?
Useless mongrel.
Hey, now...
Maruo, look at this for a second.
Hey, hey, look at this magazine model! He looks just like you!
It's almost time for the morning assembly, you two.
End the blabbering and get moving to the schoolyard.
Aw, he won't play along.
Since he's the vice-president, he's too serious.
I wanted some sort of reaction, at least.
Yeah!
Kitamura is really popular with the girls somehow.
What's with Maruo, huh?!
Want me to roll you up, huh?!
Everyone, line up!
Lately, a bunch of you numb nuts have been forgetting your student handbooks!
We have proof too.
According to the Disciplinary Officer's report, during last week's inspection of personal belongings, there were...
Uh, how many was it again?
Fifty-nine.
School-wide, a total of fifty-six people have been forgett-
Wait, that was wrong. A total of fifty-nine.
Minor details aside! Anyhow!
Coming to school without your student handbook is like forgetting your pride as students at Oohashi!
You drill that into your skulls, huh?!
YEAH!
Are you one to speak?
You're forgetting things too.
A-Aisaka...
You little runt, you say something?
You're forgetting to put people at ease.
Huh?
E-A-SE!
Oh, my bad.
Everyone, at ease!
Man, we're high schoolers now and yet we're lining up like idiots and listening to this worthless crap for ages.
Is it really that bad? You're just holding your hands on your hips.
What was that?!
Hey, Aisaka-
Great, trying to work up a sweat early this morning?
President, calm yourself too!
What would you know?! No back pain, no pain from being in labor, and yet we're holding onto our hips!
We look so-
Aisaka!
A-Aisaka, please calm down.
I'm sorry, president, please continue the morning assembly.
Y-Yeah.
What's going on?
The Palmtop Tiger was biting at the president?
That idiot...
She's so obviously depressed...
Wait, she's happy?
Okay, okay, that's enough Haruta-kun.
Next we'll... Aisaka-san?
You're in a good mood today, aren't you?
Let's have you happily read for us!
Just kidding, got you there!
Haruta-kun!
Yuri-chan, give me a break!
With enthusiasm, now!
Aw, come on!
Here. Your lunch box.
Don't want it. Lost my appetite.
I was being a nuisance to Kitamura by fighting it out with the student council president...
But...
then there was an excitement carnival when he held me back...
T-Taiga...?
But I wanna apologize too!
Don't sweat it.
The student council president doesn't care about minor things like that.
Oh, lunch box? Can I join too?
That's nice, real nice! I'll barge in on you too!
What?!
Doing this once in a while is real nice.
Yeah!
Man, I'm hungry.
Thanks for the meal!
...thanks for the meal.
What can it be? What will today's side dishes be?!
H-How did things end up like this?
Whoa, fried chicken!
And a one, and a two... CHICKEN IN!
Taiga! She's way too tense!
Whoa, Taiga's got a mountain of side dishes.
Oh shit, our lunch boxes are identical!
Aisaka, you've been bringing your own lunch box lately. Are you making it yourself?
What, Takasu's making it?
You got it wrong!
You know, Kushieda decorates cell phones part-time, doesn't she?
I figured I'd get some pocket money by making lunch boxes.
Really? I'd like to try one of Takasu's lunch boxes some day.
Oh, me too! The lunch is probably going to be brownish and cool! You have me interested!
I'll make some for everyone next time.
Kitamura-senpai, Kushieda-senpai. We should, uh, go now.
Oh, it's the softball club's manager.
Right, the meeting.
Sorry, you two. Go on and eat without us.
Yeah, okay.
That was too close for comfort.
Eating with Kitamura-kun, talking with Kitamura-kun-
Taiga?
Listen, was it okay to just casually let
Kitamura know I made your lunch box?
And we finally got the rumors about us cleared up too...
What should we do?! What should I do? What are we going to do?!
Calm down a notch!
Sheesh, why do you get so stressed out when involved with Kitamura?
Look, you have to be more careful from now on-
What? If you got something to say, swallow first.
There's no meat in today's lunch box.
If you prefer having meat in your lunch every time, then go join a different family that does too.
As I thought, the mold's roots are deep around public facilities!
But being discovered by me is the end of your days.
Takai-chan, let's go home already.
Yeah, I'll finish up here; you can go home.
Oh, that's cool.
I'll leave it up to you then.
Hey now, you black little devils! You've given up already?
I'll treat you guys to one of the 48 Takasu-style Housework skills!
The Takasu Mold-killing Buster!
Ryuuji, what are you blabbering about?
Let's go already, you dumb dog.
Taiga! What the hell are you doing here, this is the male bath-
Whatever, let's just go!
What is it, Taiga?
What are you doi-
Oh, right, Kitamura.
Quickly, take a picture!
This girl...
Look, now! Now! Quickly!
Yeah, yeah.
The shutter was-
Now, get one now!
Wait, I'm setting it u-
Oh jeez, just hand it over!
Huh?
So this is how the foggy pictures got mass produced.
Wow, Kitamura-kun's looking real go-
CHAAAAAARGE!
Hey!
Hey. Look how happily he's waving.
Oh, shut up...
Klutz.
Welcome to Sudoh-bucks!
Master, one Americano with some Naporitan!
You mean Napolitain chocolate, right?
How is this place not getting sued?
And you had to go print them out, didn't you?
Hey, you're overflowing with drool!
There's so much Kitamura-kun, it's a Kitamura carnival...
What are you doing?!
I know youngsters these days get pissed off easily, but this is too much!
I want to help out, you mongrel.
You took pictures for me, after all.
No, it's okay, I still want to be able to hang out futons tomorrow.
Keep up the nonsense and I'll drop you!
Drop? You little...
You're going to bring lunch boxes next time, right? For Minorin and Ki-Kitamura-kun...
Okay, how about you peel the skin off the potatoes?
D-Don't make fun of me!
I'm sure I can... I just got to peel the skin off these, right? Sheesh.
She wants to make homemade food for Kitamura, huh?
It's the same goes for me. I finally get a chance to have Kushieda eat the food I make.
I must be more fired up for-
What the hell are you-?!
What? The skin's gone, isn't it?
I won't cut my fingers if I do it like this.
Well... I guess...
Onigiri for dinner? This is like a picnic!
And this onigiri is so small and cute!
I made that!
Whoa, Taiga-chan's a genius?!
Well, she can practice as much as she want with these.
There's no need to peel them after all.
Like I said earlier, eat before you speak.
These are so good! They have Taiga-chan's scent in them!
Here, I made you some tea.
You better stick them in an album before they get damaged.
Stop nagging like you're my brother-in-law.
What's up with you? Here someone's wanting to laminate the ones you really like and stuff.
You can do that?
Well, yeah.
Okay, gimme a moment. Um...
If you laminate them, they'll be okay regardless of how many times you fall over or drop them into water.
Taiga, something wrong?
N-No!
You know, you can get more than just one?
Like two, or three...
Oh, shut up! Just wait, I'm picking them out now!
What's up all of the sudden? I just-
I'm going home.
Why, out of nowhere?
I can't calmly pick the ones I want while I'm here so I'm going home to do it instead.
Hey, Taiga! Wait up!
What's up with her?
I really want a picture...
of Kushieda too...
Hey, look at this!
T-This is... a dead light yellow squid? No wait, slime?
Isn't it awesome? I made pudding in a bucket!
This is pudding...? It rather blows my mind-
A bucket of pudding! A haven for a woman's appetite!
But, it was real huge after all, so making it didn't go so well.
The sticky and soft bits kept splitting from one another and...
Aha! You ladies over there, have a look at this!
This is my all-out bucket card play!
This...
And then the sticky and soft bits wouldn't stay together and the harmony between them got all ruined!
A picture of... Kushieda.
It's not what I had in mind, but...
I guess I'll keep it.
What are you doing?
Oh, it's just Ryuuji.
You're still choosing?
Oh, shut up you.
What's with that attitude?
Yesterday you just went home.
I said I could laminate as many as you want if you can't make up your mind!
What are you doing...?
If you're going to pester me so much about it, then you pick for me.
What?
I'll leave it to you.
As if I could pick for her.
That Taiga...
Are those Aisaka's pictures?
Well, yeah.
They're pictures of me, aren't they?
No, um... you see... How should I put it...
Right, that reminds me, I forgot all about this.
I left it sitting in here.
School Handbook
This brings back memories.
You, why do you have this picture?
Back in the day, the photography club was selling photos like these.
Among those, ther-
Not that! Why do you have a picture of Taiga?
I put it there because I was in love with Aisaka.
That's all.
What?
Well, when I confessed to her, I got rejected in less than a second.
Whoops, I spilled. Keep it a secret from everyone, okay?
Wh-
Takasu, what's wrong? Hey!
WHAT THE HELL?!
What a wasteful thing to do...
I couldn't help it.
Saying he l-loved me...
Startling me like that...
I just refused him, but....
After that I came to my senses and... then I, uh...
Kind of just fell in love with him too!
It happened right here.
Aisaka!
Your rage that you don't hold back...
Your straightforward personality is great...
I...!
Kitamura...
Weird confession, wasn't it?
I had no idea whether he was praising or speaking bad of me...
But you know, I was happy.
Having someone saying you're okay as you are, and being needed by that person...
It was nice to have someone like that.
Somehow Taiga's lifestyle and her room
suddenly just came to mind.
There were so many pictures, and yet there was not one...
I wanted one of that look.
The look he had back when he confessed to me.
Just to see it once more...
Wh-Wh-Why are you making me say
embarrassing things, you perverted dog!
Why is it my fault?!
Who else is there that's around here, huh?!
Being needed by someone.
I wonder what that means to Taiga.
But man, she sure is a klutz.
If you end up liking him right after, you should've waited with your answer.
Right, Inko-chan?
Kitamura's being Kitamura too.
He needs to take responsibility and go out with her if he was already in love.
You think so too, Inko-chan?
Go on, Inko-chan!
It'd be okay, wouldn't it?
Next Episode Preview
Kawashima Ami
The airhead-type pretty girl, Kawashima Ami, suddenly appears.
For now all I can say is...
Women are scary!
Huh, what do you mean? Ami-chan doesn't understand!