Millions of people live...
...beneath this expansive sky.
And they all harbor a myriad of wishes and feelings.
Those feelings sometimes touch,
and collide with, other people's feelings.
But within some of those people are even deeper
ties that surely connect them all together...
...so the feelings can be passed along.
A story full of those contacts and
encounters is about to begin.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha is about to begin!
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Ethereal Echo, become light!
Forbidden monster, enter this sealing circle!
Jewel Seed Seal!
I let it... get away...
I need to... chase after... it...
Someone... please hear my voice...
Lend me your strength...
With my magical... power...
Episode 01
Is this what you call a
"mysterious encounter"?
Is this what you call a "mysterious encounter"?
That was a pretty weird dream...
I'm Takamachi Nanoha. A grade-schooler who goes
to the Seishou Auxiliary Elementary School.
As for the Takamachi family,
I'm the youngest of three children.
Good morning!
Oh, Nanoha. Good morning!
Good morning, Nanoha.
Please take this to the table for me.
Okay!
These two are my father and mother.
You managed to get up all on your
own today. That's impressive.
This is my father, Takamachi Shiro-san.
He's the owner of our coffee shop in front of the train
station, Midoriya, and the central pillar of our family.
Breakfast will be ready any minute now.
And this is my mother, Takamachi Momoko-san.
She's one of the people in charge
of all the sweets at Midoriya.
She's beautiful and kind, my beloved mother!
Oh, and by the way, Midoriya is our coffee shop at
the marketplace in front of the train station...
...that sells various cakes, cream puffs,
and different types of coffee.
It's a really popular shop for girls coming home from
school and ladies around the neighborhood.
Where's Onii-chan and Onee-chan?
Aren't they still in the dojo?
Onii-chan, Onee-chan, good morning!
Breakfast is ready!
Good morning.
Ah, Nanoha. Good morning.
Here you go!
Thanks.
These two are my older brother and sister.
Well then, Miyuki, let's leave it at that this morning.
My older brother, Takamachi Kyouya-san,
is a freshman in college.
Having succeeded my father in his sword school,
he's become my sister's teacher.
All right. Let's continue after we're
both back from school, okay?
And, of course, there's my older sister, Takamachi
Miyuki-san. She's a second year high school student.
Breakfast sure is delicious!
Especially these scrambled eggs.
Really? I used tomatoes, cheese, and basil
as toppings to really bring out the flavor!
Everyone, take a good look. You should be happy
for having a mother who's so good at cooking!
Right?
Of course. Right, Nanoha?
Yeah!
Oh, stop it, dear!
Our parents still act like newlyweds,
and are always a handful.
Miyuki, your ribbon's loose.
Huh, really?
Here, let me fix it.
And my brother and sister really get along well, too.
You can really feel the love here, but behind
everything, it feels like I'm floating apart from it all.
Good morning!
Nanoha-chan!
Oh, Nanoha! Over here!
Suzuka-chan, Alisa-chan.
Good morning!
Good morning, Nanoha-chan.
Good morning.
These are my friends, Alisa Bannings-chan
and Tsukimura Suzuka-chan.
We've been in the same class ever since first grade.
We're attending the same cram school this year, too.
As you can tell from the research I had you do,
the town we live in has a lot of different shops.
I had you look at what people actually do and how
they do it, and ask them several questions.
I believe this was a very good experience for you all.
As you can see, there's a lot of places
and a lot of different jobs out there...
...so my question to you is, what kind
of job would you like in the future?
It would probably be a good idea
to start thinking about that now.
Stand.
The future, huh...?
You two have already pretty much decided,
haven't you, Alisa-chan, Suzuka-chan?
In my family, both my father and mother
are company managers...
...so I'll have to study hard and succeed
them in their positions.
That's the plan, at least.
I really like machines and stuff, so...
I've been thinking it'd be nice to go into engineering...
I see...
You two are so great...
But aren't you next in line for the Midoriya
coffee shop your family runs?
Yeah, that's one of my visions for the future, but...
I feel like there's something else I want to do...
But right now, I can't clearly see
what that something is yet...
I really have no special skills or
strong points about me, either...
You moron!
You shouldn't be saying that about yourself!
That's right. I'm sure there's something
only you can do, Nanoha-chan.
Furthermore, aren't your grades better than mine?!
And if you say that you have no strong points,
what's that say about me, huh?!
But I wouldn't be a good as a business administrator,
and I'm no good with normal work, either...
You two, you shouldn't be doing that! Come on!
Come on, you guys!
Something I can do... something only I can do, huh?
Hey, wasn't Suzuka so awesome
during dodge ball today?
Yeah, she was so cool.
Th-That's not true...
Be quiet!
Ah, this way, this way!
This is a shortcut to get to cram school faster.
Really...?
Though the path's a little worn-down.
This is the place I saw in my dream yesterday...
What's wrong?
Nanoha?
Ah, it's nothing. Sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Then let's go.
It couldn't be.
Nanoha-chan?
Ah, yeah!
Help me!
Nanoha?
Didn't you just hear something?
Something?
Something... kind of like a voice...
Not really...
I don't remember hearing anything...
Help me!
Nanoha!
Nanoha-chan?
I'm pretty sure I heard it coming from over here.
What's wrong, Nanoha?
Suddenly running off like that...
Ah, look!
An animal? It looks hurt.
Y-Yeah. W-What should we do?
Even if you ask that...
For now, we have to take it to a hospital!
Not a hospital, a vet.
Umm... is there a vet somewhere near here?
Ah... umm, I think there's one somewhere around here.
Wait a second, I'll call my house and ask!
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha!
Nanoha!
Hey, Nanoha!
Yes, I'm coming!
Its wound isn't all that deep,
but it certainly looks pretty weak.
It's probably been on its own for a while.
Doctor, thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Not at all. You're quite welcome.
Doctor, this is a ferret, right?
I wonder if it's someone's pet...
It might be a ferret... but if it is, it's certainly unique.
And also, about this item on its collar...
It looks like some sort of jewel...
It woke up!
It's looking at you...
Nanoha, you're being stared at.
A-Ah, yeah... umm... uh...
It would be best to let it get some rest, so why don't
I watch over it for you three until tomorrow?
Yes! Please do!
If you'd like, why don't you come and
see how it's doing tomorrow?
Okay!
Ah, oh no! It's time for cram school!
You're right!
Well then, Doctor, thank you very much!
We'll be back tomorrow!
Let's start off with the problem we solved last time.
Let's look at the example at the
top of page 47 in your textbook.
Example one is... 39/45.
Both the denominator and numerator are
divisible by 3, so it then becomes 13/15.
And my family runs a food business, so raising a pet
in the house really goes against our principles...
All right, who knows the answer to this?
Well then, why don't we go with you?
#29, Takamachi-san.
Ah, y-yes!
Question 3 on page 47.
Umm... uh...
5/42
Yes, that's correct.
Some people think they have to answer and stop...
Good job!
Nice!
...but they're not done yet.
In this case, if you don't completely approximate
these numbers, or don't do it correctly...
...your answer will not be correct.
Even if you finish the problem, you shouldn't
rest yet. Your next step would be to-
So... I was wondering if maybe
we could take in Mr. Ferret...
Hmm... a ferret, huh?
While we're on the subject, just what is a "ferret"?
Come on, Dad. It's like a long rodent.
They were really popular as pets a while back.
Ferrets are pretty small, right?
You know what a ferret is?
Umm... it's about this big.
If we'd only be taking it in for a little while,
and you put it in a cage and properly look after it...
...it shouldn't be much of a problem.
Kyouya, Miyuki, what do you say?
I don't see anything wrong with that.
Same goes for me.
Well, there you go.
Isn't that great?
Yeah! Thanks so much!
Now then, let's all eat up before the food gets cold.
Okay!
Momoko, could you pass the salad?
Sure! Here you are.
Oh, me too!
Right, right.
Alisa-chan, Suzuka-chan, everyone
said I could keep the ferret here.
Tomorrow after school, let's go
and pick it up together, okay?
Nanoha.
Now to send this!
Can you hear me?
Can you hear my voice?
It's the same voice from last night's
dream, and this afternoon...
Please listen to me.
You, who can hear my voice, please!
Please lend me some of your strength!
That ferret's the one speaking to me...?
Please! Come to where I am!
The time we have left... the danger...
It's already too late!
Please... let my voice reach her.
This sound again...!
That's...!
W-What's going on? What is that?!
You... came for me.
You spoke?!
Umm, I don't really understand what's going
on here, but... what is that thing?!
What's going on?!
You're of the proper nature.
Won't you lend me some of your strength?
Proper nature?
I've come here from another world
in search of something.
But I may not be able to handle the
weight of doing such a thing alone!
That's why...
I understand it'd be a problem for you, but... I want
those with the proper nature to cooperate with me.
I'll repay you! I promise I will!
I want you to use the power I carry within me.
Use my power... my magical power!
Magic...?
I promise to repay you, so please!
T-This isn't the time to be talking about that, is it?
What am I supposed to do?
Take this!
It's warm...
Hold that in your hand, close your
eyes, and focus your mind.
And then repeat what I say.
Understand? Here we go!
Yeah!
I, who has accepted this mission...
...upon the ancient contract,
command you to release your power!
Umm... upon the ancient contract,
Wind in the sky...
Stars in the heavens...
And a resolute heart...
...beats within my chest!
This magic in my hand...
Raising Heart, Set Up!
Stand by, Ready, Set up.
Such great magical prowess...
Focus, and begin to picture things in your mind!
That which allows you to use magic,
the form of your magical staff.
And that which will protect your body, a strong armor!
No way... asking me to do that all of a sudden...
Umm... uh...
I-I'll go with that for now!
It's a success!
No way!
W-What's with this outfit?!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
I'm Takamachi Nanoha!
I was just supposed to be a
normal third-grader, but...
Something about missions
and destinies happened...
...and I've become
a magical girl!
Just what kind of fate
is in store for my city?
And what about the ferret
whose name I don't yet know?
Will raising him in my house
really be all right?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Two: My Magical
Incantation is "Lyrical"?
I, Lyrical Magical,
will do my best!