I was wondering if it's really OK
for the Dollars to exist.
I have to do something.
No matter what you see,
no matter what you learn about her,
don't look away.
A love triangle, indeed.
She was wearing a Raira uniform, glasses,
and I think she had big breasts.
No, it's impossible.
She...
A girl's being attacked
by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce.
They've started moving.
They're taking her somewhere.
Where?
I think that's a Raira uniform.
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
Huge knockers.
Why is Sonohara-san...
Everyone in
the Dollars! Emergency!
That's right!
Let's all save her!
I ain't letting them get away with this!
The Yellow Scarves have gone too far!
Now then...
I'll go enjoy the rest in my living room.
Declaration of
Disbandment
Anyone nearby, help her.
Everyone else, get over there!
You with the Dollars?
You were the one who came after
our hideout, with the black bike.
Huh?
You bitch...
These people are with the Yellow Scarves.
Officer!
Over here! Quickly! Quickly!
Wait!
What did I do?
This way.
Go straight.
There's an exit out the back.
I was sure I had to do something.
Where'd she go?
I found the girl.
I helped her get out the back
of the Orb Ikebukuro Building.
They're still coming.}
Anyone near the Orb Ikebukuro Building?
But I'm just so confused
by everything. All I do is run.
Panic! There's your exit!
Easier said than bun.
Why?
Push de button!
I got a sax-sucks-security job at the Orb Ikebukuro building,
and I'm part of the Dollars, so I g-g-awt her away.
Right outside, behind the
Orb Ikebukuro building?
That's my fortress, ain't it!
Who are you?
Why?
Why are you helping me?
Damn it...
Are you OK?
I'm a Dollars passing by.
I helped out a little.
I was gonna quit, but...
Don't quit!
You can't quit!
I thought you'd come back.
A dream?
Where did the girl go?
Is this a dream?
The girl has just transformed
into a costumed bunny!
Where did she go, damn it?
You...
You'd better get going, or you'll lose her.
Damn it!
Idiots! What are you doing?
Wh-What's going on?
The Dollars are messing with us.
Get some backup.
We'll retaliate with numbers!
Numbers!
People I've never met before are helping me.
It's like I'm dreaming.
The bunny's crossed the road!
Togusa, get the car moving.
Right!
Fighting is wrong!
You'll be the next sushi dish.
Wow, look at all of them ring!
It's not only our side whose
phones are ringing.
They're out there, too.
A bunny?
A bunny with huge boobs?
Kazu-yan
Yeah, a bunny.
Does anyone know where the girl
in the bunny costume went?
If anyone's seen her,
tell me right away!
Is that her?
We don't know if her boobs are big or not.
Have to strip her!
But...
My dreams are always lies
that I tell myself.
Wait!
There are more and more
guys in yellow!
All I dreamed of was a smiling happy family.
This is bad! Someone find
the bunny girl fast!
So this isn't a dream.
It's reality.
His hand told me so.
And then I realized that I knew it.
I'd never touched it, but...
Um...
When you realize something's important,
why's it already gone?
Kida-kun... Why?
Why?
Is there something wrong with me saving
you from the Yellow Scarves?
That's my ero-cute Anri-chan!
Even that looks good on you.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What are you doing?
When you were sneaking around,
what were you looking for?
Tell me, Anri-chan.
What are you after?
I was... You...
I... What?
It's my fault?
I was an idiot for trying to protect you?
That's right.
That's not... Don't say that.
Does Mikado know nothing?
What were you going to do with him?
I...
He...
You knew how he felt!
Why don't you tell him-
Was it fun?
Tricking me... Sucking up to him...
What am I saying?
I just didn't want you
to get hurt or hurt anyone...
I ran from you, too.
I...
There she is!
We found her!
You're with the Dollars.
No.
The hell you aren't.
If you aren't, what are you?
Do you want to know what I am?
What?
What are you?
Well? What are you?
Oh, I know!
You're a hero!
You tried to trick our guys
into "protecting the peace."
Wish I could've shown you
what happened to them!
We beat the crap out of them.
What I did...
So yeah, if you're the
only one who's not hurt...
Damn this beeping...
It just won't stop fucking beeping!
I can't read that many words!
Girls? Bunnies? The hell you want me to do?
Damn it all...
I found the girl.
She's fine.
That's about it.
Because...
Because the Fortissimo of Ikebukuro is here!
Um...
Thank you for saving me again.
Who were you again?
Hey, I'm turning my phone off.
See you.
Celty-san...
Mission Success!
Go Dollars!
We did it! We did it!
That's the Dollars for you!
If we all join together,
there's nothing to fear!
Thank you, everyone.
I found it.
The most important thing is...
Mikado?
Oh, my! The match's over?
Shizu-chan showed up at
just the right second.
But we're not done yet.
Just a bit more, and I can get
the checkmate and the oute.
Thank you, everyone.
Oh, there it is!
Celty, get the mushroom!
Oh, come on Celty.
That's impossible.
I told you. You need to be more careful.
Hey!
Celty!
E-Excuse me...
You were so sound asleep,
I didn't want to wake you.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
It's no trouble.
Stay here for a while.
It's dangerous to be living alone.
Are you sure?
If there's anything you need, I'll go get it.
Thank you.
You're staying home from school, right?
I told Mikado.
You know Ryuugamine-kun?
Yeah, I do.
Um... I...
You don't need to worry about a thing.
I'm on your side. And the weird guy in
the white lab coat, you can trust-
...he's on our side, too.
Hey, what was that?
Why did you erase "you can trust"?
Why?
Hey!
Celty!
But I'm surprised.
What?
I didn't think Celty-san would
be living with a guy.
The general ain't been around since then.
Who cares?
We know what we're doing.
Everyone here knows what
we gotta do, right?
We beat the shit out of the Dollars!
I'll call the cops!
Where are you?
The yellow guys are beating people up again.
They're getting stronger.
They really messed up some guy.
A friend said he saw it.
We can't lose! If we all work
together like last time...
What are you thinking right now?
The Dollars are going to disappear.
What do you mean?
This is the founder, right?
Leader, are you running away?
You're not going to disband us, are you?
21:34.
The Ikebukuro Dollars are disbanded?
No!
Disappear means that we need
to be colorless, invisible!
That's irresponsible, leader!
No! Let's believe!
Say something!
Explain!
The Dollars are going to disappear.
You suck.
I can't access it anymore!
Really?
The top page is still there.
But the BBS is completely closed.
What's going on?
He was serious.
That's enough.
Forget about it.
I was alone for a long time,
so I thought and thought and thought.
And then I saw their faces...
Their smiles... And they wouldn't go away.
Uh, can I talk to you?
Of course.
I wanted to talk to you, too.
I thought that since you knew about me,
I could tell you everything.
I see.
I understand.
Then those two don't know about you.
The two of them have always
been there for me,
Kida-kun and Ryuugamine-kun.
But I...
First, we need to stop this gang war.
Yeah.
We'll have to talk to Mikado.
Um, what does Ryuugamine-kun...
How much do you know about him?
So you don't know...
He's like you.
It may be that he's hiding what's important from you
because you're so close and mean so much to him.
Anyway, he should tell you.
I'll bring him here.
Don't give her any strange
ideas while I'm gone.
Or interrogate her or try to
use her for any weird experiments.
Got it.
Trust me.
OK.
I will.
Anri-chan, wait a minute.
Celty-san.
I don't want to run anymore.
Let's go! Let's go!
Blame Kida Masaomi for ordering this!
Kida Masaomi
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Complicated
and Confused
Why couldn't I move then?
What made me hesitate?
What was I afraid of?
Saki... I'm not scared anymore.
I won't run anymore.
Next time:
Complicated and Confused