When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
What? A party to celebrate my acceptance to Hakuou?
Yeah, isn't it a good idea?
But we haven't received official notice yet.
Isn't it a little hasty to have one?
Don't worry about it! You definitely passed the exam!
To be honest,
I have confidence, too.
One hindrance...
...after another.
I was toyed with by the proctor,
and I even had to fight monkeys.
I can't go to school!
Even after all that, I did my best.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, go!
Yes!
Also, I was lucky that all the questions were three-choice multiple choice questions.
I'm really good when it comes to multiple choice.
This one!
You idiot!
Why did you have to open that box out of all of them?!
I'm sorry Milady!
Hey, come back here!
I cannot believe you are good at multiple choice questions.
If Hayate had realized how unlucky he was,
then the coming comedy, I mean tragedy,
might have been avoidable, or not; who knows?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
In a -40° C environment, you can hit a nail in with a banana.
What are you saying, Onee-chan?
I want pickled cucumber.
HIIIIINAAAAAAA!!!
Hina, I'm in trouble!
I'm in deeeeep trouble!
Haven't I always told you to knock before entering other people's rooms?
I'm sorry... I'm really sorry...
Listen, Onee-chan.
Knocking is the best invention mankind has ever invented.
Next time you forget, I'll seriously hit you.
Seriously?
Ah, Yuki-chan.
You came home?
Yup, I'm home, Mom.
You should have given us a call.
Are you managing, living alone?
Don't worry. Have faith in your daughter.
I haven't spent money at host clubs,
and I haven't been tricked by "It's me" frauds or phishing mails!
But I want to see your room once.
I'm in the middle of an important conversation with Hina!
Anyway, can you bring milk tea and some snacks.
Dash! Now!
Okay.
Onee-chan!
Make sure the milk tea is sweet, okay!
Three teaspoons of sugar, got it?!
She always does whatever she wants.
Ah, it's so sweet!
I love dorayaki!
Maybe you'll get along with the cat robot from the future.
Life's great!
So? Didn't you come because you had something you wanted to talk to me about?
That's right!
I'm in trouble, Hina!
Eat or talk. Make a choice.
You see, the Sanzenin butler boy came to take the transfer exam.
Oh, did he really?
Good for Hayate-kun. Hakuou's exam's pretty hard.
But with his position of Nagi's butler,
he probably has no other choice but to pass.
He probably put a lot of effort into it.
Maybe.
You can't get in his way, do you hear me?
Yikes!
"Yikes"?
Don't tell me you...
N-No! I meant it as a prank!
I meant it as a simple joke!
I never thought he'd fail by just one point!
Stop breathing like that!
Your dark side is coming out all over!
What do you think you're doing ruining other people's lives?!
So, your prank is responsible for him failing,
the Superintendent ordered you to report the result, and you've come to me.
Is that right?
Yes, it's exactly as you say.
You're hopeless.
Let's see, the only person I can turn to for things like this is...
Huh? Failed?
Yes. And we're headed your way as we speak to give the report and the apology.
Yes, thank you very much.
I-I'm sorry.
Just so you know, I'm not coming along for you.
It's my duty as Hakuou Academy's Student Council President.
What an amazing sister I have.
When you see Hayate-kun,
make sure you apologize sincerely, do you hear?
Y-Yeah, I'll do my best.
I had an inkling that something like this would happen.
But, what do I do now?
Hey, Hayate!
Listen to me and wear the clothes I picked!
You're the party's guest of honor!
I'll be fine the way I'm dressed now!
What are you talking about!
Get changed already!
But the clothes you pick out are things like sailor uniforms and animal ears!
You're wrong. Tonight's this!
Over my dead body!
PLACEHOLDER
Why? It's neither of the things you said.
It's no longer possible to tell the truth.
I'll never put it on!
What should I do... What should I do... What should I do...
What should I do... What should I do...
What should I do?! What should I do!?
Why don't you calm down?
Welcome, both of you.
G-Good evening!
Th-This is Oka**ya's An**yaki!
It's still early to give it!
It was hard to decide if I should get
****tasia's Green Turtle Bread instead or not.
I-In any case, please come in.
So, um, where's Hayate-kun?
Well...
M-Maria-san...
What is... going on...
Well...
Klaus-san.
Without an event like this, our Lady won't host a social affair.
Since we don't have many opportunities, we took the chance to host a big one.
There you have it.
It's all thanks to him getting admitted to Hakuou.
He sure is a troublemaker,
but he's finally done something good for our Lady.
Where do you think you're going, Onee-chan?
I have urgent business to take care of...
You're not going anywhere.
He loves me.
He loves me not.
Argh, this is getting annoying!
The language of flowers for corn is trust!
Hayate-kun and I are...
They're dancing.
Yes...
It's almost embarrassing to see how merry they are.
He must be really happy he got accepted.
It must be because of the lecture
I gave him about what the exams are like.
Plus I even cornered him in that he'll be fired if he failed!
Oh, is something wrong?
N-No, my chronic peritonitis triggered a neuralgia, and it's hurting the sties in my head.
So please don't worry at all.
Damn that Klaus. I originally wanted to have a cosplay party with just the two of us.
Oh please.
If this wasn't your congratulation party, I would have been long gone.
But Milady, you look great in that dress.
You're more dazzling than anyone else in this room.
You idiot! You're the guest of honor today!
You flatter me.
But I'm happy. Thank you very much, Milady.
Well, if you're happy, then I guess all is well.
Yes.
This situation makes it harder to bring the issue up than I'd thought.
So, please continue to watch them be merry for a while more.
Kushiyaki da!
Kushiyaki da! = We'll have meat on a skewer!
Raja-! = Roger!
Raja-!
Japan! Go desu! = Japan! I'm go!
Note: Quote from "Go Hiromi"
Japan! Go desu!
So what do we do now, Onee-chan?
For now, do you want to wait until the party ends?
Yup, I will.
N-No, this is my responsibility.
If you can't take care of your own responsibilities, you can't claim to be an adult.
Onee-chan.
A-Ayasaki-kun.
Ah, hello, Katsura-sensei.
Welcome.
Is something wrong?
To... To tell you the truth...
To tell you the truth-
The teacher herself has come all the way from Hakuou Academy to celebrate the Acceptance Party of our Lady's butler, Ayasaki Hayate!
Please, give us a speech.
U-Um...
Ah...
Congratulations, Ayasaki-kun.
Here, my congratulations gift.
Thank you very much.
You've worked very hard. I'm really happy for you.
Onee-chan...
Counter... That was a counter hit.
I thought adults had to take responsibility.
But! But!
Next, we'll have Lady Nagi's best friend, Saginimiya Isumi-sama, give us a word.
Ah...
Isumi-sama was headed this way but got lost and was found at a gift shop by Lake Mashuu, so we'll save this for another time.
Note: Lake Mashuu is in Hokkaido.
That's the Isumi I know.
How did she get out of Honshuu?
Next, we have a congratulatory gift from Lady Nagi's cousin, Aizawa Sakuya-sama.
Open!
The title is "Fly"!
How is it flying?
The size, perhaps?
But isn't it a shame that neither Isumi
nor Sakuya could make it to your party?
It's fine.
I'm happy enough that Katsura-sensei and Hinagiku-san came.
Come to think of it, why are you here, Hinagiku?
Th-Th-Th-That's because...
Can I have a moment?
What?
Just come.
WHAT?!?! He failed?!
You're too loud!
That's impossible coming from Hayate.
It's the truth, so you can't do anything about it.
I want to somehow let him know, but...
That's impossible. I can't tell him now that he didn't pass.
Why are you guys even saying that he passed before he even received notice?
Can't you do something with your authority as the Student Council President?
Then how about Sanzenin family's authority?
The night is starting to come to a close.
So now let's have our last event.
Tonight could not have happened without all of you.
Therefore, let's have a word of gratitude from Ayasaki Hayate.
U-Um...
Thank you all for your time and coming today to celebrate for the likes of me.
I never imagined I'd be able to go to school again.
It's really like a dream.
I had completely given up on it...
...that I would ever be able to go to high school.
The days where you chat
and fool around with your friends in class.
A really mundane life, yet a life that seems so far away and a life I miss.
I thought I would never gain it no matter how much I wished for it.
However, Lady Nagi made my dream come true.
I'm really a blessed guy.
I'm the luckiest butler in the world
to be able to serve such a kind Lady.
Hayate...
Th-Thank you very much.
Ayasaki-kun.
Listen to me, Ayasaki-kun.
Yes, what is it?
Onee-chan.
Truth is... I have very disappointing news for you.
Disappointing news?
Yes.
Is... Is she finally going to say it?
The truth is...
I know.
Ehh?!
Hayate-kun?
My homeroom teacher is you, right, Katsura-sensei?
Heh?
You're right. With you as my teacher,
I can imagine a really rough school life waiting for me.
I have some concerns that I might get physically and mentally worn out,
but please don't worry.
That'll probably be a fun life in its own way.
You're right; it sounds fun.
How much more do you intend to fool around?
Whose fault do you think it is that this happened?
B-But...
With that innocent look on his face, I can't make myself say it.
And it's like, "Why haven't you figured it out yourself by now, asshole."
That's right!
I'm troubled by it so much,
yet he's just smiling with an idiot look.
Suddenly rage is starting to take over!
Onee-chan?
I've decided! I'll take the secret that he failed all the way to my grave!
What?
It's a huge school. No one's going to notice one fake student.
I, Katsura Yukiji, fear nothing!
What kind of nonsense are you speaking?
I'm not speaking nonsense!
He's the nonsense!
Um, what are you all talking about so exuberantly?
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing important.
We're sorry, Hayata-kun.
Y-You girls!
Why are you all here?
We visited Katsura-chan's room, and we found this.
Therefore we came to console Hayata-kun, who we were sure would be sulking.
I'm very sorry for you, Hayata-kun.
Right now, you might be feeling that your life's over.
There's nothing good from here on out.
But mistakes you make when you're young are valuable for your future!
No matter how many times you may tumble over, keep rising up like a weed and Princess **rah!
Cheer up, Hayata-kun.
Fight, ya!
Goodbye, Hayata-kun.
Um...
I still don't understand what exactly is going on, but...
Basically, I failed, right?
Yeah...
I...
I see...
I'm sorry!
I'm fully responsible!
So boil me or roast me or do whatever you please to me!
In fact, just kill me!
Eh?
He's gone.
Hayate-kun?
Hayate!
Where did he go?
You'll catch a cold if you stay out too long.
Nagi and Katsura-san are worried.
I've done something horrible to Milady.
To Katsura-sensei and Hinagiku-san, too...
To all the people who celebrated me today, too...
Hayate-kun?
It's because I was so merry and had high hopes.
I'm such an idiot.
Before coming here, I learned the lesson to not have hopes for the future so that I wouldn't be hurt.
But as I indulged myself in Maria-san's, Milady's, and everyone's kindness, I was forgetting that very basic mindset.
The emptier you are, the less you lose.
So... So...
Would the empty person you describe ever manage to be Nagi's butler?
W-Well...
Of course, I'm aware that I cause a lot of trouble.
But I'm ready to refocus my mind and work harder.
"Work harder"?
Oh, but your face says you can't do it alone.
Maria-san?
Therefore...
...go here and learn everything you can.
Th-This is a Hakuou Academy...
M-My student ID?
Yes. I sent my recommendation,
and with that factored in, they admitted you.
Someone who's empty and has nothing to lose can't possibly become her butler.
Maria-san...
Hayate-kun. I think one day, there'll be a time when your strength will truly be necessary to protect her.
So please become Nagi's best butler.
Yes. I will go to Hakuou and become the best butler!
Okay.
All right, I'm going to work hard!
I'm going to become the best butler for Maria-san's sake, too!
Not for me, you know.
And, I cannot believe how close I was to Hayate-kun just then.
So that was Maria's embarrassing moment.
You're better off not doing it
if you're going to blush over it later.
Next time, we'll fight against the girls' expectations.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Good mor-eve-noon. I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
Hello. I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I don't really get it, but you can go to school, after all?
Yes, thank you very much. I'll study hard so as to not shame you as your butler.
I-I see, so you're making serious considerations about our future.
What's wrong, Milady?
Nothing. I was only doing some meditation.
It's about aura power!
Bye bye.
I was happy out of my mind that I got accepted,
but will I be fine here with my borderline grades?
You'll do fine, Hayate.
Battles are meant to be fought while reading two, three moves ahead.
It's nice to wake up early once in a while.
I met an interesting person.
Do I lose if I comment that you're the most interesting one?
I think so.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Samurai, Chivalry, Mobile Vandam.
Himuro, are these enough flowers?
Thank you, Sir Taiga.
It's dangerous, so don't copy what Ayasaki-kun's doing.