Run! Hurry it up!
Tooru-chan's waiting for you!
Coming...
Did you forget anything?
Of course not.
Take care!
Okay. See you tonight.
Thanks for waiting.
Good morning, Run-chan.
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
On Rainy Days, a Bath
Wow, really?
Hm? I texted you about it after dinner yesterday.
Huh? Really?
I didn't see that text.
Hm?
Run-chan.
Your socks.
I forgot to put on one of them!
This is so embarrassing...
I might as well go barefoot then.
R-R-R-R-Run-chan...
W-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
Where are your panties?
How on Earth did I not notice that!
How on Earth...
Don't squat! You'll be exposed in front!
It was because I was sleepy...
Is that the only reason?
Don't worry!
Am I the only one who does this?
Everyone forgets things sometimes!
Usually not their panties, though.
Tooru... just now...
Just now...
You thought, "Usually not panties," right?
Run-chan! Don't run-
Not again...
You sure have it rough, Tooru.
Sorry about that, Tooru.
I'm just not a morning person...
I get so sleepy that I space out.
Is that the issue here?
She's wearing them now.
O-Of course she is!
I... I was just thinking, what if...
Ah, oh yeah, Run.
What?
Can I copy your class notes from yesterday afternoon?
Ah.
That's right, you left early yesterday.
Sure thing.
Here.
Thanks!
You're a lifesaver.
What language is this?
Oh, come on, it's Japanese!
I had a fit of sleepiness during class.
So it's not just mornings then.
Is it hard to read?
N-No, not at all!
Thank you!
If there's any part you can't read, just say so.
Here.
Thanks!
Hey, Yuuko-chan.
Can you let me see that afterwards?
Sure.
When you're done copying, give it to Run.
All right then.
Right then.
Hey.
Hm?
Nagi, are you nearsighted?
What's your acuity?
2.0
These glasses are just for show.
Really? Why do you wear fake glasses?
If I don't wear these...
I end up seeing things I don't have to see.
You mean... don't tell me...
Oh!
Just now, right behind you, Yuuko...
No, I'm kidding.
I told you, I'm joking.
It's too much fun to tease you.
I'm just nearsighted.
Seriously, stop it!
I'm bad with scary stories!
You scared me too!
Nagi-chan, you're a good actor!
You should join the drama club!
I'm in it.
Eh?
note: people who never go to club meetings
I'm a phantom member, though.
Clever!
Not at all!
"I received two or three letters from you this summer.
If I remember rightly, it was in your second letter
that you asked me to help you find a suitable post."
I need to go to the bathroom...
Consider the sense of human ego and conflict
that can be inferred from "Sensei"'s letter
An existence who
clearly portrays 1 of
the flaws of a
self-centered world view
The "Sensei" of the following chapter
The "I" of this passage
Um, sensei...
What is it?
Uhh... umm...
Oh no! I'm too embarrassed to say I have to go to the bathroom!
My... my head hurts...
Yuuko, that's your stomach!
Um, I mean, that is...
Sensei, excuse me!
I need to use the bathroom,
so can I bring Yuuko to the nurse's office, and go along the way?
Very well, you may go.
Run...
Let's go, Yuuko-chan!
Right.
S-Sorry about that, Run. You saved me back there.
It's okay. I needed to go, too.
Oh, to the bathroom, too?
No, to the...
...nurse's office.
Run!
Run, what's wrong?
Does it hurt anywhere?
I'm not sure what's wrong, but I don't feel so great...
Maybe I caught something-
I'm gonna be sick.
Should we go to the bathroom?
But wait, uh, to the nurse's office?
No, to the bathroom?
To the... to... to... to...
That's right!
Tooru!
Yuuko-chan! That's not what I...
Nurse's Office
Run! Hey!
Run! Pull yourself together!
Yuuko.
You here?
Tooru!
Run suddenly lost consciousness!
The nurse isn't here today, either. What do we do?
Calm down!
Why don't you call another teacher or something...
Both of you, be quiet.
There's nothing to worry about.
She was just sleep-deprived.
It's raining.
No umbrella.
Me neither. It was sunny this morning.
But it's just showering. If we run, we can make it.
Wait here, Tooru.
Watch me!
Aoigaoka High School
I discovered recently,
that I'm a rain woman.
You don't have to risk your life!
Hurry up and get back here!
I got all wet!
Don't be so reckless.
Who's that?
He's staring at us.
With Run-chan in the state she's in now...
Run-chan.
Hm?
Let's go inside.
Sure.
Wonderful.
Thank goodness. At this school...
Please turn in your overnight camp permission
forms to your class monitor or Yamada.
What a pain...
Run-chan, if you don't dry off quickly...
Okay, it's done!
Tooru, put this on!
Trash Bag
Ta-dah!
Now you don't need an umbrella!
At our age, isn't this a bit awkward?
I mean, if we were elementary schoolers...
Yeah, I guess it is.
People might think we're a couple since we match.
Then, one of us should...
No, that's not what I meant.
What is that?
Then I'll take mine off.
What's this?
I'm already wet anyway.
No, I'll do it.
Let's go home.
Nagi-chan, Yuuko-chan!
Don't come after us!
Good grief.
I was wondering what you were doing.
Run! You're soaked!
My place isn't far.
Want to dry your clothes there?
Can I? Thanks!
But it's still...
Wow...
Wonder if there's a rain woman on campus.
Now what do we do?
It's raining harder, but if we run, it'll be fine!
If we all get wet, we won't be scared!
Well, if it's just to Nagi's house...
What a drag.
I don't want to get wet, so I'll call a taxi.
Such an un-high-schooler-like utterance!
Maybe it'll stop if we wait?
Doesn't look like it.
I'm telling you, I'll call a taxi-
Here I go!
Nagi-chan, your house is this way, right?
Hey, stop!
Wait, me too!
I said wait up!
Come on, come on!
Hang on!
Don't leave me behind!
You'd think rainy days would make them depressed,
but they're having so much fun.
Ah, to be young!
K's Poems
In the rain, your smile was simply so radiant, that I
No matter how strong the rain nor how dark the clouds nor how sharp
They could not hide your radiant sunlight. Indeed, even if they
It's coming to me!
Kitou
-sensei
Hobby:
Poetry
It's all coming to me!
Reality
I'm home.
Pardon the intrusion!
Go ahead, come in.
Let's hurry up and get in the bath.
Hm? Aniki's home already.
Nagi, you have an older brother?
Onii-chan!
I've got friends over!
So don't use the bathroom, 'kay?
Nagi-chan,
do you call your older brother "aniki,"
or "onii-chan"?
I call him "aniki"!
Well then,
only two people can enter the bath at once.
Let's split into two groups.
Ready, set, and shoot.
Well, I'll go first with Run then.
Enjoy!
Why don't we get changed, then?
There we go.
That's right!
Come to think of it,
I've never spoken with Tooru alone before!
What should I do?
This awkward silence is kinda...
Kinda...
Yuuko.
Y-Yes?
Want to watch something?
There are plenty of DVDs.
Th-There sure are.
"Scary but True Urban Legends"
"Scary but True Urban Legends,"
or silence.
Which do you prefer?
The ultimate decision!
Just leave your clothes there.
Okay! Here, right?
Let's hop right in, then.
Whoa, who are you?
Huh?
It's me, Run.
Well yeah, I know that.
But man,
just letting your bangs down
sure changes how you look.
Who are you?
Your reaction...
I have no words.
Ah, it feels so nice!
Makes you feel refreshed, doesn't it?
But we'd better finish up quickly.
You're right.
We've got to switch with Tooru and Yuuko-chan.
Those two are alone in my room right now.
Will they be all right?
They'll be fine!
They get along so well!
Well...
Even so...
Oh no! Oh no!
I can't keep this up!
That's right!
If I close my eyes, I won't be scared.
I'm the one who wants to scream.
Sorry for the wait!
Go ahead and use the bath- huh?
Oy, Yuuko?
The bath is free.
Yuuko-chan!
Yuuko-chan?
Yuuko-chan?!
Yuuko-chan!
Oh no, Yuuko-chan has...!
What the heck happened?
Whew.
That was really scary.
We finally get to take a bath!
Right, Tooru?
Yeah.
Shall we get in?
Say,
Tooru, do you ever get scared while washing your hair,
because you can't see?
You see,
when I was a kid, I was really bad with shampoo...
Shampoo's getting in my eye!
What are you doing, Tooru?
Where's the shower head?
My eyes...
Hey!
Yuuko!
You're being too loud!
Please, stop it!
Gosh.
I thought my heart would stop.
My mind is going hazy.
Run.
Look at that.
I can see an oasis.
Nagi? Run?
W-What happened to you two?
Yuuko...
How was the temperature of the bath?
Never mind that!
More importantly, shut off the heater already.
We figured... we'd dry out our clothes...
Delicious!
Ah, I'm alive again!
Gosh, don't worry us like that!
They're pretty much dry.
I wonder if the rain will stop soon?
Not yet, it looks like.
It sure is coming down.
Rainy days really get to your hair.
Mine sort of goes all limp.
Mine gets all spread out and won't stay down.
I guess we have different hair types.
Yuuko-chan, let me touch your hair!
Sure, go ahead.
Yuuko-chan, your hair is so pretty!
Tooru!
Hm?
You don't have any split ends!
Wanna play?
Aw, that's not true.
Sure.
Hey, isn't this outfit cute-
Don't move!
This is the delicate part!
All right.
There we go!
W-What?
Don't move!
I lost!
You're still playing?
I'm going to beat Nagi's high score.
That's quite the temperament you've got.
Yuuko, your hands are kinda pretty.
T-They aren't really...
How do you take care of them?
I don't do anything in particular.
Well then, in that case...
Ba-ba-bum!
It feels nice,
b-but it's kinda embarrassing.
T-Tooru? Ah, wait-
Don't move!
Gosh! What am I supposed to do then?
I've got no plans after school.
Looks like it's still going.
Since it's raining outside,
It sure is coming down.
But you know, I really like the sound of rain.
let's meet up at my place.
Really?
You never were one to show your true feelings.
I sorta know what you mean.
Right?
Come on, Nagi-chan, close your eyes and listen, too!
But today I'm sure you'll understand.
What?
No, I'll be...
I just want to see your smile.
You don't have to hide over there.
Here now, come a bit closer.
You're my friend, too.
From here on out, no matter how many seasons pass us by,
stay close by my side forever.
I want to be with you.
I want to laugh with you.
Well,
it's certainly not bad.
But...
it sorta sounds like something's grilling.
It's making me kind of hungry.
Run-chan.
That was me.
Again?
See you.
Be careful on your way home.
Will do!
Thanks for lending us umbrellas, too!
See you tomorrow, then!
Thanks for letting us stop by!
See you!
Hey, that umbrella's pretty cute!
It sure is.
Ah, the rain's still coming down strong.
What time's the next train?
Onii-chan!
You can use the bathroom again now!
Min.
Later
Didn't I tell you
to be careful?
I'm sorry.
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
Our chatter goes on and on,
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
Everyone, sorry for the wait!
Next week, Yutaka and Miporin are finally appearing!
Sorry for the wait!
Thinking back, it was fifteen years of determination...
Right! Enough nostalgia!
So wait, meaning we weren't supposed to show up in episode one?
Well, if you put it that way, we did show up in the opening.
Well, I guess you're right.
Next time on A-Channel!
"Classmates"!
Ah, but of course, aside from us classmates,
the upperclassmen will show up as well!
See you next week!