He comes by sometimes.
It's been a while, Kida Masaomi-kun.
What?
They got in a fight with another
gang and then vanished.
<Tanaka Tarou> The Yellow Scarves
Can't ask Orihara Izaya
about that, yeah...
The bastards dragged me back,
damn it. Damn it all!
Mikajima Saki
Your friend was hospitalized?
Who told you?
I saw it from the window.
You were here every day.
A girl, right?
A quirky, charming high school girl,
with a hot body and glasses.
You love her?
Yeah. It's a love triangle
with my best friend.
If you add me, it's a square.
We're over. Finished!
All finished.
Right?
Then why are you here?
You felt like you wanted to
return to old times?
Sorry. I'm heading out.
You'll come back.
That's how things are.
So you can love all the other girls
you want, and I don't care.
In the end, you'll love me more
than you love them.
I didn't need to ask.
The same thing, over and over.
Even if you date tons of girls,
you'll still come back to me.
Then you'll love me, more and more
than you ever loved her.
But I didn't want to hear her next words.
Izaya-san said so.
When you look at it like this,
you feel like a god.
It feels pretty good.
Three-way struggles are nice.
Especially when all three leaders
are so closely connected.
God attack!
The hotter the honeymoon,
the higher the flames of despair.
Look! The pawns burn like garbage!
Now, then...
How will each of the non-pawns move?
Kadota and his gang,
Shinra, Simon...
I guess Shizu-chan would be the king.
Celty's the queen.
So the joker's...
Who cares?
It's gotten fun.
You think so, too, right?
Out of
Your Control
Raira
General
Hospital
-One Year Earlier-
I heard she hadn't died.
Good to hear...
Long as she's alive,
the rest'll work itself out.
Izaya-san...
You're smart.
You know what happened to
her is your fault.
I think it was pretty wise,
not letting your feelings
overwhelm you and trying to punch me.
Right answer.
It's natural to direct your
anger at me right now.
I was deliberately provoking you.
She's in a coma?
Hope she wakes up.
Or would it be better for you
if she never does?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
You're scared, aren't you?
If she wakes up,
she might blame you forever.
But what if she dies?
You gonna spend the rest of
your life feeling guilty?
In other words, whether she lives or dies,
it won't affect the guilt you feel at all.
You can't get away.
The past will follow you,
wherever you go.
Forever and ever and ever and ever...
You know why?
They're lonely.
A person's past and memories are
very lonely things.
I don't believe in god.
There's no proof of his existence.
In a world where there isn't
even proof of the future,
the past exists.
Even if it's tainted with
misunderstandings and delusions,
if the people themselves believe it,
the past is the truth to them.
And if you base your actions or
your life around it,
in a way, it's a type of god itself.
I have no idea what you're getting at!
Sure you do.
You can't get away from her, ever.
Your guilt will become your past,
and she your god.
But isn't that fine?
You love her...
Anri's back to her old self!
Glad she and her hotness are safe.
Don't talk like that.
But I'm really relieved.
Really.
U-Um, thanks, you guys.
No need to thank me.
As long as you and your hotness are safe.
I'm the same, except for the hotness.
Yeah?
OK.
Got it.
Be right there.
Sorry! A friend has something
he needs right away!
Yeah?
If you want to hate someone,
hate my friend all you like.
Hating someone's free,
and it doesn't hurt me at all.
Two birds with one stone!
Two chicks and one guy!
Two chicks and one guy?
See you tomorrow!
Was it really that important?
Kida-kun's been acting weird lately,
don't you think?
Really? Sure you're not
overthinking things?
I never spoke about the
Yellow Scarves to Mikado.
This reality and the one that exists when
I'm with him are both true to me,
but I feel like there's a
big difference between them.
We spent all our days fighting.
That was the only thing that connected us.
I wanted someone to say they liked me,
that I was a good person.
That was when I first met Saki.
I like that yellow scarf.
You're much cooler than the
rumors say, Kida Masaomi-kun.
What?
How did you know my name?
You an esper?
Maybe like Esper Ito?
You keep reading my mind, and I'll stuff
you in a bag and take you home!
Yes...
Aw, you're so silly.
But it's not me.
There's another esper.
Who's that?
Got a girl here with the sixth sense?
They're amazing.
They know everything.
That was when I met the man
I really wish I hadn't.
Hey there.
Kida Masaomi-kun, right?
Who're you?
Orihara Izaya,
information broker.
I'm kind of her guardian.
Not her boyfriend or anything!
Don't worry.
Pleasure to meet ya.
General!
I told you, call me Kida
Masaomi, not General.
But that's just kinda...
We can't find out anything
about the Dollars.
Some of our guys are members,
but we don't know who their leader is.
They say, even at their first meeting,
six months ago, no one could find it out.
They doing anything?
The leader issued a request for
information on the Slasher.
Maybe they really aren't behind the attacks.
Even so, they're still fishy.
Anything else?
Horada-san was taken
out by the black biker.
Horada-san?
A bit back, I was making fun of
some weirdo in a white gas mask,
when the black biker got me...
The black biker?
Yeah, some kind of weird
black oil enveloped me...
Yeah...
Wonder who the Black Rider really is.
Some say they're part of the Dollars.
Whatever.
By the way, you guys are
older than me, right?
Well, yes...
Don't bring in anyone older than you.
We start seeing names like "Someone of
the Something Yakuza," and we're done.
We're kids!
We've got a lot of members,
but we can't win against adults.
We'll be used and thrown away!
Like Orihara Izaya used me.
From then on, whenever I wasn't
sure about something,
Saki would tell me to ask Izaya-san.
She would always bring up what
he thought about things.
I'm glad this could be resolved
to your mutual benefit.
At first, everyone was pretty annoyed,
but actually, if you did stuff his way,
things went well.
I didn't trust him.
I tried to keep as far away
from him as I could.
Izaya-san's amazing.
He knows everything.
He's never wrong.
So if he told you to jump off a
bridge and die, would you?
Probably, yeah.
I kinda pitied her.
I wanted to free her from him.
So, you think we're dating?
I don't know.
What are you doing with
a guy like me, anyway?
I like you.
Did he tell you to?
Just at first, yeah.
He doesn't get involved in
other people's love lives.
Then why do you still like me?
You're cool!
You're cute, maybe.
Do you like me?
If you stopped your fanatical
worship of him, I might!
I can't!
I'd be happy if you overlooked
that one flaw.
So you know it's a flaw?
Yup.
Not that I'm gonna fix it.
If you think it's a flaw, fix it.
I'll help you.
So we started to date.
No one was mad at me for dating Saki.
I was serious,
and the Yellow Scarves were
too busy fighting Blue Square.
They fought dirty.
They'd fight small groups with big ones.
They wouldn't attack unless they
were sure they could win.
Over a hundred of my friends were hurt.
Everyone was scared.
So was I.
I was afraid of losing my place in life
if I disbanded the Yellow Scarves.
So...
Ask Izaya-san.
I relied on him.
I was too scared to do otherwise.
Welcome!
I told myself it was for the others' sake.
Come in and let's chat.
His information changed the
Yellow Scarves dramatically.
He didn't just give us information
on where they were,
he gave us information on how to fight.
We'd been losing, but we
weren't any longer.
Your information's so awesome!
Eventually, I lost my fear of him.
Actually, I was enjoying my victory, but...
Kida Masaomi-kun?
Who's this?
Hello!
This is Izumii, head of Blue Square.
I have a quiz for you!
Question 1: We've got a special
guest here today!
Who do you suppose it is?
Hint: It's someone very, very,
very important to you!
Hey!
Time's up, but I bet you
figured it out, didn't you?
That's right!
What did you do with Saki?!
Question 2: What do you suppose
she looks like right now?
Question 3:
What bone was that,
that just broke?
Hint: She won't be walking for a while!
Final Question:
What's going to happen to her
if you don't come to
the parking garage, where you
trapped us, in twenty mins?
I regretted it. I'd been a fool.
I'd figured this was just a bunch of
middle schoolers fighting.
It wasn't.
It was a war.
And I'd started it!
Orihara Izaya
Pick up! Pick up, damn it!
Kida Masaomi
The person you have dialed is-
What the hell?!
Izumii-san, she fainted.
Boring.
We just broke her leg in a few places.
I ran.
I had to go.
I would go there and kill every one of
them who had made her scream.
The person you have dialed...
So yeah, the Yellow Scarves?
We're gonna beat down their leader.
I said, I ain't down for it.
No, it looks like we kidnapped
his girlfriend.
She's a kid but pretty hot.
That'll be plenty of fun!
Kidnapped?
I see.
I'll be right there.
Right?
You can't pass this up-
When you wake up, tell Izumii that
I'm done with the bastard.
I couldn't move.
What I had just been feeling was gone.
Why... Saki was in danger,
and I couldn't move.
Why?
Why am I so scared?
I thought I could do anything for her!
I was just a powerless middle schooler.
You think she'll die?
Not that I care.
She's not bleeding, so it's fine.
Sup!
Oh my, my, my...
You actually kidnapped her!
What? It's just you, Yumasaki?
Where's Kadota?
Thus, unlike in the movies and manga,
no help came,
and a terrible fate awaited her.
So I was thinking...
If a hero appeared and saved her,
maybe it'd turn into an anime,
and I could be, like,
another world's savior with superpowers,
and I'd get all the chicks and
my dream of building a harem!
Dude's one creepy bastard.
So, yeah. Here goes the "Make me an
anime hero via a happy ending" plan!
Banzai!
Hurry!
Damn you, Kadota!
We shouldn't move her too much.
We should get her to a hospital.
You guys sure you're OK with this?
We're with you.
We don't care about Blue Square.
Honestly, I always thought Izumii and
Horada were a couple of assholes.
Agreed!
It'd be cooler to throw it out the window.
I don't litter.
Eventually, Saki woke up.
The leader, Izumii, was arrested,
thanks to her testimony.
A weakened Blue Square
was forced to disband.
Hey.
You're Kida, with the Yellow Scarves.
Who are you guys?
I dunno how to put it...
I'm Kadota.
I heard you betrayed your
gang and saved Saki.
Umm... Thank you.
Actually, we just went to see her.
She said you haven't been there.
It's got nothing to do with you.
We were asked to give you a message.
She said she can see you
quite well from her window.
Thanks for coming.
I told her that you were stopped by
Blue Square and couldn't make it in time.
She wasn't angry with you.
Later.
Why... Why did you tell her that?
When did I ask for that?
I'd have told her that,
even if you'd told me not to.
You know what happened, right?!
I... I ran...
I couldn't move!
Yeah, I know.
And you're still running from her now.
You want me to lie to her?!
After I ran away from her...
Listen, kid.
If you feel guilty for running,
then for the rest of your life, you must
live with the pain of lying to her.
That's how you can make it up to her.
And if you don't want to lie to her,
then don't run.
Face her and say it!
I'll let you run from the past.
But don't run from the present
and the future.
Hey, Kadota-san's saying something cool.
Wow!
We'll call him poem boy-tan!
I never did go.
I tried to go.
I went many times.
Just to tell her I wanted to break up.
But I couldn't.
I left the Yellow Scarves.
You decide on what high
school you're going to?
I'm going to Raira Academy.
It's close.
I kept talking about how
great a place Raira was.
I was lonely.
When I was talking with him, I felt calm.
<Masaomi> You come, too.
And then I met him again.
I met Anri, too.
I thought my peaceful high
school life would continue.
But...
Damn them... Damn them
for bringing me back.
I was never going to go back.
You can't get away from her, ever.
Your guilt toward her will become
your past, and she your god.
That's right.
That's why I'm here.
I'm going to defeat the Slasher
who hurt my friend, Anri.
If the Slasher is the Dollars,
I'll take them down, too.
I won't freeze up this time.
This time, I will...
Who's there?
What is it?
A girl was looking in here!
I've got men chasing her!
A girl?
Is it the Dollars, you think?
I want to talk to her.
Catch her, but don't hurt her.
Right!
I'll go around this way.
I should be certain about this.
It's why I came back.
So why... Why am I so uneasy?
Why?
Why is Kida-kun...
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Anarchy
The girl ran.
On and on, she ran.
To escape the shadows that followed...
To escape the cruel truth she had learned...
Next time:
Anarchy.