You bastards!
What? What's happening?
There's someone else.
Eh?
You're kidding me...
Where?
Where did the shot come from?
No way.
Mission accomplished.
Good.
Move to route C and await further orders.
Yes, Master.
A gun that didn't hit stirs up discord.
Well then, how will the heroine improvise her escape?
Is it proper manners to call a meeting and then suddenly start shooting?
You will pay for this, I swear it.
What the hell are you talking about?
Didn't one of you shoot first?
Is that so?
In that case,
I'll kill you all.
Don't, Mr. Godou.
Huh?
That startled me.
Lei...
I'm...
...with you...
There's another sniper.
But...
Reiji!
Hey, Reiji!
Is something wrong?
Nope.
Let's retreat.
I understand.
My subordinate has managed to neutralize the threat.
There will be no danger of another shot.
What kind of farce is this, eh?
Mr. Godou.
He's responsible for stealing your money, threatening and attempting to kill you.
I present to you Isaac Wisemel.
What?
A traitor deep within the organization...
...has been disposed of by me.
Traitor?
You can explain this, can you?
Sending one of our own to heaven,
that is.
This sniping was plotted by Wisemel.
My subordinate has discovered and incapacitated the sniper,
which is evidence beyond doubt.
Hum, you're telling quite a story.
This is Inferno's way of settling debts.
The shot at the hotel was after I killed Randy.
I'm certain it wasn't one of Wisemel's orders.
It was a different sniper.
That guy was probably working under Wisemel too.
He's always had backup plans.
Then why did the negotiations resume and why did the sniper go silent?
Wasn't it Wisemel's objective to kill Daisuke Godou?
You sound as if you know the truth behind all this.
It's kill or be killed.
I don't care either way.
The sniper's true objective was...
...to disrupt them.
To put strife into their midst.
Did they even anticipate Claudia would shoot Wisemel?
Stop.
This whole case is a scheme of Wisemel's.
Therefore, Clau killed him based on her own judgment.
Don't overanalyze.
We are only soldiers.
There's no need to step beyond that.
It's as Lizzy said.
We don't need to know the truth.
If this crime spree was indeed perpetrated by Wisemel,
then it's obvious where the five million dollars should be.
The stolen money of the Godou clan will come from Wisemel's villa.
This will settle everything.
The deaths of the yakuza and avenging Judy's murder.
And...
...my own self-deception.
No.
No way.
No way that...
...she's alive.
Hey, I heard a rumor...
...saying that Isaac of the Bloodies died.
That's right.
The sniper you shot was his henchman, and also the one who killed Judy, right?
Yeah.
Then it's over...
My revenge.
I see.
By the way, how did it go?
Training me into an assassin, I mean.
If it's fine with you, can I help with other assassinations too?
The killing... is over.
Eh?
It's over.
Then I'm just a nuisance now?
I wonder.
But...
Eh?
I do have need of your cooking skills.
You can be a cooking maid for a while.
Really?
Yahoo, I get to be a maid.
I've always wanted to try being a maid.
Maid uniforms are soo cute!
You don't need to wear that.
Eh, I don't wear a uniform?
Nope.
I don't mind though, since I can stay beside you.
A marvelous report.
This subsumes the series of incidents were the plotting of Isaac Wisemel,
and the Godou clan will have to accept that.
But,
I'm amazed you were able to conclude this in such chaotic times.
You're talented.
I will let you take the place Isaac vacated.
Well then.
Don't disappoint me, Claudia McCunnen.
I won't.
Potential?
Correct.
She has a rare resourcefulness about her.
You can call it a talent if you like.
"Talent".
I heard the same word a long time ago.
In other words, you want to train the girl into another hitman?
Correct.
If you cannot give rise to something...
You know what happens, right?
I do.
Well then, let's see how skillful you can shape her to be.
There won't come a danger larger than this.
I should find an excuse and...
...send her away from here.
However, I...
...feel at ease here.
Cal!
I'm heading out.
I might be back late, perhaps a day after tomorrow.
Eh?
I should have told you before.
No, it's ok.
Have a nice trip.
Be careful.
You too.
You seem to have taken well to office work.
You must be kidding me.
How about doing this from now on?
Perhaps it's suited for you.
There's no need to put yourself in danger.
This isn't the end.
It's only the beginning.
What more do you want?
Greed could be the end of you.
I know you won't find rest.
But be careful where you tread.
Do I look that stupid?
At least let me warn you.
It's my hobby anyway.
Cal, I don't really understand.
This is the fruit...
Cal?
Ah, welcome home!
You're already back.
Cal, where did you go?
You bought the right one.
It's tastier to cook chicken with this.
Is it fine to leave it like this?
Leave it like this...
Reiji!
What's wrong?
I... want to be your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I understand.
Your feelings about not letting me be an assassin, I mean.
You understand the sorrow of being an assassin.
But I want to be able to do something.
I'm weak and poor.
I can't do anything without help.
I don't want to stay like this.
Cal, you have so many paths you can walk.
You can be anything.
Why must you become an assassin?
Reiji, do you hate being an assassin?
Yeah.
Then, do you hate yourself?
Yeah, I hate myself.
I became a killer and can't stop being a killer.
I really hate myself.
But, Reiji...
I'm already broken.
Do you want to be like me?
I-I'm sorry, Reiji.
I...
Cal, I said too much.
Sorry.
But I told the truth.
I don't know how many have died because of me.
If I were not in this world, they would be alive.
They could return to their lovers and family.
It's not your fault.
Killing was just your duty.
It's not so simple.
Then, do you wish to kill?
Did you kill because you wanted to?
Do you like to kill?
You're different, aren't you?
You feel hurt, pained and sad.
You can't forgive yourself.
You want to kill yourself.
But unlike Judy's killer you don't shoot without reason.
You're bearing the pain of living.
That's why you don't make mistakes, Reiji.
You won't kill people at random.
If those people had been like you, Reiji,
I'm sure Judy wouldn't have died.
But, Cal,
once you kill someone, the entire world changes.
Even the sceneries you see...
...and the sounds that reach your ear...
...will change.
The way you are now...
You won't be able to accept kindness any more.
I don't want you to be like that.
This place was not meant for you.
You shouldn't come over to my world.
But...
But you will always stay in that world, won't you?
If I step into your world, I can be beside you.
Cal...
I don't want to be separated.
I want to stay beside you.
To be useful for you.
I want to be...
...together with you.
So that's how it is.
I...
...wanted to return.
I could be with you then.
It's okay.
I'm going.
I will come to your side.
Let me go.
Let me go back...
...to Cal's world.
Cal, before I met you, I was as good as dead.
If we're seperated...
...I would be the walking dead again.
You're the one who made me recall...
...how to laugh...
...and how to cry.
What, it's him...
Do you know him?
Of course I do.
It's that kid.
I was shocked as well.
Ms. McCunnen should have been helping you join Inferno.
When did that change, I wonder?
I don't fucking care.
Contact the boss immediately.
Quick!
Understood!
Your turn will soon be over, Ms. McCunnen.
I will gift you with a grand flower for the falling curtain.
Hello.
Phantom, can you move out now?
What is it so suddenly?
The Bloodies are making suspicious moves.
I'd like it to be silently taken care of.
Could you do me the favor?
Okay.
Where should I go?
We will meet at the usual spot, and hurry.
Roger.
Job?
Yeah.
I wanted to have the whole day with you.
What are you saying?
We will always be together from now on.
Eh?
There's plenty of time.
I'll return to my old self.
For Cal's sake...
...and...
...for Elen's as well.
Don't call me Elen.
I'm Ein.
From the days of yore until now, simply Ein.