Um... thank you for saving me when I was in trouble!
So... what's your name?
What do you think you're doing?!
You're being way too bold!
I'm not ready for that yet!
Tsubomi?
Pushing us away like that was mean!
I'm sorry! I just had a rather shocking dream...
Shocking?
What was it about?
It's a secret!
Mornin', Tsubomi!
Good morning!
It's almost time for school.
Shouldn't you get changed?
It's already this late?! I totally forgot to get changed!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
So you did take my advice after all!
Huh?
The glasses and your hairstyle.
I figured if I wanted to change my personality, I should start by changing my looks...
You do look a lot better that way.
Hey, we'd better hurry!
Like I told you yesterday, it's fine if you call me Erika.
Next time you don't use my name, you're gonna have to buy me a carton of milk!
You got i—
Safe!
The Second Precure
is Raring to go!
Hurry, hurry!
Eating lunch up here really is the best!
It really is nice!
Let's eat!
Hey, Tsubomi.
Yes?
Recently, I've been... having some kinda weird dreams.
About some Precure
something-or-other getting defeated.
You mean Cure Moonlight?!
Yeah, that!
What?!
So you've been having the same dreams as me?!
The same dreams?
That means she can become a Precure!
Th-The plushies are talking!
Why on earth were you in there?!
And where's my lunch?!
There's more important things to worry about!
There is?
This girl has what it takes to become a Precure!
Right!
What's with these guys, Tsubomi?!
Th-They're the fairies that protect the Great Heart Tree...
I'm Coffret!
And I'm Chypre!
Oh, so they're fairies.
So you understand now?
You said "the Great Heart Tree" just now, right?
Now that you mention it, that was in my dreams yesterday too.
Erika!
The dream you had while you were unconscious...
was real!
Huh?
And the Cure Blossom who defeated the monster...
is actually me!
Seriously?!
Seriously!
I can't believe that another
potential Precure was so close by!
Erika, become my partner Precure!
Become a Precure?
That costume was really cute...
Wasn't it?!
You'll become the second Precure!
It's the student council president!
The student council president?
Kurumi, I've yet to receive the list of Fashion Club members.
I'm sorry, President! I'll be sure to get it to you this week!
Until I receive your list, we cannot produce our budget, so I urge you to make haste.
Y-Yes!
The student council president... is really amazing.
I guess.
He's the grandson of the school's board chairman, you know?
More importantly, we want you to become a Precure, Erika!
Precures sure are neat...
But...
Sorry, now's really not the time!
Tsubomi, come give me a hand!
Huh?
Come on, quickly!
Hey, hold on! Hold on, Erika!
What do we do?
We should consult with Cure Flower!
What was that?
You say a new Precure has appeared?
I slipped up because her sudden
appearance caught me off-guard.
If she manages to collect the Heart Seeds, she could become quite a nuisance...
Don't worry.
Cure Blossom is but one obstacle.
I should be able to defeat her quite easily by myself.
I'll be off, then.
We need you!
My fellow first-years,
I apologize for interrupting you during your
lunchtime, but please listen to what we have to say!
Those of you who haven't joined a club yet, come join the Fashion Club!
What the heck, you're just recruiting for a club?
If you join the Fashion Club, you'll be able to brush up on your fashion sense,
and make your own trendy clothes!
We aren't interested in fashion. Right?
Hey, Tsubomi, try to pitch in a little!
I have to say something too?
The Fashion Club is counting on you...
You have to speak louder than that!
We beg you!
In that case, we'll just have to recruit directly!
R-Right!
If you please!
Don't wanna.
I've already joined the tennis team...
If you please!
Not interested.
Leave me alone!
Looks like this class is no good...
Erika, let's move on to the next class.
Over here!
Hey there! Wanna join the Fashion Club?
I'm not joining such a pansy club.
What did you say?!
You listen to me...
Erika, come on, let's go to the next class...
In the end, we couldn't even get a single person to join...
We'll just have to try something different tomorrow!
We'll bring in some of our shop's cool clothes and use those to—
How many times do I have to tell you?!
No means no!
Isn't that the girl from...
I told you, girls aren't allowed on the soccer team!
I'm begging you, please!
You're interrupting our practice.
If you'll excuse me.
Quit worrying about the soccer team and come join the Fashion Club!
Don't talk to me about the soccer team.
And didn't I tell you I don't want to join something like the Fashion Club?
Whaddya mean, "something like"?!
Why can't girls join...
They don't have any idea how much I love soccer!
Hm?
The Flower of her Heart is wilting.
To the right, the right!
Over here!
This way!
Pass!
In grade school, we played soccer
without caring about boys and girls...
Damn it!
Who're you?!
I'll be taking the Flower of your Heart!
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
Th-That's...
It's Sasorina!
The Flower of her Heart is in danger!
We have to let Tsubomi know!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Lure out the fairies and that Precure!
Ball! Baaall!
Bababababall!
Erika, I promise I'll help with
recruiting tomorrow as well...
so please become a Precure!
Those two are completely unrelated!
What the heck is that giant soccer ball?!
It's Sasorina's doing!
Huh?
It's bad news!
Sayaka's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen !
This girl's...
For her to steal the Flower of the Heart from Sayaka...
Tsubomi, transform into a Precure!
Okay!
I'll save her!
Chypre, the Seed of the Precure!
All right!
Go forth, Seed of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
Wow! Super cute! It's so adorable!
Super cool!
Desertrian, take your anger out on these kids!
You're saying that just because I'm a girl, I can't join the soccer team?!
That's cruel! So cruel! So cruel!
It's not like it's our fault...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Why do you get to have all the fun playing soccer?!
Come on, everyone! Run!
Desertrian, get her!
Baaaaaall!
I've loved soccer since I was a child!
I thought now that I was in junior high I'd get to keep playing as much as I liked!
You can play soccer on your own, can't you?
You really do worry about such petty things.
It's not petty!
Hm?
You're just playing with Sayaka's pure heart...
Her love of soccer!
And I've had it up to here with this!
Huh? What's with you? Just disappear already!
Desertrian!
Ballll!
Tsubomi!
You should have a taste of my suffering!
The Flower of her Heart will wilt soon!
Unless we recover the Flower of her Heart, we won't be able to return this girl to normal!
Tsubomi became a Precure to help everyone, right?
That's right!
In order to protect the Flowers of everyone's Hearts, Blossom is fighting so hard!
I'll become a Precure!
You will?!
I'm totally serious!
I want to protect everyone's hearts too!
What's this?!
The Heart Perfume is resonating with Erika's heart!
So Erika really does have what it takes to become a Precure!
Desertrian, crush her!
I won't let that happen!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Kurumi Erika!
The second Precure!
Go forth, Seed of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A second one?!
How did you transform into a
Precure without being told how?!
I saw it in my dream yesterday!
As for the name... After you asked me to become one this morning, I spent the whole time thinking about it!
Leave this to me! Just rest!
Cure Marine!
Yup!
All right then, I'll be your opponent!
Come get some!
Why are you spacing out, Desertrian?!
Get her, quickly!
Baaall!
The same trick won't work on me!
The top of your head is one big weak spot!
Ball!
Marine Shoot!
Cure Marine, you have to take back the Flower of her Heart!
I already know that!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
We did it!
Curse you!
This time, you'll be facing me!
Sasorina, if you're going to continue your evil deeds...
then we will be your opponents!
Damn you, Precures!
I'll let you off for today!
We did it, Cure Marine!
Yay!
Cure Marine, hurry and return this girl to normal!
To normal!
Right!
The Fashion Club girls...
What have I...
It seems you overworked yourself
while practicing and collapsed here.
Oh...
Here.
Oh, thanks.
What's wrong?
I had this dream.
A weird dream where I turned a
soccer ball monster and ran wild...
I've had the wrong idea.
I thought that just because I was a girl, I couldn't play soccer in junior high.
I got caught up in my thoughts and got depressed.
You love soccer, though, don't you?
Yes! I love it!
That's why I'm going to start a girls' soccer team!
That sounds great!
All right, then! I need to follow your example and start recruiting!
Bye!
Go for it, okay?
Fight hard!
Thank goodness!
In the language of flowers, a poinsettia means "My heart is aflame!"
I'm sure Sayaka will become a great female soccer player!
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born!
Oh, that's right!
I forgot about this...
Here. The doll you gave me yesterday.
You fixed it for me?!
It's so cute! Thank you, Erika!
Oh, it's Mako!
Could this doll possibly be yours?
Yeah!
I'm terribly sorry! She lost it at the park yesterday, you see.
Is that so?
You see, your dolly here got hurt, so this nice girl fixed it for you!
Sorry for the bother. Thank you very much.
Come on, thank the nice girl.
Miss...
Thank you!
You're quite welcome!
Bye bye, miss!
Bye bye!
It sure feels nice to do a good deed!
It sure does!
Erika, let's both do our best as Precures from now on!
Let's do our best at recruiting too!
Right!
Man, I'm starving.
We didn't get a chance to eat our lunch, after all!
I know a really delicious crepe place.
Let's go eat there, Tsubomi!
All right, Erika!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
People grow through continuous
meetings and farewells, Blossom!
Does that mean that I'm so useless and pitiful that I don't have the right to team up with you, Marine?!
That's not so! It is the light that shines within your heart!
People can't survive alone! That's why we combine our strength!
Now, put your heart into the Flower Tact and shout...
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Precure Partnership
is Already Dissolved?
We'll catch everyone's hearts!