Are you awake?
Let me out.
And then?
I'll meet master.
He betrayed the organization and escaped.
He abandoned you.
The mission is still ongoing.
I'll meet up with master.
If that's impossible, I'll help him escape.
If I create a commotion, I can cut off the pursuers of the organization.
Stop.
I can't.
If you want to continue your mission, stay with me.
Scythe is on run, but he's being protected by Phantom even now.
The fear of Phantom is always with him.
That's why the organization can't act carelessly.
If you got caught now, he'd be at a disadvantage, too.
You've changed, Zwei.
Have I?
Yes. It's like you're different than you were yesterday.
Yes... You're no longer Zwei.
You're Azuma Reiji.
You were listening?
You have a place to return to.
You still have your real self.
But I... I have nothing.
I'm Ein.
All I have is a number.
The only place I can return to is to my master.
That's not true!
I don't have anything else...
Except the name "Ein" he gave me.
Ein.
That's me.
I'm no one... A phantom...
You're wrong.
Thanks.
Thanks for your business.
You should eat something.
Didn't you think that I'd be gone?
You're reckless, but not stupid.
The robbed vehicle was found.
It was empty, though.
So they completely escaped from our hands.
Scythe is your dog.
You ought to take care of this.
Understood.
You know this song?
Sorry. Is it too loud?
What is it called?
Uh... I forgot.
I don't remember the title, but I used to hear it quite often in the city.
Does everyone in Japan listen to such songs?
People have different tastes in music.
Los Angeles is the same as Japan.
Tell me more about Japan.
You remembered, didn't you?
The time you spent as Azuma Reiji.
Yeah.
It's me.
We got the goods as planned.
Have a safe flight.
What are you saying?
From the escape route to the logistics...
Everything is done by you.
I'll call you again once things calm down.
May our good relationship continue.
We can't trust that woman.
If we let our guard down, she'll even betray the Godoh clan.
Who cares.
We're using her, too.
Right?
It's too risky.
Don't freak out now, Shiga.
Show some guts.
I'm going to rise up high.
Azuma Reiji...
You should go back.
Go back?
Yes.
Where are you telling me to go back to?
You know what I've been doing for the last six months.
I can't go back at this point.
But you have a past.
You do exist in this world as Azuma Reiji.
The same goes for you, too.
You are right here...
You have something I don't.
You can prove your identity.
Is it that important to have a passport?
Yes, that's proof that you are indeed you.
Something I don't have.
What are you doing, Reiji?!
Do you realize what you have just done?
That's your-
Just a scrap of paper.
The thing that makes me myself are my memories of the past.
And you have that too.
Didn't you tell me about your dream before?
Your memories about those colors.
The strongly blowing wind and the brightness.
Aren't they memories of your hometown?
I just vaguely remember that.
There's no proof that it's my hometown.
But it's your memory.
You have a past.
You have a real name. Not a number like "Ein."
Why are you so concerned about me?
You won't benefit from this in any way.
I don't want to let you die.
I don't want to leave you to your death.
This isn't for anyone.
I'm doing this on my own will.
Sticking to this is the proof that I'm myself.
I don't need a paper or a stamp to prove that.
Your drivers license please.
Where are you from?
I'm coming from Los Angeles.
I'm visiting my friend.
Wallace Yang, 20.
You look younger.
People often tell me that.
Who's she?
She's my sister.
She looks kind of pale.
Well, yeah. We've been driving for quite some time now.
She's carsick.
Okay, you can go.
You've gotten better.
You mean my acting?
What are you saying? You taught me all that.
What are you planning to do now?
We'll move around and make you rest a little.
When your wound has healed, we'll go somewhere far away.
Somewhere far away?
Where exactly?
As far as we can.
That's absurd...
I told you. I decided that on my own.
I'll buy us something to eat.
Ein. Ein!
I haven't felt fear until yesterday...
My finger... doesn't move.
Reiji, shoot me.
Bring me to peace.
You're so selfish!
What happened?
Weren't you much stronger than me?
That's not true.
I...
Did it for master.
Just for him...
Even if I made the organization my enemy,
as long as I had master's orders...
Yet...
Why am I living now?
Being hunted by the organization... I'm just on the run.
I can't even pull the trigger.
If I had died there yesterday,
I could have at least died as Ein.
No way...
Were we fighting all the time to die?
You're wrong.
We've been fighting to survive.
I don't want you to die because of something this silly.
I want you to live.
That's all I want.
I'm being hunted by Inferno.
If the pursuers come here,
whom would you point your gun at?
Me or the organization?
I've already decided. I'll shoot at the organization.
I'll pull the trigger with my own will.
Why?
Why are you going this far to live?
Do you expect me to lead that life, too?
You don't want that?
I'm nobody now.
I don't have anything.
Not a mission, nor a reason to live.
Ein...
I'll stop calling you Ein.
That's just a number.
It isn't a name.
You need a new name.
A name?
Not Phantom nor a number.
A name for you to live as yourself.
Elen. Your name is Elen.
From now on I'll call you Elen.
Why Elen?
Do you need a reason?
I've decided that.
A name to live as yourself. Not as a puppet or an assassin.
Elen.
Elen... It sounds kind of strange.
Really?
Let's look for your lost past, Elen.
If you find your real name,
you can find enough reasons to live.
You'll think about living even if you have to hurt someone.
It might be hard for you at this point.
But please move on with me.
What if your favorite puppy sides with Scythe?
Kill him.
I'll get a new car and some cash.
I'll be back in an hour.
How's your wound?
It's fine as long as I don't move too much.
Be careful, Elen.
I will, Reiji.
Elen.
The name Reiji gave me.
With this name, I will...
That isn't like you, Ein.
Overcome your pain with your will.
Master.
This is the end, Zwei.
Was your childish honeymoon fun?
Lizzie.
Seems like you were dancing in Scythe's palm, huh?
I have nothing to do with him.
I wonder about that.
I'll listen to your story.
I just got a report...
...that my subordinate, who was following Phantom, was killed.
She went back to Scythe.
No way.
Elen!
How about you start talking already?!
Where did Scythe go?
I don't know. We...
Seems like he really doesn't know anything.
Leave the rest to me.
You may go now.
You are indeed stubborn.
The mic is off.
You can talk now.
Rescuing Ein and running away together...
Is that what you decided?
Idiot. You assisted the traitor.
You're a suspect now.
You cannot return to Japan anymore.
But you still have an ideal choice left.
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back.
What is that?
You know how to use this, don't you?
I'll kill Scythe.
Elen, one day I'll make you smile.
I'll get your usual smile back.