Why're you asking about The Dollars?
You're not thinking of joining The Dollars, are you?
Whaaaat's thaaaat?!
Why is my head on someone else's body anyway?!
Maybe it found a newly dead corpse.
I can't wait!
What do you think will happen to us if the police get wind of this?
I don't care whether she dies or not. Depending
on the circumstances, dispose of her on the spot.
I guess my budget's pretty tight this month after all.
Now all I need is a kitchen sponge and...
Thank you very much.
The black bike!
It should be right around this corner!
Owowowow...
Um...I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
You're...
Help me!
Please!
The black bike!
Just what is that!? It's totally cool!
Can we take a picture?
Here we go!
This is awesome!
This picture's insane!
So the beautiful girl you bumped into on the
corner was being chased by some bad guy on a bike...
...she's lost her memory...
...and she already fell asleep due to exhaustion by the time I got here.
So you expect me to believe this dream you had, which in many ways isn't very dreamy.
It's true, so I can't change it.
It'd be better if this made you late for school in the morning.
And it'd be marvelous if she were a transfer student.
Also, if she were a queen and your childhood friend, it'd be perfect.
Ah, did you notice my pun on "better" and "clichéd?"
I think it makes the joke even worse when you have to point it out.
I don't know what to do, since not only has she
lost her memory, but I can't even go to the police.
All we can do is see how things develop.
For now, we'll wait until tomorrow,
and then ask her all about her situation.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks for coming this late.
The black biker might remember my face.
The black biker of urban legend...
What am I doing by making an enemy of her?
I hated normal things.
Good morning.
I wanted to live a different life from other people.
Those feelings may have led me to get involved with this girl.
There's only one thing Kida doesn't know.
It's about that wound on her neck.
It looks like her head was chopped off
with a saw and then forcefully reattached.
This is an announcement from the school store:
Our stock of jumbo melon bread has sold out for the day.
Wow, Mikado!
How's the sleeping beauty at your apartment doing?
Kida?! Shh! Shh!
What's this about a beautiful girl?
I like hearing about that kind of thing.
Actually, when Mikado turned a corner, he bumped into this girl with amnesia who was being chased by an evil person...
And so, now he's living with a cute girl!
C'mon, now. That's just a dream Kirigamine has.
Uhh, umm, err, it's Ryugamine.
Anyone want to sell me their extra meal tickets?
No one will believe it, so it's okay.
Anyway, what's up with the girl?
She was still asleep when I left this morning.
Getting her beauty sleep, I bet.
Alright, let's get down to business.
What business?
This is what I've been doing during lunch break and
it's the reason why I ate my lunch during fourth period.
"Who's in The Dollars?"
This is a pretty popular fad amongst our classmates, you know.
Everything about The Dollars is shrouded in mystery.
So, if someone in school says, "Hey, doesn't
that dude look kinda like he'd be in The Dollars?"
I get them to vote for that person.
Wow, it looks like there's a real consensus.
That's because one person can vote for multiple people.
Huh? Takiguchi from class 1-D only has one vote.
So you noticed?
And who voted for him? None other than me, Kida Masaomi.
My class has P.E. with his, and I'm sure he has to be in The Dollars.
Why do you say that?
Intuition.
On that note, I'm going to see if I'm right.
Wait!
Excuse me!
Is Takiguchi Ryo here?
No, he's not.
He in the cafeteria?
I dunno. Probably on the roof.
He goes up there a lot during lunch.
Ryo must take his smoke breaks up there.
Don't you think you should leave him alone?
There might be a lot of scary people up there.
That was a joke.
Smoking on the roof during lunch only happens in old, clichéd manga.
But I doubt he'd tell you the truth if you just
go up to him and ask, "Are you in The Dollars?"
Just leave it to me.
I have an idea.
Ummm...
Oh?
He...He's smoking...
Hey, Takiguchi!
Yo.
Hey.
Oh?
Wow, you write songs?
Huh? Oh, yeah...
What's up?
You need to talk to me?
There's something I want to ask.
Shoot.
Are you in The Dollars?
Kida, what're you...?
Yeah, I am.
I knew it.
I just knew you had to be.
See? My intuition is 100% perfect.
He's my childhood friend.
Uhh, err, umm, I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
So you're that famous guy.
Huh? Famous guy?
Your name.
Want some?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Um, Takiguchi...
Why did you join The Dollars?
I don't really know how to answer that question.
I guess it was six months ago.
I got an invite from someone I didn't know.
It said, "The Dollars don't have any rules or regulations."
At first I thought there's no way a group like that
could exist, but then I figured it'd be interesting if it did.
I don't like either giving or taking orders.
So, what kind of group is it?
If I had to say, I guess they're "clearly colorless."
"Clearly colorless?"
Yeah, they don't try to get as many members to wear the same colors as
possible and have power struggles like The Yellow Scarves or The Blue Squares.
Who're The Blue Squares?
They're a color gang that was around when I was in middle school.
I don't know much about them, but apparently
they caused some incident and broke up.
Kida?
So, you like The Dollars, Takiguchi?
Yeah.
Do you meet with the other members?
We only know each other's handles, so...
But I have met some.
Like at my part-time job or around town.
They've all been coincidental, though.
Somehow, you just know that they're members.
What kind of people are they?
They are who they are, so you'll have to ask them, like you did me.
I bet most of them would answer you.
Aw, crap.
See you!
Ever since I found out that Takiguchi was a
real Dollar, I decided I wouldn't tell anybody.
I figured that Takiguchi wouldn't want people making a fuss over it.
Okay, everyone, let's begin.
I assumed that only the people who asked needed to know.
Stand.
Bow.
That's all for our class representatives meeting.
I wonder if Kida's still doing stuff for the disciplinary committee?
He'll probably be done soon.
Wait!
Harima Mika, the girl stalking Yagiri Seiji, has been
missing ever since the day before the entrance ceremony.
Did you learn anything regarding Harima's whereabouts after that?
No, nothing.
Ryugamine!
Kida says to go home without him!
Eh? What's keeping him?
Apparently he's in the middle of a heated
debate with the disciplinary committee.
See you.
Umm...
Shall we go?
Okay.
I wonder what Kida's debate is about...
Uh, maybe it's about the dress code or hairstyles.
Mikado!
I'm going to ask you all about that beautiful girl!
Introduce me to her sometime!
Snap!
Later!
Th-That beautiful girl he's talking about is a
French person we met at Russia Sushi, and...
H-H-Her nose is pierced!
And so Kida must be debating nose piercings!
I actually knew about you a long time ago, Ryugamine.
Huh?
When I passed in my matriculation forms,
there was a checklist on the receptionist's desk.
I thought your name was cool, and I
noticed someone had checked it off already.
Now I get to be a class representative with you...
Wait!
Doesn't this sound a lot like what happened
between Harima Mika and Yagiri Seiji?!
I don't want a stalker!
Wait, maybe it's okay since she's so cute.
No, wait, it's totally not!
If things go bad...
Sh-Sh-She'll stab me!
Fire!
I-I-I might be killed!
Wait, maybe she'd take my parents hostage!
But if she has a good personality,
then it might not matter that she's a...
Wait, stalkers don't have good personalities!
That was a joke.
Eh?
It'd just cause trouble for you if someone like me were following you around.
Um, that's not...
Don't worry.
I'm not a stalker.
Uh, umm, err, well...
I'm sorry.
No, I'm the one who was teasing you.
Please, don't apologize.
Uh!
Um!
Well...
I-I hope we work well together!
I hope so, too.
Huh?
That's him, Takeshi! That's him!
Who does she mean by "him?"
It's not me, is it?
I mean you! It's you!
Why are you ignoring us?!
Umm...who might you be?
I had to buy a new cell phone, thanks to your friend!
Uhh...I don't really understand what you're saying...
So, you're friends with the guy who broke my girlfriend's cell?
Well, I wouldn't really call him my friend...
Then what is he? Your parent?! A cosigner?! Huh?!
I think your assumptions are a tad biased...
Huh?!
Are you trying to lecture me!?
You want me to teach you how to act towards your elders—
Huh?!
How commendable of me to say, "My hobby isn't punching girls."
I'd like you to be my girlfriend, but I'm sorry.
You're not my type.
Go home!
You're horrible!
See you again!
Well now, Ryugamine Mikado, I've been hiding
behind the school gate because I wanted to see you.
I have some business with you.
By the way...
Why's the black biker here?
She's searching for the girl!
I forgot!
S-Sorry, but I'm in a hurry!
See you later, Sonohara.
This is too surreal.
Anyway, these people will definitely follow me back to my apartment.
So then...
Help me!
Uh, umm...
Well...
If you want to talk with me, let's do it here.
I'll talk with you after the black biker's done.
Hello?
Thanks for your continued patronage.
Th-There's something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
She'll listen to me?
Um...just who are you?
I'm looking for the daughter of one of my relatives.
I found her yesterday, but she ran away for some reason.
She...She's horrible at lying.
S-Sorry, but I don't believe you.
How much do you know about me?
You're somewhat of an urban legend...
You ride a bike with no headlights that doesn't make any noise...
And...
There are rumors you have no head.
Do you believe that?
Um, could you let me see inside your helmet?
I never thought I'd be able to ask that.
Promise you won't scream?
However, I felt like I'd been waiting a long time...
For this moment.
I still don't know how to describe the way I felt at that time.
I just kept repeating, "Ah, I knew it. I knew it," in my heart.
Th-Th-Thank you very much.
After that, the legendary black biker told
me the real reason she was chasing that girl.
She was a dullahan named Celty...
She came to Japan in search of her stolen head...
And the girl with stitches on her neck has a face that looks exactly like hers.
Normally, every part of that story would be unbelievable.
But, mysteriously enough, I believed every single word of it.
Are you her friend?
No, I just met her yesterday.
I asked her a bunch of different things, but...
It seems she lost her memory.
Celty?
Would you let me see her?
It's probably because you suddenly
started chasing her, but she's afraid of you.
I need to see her, no matter what!
Could you do something to help clear up this misunderstanding?
I understand.
Fruit milk in the afternoon is the best.
I think this development's a sign that Biribiri's going to be the heroine!
No way! I bet the heroine's a princess goddess!
Hey!
What're you doing?!
Those bastards...shot a pebble...
Eh?
They shot a pebble into my car!
Calm down, Togusa!
I'll never forgive them!
The light's red!
It's red! It's red!
Please wait here a bit.
I'll explain everything to her.
I don't want her to think I betrayed her if she sees you first, Celty.
I understand.
He's a pretty cautious kid.
Huh?
That's the first time I've ever heard your name.
I didn't know you were a foreigner.
You liar.
I'm not going to let it slide the next time you throw a rock at my horse.
Eh? So that's a horse?
Despite the situation, isn't he a bit slow?
Why's there a cleaning crew at this run-down apartment?
It couldn't be...!
That's why we want to know where that girl you were with went.
This hair I found on your futon is from a girl, isn't it?
I-I really don't know!
P-Please...Please have mercy on—
You've seen our faces.
We don't mind killing you right here.
Hey, someone's coming!
I-I-I'm saved...
You don't have to go after them.
I know where they're going.
I remember the van.
They're probably from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
Yagiri...Pharmaceuticals?
Yep.
They're a puppet company that hasn't been doing well lately, so they're on the verge of being absorbed by a foreign firm.
A girl who lost her head,
A dullahan,
Gone missing,
Harima Mika,
Yagiri Seiji,
Human trafficking,
And The Dollars.
What's he planning on starting?
I was tired of normal things.
Honestly, I half-assumed he was.
Please.
Even if it's only for a short while, please cooperate.
I wanted to live a different life from other people.
This evening, the ball is in my court.
That's why...
Jackpot!
I...
I was tired of normal things.
I wanted to live a life different from other people.
I can't believe that simple wish changed the destinies of so many people.
Next Time: Tempestuous Change.