It reminds me of Hope Kingdom!
How bien it is to hear this song again!
Kanata...
Brother...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
I'm glad your memories have returned, Kanata.
But if you still need help,
you're free to stay here as long as you like.
But I...
Come now, don't be shy.
Also,
think of that violin as a gift from me.
Please, take it.
Thank you very much.
Brother!
Towa...
Oh, wherever should I begin...
What's gotten into her?
She's shy.
They haven't spoken to each other since childhood.
I've been so worried...
but it looks like you're back to normal as well.
Yes...
You were always on my mind, Towa.
Brother!
Towa's Determination!
The Shining Rainbow of Hope!
Look at all I've learned in school!
Well done.
This is a landscape I drew in one class.
These are the ballet shoes I use in another!
And I made this in another—
It just keeps coming!
You've worked hard to fit into this world.
Oh, I've done nothing so grand!
Towie's acting all coy!
Oh, hush, girls!
Towa, have you been practicing violin?
Yes, of course!
What's that?
It's the violin she got from you!
It is?
The violin transformed to protect Towa.
I see.
Thank you, Haruka.
Your dream of playing together will finally come true!
Dream...
You and I...
The Royal Key!
Wh-What now?
A red light?
Royal... Majesty...
Huh? What was...
This light...
The Forest of Despair?
Where are we?!
We're most likely...
in Hope Kingdom.
Good heavens!
It's like night and day from when we first came here!
The Royal Key must have called us
to warn us of the peril this land is in.
Curse Dyspear for abusing my absence...
The rainbow...
The rainbow's gone!
Is this really home?
Hey, what's that castle?
Could it be?
It's the Gate of Despair!
Then, we really are in Hope Kingdom?
Beyond that door lies le stolen dreams of Hope Kingdom's people!
Both Mother's and Father's dreams must be inside...
No...
This isn't Hope Kingdom!
Wait!
Kuroro!
A frown like that will worry our citizens.
Mother! Father!
Listen well, Towa.
Just like the rainbow that watches over us,
your duty is to greet the people with a smile that grants hopes and dreams.
For you are Hope Kingdom's princess.
Hope Kingdom's princess...
When we smile, the people smile.
When we shed tears, the people shed their own.
Be sure to take this to heart.
Yes...
Just be who you naturally are.
Naturally?
That's for the best.
Now, our people await.
Citizens, I thank you for gathering in honor of my daughter Towa's birthday!
Now, Towa.
Thank you all for taking the time to visit me.
Princess Towa!
Mother... Father...
Kuroro!
Where'd you go?
Are these vines all made of despair?
Yes...
Our countrymen's dreams were twisted into despair...
Bro...
Tout le monde,
make le castle shine!
Good morning, Perf.
The rainbow's beautiful today!
When the rainbow's shining, you know it'll be a good day!
And the rainbow's always shining!
Indeed.
When Princess Towa went missing,
the country was pulled deep into despair.
We all tried to stay positive,
but in the end...
it's come to this.
Kuroro, over here!
They say happiness lies at the end of the rainbow!
Let's go!
Wait for me!
Guys!
You'll do nicely.
I'm takin' that body, 'kay?
My apologies.
They were almost defeated, and yet...
Prince Kanata... to think that he would show himself again.
I thought he had disappeared into the darkness...
Dyspear, you shall not go unpunished.
Those blasted siblings have returned once more.
Siblings? Twilight, too?
Very well.
Let us wipe them out once and for all.
Go forth, my fragment.
What's that?
Viiiil!
Dystroyvil.
It's been some time, Prince.
Same to you, Twilight.
That voice...
It's Dyspear!
Haruka!
Girls!
The heck is that?!
Prepare to fight!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
You'll find yourselves trapped behind the Gate of Despair soon enough.
Dyspear! You shall pay!
Scarlet!
Dystroyvil!
Dystroy...
Behind you!
Dystroy!
Are you okay, Towa?!
Scarlet!
We have to find Kuroro quick!
He's in danger!
Dystroy!
Vil!
It's no use.
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dystroyvil!
Girls!
You're too late.
This land is already steeped in despair.
I won't let you!
Towa...
Return them!
Return my mother and father! My people!
My land that I loved so dearly!
This instant!
Such futile resistance!
Return them...
I wanna go home...
to the Hope Kingdom I knew...
Kuroro...
I wanna go home...
Dystroyvil!
Kuroro!
Towa, I share your pain.
Brother!
But you must remember...
the words they left you with!
When we smile, the people smile.
When we shed tears,
the people shed their own.
A frown like that will worry our citizens.
Mother... Father...
Kuroro...
Princess Towa...
Worry not.
I assure you that I shall reclaim Hope Kingdom.
Now please...
cry no more.
Towa...
Princess Towa!
This land is already ruined.
Hardly!
For I still stand upon its soil!
I am Cure Scarlet,
Princess Hope Delight Towa,
and Hope Kingdom royalty!
Silence!
Dystroyvil!
Girls!
We feel the same way!
We want to see the land you grew up with!
Let's take back Hope Kingdom together!
Girls...
We shall!
Sun!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Prominence!
Dystroy!
Is that its core?
Now's your chance!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Lady Dyspear...
Curse those Precures...
It's here!
Scarlet?
Scarlet...
I vow...
that when I play this song next,
it shall be to a restored Hope Kingdom.
I shall fulfill my duty as princess of this land and reclaim everyone's dreams!
Princess Towa's Keys!
Let your fires bloom,
O flames of hope!
The castle has been reborn!
Princess Towa's dream must have blown life into le old castle once more!
The rainbow!
At least this area is back to normal.
Indeed. The Castle of Flames...
is our first step toward reclaiming Hope Kingdom.
It'll be back to its former beauty!
How pretty...
It's Dreamy Shore!
It seems this is le gate connecting le two worlds.
Mother, Father, I promise to take back...
our beautiful Hope Kingdom.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Yui's drawings are so splendid!
Indeed.
If you'd like, Yui, why not enter a contest?
A wonderful idea!
I'm certain you'd win.
Ms. First Place, what's your secret to drawing so well?
Huh? Yui seems kinda blue...
Go! Princess Precure:
Yui's Dream!
The Heart is in the Canvas!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!