Please!
Wait!
Stop right there!
No! Absolutely not!
Hey, you haven't heard anything.
You're asking her to show up in your next game as backup, right?
How could you tell?
One look at that arm gives it away.
You're the softball team captain, Chiba, right?
You've got your hands full with your Precure and student council work.
You can't just help everyone who comes along.
But they're in big trouble.
We sure are!
Our next game will put us out of the preliminaries!
Please!
I understand. Leave it to me.
Huh?!
Thank you so much!
Let's get you ready right away!
Hold it, Mana!
You just need to learn the signals...
They're easy!
Oh, forget it!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Awaken!
The Precure's Newest Power!!
That was fast!
It was more than fast.
Her pitch had weight to it!
Why didn't we ever scout her?
We tried!
But you see...
What's wrong?
The lace on my cleats snapped.
I have some spare shoelace on me, so I'll lend you some!
Thanks, President!
She said she liked helping people more than clubs.
I see.
Kyouda!
Pick your jaw up off the ground!
Come practice with us!
Sure!
Maybe the President will join our team?
She's nice, but still cool...
Yeah!
We'd be unstoppable with her pitching!
Well, you're our future ace,
so get a few pointers!
Hey, I'm not that...
I'm sorry! Can you throw it?
Thank you very much!
I'm home!
Welcome.
What? Why?
Are you leaving me out?
You were busy with your team, right?
Oh, yeah...
I heard the news.
You were scouted by a softball team, then?
Yeah, they said they needed me.
The Happy Prince caves as quickly as ever.
When is your game?
Next Sunday.
It'll be at our school's field.
I'll gladly come to cheer!
For a team of newbies that puts the whole game on a helper's shoulders, sure.
Are you angry?
Why would I be?
I only have to fill in for you when picking up litter off campus,
setting up the wind instrument club's next recital,
and looking over club advertisements,
and I don't get angry at that.
You're so kind, Miss Rikka!
I love you!
Makopi's angry, too!
We've gotten nowhere in the search for her queen!
Huh?
I wouldn't say I'm angry, but...
But?
I think it's strange.
People only ask you to help out,
yet you take their requests so seriously.
It's my number one rule!
Besides, I'm happy to help others!
Is helping others really so much fun?
Cure Heart?
Yeah.
Didn't you sing for others back in Trump Kingdom?
You found joy in it, didn't you?
I'm not sure.
Then why not go cheer her on?
It might motivate you.
It might.
Cure Heart...
I swear I'll return the favor!
Don't blow a blood vessel, pops.
They say to let sleeping dogs lie.
So just let him lie.
That'll do it!
President, what are you doing?
All the uniforms were dirty, so I did some laundry!
First years like us are supposed to do the chores!
You're our backup!
So spend your time practicing!
Getting better on my own won't help the team.
If you want to be regulars,
you've got to push each other and sharpen your skills together!
That passion is what makes a team strong!
Being first years...
is no excuse to hold back!
Uh, right!
If you get it, then get changed!
We're gonna jog!
Right!
They're getting into it.
Guess it's because of our helper.
I can't wait for tomorrow's game!
Yeah.
President!
Good work today!
Same to you!
Good luck with tomorrow's game!
Sure!
You're as popular as ever.
Mister!
And Ai too!
You're a widdle sight for sore eyes!
I ran out of powdered milk, so I'm going to buy some.
Speaking of sights, look at you.
What's with the sweats?
It's a long story...
Your softball team's in a tournament?
Yeah, and I'm their pitcher.
I see.
Maybe Ai and I should come to cheer.
Totally!
Oh yeah!
Here's a charm to get Lady Luck on your side.
Huh? You don't have to!
Oh, don't be shy.
Oh!
Hey now...
Oh dear.
If you like it so much, I'll give it to you.
Good for you, Ai.
Apologies for interrupting your heartwarming chat,
Aida Mana.
Or rather, Cure Heart.
It's you!
Mana, be careful!
I know that,
but I can't transform here!
Let's settle this.
I refuse!
I don't have any reason to fight you!
You babble such nonsense after seeing the ruins of Trump Kingdom first-hand?
Yeah, I saw it!
But beating you here won't bring that kingdom back!
You speak as though you've already won!
Unacceptable!
Come now, transform into a Precure.
Crushing you in your normal state
will bring no satisfaction.
Look out!
Mister!
What a joke.
It's not...
a joke!
He wanted to save someone's life!
He wanted to help someone!
Can't you understand that?
Silence!
Ai!
If you want your baby back,
come to the Yotsuba Terminal at 8 AM tomorrow.
Alone, of course.
If you bring your allies...
You can't!
Ai...
Aiiiiiii!
What happened?
Why hasn't it started?
Good morning.
Alice...
Oh?
The game hasn't begun?
Well, you see...
She's late!
What's the President doing?
I called her home, but she apparently already left.
Geez!
This is not the time for sightseeing!
Oogai Hospital
Me, of all people...
This is a trap, my sweet heart.
You can't go!
You came alone, as promised.
How bold of you.
Where's Ai?
Ai!
And, as promised, I'll return her.
But only if you beat me.
Let's go, Charles!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Oh you extremely selfish old man,
I, Cure Heart,
will take Ai back once more!
Excellent.
Well?
Can you call Charles?
We're trying to...
But there's no response.
Please, wait just a little longer!
I know how you feel,
but if you can't gather your team,
you'll be disqualified automatically.
B-But...
We can't do it without the Pres!
We can't win!
I can see why they're panicking.
They've lost the one person they relied on the most.
Captain!
Let me pitch!
Kyouda?
The President taught us something.
As long as we work together, we can overcome any obstacle!
I'm sure the President has her reasons for not coming.
So let us fight in her place!
I see.
Let's give 'em all we've got!
Thank you very much!
Play ball!
Madam.
Strike!
What's wrong?
Getting tired?
I knew it was a trap!
You coward!
That's the highest praise a Selfish can receive.
Look out!
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
What?!
Why are you here?
Sebastian searched for you.
Even an MVP can't win on her own!
We're a team after all, so have a little faith!
You girls...
The softball team's doing their best in your stead,
so let's do our best, too!
Everyone's doing what they can...
Yeah!
Let's go!
All right!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
I have more tricks up my sleeve.
That's...
A Dark Psyche!
Grant me your darkness!
Did he just do that?
What's happening to him?
I consumed concentrated selfishness to power myself up!
I am now Bel Beast!
Wow...
That's a...
How shall I put it?
It's complicated...
Don't think I'm weak, else I'll knock ya into next week!
Snapshot.
Too bright!
Cure Sword!
Silent Mode Vibration!
You've got mail!
He's strong!
But we can't lose.
Not until we take Ai back!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
She did it!
I told you.
Don't think I'm weak.
What are you thinking?
Did you forget?
I said to come alone.
It's punishment for breaking your promise.
Ai has nothing to do with this!
Stop it!
Hasta la vista, baby.
Kyupirappa!
Wh-What?!
That light!
A Lovies?
It's a new power!
Love Heart Arrow!
This is...
Use the Lovies!
Curse you!
Take this!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
What?!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Now's your chance, Cure Heart!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Huh?
What was I...
Ai!
Thank goodness!
Yeah!
So that brat...
can make miracles, huh?
Curses, I'll remember this!
Oh Ai, thank goodness!
Ai!
How is it?
Top of the ninth.
Touei
Oogai
We're up by one run!
They have two outs, but the bases are loaded!
Ball!
Another ball will tie it up,
and a hit will turn the game around!
You can do it, Kyouda!
I know you've got it in you!
Strike!
Batter out!
Game set!
We did it!
We won!
Congrats!
I know a simple apology won't cut it,
but I'm really sorry!
Geez, we never thought for a moment you wouldn't show up.
Sorry.
But this week made me realize something.
You can't rely solely on others.
But if we all believe in ourselves and work together,
we can overcome any challenge!
That's what you taught me!
Thank you so much!
If you work together, you can overcome any challenge...
It seems that the whole team has taken Mana's lesson to heart.
I'll fight with everyone.
Until the day I find my queen...
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Mana has a disciple?
Yeah, his name's Jun!
He's a real fighter!
I'm worried...
About what?
I know there are plenty of kids that respect Mana, but...
Mana's life is no stroll in the park.
I worry for anyone tagging along.
Huh?
Wh-What kind of life does Mana lead?
Dokidoki Precure:
Mana's Determination!
I'll Take a Disciple!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!