Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Why is it that I can't play well...
It's so...
Noel-chan?
You have your wallet?
Yes!
Identification tag?
Handkerchief?
Yes!
Tissues?
Map?
Yes!
Compass?
Travel provisions?
Yes!
Helmet?
Handgun?
Huh?
Hand grenades?
What?
Um...
She's only joking, Kana-chan.
What?  You really startled me, sheesh...
If you'd just thought logically, you would've picked up on it quickly enough.
That's mean, Rio-senpai.
The two of you have been getting along quite well recently, haven't you?
Rio's just like an anxious mother.
Okay then, here's the list for today.
Are you listening?
Your mission for today is to go into town and purchase the goods on that list.
Got it?
Yes!
All right, drive safely and have a good trip!
Right.
Departing.
Come back soon!
We're having Pot au Feu for dinner!
Detours aren't allowed, okay?
She's just like a mother.
This is a first, isn't it, Noel-chan?
The two of us haven't gone into town together like this.
Yeah.
But even saying that, this is pretty much my first time going into town at all...
Wow...
Amazing!
Wow, I wonder what that could be?
This is completely different from during the festival, you know?
It's such a calm, quiet town.
Ow...
The first was a chimera, a roof ornament special to Trois.
Designed to ward against evil spirits.
After that was a drinking fountain, modeled after the twelfth Helvetian Archduke, Akira Arcadia II.
We've arrived.
Oh!  You meant the earlier stuff!
Yeah.
Had to drive safely, since I was instructed to.
Thank you!
I get it now!
Noel-chan, you're really knowledgeable, aren't you?
Eh?
Uh, ladies?
Are you coming in or not?  Could you possibly make up your minds?
You're obstructing business.
The auntie from the festival!
S-i-s-t-e-r.
You shouldn't... force people.
You're as straight-laced as always.
Then at least call me "Naomi," okay?
Naomi...-san?
Then the next shipment is next month?
Yeah.
By the way, that girl, does she know?
No.
You girls are still as strange as ever...
even though you're soldiers—
E-Excuse me!
W-What is it?
It's... about those, but...
The first time you were here, you were captivated by those as well, weren't you?
You've taken a fancy to them?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Um... m-may I touch it?
Of course.
A-flat.
This is a fish, right?
What's it called?
Um... that's a...
Not a fish.
Huh?  But...
That's a dolphin.
A creature which is closer to us humans than to fish.
It's a marine mammal from the time when creatures still lived in the sea.
"In the sea"?
It lived in the sea?!
Yeah.
Wow...
How wonderful.
That old man... he's pretty good at making things like that, isn't he?
It's because he's a romantic, even though he doesn't look it.
Do you know him, then?  The person who made this?
On the outskirts of town, there's a big workshop.
All of our glassworks are products from there.
I'd love to see them being made.
That's fine.
What is?
We're headed there... now.
I see!
You have them make parts for the Takemikazuchi for you at that glass workshop.
Right.  Naomi gathers parts from the old era for me as well.
But you really are amazing, aren't you, Noel-chan?
You can fix such a complicated machine like that so quickly!
"So quickly"?
For me, my head's already too full just trying to remember the chords for the signal trumpet.
It's not really... that difficult...
Huh?
'cause machines don't betray.
Noel-chan—
There we go!
Your change is 2,750,000 yen!
Huh?  We can get that much back?
Huh?
Wrong.
The change is 2 yen and 75 sen.
Still no sense of humor, huh, Noel-chan?
Here you go.
She's right.
The morning trumpet calls recently... is that you, little missy?
Y-Yes, it is.
I apologize for still being so terrible...
It's fine!
I like it.
How to say this... it really wakes you up!
Stare...
I was just thinking how I need to hurry up and get better so I stop being such a burden to the citizens...
That's not fair, Seiya!
Then chase after me and fix it!
Kanata, I also...
Ow...
I'm sor—
Ha, you hit someone!
I'm terribly sorry!
Oh?  You two are...
The one from the festival!
The clumsy girl!
I'm so glad.
You seem to have made a full recovery!
You murderer!
Seiya-san, I'm sure these people have nothing to do with your parents!
They're all the same!
I hate soldiers!
Hurry up and get out of this city!
Every morning, with your horrible trumpet playing — it's so annoying!
Hey, Seiya!
I'm really very sorry...
He was so rude...
I-It's fine.
That boy... he's a war orphan.
Because of that, any time he sees a soldier, he indiscriminately...
Noel-chan.
That's okay.
The truth remains that we're soldiers.
So that's...
Noel-chan...
That is true.
We are soldiers.
When I joined... I properly recited the Oath of Parador,
and I thought I understood what that meant but...
Actually, what am I saying?!
That's something I've always understood!
There's no use getting all wishy-washy about it now!
That's right.
I need to get better to be ready just in case something actually does happen!
Without the signal trumpet, everyone would be in trouble!
There it is.
Huh?
Wow!
That's the glass workshop?
Yeah.
That's amazing, Noel-chan!
This is my first time ever seeing such a big building!
This one's no good either, huh?
Is the problem the aberration?
The refraction should definitely be right, but...
I-I'm the new recruit, Sorami Kanata!
It's nice to meet all of you!
Yeah.
And um, I...
And?
What?
How was the timing before it started spitting out errors?
Since our last attempt, there were barely any changes in seek time.
In comparison, the distortion of the image sensor has been slightly reduced—
Hey, I'm sorry.
When it comes to work-related things, the boss just can't focus on other stuff.
But he really is amazing, Old Man Carl.
He's one of only five outstanding artisans in the country that holds a Meister title.
He even won a competition at the capital once and got to present his work to the Archduke!
Maria!  If you're free enough to be talking, move those hands!
Got it!  Sorry, boss!
A title like Meister doesn't fit me anyway.
I can't even hold a candle to this.
What is that?
The lens of the Takemikazuchi's optic sensor.
What?
That's the real one.
In order to repair the Takemikazuchi, two of the same are needed, so I've asked him to duplicate it.
However, it's not going well.
Even though they look so pretty?
Besides the main component of silicon dioxide,
the lens also has some lesser quantities of sodium oxide and magnesium oxide mixed in.
These components rectify the chromatic and spherical aberrations,
in other words, the things which distort the image.
But we don't know the proportions for those components...
It's because this is like a product created by a magic-like technology of a previous era.
I thought glass was just pretty, but it's also complex, isn't it?
Due to the fact that high-quality materials can be gathered in Seize,
many small factories that specialized in handicrafts dotted the city.
This workshop was also originally one of those.
But when the war became more intense, glass products needed by the military increased,
and this workshop grew due to it.
Kanata, I like machines.
Right.
However, there are instances where machines hurt people.
The Takemikazuchi has surely killed many people in the past.
I suppose you would consider a machine that has killed people in the past frightening?
Yeah.
Still, perhaps what's more scary isn't the machine itself, but the people who used it, you know?
I mean, even this trumpet...
When I play it, it's terrible, but when Rio-senpai plays it, it sings beautifully.
I'm sure that a tank is the same way!
And also, just a little while ago, Rio-senpai let me hear one of the Takemikazuchi's songs.
She's able to sing so beautifully!
I'm sure she's a good tank!  The Takemikazuchi is!
I know!  How about next time—
Noel-chan.
Let her rest, yeah?
I'm sure she pulled another all-nighter.
Noel-chan is really working her hardest in order to fix the Takemikazuchi.
I know.
That little lady's a real artisan.
If she weren't, I wouldn't have accepted the job of making something this annoying.
Here, cover her with this.
Thank you!
By the way, you guys stopped by Windmill right?
Is Naomi-san doing well?
She is!
She said your boss is a wonderful romantic.
You hear that?
Isn't that just great, boss?
S-Shut up!
Hurry up and get your ass to work!
Ah, I made him angry!
Time for work, time for work!
But the technology from the past, is it really that amazing?
I suppose it is.
But the boss always says,
"No matter how amazing it is, in the end, if it was created by humans like us, it must be reproducible!"
You agree, don't you?
Yes.
Or, well... "yes" is what I'd like to say, but...
I see...
Your trumpet playing compared to Rio-san's is truly quite different.
I'm constantly dwelling on it.
What should I do in order to become more like her?
I have every intention of working as hard as I can!
Look, my lips have swollen this much.
Yet...
No matter how many times I try, I can never manage to play a sound like her's.
I guess I really don't have any talent...
Missy.
Yes!
The worst excuse given by those who quit is "having no talent."
Give that here.
I don't really understand trumpets, but...
I do know of a mistake that young people often make.
Missy, aren't you trying to force the sounds?
I'm not trying to create this particular shape.
The glass itself wants to become this shape, you see?
Thank you very much, Uncle Carl!
To allow the sounds to resonate as they wish...
Morning?
Yep.  Somehow it seems like the sun rose a step early just for her.
That little lady's an artisan in her own right, huh?
Those are some good sounds!
"Sounds"?
Depending on the amount and types of impurities,
the sound of glass changes by just the smallest, most delicate degree.
However, even if our ears can't tell the difference,
someone with a keen sense of hearing should be able to tell them apart.
I'll have Kanata find the one with the closest sound out of the samples we've created thus far.
And so, that one would probably...
Okay then, listen to their voices, missy!
Yes!
Noel-chan... she's certainly changed since she came here, hasn't she?
You think so?
Yes!
You did it!
You did it, Noel-chan!
Thank you.
This is the first time I've ever seen Noel smile.
Next time, Mountain Climbing: The End of the World!