Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
Rika-chama
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Rio-senpai!
Good work!
Did you find it?
Yeah, safely in one piece!
You can find anything as long as you look hard enough!
So nice and warm!
I feel alive again.
Huh?
Rio-senpai, you were on grounds duty today?
There was something I wanted to burn.
It's been half a year already since Kanata came to the bastion.
She's gotten pretty good.
It's 'cause she has a good teacher!
Ow, hot!
I suppose I won't need earplugs anymore.
Madame, I think it might still be better for you to stay in the city this winter.
I'm okay.
I won't kick the bucket that easily.
I've been living on this mountain by myself for the past fifty years, after all.
Keep going!
Keep going,
keep going...
Stop!
It's finally coming together!
Noel, can you take care of the rest by yourself?
Sure.  Be happy to.
Then how about we go get some tea?
Yeah!
Hey, Kureha-chan.
Huh?
Where'd it go?
It should be right here...
Oh my, what's the matter?
The military yearbook was around here, right?
Kanata said she wanted to read up to find out more about Princess Ilya.
Very sorry, but if it's not there then I'm not sure where it might be.
Man...
Oh!  Naomi-san might have one at her place!
I'll ask her for you the next time I see her.
Thanks!
Her Highness Princess Ilya was the current Archduke Arcadia's eldest daughter, you see.
I feel like I've told you already, but anyway, she was a really famous tank driver!
Before, Krause-san was saying how things might be different if she were still alive...
Yeah.  She passed away, maybe about two years ago.
In the war?
No.
Her Highness was assigned to the Imperial Guard,
but she also took on the duty of expanding national influence, so she ended up traveling all over the place.
And then, on her way to a city, she tried to save a child who was drowning in a river...
But I'm actually kind of relieved.
Now this is only a rumor, but...
Ilya...
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san!
And...
Um... it's Kanata.
Uh...
Yumina-san has, uh... she's brought Yuuko-chan over...
Oh!  And Yuuko-chan is Martin-san's daughter...
And there's also an old lady named Jaquette-san...
She lives by herself on the mountain, and early in the morning I buy vegetables and stuff from her—
Oh!  You said earlier that the pickled vegetables were good, right?
Jaquette-san was the one who made them.
So you see, supposedly no one's seen her around lately...
and since her body is rather frail, people are worried.
She lives pretty deep in the mountains and all...
And...
Ugh...
Fine, fine!
I'll listen to what you have to say, just give me a second.
Okay!
It's been said that,
in order to improve relations with the holy city of Rome, Princess Ilya was to be wed to the Roman emperor.
But if she did, she would've been the third!
His third!
Unbelievable, isn't it?!
So really, she would've just been a hostage.
But talks of that stopped after she passed away,
and we ended up fighting them until the armistice at the beginning of this year.
Phew, finally here.
A half-built house?
Wasn't she supposed to be living alone?
Yes, supposedly.
Madame!
I see...
Yuuko told you.
Yes.
She's a good girl.
She's too good to become that snot-nosed Martin's daughter.
This is a really nice house.
Thank you.
I actually built this house.
Huh?  Wow!
But wait...
What about the house over there?
That's for my son...
You have a son?
Yes, though he's in a faraway city right now.
I keep it ready for him for whenever he decides to come home.
That way it can be used easily by my son and that person, you know?
I need to keep it properly cleaned.
When will your son come home, Madame?
Soon, soon.
What's "soon" is winter.
It'd be a good idea to get off the mountain before the snow begins to fall.
I can't do that.
I need to finish building that house.
I have no intention of leaving before that, no matter what.
But—
Don't be stupid!
What about the preparations for winter?
Do you have firewood?  Provisions?
You haven't made any preparations at all, have you?!
It'll work out.
Thank you for caring, girls.
Madame!
Sheesh, what a stubborn old lady!
It takes one to know one, I bet.
Oh, leave me alone.
Why would I...
Since sometimes you also, Rio, put on a front and won't listen when you know you should.
Shut up!
Say, about that letter...
Why did you show it to me?
It already came across in last week's scheduled communications...
The fact is, the Roman army on the Eastern border has begun to move.
I see!  Those are for old lady Jaquette, huh?
Okay!  Then take these along, too!
Thank you!
By the way...
you wouldn't know what's going on
with the peace talks, would you?
I'm... sorry, I don't.
If only Princess Ilya were still alive...
Speaking of that, Martin,
Ilya-sama had a younger sister, didn't she?
And 4,000,000 in change!
That's fresh news.
Well actually, the Archduke had her elsewhere, so most people don't talk about it.
She's something like the third-in-line for succession.
Um, that little sister is...
See you!
Thank you!
Thanks.
You wanna... take a little walk?
Hey, Kanata...
What kind of place was the village where you were born?
Just a typical countryside village.
There were lots of fields, cows, and sheep, but not so many people.
I guess that's the biggest difference between here and there.
But it was a good place, right?
And you had good parents too, didn't you?
I can tell just by looking at you.
Where did you grow up, senpai?
In a small village a short distance from the capital, with pretty forests and lakes.
I lived there with my mother.
It was boring.  The days were too calm and nothing ever happened.
The only relief was when my sister,
well actually my half-sister, who cared for me very much, would sometimes come over and play with me.
She was my idol.
She was beautiful and kind.  She accepted her fate with dignity.
I learned how to play the trumpet from her.
But... she was too kind.
And because she was, she paid with her own life.
When I first came here, I thought this city was like a maze.
I lost my way and ended up here.  I felt that, in doing so, I'd reached my goal.
But later on, I realized...
This is just a dead end.
That's not true!
I often lose my way.
But I like getting lost!
And that's just fine, isn't it?!
To you lose your way... or hit a dead end!
Since, after all... because of that I was able to meet you, senpai!
You make me jealous of you at times, Kanata.
If only I were able to be as honest with myself as you are...
This should do it.
Why are you so concerned about me?
You resemble my mother.
I know I don't have a beautiful daughter like you, though.
She had an inexcusable romance, and from that I was produced.
She was always waiting for that one time every year when he just might come by.
And so... while living through such an unhappy existence, she passed away.
Why do you say she was unhappy?
Because!
I'm happy.
That man promised that he'd come back someday.
He promised to come for me one day.
That promise is enough for me.
But!
What else could I have done?
I suppose you're right.  If there was something else I could've done, perhaps I would've.
But well...
Are you really okay with that?
Are you really happy with just that?
Yes, because I loved him.
Because I still have my memories of him.  Because I have hope to be able to see him again one day.
That's enough to make me happy.
I thought it was getting colder.
It was on a snowy day like this that I first met you, wasn't it?
When Madame was young, Seize was a flourishing resort area.
She fell in love with the son of a merchant.
And from that, she became pregnant with his child.
But the young master already had a family.
For better or worse, his legal wife was unable to have a child,
so he took the child away and returned to his hometown.
He swore he'd come for her, one day.
Now that I'm already this old, I sometimes muse to myself...
"What if," back then...
Life is a continuous cycle of losing things, you see.
But in order to lose, you must first gain.
And the greater the joy at your gain, the greater the sorrow will be at your loss.
But as long as we have the memories of those happy times,
indeed, because we have those memories, people are able to go on.
Oh right.  This might not be the best time, but I found the pictures of Princess Ilya you were looking for.
Naomi-san!
Phylicia, it's okay.
I think it's from five years ago when the princess came by to visit Seize.
Is that Shuko?
Rio-senpai!
To be honest, I think my parents wanted me to find a husband and take over the household for them.
But I was enchanted by the sound of that trumpet...
and there was no forgetting it.
That person was Ilya-san, wasn't she?
I knew it.  You've met her as well, haven't you?
Ilya-san's sound resonated within me, and oh, how wonderful it was!
And then you and I met.
I was probably just running away to this city.
So at first, nothing really mattered to me.
I thought it was just some place I'd end up leaving someday.
But now, I honestly believe that I don't want to part from this place.
And so that's why, I suppose, I must leave now.
Because there are things that I can do— things that only I can do!
I have no intention of saying goodbye.
No matter how far apart we become...
Sounds resonate...
They resonate...
And... reach out to the hearts of others.
Kanata, have I been a good senpai to you, I wonder?
You have.
And thus, Rio-senpai left us.
Leaving in my heart a forever-resonating, oh-so-beautiful sound from the sky.
Next time, A Visitor: Burning Snowfield!