Hey, is that big bag yours, Mana?
Yeah!
What did you bring?
Heh, that's a secret!
We shall arrive shortly.
So, will you finally tell us?
What will our final trial be?
You have all grown much over this summer's rigid training.
To tie it all together,
you shall acquire one of the three Sacred Treasures obtained by the Precures of ten thousand years ago.
Specifically, the Crystal Mirror.
The Crystal Mirror?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Final Trial!
The Legendary Precure!
Long ago,
back when the universe was still enveloped in darkness,
the legendary warriors known as the Precures appeared.
They came to deliver love and peace to the world!
The spear of light that could pierce any obstacle, Miracle Dragon Glaive!
The mirror of crystal that could reflect any truth, Magical Lovely Pad!
And the coronet of gold imbued with boundless wisdom, Eternal Golden Crown!
By employing these three Sacred Treasures,
these women dispelled the darkness, according to legend.
Wait, I've heard this before...
The Miracle Dragon Glaive...
That was the name of the spear the princess wielded!
Indeed, I've heard that the Trump Kingdom princess wielded the spear of light.
And to think that King Selfish sealed the princess away with that spear's own power...
So, the crystal mirror that we'll be searching for...
holds the same power as that spear?
That it does.
Makopi?
I'm worried...
I feel that if we fail here, we'll be back at square one.
Don't worry.
This is what we've been training for!
Mana is right.
We're not just saving Trump Kingdom.
We've also got to get Regina back!
That's right.
What happened?
A near miss.
Pwane! Pwane!
Huh? Where?
What the Chell is that?!
What're you askin' me for?!
Please fasten your seatbelts.
We're making an emergency landing!
Are you girls all right?
Yes, somehow.
What is it?
I lost my glasses...
Do your glasses matter more than your life?
Maybe...
Oh, Rikka...
It's been a while, Aguri.
I'd have never thought you were on that plane.
Melan!
Do you know her?
For ten thousand long years,
this fairy has protected the Crystal Mirror!
Is she a Precure's partner like us?
Nice to meet you!
I'm Aida Mana!
Always so quick to adapt...
We absolutely must have that Crystal Mirror!
We came to obtain the power fit only for the legendary Precure warriors!
I beg you, please give us the Crystal Mirror!
Very well.
After such persistent requests, I have no choice...
but to put your strength to the test myself!
This can't be happening!
Is that...
the dinosaur we saw earlier?
I don't think so!
For one thing,
dinosaurs don't breathe fire!
What a magnificent beast!
Sebastian!
No, you may not.
Now, this way.
Hm?
What's wrong? Lost your nerve?
And yet you dare bear the name of legendary warriors?
If you wish to obtain the Crystal Mirror,
then you must first defeat me!
Is this our final trial?
Well, it certainly doesn't disappoint.
Let's go, girls!
Right!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
You cannot defeat me with numbers alone!
We have more than numbers alone!
Oh?
I've obtained true power, as well!
Ai, let us begin!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Hmph. It'll be easier to crush you all at once!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Precure Double Kick!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Pretty cool, right?
You dare attempt to freeze me in ice?
You're a million years too green to succeed!
She's strong...
You mustn't lose faith.
We must combine our strengths as one!
You're right. Let's do it, girls!
Right!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
But how?
Our attacks didn't even scratch her!
Is that all that Precures these days can muster?
This is the end!
Never knew there was a fairy that strong.
Aguri, you seemed to know Melan.
It was before I sought to become a Precure.
I was led to this island by a mysterious power.
That was when I met Melan, who told me this...
You say you want the Crystal Mirror?
The only ones I may entrust it to are the legendary Precure warriors.
Return once you are one.
I can't reach the stage on which the legendary warriors stood on my strength alone.
With that realization,
I decided to search for partners with whom I could train and, together, reach ever greater heights.
So that would be why you trained so much with us.
But I failed...
I'm further from that legendary stage than I ever imagined...
This isn't over yet!
Mana?
You're never going to get anywhere if you give up after a slip or two!
If we just bowed out right now,
that'll mean my only summer break as a 14-year-old will have been for nothing!
Sebastian!
Wait, Mana?
What did you bring?
Cooking utensils, as you can see.
Let's eat some dinner for now.
Thou canst not do battle on an empty stomacheth!
Know how to cook this?
No...
Then you do it, Rikka.
I'll peel the vegetables.
Alice and Makopi, you two can gather kindling and get a fire going.
Sure.
Um...
Could you possibly teach me to cook, too?
You got it, partner!
Countless warriors have come to challenge me for this mirror over the years...
However...
I've seen not one with a heart as strong as yours.
What is that scent?
Dinnertime!
What is this flavor?
It's delicious!
It's so mild and rich...
Simmered food tastes the best!
You!
Melan!
I recall telling you to leave!
Did you come to play games?
Aw, don't be like that. Have a bite.
Curry tastes better the more people eat it.
Eat up!
Is something wrong?
Is it too spicy?
You know, I've always lived alone on this island.
It's been ten thousand years since I've had a meal with someone...
So my stomach simply acted up out of surprise.
Eating food with others tastes this wonderful, does it?
I have people I'd like to eat this curry with, too.
I don't know what's happened to Regina, so I can't help but worry,
even though I have no way to find her...
If I could, I'd like to bring Regina back right this instant.
I'd like to awaken the princess and restore Trump Kingdom!
But I have to become stronger if I want to do that!
That is none of my concern.
Now, finish your meal and leave.
We won't leave!
Mana!
I beg of you as well, please give us another chance!
Please!
There is a cave at the foot of that mountain.
We shall settle this there at dawn.
Thanks!
Thank you!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
That barrier's such a pain!
I shall strike it with a Rosetta Reflection to cancel it out!
You can't do that alone!
Then how about us four do it?
We can use a Lovely Force Arrow,
so maybe we can use a Lovely Force Reflection?
Sounds like it's worth a try!
I shall draw Melan's attention!
Take the chance to attack!
You got it!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
No matter how often you try, it will always end the same!
Now!
We'll give our power to Rosetta!
Precure Lovely Force Reflection!
That's kinda small!
Here we go!
What?
We did it!
Now!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot—
Oh no!
Five minutes have passed!
Fools!
Cure Heart!
What's wrong? Through already?
Where is the vigor I saw before?
Do you not want to save your friends?
Is this all your heart can muster?
Not even...
close!
I won't...
We won't...
ever give up!
Not until we save Trump Kingdom!
If there's even a one in a million chance...
Then we shall fight to our last breath!
Girls...
We'll become stronger and stronger.
And once we have...
we'll meet Regina once again!
Impudent!
Burn!
Cure Heart!
What?!
Mana!
Why you...
Cure Empress...
You've awakened?
Sebastian...
Wait, did we lose again?!
No freaking way!
Okay, first comes lunch, then we take another shot!
We can't quit until we get that Crystal Mirror!
Which would be this!
That's... the Crystal Mirror?
Long ago, we wagered our lives in a battle against an evil that appeared on this planet.
"We"?
While our comrades fell one by one, and all hope seemed lost,
my partner, Cure Empress, smiled and said this...
I won't ever give up!
You remind me so much of her.
Melan...
You won't ever give up.
One with as indomitable a spirit as yours will certainly make good use of it.
Now take it.
Thank you, Melan!
Melan, I must thank you as well.
It has arrived.
Let's return home.
Um, do you want to come with?
I'd like you to fight the Selfish with us!
I'm afraid I can't.
Why not?
I've lived long enough.
You'll be the ones to usher in a new era, which is why you should go.
Now go.
Save the people who wait for your rescue.
Thank you, Melan.
Is this enough, Cure Empress?
Their true trial begins now.
Do not waver, Precures!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Oh no!
Leva and Gura turned everyone in the city into Selfishes!
King Selfish will revive if we do nothing!
We must do whatever we can to stop them!
The only way out of this crisis is to use the legendary mirror's power!
Please, Mr. Legendary Mirror!
Lend us your power!
Dokidoki Precure:
Crisis in Oogai City!
The Birth of the Lovely Pad!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!