I've found it...
the thing that's most important to me...
Why won't you tell—
Was it fun?! Tricking me and sucking up to him—
I...don't want to keep running away.
You can't run from the past, Masaomi.
You're worrying about something to do with that past, aren't you?
If you're going to hate someone, hate the guy who ordered us to do this—Kida Masaomi!
The Dollars shall disappear.
Russia Sushi, Russia Sushi!
It's good.
It's cheap.
How about it, mister?
Boss.
Hello, Russia Sushi.
I didn't know whom to call, so I decided to call you.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I thought I should tell you what he's thinking.
Namie, what do you suppose this is?
Check? Checkmate? Or atari?
Hey...
Oh, she's not here...
What should we do?
The yellow guys are still acting out.
Apparently, that Horada guy is really influential.
What's Kida up to?
I don't know.
Horada?
Do you mean that Horada?
What Horada?
I'm the worst.
Suspicion is swirling about inside of me.
Has Mikado been ordering the Dollars
around like this because he knows everything?
Has Anri been colluding with him?
Or has she just been using him?
Either way, that's low.
But I'm even lower than that for doubting them like this.
What should I do?
Where should I go?
There's no place left for me to go...
Come in.
I know why you're here.
I figured things would get out of hand if I didn't do it.
I thought it was the most Dollarsesque thing to do.
Even if it's only in name...
Not having a specific form is what the Dollars are all about.
This way, we'll go back to being completely colorless.
The Slasher and the Yellow Scarves might also calm down.
I've found what's important to me...
And I think I'm okay with things as they are.
I get it.
But that's not why I'm here today.
Hello?
Hey, it's me, Horada.
What? Did something happen?
Well, you don't have to come to the meetings anymore.
Huh?
You're fired. You, the shogun, have been fired.
You've been terminated, sacked.
What are you talking about?
Ryugamine Mikado, was it? Your friend's name.
I was surprised to learn that our boss is friends with the Dollars' boss.
Wait, who'd you hear that from?!
It doesn't matter who.
By the way, you did a great job tricking us this whole time.
Everyone here has a look of shock on his face.
What are you planning on doing?
Killing the Dollars' boss, obviously.
Everyone's just itching to go on a rampage.
I've also ordered that you be killed on sight.
You'll never be able to walk around Ikebukuro again.
See you.
Mikado...!
Do you love Sonohara Anri?
Do you see Kida Masaomi as a close friend?
What's the meaning of this?
The number you have dialed is currently—
Please leave a message after the beep.
Coming!
Yo.
This is earth-shattering!
What happened?!
Stuff and things...
I've been shot.
You've sustained massive injuries to a section of your abdominal muscles.
Why are you walking around in this condition?!
Why? Because I can.
Mr. Heiwajima?
Why are you here...?
Oh, this is bad...
Who are you, again?
She's Anri.
Oh, sorry, Anri.
What in the world happened?
Well, at first I thought that I'd slipped and fell in the rain.
Then I noticed that blood was gushing from my stomach and leg...
So I realized, "Oh, I've been shot."
By the time I decided to kill the people
who did this to me, they'd already run away.
He's an idiot, isn't he?
Do you want to die?
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
Hurry up and fix me.
I have to go kill them.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll kill the guys who shot me, along with the guy who ordered them to—Kida Masaomi!
The number you have dialed is currently—
I no longer felt suspicious of Mikado or Anri.
If the Yellow Scarves were to attack Mikado...
Or if they kidnapped Anri to bring Mikado out of the woodwork...
Why couldn't I move back then?
What was I hesitating for?
What was I afraid of?
The past will be only too happy to chase you.
That's...not true, is it?
It's all true.
What about Masaomi?
Does he know about me?
I don't know.
But something about Kida didn't seem normal when he was berating Anri.
He may have known at the time that you're the Dollars' founder.
That's...
Who told him that?
I know a certain information dealer who loves seeing people worry and suffer.
You started the Dollars; you can do with it what you want.
However, what's going on between you three won't change just because you disbanded the Dollars.
Why didn't they tell me...?
Why couldn't you tell them?
That's because I thought that stuff with the Dollars was my problem.
They probably thought the same thing.
What you see isn't necessarily reality.
Everyone has secrets...
...things they can't tell others.
There are no normal people anywhere.
So, don't be afraid!
Face Anri, Kida, and your own reality head on!
If you love her, confess everything to her!
This is a problem for you three to solve—not
the Slasher or the Dollars or the Yellow Scarves.
Hello. Celty?
I'm running after her right now...
...but Shizuo's been shot and Anri suddenly ran out of the apartment.
Well, that's not why she ran out.
And apparently Kida Masaomi's the one who ordered the hit.
I can't keep up.
My breath...
Sorry, I can't make a coherent conversation...
She's so fast!
Anri's so fast!
Hey, Kida!
What's wrong?
You don't look like business is booming.
Are you hungry again?
Simon...
You seem down.
That's not like you.
Hey, Simon...
Your sushi is awesome.
If I could, I'd not only give it five stars, but the whole Stars and Stripes.
Russia Sushi always had great food.
Are you going to go fight?
Or are you going to kill and be killed?
What? Why would you say something like that all of a sudden?
Are you pretending to have ESP or something?
Has Izaya started something again?
It's not like that.
Killing and being killed isn't good.
Where I'm from, you would definitely die if you said the word "fight."
Kida, your eyes look like those of someone who's prepared to die.
Simon...
That won't do. This is Ikebukuro.
It's not the town I'm from.
It's warm and people will give you food even if you have no home.
No one will freeze to death by forgetting to drink vodka before going to sleep.
There's no reason...for kids like you to kill each other.
I'm sorry. I have to go...
Kida...
Someone!
Anyone in the Yellow Scarves!
They're not here. None of them are here.
If that's the case...
How interesting...
How interesting, indeed!
The three close friends—who each carry their own secrets...
...are about to learn each other's secrets in an almost-ideal way,
all because ill will has been coincidentally accumulating bit by bit.
Although, most of that ill will comes from me...
But still, the go-between...
He's a callous person and doesn't really hold the viewers' interest.
I wonder if I should've chosen better actors?
What do you think, Namie?
Do you really think the Yellow Scarves should stay like this?!
Look, we're not some ragtag group like the Dollars.
We have a power that stems from leadership!
It seems that the Dollars' leader has ordered them to disband, but don't be fooled!
That's definitely just a half-assed trick!
We're going to completely crush them!
If we use this momentum to take out the Dollars, we won't just rise to the top of Ikebukuro, we'll take all of Tokyo!
Do you understand? Imagine it!
Imagine absolutely every single group in Tokyo taking orders from us!
That eyesore named Heiwajima Shizuo isn't around anymore.
The only ones in the Dollars acting tough are Kadota and his friends.
We'll crush them, and then take out their leader—Ryugamine!
If we do that, we'll have nothing to fear!
Alright, let's go out into Ikebukuro!
No matter what, isn't killing a bad idea?
It's fine.
We have nothing to fear now that Heiwajima Shizuo's gone.
We'll get crushed by the police!
If it comes to that, we'll just say we're having a disagreement with the Dollars.
There's no way that would go over well!
Shut up! Yes, it will!
It'll be totally fine!
Horada...
It'll definitely go well.
It's in the cards.
The police?! They're already here?!
You!
What the hell did you come here for?!
Oh, Celty...
Are you going to eat sushi again?
I'm looking for Kida Masaomi and Sonohara Anri.
Have you seen them?
I saw Kida.
He looked very, very serious.
Probably a fight.
I couldn't stop him.
Do you know where he went?
I haven't seen any of those yellow guys.
Kida's definitely at their place.
Understood.
Thanks.
Are you prepared to accept what you're
about to see, no matter how horrible it may be?
Yes.
What's the meaning of this?
I barely see anyone I know.
I can't reach anyone by cell phone, either.
You guys couldn't be—
Well, last night, a mysterious group ambushed everyone
who was opposed to me being the leader for some reason.
My, how scary!
It must've been the work of the Dollars!
Am I right, guys?!
You bastard!
You're an idiot for wanting to come here.
"Like a moth to the flame," right?
Or maybe I should try what Izumii did.
I'll break your leg and say, "Okay, it's question time."
What...did you just say?!
Huh?!
Did you...just say "Izumii?!"
After that, hmmm...
I've done some very bad things with the Yellow Scarves.
I think I'll totally change the name and color of this gang.
Yes...to a color as pale blue as your face is now.
You...!
No, you guys...
It couldn't be...
So, you finally noticed?
Yes, everyone here is a member of the
Blue Squares, who you hate so much.
Don't call us refugees or anything disgusting like that.
We've taken over the Yellow Scarves.
Seriously...
All we had to do was take off our blue
colors and say we wanted in, and you let us!
What?
You finally feel like getting down on your knees and groveling?
No, I actually feel kind of refreshed.
Huh?
Now that I've been fired from the Yellow Scarves, I'm just a simple high schooler who hits on girls.
I'm just a loser who couldn't even save his own girlfriend.
I was an idiot for thinking I could turn my back on my past and live as a normal high schooler.
That's why I came here.
I...I'm just Kida Masaomi.
That's why... That's why I came here!
My past, which had been continually
chasing me, had suddenly left me behind.
You can't run away anymore.
In absolute, complete, and total earnest.
The past and memories get lonely easily.
If that's so, then it's my turn to chase my past, isn't it?
Huh?
They say the past gets lonely easily.
You have to hurry up and chase it...
What's with all the nonsense, you idiot?!
You know, I wasn't just prepared to die when I came here.
I was also prepared to kill someone.
Well, I guess...
...to be more specific, to kill you.
I'll say it again and again.
That's why I came here!
I won't let anyone contradict that!
What're you assholes doing?!
Hurry up and crush this idiot!
What was I hesitating for?
It was so simple...
Hey, he's only one guy!
What's taking you so long?!
I am who I am.
That's all it is...
Saki, I'm not afraid anymore.
I'll overtake it.
Just a little more, and I'll overtake my past.
Guys, do something now!
You're all useless!
Oh yeah...
What was that? Don't scare me like that, you piece of shit!
Y-You bastard... I'll seriously kill you!
Huh?! Just what the hell do you think you're doing?!
Sorry.
Apparently, Mother will be sad if you kill this guy, so I decided to take action.
Yes...
Huh?!
No, I know.
I'm sorry, but it seems that Mother is nearby.
Huh?
Kida!
Anri...
Why...?
Masaomi?!
Mikado...!
Ryugamine?
Why...?
I still think it's strange even now, but I had an experience that was very unusual and life-changing, yet common.
Next Time: Transcending Oneself.