Run!
Morning.
Morning!
Nagi-chan, Yuuko-chan!
Good morning!
What're you doing standing there?
Hey, look at this!
It was stuck to my forehead!
You just noticed?
Yep!
Same old Run, huh?
Really?
Run-chan.
Morning.
Morning!
Ruuun-chan!
Hey, hey, did you see that drama yesterday?
Yeah, I did!
Run sure has lots of male friends.
It was great!
Then what about that anime yesterday...
She sure does...
T-Tooru!
Hard at work this morning, I see.
What's wrong, Tooru?
Run-chan.
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
Love
Morning, Tooru.
I see you're small as usual today.
Don't pat me!
Whoa! Why are your clothes so dirty?
Did you fall down?
Run-chan was...
And you see,
it wasn't on the map...
Don't tell me Run was bullying her...
... chasing a butterfly, and a car was about to hit her.
That's quite responsible of you.
See you, Tooru.
Later!
See you at lunchtime, Tooru!
Good morning!
Aoigaoka High School Entrance Exam Results
Yes?
Hello? Run-chan?
Tooru! It's been a while!
Yeah.
Umm...
Can I come right now?
Sure, come right on over!
Thanks.
See you later then.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Because of exams and all, we haven't seen each other in a while.
Coming!
Oh my, Tooru-chan!
It's been a while!
It's good to see you again.
Run's upstairs.
Got it.
Pardon the intrusion.
I wonder... if Run-chan will be happy.
Run-chan!
I got into the same high school as you!
Ah! Tooru!
Wha-
Ouch!
Run, what's with this girl?
Run, who is she?
What was she just doing?
You got in?
Congratulations!
Never mind getting in!
So this is Tooru?
She really is tiny.
So she's the one you wanted to introduce us to?
Introduce?
Yep, that's right!
They were announcing the test results today,
and I figured Tooru would stop by,
so I invited you two over!
These are my friends from our school,
Yuuko-chan and Nagi-chan!
Nice to meetcha.
Friends...?
We'll be together starting spring, Tooru.
I think she's giving me the death glare...
Talk about a bad first impression, Yuuko.
You should probably explain what you were doing.
Um... looks like you misunderstood.
Run was tickling me just now.
We weren't doing anything weird,
just fooling around.
Huh?
Geez, what was that for?
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH
Looks like they've broken the ice. How nice!
Squish
Bamf
Shouldn't you stop her?
Stop it!
Whack
Well then...
I'll be sending around the elective sign-up sheets.
It's just like last year's, so you'll figure it out.
Here.
Our homeroom teacher this year is pretty lax...
And that's the procedure for filling out your elective selection forms.
Concerning electives.
Elective choices and selection
Affects future!
Take seriously!!
・Prepare you for future college or course of study
・Skills you want to develop
・If you are having trouble deciding
consult myself or your parents
Does anybody have any questions?
As first-years, you don't have many elective choices,
but your options will increase in later semesters.
Elective Subject/Course Form
Year
Class
Name
1st yr.
Art I
Mus. I
Callig. I
2nd yr.
Art II
Mus. II
Callig. II
Classical
Readings
Gen.
Sci. A
Sci. B
Phys. I
Bio. I
Math B
3rd yr. track A
Art III
Mus. III
Callig. III
Adv.
Jpns. I
Jpn. Hist. B
Classical
Readings
Classics
Oral Communi-
cation
Chem. II
Bio. II
Math II
Rea-
ding
Electives
1st year, fine arts: art, music, calligraphy, 3 choices
2nd year: phys, bio, etc.
3rd year: split based on concentration track, so
This will affect your future,
so please think carefully about your choices.
If you have any individual questions, please ask at any time.
Art I
Mus. I
Callig. I
Art II
Mus. II
Callig. II
Classical
Readings
Jpn.
Hist. B
Geo. B
Gov.
& Ec.
In order of preference...
Gen.
Sci. A
Sci. B
Classical
Readings
Classics
Oral Communi-
cation
Phys. I
Bio. I
Chem. II
Bio. II
Will Run be okay?
What is she doing?
Lunch time, lunch time~
Tooru, let's eat!
You sure are hasty.
Tooru's not here yet.
Ah, you're right, it just slipped out.
She's here, Nagi-chan!
That's my Tooru!
Run-chan
Don't tell me...
she heard her?
Ah, that squirrel toothpick is so cute!
Isn't it? It's my favorite!
I love animals!
Really? What's your favorite animal?
Birds, I guess.
Oh, like parakeets?
How cute.
Come to think of it,
Run, your hair...
looks sorta like a parakeet's.
But most of all, they taste so good!
What?
Eh? That's why?
Those poor parakeets, being eaten like that...
Huh?
That's not what she meant!
Run-chan...
always liked to eat chicken.
Oh, that's what you meant.
So your favorite food is a kind of bird.
That's right! But I like all kinds of meat.
Then why don't we go for Korean barbecue sometime?
I'd love to have some some grilled ribs and beef tongue.
This is really making me crave some Korean barbecue.
It's as if I can already hear the sizzling of barbecuing meat...
Sorry, it's for me.
That's your ringtone?!
Run, your fried eggs look so good.
Can I have a bite?
Go ahead.
Here.
Thanks.
Ah, delicious!
Run, did you make this-
Not again!
Those two sure get along well!
That's getting along well?
That was a good lunch, wasn't it, Tooru?
Yeah.
Run, where do you think you're going?
Our classroom is this way.
That's right!
We just moved up grades, so I'm still in the habit...
Hurry up, Run.
Tooru, if you don't hurry up, you'll be late, too.
See you later then!
Toooooruuu!
Run, I see you stayed awake during the afternoon classes.
Yep! I was fine all afternoon.
Did almost falling out of the window wake you up?
Honestly, you should be more careful.
'Kay.
For me, I'm sleepier in the afternoon.
Oh right.
Want some candy to wake you up?
Here.
Thanks.
One for you too, Run.
Thanks!
That's the last one.
Hm? Really...
Then I'll save it for Tooru.
But then you won't have any.
No, we'll split it in half.
Oh Run, you're so nice.
How do you plan to split that candy in half?
Ah, that's right!
Here we go!
I wonder if I can split it like this?
Don't be reckless.
It'd be silly if you got hurt over a piece of candy.
I'll be fine!
Is it working?
Oh no, it fell on the floor!
See? I told you.
I thought it'd work!
Tooru!
Thanks for waiting!
Let's go home.
What's wrong, Tooru?
I smell candy.
You smell like candy.
Huh? You have more?
Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy!
Actually...
I forgot to throw out the bag.
That's amazing, Tooru!
You could even smell the empty bag?
It's 'cause Tooru loves sweet things.
Sorry. We were eating them earlier, and we finished the bag.
I'll bring more some other time.
I want amber candy!
Er, how about something a little less sweet...
or with less calories...
Eh? But the sweet ones taste better.
I got it, I got it, tomorrow then.
What did you two choose as your electives?
As our what?
Kamate-sensei was talking about it.
Run, were you asleep?
Come to think of it, you were!
Oh, so why'd you fall down, Yuuko?
Run looked like she was going to fall over, so I tried to catch her,
but then she straightened up and I lost my balance.
Really.
Hey,
Tooru, what did you put for your first-year electives?
Tooru?
Run-chan...
I wish I could take the same classes as you.
Together.
Don't worry.
Nothing's changed between us.
Yeah.
Oh, you're just too cute, Tooru.
S-St-Stop it-
Say, Tooru.
Why don't we all go out for tea?
Get off of me.
No fair, Yuuko! Let me hug her too.
So soft!
Wh-what's with you two?
Huh?
Let's go,
Tooru!
My dreams react with the spring wind. I can't stop this anticipation.
Luck and Happiness, gather in my hand!
As we run cheerfully as always, the road ahead
is still unknown, but that's fine.
It starts here.
Going wild, taking it slow, drawing masterpieces in class,
and writing plans on the scraps.
Where should we go? We're surely in paradise right now.
The key of my uneasy heart has been wound too tight.
I was late for our appointment, but we arrived at the same time.
On this stage full of skirts,
what sort of days shall we pass?
My dreams react with the spring wind. I can't stop this anticipation.
Luck and Happiness, gather in my hand!
As we run cheerfully as always, the road ahead
is still unknown, but that's fine.
It starts here.
You know,
Run really does have a lot of male friends.
Wonder what they're talking about?
Tell us Yuuko-chan's three sizes, Run-chan!
Keep this a secret!
From the top, 88-56-87.
Wow, that's amazing!
... or something like that?
W-w-why do you know my sizes, Nagi?
Well, see you later then, Run-chan.
Later!
Uh, see you!
Huh?
Look at that. They all left.
So that's why.
Ah, Tooru!
Run-chan.
Hard at work every morning, huh, Tooru?
Tooru,
I brought the candy, just as promised.
Let's eat it together later.
Why?
Those two really do get along well.
They sure do.
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
Our chatter goes on and on,
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
note: "candy" and "rain" are both "ame"
Speaking of candy, there are all sorts of them!
Drizzles, showers, and gloomy rain.
You sure know some unusual stuff.
So we're going to have a quiz, Miporin!
On what?
Who are we?
But you just gave away my name.
Oh my, Yutaka totally messed up this time!
Next time on A-Channel!
"On Rainy Days, a Bath"!
Come to think of it, since we've talked so much, maybe we'll appear next week?
That's a secret.
See you next week!