Incinerator
So, where will we start?
I've been worried about that, too.
I think we should start with Yui.
Who?
You know...
Remember at that Guerrilla Live show in the cafeteria?
The one who was doing the vocals.
Don't you remember?
That girl, she's always so energetic.
Teasing Hinata and laughing.
She does the vocals for the band, and has ambitions.
It seems like she's pretty fulfilled, already.
All she needs is a little push.
If we can give her that push, she can leave this world.
I just get that feeling.
If that's how you feel, that's good with me.
You're in agreement?
Great!
Let's do it!
So, how did your task go?
Well, it took some time, but...
Hand Sonic: Version 5.
This is Hand Sonic: Version 5.
More than an Angel... you look like a Devil, now.
You said I'm supposed to be the coldhearted Tenshi, so make it ominous-looking.
That's why I did it like this...
No good?
Oh, no, it's fine.
It's really horrible-looking.
Horrible?
No no, I mean it's great.  Really great!
Oh, and can you grow wings?
Wings?
What would I do with those?
Don't you think they'd look cool?
You wanted me to look cool?
Well, if you had them you'd look more like an Angel, right?
I'll think about it.
Please do...
So, now what should I do?
Uh, er, that's right...
Let's go with this:
You appear right in the middle of their band practice.
Then say this:
"I've been getting complaints about noise from the other clubs."
Then point at Yui and say...
"I think your guitar playing is horrible."
"Because of you, the band is dying.
Therefore, I will be confiscating your guitar for a while."
Then, grab Yui's guitar and take your leave.
Obviously, Yui will give chase.
You just run.
Then, come to the courtyard.
I'll pretend to run into you.
At the same time, you drop the guitar.
I'll grab it, so you take that chance to escape.
That'll make it so Yui and I are alone.
Understood.
Good.
Alright, pick a good time during their practice and go!
kakumei wo okoshi ni ikou
革命を起こしにいこう
Let's go and start a revolution
yume wo kanae ni ikou
夢を叶えにいこう
And make our dreams come true.
Study Building A - Unused Classroom
kakedashitara dokomademo ikou
駆け出したらどこまでもいこう
If we start running, we can go anywhere
Stop!
ainshutain ( no riron mo bukkowashita tsukisusumou )
アインシュタイン ( の理論もぶっ壊した空き進もう )
(We'll bust up) Einstein's (theories and plunge forward)
Hey, Yui!
Don't follow my rhythm with work like that!
Huh?
Yui... isn't about time you concentrate on either vocals or guitar?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
The way things are now, we're sounding pretty awful.
No way!
Iwasawa-san played and sang at the same time!
That's because Iwasawa was good at both.
I'm trying my best, though!
You're all just being too harsh.
Everyone was having a great time at our last live show!
Yeah, well this time is an all new song.
Tenshi!
The band is dying because of your guitar playing.
She realized our band's weak point that quickly?!
She's not one to be trifled with!
She understands our music after all!
No way!
I hoped everyone wouldn't pick up on it!
So anyway, I'll be confiscating your guitar for a while.
Whoa, Yui!
Are you alright?
Here.
Why are you all by yourself?
She didn't chase me.
Hey yeah, without the guitar you don't get mixed up at all.
Yeah, but doesn't the sound come off as weaker?
We need a rhythm guitar too, right?
Well then, should we audition for another guitarist?
What I'm trying to say is...!
Having the vocalist play guitar is the best after all, damn you!
You brat...
Whoa, Hisako-san's pissed!
I'm gonna go get my guitar back!
Crap...
Hey!  Hey, Yui!
She's coming!
Where'd she go?!
Whoa, there she is!
Stop!
Sorry!
Stupid!  That's way too high!
My guitaaaaaaar!
Don't worry, it's saf-
You protected it from Tenshi, didn't you, Senpai?
Oh!  Where'd she go, damn it?!
Sheesh, what do you mean, damn it?
You're doing everything you want, as usual.
Huh?  Everything I want?
I'm not doing everything I want.
You're doing the band's vocals, aren't you?
You're even playing the guitar.
That's not that big a deal.
That's just something I've always wanted to do.
Huh?  You mean there's others?
Yeah, tons.
Tons?
Wait, hold on.
Let's find a better place to discuss this.
So, like what else?
Academy Cafeteria, Front side
Do I really have to say?
If you don't want to, it's alright...
Alright.
I'll tell you.
The truth is...
I've got a lot more things I want to do than most people.
Why do you think that is?
That's because... of 'that', right?
You couldn't do it while you were alive?
Yeah, yeah.  That's it exactly.
When I was little, you see...
I was hit from behind by a car.
And then...
My body couldn't move anymore.
I was completely confined to bed.
I couldn't live without nursing aid.
I was completely dependent on my mom.
I felt like...
I'd done something horrible to my mom.
I could watch the TV, though.
I watched bands on music programs.
I thought how great it would be if I could do something like that.
I see.
Well good for you, huh?
Yeah!
So, what else did you want to do?
Baseball, too.
I watched a lot of it.
Well if it's baseball you want, we did a lot of that at the ball game, right?
I wasn't able to hit, though!
A run?
A home run!
Huh?
It's no good without one?
No good at all!
If things start going better with the band, I was thinking that I'd start practicing my baseball skills!
This is gonna be harder than I thought.
Well for now, let's hear the rest.
What else?
Soccer!
Soccer?
It was pretty big, right?
Well... yeah, I suppose so.
Damn it, she's got way too many interests!
What world is there where a famous band member plays baseball and soccer?!
Surely, there's not any others, right?
Pro Wrestling!
I don't get it.  Where in the world would you find someone who...
Wait a minute... she only wants to do stuff she saw on TV.
But this is tough!
Trying to make all of that come true...
I've got it!
I'll make it all come true.
First up is, let's see.
The easy stuff.
Let's do some Pro Wrestling.
Huh?!  Pro Wrestling?!
What's your special move?
German Suplex!
Y-You can do a move like that?!
Can't you pick a hold, or something that seems remotely possible?
But I've always admired it.  The German Suplex.
Winning a match with that hold...
Don't say such violent stuff so cutely!
Gahhhhh... okay.
Fine, let's try it.
Seriously?
Sure.
Hell yeah!
Here I go...
Hey, you're stronger than I thought.
You can do it!
I wonder if it's too much for a girl like me...
No way, you almost did it.
You were super-close!
Huh, really?
Can I try one more time?
Um... for now, can we go somewhere with softer ground?
I'm gonna die.
You won't die!
No, that wasn't a joke.
Orya!
I'm not gonna make it.
Sorry, sorry!  I'll do it right next time!
This is seriously the last time, okay?
Oraaaa!
I'm going home.
Senpaiiiiii!
Listen, can you even do a bridge?
Of course I can!
Let's see it!
So this was the problem.
Because of this, I almost lost consciousness how many times?
We need to train you to do a bridge first.
Aww, that's boring.
Just do it!
Here I go...
Come on.  You can do it.
Come on, that's no good at all.
I've never done anything like this.
If you can't do this, you'll never do a German Suplex.
I'll try...
- A few hours later -
I'm... doing it.
You're shaking quite a bit, but...
Good enough.
Okay.  Here I go!
Bring it!
Whoa.  Her hands are wrapped completely around my stomach!
I can't escape!
This is perfect.  It's perfect!
German SUPLEX!
1...
2...
3...
Ding ding ding!
Match over!
I did it!
I really did it!
Banzai!
I did it! I  did it!  Yay!
How much longer do I have to do this?
Yeah!
UTW Presents:
Should we go for soccer next?
Study Building - Connecting Walkway
A 1-on-1 penalty kick works, right?
No way.
I've gotta take out 5 guys with my dribbling skills and then score.
You know, like Maradona.
Yeah, I know...
Alright, I've got it!
Leave it to me!
Hey, TK.  You know where Matsushita-godan is?
The way he is now...
He can't dance in my world.
Don't let me cry!
Is that so...
And?
Training in seclusion.
In the mountain.
Mountain training?
That's the last place I'd think of dancing.
So, he won't be back for a while?
Woooo!
Um, fine.  You'll do.
Can you help me get 4 players?
I'm keeping it a secret from Yuri, but...
Study Buildings: Building C, Boys Bathroom
I got this letter from Tenshi.
Even though you can't compete with one little girl,
hearing you call yourselves men is preposterous.
Oh.  "Preposterous", I'm surprised you could read that.
Has your stupidity been cured?
Naw, even idiots can read.
Hearing you call yourselves men
is preposterous.
I'll beat the girliness out
of you with sportsmanship.
I'll be waiting on the
Soccer Field after school.
- Tenshi
I'll beat the girliness out of you with sportsmanship?
I'll be waiting on the soccer field after school?
Tenshi?
What's that?!
I don't get it at all.
Did she really write that?
The current Tenshi is different from the old one.
Everything's all mixed up inside her, so this idiotic letter of challenge is the best she could do?
Like I can play along with something like that!
I'm reporting this to Yurippe.
I already said we need to keep this secret from her.
Why?
If we tell Yuri, it'll turn into another armed conflict.
Look, it says we'll settle this with sportsmanship.
She's saying we'll settle things fair and square through sports.
And besides, it's addressed to the men.
If we go and tattle to Yuri, that'll make us look even less manly.
You've got a point.
Well, should we go with us 5 then?
Kiss you!
We'd better!
Huh?
Soccer Field
What?
Hey, over there!
Someone's there.
It's Yui.
What's she doing?
So you came?
Kickoff!
She started kicking the ball.
Here I come, you fools!
I've got it!  The one who wrote that letter was her!
She was fed up with us always being such wimps.
That's why she's doing this!
Alright!  Let's protect the goal!
We can't lose this battle!
We men will win!
I don't really get it, but...
I've got it!
Don't mess with us!
I kiss you!
Hinata!  You're the Goalkeeper!
You've got it!
Out of the way, fools!
Hmph.  What lousy dribbling.
You're wide open!
Get ready!
Alright!  One down!
What's going on?
What are you doing, Noda?!
Number 2!  Take that!
Ref!  That was a red card just now!
Safe.
Who is that supposed to be?
I'm still coming, you guys!
I'm counting on you, TK, Otonashi!
Easy come, easy go!
Leave it to me!
Number 3!
Yeah!
Woo! Here we go-
Outta the way!
Hey, whose side are you on?!
The last one is... you, huh?
I'll steal this goal if it kills me!
Where'd your "sportsmanship" go?!
Like I care!
Prepare yourself!
Sure Kill Guillotine Murder Shot!
Does she want to get a goal or kill me?
There's too many jokes to be made here!
Oh!  It's a miracle!
Hinataaaaaa!
Huh?
It... went in?
I did it!
I did it, I did it!
I won against 5 people!
No way...
We... lost?
Against Yui all by herself?
Scrambled it, trouble down.
This sucks.
Let's keep this a secret for sure.
Yeah.
Well, she got the ball taken once, and she didn't really get past the goalkeeper, but...
Good enough!
Okay.
Alright, let's do the next one!
Baseball Field
Before we start, how far does it have to go to count as a home run?
Past the fence, of course.
Seriously?
Well alright, just hit it as hard as you can.
Wow, I hit it!
You have to do more than just hit it...
Look at the ball more carefully.
Hit it with the center of the bat.
You're hitting it from too high up!
That time was too low!
You can't hit it with your eyes shut!
No power...
Come on, try!
I'm trying!
Once more!
Huh?
You're too tired.  Your grip is weakening.
There's no point in continuing today, so let's call it quits for now.
Awwww.
Your shouts are getting louder, but your hits aren't at all!
I'm not done yet!
Aww, that was close!
Huh?
It's too dark to see the ball anymore today.
We'll go again tomorrow!
Awwww.
What are you guys up to?
You wanna play, too?
Some real baseball?
Full swing?
I haven't done one in a while.
Stuff like this...
Is nice every now and then.
What's wrong?
You're barely swinging at all!
Are you okay?
Lemme see your hands.
Uh-uh.
Let me see.
It's not surprising.
It was impossible from the start.
I'm giving up on this dream.
Don't give up...
Thanks for everything.
Why'd you do all this for me?
Because it's...
What you wanted to do!
You need to keep going 'til the end!
Dreaming of hitting a home run is more like a joke.
Even if I couldn't hit a home run, I was able to move my body so much!
This is more than enough.
Every day was like being in a club.  It was fun!
I told you, remember?
I couldn't move my body before.
So this was a ton of fun!
Then, they've all come true?
Come true?
What has?
The... the things you wanted to do when you couldn't move your body.
Oh...
I've still got one more thing.
What?
Marriage.
The ultimate happiness for a woman.
But...
I can't clean or do laundry.
Not even that.  I can't do anything alone.
I cause nothing but trouble.
Baggage like me...
Who would want to marry that?
God sure is cruel, huh?
I had all my happiness...
Taken away from me.
That's not... true.
Well then, Senpai...
Will you marry me?
That's...
I'll do it!
Hinata?
I'll marry you.
I'm... dead serious.
No way.
You don't even know the real me, Senpai.
kao wo awashitara
顔を合わしたら
Every time we met up,
I don't care how you were in reality, when you were alive...
kenka shite bakari
喧嘩してばかり
the two of us would always fight.
I'll marry you!
sore mo ii omoide datta
それもいい思い出だった
But that's still a wonderful memory to me.
No matter what handicaps you may have.
I can't walk.
I can't even stand.
kimi ga oshiete kureta n da mou kowakunai
きみが教えてくれたんだ　もう恐くない
You taught me that there's nothing
to be afraid of.
I said no matter what handicaps you have!
Even if you can't walk.  If you can't stand...
Even if you can't have children.
donna fujiyuu demo
どんな不自由でも
No matter how impaired I may be physically,
Even so, I'll marry you!
shiawase wa tsukameru
幸せは掴める
I can still hold onto happiness.
I'll always be by your side.
dakara
だから
So that's why...
The Yui I met here, she's not just a fake.
She's Yui.
No matter where you and I met...
hitori demo yuku yo
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll continue on alone
I would have still fallen for you.
tatoe tsurakute mo
例え辛くても
Even if it might be painful.
If by a one-in-a-million chance we meet again.
kimi to mita yume wa kanarazu motteku yo
きみと見た夢は　必ず持ってくよ
I'll definitely bring with me the
dream we saw together.
Even if you're in a body that won't move again.
I'll marry you.
kimi to ga yokatta
きみとがよかった
I wanted to be with you.
We won't meet.
Yui... she'll be stuck at home.
hokano dare demo nai
ほかの誰でもない
Not with anybody else
I'll... play baseball.
demo mezameta asa
でも目覚めた朝
But when I woke in the morning...
One day, bam, I'll break your house's window.
kimi wa inai n da ne
きみは居ないんだね
You were gone.
When I go to find the ball, you'll be there.
That's how we'll meet.
After we get to talking, we'll start to see that we're a match.
I'll start going to your house every day.
I'll start learning to care for you.
How does that sound?
Yeah...
zutto asondereru
ずっと遊んでれる
I always felt like
Hey, when that time comes...
sonna ki ga shiteta
そんな気がしてた
You were only humoring me.
The one who always cared for me alone.
Who tried so hard for me...
ki ga shiteita dake
気がしていただけ
But it was just a feeling.
My mom.
Take care of her too, okay?
wakatteru
わかってる
Please understand that.
Leave it to me.
umarete kita koto mou koukai wa shinai
生まれてきたこともう後悔はしない
I don't regret being born anymore.
I'm so happy.
matsuri no ato mitai
祭りの後みたい
It's like the end of a carnival
samishii kedo soro soro ikou
寂しいけどそろそろ行こう
It's a little sad, but it's time to go.
dokomademo yuku yo
どこまでもゆくよ
I'll go any distance
koko de shitta koto
ここで知ったこと
with the things I learned here.
shiawase to iu yume wo kanaete miseru yo
幸せという夢を叶えてみせるよ
The dream called happiness, I'll
grant it for sure.
kimi to hanaretemo donna ni tooku nattemo
きみと離れても　どんなに遠くなっても
Even if I'm separated from you, no
matter how far away you are...
atarashii asa ni atashi wa ikiru yo
新しい朝に　あたしは生きるよ
I'll be living in a new morning.
megutte nagarete
巡って流れて
As the ebb and flow
toki wa utsuroi da
時は移ろいだ
Of time begins to change
You're okay with that?
mou nani ga atta ka
もう何があったか
I can't remember
Of course.
omoidasenai kedo
思い出せないけど
What happened before anymore
What are you gonna do now?
me wo tojite mireba
目を閉じてみれば
But when I close my eyes
I'll stick around 'til the end.
dare ka no waraigoe
誰かの笑い声
I can hear someone softly laughing
There's still plenty of people for me to worry about here.
naze ka sore ga ima
なぜかそれが今
For some reason right now
I see...
ichiban no takaramono
一番の宝物
That's my greatest treasure in the world.
What did I just cut?
A shadow?
You need to clarify that a little.
I can't explain any better than to say it was a shadow.
Noda-san just rushed here and defeated it.
If Ooyama-san had been left alone, it would have been dangerous.
Dangerous?
What was it?
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 216] Irregularities have begun to occur in this world.
[c 39]  Did you do something again?!
[c 175] For him to lose his glasses is unthinkable.
[c 170] I tried to help!
[c 160] Is this a nightmare?
[c 141] I don't need reinforcements!
[c 177] This is way too irregular...
[c 46] Something's coming in! Otonashi-san!
[c 144] Dancing in the shadow!
[c 211] isn't getting erased by Tenshi the better alternative?
[c 192] You'll disappear!
[c 178] What in the world is going on?
[c 207] Damn it!
[c 280] Yurippe!
PLACEHOLDER
[c 274] I'll be waiting!
[c 280] Then, let's meet again if we can.