The only one we need
alive is Mustang...
Kill the rest.
[GUNSHOT]
[MORE GUNSHOTS]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT IN PAIN]
[HEAD SOLDIER WINCES]
[GUN COCKS]
You told them to kill
everyone except Mustang...
So that was a direct order to
kill the Fuhrer's wife then?
[BRADLEY'S WIFE SHUDDERING]
[ROY THINKING]
I hate that my
suspicions were correct.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
Does this mean...
Has my husband...
Has our country
betrayed him?
Or is it...
Has my husband
chosen to abandon me?
I don't know...
but... no matter
which one...
I promise that we'll
protect your life.
[ROY]
And once the dust
has settled...
you can be the one to
tell our country...
that we were
always on their side.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE SHUDDERING]
Here comes
their backup...!
Let's move!
We're sparing
your lives, soldier.
Be glad that we're
not from Briggs...
This would
be a kill shot.
What?
[GUNSHOT]
[HEAD SOLDIER SCREAMS]
Colonel...
It's been a while.
Yeah... good work...
I was expecting Grumman.
He's sorting out
the wreckage...
And while we're
already on that topic...
Has Mrs. Bradley
been informed yet?
No... It'll slow us down
too much if she passes out.
They sent in a
whole battalion...
You sure are
popular, Colonel.
[ROY]
I like to think so.
[SOLDIERS YELLING]
[CREMIN]
Why the hell aren't
they dead yet?!
It can't be that hard...
They've only got five men!
[COMMUNICATION SOLDIER]
Their numbers
have increased...!
They appear to have a full
platoon of soldiers now, sir!
[CREMIN GROWLS]
How many have
we lost so far?
We have fifty-nine men
injured, zero casualties.
Uh... Zero?
[SOLDIERS YELLING]
[EXPLOSION]
Damn it!
Are you okay?
[CENTRAL SOLDIER B]
Yeah... I think so.
So this Flame Alchemist
we're up against...
I thought he was supposed to be
some big war hero in Ishval?
Yeah, he
doesn't really seem
to live up to his
legend, does he...?
Good point...
All of his explosions
have been pretty tame.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER D]
Huh...?
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[CENTRAL SOLDIERS YELLING]
Hey, Jess...! Parky!
Damn... That
blew my eardrum!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER E]
What's the toll?
Five wounded,
but none dead.
It's a miracle
no one's been killed so far.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER E GASPS]
They've got
the Hero of Ishval
and the Hawk's Eye
on their side...
We should have corpses
piling up high... Unless!
[GUNSHOT]
[CENTRAL SOLDIER E SCREAMS]
[CENTRAL SOLDIER E]
There's my answer...!
No doubt about it!
[CREMIN]
What do you mean
they're not killing anyone?!
Well... We have a high
number of wounded,
but not
a single fatality.
At last check, none of those
injuries were even critical.
[CREMIN]
They're mocking us.
Send in Dimitri
and Kim Squad...!
I want their dead bodies
stacked in front of me!
And I want it done now!
[FOX]
They still haven't
apprehended Mustang...?
What the hell has General
Cremin been doing over there?
[GARDNER]
They're systematically
whittling down our forces...
and they aren't even
killing our men to do it.
[FOX]
There's no way they
can outlast our numbers
while keeping this up.
Colonel Mustang
must've gone soft.
Obviously... He can't
possibly think this will work.
If there's one thing
softer than Mustang...
it's the men under
your command...
You might as well
send in children.
Excuse me?
[OLIVIER]
Central Command was nearly iced
over by a single dissident...
that doesn't inspire too much
confidence in your troops...
Central has never endured
a full scale assault...
At least not by a large,
organized enemy force.
So then... Your men are
lacking in proper experience...
Making their defense
a joke... Simply laughable.
How about this...
Why don't you let me step in
and take command
of a battalion?
[FOX]
Have you forgotten why
you're here, Armstrong?
Your leadership skills
have nothing to do
with your presence
in this office...
You are being held here as
a detainee and nothing more.
I'm aware of your
troops' undying loyalty
to you as their commander...
Holding you here as our
prisoner helps to ensure
that the soldiers of Briggs
won't take it upon themselves
to stage a coup d'etat.
[OLIVIER LAUGHS LOUDLY]
[OLIVIER]
You don't understand
a single thing about
the resolve of my troops!
Your plan is useless...
The only law the
men of Briggs know
is survival
of the fittest...
They know to abandon me if
confronted with a crisis.
Even if you were to
murder me in cold blood...
My troops would simply write
me off for being too weak...
They don't need me...
Those men can act
as their own force...
That's the strength
of the Briggs army.
Don't even begin to assume
that you know the
soldiers I've trained!
[BUCCANEER]
Colonel Mustang is
engaged in combat
in the industrial district...
The enemy is focused
on his activities.
[LOUD CLANG SOUND]
Alright... It's time to
kiss this cellar goodbye...
Let's tear the throats out
of any spineless fool
that tries to
get in our way!
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[FOX GASPS]
And here they come...
Every single one of my men
is capable of defeating
a grizzly bear in combat.
I wonder if your dolls
are as strong as my men...
What do you think?
[GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIER 11 YELLS]
Damn!
[SOLDIER 13 YELLS]
[GUNFIRE]
[CENTRAL OFFICER 1]
More troops...? But how?
That's impossible!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER H]
They just materialized
out of nowhere!
[CENTRAL OFFICER 1]
Well, are they using
sorcery or something...?
Find out
what's going on!
What's their
head count?
We're not sure...
Although... Going
by their gear...
it looks like they're
from the North.
They're from Briggs?
[KNIFE SLICES]
[GUNFIRE]
[CHARLIE]
The Armstrong mansion?
[ROY]
Yeah... We used renovation
trucks to sneak everyone in
and hid the entire
battalion there.
Are you serious?
Just how big is this mansion?
[FABIO]
Charlie,
I need more ammo!
Hate to say it,
but I'm out too.
What do we do now...?
Where the hell is
that supply unit...?
Ya think they
were captured?
Listen, guys...
If it comes down to it,
just leave me behind.
[CHARLIE AND FABIO]
Roger that!
You could at least pretend
like you're willing
to die by my side.
[CHARLIE]
I'm fighting to live, not die.
[FABIO]
And I'd rather die
by my wife's side.
[ROY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Yeah... Figures.
[EXPLOSION]
[SOLDIERS COUGHING]
[CENTRAL SOLDIER J]
They are... They're hardly
using their guns to fight back.
They might be
out of ammunition.
Then it's time for
us to move in...!
Round up all of the men
that we have left!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER K YELLS]
[HAWKEYE GASPS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Yoo-hoo, Riza!
[HAWKEYE]
It's about time, Rebecca!
I know, sorry...!
But I think you'll find
it was worth the wait.
I've got all
sorts of goodies!
[GROUP GASPS]
[CHARLIE]
Awesome!
[DAMIANO]
I think we're set on
munitions now, guys!
[FABIO]
You're a goddess,
Rebecca, I love you!
[REBECCA]
Hey, zip it...!
You're not allowed to flirt with
me unless you've got money!
Here ya go.
[ROY]
Oh... Thank you.
It's good to see
you, Colonel...
It's been a long time, huh?
Hmm...?
Second Lieutenant Maria Ross...
Returning to active duty
without permission, sir!
[GUNFIRE]
I'm surprised they
haven't charged in by now.
Well, we do have the Flame
Alchemist backing us up.
So I really doubt they
wanna take any risks.
Little do they know,
the Colonel's restraining
himself since we're in the city.
Aw, jeez... I came all the way
to Central to find a good man,
but you're all just
a bunch of sissies!
[BOMB FIRES]
[SOLDIERS GASP]
[TEAR-GAS BOMB EXPLODES]
[SOLDIERS COUGHING]
[SOLDIERS YELL]
[SOLDIER 16]
Damn it!
[GUNFIRE]
They're Xingese
tear-gas bombs...
With extra pepper spray.
So you got those
things in Xing...?
Is that where all of
this stuff is from?
I didn't know you were
involved in this...
Not that I'm complaining...
But I do have to ask...
Where did you procure
all these weapons?
And who did you go
through to get them?
You asked who...?
I'll let him tell you.
Hmm...?
All set!
Go ahead.
[ROY THINKING]
Is it some Xingese official?
This is Colonel Roy
Mustang speaking...
I'm honored to
have your support...
[HAVOC]
Man, whose ass do
you think you're kissing?
I'd prefer it if we kept
things casual... Colonel.
Over eighty years
in business...
we offer everything
you could possibly need...
from underwear to arms and
we're just a phone call away...
This is Havoc's, your
neighborhood general store.
Jean Havoc?!
[FUERY GASPS]
So... Who do I
send the bill to?
The office
of the Fuhrer...
And start a tab.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SIRENS WAILING]
There's smoke rising
from within the city...
and I can faintly
hear a siren as well.
[ED]
I think it's safe
to say the Colonel
and the Briggs troops
have made their move.
The city's gotta be in
complete chaos by now.
I guess we
should get going.
Yeah...
I do have a countermeasure for
his transmutation circle...
but I'd rather prevent him
from activating it
in the first place.
He might have gotten
too big for his old one,
but he's still
inside a flask...
And if we destroy
his container...
[HOHENHEIM]
We might be
able to kill him...
And not only that,
we might be able
to free all of the souls that
he has trapped inside of him.
Well, how do we
find the bastard then?
We can use the same tunnel
that May and I discovered.
It's guarded by a pack
of vicious chimeras...
but we should be
able to handle them.
[DARIUS]
Can you watch
things here, Heinkel?
Of course...
I owe you one.
Don't mention it...
And you just steer clear
of the military, Doc.
Yoki!
[YOKI SHOUTS]
I think you should
stay behind, as well.
Fine with me...
Hey, Al.
[AL]
What is it, Brother?
We're heading out now...
And we're gonna kick
that bearded bastard's ass.
[AL]
Just be careful.
Right.
[METAL CLANGING]
The city is in complete
mayhem right now.
[ENVY]
All the more reason
we should hurry.
Father's about to reveal
the secret of immortality...
And we don't want
to be late for that.
And we won't be!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
I want this area
cordoned off...
Mustang's squad will
likely be headed here...
Keep them out!
[SIRENS WAILING]
[FOX]
Call off your
soldiers, right now!
You stripped me
of my command
of the Briggs
soldiers, remember?
Why you...
Do you really think you
can get away with this?
I'd like to ask you
the same question
for what you're doing...
This Father guy must've
told you his plans...
All that he intends to sacrifice
and what he gets from it.
Sure. Of course
he told me...
The select few of us
that he's chosen
will ascend to even
greater heights...
And the nation of Amestris
will change the world...!
All of the sacrifices made are
an unavoidable part of it...!
Why don't you
understand that?!
[OLIVIER SIGHS]
You bastards are
beyond hopeless.
What?
[FOX SCREAMS]
You scum sit back and
safely watch the battlefield
as if it were some kind
of spectator sport...
You don't know anything
about sacrifice
and yet you're the first
to talk about its necessity.
You're betraying
your country!
You think so...?
Our country could very
well regard me as a hero
once this is all
over... However...
I'm still not as merciful as
our celebrated "Hero of Ishval."
No! Wait!
[GUNSHOT]
What the?!
[FOX SCREAMING]
[CENTRAL SOLDIER L]
He's dead!
[FOX SCREAMING]
[SIREN WAILING]
Hey, Major!
Major Armstrong!
What are you
doing here, Sergeant?
Isn't this supposed
to be your day off?
I saw the smoke
from my house...
What's going on
down here, Major?
Colonel Mustang and
his former subordinates
have chosen the path
of dissidence.
They're attempting
to flee with
the Fuhrer's wife
as their hostage.
What?!
That devious coward...!
First he murdered
Lieutenant Ross
and now he's kidnapped
the Fuhrer's Wife...?!
The man has got
to be pure evil!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER N]
Excuse me, sir!
Major, I have just
received word that
General Armstrong
shot and killed
General Gardner at
Central Command.
[ARMSTRONG]
She killed him?!
Hmm...
[FU THINKING]
Things are happening quicker
than I expected them to...
I need to find the young
Lord soon... But how...?
It's impossible to trace him
with this enormous presence
underground interfering...
Wait...
It feels like the
presence has somehow
tripled in size
since yesterday.
[LOUD METALLIC CLANGING]
[RAT SCREECHES]
[DOG BARKS]
[LOUD METALLIC CLANGING]
[ED]
Not getting in there.
The military's got it
completely blocked off...
So much for that.
And we don't have enough men
to force our way through.
[ED GASPS]
Wait...! There's another
way we can get in!
The Third Laboratory...!
That's how Al and the
Colonel snuck underground
when they fought Lust.
They've only got three
MPs guarding the entrance.
Now that's a number
I'm comfortable with.
No... This is
perfect for me to
throw some weight
around and use my title.
Help me, please!
[MP 1]
Huh...?
My name's Edward Elric...
I'm a State Alchemist.
Wait. What was that?
You said you're a
State Alchemist?
I need you to help me...!
Scar is trying to kill me!
That guy's on
the wanted list!
Hands up!
[ED LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
That was a mean
thing to do.
Oh, shut up...
C'mon.
[LAB DOCTORS GASP]
Pardon us,
coming through.
It was around
here somewhere.
Found it!
Should we split
into two groups?
Sounds good.
I'll take a team this way...
And then you and Scar can
lead a team the other way.
Whaaaat?!
Why do I have
to go with him?!
[HOHENHEIM]
It's best to divide the groups
based on their skill in alchemy.
Now remember,
you told me that
he was somehow able to
turn off your alchemy...
Scar was still
capable of using his,
but you were
rendered helpless.
Alright. I guess that means
these two are together...
So who are you taking?
My alchemy is a little unique
so I'll be fine on my own...
On second thought...
[LAN FAN GASPS]
It wouldn't be a bad
idea to have a bodyguard,
so I might as well take
the young lady with me.
If any of us
discover the enemy,
do everything you
can to destroy him.
[GERSO]
Roger that.
Are you sure that
you're gonna be okay
with just
the two of you?
Of course,
I prefer it this way...
I'd rather keep the young
lady's company for myself
than share her
with the lot of you.
[ZAMPANO STAMMERS]
Pervy old man.
Let's go.
[ED SIGHS]
So, you're
getting desperate
to search for the Xingese
prince, aren't you?
[LAN FAN GASPS]
Go find him.
But... I...
You don't need
to worry about us.
You care deeply
about him, don't you?
Be careful...
And thank you.
[LOCK CLICKS OPEN]
[HARRIS]
What a pathetic
excuse for an army...!
They can't even handle those
Briggs Mountain monkeys.
[RESEARCHER 1]
Please, sir, don't...!
We still haven't finished
the soul-bonding tests!
Shut up...! When else
are we gonna use them?
[HARRIS GRUNTS]
[MACHINE TURNS ON]
This is the exact
kind of situation
we worked so hard
to make them for!
Go! Now...!
Teach those
treacherous rebels a lesson!
[DUMMIES SCREAM]
[LAN FAN GASPS]
[MAY CHANG GASPS]
[NARRATOR]
Fueled by the anguished
souls of the dead,
inhuman soldiers stalk
the halls of Central Command,
ravenous with rage.
Although their figures
are a terrifying sight,
the true terror lies within the
madness of their tortured souls.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode 51:
The Immortal Legion.
Who will become a killer...
and who will be killed?