I found it. The most important thing is...
Was it fun?
Tricking me... Sucking up to him...
I don't want to run anymore.
You can't run from your past.
The reason you're worrying is
because of your past, right?
Blame Kida Masaomi for ordering this!
The Dollars are going to disappear.
Russian Sushi!
It's Russian Sushi!
It's good!
It's cheap!
What do you think, mister?
President?
Hello, this is Russian Sushi.
I didn't know who to call,
so I decided to call you.
What are you talking about?
I wanted to tell you what he's thinking.
Namie-san, what do you call this?
Oute?
Checkmate?
Maybe Atari?
Hey!
What? She isn't here?
Complicated
and Confused
What do we do?
The yellows are still beating people up.
I heard that guy named Horada's behind it.
What's Kida doing?
Dunno.
Horada... You mean that Horada?
Which Horada?
This is awful.
Doubts are swirling around in my brain.
Did Mikado have the Dollars act,
while he knew everything?
Was Anri working with him?
Or was she using him?
They're both awful.
But I'm the worst, the way I'm imagining this.
What do I do?
Where do I go?
There's nowhere for me to go.
Come in.
I know why you're here.
I thought that was the only way to end this.
I thought that was the most
Dollars-like way to settle it.
I think being without any kind
of form defines the Dollars.
Now we're invisible again.
I think the Slasher and the
Yellow Scarves will stop now.
I've found what's important.
I think this is for the best.
I understand.
But that's not why I'm here today.
Hello?
Hey, it's me, Horada.
What? Did something happen?
You know,
you don't need to come around anymore.
You're fired. Fired from
the position of general.
Fired, fired!
What are you talking about?
Ryuugamine Mikado-kun, was it?
Wasn't that your friend's name?
What a shock.
The leader of the Dollars was
friends with our gang's head-
Wait!
Who told you-
Who cares?
Anyway, I can't believe you tricked us all.
Everyone's here, and they're
all lookin' shocked.
What are you going to do?
Go after the Dollar's head.
Everyone can't wait to kick some ass.
You've got an execution order
on your head, too.
You won't be able to walk around
in Ikebukuro anymore.
Bye.
Mikado...
Do you like Sonohara Anri?
Is Kida Masaomi your best friend?
What do you mean?
Maruyama Ou
The number you have dialed
is out of service...
This is an answering machine service...
Yes?
Yo.
Oh, shock! What happened to you?
Eh, you know...
I got shot.
Parts of your leg and abdomen muscles
are badly damaged.
Actually, why are you walking
around like this?
Why?
'Cause I can. Why else?
Heiwajima-san, what are you doing here?
Oh, man...
Who were you again?
Anri-chan.
Anri-chan, excuse us for a minute.
What happened?
Well, at first, I thought I'd
slipped in the rain.
And then there was all this blood
from my stomach and my leg.
So I realized I'd been shot.
And then I was gonna kill
the guys who shot me,
but they ran off.
Idiot, huh?
Want to die?
I apologize from the bottom of my heart!
Fix me up, already.
I've gotta go kill them.
That's impossible!
I'm gonna kill 'em!
The guys who shot me and this
Kida Masaomi who ordered them to.
The number you have dialed
is out of service...
My suspicions about Anri and
Mikado had lessened.
If the Yellow Scarves attacked Mikado...
Or kidnapped Anri to lure him out...
Why couldn't I move then?
What made me hesitate?
What was I afraid of?
You can't get away.
The past will follow you,
wherever you go.
No... That can't be.
It's all true.
Masaomi... Does Masaomi know about me?
I don't know.
But when he was screaming at Anri-chan,
he wasn't acting normal.
It's possible he knows that you're
the founder of the Dollars.
No way... Who told him?
I know an information broker who
loves to see people suffer.
You started the Dollars.
Do what you want.
But your decision to make them disappear
won't change anything for you three.
Why didn't the two of them tell me?
Why didn't you?
Well, I thought the Dollars were my problem.
They're the same.
What you see isn't necessarily reality.
Everyone has secrets,
things they feel that they can't tell anyone.
There's no such thing as a normal person.
So don't be afraid.
Face Anri-chan, Kida-kun,
and your own reality.
If you love her, tell her
everything about yourself.
Solve your problems, not those of the Slasher,
the Dollars, or the Yellow Scarves!
Hello?
Celty?
I'm running right now.
Shizuo was shot with a handgun.
Anri-chan ran out of the place.
Um, well, that wasn't why she left...
It was Kida Masaomi who
supposedly gave the order.
I can't run anymore...
Sorry...
I just can't get it all straight.
She's fast...
Anri-chan's so fast!
Hey, Kida.
What's wrong?
You look pale.
Hungry again?
Simon.
Kida, you look unwell.
That's strange.
Hey, Simon.
I give it five stars.
Heck, I'd give it an entire galaxy's worth.
Russian Sushi was always so good!
Are you going to go fight?
Or are you gonna kill someone,
or are they gonna kill you?
What? Why are you talking like that?
You think you're psychic or something?
Did Izaya start something again?
That's not it.
Killing, being killed...
It's not good.
Where I used to fight meant you got killed.
Kida-san, your eyes look like those
of someone ready to die.
Simon...
No, this is Ikebukuro,
not my town.
It's warm; people here will give you food,
even if you're homeless;
able to sleep without drinking vodka;
and don't have to die.
There's no need for kids like you to kill!
I'm sorry. I have to go...
Kida...
Someone...
Anyone in the Yellow Scarves...
Someone!
There's no one here.
No one...
Which means...
Interesting.
Truly interesting!
Three friends, each with their own secrets.
Coincidence and just a few
evil deeds brought them
to learn each other's secrets,
in an almost ideal way!
Well, most of those evil deeds were mine.
But yeah, the guy they're up against
is kind of a boring loser.
Maybe I should've chosen
someone better for that part.
What do you think, Namie-san?
Are you guys OK with the
Yellow Scarves this way?!
Listen! We're not like the Dollars,
just a bunch of random people.
We've got a unified power they lack.
The Dollars leader even issued
an order disbanding them,
but don't be fooled!
Obviously, it's just a stupid trick!
We need to get them all!
If we take out the Dollars, we can control
not just Ikebukuro but Tokyo, as well.
Got it?
Imagine!
Everyone, everyone, everyone in
the whole city will obey us!
That damned Heiwajima Shizuo is gone.
The only ones left in the Dollars who aren't
cowering in fear are Kadota's gang.
We'll beat the crap out of them, and then
go after their leader, Ryuugamine!
And then there'll be nothing for us to fear!
So let's head out to Ikebukuro!
Was that really a good idea?
Killing someone? Really?
It was the right thing to do.
The right thing...
Without Heiwajima Shizuo,
there's nothing to be scared of.
The police will destroy us!
If we have to, we'll say it
was a Dollars civil war.
That's not gonna work!
Shut up!
It will!
It'll go fine!
Horada-san.
It'll go fine...
It has to.
The cops?
The cops here already?
The hell are you doing here?
Oh, Celty!
Want sushi again?
I'm looking for Kida Masaomi
and Sonohara Anri.
Have you seen them?
I saw Kida.
He looked really serious.
Probably a fight...
I couldn't stop him.
Do you know where he went?
I haven't seen the yellow guys at all today.
I'm sure he's with them.
All right.
Thanks.
Save him.
Are you prepared to accept any
ugly thing you may see?
Yes.
What's going on here?
I don't see any familiar faces here.
Can't get 'em on their cells, either.
You didn't...
Well, all those I thought wouldn't
want me at the top...
They're all recovering from a surprise
hit by some weirdos last night.
Scary!
Gotta be the Dollars.
Right, guys?
You bastard!
You're an idiot, coming here,
like a moth to the flame.
Maybe I'll do it like Izumii-san,
break your leg and be like, "Quiz time!"
What did you say?
Did you say Izumii?
And then, yeah...
The Yellow Scarves have done a
few too many bad things.
I think it's time to change
the name and color.
Yeah. A lighter color,
just like your pale face.
You...
No... You can't all...
Can't be!
You finally realized?
Yeah, that's right.
They're Blue Square,
the guys you hate.
And we're not just a bunch of losers,
keeping a dead group alive.
We've taken over the Yellow Scarves.
Really...
The minute we took off the blue cloth and
asked to join, you let us in readily.
What's wrong?
You ready to get on your knees and beg?
Nah, I actually feel better.
Now that I'm fired from the Yellow Scarves,
I'm just a high schooler who likes to hit on girls.
Just a loser, who couldn't
save the girl he loved.
Like an idiot, I thought I could turn away from
my past and be a normal student.
That's why I came here.
I'm... I'm just Kida Masaomi.
That's why I came here!
At some point, the past
following me moved ahead.
You can't get away.
Not ever, ever, ever, ever...
A person's past and memories are
very lonely things.
So now it's my turn to chase the past.
I hear the past gets lonely very easily.
So I need to catch up to it.
What the hell are you talking
about, you idiot?
I didn't just come here ready to die.
I was ready to kill.
Yeah...
To kill you, to be exact.
I'll say it as many times as I want.
That's why I'm here.
And I won't let anyone deny me that!
What are you doing?
Get this moron!
What made me hesitate?
It's simple.
H-Hey... He's just one guy!
What's wrong with you people?
I'm me.
That's all it ever was.
Saki... I'm not scared anymore.
I'm going to catch up to my past a little more.
Do something!
Y-You useless idiots!
Oh, right.
What? Don't scare me, damn it!
I'm going to kill you for real!
The hell you think you're doing?
Um, well, looks like Mother would
be sad if you killed him.
So I acted on my own, yes...
Um, I can tell...
I'm sorry.
Mother's almost here.
Kida-kun!
Anri...
Why?
Masaomi!
Mikado...
Ryuugamine-kun, why?
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Selfless Devotion
I still think it's strange.
I had an experience that would change my life.
A very strange one, but one you could find anywhere.
Next time:
Selfless Devotion