FREE STUDY
Are you really going to go help her?
Why?
It's not right.
She didn't do anything.
Why are they doing this to her?
Bullies don't need a good reason to bully.
If they don't like your attitude,
that's all it takes.
But she looked at me.
She wanted my help.
That's because
we were the only ones there.
If you go, I won't be able to help you.
You stop them and they'll target you next.
Then what about her?
I don't know.
Either she makes it through somehow
or stops coming to school.
Or a teacher notices and stops it.
You're saying to ignore it until then?
Why are you always like this?
You're so irritating.
I've had enough of this.
I've also had enough!
I get what you're saying, Hina.
But it's not right.
The people who are in the wrong
can't just get away with it.
I can't ignore it.
A dream...
Was I supposed to go to the agency today?
Crap, I overslept.
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
I'll be blunt. We haven't
even reached half our projection.
That makes sense.
The video barely has any views.
Of course our subscriber count
hasn't grown.
What do you think about this, Ms. Miura?
The biggest issue is that you have more
exposure and recognition than before.
You also have a respectable number
of searches.
If you're being searched this much,
the song should have more traction.
But it doesn't.
It's the agency's responsibility.
Our promotion must be failing.
I'm sorry.
Please, that's not what I'm say...
In an age of self-publication,
talent agencies can't fall behind.
If we offer no benefits to artists,
they would leave us, right?
Yeah.
Please give me more time.
I'll think of a plan.
I've never seen Ms. Miura like that.
She did seem different.
Where's Momoka?
She said, "Sorry, gotta go."
What? She left?
I thought we were practicing later today.
Let's not today.
I agree.
Huh?
Momoka must have realized it.
I mean, obviously.
- Realized what?
- You're so slow.
- What?
- You heard what Ms. Miura said.
Our name's getting out there,
but not our song.
That means...
The song is the problem.
What?!
Ms. Miura realized
Momoka was going to say that,
so she was stopping her from saying it.
Why?
Because it would hurt Momoka's feelings.
No! Just give it time!
It's such a great song!
Everyone said so!
Ms. Miura and Mr. Nakata too!
Nobody would struggle
if that was enough to make a hit.
Still!
Like they say, Van Gogh only sold
one painting while he was alive.
But...
Ultimately,
people are influenced by trends.
They'll watch anything
if everyone says it's good.
And they won't watch something
nobody else is.
But that's...
It's true, right?
If there are videos about the same game,
would you watch the one
with 5,000 views or a million?
Stop that.
It's embarrassing.
I know that.
"The band that
picked a fight they couldn't win."
"I hate how they're acting like
they're all that."
"Go away, losers!"
Shut up!
Screw you,
I bet you didn't even listen to us!
And we're not losing to you!
It's got nothing to do with you all!
Calm down, calm down...
For the battle of the bands,
Diamond Dust sold out their show.
I mean, of course.
A follow request?
From Hina?
What?! It's a verified account.
Yo.
Made you look, dummy.
Long time no see.
You don't need a disguise?
I'm not that famous.
You still like these?
Yeah. We used to get these often
on our way home, didn't we?
I'll pay.
No, it's my treat.
- What do you want?
- Nothing.
I just figured you had the wrong idea.
What?
I didn't become Diamond Dust's
singer on purpose.
I told you I was auditioning.
Oh wait, that was after stopped talking.
And you stopped coming to school.
Did you come to brag?
That this happened
because I didn't listen to you?
That it wouldn't have come to this
if I only listened?
Correct.
...is what I'd like to say,
but that's not all.
- Your tickets aren't selling.
- That doesn't concern you.
I think it does.
We're playing a show together.
No, we aren't!
Your agent, Ms. Miura, came to us to talk.
Asking if we could do anything.
Ms. Miura did?
She asked if we would play both days
since we'd be able to sell tickets
without a problem.
She said you haven't sold enough
to fill 30% of the venue.
Our schedule's free, so it basically
comes down to our decision.
But I figured I'd get your opinion first.
So?
Whatever.
Does that mean not to do it?
Or are you saying you're grateful?
Can you hear that?
This is what it means to be a hit.
It's important.
Even crucial.
How about you acknowledge it already?
That you were wrong.
That I was right.
That you should've listened.
I thought you were going to bare it all.
Just admit you were wrong,
and I'll help you as much as you want.
I'm leaving!
Money!
Thanks for the popcorn!
Hello!
Sorry to call you.
It's fine.
What is it?
Well, like I told everyone else...
D-D asked if we could play on both days
for the battle of the bands.
They want to play
for the same crowd against us.
Ms. Miura contacted you about that, right?
- Yes, what about it?
- Nothing.
What do you think, Nina?
What about all of you?
Well, I mean...
We didn't have a chance before, but
this would make things a bit more even.
But then, the competition wouldn't matter.
D-D would get credit
for the crowd that comes.
Isn't that the same as
us admitting defeat now?
So are you against it?
Yes, I am.
Here we go.
I get where you're coming from...
No! There's no way I'll agree!
Think of everything we went through!
Momoka's not wrong.
Our whole point was to prove that
her songs can reach people!
We came this far because we believed that.
But reality won't let us.
We haven't even sold enough tickets
to fill 30% of the venue.
That's worse than before the agency.
So what?
Are you gonna take responsibility then?
Do you know how much money this costs?
Money?
Not just the venue.
We also made merchandise to sell
and marketing isn't free either.
We need to reduce our losses
as much as we can.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Does this mean
you'll bow your head to D-D too?
That's not what we're doing.
Yeah, we're just taking them up
on their offer.
We are bowing to them!
Do you really think D-D
made that offer to us?
What do you mean?
It's obvious.
Ms. Miura bowed her head and begged them.
To help us by playing with us.
Really? How do you know that?
Hina came to tell me
and told me to admit that I was wrong.
Then they'd help us as much as we wanted.
But I don't want to!
Because...
I wasn't wrong!
Nina.
So don't bow your heads to them!
Don't reject the person I was!
Money, responsibility, popularity!
I know that already!
I'm so mad and frustrated!
Just shut up already!
- Nina!
You okay?
Why am I so weak?
Did they do this to you?
I told you I can't help you.
Was what I did that upsetting for you?
You know, every time we talked,
I got this feeling
that you have this sense of justice
that you flaunt and hurt everyone with.
You make us feel like we're the bad guys.
You haven't talked since?
Right.
Well, that certainly sounds like you.
What happened to the girl
who was being bullied?
Funny thing is, she started bullying me
with her former bullies not long after.
Then she'd tell me privately
to apologize to them.
That they'd probably forgive me,
and I wouldn't have to go through this.
What the hell?
But she was shaking.
She was scared of them.
But you saved her.
She owes you, right?
So that's why you stopped going to school.
Yes.
Because you weren't wrong, huh?
But you were wrong!
You were clearly wrong!
Tomo...
Look at the results!
That Hina girl was obviously right!
But!
But...
I think that's why I was drawn to you.
I like your voice.
Rupa, Momoka, and Subaru, too, probably.
Tomo!
- Stop!
- Aw, come on!
I don't like these things!
We have our decision.
But Ms. Miura worked hard on this deal.
We need to take responsibility.
Seriously?
But I guess I knew it would turn out
this way from the beginning.
It's Nina after all.
Yeah, it is.
So mean.
You decline?
Yes, we're sorry.
They said they want to do
a proper battle of the bands.
We know, but it would look like
we're getting saved by them.
Even so, the audience would...
RESIGNATION
It's what we all decided.
We also know
how selfish of a decision this is,
and the loss to the agency
isn't insignificant.
Please let us know the cost
for this event.
I can't promise when,
but we will pay it back, so please.
Please.
Please raise your heads.
Please tell me why.
I got a message.
Hina from D-D contacted me directly.
I was happy to hear about your dedication,
that you would do this much when
I asked to take part in this competition.
And I do feel guilty about
turning this down despite everything.
I'm sorry for being selfish!
Honestly, I knew
it would go against your wishes.
Ms. Miura.
I'm a bad manager.
Don't get the wrong idea.
The agency and I will do something
about the money.
This is exactly why
I wanted to work with you.
Please let me help you one last time.
You're quitting?
Yes.
- You're changing agencies?
- No, we'll continue on our own.
Were you dissatisfied?
No.
It's just what we decided.
That's all.
You sound so naive.
Come back here
if you're still around in ten years.
I'll work for you for free.
Okay, thank you, Mr. Nakata!
Let's grab a beef bowl.
I bet you just want to drink.
Of course not.
You're not convincing.
This is where we first met you.
Yeah.
Beni-shoga, huh?
Want to make an oath on it?
It's an important name to the two of you,
so an oath just as important.
What oath are we making?
The five of us will stick together,
and we'll never quit.
I guess we have to eat here then.
I like it.
Just one drink.
Momoka!
I love this city.
I love this city where I met
lifelong friends I can laugh and cry with.
Kawasaki, right?
Yes!
Call the game, we lost.
Like four consecutive losses
in the Japan series.
No miracle, huh?
Of course not.
This isn't a soap opera.
You watch soap operas?
The only drama I watch
is Detective Granny!
Are you picking a fight?
But we knew this would happen.
That things were stacked against us,
and it wouldn't be easy.
You're one to talk.
You're the one who was the most clueless.
You got me there.
That's why you can say you weren't wrong.
Momoka.
D-D had their show last night,
so we got more comments.
You're the one who said not to look!
Now, now.
Let's see.
"I like this."
"Why do they get so much hate?"
"Shut up, songs aren't about numbers."
"It's not over until it's over."
See, there are people who say these things
instead of staying quiet.
We really can reach people.
Yeah.
But I didn't expect your guitar playing
to improve so much.
Yeah, what a surprise.
It's really okay for me to play?
You practiced so much in the park.
Seems fine.
Thanks, everyone.
Please get ready.
Okay.
NINA, LOOK UP
HINA
"Up"?
NOW LOOK LEFT
HINA
"Left"?
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
MADE YOU LOOK, DUMMY
That girl...
She's funny.
Maybe Hina didn't want you
to fold after all.
What do you mean?
She came all this way
to tell you to apologize
even though she knows you wouldn't.
True, Nina is like the final boss.
The universe's
most irritating Morality Demon King.
Beating you means the game's over,
but she still wants to play.
That doesn't make me happy at all.
It's a compliment.
You know I'm right.
Everyone, it's time.
Um, as you know,
we're competing against Diamond Dust.
But you can see the results...
Thank you for coming today!
Ow...
To be honest, we cared about it a lot.
We wanted to beat Diamond Dust.
We didn't want to lose.
We really did our best
at the last music festival too.
Let me speak about myself for a moment.
Is that okay, Rupa?
Back in high school, I helped someone
who was being bullied.
I was really happy as I left my classroom
to go save her.
I felt so proud,
and I loved myself for doing it.
But because of that, I got bullied instead
and I ultimately dropped out of school.
But not once did I ever think
"I shouldn't have gone"
or "This wouldn't be happening
if I hadn't gone."
That's when I realized...
I don't regret anything.
I became stronger
because of Momoka's song,
and I often talked about that to Hina...
Oh, I see.
She liked D-D's songs too.
It wasn't just my song.
It reached her too.
Once again, thank you so much
for coming today.
You are the contrarians
who came to see us.
But I love people like that.
And I'll scream out that we haven't lost.
That we weren't wrong.
Please be the witnesses to our beginning!
We're all the same
Living life
If you don't have a place of your own
Go fly
Fate tangled up, reverberating
I had taken all other paths
I dedicate the rest of my life
To singing with you
No light or wind, like an isolated prison
Pain and suffering
Scars all over, I hated it all
Even with wings full of holes
Even in the depths of hell
I could sing with you
I flew away, wanting to disappear
But now I don't want to disappear
I picked the flower and kept it
Waiting for it to blossom
The version of me
Who wanted to disappear is gone
I'm glad I didn't disappear
Because I met you
Our flower of fate bloomed
Ready?
Thank you!
Never influenced by anybody
Never becoming anybody
I laughed, thinking it a dream
Numbed by the weakness I had forgotten
I can't even say that I'm lonely
This fragile heart
Vulnerable to even casual conversation
Is incapable of making anyone happy
But still, I feel a growing hope
Moving past all of the lies
I just want to hear
That I'm not wrong
I'm a dreamer, I'm young
I don't care if I'm still the same today
I just want to sing with you
My emotions stir so often
I've been hated
But I'm going to keep walking
Proud of myself
Who can never become anybody
Even if I'm alone
I believe in myself
Every time I get hurt, I just need to sing