What is the cause of the massive
mosquito outbreak this year?
To find out, we'll ask Mr. Kafetch, a mosquito expert
who has published several books on the subject.
Thank you for having me on.
Well, let me get right to the point.
These mosquitos belong
to an entirely new species.
Therefore, I know nothing about them.
Get out!
Ah, excuse me.
Now, let's take a look at the areas
likely to be hit hardest by the outbreak.
Man, City Z's in their path.
A mosquito outbreak?
Please give me a break.
We interrupt this program
to bring you breaking news.
A large swarm of mosquitos
has just been spotted in City Z.
We have reports that the attacked
livestock were mummified.
If you encounter a swarm
of mosquitos, flee immediately.
This is an emergency evacuation warning.
Threat level: Demon.
No resident is to go outside
under any circumstances.
I repeat, no City Z resident is to go
outside under any circumstances.
Acquiring target.
The Lone Cyborg
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
Thanks to that warning, they're all empty!
Like someone's gonna
die from a mosquito bite.
If I get all this,
who cares if I lose a little blood?
The wind?
What the—
Come on, you guys.
That wasn't nearly enough.
Go get some more for me!
Target acquired.
I see.
You make them suck the blood,
then take it all for yourself.
You must be controlling the mosquitos
via some sort of signal.
That would explain their mysterious behavior.
So if I were to get rid of you, the leader,
would the swarm disperse too?
Our next meal is here.
Go drain him dry.
Incinerate.
I am about to eliminate you.
Stay where you are.
You? Eliminate me?
Go on and try!
Got you.
Damn mosquitos!
Incinerate.
Maybe a leg next?
Wait, where are my legs?
Impossible.
You cannot escape from me.
What the hell is that guy?
He's gonna get me if I don't do something.
The townspeople may all be hiding,
but there are plenty of animals around.
Come to me, little ones.
Dump all your pent-up juices into me!
So many...
If she's been collecting blood
from the whole town and beyond,
then it may not simply
be a food source for her.
I should put an end to this
as soon as possible.
Get back here, dammit!
You and I aren't done yet!
What's with this guy?
It got in my mouth!
Pft! Pft! You little—
Huh?
Something's squirming over there.
Those are mosquitoes?!
You over there.
Evacuate now.
That swarm's got a will of its own.
If it senses you, it will immediately attack.
Seriously?
That's bad. I gotta get—
Since you could speak, I thought you would
have at least human-level intelligence.
But you were just a bug.
You brought all the mosquitos together
into one, easy-to-burn swarm.
When I spotted you,
I confirmed there were no
living beings within 500 meters,
so I should have been free to fire away.
Wait, that guy might have—
Man, you saved me. That was incredible.
What'd you just do?
You totally made them bug out!
Ba-dum-tss.
Oh, I was just trying to make a joke
about the mosquitos being bugs, and...
Idiot!
I no longer need the little ones.
I mean...
Look...
how strong I've become!
Can't your punches kill a little mosquito?
Weakling!
I see.
The more blood she consumes,
the more powerful she becomes.
I think I'll have your head next!
I let my guard down.
I have no chance of winning.
All I can do is self-destruct.
Forgive me, Doctor.
Mosquitoes suck!
Hold on!
Please tell me your name!
Oh. It's Saitama.
I'd like to be your disciple.
Oh, sure.
Huh?
Master!
You actually came?
Uh...
It's "Genos," Master Saitama.
Can you start by not calling me "master"?
Teacher!
Not "teacher" either!
Go on home after your drink.
I'm not looking for disciples.
Wait, you're back in one piece?
Yes, my body is mostly mechanical.
As long as there are parts, repairs are quick.
You're an odd one.
What kind of parts do you use, Master?
Don't use any.
Then what about the
skin-colored armor on your head?
Yeah, that's my skin.
But that would mean you're bald
despite being so young.
Yes, I'm bald! What's your problem?!
You mean me?
You'll listen to my problems?
No thanks, I'm good.
Actually, four years ago, when I was fifteen,
I was still completely human.
Did you hear what I just said?
Although we had to pinch pennies,
my family and I lived
a peaceful and fairly happy life.
But, one day, a crazy cyborg
went out of control and attacked our town.
That crazy cyborg...
Most likely, a failed body modification
generated an irregularity in his brain.
He destroyed everything in sight.
Parks, schools, buildings, my house...
He even took my family's lives.
Miraculously, I survived, but being
only a weak fifteen-year-old,
I was left stranded
at wit's end in a ruined town.
That's when Doctor Kuseno
happened to pass through.
Doctor Kuseno, a scientist for justice, was on a mission
to stop the destruction caused by the rampaging cyborg.
I asked Doctor Kuseno to perform
body modification surgery on me.
That's how I was reborn as a
cyborg who fights for justice.
I promised Doctor Kuseno that one day
I would terminate the evil cyborg.
I see—
It's been four years since that day.
I'm now nineteen and I've been wandering
from town to town eliminating evil.
I've destroyed too many monsters
and criminal organizations to count.
But I have not found any clues
that would lead me to the crazy cyborg
and have been feeling
increasingly frustrated and restless.
I find myself chasing an image of that cyborg
whenever I square off against my enemies.
Then, last week,
when that mosquito monster appeared,
I let my concentration slip.
I was convinced I could not lose
to anything but the crazy cyborg,
so I neglected to analyze the data on
my opponent and rushed to confront her.
The result, as you know, was that an opponent
with immense strength bested me.
If you, Master Saitama,
had not been in the area,
I would have undoubtedly been destroyed.
Master, you saved my life.
My life, that Doctor Kuseno saved before,
has now been saved again by you, Master Saitama.
I feel the weight of that responsibility.
I must not die before destroying that cyborg.
And to do that, I must continue fighting evil as a
righteous cyborg until he appears before me one day.
I need to get stronger.
Last week, when I saw your punch,
I knew I had to study under you as your disciple.
If only I could be as strong as you, Master Saitama!
I have an old enemy to defeat.
And this battle is not just for me.
It's for my hometown,
and for Doctor Kuseno too.
I realize I am still inexperienced.
But right now, I need enormous power
so I can eradicate the greatest of evils!
Doctor Kuseno is—
Enough, you idiot!
Shorten it to twenty words or less!
Mosquito Lady was defeated?
With one punch, you say?
Well, she was merely a prototype after all.
Why is he naked?
Unknown.
Well, whatever.
He'll make an excellent specimen.
We shall study his physiology,
by force if necessary.
Send a messenger and invite him here,
to our "House of Evolution."
Master, here's the short version:
Please teach me how to become strong like you.
Genos...
Yes!
How old are you?
Nineteen!
So young...
I'm sure you'll surpass me in no time.
Do you mean that?
I'm twenty-five now, but I was twenty-two
the summer I started training.
Sure, I'll teach you.
But it won't be easy.
Can you handle it?
Yes!
Object approaching at high speed! It's arrived!
What?
My name is...
Huh?
Pay for my ceiling!
So...
Hm?
It seems our advance agent,
Kamakyuri, is down.
I can't sense him with my telepathy anymore.
What? Wasn't he one of our stronger guys?
There are two more outside.
Master, leave them to me!
Don't crash through people's ceilings!
Oh, never mind.
Can't you guys just come through the door?
Master!
No, I'm fine.
I kinda feel like a... bamboo shoot.
Elevated energy levels detected.
A cyborg?
Could it be...
You are not the target.
What's going on? I can't see.
You are in the way!
I have a few questions for you.
It would appear you're in
what they call a "tight spot."
Well done, Ground Dragon!
GROUND DRAGON
It complicates things if they put up a fight.
Master!
You dare look away?
Quite courageous!
I am the pinnacle of the House of Evolution's
scientific development.
I am Armored Gorilla.
Your attacks have no effect.
The "House of Evolution"?
What does it want with my master?
It is none of your business.
And it is our rule that any who
oppose us be eliminated without fail.
I must destroy you.
Hey, jerk-off!
What's with that look?
Being underground keeps you cool,
but at the same time, it's nice and warm.
I'm sleepy. Could you get lost?
I see I need to teach you your place.
Listen up!
I'm gonna slice your eyes out with these!
Then we'll see if you resist!
The Beast King never lets anyone off easy.
Well, enough fooling around.
If you wanna apologize, now's your chance.
You guys smashed my ceiling!
Hmph. Fine.
Then behold the true power of the Beast—
Aw man...
I got dirt in my special place.
Hey, are you listening?
Let me just shake this out.
You done?
One sec.
I'm done.
Okay, then behold the
true power of the Beast King!
Lion Slash!
You okay, Frog Man—
Outta the way, pissants!
Such is the law of the jungle!
And you're next!
Wait! Don't kill him yet!
Lion Slash: Meteor Power Shower!!
Lion Slash: Meteor Power Shower!
Consecutive...
Normal Punches.
Oh.
N-No one told me he'd be like that!
We should retreat for now and regroup...
Found you!
No fucking way!
Huh?
Answer the question or be eliminated.
Your choice.
It is you who will be eliminated.
You fool.
I am the third most powerful fighter
in the "House of Evolution."
At your power level,
you will never beat the Beast King,
the second most powerful.
You will be destroyed.
Is this who you mean?
Apparently so.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I'll tell you everything.
Just don't kill me!
What the hell?
What happened to your robot voice?
Sorry, I was just trying to sound cool.
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
What do you mean?
The hit team was wiped out?
How did this happen?
Wait, don't jump to conclusions yet.
Verify the report immediately!
It may be a mistake.
Right away.
Be careful!
What's all the commotion?
Next
Time
The
Obsessive
Scientist
Okay, time for Mosquito Lady's episode preview!
Next week's story will be about my birthplace.
I was born—
What?! Time's up already?!
Oh, all right.
Next time on One-Punch Man episode three,
"The Obsessive Scientist."
Scientist, huh? I wonder who that could be.