You see, I might actually be in love...
with you, Shiro.
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Six
I Might Actually
Are you serious?
Why are you asking me to apologize?
I'm sorry to say this,
but my parents forgot to transfer this month's rent.
You should be okay if you're only a few days late.
Get your bamboos!
Mayumi and Sayaka are frequently late on their payments too.
Bamboo poles going cheap!
I hear Shiro's never failed to pay on time, though.
Bamboo!
For real?!
So he can be responsible.
That's exactly what makes him so irritating.
Shiro, you pig
She's related to Sumiko,
all right
She has a sharp tongue of her own, I see.
Bamboo!
But where's he getting this money from?
Bamboo poles!
Oh hey, you two.
Completely unexpected source of income detected.
You've got it all wrong.
It's just that when I helped one of Sumiko's friends cut bamboo at their thicket,
they let me have some as thanks.
Then why were you singing?
I just felt like it.
What are you even gonna do with bamboo?
Throw a Tanabata festival?
Sounds awful.
I'd rather not see a certain someone
making a million wishes to find "Mr. Right."
Walking around on bamboo stilts proved to be a huge hit with grade schoolers and the like.
Keep doing that and someone
will call the cops on you again.
I cry slander! Grade schoolers don't interest me!
Their moms do, though.
Slander, my foot. I wasn't that far off the mark.
Shiro, you've got a call from the police!
An arrest, eh?
They call people for that?!
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I happened to find a wallet while out on a walk the other day, so I handed it over to the police.
The officer was really surprised.
He thought you were turning yourself in!
He got confused when I said I didn't want a reward.
He was wondering what happened to turning yourself in!
It seems the wallet's owner showed up just now.
It sure does feel nice when you do a good deed.
Apparently they're stopping by tomorrow to say thanks.
It was a girl's wallet, no?
Maybe this could spark some romance between you two.
That sounds too good to be true.
But it could happen!
Please.
Thank you very much for finding my wallet.
This isn't much, but please accept it.
Oh, you shouldn't have.
That wallet was very important to my daughter, so I just had to show my appreciation.
The mother's eyes are darting all over the place.
Can you blame her? We're talking about Shiro here.
He's clearly the kind of guy you'd
want nowhere near your daughter.
But the one in danger right now...
is not the daughter but the mother.
Man, having an elegant mother in her 40s
avoid all eye contact with you feels amazing...
Chinatsu, was it?
Do you like pudding?
It should be nice
and chilled now
Would you like to try some of mine?
Oh, we couldn't! We'll be leaving now.
I'll stay and have some.
You can go home, Mom.
We live nearby, anyway.
Help yourself.
This is amazing!
I'm so sorry. She really loves pudding.
I'm glad you liked it.
Yeah, it was great.
What are you making?
A kind of Rube Goldberg machine.
Are there any kids living here?
Nope.
Then why?
I just thought it'd be fun.
Even though you're an adult?
Kids aren't the only ones who get to play, you know.
We adults know how to have a good time too.
Even the normal ones?
I've already been written off, huh?
Aren't you going to put it together?
I need to build the parts first.
That's boring.
If you live nearby, feel free to come hang out.
Come back anytime.
Bye bye!
I'll make some more pudding for you.
She was a cute kid, wasn't she?
Totally.
She even showed signs of being a potential sadist.
Please don't tell me about the
sadism potential of small girls.
The "S" in "small girl" stands for "sadist"!
I'd love to watch her grow up, but I'm sure she finds playing with her friends to be more fun.
She'll probably never come here again.
However, reality defied our expectations.
Did you finish the machine yet?
Not yet. Not even close.
I haven't done much since yesterday.
Huh?
It doesn't look like you have anything better to do.
Why haven't you made any progress?
Woohoo! My sadist detector's reacting like crazy!
I do have lots of other things to do.
Like what?
Well, I'm kinda writing a novel and stuff...
Wow.
scoff
Thanks. I appreciate your scorn and derision.
Well, maybe I could put the novel aside for the time being and focus on the machine.
Should an adult like you really be so quick to abandon something?
My instructor won't stop telling me to never give up.
Well, there are times when things refuse to go your way.
You want to do your best, but you just can't.
So how many years have you been saying that for?
It doesn't look like you'll ever
finish the machine by yourself,
so I'll come here every day to help you build it!
Sure you don't wanna hang out with your friends instead?
Yeah. Not like I can leave you on your own.
In return, we're gonna build something amazing!
Roger that!
Shiro.
It's looking good now, but what are we gonna top it off with?
Something nice and flashy, if possible.
She's been coming here every day, hasn't she?
It seems she's taken a liking to Shiro.
They even built that amazing contraption together.
I have this great idea.
Let's set up a massive hammer to destroy the entire machine!
What do you think?
I hope you keep growing up in that sound manner.
Well, it's a pleasant sight as long as your eyes are only slightly open.
Can't see
I guess it's barely safe, morally speaking.
No. It looks rather precarious to me.
Sayaka?
This reeks of love, or well, the desire to love.
Stop that!
She's in Shiro's strike zone, so he might actually end up winning a loli over!
That's huge!
I don't want a fellow resident making the news!
Deviant Complex
They'll call us birds of a feather!
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Doesn't he just strike you as a friendly older guy?
Well, she seems smart, so I don't
think she'd go down the wrong path.
Yeah, yeah!
However, reality defied our expectations yet again.
You see, I might actually be in love...
with you, Shiro.
Thank you.
I like you too, Chinatsu.
I'd love to hear you repeat those words nine years from now.
I'm so glad he has such a strong "eighteen and over" shield!
Relief
I have some business to take care of
with Sumiko, so wait for me here, okay?
We could probably talk some sense into her right now.
It's just puppy love, after all. A word here, a word there, and a grade schooler will look elsewhere in no time.
You sure?
I got this. Sit back and watch my silver tongue in action.
Hey.
Shiro's too perverted for a grade schooler to handle.
And he's never gonna amount to anything. You're better off not bothering. Okay?
Zero tact!
W-Were you eavesdropping?!
There, there.
If you want somebody to love, pick this guy instead.
He's young, and he's got balls.
Shut up!
Not that you're wrong, though!
Every last bit of him is brand new, and he'd
gladly join you in your annoying, youthful antics.
Great terms, don't you think?
People don't fall in love based on terms and conditions.
What's wrong with this kid?
I'm trying to stop her from
falling for a hopeless man here.
How irritating.
Birds of a feather hate each other?
Ah, fuck it!
Hey, Mayumi!
Unfortunately, he's actually my boyfriend.
Sorry.
Shouldn't you be considering those terms and conditions?
Given your age, I mean.
Grade schoolers are way too young for romance!
Pipsqueaks like you ought to be going all squeaky-squeaky with other pipsqueaks!
Squeaky-squeaky?
That's what you focus on?
If you stay like this, you'll get
excluded from everything, stupid.
Anyway, Shiro's my dog.
Pipsqueaks like you should stay out of...
You made her cry.
You've got two dozen years on her, you know.
I'm not that old!
You were so serious that I couldn't bear to look at your immaturity.
I'm gonna tell Sumiko about this.
But... But...
She was the one who started it!
I just gave her a taste of her own medicine!
I didn't do anything wrong!
They're at the same mental age, though.
I wonder why Chinatsu didn't come.
She was all enthusiastic, saying
she'd be here all day on Saturday.
She left without saying anything yesterday, too.
And I'd made pudding for her, too.
Among us, there is an adult
who got into a serious argument with a kid and made her cry.
It was him!
No, you!
You were worried about her and Shiro,
tried to warn her, and ended up arguing?
How?
She started crying when I told her Shiro was my boyfriend.
I only kept quiet because you promised to apologize to her the next day, you know!
You're too easy to deceive, Usa.
I had no idea she was that serious about him!
Was that really it?
Something feels off to me.
I know, right? There's gotta be a different cause, right?
No, it was most definitely your unbelievably immature words that made her cry.
Sorry about this, guys.
This all happened because I have
no interest in girls under eighteen.
That's not the issue here.
In fact, I'll tie you to a post if you ever change your mind.
Really? Thanks!
Well, she might come tomorrow,
so let's wait and see how it goes.
In the end, she never did show up yesterday.
Was she that hung up over Shiro?
What did she even see in him?
I don't get it either.
Like Mayumi said, you're much better.
J-Just compared to Shiro!
You're a high schooler, you feel pain when you're hit,
you're not used to getting tied up, you've never been apprehended by the cops...
What is wrong with me? I'm so happy even
though she's only stating the blindingly obvious!
Huh?
Is that... Chinatsu over there?
Is she waiting for friends?
Really?
Really!
The teacher said so!
She's blatantly being excluded.
Say, do you remember what Mayumi said that day?
"Grade schoolers are way too young for romance!"
"Pipsqueaks like you ought to
be going all squeaky-squeaky!"
How does one go "squeaky-squeaky," anyway?
You're quite fixated on that, huh?
Also...
If you stay like this, you'll get
excluded from everything, stupid.
That's it!
Seriously?
Among us, there is a person who'd sink so low as to rub salt into a grade schooler's wounds.
It wasn't on purpose!
Someone should've put a warning label on her that said she'd experienced it before!
Pardon me!
Sorry to disturb you, but is Chinatsu here?
Not today.
Has she not come home yet?
It's getting dark.
I've been looking everywhere for her... All the places she's likely to go...
We'll call you immediately if she comes here.
Please do.
Maybe we should go look around the area for her too.
Right.
I'll go look a bit farther.
If you could.
Shiro and the others are looking
near the grade school right now—
Chinatsu!
You were actually much closer than we thought.
I let your mother know.
She went quite far to look for you, so she'll come pick you up later.
Don't say anything stupid!
F-Friendship's a complicated thing, yeah?
Well, how should I say this?
Things will eventually work out.
Or well, they'll work out whether you have friends or not.
How flimsy.
You're not very convincing.
Yeah, Mayumi's clearly the type of girl who was popular back in her student days.
Why stress the "was"?
Why, just look at this loner who's spent more than a year on her own and is still having a jolly good time!
I'm tripling your rent.
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
But come on, help me out here!
Stop whispering terrifying things to me first, though!
Is that true?
Well, yeah.
Don't you feel lonely?
Well, uh...
I guess it's easier on me.
You're amazing, Ms. Loner.
Suddenly sadistic!
You seem like the kind who'd have lots of friends,
so rather than being a loner,
it's more like you fought with
them and got excluded, right?
Payback
Why did you guys fight?
My studies and other lessons and stuff haven't been going so well lately,
so I was really on edge.
Hey, Chinatsu.
Then my friend started talking about anime to me.
So I kinda snapped at her.
I hate that stuff!
That made her cry.
Then my classmates made a big
deal of it, saying how mean I was.
Wow, it's true. Who did this?
I didn't know we had a bully in our class!
But everyone has things they like or dislike.
So what if I hate anime?
Did you even listen to what she was saying?
But I've never been into anime.
Everybody does have different tastes, yeah.
That's just a fact of life.
But it would still hurt to have a friend outright reject something you love.
What the hell? It's not such a big deal.
Just give her some candy and apologize.
We're not kids!
It's not that simple!
Whenever I enter the classroom or get close to people,
I can hear the air freeze.
The thought of hearing that sound again tomorrow...
makes me wanna die!
Saying stuff like that is proof that you're a pipsqueak.
What in the world are you saying? You're the youngest here.
Would you like some pudding before you die?
I would.
Want mine too?
Are you sure? I'd love that!
Even when you feel like you
want to die, you still get hungry,
and when you eat something you like, it still tastes good.
Our bodies are made of stronger stuff than our minds, don't you think?
Hey, I'm seriously worried here!
Right.
That shows how strong you are and that you have the strength to go on.
If you want to make things right, then go give it your best shot.
If things still don't work out, let's see...
I could make a whole bucket of pudding for you!
I'll complete the machine by next weekend.
The finishing touches are gonna be awesome.
So bring your friends along, okay?
'Kay.
I sure hope they can make up.
Oh, I'm still tripling
your rent next month
I think they'll be just fine.
Wait, you
were serious?
I mean, the girls that excluded her...
Wait, you
were serious?
kept looking back.
Dude...
You have quite the eye for grade school girls!
Don't say it like that!
And then it was Saturday.
Sumiko...
Could you make some pudding for me?
O-Of course.
Hey, you said they'd be fine! So why is she here alone?!
You two are a perfect fit, don't you think?
Quiet, you!
You can eat sweets to celebrate too, right?
Of course!
Without further ado,
behold Shiro & Chinatsu's Bamboo Goldberg Machine!
Here goes!
And the grand finale: flowing noodles!
Help yourself!
Lame
Uh, it's not flowing at all.
Hold on. I'll get some more water right away.
It's not gonna let a single drop through.
Sounds like one of those adult diaper commercials.
Bamboo and
water...
Do you mind not ruining my
appetite before I've even eaten?!
By the way, I had nothing to do with all that pointless stuff at the end.
The "S" in "Japanese Schoolgirl" is for "sadist"!
Had to
resort
to a hose
Had to
resort
to a hose
Had to
resort
to a hose
I bet you your
voice can't hit those
high notes now
I bet you your
voice can't hit those
high notes now
Hey.
It can!
Are you having fun, Ms. Loner?
You are, right?
I am.
I knew it!
Want me to be your friend?
You can start by not calling me "Ms. Loner."
Chinatsu!
It's not quite a bucketful of pudding,
but how do you like the taste?
It's great!
Amazing!
Delicious!
She hasn't come over once since then.
She must be busy having fun with her friends.
Saying she loved me was a
form of escapism, so to speak.
She did say that looking at me made her feel better,
that a total social outcast could still have fun.
What a sadist.
Feeling lonely now?
Kids are just fine being that way, man.
Relying on adults when needed,
and then throwing them away and trampling all over them!
Well, I disagree.
Usa, Shiro!
Dinner is served!
Okay!
Looks great!
Are those pork cutlets?
Uh, Sumiko...
I'm not really...
depressed or anything.
Oh, is that so?
Ah!
These are the chicken's favorite...
chicken cutlets!
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
All the singles out there can't stand how beautiful I am
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little panic in the air
So we try to help each other out
One for all, and all for one
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
Big trouble! I hear there's a molester around these parts!
Molesters are the worst. I wish they'd go to hell.
I bet you send them there yourself.
Whatever could you be talking about?
Well, I won't let them go unscathed.
These two aside, I'm worried about Kawai!
Molesters are just useless losers.
You can fend them off by saying
something that breaks their spirit.
Really?
"You're hung like a hamster!" or something.
"So tiny I couldn't see it."
That's it! We gotta make Kawai practice those lines!
And why do you want to make her say that?
So it wasn't just Shiro. You were a masochist too, huh?
Episode Seven
We Recommend
That's not what I meant.
You're the worst.
You've got the wrong idea!