The savior shall appear along with the word of hope...
She shall carry the red lord,
and stand amidst golden snow.
O Savior, please grant us your divine aid...
Don't worry.
I believe in the legend.
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Lene's Underground Empire Wars
Now, here's my haiku.
Thank you very much.
It is my hope that these words
charge your batteries.
"We Love Master!"
Shinki Haiku Competition
"We Love Master!" Shinki Haiku Competition
Yay, I'm finished!
Go ahead, Lene.
I love you, Master.
Both today and tomorrow,
I really love you.
Your writing is unrefined.
It really says how you feel about Master.
Oh, we got mail?
It's an urgent message from Master!
Sorry! I forgot my lunch box.
Could you bring it to me before my lunch break?
I didn't eat breakfast, so I feel like I'll starve to death...
Oh no, Master's going to die!
No, that's not what he means.
If we leave now, we can arrive on time.
You're right.
Let's go, everyone!
The weather's wonderful!
It's perfect for a stroll.
Stay focused. We are on duty.
This is heavy!
I'm parched...
We played rock-paper-scissors fairly.
Do not complain.
We should rest here for a moment.
Lene, hit me with a Jellycan.
I have one in here.
Wait!
Really now...
Waaaait!
She's late.
Hey, Lene!
This hole seems pretty deep.
I'll go see what happened.
I-I'm coming too!
Hina, guard the lunch box!
Now wait!
Good grief.
Um, where am I?
This is the forgotten city.
It is no place for outsiders.
Bomb
I never knew something like this was right under the park...
The place feels... kinda wrong.
Ines, look!
Um, excuse me...
Who the hell're you?
Whoah, she's wasted...
Um, I'm pretty sure we've been searching for that rice ball...
Oh, so this was your doing?
Huh?
We'll capture you and report you to Empress Claudi!
What're you doing?
Please stop!
Hey now.
You all better shut your traps if you care about your friend here.
So, you came here for your master's sake.
Yes.
Then we welcome you.
Those who care for their master
are our allies in this underground empire.
Underground empire?
Yes.
A number of stray Shinkis who could no longer live with their masters gathered here,
and founded this colony.
But aren't unowned Shinkis supposed to be seized by the manufacturer?
We refused that fate.
We would be reset and lose our memories of our master.
The amount of Shinkis who felt the same increased one by one,
and the city soon grew large.
Even in poverty, we were happy.
It was once a peaceful place...
Until she came.
Who's she?
What the heck're you doing?
Empress Claudi, we brought the rice ball criminals.
Now what were you two thinking,
bringing somethin' like this here?
Well, it wasn't quite a matter of thinking...
We were taking that to our master,
and we accidentally dropped it on the way.
Hey. What'd you just say?
Who'd you say owns this?
It's... our master's.
Master?
You shall never say that word before me again!
You fuckin' pissed me off!
Hey, toss 'em in the slavery barn.
Gotcha!
Don't you two ever think you'll see the sun again.
I can't tell what's what!
Hey, aren't those...
Hey kitty, your output's getting pretty fucking weak.
I need more power, slaves!
Tamami!
Are you okay?
Noooo! I wanna go home!
I wanna curl up with Master!
I love you
Master...
Well, looks like you've just violated the law.
Gimme that back!
Here's your sentence!
Well at least it makes a good frame!
I love you
That's doggone evil...
Waaah, Master...
How cruel...
Claudi arrived out of the blue six months ago.
She conquered this city by force,
and forbade the very existence of masters.
Why would she do that?
The Shinkis of the Anti-Master Army were cast away by their own masters,
and bore dreadful grudges because of it.
All who opposed were made into slaves.
That's horrible!
That's unforgivable!
We of the Liberation Army escaped their oppression,
and are now preparing to fight back.
With our imprisoned comrades at stake,
failure is not an option.
The tailwinds of victory shall soon blow.
I'll help in any way I can!
Our feelings for our masters know no bounds!
Thank you, Lene.
The only one who may
call me by the name "Hina"
is you, and only you.
They are late.
Status report! The patrol unit has returned.
They say a chance will come at noon today,
as the enemy dug up the aged wine we prepared.
Just as planned.
Empress Claudi is even bathing in it.
Bathing in wine?
The time has come.
Now is the time to make our move.
Prepare to march at once!
Everyone, you've done well to bear these humiliating days.
You've worked with all your strength.
But now we will begin our campaign.
Zelnogrard Vanguard,
you will cause a riot in the slums,
and draw the attention of the enemy army.
Roger!
We will free the slaves within that window.
For that, Lene's squad will be deployed here.
Well?
Roger that!
Concurrently, Zil and I will infiltrate the pyramid,
and attack Claudi during her bath!
Roger.
Zeruno,
our military force is limited.
I know it will be difficult, but please hold out...
Trust me.
I cleaned my guns for this day so much, they're sparkling!
Let's go.
Take pride, Liberation Army,
for we shall reclaim peace and freedom once more!
This sucks!
This is a problem.
It's already afternoon.
O Savior, please save our tails.
Savior?
It's a legend that's spoken of around here.
When our darkest hour comes,
a savior of victory will appear and save us all.
You two know a lot about this place.
We have friends here, so we come over to play sometimes.
It was a fun, peaceful place less than a cat year ago...
And now...
It looks like Maste—
Waagh!
That word's forbidden here!
Hey!
I'm sorry!
There's a revolt!
The city's being set aflame!
It's finally come.
Zil, I truly thank you for everything you've done.
What's this, now?
I didn't want it left unsaid.
This might be the end, after all.
Why would you...
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to seem weak in front of everyone else.
Oorbel...
Let's win, Zil.
We'll be fine.
We have the Savior to protect us.
Status report.
Someone has incited mutiny,
and the slums are revolting!
Guess the gutter rats are raising their voices.
Deploy the soldiers!
Exterminate with extreme prejudice!
What's happening?
Everyone, you have to run!
Oh, Lene!
You're safe!
What are you two doing here?
We should ask you that!
I'm on a crusade!
Anyway, just escape!
I have to free the other slaves!
Ain't that a shame.
The root of all evil that tramples upon our hearts...
We'll bring you to justice here and now!
You kept me waiting.
So, you think you've been playing hero?
I've completely seen you through!
I'm terribly sorry!
Everyone...
What a pleasure.
I've been waiting for someone dumb enough to oppose me to my face.
Now, I'll have you two kill each other!
Give me the greatest show on Earth!
Are you mad?!
Oh, would you like your friends up there to be turned into scrap?
Does your cowardice know no bounds?
What'll it be?
Will you kill each other, or abandon your comrades?
Choose whichever you like.
I'll give this all I have.
Holding back is useless.
Oorbel! Zil!
Who are they?
They're the friends we told you about!
Both of them are really nice Shinkis!
This is too much...
If only we could get out of here...
If this were on TV, a hero would show up in the nick of time!
This isn't the time for stupid fantasies!
I've been looking for you.
Strarf!
I thought you were late,
but you were simply having fun on your own.
This ain't fun!
C'mon, unlock the cage!
Fine. Crouch.
Pretty quick for a fly.
This turned out okay!
Snow?
Master!
Master?
She said Master?
The savior shall appear along with the word of hope...
She shall carry the red lord,
and stand amidst golden snow.
The savior!
Savior?
Bullshit! That's just a legend!
How... dare you...
You harmed Master's lunch box!
Lene!
Oh, not bad.
Lene's scary when she gets mad!
This ain't good.
Time to skedaddle!
I'll make you pay!
This is the power of my love for Master!
Today marks the birth of a new era.
We've got a lot of work ahead, Zil!
I'm so hungry...
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Christmas is finally here!
We've all been working to buy Master a present!
If good little boys and girls hang a stocking by their beds,
Santa will leave a wonderful present inside!
Speaking of which, I first came to Master's house on Christmas Eve!
So, you were a Christmas present for Master?
How was it?
How was what?
The feeling of being inside Master's stockings.
That's what's on your mind?
Next time
"A Christmas Song for You"
Next time on Busou Shinki,