Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
Oh, come, come!
Wrong!
You do know what the baobabs are a metaphor for, right?
You do, right?
As the prince, you need to lead him on with eyes full of yearning.
You should appear as if you know you're toying with him.
Once again from the top!
Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
Oh, come, come!
Come on, you guys! Do it right!
We are, dammit.
Are you even going to finish on time?
We're really counting on this musical, you know?
Oh, did you finish the costumes?
Lemme see, lemme see!
Wow, these are amazing.
Look at the beautiful stitching!
Hikki
Hey.
What's up? It's rare of you to randomly call—
Did you know Yukinoshita was absent today?
Huh?
Apparently she's sick.
In this room filled with light,
I'll be waiting for you
If you'd realize you're floating and gazing upon a box,
You'd notice it doesn't return your gaze
The reflected heart is pure white
Just like the light from the falling snow
This shivering rain that blankets me
Isn't going to dispel until the spring breeze returns
So let's search for some azalea
Bring me with you to a comforting garden
Is not something I can ask
That fairy tale-like happiness isn't real
I know that much already
But still
I want to go there
And thus, the curtains rise on every
stage while the festival heats up.
Holy crap.
Ignoring us?
I'd be okay with that,
but what if she's too sick to even answer?
Hello?
Yukinon!
It's Yui.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine, so...
"So"?
So what?
Is she trying to tell us to go home?
Just open the door already.
Why are you here?
I have something to talk to you about.
Welcome.
Come in.
Please have a seat.
So what did you want to talk about?
You were absent today, so I was just wondering if you were okay.
It was only one day. You're getting worried over nothing.
Aren't you tired though?
You still look pretty pale.
I'm somewhat tired, but it's not a big deal.
Isn't that the problem though?
You don't have to keep doing everything by yourself.
I know that.
That's why I divided the work to reduce the burden—
But you didn't.
I'm sorta mad, y'know.
I'm mad at you too, Hikki.
You said you'd help her if she was in trouble.
He did all the paperwork and duties assigned to him.
That's all I can ask of him.
But...
It's fine.
We still have time.
I'm still making some progress at home, so there won't be any major delays.
You don't need worry so much about it, Yuigahama.
But that's just wrong.
You think so?
Most people think that relying on someone, helping each other out, and supporting one another is the correct way.
I see.
But that's just idealism.
Someone will always end up with the short end of the stick.
So I won't tell you to rely on others, but...
You're going about this the wrong way.
Then do you know the correct way?
Nope.
But I do know it's not what you've been doing up until now.
I'm sorry. I didn't bring you any tea.
Don't worry about that. I'll do it.
There's no need to worry over my health.
I'll feel much better after some rest.
"My health," huh?
Um, Yukinon...
Rely on me and Hikki.
Not "someone" or "everyone," just rely on us.
Hikki is—
Is black tea okay?
Thanks, Yukinon.
Well, I'm going home now.
M-Me too.
Yuigahama.
Yes?
Well, it might be hard for me right now,
but one day I will definitely rely on you.
So, thank you.
Yukinon.
But I'd like to think it over some more...
See you later, Yuigahama.
Huh?
W-Wait!
People often say, "If I change myself, I'll change the world."
That's a load of crap.
They jam that convenient farce down your throat so you're forced to compromise.
Let me show you how someone really changes the world.
Oh, really?
Everyone's here, Sagami.
Oh, okay.
Vice Chairman
Chairman
Yukinoshita.
Huh?
Let's begin the meeting.
For today's meeting, as you've already heard from President Shiromeguri,
we'll be coming up with the slogan for the cultural festival.
Friendship   Hard Work   Victory
Not a chance.
Funny! Too funny!
You can hear the sea breeze,
at Sobu High's Cultural Festival
That one's no good either.
-  Single-minded
Whoa. I have an idea who might have written that one.
That one's pretty good.
One for all.
I like stuff like that.
Ha! That kind of stuff?
It's quite simple.
You hurt someone, then toss them to the curb.
One for all.
It happens all the time, doesn't it?
Hikigaya, you're...
The last one will be from us then.
Bonds
_
~   A cultural festival where
everyone cooperates~
Yikes.
Bonds
_
~ A cultural festival where
everyone cooperates ~
What is it? Something wrong?
Not really.
Isn't there something you'd like to say?
Nope. Not really.
That so?
If you don't like it, let's hear your suggestion.
Okay.
Human
_
~ A cultural festival
where if
you look
closely,
one side is
just slacking off ~
What about something like "Human: A cultural festival where if you look closely, one side is just slacking off."
He's an idiot. A true idiot.
This is the best!
I can't take it! My sides hurt!
You're laughing too much, Haruno.
Well, I think it's a pretty good idea.
Anything goes as long as it's interesting.
Explain, Hikigaya.
Well, the character for human represents people supporting one another,
but isn't one side just leaning on the other?
The general idea behind the character "human"
is the approval of the practice of making someone the victim.
That's why it's a perfect fit for this cultural festival and its committee.
What exactly do you mean by "victim"?
Me. I'm a total victim here.
I'm being forced to do a stupid amount of work.
Actually, I'm being forced to do other people's work too.
Or is that what the chairman meant when she said "everyone cooperates"?
I wouldn't know though, since I've never cooperated with anyone before.
Hikigaya.
Rejected.
Let's end the meeting here for today, Sagami.
It doesn't seem like we'll be getting any decent ideas anyway.
But—
It would be foolish to waste a whole day on this.
Everyone should give it some thought on their own. Let's decide tomorrow.
As for the remaining work, if everybody comes everyday,
we can make up for lost time.
Isn't that right?
R-Right.
All right, everyone. Please come everyday starting tomorrow.
Good work today.
What was that about?
I bet he just wants to slack off too.
You okay with that?
With what?
I think you should probably clear up their misunderstanding.
It won't make a difference.
We've already got the solution.
The problem ends here.
You'll make an excuse for something totally inconsequential,
but you won't when it really matters, huh?
Excuses are meaningless.
People just make up their own mind when it really matters anyway.
Fair enough.
That's probably true.
Excuses have no meaning.
Then you'll just have try it again, won't you?
Anyway, what was that earlier?
Talk about senseless.
Still better than yours.
Are you some kind of thesaurus or what?
It's amazing how you never change.
Humans don't change that easily.
Especially when you're a weird person from the start.
That last part was unnecessary.
Watching you makes me think forcing yourself to change is foolish.
Later.
Yes. Farewell.
See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow then.
Meeting room
As you can see, this will be our slogan this year.
Chiba's specialties are dance and festivals!
We're all fools, and so that we can dance,
Sagami, we should start including the slogan wherever we can.
Okay. Please start adding it.
Let's get these posters finished up quick, guys!
Vice Charmain, the test version of the website has finished uploading.
All right.
I need your permission, Sagami.
Huh? Yeah, okay.
Please move on to the real thing then.
Roger that!
Well, well.
Working hard or hardly working?
What's it look like to you?
Looks like you're hardly working.
Duty
minutes
Why? I'm working hard here!
I mean, there's nothing in these minutes about your achievements at all.
Here's a quiz for you!
What's the best way to unify a group?
A ruthless leader?
Oh, silly.
You know the answer.
A common enemy.
Well, the enemy's a little underwhelming this time.
Leave me alone.
But if a bad guy like you is working hard, people will want to oppose you.
People won't get any better if their enemy isn't doing his job.
Conflict gives birth to progress.
Yikes. So annoying.
Um, did you do that on purpose so Yukinoshita—
I hate perceptive brats, you know.
Please do your job.
Finish the paperwork for finalizing the slogan and the minutes.
Then send each group participating a
message notifying them of the slogan.
Oh, and while you're at it, collect all planning applications and upload them to the server.
Have it all done by the end of today.
Should I help?
You're in the way, Sis. Go home.
How cruel!
You're so cruel, Yukino!
Well, I've got nothing better to do, so I'm doing it anyway.
We're going to review the budget, so whatever you're doing, do it over there.
'kay!
That's how a cultural festival committee's gotta be!
Ah, this is the best time of your lives!
Three minutes until the curtains raise. Three minutes until the curtains raise.
This is Yukinoshita.
I have a message for everyone.
We're going to proceed on schedule.
If there are any problems, please report them immediately.
No problems with the lighting!
PA system here. No problems.
Dressing room here.
The cast is rushing to get ready, but it seems like they'll make it in time.
Understood.
Everyone on standby until I give the cue.
Ten seconds to go.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Sobu High Cultural Festival!!
Chiba's specialties are dance and festivals!
We're all fools, and so that we can dance,
Three.
Two.
One.
Sobu High Cultural Festival!!
Chiba's specialties are dance and festivals!
We're all fools, and so that we can dance,
Is everyone getting their culture on?
Chiba's specialties are dance and...
...festivals!
We're all fools, and so that we can dance...
...sing a song!
This is the PA systems.
The song will be ending shortly.
Roger that.
Chairman Sagami is on standby.
And next up is a word from the cultural festival committee chairman!
Ev—
Let's try that again!
You're up, Chairman!
She's wasting time.
Hikigaya, give her the signal to move on.
I have been. Doesn't seem like she's noticed me though.
Oh? I guess I picked the wrong person for the job then.
Are you ridiculing my lack of presence?
I'm doing nothing of the sort.
Anyway, where are you? In the audience?
You are ridiculing me!
I mean, you can actually see me!
I am the chairman of the cultural festival committee, Sagami Minami.
Um, Vice Chairman. Everyone can hear you.
This year's slogan is "Chiba's specialties are dance and festivals!
Sobu High Cultural Festival!!
We need to adjust the schedule.
We're all fools, and so that we can dance, sing a song!"
Everyone keep that in mind.
The Little Prince
I did not know how to understand anything.
I ought to have judged by deeds and not by words.
He cast his fragrance and his radiance over me.
Do not let it weigh down on you.
You were too young to know how to love him.
What's up with that role? Was I supposed to do that?
Tonight, you know... do not come.
Why must it be so?
I shall not leave you.
How odd.
Even lines from the original work sound like BL to me.
Do not come to see that. It is not worth the trouble...
I shall not leave you.
There's no other choice!
Just give up on me!
I shall not leave you!
She's a total failure. I have to do something...
You chose him over me, didn't you?
It matters not though.
We shall meet again very soon.
When I drew the muzzle for you,
I forgot to add the leather strap to it.
Sheep...
On Break
Reception
Hey there.
How'd it go?
Went well, I guess?
The audience enjoyed it too.
Reception
Everyone really worked hard.
I guess so.
I wouldn't really know though, since I wasn't around.
You had committee work, so you couldn't help it.
Why?
Quit messin' around!
Let us in already!
This is messed up!
Really messed up!
Yikes. Looks pretty rough over there.
I don't think they'll be able to regain control if this continues.
Let's do this, folks.
Please line up over here.
The end of the line is over here. Over here.
End of the line
is this way
Is the Class E representative here?
Yukinon is so cool.
She seems a bit more energetic too.
Suppose so.
Mind if I ask you something?
Reception
What's up?
When we went to Yukino's house before, did you guys talk about something?
Nothing at all.
I got hungry after you left, so we ate dinner together.
Then we watched some DVDs.
I went home after that.
So I didn't hear anything about what you want to know.
Reception
Well, it's not like there's anything I wanted to know really.
Really?
I wanted to know.
You see...
I decided to wait for Yukinon.
She's probably trying to talk to us and get closer to us.
That's why I'll wait.
But some helpless people won't wait even if I do.
Huh? Well, there's really no point in waiting for those types anyway.
That's not it.
I won't wait then. I'll go straight to them instead.
That so?
It is.
Oh, I totally forgot.
You haven't had lunch yet, right?
Tada! It's honey toast!
It's not that rare.
Huh? This is just bread.
Couldn't they have tried a bit harder to hide that?
It's still bread no matter how you slice it.
On Break
It's delicious!
It's hard.
The inside of the bread has barely absorbed any of the honey too.
Now it's really thick and hard to chew.
This some kind of punishment?
The fresh cream is yummy!
Did it even have to be honey toast then?
And you're eating my portion of fresh cream, aren't you?
Well, it's pretty good,
I guess?
I'm so full!
Reception
Oh, yeah. How much was it?
Don't worry about it. It wasn't much.
That's not how this works.
I said not to worry about it!
While I do like the idea of being supported, I do not want any charity.
What's with that confusing pride of yours?
Fine.
Then you can treat me to some honey toast next time.
At Pasera.
Even picking the place, huh?
Which means...
Well...
On Break
Reception
Is something else instead okay too?
Yeah, sure!
When do you wanna go?
Um...
Sorry. Let me think about it for a bit.
Reception
Shining in the bright blue sky I hate so
An airplane soars toward the horizon
Something is stirring from within my heart
I keep all the things I want to say pent up
And turn them into things I can no longer say
I can't even be honest until the end
Just forget that I wanted to be with you,
And that I set you free
If I had told you I wanted to see you
Before the faint trail you left behind vanished,
I would be freed from this
Heartbreak that never ends
I could be here with you again
Hello! Hello! Alone!
My heart races every time I see you
I want to get closer to you
Before this sweet dream melts away,
I hope you realize my feelings
I want to be special to you
Next time.
And thus, his, her, and her mistaken
youths continue.
And thus, his, her, and her mistaken youths continue.