It's been raining so much lately...
Even today it's like this.
Geez, my clothes won't ever dry!
That's why I've bought these clothes from downtown.
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
Fil Nilvalen
Loves
Shopping
How much did you buy?
Since the new King took power, the supply of clothes have increased,
so I had a hard time choosing.
Sure you did...
Now, now, let's get you out of those clothes.
A girl shouldn't let herself catch a cold.
Yeah yeah...
That's "Yes" — and it's said only once.
Yes!
Hmm, it's a little jumbled and feels strange...
Frills and laces exist for girls.
Recommended Attire for
Elkian Women
Can I really do maid work in this?
You can please everyone just by being in those clothes!
Recommended Attire for
Elkian Domestic Workers
Those are supposed to look good on
people with smaller breasts.
Take these off! Take these off right now!
Recommended Swimwear for
Elkian Schoolgirls
What's this? A bunny-werebeast costume?
Oh my! Just by wearing it,
Cramy turns it from beastly to divine!
Recommended Attire for
Elkian Retail Workers
Oh, these are so easy to move around in!
For clumsy Cramy, they might be the perfect outfit!
Recommended Athletic Attire for
Elkian Schoolgirls
Wow, these are just the right size!
I'm sorry, those are actually child size!
That was on purpose! That was
definitely on purpose, right!?
Recommended Uniform for
Elkian Schoolgirls
Wha—Where's the bottom!?
They'll see everything!
But that's what makes it good!
Elkia Kingdom Commemorative
Goods Top Sale Item
As can be expected from the King's Brand store;
each item is such a fine piece of work.
Enough already! Fi, you're just
having fun with me aren't you!?
Cramy's been made to wear shabby
clothes all her life hasn't she?
I've always wanted to let Cramy wear better clothes.
But, I'm sorry. This is merely a
selfish wish of mine.
Fi!
Well, putting that aside...
We're going to dry your clothes before you catch a cold!
What?
You could have used
magic to dry them from the get go!
So you were just playing with....