Why the hell did we take her with us?
She saw our faces! We had to!
Setouchi says she'll be here soon.
Let's figure out what we're gonna do before she gets here.
Look at where we brought her after kidnapping her.
You know what we gotta do now, don't you?
Do you want to be a criminal or something?
We're already criminals.
Fuck, man. This ain't worth what Setouchi gave us anymore.
They couldn't have taken me very far.
I think they're holding me in an abandoned warehouse by the school.
Did you guys get that?
Yeah! That was from Inaba!
An abandoned warehouse by the school!
kaze ni hazumu sono koe meguru nichijou rizumu
Your voice, bouncing through the air, to the rhythm of each passing day
futo shita hyoujou no kimi ga mabushikute
Every little expression you show shines so brightly in my eyes
zawameki wo oboeta no wa itsu kara dattan darou
When did I start feeling this way? I don't think that I'll ever know
15 minutes to give a presentation
How will the
judges assign
points?
Club Presentation
15 minutes to give a presentation
How will the
judges assign
points?
Map of Places
Around School
mitsumeru saki ni wa nani ga matteiru
What's waiting for me over there, in the place that I see?
Jazz Band
How about
Disney Sea?
Good job, me!
is going
DOWN
The girls do
some killer cosplay
Exploding Ring, Barbed
This is serious,
people!!
15 minutes to give a presentation
How will the
judges assign
points?
CRC News Extra
Inaban's white bunny
I'm screwed
for that
physics
quiz...
Jazz Band
Frankensteiner
Let's go
Field trip?
I'm the President!
How about curry doria?
chirp
Inabaaaan!
How about
Disney Sea?
Universal's good too!
I'm hungry
to Disneyland again!
The fate of the CRC is on the line!
is going
DOWN
Club Presentation
Wire Barricade,
Double-Hell Mat,
Megaton
Steel Cage Deathmatch
Battle for Gossan
Map of Places
Places no one knows about
Yui's favorite stores
Yui's favorite sights
Yui's favorite pastries
Around School
The girls do
some killer cosplay
Good job, me!
All we can do is try!
kirameki he to konekuto
Connecting to the light
boku wo oikoshite
Always passing me by
nanairo ni tsunagatteku yo
Connecting in all seven colors
zenryoku de susumu michi
Keep going, running at full speed
hikari no ko egaku you ni
Leaving behind a trail of light
todoita sono egao
In that smile that you showed me
nukumori wo shitta
I felt a gentle warmth
itsudatte koko ni aru takanari wo shinjiteyukou
Let's believe that that voice will always be there singing for us
sou yatte umareteku asu ni naritain da
Because that's how we can make it so tomorrow will always come
Shouldn't we call the police?
This isn't the time to be keeping secrets!
I know!
But we need find where they took her first!
Inaba!
What am I doing?
Inaban's in trouble, but I don't know what I should do.
I don't know what I can do.
I'm just lying here, not doing anything.
The ideal me would have gone to rescue her,
and a horrible person wouldn't so much as lift a finger.
I can't decide on what to do, so I'm just lying here.
I'm doing exactly what a horrible person would do.
That means I'm a horrible person...
We'll save you!
Connecting Hearts
It's your damn life!
Live it any damn way you want!
Sure, we expected too much out of you and didn't know it.
But you tried way too hard to live up to our expectations and pushed yourself over the edge.
That makes you stupid!
Setouchi?
Even if it wasn't the real you, I still fell in love with you, Nagase Iori.
Even if I'm not perfect...
Even if I'm not the ideal me...
He says that I'm still my own person.
The point of life isn't to be perfect.
It's to do what you want to do.
To be who you want to be.
That's how I should be trying to live!
We'll save you!
I've had enough.
I've had enough!
I'll do whatever I feel like!
Nagase Iori will be Nagase Iori!
What do I want to do?!
I'll live more freely!
Much more freely!
I'll...
Setouchi's here.
Setouchi-san?
How many are there?
Three men.
You've gone too far, you guys.
This is really bad!
I told you, it's not our fault!
She came at us from out of nowhere!
This wouldn't have even happened if it wasn't for you!
You're the one who told us to fuck up their presentation!
But the other girls told me to.
Quit trying to play innocent!
What?
The fuck're you lookin' at?
Stop!
Who're you?!
Get outta here!
We're in the middle of something here.
You don't want to get hurt, do you?
Get 'em!
Fucking bitch!
That was so cool!
But they won't be out for long.
Inaba, it's o—
P-Put that down!
You could kill her!
Don't be stupid!
Shut up!
Don't move an inch!
What happens to her is on your head!
We understand.
We understand. Just calm down.
It's all her fault!
She was all full of herself when she asked us to wreck your presentation!
It's okay. Just calm down.
Let her go, and we'll leave you alone.
And why should I trust you?
Who's there?!
Well, well. Looks like we've got a stalemate.
You can't get out of it alone, can you?
Let me help you.
What are you talking about, Nagase?
I've got a bone to pick with these guys.
So I'm here to help you.
You know what they say. The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Happen!
The enemy of my enemy is my friend?
Makes sense.
Iori! What are you doing?!
Please...
Happen!
Iori-chan, you traitor!
What are you doing?!
Stop acting like you know me.
So, what should I do?
Well, uh...
What do you want me to do?
Happen! Happen! Happen!
Happen! Happen!
Happen! Happen! Happen! Happen!
Please just happen!
Save Inaban, now!
Taichi!
I was so scared!
I never want to do something like that again!
Never! Never, ever!
I was so scared!
Iori!
Let's just get out of here.
You come along too, Setouchi.
Let me get this straight. You like Shiroyama from the jazz band,
and it pissed you off when he confessed to Iori and she turned him down,
so you started bullying her.
I never wanted to mess up your club room,
but my friends kept egging me on, and I couldn't say no...
But that's no excuse.
I'm sorry.
What should we do?
I have something in mind.
Stand up, Setouchi-san.
Prepare to die!
Take this!
Hey!
Huh? Was that too hard?
That was more like a palm strike than a slap...
It was a flawless straight palm strike.
You put your hips into it, too.
You may have given her a concussion.
A-Are you okay? I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to hit you so hard.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry too, but that hit was on behalf of everyone else here.
I didn't want to hit you.
All of this was partly my fault. So now, we're even.
Think you can you forgive me?
You know, something's been bugging me.
You're a good girl at heart, aren't you, Setouchi-san?
I'm good at telling what people are really like.
Why are you putting on the bad girl act?
Because... the guy I used to like was...
I wanted to...
...change yourself to match him?
I've been there before.
We're two of a kind.
To me, you look like a girl trying too hard to be someone she isn't.
What do you really want to do?
I...
I want...
I'm not very diligent, but I want to dedicate my time to a club!
I want to join the student council, too!
And I want to ask Shiroyama-kun—
Then just do it!
Why are you beating yourself up just because you aren't perfect?
Wait, sorry. I did exactly what you're doing, so I shouldn't be lecturing you!
And Setouchi-san, would you be my friend?
Y-Your friend?!
We're two of a kind. We'll make good friends. I just know it.
All right! Nagase Iori is back, baby!
Sorry for causing you so much trouble!
I've lived my life under a really silly impression.
I cared too much about the way I thought a normal person should behave.
I compared my actions to that idea of normal,
so I've always perceived myself to be acting like I was someone else.
Each time my mom divorced and remarried, and I got a new dad,
I tried to be a good girl according to his ideals.
I kept trying to be a good girl no matter who I was with.
But that wasn't how it should've been.
It's not about being normal.
Whether I'm acting in line with common sense or not, they'll always be there tell me that I'm me.
It's my damn life!
I'll live it any damn way I want!
Nothing else matters.
Man, it's already morning.
Iori, does your mom know you went out?
We told our parents we'd be staying at school overnight.
Yeah, I took care of that.
I called her last night.
You really surprised me back there.
I can't believe you asked her to be your friend.
Seriously, all I could think of was how amazing you were.
But I'm not trying to force my own ideals on you or anything.
I was putting a lot of pressure on you without even knowing it.
I'm really sorry about that.
Either way, you were really amazing!
Don't let it get to you.
It's okay. I know what you're trying to say.
But asking her to be your friend was just way out of left field.
No normal person would ever ask that.
I'm done caring about what's normal and what isn't.
It's my damn life, and I'm living it any damn way I want.
Inaba!
Taichi!
Do you think we were in love?
I think we were.
As immature as we were.
I think so, too.
I'm sorry I was so immature.
I never saw the real you.
I always just imagined my ideal version of you.
But I was really happy that you fell in love with me.
I mean it.
I know.
Thanks.
I loved you, too.
My feelings for you were real.
But there was so much I didn't know back then.
I did so many things wrong...
So I want a reset on our relationship.
Sorry for being so selfish.
I have to apologize for that, myself.
To be honest, I was kind of drunk with love back then.
This conversation is really embarrassing.
We can only have it because we're here.
I guess we have the phenomenon to thank for that.
You'll never get me to be thankful for that.
Just let me say one last thing.
I have something I want to say, too.
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Taichi?
Taichi?!
Taichi!
Good morning, Inaba.
I'm so glad...
If anything ever happened to you...
I'd...
Don't cry.
Where are we?
The infirmary at school.
One of those bastards hit you...
And then he got away...
The school was closer than the hospital, so we carried you here.
Should I call an ambulance, just to be safe?
It's not that big of a deal.
Still, sorry for worrying you.
Don't push yourself.
If anything ever happened to you, I'd...
And if it was my fault...
You... I...
I need you!
Definitely!
I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you so much! I love you so much! I love you so much!
No! Stop!
I love you so much!
I don't!
So, so, so much!
I mean, I do, but...
Love me back!
Don't listen to me!
Make love to me!
I love you!
Will you go out with me?
G-Go out?!
Do I look cute?
Yes, very.
Okay. Good.
No!
What the hell did I just ask?!
Um...
Well, um...
Yes.
Nagase-san.
Well...
I think this is the end.
I thought it might be best to tell you that.
You kept transmitting my emotions to everyone when I was feeling like total crap.
I bet you chose the worst possible emotions at the worst possible times.
Did I?
I can't say.
You said it was completely random, but you chose precise moments just to make things worse.
You did it to make me hate myself.
Now...
Isn't that something that you decide for yourself?
Well, it seems like we've reached a rather nice point.
Don't you think so?
Ah, I never imagined that I would be like this with you five.
Perhaps I'm strange.
Regardless, this is the end of the phenomenon.
I'll be going now. Good-bye.
Who's that?
Is that Setouchi-san?
So you're keeping the earrings in?
Yeah. I like them.
Kaoru-chan, don't you think you look cuter this way?
Are you trying to say I wasn't cute before, Iori?
I'm not!
What's going on here?!
Tell me, tell me, Iori!
What happened to you?
Is that seriously you, Setouchi?
She definitely looks cuter like this!
Hey, do you guys know what happened?
Let's just say things ended on a positive note.
Nagase's amazing.
Just as I planned.
Good work, children of Class 1-3.
Club Presentations
And so, the day of the club presentations arrived.
Our next best spot is here!
A fancy café that's perfect for dates!
You have our word that your relationship is sure flourish after just one visit!
As proof, two of our club members who went there have already started dating!
Isn't that right, Taichi? Inaba?
Hey, that wasn't in the script!
But we did start going out...
That's not what we're here to present!
Good job, you guys!
As your moderator, I'm very proud!
Are you allowed to be in here right now?
The jazz band just finished their performance.
Yeah, and their performance was great, too!
I'm moved by the hard work both clubs put forth!
And I'm touched that I'm popular enough among my students
for them to be fighting over me!
With that in mind, I thought maybe I could be moderator for both clubs.
Excuse me?
You can do that?!
Yeah!
I thought about it,
and all I really have to do is be your moderator and supervise jazz band practices in my spare time!
What do you think?
If you could've done that from the start...
you should've spoke up sooner!
You freaking retard!
Inaban, tighten that lock!
Hey! I want in, too!
Then it won't be punishment anymore!
I'd be more than happy if you did it to me!
Where did Inaba learn that technique?
Don't just sit there! Help me!
We were somehow able to ride through another phenomenon.
When April rolls around, the CRC will have the same moderator and be run the same way.
Just as Aoki feared, he had to take make-ups.
Because failing meant not moving on to the next grade with Kiriyama,
he studied like there was no tomorrow.
I heard Kiriyama helped him study, too.
It seems like they're getting closer, slowly but surely.
Inaba and I have started dating.
Are you sure you wanted to choose me?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It just took us too many detours to get here.
Iori said that, too, but...
I need you, and you need me, too.
There's no reason to hesitate.
Taichi!
Wait, Inaba...
Taichi...
Stop that! We're in public!
Hey, Inaba!
After seeing Inaba act like this,
Nagase started calling her "Dereban" instead of "Inaban."
Nagase is back to being popular again.
She found a new friend in Setouchi, and they're getting along great.
As for the guys Setouchi asked to mess up our club room...
You don't have to worry about those thugs.
Inaba-san and I took very good care of them with my dad's help.
They will never try to harm you again!
Thanks...
Just what did they do to them?
I'm too scared to ask.
Entrance
Ceremony
Yamaboshi High School
Time for new students already?
I wonder if there's anyone weird enough to join us.
We'd better start planning on how to deal with them.
Joining the CRC means that there's a chance they'll be dragged into some crazy stuff.
I don't think we need to worry about that.
Cultural Research Club
Balloon Vine hasn't shown himself since the last school year.
Recruiting new members
Come, new members!!
Let's not let our guard down.
He might be planning to strike when we least expect it.
Well said.
You can never tell what'll happen next in life!
But so long as you have faith in your feet, the road you walk will be a part of you!
Iori-chan with words of wisdom!
Full speed ahead!
Let's have all the fun we can today!
We still have long lives ahead of us.
We'll all have our share of hesitation and worry.
But we'll plant our feet firmly on the road we walk.
Connecting our hearts with the hearts of others.
hanarebanare itsu no watashi
It's time to say good-bye to the person I once was
sashinoberareteru te no naka
In the palm of the hand held out to me
kagi wo kaketa chiisai hako ni
I turned the key in the lock of a little box
shitteta hazu no michi no mikaku
The bends in the road that I thought I knew
itamu kizu wo hoobarugoto ni
Each time I filled my cheeks with all those wounds and pain
mata netami ga netsujou ga
In me, the envy and the passion
tsumetasa ga hikari ga
And the cold and the light
kyozetsu ga kibou ga
And the rejection and the hope
karamariai nani mo dekizu ni
Knotted in my heart; I couldn't stand it,
sakebu
I screamed
torokeru amakute kuroi kanjou wa chocolatl
This sweet, flowing, black emotion is like chocolatl
risou nante mou moetsukete shimatta no
All my ideals are already burnt to ash
yowamushi no miminari wa yamanai
The word "weakling" won't stop ringing in my ears
afureteku watashi wo
I'm spilling over, full of myself
mitsukete
Find me
Thank you for watching!
Yaegashi Taichi