We've come to return the car we borrowed.
"Fukumoto Gang"
Thank you very much.
We'll be going now.
Hold on a minute. I heard about you.
You must be the ones who worked a
number on that fool Tsubouchi
before my young members even arrived.
That's impressive.
For kids these days, you have real guts.
What do you say?
Won't you be part of my manly business?
Chairman. I'm not sure that's...
Oh, come, now.
We appreciate the offer, sir, but
we'd like to remain regular civilians.
Oh, I see.
Well, just let me know if you ever change your mind.
Hey, let's go, Cabbage.
A manly business...
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Ryuga
Typesetting:
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon, Ryuga
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Shades
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
What are you going to do now, Joe?
Well, I thought about living with Meg,
but I have to start all over from square
one and don't have much money
so that won't work out...
What about you, Meg?
I'm happy just being able to see my brother again.
Plus, my work has a dormitory.
Hey, Meg! Where is your club?!
I'll definitely go there!
Shut up! Butt out, you big pervert!
Lay one finger on Meg and I wont forgive you!
What does it matter to you?!
Oww...!
Okay! Let's go toast to Joe and Meg being reunited!
Cheers!
--Cheers!
--Mario was so strong then!
--Really?!
--What about you, Soldier?
--I was devoted to my profession.
Hey, what's up with Cabbage anyway?
Yeah, he's got somethin' on his mind...
I better get going. I got a curfew.
I gotta get to work myself.
--I'll walk you to your dorm, Meg.
--Okay.
They're such sticks in the mud...
Meg...
They're so lucky...
Mario and Soldier and Joe all have things to do...
Hey! What's going on, Cabbage?!
You too, Scam.
You're always studying...
You're gonna be a big shot, right?
Turtle and I are the only ones without anything...
I do have a job, actually...
Then it is just me after all...
Hey, Cabbage...
Alright! Let's go drinking at another place! My treat!
I've decided!
I'm going to train with the Fukumoto Gang!
The Fukumoto Gang?!
Don't be stupid! Do you wanna die
before you're an adult?!
Listen! That's not the kind
of work for a nice guy like you!
So just forget it!
Later, Cabbage! Take care on your way home!
Yeah. See you later...
The Fukumoto Gang eh...
That moron really will join the Yakuza
if we don't do something first.
We just need to find a job that's perfect for Cabbage.
Leave it to me!
I'll reinvigorate our withered Cabbage!
"Unequaled Energy"
"Fresh Turtle Blood Meal"
"2 for 100 yen"
Okay! Step right up! Have a look!
Uh...
I have genuine turtle blood powder!
Oh! An energy medicine!
Only two for 100 yen?! That's insanely cheap!
Just one and you're in tip-top shape!
W-Works wonders for men who come home exhausted!
Wives just love it!
Wait, is this that really true?!
Sounds fishy after all!
Y-Yeah! Take some yourself and prove it to us!
S-Sure! In that case...
Ugh...
Alright, Cabbage.
When Turtle says, "Prove it," you
take some of that fake medicine
and then break this cracked rock for everyone to see.
Got it?
What?! This is fake?!
Of course it is!
Why would you bother selling real stuff?!
I see...
Take the medicine, break the rock.
Take the medicine, break the rock...
Will you hurry up already?!
Oh, right!
Next, I'll...
--Cabbage...
--You did it backwards...
Hold on! What's going on here?!
Th-That's amazing! I'm sold!
--I'll take ten!
--Thanks, Scam!
Wh-Why would you say my name...?!
Ridiculous!
What a scam, using plants and shills like that!
"Unbreakable
Glass Cups
Two for 100 yen"
Step right up! Take a look!
See the glass cups that will never break!
--Are they really unbreakable, Mister?
--Y-Yeah...
Yeah, right! Prove it, then!
S-Sure!
Lets see...
Wow! It doesn't break at all!
You idiot! There's a trick to it!
Glass cups are made to be strong on the bottom!
They're tough to break like that!
I see!
Hit the bottom, hit the bottom, hit the bottom...
Hurry up, Mister!
Oh, right!
Okay, pay close attention now!
So they are breakable.
This is stupid. Let's go!
You're the one who comes up
with these cheap scams in the first place...
Whatever! You had no problem agreeing to it!
I'm sorry, guys...
I guess there's nothing I'm good at after all...
Well, I should go. Thanks for trying...
Cabbage!
Cabbage...
"Fukumoto Gang"
Please let me join you!
My name is Mansaku Matsuura!
Oh, I'm glad to hear it!
You're welcome here! Train hard, now!
Th-Thank you!
So, you guys basically talked Cabbage
into doing some cheap scams...
...and then you just let him run off and join the Yakuza?
What do we do, Mario?
What can we do... It was his own choice...
How can you be so carefree?!
You know Cabbage isn't cut out to be a gangster!-
And who's fault is it?
Let's see how things go for now.
He'll come back once he realizes
he's not cut out for it.
Thank you for taking me in!
--Hey. Tanaka.
--Yes?
You're Matsuura's teacher. I leave him to you.
Yes, got it.
C-Clean?
Yeah. Clean the entire office, from top to bottom.
Got it?
Yes!
So... when do we eat? I'm starving...
Ouch!
Matsuura. C'mere when you're done with this room.
Yes!
Shoe-polishing?
Yeah. Yakuza always need to look their best.
Make 'em all shine.
Umm... when do we eat?
Ouch!
Matsuura! What the hell are you doing?!
Hello?
Yes, this is the Fukumoto Gang!
You dumbass! Who told you to answer the phone?!
Do you even know what this place is?!
That could be anyone calling!
Answer the phone again and I'll kill you!
I see...
Ol' Cabbage still hasn't come back?
What is he doing? It's been two weeks now!
So, how's Matsuura?
Terrible. He's completely useless.
He's not a bad guy, though.
I see.
The chairman and I have to
attend a family meeting tonight.
You're in charge while we're gone.
Yes! Got it.
Hey, Matsuura...
Yes?
Why do you wanna be a gangster?
If I were you, I'd split while I still can.
I'm no good at anything else, really...
Is anyone home?
Oh, a visitor...!
Wait!
I'll check it out. You stay here.
Hello?
May I ask who you are?
Sorry to bother you this late. I'm Kato, I live nearby...
Ugh. What do you want--?
Say your prayers, Fukumoto! This is the day you die!
Mr. Tanaka?
M-Matsuura... Run...
Where is Fukumoto?
Fukumoto! Quit hiding and show yourself!
"Three weeks later"
Mario! This is bad!
It's Cabbage! Cabbage might be dead!
What are you talking about?
I heard it myself!
People who live near the Fukumoto Gang
said there'd been an attack!
It really happened. I confirmed it...
It was a big commotion, with the
cops and ambulances showing up...
Some young members of the gang
were chopped up during the attack...
It's... It's my fault!
If it hadn't been for that stupid plan of mine...!
What do we do, Mario?!
Don't be stupid! Cabbage would
never kick the bucket that easily!
You said there were ambulances, right?
Yeah...
He must've been taken to a hospital, then.
That's the only possibility!
All right! We'll look into it!
The cops should be able to tell us!
"Watanabe Hospital"
This is the place...
This is where Cabbage...
We don't know that for sure yet.
Let's go.
We have no patients by the name of Mansaku Matsuura.
Look again! Mansaku Matsuura!
He was definitely brought here!
I'm sorry, but...
What do you want with Matsuura?
Oh, you're the guy who brought the car back with him…
Where's Cabbage?! He's here, isn't he?!
First...
Hand over the weapon in your coat.
Mario, what are you...?
What were you planning to do with this?
Were you thinkin' of attacking us with it?
Dumbass! A civilian waving this at us
would mean serious trouble!
I would mean serious trouble, too.
What?!
If anything happens to Cabbage, I will avenge him.
I can't back down, no matter who I am dealing with.
Because Cabbage is an irreplaceable friend to us.
I can't stand dealing with snot-nosed kids.
Visit Hibiya Park tonight at 7:00.
Cabbage is going to be there?!
Cabbage has some good friends.
Now get goin'.
Thank you very much.
"Who would've guessed that lowlife
Matsuura had any friends like them..."
His face distorted by living in a savage world,
Tanaka fully understood
that friends are far more reliable
than parents, money, or women.
"I remember having brothers like them once..."
He uses the ropes and attempts a trap throw!
He starts to get up and... a drop kick!
The crowd is going wild!
Hey, is he really gonna be--?
It's Cabbage...!
It looks like Matsuura won't get his wish
for his first victory today!
No way... Cabbage?
"Restaurant"
Another bowl, Mister!
Hey, Cabbage. I thought you joined the Fukumoto Gang...
Yeah, I did.
So how are you a pro wrestler now?!
Well, actually...!
Die, kid!
Then I called for an ambulance,
and then the police showed up too!
Before I knew it, the place
was swarming with investigators!
You dumb fool! What Yakuza
gang calls an ambulance to their office?!
I-I'm sorry...!
You damn kid! I am going to chop
you up and feed you to the dogs!
Chairman...
Allow me to deal with him.
A finger or two won't be enough! Understand Arito?!
Yes.
Umm... Is Mr. Tanaka okay?
Yeah.
Really?! That's a relief!
You're worried about someone else
after the chairman almost killed you?
Huh?
You're definitely not cut out for the Yakuza.
So he said if I wanted to be in a manly profession,
I should give pro wrestling a try!
It's really great! I can eat all I want at the training hall!
Wh-What? What's so funny?
At this time, the Yakuza still had an air of romanticism and glamor.
Unable to blame Cabbage for his serious blunder,
Arito of the Fukumoto Gang instead
introduced him to the world of wrestling.
"Cabbage! You can now eat to your heart's content!
Set all of Japan abuzz with your freakish strength!"
Thank you for helping Cabbage.
Tanaka was released from the hospital today.
Tanaka would've died, had he not called for help.
If you see Matsuura, tell him this for me...
"Never show your face around the gang again."
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
His first woman.
Drunk with love, Scam loses sight of everything.