A ball game field day?
It's a Noble Academy tradition.
It'll be discussed during tomorrow's homeroom.
What's a ball game field day?
It's a day where everyone plays sports that use balls.
That sounds fun!
I'm your brother, not a ball!
So, which ball games in particular?
This year's games are...
soccer,
basketball,
and tennis.
Each team will be coed.
So, boys and girls? That's unusual.
The event is meant to foster friendships.
The boys and girls otherwise keep to themselves, right?
Now that you mention it, I don't think we talk much...
So, what do you wanna enter?
Me?
Obviously...
I'd pick tennis!
Why?
Why not?
It's the most princess-y sport!
Good lu—ugh...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Reunited by Tennis!
My Old Bully?!
Field Day Team Rosters
One, two!
Hooray! My luck's in full bloom!
Winner
Same here!
Really? Good luck!
My God, why hast thou forsaken us?!
Field Day Team Rosters
Tennis Pairs
Shiraishi
&
Nanase
Shiraishi
&
Nanase
Aihara
&
Haruno
Aihara
&
Haruno
And so, Shiraishi and Nanase will make up Doubles 1.
Doubles 2 will be Aihara and Haruno.
Aihara, you entered tennis when
you're already on the tennis team?
You're a real tennis nut.
What can I say?
The tennis, she calls to me!
Field Day Team Rosters
Tennis Pairs
Shiraishi
&
Nanase
Shiraishi
&
Nanase
Aihara
&
Haruno
Aihara
&
Haruno
Good luck, Haruno.
Sure! Same to you, Aihara!
Those girls are fans of Aihara's...
Fans? He has those?
Soccer
Team
Roster
Soccer
Team
Roster
Next up is the soccer team!
Aihara?
Are you free after school?
Huh?
Practice?
Just a little before I meet with the team.
I wanna know how good you are, too.
All right!
Let's start with your serve!
Okay, coming right up!
Just try and return my Princess Serve!
Huh?
I'll get the next one! Probably...
Is this your idea of "coming right up"?!
Sorry! I've never played tennis before...
Never?! You've got nothing?!
Then why would you pick tennis?!
But it's the most princess-y sport!
Huh? Princess?
Nuh-uh!
You couldn't be a princess in a million years!
Aihara? As in Aihara Yuuki?!
Haruno Haruka... don't tell me you're that Haruno!
I didn't notice at all...
Me neither. It's been a while since kindergarten.
I never thought you'd end up in this school, much less in my own class.
You're not going on about that Princess of Flowers stuff anymore, right?
Gulp!
Wait, seriously?!
Do you need a shrink?
Come on, I'm a Princess Precure now!
You have to keep the Precures a secret!
I know that! That just makes it worse!
Darn you, Yuuki, you big, fat...
There, there.
I guess even you have people you dislike.
When we were in kindergarten,
he made fun of my dream to be a princess.
He did a bunch of other mean things to me...
He's nothing like the gentleman Kanata is...
Tch, tch, tch!
You'd be hard-pressed to find a man nearly as gentle as Sir Kanata!
Oh, why did I ever pick tennis?
But this might be a good opportunity.
Huh?
Working together may give you two the chance to bury the hatchet.
You've barely talked at all since classes began, right?
Yeah...
Bonjour!
See ya!
Hey!
Yuuki!
Huh? Whatcha need?
Can you give me some tennis lessons after school?
I'll practice for real this time!
Uh... nah, you're fine just standing.
Huh?
Just let me handle it.
We can win if I do all the work.
But then there's no point in us being a pair...
Sloppy play would only bring me down.
Nobody beats me at tennis.
No matter what the stakes.
But hey, feel free to practice serving.
You can handle that on your own, right?
See ya!
Wha...
What's that supposed to mean?!
He completely blew me off!
Well, I'll show him!
Are you gonna transform?
The Precure's power is meant for fighting Dyspairvils!
Bonjour, tout le monde!
Bonjour, Madame Siamour!
Ma pauvre, there's not much "bon" in ta "bonjour."
Please give me lessons in tennis!
There's someone I gotta show up!
He's not making a fool of me again!
I think I'm missing something here...
but I feel ta passion!
Oui, let's commençons the lesson!
Huh? Where are we?
And where'd I get this tennis outfit from?
This is la Lesson Scène.
It's a flexible space that suits the lesson's needs.
Wow.
And who might you be?
That's Madame Siamour.
Huh?!
Je am also flexible here.
Now, let's begin by getting you used to the ball.
Thanks for the help!
Beat Yuuki!
Beat...
Yuuki!
At this rate, I'll kick Yuuki's butt!
Who's your opponent supposed to be, again?
You're getting better, Haruharu.
Kirara, what game did you enter?
Basketball.
Wow, that's so cool!
How skilled are you?
I'd say I'm average,
but basketball is the only sport held indoors.
I can't let myself get a sunburn.
Oh yeah... that's right.
Modeling is your dream.
That's reasonable.
Nobody beats me at tennis.
No matter what the stakes.
Oh, Aihara!
I thought club hours already ended.
You didn't know?
Aihara always stays late to train as much as possible.
He does?
Aihara!
You okay, Aihara?
This is nothing!
I'm not done yet!
All right, let's run another set.
Right!
We'll now begin Noble Academy's middle school division field day!
Since Close is busy contending with Lady Dyspear's wrath,
there is naught but for me to defeat the Precures!
Double bun!
Good going, Amanogawa!
Nice shot!
Kirara's on fire!
Oh, Minami!
I didn't think she could play soccer.
Minami can do anything.
Minami, you're splendid!
So, practiced your serves?
I-I did.
Well, I'm not counting on you, so take it easy.
I'll take care of everything.
Gee, thanks.
Oh, we're off to a bad start...
Can Haruka do this?
One set match, Haruno to serve!
It got over?
Yuuki!
Got it!
15-Love!
Yay, Aihara!
Yay! Haruka's training worked!
She still has lots more to work on!
Haruno!
All right, we can do this!
Let's go!
There is naught but to interrupt this game.
It's Shut!
I came drawn by your cries of joy
only to find the perfect specimen.
Hey, move it, pal!
Stay away from him, Yuuki!
Beat it!
I don't care what's at stake,
nobody interrupts my tennis games!
Oh?
You seem quite passionate, boy.
I'm certain the same applies to your dream.
There is naught but to use it!
Now, show me your dream.
I won a Grand Slam!
There is naught but to imprison that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Yuuki!
That must be...
Haruka!
Transform!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil...
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
'Scuse me, coming through!
Where do you think you're going? That's dangerous!
Hey, lemme go!
Minami, this way!
But there might be students left behind...
Dyspairvil!
Dys! Pair! Vil!
Shoot!
Flora!
That's a good look for you, Cure Flora.
There is naught but for me to end these foolish games of yours.
Dyspairvil! There is naught but to finish her!
Dyspair!
It's not foolish...
Just wait, Yuuki...
I understand...
I know how much it hurts to have your dream trampled upon!
That's why...
I swear I'll protect your dream!
Dyspair!
Vil...
Stop right there!
Minami!
Kirara!
Flora!
Sorry for the wait!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Dyspairvil!
What are you doing? You are naught but to capture the Precures!
Dyspair!
Over here!
Dyspairvil!
Twinkle!
Okay!
Here goes!
Flora! Now's your chance!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Hmph. There will be naught but for me to return and finish what I began!
Open!
The door to your dream!
A princess... of flowers?
I hope your dream comes true.
Were we all just seeing things?
Well, it's good that nothing happened.
Now let's get back to our matches!
Yuuki, we're up soon!
You know, I saw someone...
who looked like a princess of flowers.
H-Huh? What's gotten into you?
That's just what I saw, so...
your dream of being a princess isn't just a fantasy.
Hey, you've got guts!
That serve was great. Honestly, I had you all wrong!
Yuuki!
Th-Then...
do you think I could become a splendid princess?
Good question.
Keep at it for a few hundred years and we'll see.
You're basically saying I can't!
Just so we're clear, that princess you saw was—
Haruno to serve!
Haruharu, you've got this!
Come on! I'm Cure Flora!
Why you...
What was that for?!
I'm sorry! It wasn't on purpose!
It totally was!
Aw, so much for their shot at winning this.
Seems like it'll be a while before they're on good terms.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
It's my first time trying to make a dress!
Go! Princess Precure:
Not in a Million Years?!
Haruka Makes a Dress!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Nagasaki Prefecture - Honoka (Age 7)
Saitama Prefecture - Hana (Age 6)