When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
So good~
It's already February...
I've yet to see Hayate-kun once this year.
But soon, the greatest opportunity of the year will come!
Yes, the biggest event for all girls in February is-
Gosh, mister. What do you think you're doing in front of a girl?
Me?
Oni stay out!
Setsubun: An activity to ward off Oni by throwing roasted beans on February 3rd.
Luck stays in!
Oni stay out!
Um, why are we doing this now?
What are you talking about, Maria?
She's right. The biggest event in February has to be this.
That is all right, but Nagi, it's getting late, so please start getting ready for bed.
Yes. Then let's end this by eating your age's worth in beans.
Here.
Yes.
How about you, Maria?
Okay, I guess I will, too.
What's wrong, all of you?
What were you staring at?
N-Nothing!
Nothing at all!
Don't tell me you were thinking that there's not enough beans.
No, absolutely not!
No matter who looks at you, you're a fresh seventeen year old.
Then why are you drenched in sweat?
All of you, go to bed now!
An Oni was inside.
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
Seriously, why are they such...
Ow! Oh no, my lower back. It hurts...
Gosh darn. We made Maria mad again.
You don't say.
Don't give her too much trouble.
She's not forever young.
Don't say such a scary thing!
But, Maria has been working without any breaks.
She may be the best of all professional maids, but she must be letting fatigue pile up.
We are always in her great care,
so it'd be nice if we could show our appreciation.
Okay! Then I shall become a maid and-
If you do that, Maria-san will become even more tired.
But she's not the kind of person who will take a break even if you tell her to.
E-Exactly as you say.
Oh right. That's a perfect plan!
A plan?
Approximately one hour later.
What is this about?
Where are we going all of a sudden?
I wonder where.
It'll be a surprise for when we get there.
Where is this?
Tonight, we're staying here!
The thing is, Saki-san gave us some input.
Ladies Overnight Plan, Relaxation Tour?
A friend of mine went there the other day.
Stay at an expensive hotel in the middle of the city, enjoy the spa and aesthetic salon,
forget about work, and relax.
I heard it's popular among young working women as a gift to themselves for working hard.
Young...
...working women.
Young... Young... Young...
That's the key word?
Yes, this is it!
Get right to it, Hayate.
Yes.
Therefore, we call it, "Maria-san, thank you so much all the time. Gratitude to our Onee-sama, Relax Plan."
What? But, um...
This is a present from Milady as a sign of our gratitude.
Maria, thank you so much for working so hard for us all the time.
But for today and tomorrow, forget about your work and enjoy a vacation in the city.
Thank you very much.
Then I'll take your offer and have a good rest.
Yes. Relax all you like.
Let us go then.
Yes.
Welcome.
Who knew that Hayata-kun and the others would come to stay.
I'll take the room over there.
I guess Maria and I will use that room then.
First, let me get some tea ready.
Maria-san, you're on vacation, so please don't do anything.
Ah, yes, that's right.
Hayate prepared lots of things.
Hello? This is the imperial suite; I'd like to order room service.
The pool, jacuzzi, gym, aesthetic salon, and nail salon.
A pot of royal milk tea, please.
You can use any facility as much as you want.
Apparently this hotel's sales point is service towards young women.
It's perfect for a young working woman like Maria.
You don't have to emphasize "young" so much.
Excuse me. It's room service.
Yes, thank you.
So? Don't I look good in this? Did I surprise you?
Class rep? What are you doing here?
It's a one day experience event at school.
I've seen it on the news before.
Ah!
What is it, Hayate?
Oh, well for some reason, today's a 5%-off service day.
That's the reason I chose this place, but...
Makes sense.
Exactly. Today, this hotel is covered by Hakuou.
I saw Hayata-kun and his group here just a while ago.
Oh...
I was hoping Oo**** or Yoshi**** were coming.
Yoshi****? Because we're right in front of the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building?
Oh whatever. Where's Hina, by the way?
She got trapped with the manager.
Looking back at it now, it was back when
the Tokyo Olympics were going on that I started this job.
I can't get a sense of the timeframe at all.
Hayate, you've got to get this right!
We need to have Maria enjoy the vacation.
I'm sorry. My habit of saving on things took over.
Hot!
I'll do it.
Thank you, Maria-san.
See what I mean?
I'll do it, Maria-san!
By the way, what did all of you come here for?
Well...
That's such a great story.
I'm touched!
I'll help you out.
I'll tell everyone, too!
Segawa-san!
I have a...
...really bad feeling about this.
Um... If it's about me, please don't worry. I'm already relaxing.
No! We can't give up now!
We must protect Maria's break no matter what!
Let's split up!
Milady and Maria-san, please proceed on to Plan 2!
We'll meet back here in three hours!
Leave it to me, Hayate!
Wait!
Wh-Why is this starting to feel like a battle?
She's right. This is a form of battle.
How is it, Maria? Relaxing?
Yes, thank you!
Oh wow! It's like a rose bath.
But wait, this is the pool.
Strange. I don't recall asking for service like that.
No need for your thanks.
Take this instead.
Excuse me, but who are you?
Himuro, is this enough?
Yes. Was it educational, Sir Taiga?
Yes. Working sure is hard.
Meanwhile, Hayate was...
Oh no... People from Hakuou are here, too.
What's the matter, Sir?
At that rate, you can't possibly give the customers satisfactory service.
Leg... my leg... This is impossible...
Okay. Next we'll go for the aesthetic salon.
Make sure you get relaxed this time!
Y-Yes. But, Nagi...
Why the Super Special Marvelous Anti-Aging Course?
Don't let the details bother you!
I'll be in the room next door!
Thank you for coming.
What? You're the trash robot!
Please come right over here.
Hey, you're surprisingly pretty good.
Of course, since I always give massages to Makimura-san.
I guess I'll go get relaxed, too.
Hey.
I heard the story from Segawa-san.
Wh-Why is even Katsura-sensei here?
It was an opportunity to try, and also,
I wanted to learn some new skills in case I get fired.
Come on. Leave everything to me.
I'll do everything to make you relax.
I feel a serious error... I mean...
a serious danger threatening me.
Ahhh. This is so relaxing.
This is so good~
Looks like being a teacher really wears you out.
And before I know it, I'm already twenty-eight.
Makes me wonder if I can continue to live the way I do.
But, you are who you are, so no matter how much you worry, you can't become another individual.
So please always be yourself.
But do watch out how much you drink.
You feel this? It's the pressure point for your liver.
Thank you, Maria-san!
It... It feels like I just met a role model for life!
Um, I'm more than ten years younger than you!
Hey, Maria, is something wrong?
I just sensed a strange atmosphere.
N-No, it's nothing.
I just sensed a bad omen.
Your new dress looks great on you, Kuzuha-sama.
It's specially made by COSPA.
I must be dressed in formal attire like this all the time.
You look so great, Kuzuha-sama.
Okay, Shion. Before we start the tour, let's go raise our blood sugar level.
Yes, Kuzuha-sama.
Oh yuck.
It's heading away from relaxation and continues on.
Nonbiri yuttari.
Nonbiri yuttari. = Relax and make yourself at home.
Rizumu de shiritori suta-to.
Rizumu de shiritori suta-to. = Starting rhythmical shiritori.
Tan tan tan nta. Matteru.
Tan tan tan nta. Matteru. = Tan tan tan nta. Now waiting.
I hope they're both enjoying the city vacation.
Hey, Hayate! I'm back.
Welcome back. But where's Maria-san?
She said she'll take a stroll in the garden to relax.
"Relax", she said?!
Yes. "Relax" it is!
Hold on! Since Maria won't be coming back to the room for a while...
Hayate and I are alone!
I'll make some tea right away.
Plus, we're in a suite that newly-wed couples are likely to stay in!
Is something wrong?
Nothing!
It's not easy to take a break.
But, since the two of them are being considerate...
During the time I'm here, I must respond to their thoughts by having a slow day.
Um...
Isumi-san!
Um... Um... There's something I'd like to ask.
Might this be where Hakuou's practical training event is?
Yes, it is.
I'm so happy!
I was finally able to make it to a destination in episode 45.
I thought I would never make it in time.
A-Anyway, let's go to the front desk together.
But it's a surprise that you're going to be part of an event like this.
I wanted to learn about society through the event.
Maria-san.
Oh, the Hakuou students.
Maria-san!
Maria-san.
Is something wrong?
You seem to be distracted.
Because it's too quiet in here.
Let's turn the TV on.
I love you!
Oh no. This would get Hayate in the mood.
As much as we love each other, it's too early for us.
It's too early!
Oh, I like this actress quite a bit.
Ever since she broke up with the kabuki actor,
she's been doing much better.
Gosh, what is Maria doing? How long does she have to relax until she's satisfied?
She was not relaxing at all.
See? The trick is to tuck both bed sheets and the cover and line them up properly.
Thank you, Maria-san.
I just double booked a room by mistake.
Hello. We're very sorry. We can get a room with
twin beds ready instead of double beds, if that's all right.
Thank you, Maria-san.
Ah, yes. The year I came over here was the year of the Osaka Expo, 1971.
Oh please, Manager.
The Osaka Expo was in 1970.
If I remember correctly, the total number of guests was 64,218,770 people.
The number of countries participating, including Japan, was 77 countries and 4 international authorities.
E-Excuse me for a moment!
Thank you so much, Maria-san.
But, isn't today your day off? You don't need to go rest?
Please keep this a secret from Nagi and Hayate-kun.
We're in trouble, Manager!
Mari-pon. What are you doing here?
Mari-pon?!
Hello, Makimura-san.
Um, you two know each other?
Yes, through certain circumstances.
Thank goodness. I want to ask you a favor regarding something, Maria-chi.
Maria-chi?!
Is there something wrong?
Well, the cafeteria is high schooling and is in trouble!
Milady. Please stop staying on six.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who else can it be?
Hello?
Ah, Mari-
Shh! Keep it a secret that this call is from me.
Well, you see...
What happened to Maria-san?
M-Maria-san.
I was cleaning up a room
and found a customer's forgotten item.
What was the room number?
Let's look up the contact information.
Um, where is the Concierge?
I sent him over that way.
Um, sorry to bother you.
Nihao. Wo jiao Maria.
Note: This is Chinese for "Hello. My name is Maria."
Maria-san.
Please keep this a secret from Nagi.
Of course.
So, why did you call me?
May I ask for a favor?
Where's the next treat?
We're sorry!
We were making sweets at high speed to keep up with your orders, but the pâtissier collapsed from being overloaded.
Weak! I've not yet had enough!
Sorry for the wait.
This is a hidden menu, special Mont Blanc.
Th-This is...
This is concentrated yet simple,
while the sweetness covers the tongue like velvet!
It's that good?!
So good~
I'm satisfied.
I quit the tour. Before I snap out of this enchanted feeling, I'm heading back to the academy.
Y-Yes.
Wow, Maria-san's recipe works great.
After all, its effect was proven in the past.
Oh, nothing.
What are you doing here, Makimura-sensei?
Well, I'm just reading books and eating cake.
Aren't you supposed to be advising the practical?
You're flabbergasted, aren't you?
Cake is important for the brain, you know?
Please show him to the bathroom right away.
Yes, Ma'am!
Maria! So it was you!
That cake tasted the same as the one
I had tasted at a school festival in the past.
It has been a while.
It was the most delectable sweet I've had in a while. Thank you.
You should be happy!
I guess I'll head back over to Nagi.
Nothing special happened thereafter and the day ended.
I'm so tired. I'm so hungry.
Then let's all grab something to eat.
But...
You don't have money, right?
We'll treat you.
Really?
Yahoo!
Onee-chan...
Doesn't she have any pride as a fully grown adult?
I don't care! I'm going to live as who I am.
How rare to see her fall asleep at this hour.
Did she get tired from an environment she's not used to?
Milady was very excited about the plan, after all.
She was committed to having Maria-san enjoy the day.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes. Good night.
I see, Maria.
So your fatigue has blown away, huh?
That's good. I'm always so grateful to you.
The mansion feels the best.
Then what about the Thank You Tour?
Thank you very much, both of you.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
But, Nagi, Hayate-kun, and the smiles of everyone at the mansion...
Those are the best presents for me.
That's great!
Please continue to look after us, Maria-san.
Of course.
By the way, Maria, your skin looks so smooth.
Did the Super Special Marvelous
Anti-Aging Course have an effect?
You're almost like a young girl!
Yes, you look as if you've lost few years, Maria-san.
I see... So a seventeen year old isn't a young girl anymore.
Or am I...
No, no, Maria, you got it wrong.
On that note, next week, we'll fight against the sweat perspired from youth.
Student Council Trio's
Butler Network!
Howdy everyone. It's Segawa Izumi.
Hey. It's Asakaze Risa.
I'm the warrior of freedom, Hanabishi Miki.
All of you in front to the TV,
you've memorized our image song, right?
Since I'm sure they're listening to it at least a hundred times a day.
A happy bit of news for people like that!
If you collect ten dust covers and send them in...
...you won't win anything in particular!
That's amazing!
You all must have been waiting. Here's this week's service shot.
Oh, this is erotic.
Starting out so bold so early in the morning.
Bye bye!
What's going on? Tell me!
You ask the strangest questions sometimes.
Something has to be wrong!
Isumi was wearing a blazer and went off on a bus without getting lost at all!
Maybe she fell in love with a boy in another school
and is sneaking into the school wearing their uniform.
What?!
Next time, his name is miracle ball pitcher, Wataru!
Why won't Sir consult with me?
It's like it's easier to talk with Lady Nagi,
who is the same age as him.
Therefore, next week, Cross Triangle to Hayate no Gotoku!