Well then, we should get started, as well.
Hey, wait!  Since when were you part of "us"?
Ha!  What sort of question is that?
I'm here to stand in for the uselessness that is yourself.
Disappear pitifully, just like toilet paper!
What did you say?!
Quit it, you two.
Kanade's working hard outside.
We need to get in touch with everyone in the Battlefront now.
What?  What's wrong, everyone?
I guess we're satisfied.
Hearing your story, it just made sense.
It helped us decide.
We're a group of people like that.
We kind of already knew it without you having to tell us.
After all, our vocalists are gone.
There are no replacements for Iwasawa-san and Yui.
Then again, she was a horrible vocalist.
Every day was like a culture festival.  It was so much fun.
Although, this is going to be difficult for people who aren't like us.
I bet.
If you're going to start this, then finish it.
Otherwise, it'll seem like you tricked us into this.
If this long-lasting Battlefront's going to be disbanded,
then this world has fulfilled its role, you included.
Knowing that, I can believe this was for the best.
We'll just say that for a time we enjoyed the days of youth we'd missed, and that'll be enough for us.
Don't be ridiculous.  I don't know how it'll end.
Yeah, of course not.
But well, I've quit worrying.
We'll get going now.  Just wanted to say that.
See you later,
Newbie!
We'll be a band next time, too!
Yeah.  I'm sure I'll enjoy it all over again.
Yeah.  Bye now.
Thank you for your hard work in sending off the minions.
You've got the worst sort of personality, you know?
I do not!  You would dare say that to God?!
Stop being idiots and let's go.
There are so many of them...
What's going on?
Where did all the NPCs go?
It seems these are all that's left.
Maybe they know what we're trying to do?
Scum.
Noda?
Nice going, Noda!
Does this mean you'll fight with us?!
Dream on!
I only move when it helps Yurippe!
I see.
You're such a stoic guy.
Ooyama!
I don't have any special traits, but I thought even God would be surprised at this!
Yeah, show Him what you've got!
Don't go forgettin' me.
I don't think anyone'd notice even if you disappeared right now!
I'll be the one-
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Knockin' on heaven's door.
That's Bob Dylan.
But very appropriate.
What's it mean?
No clue!
The main cast's starting to get together.
What is this world?  Just what is going on here?
More like, what happened to you?
Who're you?
Well, I was in the mountains for a while, but there wasn't enough food to eat.
Is that you... Matsushita Fifth?
Tasty candy!
You've lost so much weight.
Is everything all right?
Yeah!  In fact, I feel better than ever.
I feel like I might be able to take on a hundred people now.
That's actually something you do in karate.
In any case, it's a great help.
We've got all of them to worry about.
Let's all get outta this world safely.
Yeah.
Goodbye, wild heaven.
Okay.
We're going to break through!
The Guild is a great place to hide, but... it's enemy territory, you know?
It's our hideout.
Of course they'd be here.
Feels like party time.
This is endless.
Otonashi-san, please look below us.
There's more and more of them.
Behind you!
One hundred.
One hundred what?
One hundred...  consider that the strength of my support.
You don't get it?
I will carry out your will.
Go!
Shiina...
Right, I'll leave this to you.
Come with me, Hinata!
You got it!
Where are you going, Otonashi-san?
More of them are coming out, so does that mean I'm heading the right way?
I don't have much left.
I can't get through that many with a handgun, either.
What should I do...?
Yurippe.
Cha!
Everyone at the Guild heard the story.
They're all heading to the surface.
I see.
Take this.
Thanks!
So the war's... going to end...
Yes, it will.
I see.
Then we're disbanding, too.
We worked hard because you guys fought.
Thanks for the support.
Without you, none of it would have been possible.
No, I'm not that great.
See ya.
Time to go.
I must have come too far.
A moment's respite, I suppose.
I wonder if Tenshi...
I mean, I wonder if Kanade-chan's fighting, too.
I wish I could have understood this world sooner.
If I had, maybe I could have been friends with her.
I mean, we're both girls.
This world isn't really made for it, but maybe I could have had the chance to coordinate some cute clothes with her.
But... I guess that wasn't possible.
I can't forgive God, after all.
So...
Dammit!
Get lost!
Get lost!  Get lost!  Get lost!  Get lost!  Get lost!
So you see, this equation equals this.
Wait, wasn't I just thinking about something...?
I'm going to erase this now, okay?
What's wrong, Nakamura?
Can I erase it or not?
Yes, please, go ahead.
Dammit all!
That was embarrassing.
Hey, Yuri.
What were you doing in the middle of class like that?
Nothing special.
I was just thinking about something.
"Thinking"?  So much that you stopped listening to class?
Could it be love?!
It is, isn't it?
That's stupid.  I'd love to, but that's not the case.
I think Fujiwara-kun is interested in you, though~
Hey, are you listening to me, Yuri?
Look, Fujiwara-kun is alone right now.
Fujiwara-ku-!
Hey, stop that-
Wait, who are you?
Huh?  It's me, Hitomi.
A-Ah, right.  Hitomi.
Hey now, is something wrong with you?
Maybe.
That's because...
You're about to say it's because of my heartache, right?
Right!
Get back to your seat.
Okay!
Remember this part.
Nakamura, where are you looking?
Hey, Yuri.
Okay then, Nakamura, start reading from the beginning of the next page.
What's wrong?
This is a very happy life.
What are you talking about?
This is a very happy situation.
It's too dazzling for someone like me.
This is the kind of life everyone lives...
So wonderful, isn't it?  I'm envious.
If I'm obliterated from this place... can I redo my life?
Will I be able to accept this ordinary happiness?
Nakamura...
Yuri?
Losing all my memories...
My personality would change...
I could accept it then, right?
But then, what does it mean to be reborn?
It won't be my life anymore.
It would be someone else's life.
There's only one life for me.
And it's right here.
There's only one.
This is my life.
I can't give it to anyone else.
I can't get another, either.
I can't force it upon another, forget about it, erase it,
trample it, laugh about it, or overdramatize it.
I can't do anything to it!
We have no choice but to accept the one and only life we're given, no matter how cruel and heartless it may be.
Do you understand what I mean, Sensei?
That's why I fight.
That's why I continue to fight!
Because I...
I can never accept another life!
Give me your hand!
Hey, there!  Looks like we made it in time.
Otonashi-kun and Hinata-kun?
I'm here, too, by the way.
I made it back?
Kanade heard you, or rather, said she felt an explosion of your presence, and brought us here.
Kanade-chan?
I see.  Looks like I owe you all one.
You guys saved me.
But, why are you all here?
We left the surface to the others.
They said they would carry out our will.
And so you came to save me?
We came to fight beside you.
Same difference.
I guess.  But you make us worry.
Why don't you fix yourself up first?
Okay, let's head out!
S-Sure.
Man, she never changes.
Hey, doesn't it look like they're protecting that place?
What a coincidence.  That was my thought, exactly.
But we'll never get through there unless we bomb the place.
In that case, I'll go.
Kanade-chan!
How foolish.  That's suicidal!
No, wait.
Nice!
Is her combat ability equivalent to that of a bomber?
Let's go.
Damn, more of them are coming already!
Yuri, you go on ahead.
We'll take care of them.
All right.  Please do.
That's right, you can count on us.
They're totally making fun of me.
But this time...
Just how many did they steal?
There's the evidence.
I'm amazed you made it this far.
Don't screw with me.  You even have a plate on the door.
This place is a school, after all.
You have a unique sense of humor.
No, no.  That's a rule.
A rule set by God?
"God."
Highly debatable if He exists or not.
Very interesting, indeed.
But I don't have the capability to pursue that answer.
I only follow the set rules.
So you're programmed to do this, too.
How insightful.
Who're you working for?
What would be the point in giving you the name?
They have been here since long ago.
Angel Player...
What exactly is this software?
As you know, it is software that allows one to create and alter materials in this world.
How is it able to do that?
I wonder myself.  I am not the developer.
But you all create weapons from dirt, yourselves.
Is that not the same?
So in the end, we're playing by the same rules.
Did the developer of the software want to become God?
I wonder, myself.  I would not know.
Okay, we're short on time, so let's get down to business.
What was the trigger programmed into you to start all this?
I am not aware of the nature of the program.
Then let me rephrase the question.
What changed about this world, in your perspective?
Love has developed in this world.
What?  "Love"?
Yes, love.  That which is not meant to exist in this world.
He's right.  If love develops in this world,
the two involved should be obliterated instantly.
But if it were to develop and be sustained, what would happen to this world?
If love develops, this world changes into an eternal Eden.
But this world must not become that.
That is because this is a place from which everyone must graduate.
In other words, that's what someone thought up.
However, there are times when people with amnesia wander in here after having a full life,
having lived for people other than themselves.
Glitches like this occur when people like that arrive here.
And the programmer of Angel Player was one such person.
What a surprise.  You are absolutely correct.
That same programmer found that glitch in this world and made a patch for it.
And that's what's changing people into NPCs by using the Shadows.
In other words, a reset.
Yes.
So you're telling me some NPCs were once like us?
Yes, there is another.  Just one.
I pity the person.
It's the programmer himself.
He continued to wait for the other one who had left this world after learning what love is.
What?  There'd be no way for him to meet the other one again.
The chance is astronomically small, but it isn't zero.
But the time spent waiting was too great, and he couldn't maintain his sanity.
That's why he made a program to turn himself into an NPC.
Couldn't that possibly have been the original intention for the Shadows?
The programmer also applied those to the world itself, so the same thing wouldn't happen again.
That is possible.
So will the day ever come when they're rewarded for their actions?
Who knows?
I don't have a clue what's right.
I have no idea what is right, either.
But since you have made it this far,
you may be able to discover the answer.
What do you mean by that, exactly?
You can change the world based on your will.
What's the point in that?
You can choose a path that person did not.
You're saying... I can become God?
That's a different way of saying it.
I can make this place into an eternal Eden?
That person refused that conclusion, but I would not.
More accurately, I do not have the capacity for denial.
God?  I can become the god of this world?
Is something the matter?
I've made this world mine...
I did it!
This is what I've been fighting for.
I could even beat Tenshi.
With all of these systems,
I'm invincible.
As if I'd do that.
I can't do that to Kanade-chan anymore.
Because I...  I came this far because I...
Strange.
I sense love from you.
I've never felt one this strong.
It's growing at an incredible rate.
What is this about?
I came this far because I want to protect everyone.
Ah, so you were the source.
In that case, what do you intend to do?
Shut down every machine here.
Right now.
Are you sure?
Have you considered the consequences?
There is plenty of time remaining.
All eternity, in fact.
You know what?  I'll tell you something valuable.
Humans won't... even wait... for ten minutes!
It's finally... over...
I'm sure everyone's been saved.
They should have been able to leave this place safely.
Still, how careless of me.
I cared for everyone here as though they were my siblings.
I wanted to be like a big sister that cared for you all, so that you could be proud of me.
What is this feeling?
What's become of me?
The force that was driving me forward is dissipating.
If it dissipates, I won't be able to stay here.
The world took away your lives just like that, yet every moment I spent with the people here was a treasure.
I'm starting to want to follow them...
Thanks.  That's enough now.
You don't have to suffer alone, Sis.
Take a rest from your long fight, Sis.
I'm so glad I was able to spend time with you all.
Thank you so much.
Graduation class speaker, Otonashi Yuzuru!