Yesterday,
after I got back from Mr. Braun's,
nothing happened.
Moeka and her group
always appeared on Friday the 13th.
Did the world line change when I sent the message
Do not give in to your assistant's threats.
Follow Suzuha!
telling myself not to follow Suzuha?
If so, then...
has Mayuri been saved?
Will nothing happen now?
Huh?
My watch isn't working...
That's strange.
I just wound it.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mono kodou no kazu sae
is a trivial matter with little glamor for you
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Even trapped in the past and lamenting the future
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
The dreams that stretch into "infinity" and the future we imagine
"mugen" ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
are vain privileges we allowed ourselves
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no kenri
"Finity", that's what the two hands of the clock show
"yuugen" sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
towards a cruel agreement and choice
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
and protect your smile
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
And once again, a solitary observer
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
is sucked into a time loop without sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
What's wrong?
What did you want to talk about?
Help me.
Mayuri will die in two hours?
You've time leaped and seen it over and over.
That must've been painful.
Given what Amane said,
we need to go from the alpha Attractor Field, where we are now,
to the beta world line in order to save Mayuri.
To do that,
we need the IBN 5100 to delete SERN's data on you guys.
But the IBN 5100 that used to be at Yanabayashi Shrine
disappeared when the world line moved.
The world lines moved when you sent the following D-mails:
Hououin Kyouma
No Subject
The Lotto 6,
Hououin Kyouma
No Subject
Buy Lotto 6
Hououin Kyouma
No Subject
You'll win!
Kiryuu's,
Urushibara's,
Feyris's,
and the one about tailing Amane.
Do not give in to your assistant's threats.
Follow Suzuha!
When you undid the one about following Amane,
the attack was delayed by one day.
That means,
if you go back and undo the other D-mails,
you could return to the world line that had the IBN 5100, right?
It's just a theory.
There's no definitive proof.
Made in
Complex
Even so...
if there's any chance at all...
I realize that I was the one who suggested it,
but canceling out all those D-mails...
Yeah, it'll be pretty tough,
but I have no choice.
Take care.
Y-Your brain's a valuable specimen, okay?
You're able to keep your memories across world line shifts,
and you've survived time leaping.
We should map—
Thank you, Kurisu.
I won't remember that you called me Kurisu, right?
What?
Nothing.
Going in order, the next one you should undo is...
Feyris's D-mail.
Hello?
Daru,
do you know where Feyris is?
Of course!
Where? Where is she?
The UPX Arena.
The final round of the Rai-Net ABGC just ended.
ABGC?
Short for the Rai-Net Access Battlers Grand Championship, duh.
It's a tournament among Rai-Netters from across Japan.
It just ended with her victory.
I'm so excited!
After Feyris sent her D-mail,
Akiba returned to only selling electronics.
I have no idea what was in her message.
Who did she send it to?
What did she send?
Kyouma!
Feyris?
What's wrong?
The catgirl's with some guy in a lab coat.
Don't let her escape.
Not that she could...
No one can escape my Force of Darkness.
Who's chasing you?
The Viral Attackers.
The Viral Attackers?
They're the worst kind of Rai-Netter.
They'll do anything to win.
They were mad about losing to Feyris,
so they set an ambush.
An ambush?
This way!
Where'd she go?
She's gotta be nearby.
Yeah.
By the way, didn't you just call me?
That's right...
I wanted you to tell me about your D-mail.
D-mail?
The message you sent to the past.
A message I sent to the past?
What are you talking about?
In this world line,
Feyris doesn't remember sending a D-mail.
Well, you see...
There they are!
Hypothetically speaking... Hypothetically,
if I said we built a time machine, would you believe me?
I'd believe anything you say!
Really?
Feyris just built a dimensional transport machine.
Let's imagine that Akiba was a city engrossed in the culture of cute.
Say you used the time machine to change it to the electronics market it is now.
How would you do it?
What kind of game is this?
Whatever! Please just answer!
I don't really know...
but I bet a city immersed in the culture of cute would be fun!
Actually, I talked to Dad about it once.
About opening a maid café in Akiba, that is,
but he said I couldn't.
You mean May Queen?
How did you know that name?
I never even told my dad.
It used to exist!
Here in Akiba!
Akiba had cutesy shit everywhere!
Kyouma?
You loved that city more than anyone else!
But once you sent that message,
the whole city changed!
What did you send?
Please tell me!
There they are! Over here!
What's wrong?
Here.
This is where May Queen used to be,
the café you wanted to run.
You worked here.
Mayuri too.
Daru came all the time.
We met here.
Welcome back, Master!
I'll get it right away!
We now begin the Feyris Cup day division.
Code Name: G-BACK
Here's my "the World's In Danger"!
A lot of customers came in today. It was fun!
Feyris?
I-I'm fine.
What happens if you can't undo the D-mail?
Mayuri's life is...
...in danger.
You're lying.
You're lying!
What do you mean, her life is in danger?
You remember the message?
Please tell me!
I have to undo it!
I can't.
Why not?
Mayuri... You don't care if Mayuri dies?
Of course I do!
But...
Feyris!
I brought my dad back to life
after his death ten years ago.
I changed the past...
to prevent his death.
Kyouma!
Kyouma...
Your pretty face is ruined, mister.
Now, Princess, you're coming with me.
Let me go!
Kyouma!
We caught the catgirl.
My super dangerous aura's
You'll be seeing him soon.
been telling me it wants her turned black.
Until then, we'll—
Stop it.
Only one can stand at a scene's forefront,
the phoenix with black wings.
Let her go!
Kyouma!
You there, mister.
I'll make the catgirl mine with an elegant, crazy dance.
Still want to play?
Stop it! Please!
Stop!
Oh, no! Run!
Daddy!
And that'll be the last thing she ever sees...
Wait!
What were you kids doing?
It's time!
C203 is here!
Huh? Who're you?
The police? I'm under arrest?
I'm glad you're safe...
I'm really glad.
Daddy...
Thank you.
I heard you won.
I came to celebrate,
but I didn't see you at the UPX arena.
You didn't answer your phone, so I went looking for you.
Okabe, I don't know how to thank you.
Don't mention it.
If only I'd gone to see the tournament,
this wouldn't have happened.
Daddy...
You have work. It's okay.
Rumiho...
An IBN 5100?
Yes, I know you don't have it anymore,
but where is it now?
Could you get it back?
It's complicated.
I feel bad for Hashida.
Hashida?
Hashida Suzu?
You know her?
She was the one who gave me the IBN 5100.
I'll be fine.
I'll find the IBN 5100, and I'll get it to you.
Suzuha...
She got it for us...
Daddy, you can tell him.
But...
He saved my life, and he really wants to know.
A long time ago, Rumiho was kidnapped.
The company wasn't as big as it is now,
so I couldn't pay the ransom.
But then, someone came and told me
that she'd purchase the IBN 5100 for a huge amount.
So that's how you lost it?
Because of that, I was able to pay the ransom.
Ever since,
I've always kept my promises to my daughter,
no matter how small,
no matter what happens.
Daddy...
I brought my dad back to life
after his death ten years ago.
I changed the past to prevent his death.
If I send the D-mail, he'll...
Okarin, are you sending a D-mail?
If you do that, all of this will disappear!
But if I don't, Mayuri, you'll—
Can I come in?
Sure.
Feyris?
Um... Thanks for earlier.
I was really scared.
I've never felt that much darkness
from so many people.
Were they all wearing black?
I'm being serious.
I'm sorry.
Feyris...
What's wrong?
Call me Rumiho.
If it weren't for you, Kyouma— I mean, Okabe,
I don't know what would've happened.
Don't correct yourself.
Just call me what you always do.
Anyway, Kyouma, thank you so much.
You're... my prince.
Your prince?
I'm no prince.
I'm a mad...
Mayushii...
Is it true that Mayushii's life is in danger?
Yes.
Ten years ago, on my eighth birthday,
my dad promised to take me somewhere,
but work came up, so he had to cancel.
I knew it wasn't his fault, but I was so lonely.
I thought he didn't love me.
I told him I hated him, that I wanted him to die!
And then...
that was the last time I ever spoke to him.
I sent a D-mail to change that past.
We have your daughter. Ransom is 100 million yen.
Take the Shinkansen.
So he wasn't in the crash,
and you never brought the culture of cute to Akiba,
and it remained an electronics market.
I was happy...
these ten years.
Fey— Rumiho...
I'll send that D-mail.
My dad died in an accident ten years ago.
That's what really happened.
These ten years have been a dream.
After all this time with him,
I know how much he loved me,
and Mayushii's my friend!
I can't be selfish.
Are you sure?
No.
I'm not!
I remember
what happened before the world line changed,
but I remember what happened after too!
It's all mixed together,
and I don't think I'll be able to tell
which is real for much longer.
There may be another way.
I know! I can ask Kurisu—
No! I don't want to cause you any more trouble.
You really are my prince.
It's time for me to wake up from this dream,
but let me have one thing.
Can I cry a little?
Yeah.
Feyris...
Yeah, she accepted.
Get ready.
Here I am!
What's wrong, Kyouma?
You look down!
The kidnapping was just a joke.
I love you, Daddy. See you soon.
By the way...
if the world reverts to how it was,
will all my memories vanish?
Your memories are from before and after
the world line changed, right?
I'm sure you'll remember.
Thank goodness.
Feyris wouldn't want to forget her time with Kyouma.
Thank you.
It's ready, Okabe!
Good-bye, Daddy.
Kyouma!
Have you seen my cell phone?
Feyris...
Mayushii says she doesn't know,
so you're the only person I can ask.
Kyouma, did you see what was on it?
If you did, forget it!
It must remain forever sealed!
Kyouma, why don't you say anything?
Like, "What was on it?"
Feyris...
Hey! Hey!
Get your hands off her!
You're doing something perverted again, right?
Okarin's so bold.
Kyouma and Feyris fought a great darkness
as lovers in a past life!
We're really close!
You fight lots of people, don't you?
Are Feyris and Okabe that alike?
I'm sorry.
The IBN 5100 wasn't at Yanabayashi Shrine.
Ten years ago, Feyris gave it to the shrine.
They said it was there until last year.
Where...
...did it go?
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten