When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line or a girl...
A super combat battle story!
My name is Hayate. Earth is being targeted.
Your life is also being targeted.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
You Say You Can See Time, But That Is
Probably Your Life Flashing Before Your Eyes
Ah, it's you, Isumi!
You got here quicker than I expected.
I was worried that you might
have gotten lost again.
I am sorry for worrying you.
But everything is fine,
because I did get lost.
Oh... you did...
Someone I believe to be your new
butler brought me here.
What? You met Hayate?
He was wearing a brand new cashmere coat.
Oh, that definitely sounds
like it was Hayate.
But he may end up dying if we don't hurry.
What?!
Is Hayate in some kind of trouble again?!
Well, it's certainly conceivable.
That's not good! Hayate's in a fix!
We're going to save him, Maria!
Uh, um...
Perhaps it was a bad idea to make him
wear something he wasn't used to...
It is a cold...
That cashmere coat, huh?
It is certainly the first crisis he has faced
since he became a butler.
Never mind that, Maria! We must hurry!
Yes!
Cash Advance!!
If I don't do something about this coat,
I'll never be able to go back
to the estate again.
Maybe I should just borrow money
from somewhere and get a new coat...
No, that won't solve anything.
Hey, Ayasaki!
Long time no see!
Oh! You people are...
The "very generous people",
who previously kindly offered
to send me to a tropical paradise!
Don't talk about embarrassing things
in an expository manner on the streets.
What the heck, you're still alive?
Uh... yes.
But well, if it weren't
for our business dealings,
I think I could've liked a guy like ya.
What?
Even our chance meetin'
must've been fated somehow.
If ya want, I'll treat ya to a meal...
There he is!
Hey, Ayasaki, who're these guys?
No need to even ask. They've gotta be Mafia.
I see. Colleagues of ours, eh?
I thought you were suspicious
from the start, but so you really are...
What?! No...
Hey, four-eyes, you got
a problem with our boy here?
What?! When did I become one of you?!
I see, you seem to be determined
to see some bloodshed.
I don't know who you guys are,
but you've got guts, I'll give you that.
Wait, now that I think about it,
I've become involved in a pretty
nasty situation, haven't I?
At this rate, never mind
being reprimanded by Maria,
I'll get chewed out
by the authorities and stuff.
Above all, this may cause problems
for the Miss and the others.
I have to escape somehow!
Hey, where do you think
you're going, Ayasaki?
You're not planning on deserting
your comrades, are you?
As I said earlier, when
did I become one of you?
What?! Trying to save his own hide
by deserting his comrades?!
And you call yourself human?!
What a coldhearted bastard!
What?! I'm getting condemned
by the other side, too?!
Since it's come to this...
...I guess we've got no choice
but to whack him.
Oh, I get it.
I'm going to die today.
Man, today's just been an awful day.
If this was how it was going to be,
I wish I'd offered a sincere apology
to Maria back at the estate.
Yeah, if I make it back alive,
I'll offer a sincere apology
for sure this time.
Get him!
Here I come!
What are you dragging your
feet for?! We must hurry!
Knowing Hayate, if we drag our feet,
he may be skewered by countless
swords before we know it!
Surely, nothing so drastic...
Though, the new coat may be in tatters.
You can bet on it!
Don't underestimate Hayate!
No, the coat is already in tatters.
What?
I see. That's Hayate for you.
The coat had gotten dirty because of me,
but he was very troubled by it.
It shows just how serious he is
about his job as Nagi's butler...
When you put it that way, we can't be
too hard on him for ruining the coat.
I wasn't going to be hard on him
for it to begin with.
Oh, he seems to have
come home at the perfect time.
What a hopeless guy.
Oh, thank goodness.
I managed to get back alive somehow.
Maria, you are not to scold Hayate, either.
We must give him a warm welcome.
Well, if you say so, Nagi.
Speaking of which,
did Hayate say anything about me?
What?
You know, anything
about me being cute or charming...
Um... um...
Oh, as I recall, he said you were
a little, spoiled, headstrong,
and an unmanageable bundle of energy...
Oh... I'm back.
Miss...
What?!
Wh-Why?! Why did you shut the door?! Miss?!
Shut up! Stupid jerk!
Honestly! How rude!
But also kind and adorable.
I think it would work better
if you mentioned that earlier.
And thus,
all too soon, the butler-in-debt's
miserable life came to an end.
P-Please, no jokes...
Sign: Fox Udon Dontaro
I'm hot!
I am sorry, it seems I am making
such trouble for everyone...
38.9 degrees. He's unmistakably
come down with a cold.
Honestly!
The weather may have suddenly
gotten cooler, but to catch a cold!
How weak can you be?!
Well, I don't know anything
about him being weak, but...
When someone locked him out
to spend hours in soaking wet
clothes in this cold weather,
it's no wonder that he caught a cold.
Stare...
Wh-What?!
You make it sound as though I'm the bad guy!
Are you in pain, Hayate?
Yes, a lot...
Stare...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Don't look at me with eyes like Kenshiro's.
Like when he mastered the Musou Tensei!
It was an unavoidable accident
that you caught a cold.
You just relax and get some rest.
Oh, all right...
Um, this is a milkshake.
It will warm you up.
Oh, thank you very much.
It is nothing.
While the fact that Nagi
shut you out was the final blow,
the original cause lies with me, so...
This was Isumi trying to cover
for Nagi in her own way.
It is true that the Miss
delivered the final blow, but...
I had no idea that you went
to the same school as the Miss.
And I am the one who leapt
to the horribly wrong conclusion...
Oh, no, please do not let that bother you.
Well... I'll enjoy this now.
Yes. Though, I do not know
if it will be to your taste...
This is really delicious.
I am so glad it is to your taste.
You made this yourself, right?
I see that you must be a good cook.
I do not know if I am good or not,
but I am a girl, after all.
It's wrong to think that you should cook,
just because you're a girl, Isumi!
With such antiquated notions,
you won't survive
in the information age to come!
Nagi, you only use big words when
you are trying to cover up something.
You know her so very well.
Anyway, men and women are equal
in the 21st century! No boundaries!
Having said that, you still haven't
even had lunch, right, Hayate?
What? N-No...
All right,
then I shall put special effort into
making some dish called "rice porridge".
What?!
What was with that?
You didn't sound very happy.
Or what? Are you saying you
don't want to eat my cooking?!
No, my heart is bursting with gratitude.
All right, then prepare
yourself and wait for me!
I have read through every volume of
"Mister Ajikko" and "Gourmand-kun".
There is no dish that I cannot make!
Let's go, Tama!
M-Meow...
What's with your weak response, too?!
Meow...
Then I shall go prepare
some stomach medicine.
Please hang in there, my dear Hayate.
R-Right...
And thus, Miss Nagi's
ministrations began. However...
No, considering how
confident the Miss seems,
surely her dish won't be that terrible...
Hayate could find no way to convince
himself that he would recover soon.
What's this, Saku?
I didn't know you were still here.
I got sucked into the Downtown DVD
box set, but then I got hungry...
In that case, I am about to begin cooking,
so I'll let you have a taste.
Whoops! I've still got DVDs
that I gotta watch.
Where are you going?
But since I'm going to
the trouble of making this,
I want to try seasoning it in a
unique and distinctive way...
This is the first mistake
that amateur cooks fall for.
Hmm, I want some punchy flavor...
Oh, vinegar's supposed to be good for you...
This is bad!
If yer forced to eat Nagi's cookin',
it won't be enough, no matter
how many lives you've got.
Hayate might end up dead...
Hey, Sakuya, what do you think?
Huh?
But I'm so sorry about this, Isumi.
Pardon?
Well, you know, because Hayate has
caused you all kinds of trouble...
Oh, no, it was no trouble.
But I can see why my Nagi
put her trust in him...
He was quite kind to me.
Could this possibly mean...
...that once again, Hayate
is spreading a kind of ailment
that's even more troublesome than a cold?
Welcome, Master! (Irasshaimase goshujin-sama)
Now, now, now. (Maa, maa, maa)
Here, it's ready, Hayate.
I'm quite confident of how it turned out,
so eat it with that in mind!
Oh? This looks better than I expected.
Is it just possible...?
Right, then I shall enjoy it right away.
Th-This is...
Never mind the poor use of salt
or that it subtly tastes like sushi rice
or that it's not fully cooked.
Before all that...
I can smell the faint aroma of
the detergent used in the kitchen.
What is it, Hayate?
This can no longer even be called food...
Um, could it be that it didn't taste good?
They say that there are times
when a man's pride requires
that he see something through.
It is very... delicious.
Kids, you must never try this at home.
Why? Because detergent
is neither food nor drink.
I-I see! I'm glad to hear that!
I hadn't tasted it, so I was worried,
but I guess it turned out good!
Yes, it's absolutely fantastic, Miss!
The bit of oil I used for subtle
flavor must have worked.
Is that right?
There's plenty more,
so go ahead and eat it all.
Oh, it's so good! Oh! My Konbu!
You're such a glutton, Hayate!
To live up to the mistress's expectations!
That is what a butler does!
OIL comes off easily!
Marmar Lemon
Could it be that she used this,
mistaking it for oil?
To live up to the mistress's expectations!
That is what a pet does!
Meow... Meow... Meow...
Th-Thank you for the food...
Ah, you really cleaned your plate!
You must have been awfully hungry.
Well, I'll go clean this up,
so get some good sleep.
Y-Yessir...
Unfortunate things
are always happening to me, but...
Today was kind of amazingly
worse than usual...
If you push yourself too hard,
you really will end up dead.
Maria...
Honestly! I'm amazed
that you managed to eat all of that.
What?
Because, I mean, she put in detergent
instead of oil by mistake, right?
Yes, I guess...
But the Miss worked hard to make
that dish for me, after all.
And besides, it made me happy
that I had someone taking
care me while I was sick.
Did your mother not take care
of you when you got sick?
Whether her child got a fever
or was severely injured,
my mother was the sort
who blithely ignored it
and just invested in her dreams
where the reels keep spinning.
Sign: Lunch Money
Sign: Mother
Oh... that's...
Oh, this boy! Casually mentioning
such a depressing story...
Well, at any rate, please
get some rest for today, okay?
I will, I'm so sleepy already.
Then, good night.
Hayate...
Thank you.
Excuse me, what are you doing, Miss?
That is... With your face so close to me,
it's hard for me to sleep...
Shut up! Hayate, you stupid jerk!
Oh, Miss, that's...
Shut up! You idiot!
They say that good people die young, but...
I feel like I sort of understand why now.
And thus, the poverty-stricken
butler's hellish day came to an end.
However...
A good night's sleep
and I'm completely over my cold.
I wasn't able to do anything yesterday,
so I better work hard today.
Good morning.
Huh?
Uh... right... Good morning.
The weather is so fine today,
it's perfect for laundry, don't you think?
Huh?
Uh, yes, I agree.
My, my, you are a Sanzenin butler,
and yet your strong tie is crooked.
You should pay close attention
to your personal appearance,
so as not to be an embarrassment
to your mistress.
Well, then, good day...
Huh?!
Uh, um...
Who the?
There is someone strange in the residence?
Yes, she's wearing a maid outfit
that's different from yours
and she wears glasses.
I see. Any other
distinguishing characteristics?
Let me think.
If I had to say, she looks
incredibly capable,
but she's unmistakably a natural born klutz!
Oh, I know!
She is not a problem, so please go
about your morning cleaning duties.
I see...
Oh, also, I believe we should
have one other visitor,
so when you see that person,
please show them to the drawing room.
Uh, yes, I understand.
Someone from the Tachibana family is here?
Yes, it appears Saki is here,
so security must have let them in.
Klaus, it's me.
We have some suspicious
individuals inside the residence.
Drive them out immediately!
That's right! I don't care how you do it!
I'll even permit
the non-lethal use of firearms!
Uh, um...
Just get rid of them right away! That's all!
There's no need to actually kick them out...
But... I don't want Hayate to know!
She said we should have another visitor...
Aw, man, I wish the Earth
would just get destroyed.
Wh-What is with this boy,
muttering such disturbing things...
E-Excuse me...
Huh? Who the hell are you?
Don't talk so familiarly to me
with your poor-looking face, moron!
Um... Um...
Oh, I see!
Maybe this most impudent child
is the guest Maria was talking about.
I swear! I'm in the crappiest mood!
I'm just bored, so would you go jump
into that pond for me?
Oh, certainly. Wait... What?!
Left your guard down!
If you're a butler, you should
dodge easy attacks like that.
You can't protect your mistress
if you're that feeble.
Oh! W-Wait a moment, please!
What? You got some problem with me?
No, I was told to show our visitor
to the drawing room, so...
Wow, so you're not gonna get mad?
Even after I pushed you around like that...
I'm used to it, so...
Young Sir, so this is where you were!
Who cares where the heck I go?
"Young Sir"?
By the way, Young Sir,
I have a bit of a question.
Huh? If it's about this guy,
I don't know anything.
No, that is not it.
What in the world is
that machine behind you...?
Security 8801
What the?! It's floating!
It has a Minovsky drive?!
Beep! Target sighted!
Immediately moving to eliminate!
Eliminate!
What?!
Eliminate! Eliminate!
What the hell is that thing?!
I do not know! That is why I asked you!
Like I'd know anything about
some stupid Sanzenin mecha!
Beep!
Target sighted!
Gack! More from the front!
Ugh... I don't know what's going on,
but as a Sanzenin family butler,
I have to safely escort our visitors
to the drawing room!
Please hang on tight!
You...!
Please rest easy.
As a Sanzenin butler, the one thing
I will ensure is safety for our guests...
Never mind that! Don't hold me
against your sopping wet clothes!
What?!
Th-That is right!
T-To handle a girl's body so familiarly...
I-It's depraved!
I-I see, pardon me...
Y-You can't do this!
If you struggle like that in the air...
Well, I certainly did ask you
to show them to the drawing room, but...
You didn't have to bring them
in through the ceiling...
M-My apologies...
I told you, that's cold!
Please let me go already!
What will I do if I become
ruined for marriage?!
Right...
So, who in the world are these people?
What?
This boy is Wataru Tachibana
and he is Nagi's... betrothed.
Huh?
Wataru, a mysterious boy, who has come
to see Nagi, and his maid, Saki.
And Isumi.
Is Wataru really betrothed to Nagi?
With signs of even more troubling
times in the next episode,
he will battle the vast
subterranean labyrinth of Tokyo,
the underground!
Oh, hmm... Hold on a sec,
there was one more person here.
That's so stupid!
Why the heck?!
To be continued next time!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Sign: Butler Report
Hello, I'm Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
We've just started this segment today,
but what exactly is this segment for?
In this segment, we'll follow your
progress as you become a fine butler
and take a stand against a gigantic evil!
A gigantic evil?
By the way, what's this song
playing in the background?
Ah, yes, this is my image song,
composed by the famous maestro.
It perfectly conveys my
desire to protect you!
Ah, is that right?
I'll be counting on you, Hayate.
Yes, Miss.
Bye-bye!
Preview
You're Nagi's new butler, right?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Uh, yes, my name is Hayate Ayasaki...
Since we're here anyway,
how about a little duel before breakfast?
Um, is it the norm for the rich and
famous to have duels in the morning?
I don't really get it, but he probably
wants to show off how cool he is.
Well, just beat the crap out of him for now.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"A Man's Fight".
Ready to meet your fate, you stupid butler?!
A Man's Fight
Take this!
Lots more fan service coming next time!