Flashback to lunch
Cut number 1A
We're going on a date.
What?
Well...  Umm...
What's with this situation?
I've seen similar intimate conversations before in comics and stuff,
but somehow I'm not happy at all.  If anything, I'm scared!
What's wrong, Araragi-kun?
Say "ah~".
Black
Unnumbered cut
There.
Red
Unnumbered cut
Seeing you smile makes me really happy.
Araragi-kun, there's a clump of rice on your cheek.
You put it there!
I'll remove it for you.
There you go.
... she threw it out
Cut number 37
Anyway, we're going on a date.
No, that's wrong.  That's not how it's said.
Shall...  Shall we go on a date?
How...  How about we go on a date...?
What?  Don't you want to, Araragi-kun?
No, it's not that I don't want to.
I see.  Then go on a date with me, Araragi-kun.
So in the end, you're that calm.
Do you have any complaints...  No, any questions?
No.
I see.  Then I'll make up an excuse and go home early after school today.
As soon as you're done with the preparations for the cultural festival, come over to my house.
Fuck yes!
This makes today, June 13th, my first date with my lover.
Cut number 59
It was a day to remember, but...
Cut number 61
It's better to back off now while there's still time
Before we misunderstand each other even more
Before I knew it,
The staple you used to bind your words pierced my heart
It's your fault
Don't come to me the way I am now
Don't look at me wherever I go
Don't let go of me with that smile
No matter who you are
I prayed for an endless eternity
In the sky that stretches on forever
Like the sea with its harsh love,
You dove into my heart to take it
I want to deliver these feelings to you
That can't be weighed
GHO      ST   ORY
T S U B A S A   C A T
bakemono
gatari
At least I figured this out.
Senjougahara Hitagi...
She's pretty smart,
usually near the top of the class,
but incompetent at love.  Completely incompetent.
Even during our conversation when we started dating
on Mother's Day. This girl is so reckless. She's like
an RPG hero who goes straight into a cave without a torch.
She's showing all her cards and throwing herself on the mercy of her opponent.
Does she think she needs to use that methodology,
like an aggressive diplomatic doctrine, in this kind of fond,
subtly budding relationship?
It's horrible.
99 men out of 100 would dump her if she kept pushing it like that.
It's scary.
I can tell even though I'm not experienced in love either.
Well.
I guess she's doing it because she's decided I'm that one out of the hundred.
I have to tip my hat.
Oh no.
I'm moeing so damn hard.
I can't even joke about it.
Really, I just wanted to leave it all up to force and embrace Senjougahara,
but even I know I'd lose her then.
Even from the start, I never had many cards to play...
Is I guess
how I'd describe my relationship with Senjougahara.
Not that I didn't need them.
Sleep
Lying there together looking up at the stars.  We make good lovers like that.
Yellow
Unnumbered cut
Episode 11
Tsubasa Cat Part 1
Font used in video: HGP Mincho B
I spent too much time in front of the school talking to Sengoku and Hanekawa.
Cut number 65
Red
Unnumbered cut
I'm a little late.
2 0 1
Still sooner than I expected.
Oh well.
All right, let's go.  Follow me.
Hey...
What's wrong, Araragi-kun?  You're being pretty quiet.
Come on, don't you understand the current situation?
I don't understand.  What do you mean by "current" and "situation"?
Now
Cut number 76
Situation
Cut number 77
You don't even understand that much!?
Man, her dad's coming along on our first date.
This date is like torture.  What kind of hellish memory is it going to be!?
It makes sense that you would be nervous on your first date,
but don't be, Araragi-kun.  The night is long.
Yeah...
I'm not nervous because it's my first date!
Hitagi line/voice
Cut number 84
Hey, Araragi-kun.
Do you love me?
Tell me if you love me.
What, aren't you going to answer?
Could it be that you don't really love me, Araragi-kun?
I...  I love you.
I see.  I love you too, Araragi-kun.
Thanks a lot.
Don't worry about it.
You're being really quiet, Araragi-kun.
You're not talking at all.  Usually you chat a lot more.
Is something wrong today?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, I see.  There's something wrong with your head.
You're just taking advantage of my confusion to say whatever you want!
Araragi-kun, you're always so naughty with your retorts.
Very well.  Then I'll kindly start the conversation.
You can just answer me.
What do you love about me?
It's pretty obvious what I don't love!
Dammit!
I was really looking forward to this!  It felt like my dreams had come true!
Calling it a dream is a hyperbole.
Didn't you know, Araragi-kun?
If you write "fickle" next to "person"... Hmm I wonder what that makes?
Person
Cut number 111
Fickle
Cut number 112
She probably means me.
Araragi
Cut number 114
The birth of a new kanji
Cut number 115
Hey, Senjougahara.
Just what are you up to?
Senjougahara?  Are you talking to me?
Or are you talking to my father?
Daddy, Araragi-kun is talking to you.
Hitagi-san!  I'm talking to you, Hitagi-san!
Where he calls her by first name
Cut number 119
What, Araragi-kun?
But you won't call me by my name.  Oh well, I don't really mind.
Black
Unnumbered cut
So, Hitagi-san, I'll ask again.
Can you tell me what you're up to?
What are you scheming?
I'm not scheming up anything.
By the way, Araragi-kun.  There's a famous
mystery novelist named Kuroiwa Ruikou,
Kuroiwa Ruikou
Cut number 123
but you can rearrange his name to mean "wicked, bad child".
Wicked
Cut number 124
Bad
Cut number 125
Child
Cut number 126
Do you think this was intentional?
That doesn't matter!  You're the wicked, bad kid!
Wicked child
Cut number 128
Bad child
Cut number 129
You're saying horrible things about me in front of my father.
Daddy, it seems that your daughter is a wicked, bad girl.
Oh my, you've gotten quiet again.
Perhaps I teased you a bit too much.  Araragi-kun, you
respond so easily that I dig at you even when I shouldn't.
That line cuts the deepest.
So, what do you like about me?
You're nice, cute, and like a prince who
would rescue me whenever I'm in trouble.
Cut number 140
Well sorry!
By the way, Tras-  No, I mean Araragi-kun.
Did you just call your boyfriend "trash"?
What are you talking about?  Stop putting words in my mouth.
By the way, Araragi-kun.  How did you do on the exams?
I went through so much trouble, day and night, to study with you at my place.
Why do you have to put it like that?
So, how did you do?
Black
Unnumbered cut
I scored better than I expected.
I've always been pretty good at math, but this time I did better than usual.
It was because of you.  Thanks, Senjougahara.
Daddy, I think Araragi-kun is thanking you.  Are you listening?
Thank you, Hitagi-san!
I was hoping that you'd do it right after the exams.
Well, expecting that from your current self would be too cruel.
I'm a bit surprised even though I was the one who taught you.
Surprised?
Yes, I see that you don't find it funny.
I didn't get your help in order to be laughed at!
I was sure that you were going to tell me: "I studied too hard and ended up doing worse than usual."
So I'm kind of disappointed.
Expecting that to happen is pretty cruel!
Araragi line (Naughty)!!
Oh, I see.
But really, your results are a big deal.  I'm proud of you.
If you keep it up, Araragi-kun,
perhaps you can aim even higher.
Higher?
If you'd like, Araragi-san, I can keep helping you with your studies.
Well...
I honestly wouldn't mind.
I see.
Then let's study at my place every day.
E-Every day!?
Do smart people really study that much?
No, it's obviously only necessary for you.
Smart people are smart before they even study.
But it seems that Hanekawa studies every day.
Unfortunately, the studying that Hanekawa-san
does is on a completely different level from ours.
Hanekawa-san's the real thing.  She's in a completely different world.
But doesn't Hanekawa-san usually ace all her tests?
If Hanekawa-san doesn't ace it, there's
probably something wrong with the test.
But I wonder.
Just how great is the pressure?  I honestly can't say I envy her.
Pressure, huh?
Or you could call it stress.
Cut number 181
Stress, eh?
You don't even begin to compare to her.  You have to use all your energy just to crawl up out of the mud.
So let's study every day at my place.
Sure, thanks.
We can do it at Kanbaru's place too sometimes.
Why are you talking about Kanbaru now?
I have to hang out with her sometime.
I promised.
Didn't you say you wanted to hang out with her too?
Well, she is a pretty fun person.
Oh right, about Kanbaru.
What about Kanbaru?
Why is she so kinky?
Kinky?  Kanbaru?
Am I wrong?
Even Oshino said that Kanbaru was more of a kinky character than an athlete.
I see.  Isn't that just what males see?
She's just honest with herself.
I see.
I can't ignore your mistaken "kinky" impression of my cute junior.
If you can't ignore it, what are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
I'm going to sway the basis for your judgment.
If I do that, you'll think of Kanbaru as a pure and innocent girl.
Obscene line
Cut number 201
Do *** to ***
Cut number 208
Oh...  Oh crap!
Nibble.
Cut number 217
How about that, Araragi-kun?
Just do whatever you want, Hitagi-san.
Commercials follow
Cut number 126
Parking
Silence
Cut number 222
Wait here a second, Araragi-kun.
I'm going ahead by myself to get everything ready.
To get everything ready?
You should have a chat with my father.
Araragi-kun, right?
Yes.  I'm Araragi Koyomi.
I see.  Take good care of my daughter.
Just kidding.
You've probably heard that I'm the very picture of a workaholic.
I have barely any time to spend with Hitagi.
I don't know if you'd believe me, but it's been a long time since I've seen Hitagi this happy.
Cut number 241
You heard what happened to her mother, right?
Yes.
Then you heard about her illness too.
Well, that's not all.
Of course, I'm at fault for being so caught up in my work too.
Hitagi completely closed off her heart.
Red
Unnumbered cut
Black
But lately, she's been asking me things that she hasn't asked me in ages.
She said she wanted to help with my work.
And this time.  Both of her requests involved you.
Causing that change in her is pretty impressive, Araragi-kun.
I'm thankful that you're that impressed.  But it was by accident.
Really?  I heard that you played a big role in curing Hitagi.
I don't think it matters that it was me.
And really, Hitagi was saved by herself.
I was just present at the time.
Father/line
Cut number 260B
That's good enough.
The most important thing is just
being there when you're needed.
I didn't do my job as a father.
When she needed me, I wasn't there for her.
But even if I'm like that, I'm proud of my daughter.
I believe in my daughter's judgment.
If you're the man she chose, you must be the right one.
Take good care of my daughter, Araragi-kun.
Father...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Araragi-kun.
Father, what comes next is between two young lovers.
Thanks for bringing us here.
We'll be back in around two hours, so go back to work until then.
Cut number 274
Okay.
All right, Araragi-kun.
Thanks, Daddy.
Where are we, Senjougahara?
Cut number 286
Didn't I already answer that question, Araragi-kun?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Hey, Senjougahara.  How much
longer do I have to stay like this?
You're not allowed to look up yet, Araragi-kun.
Black
Unnumbered cut
HITAGI/line
Cut number 297
Close your eyes and lie down.
Black
Unnumbered cut
You can open your eyes now.
How is it, Araragi-kun?
Amazing.  I honestly don't have any words for it.
Your vocabulary isn't big enough.
Deneb, Altair, Vega.
Those stars make the famous Summer Triangle.
And Ophiuchus is straight to the side.
So Serpens is over there.
That bright star there is Spica.
Meaning Virgo is over there.
Cancer is over there...  It's a little hard to make out.
Senjougahara HITAGI
Cut number 300
HITAGI
Hitagi
Cut number 300
Black
Unnumbered cut
That's all.
Huh?  What do you mean?
That's all I have.
Cut number 301
Being able to help you study.
A cute junior and a brusque father.
And this starry sky.
That's all I have.
That's all I can give you, Araragi-kun.
That's everything.
Everything...
Well, to be exact, I can also offer spiteful and abusive words.
I don't want those.
And there's my body.
Do you not want that either?
Uh, no...  That...
But you know, right?  A long time ago, I was nearly raped by a chauvinist pig.
Yeah.
Honestly, I'm afraid to do with you what he did to me.
I'm really afraid that I'll hate you for it, Araragi-kun.
Right now, I'm afraid of losing you.
Although my life hasn't been very fortunate until now,
I'm glad if I caught your eye because of that misfortune.
Because of that, I was able to fall for you.
So we'll definitely do something, but I want to wait just a little bit.
So right now, the last thing I can offer you...
Is this starry sky.
When I was a little girl, my mommy and daddy took me here.
It's my treasure.
Hey, Araragi-kun.  Do you love me?
I love you.
I love you too, Araragi-kun.
Thanks.
What do you love about me?
Everything.  There's nothing about you I don't love.
I see.  I'm happy.
What do you love about me?
You're kind.
You're cute.
You're like a prince who would
rescue me whenever I'm in trouble.
I'm happy.
By the way, that chauvinist pig was only interested in my body, so he took nothing from my lips.
So, Araragi-kun.  Kiss me.
No, that's wrong.  That's not how it goes.
Shall...  Shall we kiss?
H-How...  How about we kiss?
Let's kiss, Araragi-kun.
So in the end, you're that calm.
On a day just like any other day
That's how this became a day to remember.
You suddenly got up and said,
"Let's go watch the stars tonight"
For both of us.
Deneb, Altair, and Vega
That's the Summer Triangle you pointed at
I remember that when I look up at the sky
I finally found Vega
But where are you, Altair?
You'll be alone like this
I looked up from the pitch dark world
It's like the night sky is filled with raining stars
I wonder when I started to chase after you
Please, no matter what
Don't be surprised
Listen to these feelings of mine
Unnumbered cut