Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Right?
Doesn't it stink?
Sure does!
Golden Week's almost over...
Did you already take care of your homework?
Not yet, actually...
You know how you can't help having fun on long vacations?
We're in trouble now!
Right, Sis?
Sorry.
I'm almost done.
But you've been playing with me the whole time...
Effort
and
Results
Thanks for the food.
I have a
question about this part...
How would I know
the answers if you don't?
Aren't you in college?!
Go wake up Tsukasa already.
No way.
She's not gonna wake up.
Wake up already!
Dad and Sis sure are late.
Didn't they have a
ground—breaking
ceremony this morning?
What...
...time is it?
I'm home.
It's already noon.
Welcome home.
Good morning...
It's already past noon.
I can't believe how
you can sleep so much.
Did you see the special final episode of Apron of Love last night?
Nope.
I fell asleep halfway through.
You were asleep?
It got really crazy!
A guy balanced a red wash basin on top of his head at the end!
Kagami!
You have a call from Miyuki-chan!
Okay.
Would you like to hold a study
session for checking homework answers?
Sounds great!
Let's do that!
Kagami!
You have a call from Konata-chan!
How about we do a study session for finishing off homework?
Wait one sec!
You're just going to copy my answers, aren't you?!
So let me copy your homework.
Right to the point, huh?
You can copy them...
...but if you don't do the homework yourself...
...you'll totally bomb the test after vacation.
You're right...
We'll only end up hurting ourselves...
I'm good at winging stuff the night before, so I'll be fine.
So let me copy.
At least pretend to be guilty!
I'm sorry to intrude.
Oh, welcome!
Welcome!
Oh.
Are you also here to study, Izumi-san?
No.
She's just copying.
Anyway...
You've barely touched it.
What were you doing during break?
Um...
First Day
Twenty-three pages of math...
Twenty pages
of world history...
Finally made it to
the Imperial Gate.
Thirty pages of English...
We have five days of vacation.
Assuming five
hours spent a day...
No, four hours...
That means 1.15
pages of math an hour.
Second Day
Getting a lot more
experience than I expected.
Oh no!
I haven't done any work today!
Wonder how much
more I need for a level.
Um...
I have three days left...
So let's go
with six hours a day?
Found a loincloth!
Third Day
Nobody remembers
the name of the guy
who spent ten years...
...watching over new workers.
This is starting to
get really slow.
It's Yutaka.
Well, I'm almost maxed out.
Two days left!
If I cram for the last two days...
So all that's left is...
Fourth Day
Golden Week's almost over...
Did you already take
care of your homework?
How about we do a
study session for
finishing off homework?
I wanted to do everything just as planned...
Mission failed.
Shouldn't have even bothered.
You're even worse!
So she ended up doing it herself, huh?
I guess she's still a hard-working girl deep down.
But her accuracy rate is too much for me to bear!
Pathetic...
Just pathetic!
Howdy!
Did y'all have a fun vacation?
Then again...
You had bunches of homework...
...and a test right after vacation...
...so you couldn't have been having fun the whole time.
It barely felt like a vacation.
So sad.
Too bad I just let loose and had a blast!
Teacher.
I also let loose and had a blast!
Hey.
Aren't these things designed so you can never get anything?
Depends on what you're going for.
Some things are especially hard to grab.
Right?
I could never bring myself to touch one of these machines.
Incredible!
Nah.
I already knew this one was gettable.
So maybe...
...if I went after that one...
I might actually get it.
Is that what you're thinking?
Nope! No way!
B-But...
...I guess I'll give it a try.
So you wanna.
Go for it, Sis!
Thought I had it...
Too bad...
Huh?
No way!
Why?!
A great person once said...
...that operating a UFO catcher is like opening a savings account.
Smart guy...
Not again!
Screwed up!
Here are your scores!
I was hopeless...
You achieved Taiko Rank 1!
You've got a great sense of rhythm, Kona-chan.
You achieved Taiko Rank 5!
Nah.
It's got nothing to do with rhythm.
The skills you pick up from gaming
end up being pretty useless in real life.
You're living proof of that.
You're strong, Kona-chan.
Pretty much.
How much time has she spent on this stuff?
Izumi?
Izumi's absent today?
Ms. Kuroi.
You have a call from Izumi-san.
Yes.
It's me.
Teacher, I'm terribly sorry...
...but I need to take a sick day...
That's unusual, Izumi.
Did you catch a cold?
No.
It's a bad case of May sickness.
I can barely move...
Just get your butt down here, now!
Hey!
We're leaving.
Why is your bag so full?
Testing starts tomorrow...
...so I have to take everything home for an all-nighter.
Don't tell me...
...you're going to cram all that tonight?
Honestly...
Waiting till the day before a test to take your textbooks home...
...is way too late!
But this is how I always wing it.
You sure sound confident.
Well.
Show me how good you really are then.
Modern
Literature
Math
English
First Semester Midterms
Okay!
Time to return your tests!
I want my mommy!
So-so, I guess.
How'd you do?
You probably shouldn't ask...
I worked hard, though...
Well, now...
What about Miss All-nighter?
Just fine. Thanks for asking.
That's just wrong!
So tired...
I don't feel like doing anything...
Come on.
Let's go.
But you still ended up wandering around with us, huh?
Comp Festival!
Discount on all QUO cards!
Gotta collect 'em all!
Okay.
Time to get a job.
You're so easy to read.
Seriously...
I've never heard of anyone being absent for May sickness.
I can understand how she feels though.
Doesn't it say sickness in the name?
Shouldn't it count as a serious disease?
Do you seriously mean that?
What exactly is May sickness again?
Miyuki.
Tell her.
Let's see...
It begins with the feeling of achievement one experiences...
...after accomplishing a major goal such
as getting into college or getting a new job.
When new relationships beginning in
April don't work out as well as you'd like...
...you are unable to keep up with the gap
between the new life you imagined and reality.
As a result, you feel helpless and weary.
So plain lethargy might not be considered May sickness...
Besides, it's got nothing to do with...
...second-years in high school like us.
I'm always pumped by the change of pace in spring.
Oh, really.
Still, while I'm not as bad as Konata...
...I do feel unusually tired this time of year.
Once I'm home...
...I can't bring myself to do homework.
Me too!
Nobody's gonna comment?
Why are you sighing, Miyuki-chan?
I'm embarrassed to be saying this at this age...
As embarrassed as I was about the contacts matter...
...but I've been avoiding the dentist's because it terrifies me...
...and I got a cavity the other day...
It even hurts when I drink water.
Isn't that...
...normal?
I'm pretty scared of the dentist's myself.
But why did you avoid the dentist's...
...until your teeth started hurting?
Strangely enough...
Even when I know that my teeth will end up hurting...
You still don't want to go to the dentist's, right?
When the pain first starts...
...you choose not to go to the dentist's...
...while you can still live with the pain.
Is the dentist really that scary?
I've never needed to go so I don't know.
You've never gone to the dentist's?
Lucky you...
There's that hospital smell...
Or the nerve-wracking wait.
Ooh! Ooh!
And the sound of the drill gets me every time!
Change Getter!
It's terrifying!
But guys probably like to go to the dentist's, right?
Why?
Aren't drills like a man's romance?
Dinosaur Empire!
I've heard they love it when robots fight using drills!
But they probably don't like having their teeth drilled...
I've been wondering...
Aren't the receptionists and assistants...
...usually pretty ladies?
Now that you mention it, it does seem that way...
Wonder why...
Perhaps it's one of their hiring criteria...
Exclusively beautiful assistants and drills, huh?
That does indeed sound like something geared towards males.
Then...
What would a dentist's office for females be like?
You'd have to get rid of that smell first.
And switch the patient's chair for a soft, auto-massaging recliner.
Then they should also utilize aromatherapy, right?
And include a foot massage while you're being treated.
That sounds nice.
And to numb the pain, they let you play games.
It might be a little difficult to play games at the same time...
But it's a good way to distract you from the pain.
They could give you headphones and play your favorite songs.
Sounds good.
That would also be nice.
But I still don't like the dentist's.
That's true.
What's this?!
What's wrong?
Well...
They're animating another series I like...
...but they're using a completely different cast from the drama CD.
Don't get it.
Was this the work of a higher power?
Personal issues?
Money?
I never buy drama CDs...
...so as long as the voices match the original characters...
...I don't care who they use.
It doesn't work that way, Kagami.
People who have gotten used to the drama CD...
...feel like something's wrong when they start watching the anime.
It takes a while for the feeling to go away.
Well...
...there's one good thing that comes out of this.
What's that?
Drama CD and anime.
You can enjoy two different worlds through them.
Two for the price of one.
You're a die-hard fan, huh?
Thank you very much!
Well...
One of us will be taking Miyuki-san's leftover nugget...
Let's say it goes to whoever wins a staring contest.
Wha—
You're like a little kid.
A staring contest?
That sounds fun!
Kagami's probably gonna lose.
Did you say something?
Then let's go...
Stare-down!
That was...
...so bad!
Wow...
You...
You didn't even look human!
Hey, you guys are overreacting.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
There was a long line for the restroom.
Did something happen?
Hey.
Show that face to Miyuki!
No way.
It was incredible, Miyuki!
I've never seen anything like it!
Fine then.
It's amazing every time I see it!
That face may come in handy
during the talent stage of entrance exams.
That's it, Konata!
It'll get you into college!
Guaranteed!
I'm not exactly thrilled.
There was this thing on TV about the average
number of books a person in Japan reads annually...
...and they said to omit manga and limit the count to normal books.
Well, manga's...
Do light novels count?
I'm not sure.
Light novels should be okay...
What about picture books?
Since they're called books, they might count...
Other fantasy stuff like Harry Potter is considered normal...
So what do you call a normal book?
And the TV show ended by saying...
...how young people are becoming increasingly illiterate...
...but doesn't browsing the Internet and blogging...
...actually improve your literacy?
I get it, and then I don't...
Yo.
Let's get going.
Wait one minute.
Sorry.
I can't go home with you guys.
Do you have something to do?
That's unusual.
I started working.
Wait!
She actually got a job!
Is Comp Festival really that important?!
Anyway...
Konata sure surprised me.
She sure did.
She really got a job.
I thought she was just joking.
That's also true...
...but I was talking about how somebody actually hired her.
Th-That's a little harsh...
Besides...
I can't picture her doing manual labor.
Th-That's true...
I wonder where she's working.
Maybe at a bookstore?
Since she likes manga?
Excuse me.
I'd like this.
Hold on.
I'm busy right now.
Ka-ching!
I hope she doesn't get fired...
Then how about a convenience store?
Excuse me.
I'd like this.
Fourhundredninetyeightyen.
Exactchange.
Thankyoupleasecomeagain.
Doubt it.
Then what about a fast food place?
Fresh Salad
Ice Cream Cone
Vanilla
Chocolate
Strawberry
Smile
I'm smiling. Gotta problem with it?
I don't see it happening...
I guess that also eliminates a family restaurant.
Welcome.
I wonder where she's working.
Traffic survey?
No way.
Video rental store?
Not too sure about that.
A bar.
Nah.
Pizza delivery.
No driver's license.
Supermarket cashier.
Impossible.
Cram school teacher.
Unthinkable.
A bread factory!
That leaves...
Let's ask her tomorrow.
Hey, Konata.
Where're you working?
Tell us!
Just a normal costume café.
It fits her so perfectly!
But should she really be working there?
Good lucky!
I'm Akira Kogami!
This is the second episode of Lucky Channel!
Akira's going all-out!
O-kay!
Next to me...
...we have my wonderful assistant!
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Take it away!
For-For-For-For—
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
I'm just a beginner...
...so I hope that you'll just remember my name.
Yes.
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Okay!
This segment's only just begun...
...but we already have an eruption of messages from everyone!
Akira's super happy!
Thanks!
Man...
This is really something.
I suppose you could call this...
...an indication of Akira-sama's popularity.
Wha—
What?
I saw today's episode.
Yes?
Didn't you show up?
In the actual show.
You were in it, weren't you?
They were gracious enough to put me in.
Whatever.
Oh, yeah...
What scene were you in again?
Uh, I believe...
...scene 45 in part A.
The classroom scene right after vacation.
Now I remember.
You didn't have much of a presence so I forgot.
Well, I only had one line this time.
Whazzat?!
Not good enough for you?!
No! Absolutely not!
Not sure a newbie should be actin' that way.
Y'know, back when I debuted...
Debuted?
How old were you then?
Three.
I was happy just to get any lines then.
Quantity isn't the issue.
You're absolutely right.
My nerves were a wreck after
being surrounded by so many veterans.
It was an educational experience!
You were pretty stiff.
Stiff as a board.
Ooh, look! I'm an amateur.
Y'know.
That was way too...yeah...
Do it again right now.
Here?
There's a chance you'll appear again, right?
I suppose...
Then you better practice some.
I'm offering you help here!
Yes, ma'am!
Please help me out!
Gimme the script.
Which scene was it again?
Scene 45.
This one, huh?
Then I'll be Ms. Kuroi.
Please do.
Ready and...
Action!
Howdy.
Did y'all have a fun vacation?
Then again...
You had b-b—
Bunches.
Bunches of homework...
...and a test right after vacation...
...so you couldn't have been having fun the whole time.
It barely felt like a vacation.
What was that?
No good at all.
That line had no feeling to it.
Feel—
Here!
Right here!
You gotta make 'em feel it right here!
I'm sorry.
If you're just gonna read your lines, a monkey could handle that.
A monkey can't...
It's time to say goodbye!
Time just flies...
...when you're happy, right?
And so...
Send us any questions or comments about the show please!
We'll see you next time.
Bye-bye!
So yeah.
What were the regulars like?
What do you mean?
Y'know...
Does it look like anyone's going to get knocked off?
Aren't they all like fighting with each other?
No...
It didn't look that way to me...
Then you're supposed to...
You're amazing, Kona-chan!
You were very passionate.
Hey, Konata!
Are the other two songs like this?
There's anime stuff along with the SFX stuff.
That's not what I meant!
Sing something the rest of us know!
I can sing whatever I want.
Let's see...
Here's the remote.
Come on, Tsukasa.
If you don't order a song...
...we'll end up listening to her endless medley of anime songs.
I'm okay with that.
This is actually quite fun.
Even you, Miyuki?!
Sorry if I block anyone's view.
I'm gonna stand this time.
Now what?
If you don't stand up when you sing...
...your voice can't truly shine.
You're gonna sing even louder?!
Actual footage from the show!
This is kinda cool!
Looks like it was made way before we were born.
ZARADO!
ERADO!
GARADO!
SHINE, JANKERU!
OH! OH, OH!
HIGH IN THE SKY!
OOH, OOH!
USE SKILL, POWER, AND SOUL!
Here are your drinks!
Thanks.
ZABITAN!
TAKE THAT!
EVIL!
Who ordered the oolong tea?
GABURA!
That's me.
OH! OH, OH, OH, OH!
The iced lemon tea?
ROAR, JANKERU!
That would be mine.
The orange juice?
AKUMAIZER 3!
Over here.
The ginger ale?
THERE IS ONLY ONE PATH TO TAKE!
Sorry.
Could you just set it over there?
OH!
ONLY ONE PATH TO TAKE!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Kagami.
When you buy juice from a vending machine...
...and put in a 200 yen coin and get back a
50 yen coin and a 10 yen coin as change...
...it's like, winner!
But when you ride the train...
...and try to buy a 150 yen ticket...
...and put in a 100 yen coin
thinking that you have five 10 yen coins...
...but once you put in four, you find out you're short one.
Since you have no choice, you put in another 100 yen coin...
...and get back nine 10 yen coins...
...and it's like, loser!
Next time:
「All Kinds of People」
All Kinds of People.
Look forward to next time.