You're really going for it, huh?
Where are you headed?
I'm following the eastern sea road to Tokyo.
Wow, that's pretty impressive!
Good luck!
Thanks!
Stitch, stitch...
What's with the stitching mantra?
If you stare at it so closely, you'll put your stitches in the wrong place, ya know?
Hm?
I really have...
Hey, Tsubomi! Have you finished it?
I'm nearly done, but I just can't quite...
Why are you doing this at school, anyway?
Today's the day our classmate Hayashi reaches the end of his cycling journey,
so we're all going to head out to meet him!
The end of his cycling journey?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
He's reaching the end of his journey?
You see, in homeroom after the school's closing ceremonies...
My plan for the summer vacation
is to bicycle all the way from Kyoto to Tokyo!
Come on, there's no way you can pull that off.
Didn'tcha nearly kill yourself
back in the spring marathon?
Everyone, please.
Jeez, if he says he's going to do it, then why be so harsh on him?!
Erika's right.
Kyoto
Tokyo
I hope you know the distance between
Kyoto and Tokyo is about 500 kilometers.
Just don't overdo it, all right?
Right.
I'm going to do this, no matter what!
Wow, that's amazing.
So he's reaching the end of his journey today, then?
That's right!
When I heard that, I decided I was
going to finish my dress all by myself!
I should make a medal for
Hayashi from the same material!
A medal?
A medal for accomplishing his summer goal!
The Final Stretch of Summer!
I've Finally Finished My Dress!
Somehow I managed to finish it in time.
That's your medal?
Yep!
Here he comes!
You're amazing!
You guys...
Welcome back, Hayashi!
Totally awesome!
You really did it!
Good work, dude!
U-Um...
Please, take this. It's to celebrate your success!
H-Here you go!
Okay...
It's a medal, apparently.
Th-Thanks...
You're welcome!
Hey, you took photos of the places you visited, right?
Can I see them?!
Sure.
Whoa!
Journey Map
This is where I started from, the Grand Sanjou Bridge.
What's this castle?!
That's Okazaki Castle.
Hey, look at this!
Oh, those are the eels I had in Hamamatsu!
They look so good.
Where's this?
Takahashi B&B
That's taken in front of a bed and breakfast I stayed at.
The breakfast there was so delicious.
But man... this is seriously amazing.
You achieved your goal for the
summer with flying colors, Hayashi.
Well, of course!
I can't just sit around like this all day!
Please excuse me, everyone!
We'd better get going too, huh?
Yeah.
See you later, okay, Hayashi?
Huh? Hayashi, did you skin your knee?
You're right! He did!
There you go.
Thanks.
I'm glad you made it back in one piece.
Come on, Ms. Tsurusaki! It was a piece of cake, really.
Ms. Tsurusaki?
Tsubomi pricked her finger with a needle.
Could you bandage it up for her?
All right.
Is something the matter?
What's with your knee?
Oh, it's only a scratch!
Hayashi, you really are great!
I need to complete my goal for the summer too!
What's your goal, Hanasaki?
To make my very own dress
from a design I created myself!
But, well, I just can't quite get the last bit right.
I guess making a dress is harder than I thought it would be.
If it's just a tiny bit left, why not get Kurumi to help you with it?
No! My goal is to finish it myself, and I'm
going to see that through to the very end!
That medal...
I made it from the same material I'm making my dress from.
You've really given this your all,
so I wanted to give you something.
Though I guess it's kind of crappy.
It's really not that bad.
Ah!
I messed it up again.
Now I'll have to start over.
That part really is difficult, isn't it?
Want me to do that bit for you?
No, that's okay. Thanks, Erika.
I just really want to do this myself!
You can do it, Tsubomi!
Thanks!
All right then! We'll stay here to watch over you!
Okay. Next stop is that telephone pole.
Ow...
Hayashi?
Huh?!
Are you all right?
I don't want it!
I don't...
What's the matter, Tsubomi?
You must be Hayashi, right?
I was wondering if you'd mind giving a speech at the post-vacation assembly.
I couldn't give a speech...
I'm sorry, but please, take it!
Huh?!
Hayashi!
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
Maybe he didn't like your medal.
If one clears the mind, even fire
itself can be made to cool the body.
This chilling sensation is intoxicating!
You whelps lack spirit!
If you rouse your spirit, then this heat should not affect you in the slightest!
I'll use this newfound spirit to beat those Precure to a pulp!
I see.
Next question: what was the most memorable place you visited since leaving Kyoto?
I'm sorry, but I really have to go.
Huh?!
Wait, Hayashi!
Well, well, don't you look troubled?
Who are you?!
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles,
Kumojacky.
And I'll be taking the Flower of your Heart!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
Wow, that looks really adorable!
It doesh!
It feels so weird wearing something I made myself.
It's really cute!
You look fantastic!
It really does suit you!
Do you really think so?
It really does!
Come on, give us a twirl!
Huh?
Like this?
You're so cute!
You did a great job finishing it all by yourself!
I might've done it by myself, but I didn't do it alone!
I had you two cheering me on all the way!
Cycle!
Hayashi's Flower of the Heart...
...is the one that was stolen!
Hurry and transhform into Precuresh!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Cycleclecleclecleclecle!
I... I...
I didn't actually ride my bicycle the whole way there!
I got off and took the bus instead!
Huh?!
I just couldn't bear to tell everyone that I'd given up halfway through.
I just wanted everyone to admire me.
So that's why you gave the medal back?
Cleclecleclecle!
Damn it! Just take them down already!
Cycle!
Sunshine!
Your courage has been sealed away by the darkness.
That darkness in your heart shall be illuminated by my light!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Cycle...
Tch!
I'm such a loser, lying to everyone like this.
How idiotic.
If you're spineless enough to call yourself a loser,
then you are naught but a coward lacking in spirit!
How utterly pathetic!
Hayashi isn't pathetic at all!
If he was, he wouldn't feel so
ashamed to have lied like this!
That's proof that he's earnest at heart!
And now you're toying with Hayashi's heart.
I've had it up to here with this!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
It seems you have a lot of spirit, Cure Blossom!
Are you all right?
Is that what you've been working on?
Yes! I finally finished it!
It's really colorful, isn't it?
Oh, no, I just thought you'd pick
something a bit more subdued is all.
I've always been very reserved, that's true.
I didn't even really like speaking in class very much.
But I wanted to make something that would show a new me when I wore it.
"A new me," huh?
I wish I had clothes that could do that.
Hayashi?
You have your bicycle, don't you?
I have to go back to school!
I have to tell them what really happened.
I've lied to you all.
I-I didn't actually get past the mountain roads in Hakone.
I stopped halfway through and took the bus instead!
Huh?!
I really didn't make it the whole way by bicycle.
I'm sorry I lied to you all.
What the heck, man?
I really thought you were
awesome for pulling it off too...
Getting from Kyoto to Hakone is pretty impressive in and of itself, you know?
That doesn't change the fact that I lied to everyone.
U-Um...
Hayashi is still amazing!
After all, he had the courage to admit he lied to everyone!
That's why...
Here.
I'm going to try to climb the
hills of Hakone one more time!
And I'll use this bicycle to do it!
In the language of flowers, rapeseed
blossoms mean "to be blessed with spirit."
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
I hate when you leave me alone, Ichuki!
Summer vacation's over, so I have to go back to school.
What'sh more important, me or shchool?
Huh?
It'sh obviously me!
Play with me inshtead!
Stop being so selfish!
I hate you, Ichuki!
HeartCatch Precure:
Potpourri Runs Away!
Itsuki is Heartbroken!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!