itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
toki o koete
...transcends time,
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
How awful!
It can't be helped.
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
It was too much for her to handle alone.
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
But she knew that this might happen.
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
This is too awful! It shouldn't be happening!
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
If you give up, it'll be the end of everything.
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
But you have the capacity to change fate.
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
This unavoidable destruction, this sorrow...
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
...you can change it all.
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
That's why you have this power.
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
Are you telling the truth?
negai
...the light.
Can someone like me really do something to stop this?
Can I really prevent everything from turning out this way?
Of course you can! Form a contract with me and become a magical girl!
It was a dream?
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 1     It was like I met her in a dream ·  ·  ·  ·  ·
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning, Madoka.
How's Mum?
Tatsuya already headed up there. Go help out.
Okay!
Mama! Mama!
It's morning! Morning!
Wake up! Mama! Mama!
Wake up!
Huh?
Mama woke up!
How's it been going lately?
Hitomi-chan got another love letter.
That makes two this month.
Guys who don't have enough guts to tell a girl they like her in person are worthless.
How's Kazuko?
Our teacher's still at it.
She talks about him all the time in homeroom.
This week will be their three month anniversary, so it's a new record.
I'm not sure about that. This is a risky time for them.
Really?
If it's just a fluke, then problems would be showing up about now.
I guess if they can get past this, then they'll be able to make it through the first year.
I see.
All done!
I wonder which ribbons I should use.
Huh? Isn't that too flashy?
It's supposed to be flashy. We girls must always pay attention to our looks.
That looks pretty good. Now all your secret admirers won't be able to resist you.
Like I'd have any.
You have to think you do. That's the secret to being pretty.
Safe.
Anyway, eat everything all up.
Okay!
How about another cup of coffee?
Hm, I'm fine.
All right. I'll see you guys later.
Bye!
Madoka, you need to hurry, too.
Huh? Oh, right!
Later!
Bye!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Madoka, you're late.
Oh, those are some cute ribbons.
R-Really? You don't think I'll stand out too much?
They're very nice.
So, she said that you shouldn't date someone who asks you out in a love letter instead of directly.
Your mum's pretty cool! She's really beautiful, and she's a career woman.
If only it were that easy...
I wish I had that problem.
I wish I could get even a single love letter.
So you want to transform into a cutie like Hitomi that everyone wants?
I guess that's why you started with those ribbons, huh?
No, my mum...
I bet your mum taught you the secret to being popular! You dirty, dirty girl!
A girl like you needs punishment!
H-Hey, stop! Stop!
You're cute, but I won't let you become popular with the guys.
You're going to be my wife!
I have something important to discuss with all of you today. Make sure you pay attention.
Should a sunny-side up egg be hard or soft?!
What do you think, Nakazawa-kun?!
I, uh... I-I guess either is fine?
That's right! Either is fine!
If you think a woman's value is decided by how she cooks her eggs, you're horribly mistaken!
You girls out there, don't associate with anyone who says they can't eat a sunny-side up egg that isn't fully cooked!
It didn't work out, huh?
Yeah, it didn't.
And you guys out there, don't grow up to become someone who nags about how they want their eggs cooked!
Also, I'd like to introduce all of you to a new transfer student that'll be joining us.
She left that until last?
Okay. Akemi-san, come in.
She's cute! She's cool!
Wow. She's really pretty.
No way... She can't be...
Okay, introduce yourself.
My name is Akemi Homura. Nice to meet you all.
Akemi Ho
Akemi Homura
Um, Akemi-san?
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
A Christian school in Tokyo.
Were you in any clubs?
Did you do any sports? How about art?
I never joined any.
Your hair's really pretty. What shampoo do you use?
Akemi-san has some kind of mysterious aura about her.
Hey, Madoka. Do you know her?
She was staring at you, wasn't she?
Um...
I'm sorry... I guess I was really nervous.
I don't feel very well.
Would you mind if I went to the nurse's office?
Oh, then I'll take you there.
I'll go, too!
No, don't worry about me.
I'll ask the person in charge.
Kaname Madoka-san, you're the health officer for this class, right?
I, uh...
Could you take me to the nurse's office?
She's really cute!
Um, how do you know I'm the health officer?
Saotome-sensei told me.
Oh, I see. The nurse's office is...
This way, right?
Huh? Yeah, but...
You... just kind of seem like you know the way.
A-Akemi-san?
You can call me Homura.
Homura-chan?
What is it?
I, uh... That's a unique name.
No, I didn't mean it was weird...
I-I think it's cool!
Kaname Madoka, do you value your current way of life?
Your family, your friends... Do you think dearly of them?
I, uh... I do.
My family, my friends... I love them. They really mean a lot to me.
Is that true?
It is. Why wouldn't it be?
I see.
If that's true, then you mustn't ever think of trying to become someone else.
If you do, you'll lose everything.
You just need to stay Kaname Madoka, like you have so far.
I-I think that's a prefecture record...
Huh? What's that about?
Doesn't make any sense, does it?
I thought she was one of those smart, beautiful girls who are well-read and athletic, but instead she's one hell of a nut.
Just how big of an impression do you have to make on people?!
Is that moe? Is that what moe is?!
Madoka-san, is this really the first time you've met Akemi-san?
Hmm, I guess I'd have to say yes.
You guess? Is there some weird reason why you'd say no?
I... think I saw her in a dream I had last night.
That's great! You're trying to get some attention, yourself, now!
That's mean! I'm seriously worrying about this!
It's decided, then! This is all part of your karma from your last life!
You're friends, meeting each other again after having travelled through space and time!
What type of dream?
I don't really remember... I just know it was really strange.
Then maybe you really have met her before.
Huh?
You might not remember her, but subconsciously, you know her from somewhere, and that may have come out in your dream.
Isn't that just a little too convenient?
How much of a coincidence is that?
You have a point.
Oh. Look at how late it is.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
What do you have today? Piano? Japanese dance?
I have tea ceremony practice.
We have entrance exams soon, but I guess I have to keep doing it.
I'm glad I was born petit-bourgeois.
Shall we go as well?
Oh hey, Madoka? Could we stop by the CD store on the way back today?
Sure.
Kamijou-kun's again?
You know how it is.
Talk to you later.
Later!
See you!
Save me.
Save me, Madoka!
Who's there?
We're currently under construction
Store areas under reconstruction are closed
Save me.
Where are you?
Who are you?
Save me.
Was that you?
Save me...
Homura-chan?
Move away from him.
B-But he's hurt.
N-No, don't hurt him!
This has nothing to do with you.
But he called for me!
I heard him telling me to save him!
I see.
Madoka, this way!
Sayaka-chan!
Out of all the times...
What is she doing this time?
Attacking people randomly while cosplaying?
Actually, what is that?
It's not a stuffed animal, is it?
Is it alive?
I don't know. I don't know, but...
I need to save him!
Huh? Where's the emergency exit? Where are we?
What is this place?
Everything keeps changing.
Damn it! What's going on?!
S-Something's there!
This can't be happening, can it?
I must be having a bad dream or something, right Madoka?
Huh? What was that...?
What's going on?
That was pretty close, but it's all okay now.
You saved Kyubey, didn't you?
Thank you.
He's an important friend to me.
He called for me.
I heard his voice in my mind.
Hm, I see.
From the look of your uniforms, I assume you're Mitakihara students, as well?
Are you second years?
Who are you?
Oh, that's right. I should introduce myself, but before that...
Would you mind if I took care of a little something first?
W-Wow...
E-Everything is back to normal!
The witch ran away. If you want to take it down, you'll need to chase after it quickly.
I'll give the witch to you this time.
The witch isn't what I'm interested in.
You don't seem to understand what's going on here.
I'm saying, I'll let you go.
I think we would both like to avoid any unnecessary trouble.
Thank you, Mami. You saved me.
Thank these girls. I was just passing by.
Thank you very much.
My name is Kyubey!
Were you the one that was calling for me?
That's right, Kaname Madoka and Miki Sayaka!
W-Why do you know our names?
I came here to ask you two for help.
To... help?
I want you to form a contract with me and become magical girls!
sore ja mata ne tte te o furutte
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
I say, "See you," and wave my hand,
muri ni waratte samishiku natte
無理に笑って　さみしくなって
while laughing too much and becoming lonely.
kousaten shingou tooku no kurakushon
交差点信号　遠くのクラクション
Lights at the crossing; a car's horn far away.
shiranai dareka no warai au koe
知らない誰かの　笑いあう声
A stranger's laughing voice.
kyou wa hitori de aruku kayoi nareta machi
今日は独りで歩く　通い慣れた街
Today, I walk alone through familiar streets.
demo itsumo yori mo nandaka
でもいつもよりもなんだか
But I feel a bit smaller than usual all by myself.
jibun ga chotto chiisaku omoeru yo
自分がちょっと　小さく思えるよ
sore ja mata ne tte te o furutte
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
I say, "See you," and wave my hand.
egao o tsukutte samishiku natte
笑顔作って　さみしくなって
I force a smile and become lonely,
honto wa mada hanashi tarinai kedo
ホントはまだ　話し足りないけど
but the truth is that I still haven't talked enough.
sore ja mata ne tte kotoba de
それじゃまたねって言葉で
I say, "See you," but my words...
"mata aeru" tte uso o tsuite
「また会える」ってウソをついて
My words, "Until next time," are a lie.
itsumo toori no egao de iu yo
いつも通りの　笑顔で言うよ
I say them with my usual smile.
mata ashita
また　あした
See you tomorrow.
Illustrator Hanokage
I can grant each of you one wish.
What? Is that true?
A wish...
It can be anything.
I can make any miracle you want happen.
Episode 2        I thought that was really nice
I thought that was really nice.