I will grasp it,
here and now.
My own star!!
All right.
Position Zero!
The first day of auditions is over!
Aijo Karen-san.
You have been approved as a participant in the auditions.
Huh? What?!
Let us compete in song and dance,
and aim to become the Top Star.
Wait a moment! What about Hikari-chan?
As these auditions are being conducted in absolute secrecy,
you must not speak of them to others.
Breathe a word,
and you will be fined.
Fined?!
Karen-chan, what's wrong?
Nothing! I had a weird dream, that's all!
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm fine, just fine! Pas de problème!
What on earth happened yesterday?
H-Hikari-chan?
I'll be living here too.
What?!
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Who shall be the one to grasp hold of that star?
To stand at the peak of that tower?
A quietly kindled flame now blazes and consumes my heart
Whatever fate might bring
We dance on this stage of our own will
to
bi
ta
te
And we take flight!
I AM REBORN
I'm certain of what I saw on that day
The sparkle of those scattering stars
Shine on me until my fingers touch yours
From across a promise faded by time
The true story begins before the curtain rises
And it unfolds before our very eyes
It's here, in the place where I was reborn
That I found you once more
Hikari-chan!
Hikari-chan! Hikari-chan!
Won't you tell me what's going on?
Come on, Hikari-chan!
All three of us? In the room I share with Karen-chan?
Three of us?
What was that about, Hikari-chan?
That theater, and that giraffe!
Were you not informed?
You're not to speak of any of this.
T-The fine!
Karen-chan!
Sorry, private conversation!
I didn't know about any of this!
There was that giraffe, and that weird stage,
and the two of you dancing up there like your lives depended on it...
Move!
Hey, Kaoruko, we're here!
Yo, Kaoruko!
Aw, and I was having such a lovely dream!
I can't believe you're able to sleep like that in the first place.
It's so soothing entrusting myself to your back, Futaba-han!
C'mon, get moving.
Okie dokie.
So this school is fine with its students riding motorcycles?
Yep, just fine.
Forget about that!
Kagura-san, what's going on here?!
Why are you back in our room?
I thought we decided it was impossible!
I think it will be fine.
What?
Hey, wait, Hikari-chan!
Cancel! Cancel! I want to cancel!
Oh my, up with the sun and
already passionately rehearsing.
Can't say I recognize the play.
But what big, bold movements!
Yes, this will do nicely!
That's not it at all!
Oh yeah! Hoshimi-san, what happened yesterday—
That was a violation of the rules.
The result is going to be invalidated for sure.
Aren't you Miss Popular, Karen-chan?
Stop and hold it.
But be sure not to hold your breath.
Focus on your abdominal muscles.
Keep your breathing steady.
Very good.
Up to the next scale.
Aijo, sing the next one.
Hikari-chan?
Do you want to eat lunch with...
Huh?
Hikari-chan!
Do they not have lunchtime in England?
No entry until the curtain rises, then?
I know you can hear me. Hey.
Remove Karen from the auditions.
She's in the way.
I understand.
I made a promise with Hikari-chan!
I—No, we...
We absolutely will become stars, together!
Her participation is valid.
Stupid.
Dorkaren!
Found you!
So this is where you were, Hikari-chan.
We were looking for you!
Why?
Are you looking for something?
I was lost, that's all.
Oh, glad to hear it.
Look what I brought!
My homemade banana pudding!
Won't you come have some with us?
I don't care for jiggly things.
Oh my.
Transition from the natural turn into the rumba cross.
You there! Don't look at your feet!
Remember the step sequence.
Yes!
Sorry!
I didn't get to talk to Hikari-chan during lunch, either.
Wow, they're amazing!
The two of them really do shine.
Tendo-san, the child of two stage actors,
and Claudie-chan, who's been acting since she was a kid.
The Top Star.
Could I ever shine like that?
That's our Maya-sama!
Perfect as ever!
Saijo-san accompanied her beautifully, too!
They're both so amazing!
If you're only here to spectate, then get out.
Get out.
If you can't overcome them,
you'll never get to center stage.
That's quite enough, Hoshimi.
I'm sorry.
Time to alternate.
Everyone find a partner.
Yes!
Nana—
Hikari-chan!
Wanna pair up with me, Hikari-chan?
Let's you and me be partners!
Excuse me?
Hey, Hoshimi-san.
Hey... Hello?
Do you know anything about that stage from yesterday?
It was all in the e-mail, remember?
E-mail?
A revue for the chosen Girls of the Stage.
Wait, are you saying you didn't get one?
What're you talking about?
Did you just drop in?
I suppose you could say that!
You've got to be kidding me!
There's no way that's allowed!
Wow, those two have some mad skills.
I think one of them's just mad, period.
If you weren't even chosen,
you have no right to get in my way!
I'm giving this my everything.
I'm not like you! I'm—
Stop there!
Hoshimi-san...
Karen-chan, good job up there.
What happened?!
Junna-chan?
Junna-chan!
Hoshimi-san?
Hoshimi!
Get a hold of yourself, Hoshimi-san!
Junna-chan's been spending every moment of her free time practicing by herself.
I'll stay with her until she wakes up.
All right. Come get me when she does.
Hoshimi-san...
You go on back to class now, Karen-chan.
Thank you, Banana.
Leave her to me.
Actor Training Department
It's vitally important to broaden your horizons.
The role you portray is represented by the very smallest circle.
In order to have a complete and objective view of your own performance
you must consider the entire stage as a whole.
Karen-chan, let's go... home?
U-Um, Hikari-chan?
You know what the auditions are.
A revue for the chosen Girls of the Stage.
That's right.
So you shouldn't be part of them, Karen.
What?
Good morning.
I see.
Did something happen between you and Karen-chan?
It's nothing, really. I just got a little angry.
Oh?
Is it that, or is it something else?
To me, it's the same thing.
If you weren't chosen, it's because you don't shine brightly enough.
Stay out of our audition and out of my way.
I can't!
I can't leave the audition!
My heart skipped a beat at what Hoshimi-san said!
As hard as I try, I can't reach their level.
I can't close that distance, no matter how hard I work.
But that doesn't mean I can give up.
Junna-chan...
I will grasp it,
here and now.
My own star!!
I want to become a star.
Maybe, just maybe...
Once I reach the stage we promised to stand on together,
even if Tendo-san or Claudie-chan get there first,
then we just have to do what Hoshimi-san said.
We have to overcome them.
We can't share the stage.
Karen...
But I was given a chance.
A chance to shine with my own light.
To stand center stage,
with the spotlight right on me.
I think I might be able to.
I'll become a star.
It's as though when you came back,
you opened my eyes.
I want us to become stars together.
To make that dream a reality.
Hikari-chan, I want to do Starlight with you!
Karen...
Day
I AM REBORN
On the stage that overflows with stardust,
a magnificent flower of love shall bloom!
Student of the 99th cohort, Aijo Karen!
You will all gaze upon my Starlight!
Upon every person shines a star of fate.
A star shining at night, or twinkling in the dawn.
A star that shoots across the sky.
Even if your own star lies hidden from your view,
I will raise my eyes to the heavens, and on this day...
Student of the 99th cohort, Hoshimi Junna!
I will grasp it, here and now. My own star!
I used to think a single defeat would mean the end of it all.
A Girl of the Stage carries her own individuality.
To choose the Top Star from among them—
that is the purpose of this audition.
The Top Star. She who stands upon the fated stage.
She who unleashes a barrage of unending light
which will shine ever across time.
An eternal leading lady.
Leading lady?
If I become the Top Star, does that mean I can attain the lead role I'm destined for?
Hoshimi-san!
This is my revenge, Aijo-san!
Well then, we will now begin the second day of auditions
for this Revue of Longing.
Let us compete in song and dance
and aim to become the Top Star!
A Revue of Longing
How this came to be I cannot know
donna wake ga atta no ka
I stand here engulfed in flame
watashi wa honoo ni tsutsumarete
Though so long imprisoned,
torawareteita totemo nagai aida
Gla—
Glasses?!
I will achieve it.
The flame within my breast has not ever disappeared
sono honoo wa oku no kieru koto wa nai
I will become a star! The leading lady!
My veiled potential was unseen and unsung
mikaisa nado dare ni mo ii
For there was no one who stood by me to see
soba ni wa inakatta kara
She disappeared?!
Hoshimi-san?
The wind that drives me fanned this flame
mukaikaze ni aorare
Burning my heart to cinders
kokoro wo yaita no
What it is I truly strive for
nani wo motometeiru no ka wa
Only the star knows
ano hoshi dake ga shitteiru
Hoshimi Junna
Age 8
All I'd done with my life was study.
Until the first time I found it. That sparkling dream.
What I desired wasn't status or knowledge.
I met a star of my very own.
Fate brought me to it.
On that day, I was reborn.
As a Girl of the Stage!
But,
no matter how hard I tried,
I could never catch up to them.
They were already running so far ahead of me.
The liberated song of my future
fumerarenai miraika wa
Has no one to sing it at my side
dare ni mo wakaranai kedo
I fought to reach this place, by no effort but my own
tatakaitsuzuketeta jibun jishin dake de
What it is I truly strive for
nani wo motometeiru no ka wa
Only the star knows
ano hoshi dake ga shitteiru
To become a star, I will—
When the curtain rises,
maku ga akeba mirai ga
My future will arrive to spirit me away from here
kanarazu watashi no mukae ni kuru
A mannequin?
I cannot remain in this place
soko ni ite wa ikenai
Give me more fire
honoo wo motto kure
I cannot lose here
makerarenai, koko de
More of them?!
I won't let myself be buried.
This is no defeat
make nanka nai
I cannot afford to fail
shippai dekinai
I will overcome them!
This is no failure
shippai ja nai
You couldn't understand
anata ni wa wakaranai
I don't understand, so that's all the more reason
anata no koto wakaranai dakara koso
For us to talk together
katariaeru futari
The darkness of night
yoru no yami wa
Until the dawn arrives
asa ga kuru made
Grows ever deeper, and I sink into its depths
fukaku naru, oborete yuku wa
There is a future for us all
mirai wa dare ni mo aru
I will not lose! I cannot!
I cannot allow it
sore de wa ikenai kara
You, incapable
hitori dake de
I'll catch up, no matter what!
To my near-forgotten dream
wasurekaketeta yume ni
Of accomplishing anything on your own
nandemo dekinai anata ni
Even so
sore demo
I alone
watashi dake
Cannot afford to lose
makezu ni irarenai no
This audition is my chance.
I won't let it pass me by.
Not for anything.
I will seize my star with my own hands,
so that my time to shine will never end!
This is it!
That's a big non, non!
It's not true that you only get one shot!
We will return to stand on the stage again and again!
Passion and brilliance.
I understand.
This is the power of a Girl of the Stage.
I'll never give up! I'm a Girl of the Stage!
For one alone, for one alone
hitotsu no, hitotsu no
And I want to become a star!
I will become a star, together with Hikari-chan!
Solely for the sake of my only light
tatta hitotsu no hikari no tame
If this star alone knows the future
kono hoshi dake ga mirai wo shitteiru no nara
I shall look up and raise my hand to the sky
sora wo miagete, sotto te wo nobasu
Position Zero!
The second day of auditions is over!
Why was she not chosen from the beginning?
Now I understand.
Two, with one destiny between them.
Karen, I'm sorry.
Their dream...
I lost again.
Nicely done!
Maybe I'm overthinking this.
Huh?
It seems that the simple ones are the strongest, after all.
That's so mean! I'm not simple!
But this isn't over.
And that means I've got to stick it out until the very end.
With everything I have, I'll aim to become a star.
Right?
Hoshimi-san!
You can call me Junna.
Sure thing, Jun-Jun!
Already?
And you can call me Karen!
Come to think of it, they do call you Dorkaren.
Aw, Jun-Jun, don't be like that!
A dream isn't something you have yourself.
It's something you give to others.
Only one star can shine at the top.
This is Tendo Maya.
THIS IS
TENDO MAYA
Next Time: Top Star
Shoujo Kageki Revue Starlight.
I-I understand.