Tooru!
Run-chan! Gosh...
What is it?
Thank you, Tooru!
Right...
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
Won't you come with me?
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう？
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　あつまるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日射し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ちあわせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
and we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
Birthday
Push-
button
cross-
ing
at
night
Morning!
Good morning!
Oh! Morning!
Another cold day today.
Ah, won't spring come sooner?
Oh, come to think of it, isn't Tooru's birthday coming up?
Yup, it is!
Then should we throw a party?
I'm okay without one.
But I insist!
Look forward to the present I'm getting you this year!
Okay.
Look forward to it?
Don't tell me it's that again.
What kind of animal was that, anyway?
Those uniforms...
Oh, they must be middle schoolers.
There's a school open house going on today.
Oh, that explains it.
After the New Year, it's exams for them, isn't it?
And we'll be yet another year older.
Exams...
Exams, huh? Brings back memories, right, Tooru?
Huh?
Yeah.
"First choice: 2nd High"
Ah...
Gotta figure out my second choice school soon.
So you've figured out your first choice?
Yeah. With my grades, I figured this place is about right.
Tooru, what will you do for high school?
Haven't decided? You're still in second year, after all.
I'll aim for wherever you go.
You mean 2nd High?
With your grades, I'm sure you could get in somewhere better, Tooru.
No...
Anywhere you go, I'll go too.
Here.
Thanks!
So, have you decided on a high school?
Well, you could say that.
How does 2nd High sound?
Oh my. That sounds wonderful. They have a good reputation, too.
Your class rank's about right for there, isn't it?
Yeah.
Ah,
speaking of which, Tooru said she'd aim for whatever school I get into.
Huh?
Apply for a better school.
B-But...
It will make your life easier in the future.
Didn't you just say 2nd High was wonderf-
I CHANGED MY MIND.
What?
But we both know how I'd do on the entrance exams.
My class rank isn't good enough, either.
You're right.
Not at the moment, it isn't.
Ah! Wait!
Who are you calling?
A cram school.
Noooo!
All right, I understand.
We won't get anywhere if I force you to go.
So.
How about all the Kobe beef you can eat?
Got it! I'll give it a shot!
Really?
So you're applying to a better school, Run-chan?
It looks like I am.
I talked it over with my mom.
So you're going to cram school, and getting a private tutor.
You're really motivated!
The private tutor's someone you know, Hira-chan!
Really?
Look!
Allow me to introduce! Meet Tooru-sensei!
Greetings.
But...
Isn't Tooru-chan...
Yep, you're right.
But come on, you can't have a teacher without the glasses!
I wasn't talking about the glasses...
Then let us begin studying.
All right!
Let's start with the easy stuff.
Huh?
For starters. Memorize these. All of them.
They're the basics. It's just rote memorization.
T-That's quite the stack...
Jenga!
The answer is A!
Is what they're tricking you into thinking!
Be careful!
What is this voice? It speaks straight into my mind!
My right arm is writing answers, even though I'm not controlling it!
What's happening?
Huh?
A dream?
Oh no! The words!
Wait up!
I won't be able to solve the problems like this!
Huh?
Run-chan. Wake up.
A dream?
Yes.
Push-
button
cross-
ing
at
night
Japanese
Math
Complete
Master
Wow!
Your grades got better!
I've been reading study books every waking moment!
I see.
So much that the books all ended up this ragged...
Oh, my bad.
I dropped them in the bath...
What? All of them?
I'll buy you new ones.
Well, I'm off now!
Run-chan, go for it!
Aoigaoka High School
Entrance Exams
Okay then!
When the bell rings, flip over your test sheets and begin!
Here I go!
Begin!
Oops. On to the next pencil.
Sabotage?
Tokyo is a scary place!
Okay! I'm coming to collect your answer sheets!
Excuse me...
Sorry about earlier. Did that pencil point fly at you?
Huh? Oh, no, it's okay.
Oh, that's good to hear.
So it wasn't sabotage.
Oh? So you came all the way from Kansai to take the exam?
Yeah. We're moving here this spring, so...
Oh! Speaking of Kansai...
This is my lucky charm for today!
Really? To the God of Cows or something?
I did it! It's there! It's right there!
Look! My number's up there!
I passed thanks to you, Tooru.
No you didn't. It was your own effort, Run-chan.
Congratulations.
And so, I somehow managed to pass.
Wow.
Run, you really gave your all, didn't you?
I'd write vocabulary on my hands, so I wouldn't forget them.
Ah, I sometimes write things on my hand so I don't forget, too.
On a test, that would be cheating, though.
Well, of course I washed them off for the test.
But I got into the habit and wrote things all over my body,
so it was a pain to get it all off.
Morning.
Morning...
Good morning.
They announce
test results today,
don't they? Won't
they have posted
them already
by now?
They announce test results today, don't they?
Won't they have posted them already by now?
Hmm...
I'll go later.
You're
certainly
taking it
easy
You're certainly taking it easy.
I wouldn't
be able
to see
anyway.
Accepted
I wouldn't be able to see anyway.
Coming!
I've got a present for you today, Tooru!
Really?
Here! Seeing as your birthday's coming up.
Is it cake?
It's cake!
Well, three second rule, as they say.
Um... but it fell totally upside down.
Just kidding!
Ta-dah! This is the real one.
What?!
Did I surprise you?
They say you feel twice as happy if your hopes are lowered first!
I wanted you to be happy, Tooru.
Who told you that?
I'll carry the cake.
Don't worry, I won't drop it again.
Just give it.
But I couldn't make you carry my stuff...
Tooru, are you mad?
Tooru, you're turning 16, aren't you?
You've gotten so big!
You used to be so tiny.
Huh?
Crawling on the ground after me...
Always crying if you didn't have candy in your hand...
You were so cute back then!
Run-chan.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Huh? It was in a dream I had the other day.
They met in elementary school
A dream?
Look how tall you've gotten! Still tiny as ever, though.
So I'm small either way
Don't treat me like a kid.
Found a white hair!
That's pretty daring, bringing a cake to school.
There's a piece for everyone, so we can eat it at lunch!
Where should we leave it until lunch?
Oh yeah! We'll need a refrigerator.
But there aren't any at school.
Where would be the coldest place in school?
The bathroom?
Gulp...
You're eating this too, you know.
On that note, Tooru's birthday's coming up, is it?
A happy occasion!
Thank you
very much
So what will you do for that?
Don't worry. I've got a present ready for her actual birthday.
I see. Well, I'll buy you that book you wanted, Tooru.
Thanks.
And... I'll get you...
Cups.
Cups? What kind?
What's with the ruler?
E cups.
Wha... What?
Come on, let's eat the cake already, before it goes bad!
Sounds like a plan.
Oooh!
Nice!
Looks good!
A heart-pounding game!
Huh?
One of these is actually a wasabi-filled cake!
Can't you celebrate normally?
Also, one of them is obviously green.
That's no secret at all.
Yuuko, you get the best job.
Here.
What?!
She is from Kansai.
How I envy her.
Spicy...
Shall we dig in?
But be prepared. There was actually one more wasabi cake-
Run-chan!
This cake is so cute.
Oh, a commemorative picture?
H-How nice.
Let's take one together, for the occasion.
Okay then.
Yuuko, you're blurry.
Huh?
But I wasn't even moving.
Maybe you twitched a tiny bit.
Because of the wasabi?
Once more, to get it right!
Then let's all match Yuuko.
Hey! Do it normally!
I moved! One more!
Then let's match Yuuko again.
Ready, and...
Ah, I moved again!
Geez!
Okay! Continuing from yesterday.
Yesterday, using Cavalieri's principle,
we derived equations for the volume and surface area of a sphere.
The volume V equals 4/3 π r
Toorun?
and the surface area S equals 4 π r .
Cake!
T-This must mean... um... um... um...
Toorun! Toorun!
Happy birthday!
You mean
Whaaat?
Okay then, Yutaka-san! Solve this problem.
Whaaaat?
Here, take a look!
Huh? What's this?
A picture from when I was studying for exams!
Oh, from two years ago?
You're eating cake.
Yup. It was Tooru's birthday that day.
Why are you being fed?
That's what being an exam student entails!
Stop bothering me, Tooru!
Just kidding!
Here.
Happy birthday, Tooru!
Huh?
But you didn't forget her present.
Yup. Even if I forgot everything else.
Also...
Look.
Oh? What's this?
This was Tooru's birthday last year.
When it was her turn for exams, huh?
You got it.
Tooru said not to bother since she had exams, but I wanted to at least get her cake and a present.
"Tooru, good luck!"
Weren't you bothering her?
Oh, of course I wasn't. Right, Tooru?
Tooru, you gave it your all too, right?
And then...
Ta-dah! Here's this year's commemorative picture!
Hey, what's with that picture?
Tooru sent it to me!
Gosh! Delete it already!
Hey! Honestly...
Don't wanna!
Give me your phone!
Let's go, Tooru.
Okay.
Hey!
Slipping past the words that pour from the classroom,
I felt a little lonely in the hallway by myself.
Fun times always
pass by so fast.
700M UNTIL STATION
That's why the pages of the album in our heart are infinite.
Surely, surely, surely,
always, always, always,
my memories of your smile will not fade.
Hey, Tooru.
Let's eat cake together next year, too!
More, and more, and more,
Spare me the wasabi cake, please.
today, and tomorrow, and the day after too,
Hold your horses. We've got exams next year.
let's make even more of those memories.
Gosh, Nagi, don't mention scary things like that!
What do you mean?
That's reality for you.
That's right. We'll have exams this time next year, won't we?
100M UNTIL STATION
Exams.
We're heading this way today.
Bye-bye!
Time just flew by, didn't it?
It feels like you entered our school just yesterday,
but you're becoming a second-year already.
That's right...
And Run-chan will be a third-year...
Tooru?
What's up?
Nothing.
Really?
Yeah.
By the way, Run-chan.
Huh?
It's rather late of me to ask, but why'd you switch to this school?
Why do you think?
Tell me.
It's a se-cret!
Come on...
The tall shadows
akane ni narabu
茜に並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kageboushi
背高かげぼうし
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　お喋り
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね、明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね、明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigato
いつもありがと
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれて　ヨカッタな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
ル・ル・ルン・
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風とココロ　ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
つぎの角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
Here to correct the mistakes of the past?
That would be a time traveler.
Pithecanthropus erectus!
That's called "Homo erectus" now- and isn't that prehistoric?
Next time on A-Channel!
"Alien"!
Only Miporin can keep up with Yutaka's gags until the very end!
See you next week!