[REIA] "And so, having
completed their Promise Kiss,
the two began a journey
beyond severance,
guided by the star of love."
[KUREHA] Hey, Mommy, what's
your new book gonna be about?
[REIA] It's the story
of you and your friend,
the girl who taught
us all about Kumaria.
This is the last page.
[KUREHA] Huh? I don't
know what girl you mean.
[REIA]
Of course you know what girl!
She's the one you love.
Don't you remember telling me
you sang the Love
Song together?
[KUREHA]
I don't know any girl like that.
[REIA]
What?
Oh, Kureha. What's happened?
Don't tell me you've
forgotten her?
[GINKO] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also, we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you,
so we had to cross the wall.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[HARISHIMA laughs]
It was amazing.
I wish you could've seen
the look on Kureha's face.
I didn't expect it
to feel so good.
Thank you for choosing
me from the crowd.
You found me, and I love you.
I'm not a weak girl at the mercy
of the Invisible Storm any more.
I'm far too important and will
never get excluded, now.
It's wonderful!
[gasps]
[BEAR growls]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Kuma shock!
[HARISHIMA screams]
[LULU humming]
[LULU]
♪ Simmer, simmer, ♪
♪ porridge, simmer,
simmer softly! ♪
♪ Growl, growl, growl! ♪
[LULU]
After Ginko saved her letter,
Kure-pie gave us official
permission to freeload
at her house! We're so close
now, Lulu can almost taste it!
[GINKO sighs]
[LULU] Ginko's gone through a
lot, but it seems like it's
just a matter of time before
she gets her Promise Kiss.
[GINKO groans]
I won't.
I'll never back down on love!
[KUREHA]
I don't understand.
Why would you protect
Sumika's letter for me?
Why, when it cost
you so much?
[KUREHA gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE]
♪ Yuri Amour! ♪
[KUREHA]
Ginko?
Oh, good, I'm glad you're awake!
[GINKO]
Mm.
[KUREHA]
Uh...
Um.
If you want, I can tell
you all about my love.
[KUREHA]
Oh.
As long as you
don't forget love,
you'll never, ever
be truly alone.
And if you don't
give up on love,
even if you lose something
you'll never be invisible.
[KUREHA] Wait, how do
you know those words?
You are, and have always
been, my Lady Kumaria.
Your Lady Kumaria?
Like the one from Mom's book?
[GINKO]
Delicious smell.
You smell, Kureha.
Growl, growl.
You need to search.
You need to find what you want.
[KUREHA] But does what
I want need to be found?
[GINKO]
Yes.
[KUREHA gasps]
[KUREHA]
I don't know what to look for,
and I don't know
where to find it.
[GINKO]
I know you remember.
It's in your fingers,
in your lips.
[KUREHA]
Uh!
[GINKO]
It's inside you, right here.
Please, will you give
me the Promise Kiss?
[KUREHA]
Promise Kiss?
From me, to you?
[GINKO]
And me to you.
Then, everything will awaken,
and it will all change.
[KUREHA gasps]
[GINKO labored breathing]
[KUREHA]
Whoa. What was that?
Oh wow. What a thing to dream.
[LULU] Growl!
The honey porridge is ready.
Is everything all right?
You're blushing, Kure-pie!
[footsteps]
Just your imagination!
You don't mind keeping
your eye on Ginko, do you?
She's sweating a lot. Thanks!
Growl?
My Lady Kumaria.
[music box plays]
[sighs] What would
I dream that for?
[REIA] Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
[KUREHA]
Yep! Guess what, Mom?
I taught her how to
sing the Love Song!
[REIA]
Oh, my! You did?
[KUREHA] Uh-huh! It's because
she's my special friend,
so I figured she
gets an exception.
[REIA laughs]
I see!
You really love her,
don't you, sweetie?
[KUREHA]
Yeah! I do!
Her? Who is "her"?
Maybe... Oh. How could
I forget? I did have a friend.
Mom, please help me.
Who was that girl?
I think I'm starting
to remember.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[STUDENT A] I heard
there was another bear attack!
[STUDENT B] No way!
Wasn't it exterminated, though?
I thought that girl shot it.
You know, what's-her-name?
[STUDENT C]
Oh, yeah!
The one who attracts bad
luck to, like, everyone.
[STUDENT A] Whether she did
or not, I'm telling you
another girl from her class
totally got attacked.
--[STUDENT B] For real?
--[STUDENT A]  For real.
[STUDENT C]
So, who was it this time?
[KUREHA]
What? Kaoru Harishima?
[YURIIKA]
Yes.
She was discovered this morning
in front of the flowerbed.
They declared it a bear attack
based on the poor
girl's injuries.
But how? I thought
I shot that bear.
Which means, unfortunately,
there's yet another bear
still roaming the
halls of this school.
It's horrifying. The bears
didn't just take Reia's life.
They stole the
proof of our love.
They took the star
pendant I gave her.
Oh, Miss Yuriika.
[YURIIKA]
The bear with Reia's pendant.
That one is our mortal enemy.
One day we'll find
it, and then...
[KUREHA]
And then, I'll kill it.
I'm so sorry.
You came here to ask me about
something, didn't you, dear?
Yes, it's about an old friend.
I'd like to know what you know.
An old friend, of yours?
Right. I remembered her
while I was listening
to Mom's music box.
When I was younger, apparently
I had a friend who was
very special to me.
I know this girl as "her".
[gasps]
But for some weird reason,
I can't remember her
face or her real name.
I was hoping you might know
something more about my friend.
[YURIIKA grunts]
Come to think of it,
Reia made a rather
strange comment once.
It was shortly before
she died, I think.
She told me you had suddenly
and completely forgotten
about a close friend.
[KUREHA]
Huh?!
[YURIIKA] What else?
Ah yes, her last book.
The Moon Girl and
the Forest Girl.
She said she wrote
that story about you
and that forgotten girl.
Mom's last book, was
about me and my friend?
[LULU]
Ginko, hang in there!
Sniffle-growl. Your
fever's not going down.
[LULU]
Lulu knows!
[LULU] This'll turn you into
a nice, cold growl-sicle,
and you'll feel way better!
Lulu is so clever!
[LIFE SEXY]
Kumaria is love.
As the world's mother,
she is the one
who approves all living
things and gives them love.
[crying]
[LIFE SEXY] The cub who appeared
the day of that silvery blizzard
was named "Ginko".
--[KUMACARON grunts] Yo, Ginko!
--[KUMAMI laughs]
[GINKO growls]
You're an unwanted bear, y'know!
A lonely Lone-Wolfsbane that'll
never be wanted by anybody!
Hey, what's this about?
What, you think you're the
Lone-Wolfsbane princess?
Lone Wolfsbane.
Lone Wolfsbane!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Kuma shock!
[GINKO]
Shut up!
[LIFE SEXY] And so,
Ginko was left all alone.
For obvious reasons,
she became known as
"Ginko the Lone Wolfsbane".
[GINKO] I understand now.
This world is ruled by power.
No one will ever be
kind to the weak ones.
It's a dog-eat-dog world,
and bear-eat-salmon!
[KUMAMI'S MOM]
Kumami! Dinnertime!
[KUMAMI]
Okay!
[GINKO]
Growl?
[KUMAKO'S MOM]
Kumako! Come back home!
[KUMAKO]
Uh... Okay.
[GINKO]
Growl?
[KUMARY'S MOM]
Kumary!
[KUMARY]
Okay!
[KUMARGARET'S MOM]
Kumargaret!
[KUMARGARET]
Okay!
[KUMACARON'S MOM]
Kumacaron!
[KUMACARON]
Okay!
[KUMACARON'S MOM laughs]
Kumacaron, today's your
favorite! Salmon pizza.
Hooray! I love salmon pizza!
[KUMACARON'S PARENTS laugh]
[KUMACARON'S DAD]
You are just so adorable!
[LIFE SEXY] Eventually,
the Day of Severance came.
[LIFE SEXY] Bear cubs in Ginko's
situation were gathered up
by the superior, Lady Kumaster.
[LADY KUMASTER]
Rejoice, my children,
for you have finally been found.
Yes, surely you were unwanted
bears, but now you shall be
given a chance at approval.
[CUBS sigh]
In this world, only One needs
you and gives you approval.
We thank her daily for
her love and graciousness.
Thank you, Lady Kumaria!
"Lady Kumaria"?
[LADY KUMASTER] From this day
forth, you are cubs of Kumaria.
You shall be guard-bears
and defend the great boundary
between bear and human!
[GINKO sighs]
[LADY KUMASTER] Exclude the
vermin known as "humans"
from our border
and eliminate them
in order to protect our world.
That is the mission you shall
carry out for us, for
we are the ones loved
by the Holy
Mother Kumaria.
[GIRL SOLDIERS yell]
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Growl!
[CUB SOLDIER A]
[GIRL SOLDIER A screams]
[CUB SOLDIER B]
Human excluded, growl-growl!
[CUB SOLDIER C]
Growl!
[GIRL SOLDIER B screams]
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Humans excluded, growl-growl!
[CUB SOLDIER D]
Growl!
[GIRL SOLDIER C screams]
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Humans excluded, growl-growl!
[OFFICER GIRL A]
HQ! HQ!
Request backup immediately!
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Growl!
[GIRL SOLDIER D]
Bears excluded!
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Growl!
[LIFE SEXY] Ginko believed
if she fulfilled her mission,
surely Kumaria
would approve of her,
and she would one
day be granted love.
[GINKO] I'm not an
unwanted Lone Wolfsbane!
I'll keep eating more
and more people,
and someday, I'll get approved!
Soon enough,
Lady Kumaria will do it.
[gunshot]
[GINKO] I'll finally
be granted my love.
[KUREHA] "There must be an
amazing world beyond that sky.
Day after day, the moon girl
and the forest girl looked
at the sky." I wonder if the
forest girl must be "her".
Oh, I just don't know.
--[LULU] Hello?
--[KUREHA] Uh?!
Kure-pie, you're here!
[KUREHA]
U-Uh. Yep.
Welcome home.
Thanks, Lulu.
[LULU]
Growl! What book is that?
It's a picture book
my mom wrote.
How cool! May Lulu read it?
Yes, of course, but I'll warn
you: it doesn't have an ending.
Why doesn't it have one?
[KUREHA]
Because my mom died
before she got the
chance to finish it.
[LULU]
Aw.
[KUREHA]
She was killed by a bear.
Go ahead. I can check on Ginko.
[LULU whimpers]
[GINKO labored breathing]
Tell me, Ginko.
Ginko loves you so much,
look at what she's done for you.
[KUREHA] Why?
We only just met each other.
And I haven't done anything for
you. Your injuries and your pain
should've been mine, but you
sacrificed yourself anyway.
[CUB SOLDIER M]
No way she's not done for.
[CUB SOLDIER N]
Either way, she'd slow us down.
Let's exclude her.
[CUB SOLDIERS]
Exclude her.
[LIFE SEXY] The animal world is
merciless. The weak, the scared,
the ones who can't keep
constant within the group.
They are summarily excluded.
[GINKO]
Oh, no. It looks like I failed.
Unwanted bear. You are
a Lone Wolfsbane! Goodbye!
[GINKO] Lone Wolfsbane. So I
don't get to be chosen, then.
I don't get to be
approved by anyone.
I don't get to be loved.
I'm going to die here,
without ever being found.
--[GINKO gasps]
--[music plays]
[KUREHA] This is the love
song my mom taught me.
It's okay. I'm your friend.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
[GINKO gasps]
I'm here now, and I love you.
[GINKO]
Lady Kumaria?
[GINKO gasping]
Kumaria. From the book.
You know it, don't you? But how?
--Kureha.
--[KUREHA gasps]
[KUREHA gasps]
[gasps] Well, this is great.
I'm glad you're awake.
Don't go. You were
singing something.
Um. I, uh...
I need to go tell
Lulu you woke up.
[LULU chuckles]
It's almost done! Growl, growl!
Ginger milk is on its
way to completion!
Lulu just needs to mix in
lots and lots and lots of honey.
Then, the yummy ginger
milk will be all done!
[REIA] There, all done.
You two enjoy it together, okay?
[KUREHA]
Yay!
[GINKO]
Growl!
[REIA]
Oh my!
You two really love honey
ginger milk, don't you?
[KUREHA]  Yeah! That's because
it's the flavor of our love!
Kureha? You spaced out.
I just remembered it.
The ginger milk...
[LULU]
Hm?
Yeah, my Mom made it.
And we drank it here.
She gave it to me and a friend
of mine a long time ago.
I'd forgotten how that felt.
A memory can change so much.
Like now. I feel happy again.
--[LULU] Lulu knows why.
--[KUREHA] Uh?
[LULU] It's because of
the honey ginger milk.
That's actually
Ginko's love flavor.
It's the flavor that tells
her she's not all alone
in the world. That she
matters to someone.
The taste of a twinkling star.
Her love flavor is
honey ginger milk?
Growl! Lulu hasn't added
the honey to finish this off,
yet, so she needs
to go get some.
Lulu will be right back!
[KUREHA]
I don't understand.
How could I forget a friend
I cared about so much?
I remember now,
that I loved her a lot, but why?
[LULU] Heh, heh! Honey ginger
milk will get Ginko and Kure-pie
totally close in no time at all!
[giggles] Lulu is so clever
Uh?
Oh yeah,
Kure-pie's mom's book.
"The Moon Girl and
the Forest Girl?"
Kureha! Are you
trying to tell me
the moon girl is
supposed to be Kureha?
Then, would that make
Ginko the forest girl?
Probably.
"Once upon a time,
the worlds were divided
into two parts by the sky.
There was the moon world...
[LULU, SUMIKA]
And the forest world.
'I am sorry, but you
may not,' said Kumaria,
for the two worlds have
been severed forever.
Wanting to cross that
severance is pride."
[music plays]
Hold on. This is my
mother's love song.
[SUMIKA] "There is one way
to make your wish come true.
If your love is true,
your friend will
be waiting for you.
You'll find her on the
other side of that door."
[KUREHA gasps]
[SUMIKA] "Kumaria asked
the two girls a question."
[SUMIKA]
"'Is your love the real thing?'"
[KUREHA]
I found you.
You're "her," aren't you?
You're my old friend.
[LULU]
Growl-giggle!
Okay, Lulu's Special Honey
Ginger Milk is complete!
--[LULU] Growl?
--[footsteps]
What's this?
Criminal bear?
[LULU] "Ginko Yurishiro,
I know all about the grave crime
you committed.
I know what you did.
You were the one who..."
[gasps]
[LULU]
Ginko. Oh, this can't be true!