[PINAKO]
You look down.
Drink up.
Pinako?
It's unhealthy
to drink alone.
It's nice to relax
like this for a change.
I guess you
don't think this is
the right time
for a party, do you?
Oh, I don't know...
Times like these...?
People have to enjoy
themselves when they can...
[PINAKO]
Especially in this country.
This conflict in Ishval...
It's just one after another...
we're always at war.
[LUST]
And no matter how
many times it happens,
they never learn...
The human race is made up
of violent, miserable fools.
[FIGHTING NOISES]
[GIRL CRYING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[HUGHES]
Ishval and Liore.
The east has been
a real hotbed, huh?
I'm afraid it's
not just the east...
There have been reports
of uprisings in the
north and west as well.
[ED]
Even now, we still
have skirmishes
at the borders of
Aerugo to the south
and Creta to the west...
North of us is the
huge country, Drachma...
The bodies are
piling up all over.
The government's
gonna have a hard time
keeping control
at this rate.
Sounds like you guys have
got your hands full alright.
Things began to
get more militaristic
when the current Fuhrer, King
Bradley, first came into power.
Hey! Dance with me!
Well... Aren't you the
ladies man, Hohenheim?
I don't dance...
I'll just sit here
and watch you.
But that's no fun!
Come dance with me!
[PINAKO]
Look at this codger...
He'll break his hip if he
tries dancing with you...
There... Why don't you
go dance with those kids?
That girl...
So bossy...
Weren't your two
boys around her age?
When they started planning
to bring back their mom?
[PINAKO]
You're their father.
Why didn't you say
anything to them?
Because it
would've been
pointless
to do so...
Nothing can
change the reality
of what they've done...
They'd still be damned.
That's a little harsh.
Their sin is
still a sin.
[ED]
NO!
He's gone! What have I done?!
Somebody help me... Somebody...
Please, Mom... Mom, please...
No... this...
this is wrong.
This isn't... this
isn't what we wanted!
Al... Alphonse...
Alphonse! Alphonse...!
This is all my fault...!
Alphonse, no!
No, dammit...!
You won't take him, too!
Give him back...
He's my brother...!
Take my leg! Take my arm!
Take my heart! Anything!
You can have it!
Just give him back...!
He's my little brother!
He's all I have left!
[ED]
The celestial stone
that destroyed
the city of Xerxes
in one night.
If we could just get our
hands on it somehow,
I might be able to
get your body back.
Doctor... what exactly
was it you were ordered
to do research on...?
What 'thing'?
The Philosopher's Stone.
You must not
seek after the stone.
[MARCOH]
This is the
devil's research.
If you chase the stone,
you will go through hell!
[ED]
This is the devil's research...
It should have been destroyed.
Dr. Marcoh was right...
It's evil.
The main ingredient for
a Philosopher's Stone...
Is the life of a human being!
[FATHER]
It's remarkable
how weak they are.
They've an innate
fear of the dark...
And how do they
handle this fear...?
They simply pretend
that it doesn't exist...
They run away from it...
How could anyone say
humans aren't weak?
It's an inherent trait.
So then...
How about we take advantage
of their weakness...?
They certainly do make a
good natural resource...
Right? It's all
they're good for...
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[MARCOH SPEAKING IN FLASHBACK]
Maybe you'll find the truth,
hidden within the truth...
What is all this...?
I bet this is what they use
to transmute a
Philosopher's Stone?
[48]
All right then...
let's see what you've got.
A prosthetic arm, huh?
No matter... My sword can
pierce steel as well as flesh.
[48 YOUNGER]
Brother!
[48]
As much as I hate
to admit it, we've lost.
So you're not
going to tell me
you're really three
brothers, are you?
- No, no.
[48]
Come on, boy, you've won...
Hurry up and destroy us.
No. I'm not a murderer.
[48]
With bodies like these
are we really even people?
I consider you people
whether you have
physical bodies or not...
If I didn't, that would
mean I didn't believe
my own brother
is a person either.
I know that my brother
is a human being...
That means you guys
are human, too...
I will not take the life
of another person.
[48 CHUCKLES]
[48]
Brother?
My brother and I
have been lying,
stealing, cheating,
and killing together
for as long as
we can remember.
And now that we're
in these pseudo-bodies,
we're being treated like
humans for the first time...
Don't you see the irony?
For that, boy, I'll give
you a parting gift...
I'll tell you everything...
I'll tell you who made
the Philosopher's Stone,
and ordered us to
guard this place.
[LUST] My, that
was a close call.
Number Forty-Eight,
you should know
better than to talk
about things that
don't concern you.
Quit your pathetic
blubbering, you idiot!
You could've messed
up the entire plan!
What would we
have done then?!
Huh?!
Tell me who you people are...
What plan are you
talking about...?
What do you mean by
'important sacrifice'?
He'll be happy since
you're a human sacrifice!
[AL]
Oh, sure, right...
That's why he'll
wanna meet me.
And I guess I'll find out...
What that means.
[BRADLEY]
Their teacher seems
to be a worthy candidate
for human sacrifice, too.
[LUST]
I really hate to do this...
you were a prime candidate
for sacrifice and all.
But you forced me to kill you.
[MARCOH]
You know what...?
I've been
sitting here awhile...
trying to decide what
you mean by 'sacrifice'...
trying to figure out
why I'm here...
and what it is exactly
you want me to do.
[HUGHES]
Liore... these
endless uprisings...
the Philosopher's Stone...
Human sacrifices...
And the outright genocide
of the Ishvalan people...
And this means...
How could this even happen...?
And who could orchestrate
something as
terrible as this...?
[MARCOH]
I'm fairly certain that
what you're doing right now
is using this
land and its people
to form a giant
transmutation circle.
And your hope is
that the end result
will be the creation
of a Philosopher's Stone.
Am I wrong?
[PINAKO]
You've always known
about their plans...
Haven't you?
Well, Hohenheim...
Why have you
kept quiet about it?
Tell me, dammit!
[HOHENHEIM]
Even if I'd spoken up...
warned them...
It wouldn't've
changed anything.
I've watched humanity
for a long time now...
And all I've seen them do
is endlessly repeat
the same mistakes.
[HOHENHEIM]
It's like they
choose to be helpless.
They either run away
or they roll over.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
They're so fragile...
How can they not break?
I told you,
the Philosopher's
Stone's my core.
[GREED]
I'm a Homunculus.
You know what
that means, right?
I'm an artificially
created human.
Really... no joke.
I'm gonna show you two boys
somethin' neat before we die...
Consider it a parting gift.
Then it's time to eat you!
Mustang!
[LING]
The Homunculus...
He had another monster
hidden inside his belly.
He's swallowing up
everything in sight!
[ED THINKING]
Alchemy can produce
something like that?
How disgusting.
Just what do
you want, old man?
[BRADLEY]
I may not have
the protection
of your Ultimate Shield...
but I clearly see your weakness
with my Ultimate Eye.
[ROY THINKING]
Ah, I understand now, Hughes...
When you said that
we were in trouble,
you didn't mean that danger
was closing in on us...
No...
you meant that the danger
was coming from us.
[AL]
What did you say...?
You have a father?
Uh huh.
Is he the one that
made the Homunculi?
Father made us.
[HOHENHEIM]
Humans are defenseless.
They don't have
an Ultimate Spear.
Nor an Ultimate Shield.
It's no use...
They're all so busy
with their trivial lives...
They don't even
see the real danger.
So what could they do...?
They can't defend themselves...
Not against the likes
of the Homunculi.
But that won't
make us give up.
We will never give up!
[HOHENHEIM]
That is true...
It is a human characteristic.
[LUST]
You should have
bled to death by now!
[ROY]
I seared the
wound closed...
I came close to passing
out from the pain.
[GREED]
I appreciate the effort,
but you just can't win!
So, are you ready to
tell me your secret now?
Huh?
Thanks for toying with me.
What?
You gave me
just enough time
to cool off and
start thinking clearly.
How long you wanna
drag this out, kid...?
It'd be so much easier
if you just stay down!
[AL]
True, there are plenty
of things about this body
that are inconvenient,
but it's nothing
I can't live with...
I don't need pity
from anyone...
least of all from you.
My brother used alchemy
to save my life...
To regret the form I have now
would mean not only
rejecting alchemy
but also turning
my back on him.
I believe in my brother,
and I believe in alchemy.
I will not lose faith...
I want to believe!
[SCAR'S BROTHER]
He's a State Alchemist!
Get back!
[SCAR'S BROTHER YELLING]
Stay with me...!
Don't you die!
[SCAR PANTING]
[SCAR'S BROTHER]
Damn, I can't
stop the bleeding!
Someone!
Don't die... I won't let you.
[LING]
Lan Fan! Run!
[LAN FAN YELLS]
No, Lan Fan!
What happened to me?
[LING]
What's wrong?
My arm...
My lord...
[LAN FAN]
I'm useless
to you now.
Lan Fan!
What are you planning?
No! Don't do it!
That was
well played girl.
[PINAKO]
They can put us through hell.
But it doesn't matter...!
Nothing they can do
will make us give up.
And someday we will win.
[HOHENHEIM]
You're just wearing
yourselves out.
[PINAKO]
Well the only way
we're gonna find out
is if we try!
It's better
than just lying down
and accepting it!
You really don't care?
You're fine with
losing Ed and Al
and everyone else you know?
[FATHER]
You're really getting worked up
over this, aren't you?
[PINAKO GASPS]
[FATHER]
Don't kid your
self into thinking
you can help any of them.
You know that they're
going to wind up dead
no matter what you do.
And then what happens?
You're left with
nothing, that's what.
The smart thing to do?
The only thing?
Take whatever is
important to you
and run away as far
as you possibly can.
What?
You act like you
have a conscience,
but you're just
being sentimental.
Isn't that right, Hohenheim?
You think you
can change things?
You honestly
believe one act of caring
will make you human?
[FATHER CHUCKLES MANIACALLY]
[FATHER]
How could it?
Look at your own face.
Humans are nothing
but a resource...
And if we don't use them,
they'll spread like weeds.
You can't change reality,
only your perception...
Tell me what you think
you could actually change?
The nature of their species?
They will always be weak
and frightened creatures.
[TRISHA]
We will change.
Because we can change.
I know it.
We may be weak...
But we just have
to be... If not...
Then we wouldn't have
any reason to grow...
to get strong...
I know that it may
seem futile to you.
But it's not...
Because we are
getting stronger
with every
step we take.
[ROY]
And in turn they'll
protect the ones they love.
It seems like the least
we tiny humans can
do for each other.
[LING]
But I... I wasn't
ready for this...
Lan Fan was though...
She made the decision
that I was too weak to make.
[AL]
I'm sick of
watching people die...!
And I can't just sit back
and take it anymore!
I won't let anyone
else get killed!
Not when I
can protect them!
I won't run away this.
We'll knock that
Truth jerk on his butt!
Al!
Al! Come on! Please...!
Hurry, Al!
Alphonse!
Look at me!
I'll come back!
Just you wait!
You see? I'm sure
we can change...
Because we're weak...
And because we die.
[TRISHA]
We have to fight
in order to live...
And that's what
will make us strong.
And if that's not enough...
If you're still not convinced
that we can change...
Then think about us.
All of the days we spent...
With our family in Resembool.
I was dreaming...
Thanks for all the help.
[NARRATOR]
If you find
yourself overwhelmed
with a debilitating fear
by the unfathomable power
looming before you,
then you should
run like a coward.
And if you lose
what you believe
to be your only power,
then you might
as well succumb
to your own weakness.
This is the battle
that you feared was coming.
Put everything you've
got into it, human.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Twenty Eight... Father.