Now you get to see
the "Briggs way," kid.
Uh, "the Briggs way"?
That's right.
Come, alchemist...
gimme a hand.
[Ed yelps]
[Al] Brother!
You, too, tin man!
Hey, hold on! We can't just--
You were forced to
help us under duress...
How does that
excuse work for you?
Hmm? Who's this?
He's an old friend of ours.
Ah... Then he'll help too.
Huh?!
[Buccaneer]
Hurry! Don't spill any!
[Miles] Buccaneer...
Head for Gate 8!
Sir!
[Olivier] Let's move!
Drive it into the elevator!
[Sloth groans]
[Sloth struggles]
What... a pain...
Move it! Push us!
Good! It's working!
Rotate... turret right!
Yes... sir!
Do it, Miles! Close it!
Sir!
Uh...
Yes! It's gone!
Uh, where... am I?
[Buccaneer growls]
Ehh?
Rryaaahhh!
All right! Do it now!
Huh?
Nice!
[Al] Okay... What next?
[Ed] Yeah, how were
you planning to get
this big guy through
the gate, exactly?
[Sloth]
Stink.
[Ed and Al gasp]
Move it, you little runt!
Uh...?
Uhh...
Hey! One more!
We're out of ammo!
Well, in that case...
Hey... ow.
[Ed and Al yell]
Nice!
[Buccaneer] That fuel is
specially blended for the cold.
It'll vaporize
almost instantly...
and as it evaporates,
it will sap his body heat.
This blizzard will help, too...
It'll freeze him,
right down to his brain.
[Sloth]
It's so... cold...
Body... won't... move...
What... a pain.
You can sleep there
until spring, monster...
Alright, Buccaneer.
Now take these two away.
Sir!
Huh?!
[Ed] Hey hey, hold on a second!
We helped you! Why are
you doing this? How can--
[Olivier] You were forced to.
That was just the excuse
you needed to fight, right?
Besides which, I'm not
letting you go anywhere
until you explain
exactly what that thing was
and what it wanted.
[Ed yawns, shivers]
It's so cold.
[Ed] Restraints?
[Al] Good morning...
Nice chains.
Yeah... they're just lovely.
[Neil] Hey...
you two sleep well?
[Ed] I guess, considering...
[Neil laughs]
[Ed] Hm?
I heard you helped defend
the fort from that monster.
[Ed] Thank you.
That's a hundred cens.
You're charging me for this?!
[Al] So... find
anything else out?
We sent a party down
to investigate the hole.
They should be
back anytime now.
Also, Major Miles
is at the hospital.
Is he hurt?
Hardly. He's there
visiting a soldier
who was wounded fighting Scar.
Scar's in the north now?
[Soldier 4]
Oh, here they are.
[Ed] Hm?
[Soldier 5]
They're awake.
[Soldier 6]
Thanks for yesterday.
[Soldier 7] Yeah... You
saved our buddies' lives.
I'm impressed. You
guys stick together.
You really seem to care.
Well, here at Briggs, we have
to look out for each other.
You saved our pals back there,
so that makes you
our pal as well.
Well, you want to let your
pal out of here, then?
No, we're not allowed
to do that, sorry.
It was worth a try, I guess.
[Miles] Apparently they
didn't find any sign
of Scar's body at the site.
He could always be holed up
somewhere nearby, though.
That's true.
[Miles] Interesting...
First a search for a
strange black-and-white cat,
then a search for Scar.
[Miles] All right.
You can leave Scar to us
and focus on getting better.
Hold on a sec.
I want you and your
people to stay out of this.
The Ishvalan is
mine to hunt down.
[Miles]
I hate to tell you this,
but the soldiers
of Briggs won't let
a serial killer
roam around free.
Here in the north, the law
is survival of the fittest.
[Kimblee gasps]
You get careless, and you
get dead. Understand?
You tell me what to do again,
and you'll never
leave this hospital.
This case is ours now.
The Briggs branch will
take care of everything.
You behave yourself.
[Kimblee laughs]
Another Ishvalan.
That's interesting.
Hm?
Hello, Kimblee. And
how are you recovering?
Well, hello, General Raven.
You got here quickly.
I heard the news and
came as fast as I could.
I was worried about you.
These are what you're
really worried about.
Isn't that right?
Very good... Now,
we have work to do.
I'm not exactly in great
shape at the moment.
No problem. I brought a
doctor who knows alchemy.
And we have the
stones, as well.
You'll be fine in no time.
[Doctor laughs]
[Marcoh groans]
Alkahestry seems to
be pretty complicated.
This "dragon pulse" business
is especially confusing.
It's about the chi of the land.
What do you mean by the "chi"?
I'll try to explain.
Basically, it's an
energy that exists
in all things in this world,
like rivers of power
flowing through it.
Those rivers are far-reaching.
They touch everybody
and everything.
All you have to
do is understand
how that power flows,
from where it enters,
and where it leaves...
And then you can use it to
affect just about anything.
Just about anything.
So... the body, too?
Yes!
It could be... your back!
[Marcoh]
Oww... my leg!
Or else... your neck!
[Marco screams]
Why did my eyeballs hurt
when you pressed my neck?
[May] Dr. Marcoh,
you should take
better care of yourself...
All the power in your body
is starting to stagnate.
Uh... So, that's it, is it?
The theory behind your
"remote transmutation"...
[May] Then, alchemists don't
use the dragon's pulse?
They do not. They use energy
from the movement
of the earth's crust.
A great deal of energy
is created, then released
during earthquakes
and volcanic eruptions.
That's what fuels our
alchemy in this country.
I don't know...
That doesn't seem right.
Hm?
I've felt that
something was out of place
ever since I got here...
I noticed it especially
when we were under
Central. I can tell
that there's energy
flowing under my feet...
But it doesn't feel like
it comes from the
land's movement...
It feels like...
a crowd of people...
squirming around.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Soldier] It's huge.
A platoon could fit
through the hole...
It curves gently
and then continues
on for a long way.
But there were no
signs of anyone in it.
Lower some horses...
[Buccaneer] Yes sir!
...and I want to see
the Elric brothers.
[Ed] Awesome... this
is a serious tunnel.
I still can't believe
that an intruder was
able to get this far
through our defenses.
So has anyone else ever
made it into the fort before?
No, not in all the time
I've had command here.
But once, nearly
twenty years ago,
there was a strange incident
where the Mountain Guard
was attacked in
the middle of winter.
Apparently, a mysterious woman
stole food and supplies
for a full month.
[Izumi] I survived
for a whole month
in the Briggs Mountains!
[Ed and Al ]
It was Teacher!
This should be far enough.
You. Dismount.
[Ed] Hm?
[Olivier] Now then...
We're safely away
from any prying eyes.
You can tell me everything
without fearing discovery.
And I mean everything.
Don't hold anything back.
Yesterday I asked you
about that monster.
Remember what you said?
"I can't answer."
You refused me...
And that, even as a hint,
is a dangerous thing to do.
I told you to answer my
questions fully and completely.
At great peril to yourself,
you neglected to do so.
I think there's something
you're trying to hide.
And you'd risk your
lives to protect it.
Something, or maybe someone.
This time, don't lie to me.
I want the truth.
We need your help, General.
[Olivier]
The Philosopher's Stone.
Homunculi.
Fuhrer King Bradley.
A mysterious man called Father.
Corruption in the senior staff.
There are hostages
involved, as well.
Your childhood friend
the automail engineer
and all Mustang's men...
We've done some joint training
with Eastern Command
over the years, so I know
officers Hawkeye and Havoc,
and I'd hate it if we
lost either of them.
I would like to help them.
And, um... what about
Colonel Mustang?
Yeah... I couldn't
care less about him.
I'd just as soon see
him fall from power.
That would
eliminate another rival.
Never mind him.
The question is,
what do we do next?
This tunnel here.
I would like to know
what you alchemists make of it.
[Ed] First of all, the
tunnel probably didn't
originate in Drachma...
This is just my guess...
but I'd say chances
are we'll find it's dug
in the shape of
an enormous circle.
Why?
It has to do with alchemy.
In our field, a circle
is the symbol used
to control power.
We need to look at
this more closely.
[Ed] Lieutenant Falman.
Can you list the major
events in Amestris
that were accompanied
by bloodshed?
By bloodshed?
[Falman] What are
you getting at?
[Falman gasps]
First, there's
July, 1588. In Riviere.
Okay, Riviere. Next.
[Falman] October, 1661.
The Cameron Uprising.
February, 1799.
The Soapman Incident.
There, in Fisk.
March, 1811.
The Wellesley Incident.
October, 1835. The first
Southern Border War,
in what is now
known as South City.
Then, in 1911, there was
the Second Southern
Border War in Fotosett.
[Ed] What about
Pendleton, in the west?
[Falman] There's been
fighting with Creta.
A lot of soldiers
have died. And then...
Later, in 1914, there was
the Liore Insurrection.
There were many casualties.
What?
[Al] An insurrection? But why?
I don't understand. I exposed
the fake priest in Liore.
And I reported it to Eastern
Command immediately.
Yes, you did... but the
Central forces came in
and ran out the
troops from the east.
After that happened,
Liore just fell to pieces.
Oh, no... damn!
[Olivier] No time for that.
Back to work, Fullmetal.
All right. Fine.
And now... we just
connect the dots.
[Olivier gasps]
How is that possible?
It... It looks like
the transmutation circle
from the Fifth Laboratory!
Is that so? The
Philosopher's Stone array
that draws power
from human lives.
[Buccaneer] If they make
a Philosopher's Stone
with something this huge,
how many people
will have to die?
[Marcoh] Once I asked
Envy if the Homunculi
were planning to
use this country
to create a
Philosopher's Stone.
But he just laughed
at my question.
Then he said no, that
was not it... but close.
Earlier, I had spoken
to Edward Elric.
I told him that maybe
he would be able
to find the truth
hidden within the truth.
Three truths: first,
that the ingredients
for a Philosopher's
Stone are live humans.
Second, that there
is a group of beings
seeking to create
an enormous stone.
And third, that they plan
to use the entire country
as a transmutation
circle to make it.
But even all that doesn't
explain everything.
Ultimately, what
is their motive?
What is it they're
really trying to do?
I know you're seeking
the secrets of immortality.
But you can't let your search
lead you to the
Philosopher's Stone...
By combining the
information I have
with your knowledge
of alkahestry, we'll
figure out these notes
somehow, I'm sure of it.
[May] Right!
Hmm...
The first of the conflicts
happened in 1558.
Right. It was just after
the founding of Amestris.
They attacked Riviere...
That was the neighboring
country at the time.
And then the military--
Hey... Wait...
That's it!
It was the military!
They were involved
in all of it!
[several gasps]
[Falman] Each incident was a
coup d'etat or insurrection.
Like in Liore. Forces from
Central would be sent in,
and they would make
everything worse.
It's been going on that long?
We kept growing...
Our country started out
as a small nation,
but we expanded
as we took over more and
more neighboring countries.
That was all to
create this circle?
So that means... not only
are they planning to use
this country to do whatever
it is they're doing...
but they actually created
it in the first place
for that single purpose.
My country...
[Al] Do you think...
General Hughes...?
Yeah... before
he was killed...
he must've seen the
transmutation circle.
He was serving in the
court-martial office.
He had all the information
about the military incidents.
He would've known that
something wasn't right.
That must be why--
[Isaac] You've sworn
your life to the state
as a Dog of the Military...
But do you really know
the ones you serve?
Or what their true plans are?
You get a speck of power...
and you have the arrogance
to assume you're the one
who's in control of it.
Don't be a fool!
He'll lead us all to ruin!
I'm only doing what
needs to be done!
[Ed gasps]
I do not like this!
As far as I can tell,
there's only one place left.
If you're right about
your theory, the next place
they're going to hit is
right here in Briggs...
Those bastards in Central...
What kind of dirty plans
do they have for my fort?!
[Soldier 9]
General! You're needed
back at the fort.
Lieutenant General Raven
from Central is
here to see you.
It looks like our
time's already up.
Excuse me, General Armstrong.
I'd like to ask
a favor of you.
[Olivier gasps]
Do you think you could con
some information
out of General Raven?
[Miles]
General Raven, sir.
I'm terribly sorry to
have to ask you to wait.
No, please don't
worry about it.
It's my fault for
dropping in like this.
General Armstrong should
return at any moment now.
This way... please.
[Raven] Oh, and...
As you can see,
I've brought a guest with me...
If it's not too much trouble...
then perhaps you
would be so kind
as to show him
around the fort.
I'd appreciate it
Thanks, Major Miles.
[Al] Winry's apple pie.
That was the first
thing I wanted to do
when I got my body
back... But now...
even that much may be
out of reach forever.
You'll have all the apple
pie you could ever want.
We're going to get
our bodies back!
And the monsters who
have been messing with
our country for all this
time are going to pay!
Just you wait!
[Olivier] I apologize
for the chaos, sir.
We were attacked yesterday.
[Raven] By whom?
[Olivier] I think it's
most appropriate
to call it a monster...
but fortunately,
we were able to fend it off.
A monster? What do you mean?
We killed it,
but it didn't die, sir.
[Raven laughs]
Is that so?
[Olivier] I suspected that
it originated in Drachma...
but the Elric brothers...
Didn't I mention?
The Fullmetal Alchemist
and his brother are here.
I found it disturbing...
They seemed to know
about this monster...
but they wouldn't talk.
Obviously, if we
have a State Alchemist
doubling as a spy for Drachma,
that's a serious problem.
I've locked them up.
Perhaps you'd like
to speak with them?
[Raven]
Hmm... Certainly...
They won't tell you anything?
[Olivier] Correct.
They said they came here
to research living
transmutation or something.
What could be more suspicious?
I distrusted them instantly.
I had thought about torturing
them to get the information...
But I am a woman, after all...
The thought of
hurting those boys...
Let's just say I
couldn't stand it.
Now, that's rich...
She would've tortured you
in a second and not
thought twice about it.
[Raven laughs]
But General Armstrong,
aren't you known
as the "Northern
Wall of Briggs"?
Walls aren't so soft as that.
[Olivier chuckles]
You know General Raven,
at my age, most women
are expected to have had
a child or two at least.
Unfortunately, I'm
well past that now.
[Raven] Come now,
surely men are lining up
to have children with you.
[Olivier] Hardly, sir.
I hate to say... but
like everybody else,
I'm growing older...
And my body is too.
[Ed and Al exhale]
[Olivier] That Drachman
monster, though...
it had an outstanding body.
An immortal body. Like
something from a dream.
[Raven] What if I told
you that very soon,
it wouldn't be a dream anymore?
[Ed and Al gasp]
[Raven] Tell me, General...
Would you be interested in a
legion of immortal soldiers?
[Ed and Al]
He took the bait!
[Narrator] In the north,
only the strong survive...
Either you have
power or you do not...
If you have it, you may live.
If not, your chances dwindle.
Because there will always
come a time when power
must be fought with
an even greater power.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 36... Family Portrait.
A man sets forth, with
resolution in his heart.