Are your feelings of guilt gone?
Go!
Don't you think Kushieda-senpai is acting weird?
You're right.
I mean, she's a weird person by nature,
but she's been spacing out a lot more than usual recently.
What the heck am I doing?
My silky love
nijuuyon jikan zutto
24時間ずっと
Every hour of the day
My silky love
kimi no koto omou tabi
キミのこと想うたび
whenever I think of you
My silky love
modokashii kono kimochi
もどかしいこの気持ち
these impatient feelings
My silky love
tada afurekaetteku
ただ溢れかえってく
simply overflow.
suki to ieba kantan na no ni
スキと言えば簡単なのに
Even though it's easy to say "I love you"
kimi ga mae ni kichau to
キミが前に来ちゃうと
when you stand in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
個性がそびえ　私のコトを邪魔してる
my personality stands up and gets in my way.
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
いつもならば強気でイケる
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku na no ni
そんな性格なのに
that's just how I am.
donna ganbatte mite mo kabe wa kuzusenai
どんな頑張ってみても　壁は崩せない
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us.
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
察して欲しい…　この気持ちを
I want you to realise… my feelings.
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
だから私は　いつもキミに
So I always send a gaze
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
大好きだよと送る視線
of "I really love you" your way
saidai no yuuki de
最大の勇気で!
with all of my courage!
yaburesou na shiruku no haato
破れそうなシルクノハート
My flimsy silky heart.
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
キミに逢って気づいた　やっと
After meeting you, I finally realised
ai ni wa bukiyou dattan datte
愛には不器用だったんだって
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love.
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
忘れかけた恋の傷跡
The scars from love that I'd almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashita no kyun to
急に疼きだしたの　キュンと
have started to ache all of a sudden.
itsuka wa watashi rashiku suki to
いつかは私らしくスキと
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
言わなきゃ…今より弱くなっちゃうよ
I must say "I love you", or else I'll become even weaker.
Mercury Retrogrades
at Christmas
Oh yeah, the big year-end sale is coming up soon,
and then spring cleaning is after that.
From the deepest parts of the cupboards to the tatami mats,
I'll clean every inch.
No! No!
You're thinking about it wrong; it's Christmas. Christmas!
Huh?
Oh, I'm so looking forward to it.
I guess I have to be good for the time being,
because he's probably near the skies of Japan right now.
Who?
Do you really need to ask?
Santa! Santa Claus!
Give me that, I'll help you carry it.
Are you okay?
It'll be great if he visits our house again this year.
What's wrong?
You know,
I love Christmas!
I know you love Christmas, but why so much?
Do you need a reason to love Christmas?
The street decorations are sparkling beautifully...
...and everyone is smiling and happy...
Hey, you'll spoil your dinner!
I know, that's why I'm only eating one.
No, you don't understand.
We're going to celebrate the end of your suspension tonight.
Also, yellowtails are a natural product, so they're really expensive.
You should at least pretend to appreciate them because of the price.
Yay, yay!
Yellowtail hotpot!
One more time.
There are a lot of yellowtails, yay.
One more time!
So...
Did you get closer to Minorin during my suspension?
No progress at all, right?
Sheesh, what did you do with the chance I gave you?
B-But it couldn't be helped...
If you're not here,
Kushieda won't come to the meeting place in the morning,
and she'll eat lunch with some other girls.
Then after school, she's busy with club-
"With all that waiting, do you think you're the faithful dog, Hachiko?"
"Do you really think Minorin will come for you if you wait long enough?"
"Fool. Stupid. Dumb dog. Idiot Ryuuji."
Although I was planning to say that...
You've already said it all out loud.
Well, I guess not progressing at all is something that can't be helped.
Fine, I'll come up with a plan for you.
Huh?
It's Christmas, so I'll be reborn as an angel of love to help you.
T-That's so wrong.
Say whatever you want, I'm a living saint right now.
Saint? I thought you were an angel.
My bad, I meant angel.
In order to give everyone a happy and joyful Christmas,
I'm prepared to take off one or two
pieces of clothing, or even take it all off.
So just leave it to me!
So, do I look like an angel?
No,
and the crumbs are falling onto your head.
No way! Get them off!
Taiga-san is here!
Taiga-san is back at school!
Taiga-san, we appreciate your effort!
What's with you guys?
We became your fans after we saw that fight.
The battle between the boss and the Palmtop Tiger...
It was actually your victory, right?!
You fought the first and final battle against her for your love...
...because you found out she's going to study abroad, right?
Quiet down!
That fight was very difficult and caused a lot of hardship.
However, the last person standing was the victor.
In other words,
I was the true victor!
Come on, don't mess around.
Let's go, Taiga.
My tense thigh, and...
...my shaking calf...
W-What's going on?
Minorin, I'm back at school!
Stop singing weird songs and give me a hug!
Let go of me! I'm a human!
Minorin, I missed you a lot!
Why didn't you wait for us at the meeting place?
To be honest, I overslept so I had to rush here today.
That's why my thighs are so sore.
Wait, how did I get here before you guys?
W-Well...
We were surrounded by some weird guys.
Anyway, Kushieda-
Shut up, brat!
Why did I say that?
Or did I make a bad joke?
Crap! I screwed up!
Sorry! Forget it!
Mornin', Takasu.
Oh, Taiga, long time no see.
Hey, are you doing all right?
Huh?
Kushieda broke down again?
I screwed up so badly.
I should seriously become a monk.
Just let me be bald for now.
No...
Why is a high school girl like you wearing a bald wig?
Aisaka!
W-What's going on now?
Good morning, Aisaka.
K-Kitamura-kun, good morning...
Takasu, good morning to you too.
W-Why?
It's morning, that's why I'm saying "good morning".
No! I mean your pose!
Oh, I am...
...full of admiration!
Full of...
I am full of admiration!
My feelings for Aisaka can't be shown by just kneeling,
which is why I'm lying down.
Aisaka!
Yes?
Regardless of who it's for, you shouldn't fight anymore.
If you can't forgive someone, you have to talk to me about it first.
So yeah, I saw it with my own eyes.
Yes.
I mean, he's an assistant professor,
but I saw him coming out of a casino!
Oh, that confirms it.
He wasn't late for the date because of his work,
but because he was playing slot machines!
Broadcasting Room
Yeah, so I messaged one of my girlfriends...
Because I was being treated badly by him, I asked her what I should do.
Oh...
Then I found out something else.
Such a breathtaking development...
It seems there's no such occupation as an "assistant professor".
There is only "assistant teacher".
That means...
...he was lying about his job!
Ever since then, I haven't heard a thing from him.
What did you do to make our teacher cry, Kitamura?
Let's just pretend we don't know it's actually Yuri-chan.
"Cheering For Your Love" was brought to you by Kitamura Yuusaku,
Yeah...
the God of Broken Hearts.
Our guest today goes by the pseudonym of Y-chan.
God of Broken Hearts? What's that?
Oh, because of that confession,
Kitamura has become the school's love saint-
I mean, he became a religious figure for those wanting to confess to someone.
Huh?
They say Kitamura will take all the bad luck away.
It's something like "The Lucky God of Broken Hearts Legend".
Let me remind you, final exams are coming up.
That's so stupid.
Why do the people of our school love to believe legends so much?
Everyone, are you prepared?
I, the God of Broken Hearts, should also start studying,
Don't you think this broadcast is really annoying?
Why did he bring up the topic of studying?
but not everything goes my way.
Shouldn't the title be "Cheering For Your Love"?
Taiga is listening to it, so shut up,
or else she won't be able to hear the touching stories of Master Kitamura.
Taiga, are you all right? Can hear it clearly?
Huh?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Speaking of which, Taiga is being really modest today.
I mean, she would've killed Haruta had he done that any other day.
You noticed?
Yeah, I'm being good.
Good?
Well, I'm being good because it's nearly Christmas.
I mean, look, Santa is watching us.
Oh, what was that?
Are you stupid?
I can't believe you think Santa really exists.
That's not like you at all.
Stupid Chi', it's nearly Christmas!
If you're naughty, Santa won't visit your house.
There's definitely something strange about you.
Did something happen during your suspension?
Or is this a sign of death?
Are you going to die tomorrow?
Why am I going to die tomorrow?!
Both of you, cut it out!
Thank you for listening!
Next...
After the dreaded exams, it'll be Christmas,
the time that everyone's looking forward to!
Now an announcement from the student council.
After the ceremony on Christmas Eve,
there will be a Christmas party in the gym.
You have to come as couples.
Troubled by love?
Can't ask him or her out?
Why don't you try to invite the person you have feelings for to the party on that romantic night?
Christmas...
...Party?
Listen, Ryuuji.
This is the perfect chance.
You have to invite Minorin to the Christmas Eve party.
Huh?
Don't "Huh?" me!
You have to confess to her in a snap!
C-Confess?
Y-You're asking for the impossible.
You have to do it.
It's Christmas Eve.
It's the holy Christmas Eve.
I am the angel of love!
I'm the holy child of Christmas and the model for being good!
Even Santa is looking at me!
Huh?
In order to make your love life successful,
I will become Cupid!
No, thanks.
Well, well...
H-Hey!
So...
Do I look like Cupid?
No, you don't.
You really don't.
A
Cool
guys
only
My god, aren't you slow?
The special party for cool guys is in here...
Merry Christmas!
Oh, god! Look, Nanako!
That guy over there is really cute!
I'm totally fine with that type of guy!
Oh my, what a gentleman.
There's a lot of time left, so if you're hungry, eat this first!
Huh? Where are you going?
What did you say?
Am I really that boring?
It's Christmas, and I'm waiting for you to do fun things to me...
Exactly, let's do fun things together!
Let's get naked!
We're naked!
What?
Someone cuter?
So you want a cuter and prettier Santa?
Are you talking about me?!
That was the dream I had.
What a pervert.
You're the worst.
Gosh, Haruta-kun...
Wait, why am I the most unfortunate?
Putting that aside,
let's talk about the real party.
First, we have to decide who will be staff.
Taiga, go for it.
Didn't you say that you love Christmas?
Yeah, good idea.
I-If everyone's asking me to go for it, I guess I'll have to.
Come join me, you sugary-slug-dog!
S-Sure.
Wait, what type of dog did you say I am?
Minorin, come join us!
Sorry.
I'll pass this time.
Why?
I'm really not in the mood to go to a Christmas party.
I mean, it's not the time for me to have fun.
What's wrong, Kushieda?
I screwed up unbelievably during the softball match,
and we lost because of that.
It's really embarrassing.
If I go and have fun at a party during a time like this,
I don't think the club members will look up to me anymore.
Also, I have to practise for a match I have after New Year's.
Minorin...
Y-You don't need to help out, just come for the party and-
I won't be going to the party.
Then, I'll help you guys set stuff up.
Ami-chan, you're going to?
Then, I'll help too!
I'm really looking forward to the party!
We'll heat it up using the power of Class 2-C!
Oh, my...
What's with that look?
You don't want to be with me?
Let me make this clear, Takasu-kun.
It's in your best interest to be nice to me.
Why?
This sort of plan is my specialty.
I'll determine whether the party will be a success or not,
and it's also up to me to get that unhappy somebody to come.
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, so you want to join us?
If that's the case, we'd be glad to have you.
I said I'm not going to.
Minorin!
Wait, Minorin!
Huh? Ryuu-chan, you're going out?
Taiga-chan is going too?
Yeah, to study for our finals.
We're meeting Kitamura and the others at the restaurant we always go to.
There's a salmon fillet in the frying pan,
remember to heat it up before you eat it.
Eh? Ya-chan will be giza lonely gansu!
W-What's with that "giza" and "gansu"?
Ryuu-chan, don't you know?
It's a popular saying right now.
Some new person at work told me about it.
Young people say things like "gansu",
and "giza" sounds cute, right?
Ya-chan is giza-ly smart!
Cut it out.
It sounds really wrong.
How does it sound wrong?
This is giza-ly good! It's tera-ly correct!
Inko-chan, take care of Yasuko for me.
You're the only one I can rely on.
Too bad!
No! No! No! No!
Such a rebellious reaction!
What's going on, Inko-chan?
What happened to your cute and honest side?
Oh, I know.
It must be the book you borrowed.
How to Cook A Special
Poultry Christmas Meal
I'm sorry, Inko-chan!
I did something really stupid!
I'll never cook you!
I promise!
R-Really?
Of course!
S-Seriously?
I'm serious!
What are you guys doing?
Hey, did you bring it?
Of course.
It's safe in here.
The prize I got at the cultural festival for winning the Mr. Lucky Guy contest...
They call it "The Boss's Notes".
There will be nothing to be afraid of if we use this to study.
But to be honest, this belongs to Kushieda.
She let me win with her.
She said she can't come because of her job, so it can't be helped.
Quit living in the past like an old person.
I'm not living in the-
Then, stop standing there.
We're going to study at the place where Minorin works,
so you should try and have a chat with her before everyone arrives.
Y-Yeah!
Kushieda took the day off.
When you're ready to order, press the button.
Hey, Ryuuji.
Do you think Minorin is avoiding you?
W-Why would she?!
You guys don't speak to each other at school,
and I was the one who invited her to the study session.
That's because you told me to leave everything to you.
Do you guys even talk to each other at all?
N-No...
"Going to work" was an excuse,
and she said she's not going to the party.
She's feeling down because she screwed up during a match.
Isn't it your specialty to make everything better in times like these?!
But...
It's really weird.
I don't even know how to support her now.
Your relationship with Minorin seems different from before.
Before, you guys were more...
Yo, Takasu and Taiga,
sorry to make you wait.
I'm really hungry.
O-Oh...
Yo.
It's really cold today.
Wearing a winter coat on cold days makes you really warm!
Maruo, you should buy one for yourself.
Kihara?
What are you doing here?
This isn't like you at all.
I also want a copy of The Boss's Notes!
And I can't study by myself...
Come on, let's sit down.
All right, this table is ours.
Hey Taiga, stand up.
Haruta, go over there.
Okay.
Kihara, you're sitting next to Takasu.
Wait...
Here you go.
I'll sit next to Haruta, and Kitamura, you're sitting at the other table.
W-Wait! I want to sit there too!
No, um, well...
Girls should sit together!
Right, Taiga? Let's do that.
Don't be so selfish.
Do you not want to sit next to Takasu?
No, it's not that!
Let's order now.
Everyone's going to the drink bar, right?
All right.
No point in everyone getting up for drinks,
so I'll get them for all of you.
I-I want something hot!
Okay.
Taiga, go to the drink bar with him.
Isn't it cold today?
Hey, what are you plotting?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Why are you pairing Taiga and Kitamura up on purpose?
Oh, we've been found out.
Whatever, I want you to help out too.
Huh?
I think Kitamura and Taiga would make a good couple.
Oh, I think so too.
Look, Kitamura is probably still upset about the Boss rejecting him, right?
Don't you think a new love would help cure him?
T-That might work.
Taiga likes Kitamura.
I'm serious.
I don't think you've noticed it.
You're surprised, right?
I was surprised too.
After all, you're the closest one to her since you take care of her and stuff.
Yeah, so being surprised is only natural.
You guys are wrong.
Huh? What?
Never mind.
You guys are right.
Wow!
Taiga, it seems you really like this.
Yeah, it's really beautiful!
Taiga likes Kitamura.
Haven't I known that for a long time?
But why am I...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
I don't understand.
Hey!
Takasu-kun, what do you think?
Do you think it would be good for Taiga and Maruo to go out with each other?
No, that's...
Actually, it'd be too sudden.
Exactly! You agree, right?
Even though everyone says it, it's not like that, right?
Wait a second.
What do you mean by "everyone"?
If Taiga goes out with Maruo,
you don't think it'll be interesting, right?
Huh?
Everyone says you're gentle, and you love to care for others,
Wai-
but you actually like Taiga, right?
I'll support you, I swear!
Don't tell me you like Kitamu-
Hey, Kihara!
Hurry up.
Coming!
Takasu-kun, don't give up!
Come on!
Stop annoying me!
I said I'm coming!
This is some super confusing Guns N' Roses.
nemurenai yoru ni wa
眠れない夜には
On the nights I can’t sleep
hitori de tameiki
ひとりでため息
I sigh alone.
minna wa dou na no
みんなはどうなの？
How is everyone?
nandaka sabishii
なんだか寂しい
I feel a little lonely.
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
広い大地に　ひと粒の種
Within the vast world, a single seed
nekko nobashite
根っこのばして
extended its roots
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
まだ青い　実をつけた
and put out a fruit that was still unripe.
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish would turn orange soon
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
The fruit that I wish would turn orange soon
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams just swell-
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
orenji kyou mo
オレンジ　今日も
Today, I tried eating an orange
tabete mita kedo
食べてみたけど
Today, I tried eating an orange
mada suppakute naita
まだすっぱくて　 泣いた
but it was so sour I cried.
watashi mitai de nokosenai kara
私みたいで残せないから
I couldn’t leave it behind like I have been
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
suki da yo nakeru yo
好きだよ 泣けるよ
I love it… I feel like crying.
suki da yo suki da yo
好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it… I love it.
Next Episode Preview
Beneath the Fir Tree
It'll definitely be interesting!
It'll get your spirits up!
That's why you have to come to the party, Kushieda.
I can't be my usual self anymore.
Yes, surely...
Probably...