It's now the last day of the Golden Week holiday!
How has everyone been?
I'm so bored that I could die...
Geez! It's all because the mongrel is so useless...
It's not my fault that you didn't get to meet Kitamura, right?
Didn't I say he'd be busy with the student
council and club practice during the holidays?
Isn't it a dog's job to do something about that?
Though if you met him, you wouldn't be able to hold a conversation with him anyway.
I'll send you to hell!
It spilled on me!
What are you doing?!
Quickly! Find something to wipe it with!
Geez...
Didn't it happen because you were talking crap?!
So noisy...
We woke her up...
Here, wipe it off with this for now.
You two were planning to eat omelet-rice by yourselves while Ya-chan was sleeping!
Yours is already wrapped up and in the fridge!
Did you write my name on it properly?
"Yasuko" with ketchup...
I'll write it, I'll write it! So don't cry any more!
Sniff... I got it. I'll sleep some more.
What should I do? It's going to become a stain.
It'll come off if we treat it properly.
I'll make it come off properly, so in return...
Jonny's again?
It's fine, right? Please!
I can't go by myself!
You can at least help matters between me and Kushieda!
Ah, geez! Shut up! I'll skin you!
What the?!
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Kawashima Ami
Kushieda... a day off...
Even a labouring girl will take some days off too.
Isn't it punishment for coming just for your own happiness?
I'm different from you who's confessed and been confessed to.
I've yet to-
My eyes! My eyes!
Don't say embarrassing things, horny mutt.
What are you doing?!
This is cute!
Which? Which?
For you to wear that is a bit-
What I want is the bag! The bag!
Y-Yeah...
Welcome!
After all, I'm tiny and have short legs.
But with that, I haven't had any trou-
What's-
Ryuuji, this!
A bag, right?
Not that! The model!
The model?
Look! That person.
It's this person, right?
It's true!
She's Kawashima Ami.
She's the actress Kawashima Anna's daughter.
What's a girl like that doing here?
Sorry, Ami. I made you wait.
K-Kitamu-
Oh! If it isn't Takasu and Aisaka?
What a coincidence!
Why?!
H-Hey! They're coming over here!
Even if you say that...!
What are you getting entangled over?
You're getting along well, as usual.
I-It's not like that!
It's not like that!
What's going on, Yuusaku?
Yeah, I was thinking of introducing you here.
"Yuusaku"?
She's Kawashima Ami.
She used to live in my neighbourhood.
I guess you can call us childhood friends.
And these two are Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
Childhood... friends?
H-Hello.
Nice to meet you!
Is that...?
Eh?
Ah, y-yeah. We were just looking at this, and-
Oh no, you've seen an embarrassing side of me.
I should have put on some better clothes and make-up.
When I'm not working, I just let my guard down...
No! Um, that's not it at all!
Since we're all here, why don't the four of us chat?
That's fine, right, Ami?
Of course!
This place brings back memories!
We sure came here often in the past, huh?
Right, right! With our families!
Here Takasu-kun, have some too.
Would diet-sugar have been better?
Eh? No...
Rather, are you someone who drinks it black?
Hey, you sure are careless.
I'm so sorry!
Since Yuusaku put some in, I just...
N-No, it's...
I did it again.
They always tell me: "Really, Ami, you sure are a clumsy airhead."
I'm sorry.
No, not at all. I like sweet things.
Thanks! You're so kind.
Oh, no! What am I doing?
Ah, sorry.
Oh, no. Why are you apologising?
I-
Well then, I'm off to the restroom for a bit.
Wai-
Me too... the restroom...
Geez, I can't fill the time.
As expected, you left your seat, huh?
You! What about the rest-
W-What is it?
I want you to answer honestly.
Takasu, what did you think of Ami?
Forget what I thought! Since you suddenly brought such a cute girl, I got all nervous.
I'll admit that she's cute.
And she's a really nice girl too!
She's a bit of an airhead, but you could say she's innocent or...
Well, just have a look.
This is boring.
Hey, Ami-chan's iced tea is all gone.
Go get some more.
Ignoring me, are you?
Speaking of which, didn't your attitude earlier kind of suck?
Ah, that's it! I'll have your boyfriend bring it.
If Ami-chan says it, it seems like he'll listen to anything.
Is it okay if Ami-chan steals him?
Though I don't really need him at all!
He's not my boyfriend.
I see. It's fine either way.
Precisely, these are Ami's true colours.
Spoiled, selfish, and tyrannical. Your typical princess.
I can't help but think she's been possessed by a demon.
Well, in a deserted town like this,
there aren't any guys better than that.
Hey, how many centimetres tall are you?
I only just noticed, but aren't your proportions strange?
Actually, I'm shocked that they even sell clothes that size!
But you know, when you buy things like denims,
Even so, that Taiga can put up with tha-
don't you have to cut the cuffs?
Ami-chan's never had to, so-
Wha-
There was a mosquito on your face.
Ah, it was a fly.
Why, you-
Hey Ami, we're leaving already!
Yuusaku!
I get it, I get it.
I'm sorry, Aisaka. We'll leave it here for today.
Seconds!
There's none left.
You've already gulped down two and a half bowls.
It's all her fault.
That fickle woman... Just remembering her makes me hungry.
You mean you get angry, right?
But Kitamura was troubled.
W-What should I do?
Doing that might have made Kitamura hate me...
Well, I don't think so.
Kitamura knows whole story-
I hate that woman!
Don't cry...
What about you?!
Being so mushy around her!
I wasn't really-
You know, there really aren't any upright,
honest people who refer to themselves as airheads!
Huh?
Well, whatever. I won't ever meet her again.
I'll just be mature here and swallow my hatred!
Hey! That's mine!
Shut up!
Kawashima
Ami
I'm transferring to this school starting today.
I'm Kawashima Ami.
Please call me "Ami."
Kawashima
Ami
Eh? Could she be...?
The girl who's modelling for Can Vi?
Too cute!
An angel has descended upon us!
Thank you, lord!
Kawashima
Ami
Everyone! Let's all get along with our new friend, shall we?
Then first, let's decide on a seat.
Put her next to me!
No, next to me!
A big win!
I'm so glad that I'm in this class!
Standing out like this is kind of embarrassing.
Why? It looks good on you, so it's fine!
Yeah. You've got a really nice body.
I want to hurry up and get the same jersey as everyone else.
Ami-chan is certainly cute and has an exceptionally nice body, but...
...my cute girl detecting Minorin Radar isn't reacting at all this time.
Minorin?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Ah, geez, why do I fall over in the middle of nowhere? So uncool!
Ami-chan's pretty clumsy.
You're a bit air-headed, huh?
That's not it at all!
But, they sometimes tell me that, "Ami, you really are an airhead."
As expected!
But that's really not it!
Yeah, yeah, we got it.
Geez, it's true though!
That's amazing.
Yeah, she's got a complete grasp of how to win people's hearts.
Why didn't you tell me she was transferring?
If I had, Ami wouldn't have shown her true colours, would she?
That wouldn't have worked.
What is that?
To be honest, I don't dislike Ami's true colours.
That's why I want everyone to know the real her.
I like that Ami.
No, that's-
Even if they hate her, I'm sure she can cope.
I just don't want her to keep lying.
First!
So they even have vending machines here.
Why...?
Because you left the classroom just as fourth period was about to start.
I was interested, so I followed you.
Not good, her true colours are...
Buying drinks outside lunch breaks is against school rules, you know.
Then,
we're partners in crime, right?
I'll pay for it.
It's fine!
That's an apology for yesterday.
An apology?
I was really shocked when I found out that you were in the same school...
Aisaka-san too... Yuusaku didn't say anything.
Say, about yesterday...
Did you hear anything from Aisaka-san?
Yesterday?
Yesterday, you see, was all my fault.
I'm somewhat of an airhead, so I think I annoyed Aisaka-san.
Even though I was just casually chatting,
she suddenly started calling me cheeky,
saying that I was getting carried away, and then...
But Aisaka-san isn't bad!
If I were a more level-headed girl, it would never have happened...
It happens sometimes.
After all, I get hated by other girls like this, so I'm not worried,
since I can keep going.
I get it.
So I don't want you to tell anyone about what happened yesterday.
I-
I understand what you're saying, so let's go back for now.
Thanks!
Let's hurry!
"The sun was high when they, with no
fanfare in their preparations, departed."
The sun was high when they, with no fanfare in their preparations, departed.
The Tale of Genji
The Carriage Competition
The parts about the sun being high here explain how the sun is rising up by saying that it is climbing upwards.
It is simply pointing out that the sun is flourishing.
Why did you return to
the classroom, barely in time,
together with
Kawashima Ami?!
Taiga
"Why?"
Sheesh.
To Takasu-kun
From Minori
Takasu-kun. Minori is angry!
You're being somewhat suspicious together
with Transfer-Student-chan!
Is it cheating? Are you cheating?!
If you dump Taiga...
at that time...!
Takasu-kun. Minori is angry!
You're being somewhat suspicious
together with Transfer-Student-chan!
...there will be punishment!
Is it cheating? Are you cheating?!
If you dump Taiga... at that time...!
Minori
...there will be punishment!
Dammit! Why do I have to go through this?
From Takasu to Kushieda,
Sorry about the completely different subject, but...
...what do you think of people that refer to themselves as airheads?
Okay, is there anything up to this point that you don't understand?
What's the matter, you guys?
Hey, Takasu.
Haruta says he'll introduce us to freshmen girls in the track club as a three-man set.
You'll go for sure, right?
Even If I went, I'd only scare them, right?
No way!
After all, we're just getting enough pe-
And besides...
The Palmtop Tiger...
That's how it is.
Just how did it become like this?
It wasn't on purpose!
I fell over, so I couldn't help it!
I'll go get some rags. Go on ahead.
It's fine. I'll wait in the classroom.
Ryuu-
Oh, no! Why are you here?
You're a real eyesore.
Don't come near me, damn kid.
Scary!
Just what I'd expect from the girl that even the teachers find annoying, Aisaka-san.
When I went to the teachers' office earlier,
the teachers were all fawning over Ami-chan.
They were worried about whether Ami-chan was being bullied by Aisaka-san or not!
You're really hated around here.
I'm going to have a good time,
seeing how long you can keep up your little persona.
Revealing your true colours would be simple.
But that would be boring, right?
I'll keep watching you.
Even if we change classes, even after we graduate...
Just like a stalker!
You're such an annoying runt!
Isn't that why you don't have any friends?
Just one: Takasu Ryuuji.
He looks like a delinquent, though he's entranced by me.
Gross!
But won't you really be all alone?
I really do pity you.
To even be hated by humanitarians like Yuusaku...
What was that?
I already told him all about what happened at the family restaurant.
I think he probably hates you now.
It really is the end!
Kawashima?
Hey, out of the way.
It's Ryuu-chan's pork cutlet!
Sheesh.
Even though I told her it's best when eaten right after it's cooked.
If you're worried,
go pick her up.
Aw, it fogged up.
Taiga, I'm coming in!
What? You're here after all?
The lights aren't even on.
Hey, Tai-
What did you come for?
"What", you say?
It's about the food!
T-Taiga!
Are you all right?
She said Kitamura-kun...
...hates me.
That woman said she told everything...
I... I...
It's all right.
What is?
Kitamura knows everything.
How she really is, what happened at the family restaurant, her lies... Everything.
Really?
Really.
Also, Kitamura's not the kind of guy who
starts hating people for something like that.
That's something you understand the most, right?
Then, why am I tiny?
Huh?
Why do I have a weird name?
No. That's-
What?!
Just because she's 165 centimetres tall!
Just because her name looks just like Sailor Mercury's!
As a bonus, just because she's childhood friends with Kitamura-
Sorry. Are you all right?
Still, worrying about such useless thi-
Unlike you, I'm delicate!
You...
Ryuu-chan!
We're having pork cutlet, but there's no sauce. This is...
Pork cutlet...
Sauce! Ryuu-chan!
From a black pig.
Hey, what about pudding? Pudding!
Only sauce!
This is...?
Hey, let's get back. Yasuko will be late.
Ryuuji, look at this.
Notice
Kawashima Ami-chan will temporarily
be taking a break for her studies.
This is...?
That means she's on holiday, right?
Is it really worth taking a break from work just to go to our school?
Isn't that...?
That woman!
That really is Kawashima Ami, huh?
What's up with that outfit?
And those bags are only filled with sweets.
Is she having a party?
No, that's not it. That's...
I spotted something very interesting.
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
True Colours
Ah, it's really annoying!
If you keep following
me around like that...
...Ami-chan will
give you a swift death!
Named: Stupid Chihuahua!