It hit me really hard this time.
Iori was completely in the right.
I have no right to complain if
.I get yelled at or condemned.
I thought I understood
.just how selfish I was,
but there was a spoiled part of me that turned a blind eye to it all.
Nagase didn't have to say it like that, though.
Inaba! Come to the clubroom
and get to work already!
We need to finish before
finals and then break!
I'm sorry!
Taichi's with me, so I'll
.bring him along too.
Hurry up!
Let's go?
Yeah.
I hear your voice on the wind
like the rhythm of our daily life
You smile impulsively like the sun itself
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Since when can we remember these exciting days?
How to get
points from
the judges
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Inabaaaan!
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Universal Studios
sounds good too
A map that shows
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get
points from
the judges
recommended places
around school
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Inabaaaan!
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Universal Studios
sounds good too
What awaits us past tomorrow?
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
I'm hungry
Inaban's white rabbit
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Let's beat the jazz band!
Frankensteiner!
How about curry doria?
Cheep
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Today connects to brighter days yet
which catch up with us
in a flood of colors
We walk our path through life with strength
and after today know that the light itself is with us
In your smile I can see warmth
Forever and ever
we live through ups and downs here
Let us believe in that and the future it brings about
Resolve and Resolution
Club's on break from tomorrow on, right?
The presentation's immediately afterward.
We're cutting it really close here, you know?
To be perfectly honest, I wanna study too!
I'm blaming you if I fail, you hear?
You can only blame yourself!
Actually, you studying for a day
.wouldn't change a thing.
Why would you berate me right now?!
Whatever happens, it's your responsibility.
Why would you pick up where she left off?!
Now I'm really scared!
I don't wanna flunk and become Yui's junior!
Relax. I'm sure you'll be able to
.pass your second time around.
So we're operating under the assumption that I'm gonna repeat a year?!
But I'm surprised we managed to get so much done in such a short time.
Our Recommended Places
Around Yamaboshi
This is quite the masterpiece,
if I do say so myself.
Our Recommended Places
Around Yamaboshi
Isn't this the first time we've worked so hard on something for the SCS?
Yeah.
Personal bias aside, both the amount and quality of information we've gathered is impressive.
We've totally got a shot at winning.
The real question is...
whether we can do the
.presentation with five people.
It'll be fine, Inaba.
Thanks.
Yo!
You guys hanging in there?
Oh, it's just Mr. Go...
Phew.
Are you really that happy to see me, Kiriyama?
You're so cute!
C-Cute?! No way...
Wait.
Hearing that from Mr. Go
doesn't make me very happy!
Hearing that doesn't me very happy.
I guess I'll just take these
.snacks I brought along back.
You're not holding anything, Mr. Go.
Huh?!
Crap! I forgot them back in the faculty room!
Heh.
Looking at an idiot sure does help in
taking your mind off things, doesn't it?
Hey, Inaba.
Did you just say something rude to your teacher?
Go away already.
I rebuked her for abusing me
and only got more in return!
But, Mr. Go, it's quite rare for
.you to be bringing us snacks.
Well, it seems like you guys're working hard.
I can't take any sides,
but I'm rooting for both you and the jazz band.
Hard work is something that's easily noticed,
and there'll always be someone willing to help out those that do their very best.
Mr. Go, you really are a teacher, huh?
He shows it occasionally.
This might be the first time
.I've ever seen this side of him.
Where's Nagase?
Did she go to the bathroom or something?
Today's cold too.
Yaegashi...
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
You received a thought transmission from Iori earlier, didn't you?
Yeah.
It was just about her feeling cold, though.
If only she'd come to the clubroom...
Stop getting depressed like that every time!
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
You need to be more headstrong,
like you used to be!
Yeah.
But first, we gotta finish up that presentation.
That's right.
That'd be the best thing for Iori too.
She'll surely be back to her
cheerful old self soon enough!
Yeah.
We're not alone.
I'll do what I can for Nagase.
Iori will definitely go back to her old self.
So we'll believe in her and wait.
They don't understand.
I'm done with this.
I really am.
The emotions I feel from everyone
.are so warm and dazzling.
It's too much for me to take.
They're all too nice,
even though I don't deserve it.
Watase.
How did that whole
"It's not like I got any chocolate from her, but I'll give Fujishima something on White Day and ask her out on a date" plan go?
Unfortunately, it turned out that Fujishima had a vital mission on that day...
Namely, Mission: "Kick the asses of guys who got
chocolates but don't have the balls to seal the deal."
You know, last night...
I ran into Fujishima while she
.was out walking her dog.
It was a bulldog—a totally cute one at that!
Huh?
I don't think bulldogs are very "cute."
Now that's an inexcusable opinion.
Fujishima!
Let me give you a thorough explanation on just how cute bulldogs are!
By the time I'm done with you,
my cutie-pie will charm your socks off!
Here's a picture, by the way.
Fujishima's quite popular, isn't she?
So cute!
I know, right?
I'm more interested in the
.conversation over there.
I've been thinking for a while now that Iori had just been putting on a facade.
Airheaded happy-go-lucky girls like that don't actually exist, do they?
That rumor about her tricking guys into doing her bidding seems a lot more believable now,
considering how she's been acting lately.
Listen up, everyone!
I'm pretty sure you all know by now that Nagase's been acting weird recently.
There've also been some weird rumors going around.
"Rumors"? Wouldn't it be better to call them facts?
I have no idea what you guys've heard, but I'm asking you to take it all with a grain of salt.
The way she's acting now
makes things quite clear, though.
Exactly.
Yeah, that was a bit too much to take.
It was a straight face heel turn.
She has her reasons!
Really? What would they be, pray tell?
I was in love with Nagase,
so I came on to her!
In a way that's hard to talk about!
Hold it, Yaegashi!
Should you really be saying all this?
Honestly, I took it too far!
Way too far!
Waay too far!
Waaay too far!
Waaaay too far!
Waaaaay too far!
Waaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay too far!
I couldn't even begin to tell
you about how far I took it!
Because of that, Nagase has
lost her trust in people!
What I'm trying to say is, it's my fault Nagase's been acting like this lately,
and not hers!
So basically...
If you're telling the truth...
Dude, this is not good!
Did he assault her or something?!
Don't say any more!
I feel kinda bad for Iori if
.he's really telling the truth.
I can see why she'd act like that now.
Wait. So Yaegashi was that kinda guy?
Dude, I think this is your last chance
.to explain yourself or take that back.
No, but...
Hello. Dad?
One of my classmates is a criminal.
Could you send a few people over?
Hold on.
Wasn't your father the high-ranking cop?
Yeah, and I tipped him off.
Hey, I haven't broken the law!
Just kidding.
Come with me!
What the hell was that?
I just wanted to kill the rumors.
That I know.
So I figured that if someone else could take the fall for Nagase's behavior,
it'd stop people from badmouthing her
and maybe even get some
.people to sympathize with her.
And that too.
That said, I couldn't talk about Heartseed,
so the only thing I could think of was saying that I forced myself onto her.
So why did you have to take the blame?!
I didn't have a better idea!
You seriously could've come up with something better than assault.
Objection!
I only said I came on to her!
Not once did I use the word assault!
Still a terrible choice of words!
Also, this doesn't solve a thing!
You're right...
I'll knock the living daylights out of you if you say
something like "I wanted to shoulder some of her pain."
That wasn't my intention!
But it'd make things a lot easier for Nagase
.if our classmates stopped badmouthing her.
And Kiriyama told me I wasn't
.being as headstrong as I used to.
That bitch...
Look. She didn't do anything wrong!
No verbal, corporal, or capital
punishment for her later, all right?
Huh? I didn't transmit my thoughts,
so how'd you know what I was thinking?
Your expression said it all.
A-Anyway...
The next time you decide to do something
as retarded as that, talk to me about it first!
Don't do whatever comes to mind.
Understood?
Understood.
You two seem to be quite close these days.
Oh, pardon me.
Did I interrupt some roleplay?
We aren't roleplaying!
Good work back there.
Don't worry. I'll put in a good
.word for Yaegashi later.
Considering he likely got the people
.badmouthing Nagase to tone it down a bit.
Actually, what I want to know is
.why you didn't do anything.
You're usually the first to make a move in these kinds of situations.
Well, I did consider it,
but I figured it wouldn't be a very
.good idea for me to get too involved,
and as the class rep, I should silently wait for everyone to grow from this endeavor.
Why are you acting like a parent
looking after their kids?
Guiding everyone down the right path without hindering their chances for personal growth.
That is the vital task I've been entrusted with.
That said, I'll help out if absolutely necessary.
Unnecessary.
Nothing's impossible for the two of us!
I think a lot of things are, actually.
Have you reflected on your actions yet?
I don't need to.
You're seriously so full of yourself.
I'm sure you were behind
.Yaegashi saying all that stuff too.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I hear that Student Whatever Society you're in and the jazz band are competing over your advisor.
What about it?
Let the jazz band win.
What does the jazz band have to do with you?
Oh, right. Is this because Shiroyama's in it?
Shut up!
Calm down, Kaoru!
There's seriously something
.wrong with you, Nagase.
Let's go, Kaoru.
God damn, that pissed me off.
We should probably teach her a lesson.
Like, for example...
Are you serious?
Sounds good.
Wh-What?
Mind your own business.
It's all his fault, anyway.
What's on your mind—
Yamaboshi Academy
FINALS
This sense of freedom is amazing!
You could say this is why exams really exist.
Have you forgotten that you might
have to take supplementary exams?
That's not at all funny. Please stop.
You do realize that our presentation takes
priority over your supplementary exams, right?
They're both important to me, you know!
The presentation's next week.
As long as we practice presenting,
we should be good—
Why?
I worked so hard on this one.
Who did this?
The door was locked.
Whoever's responsible for this
ain't getting off easy!
No point in flipping our lids.
Do you really expect me to
stay calm after seeing this?!
Who the hell did this?!
The jazz band?
Nah, it couldn't be.
Judging by how hard they were working.
I don't think they'd resort to this.
What should we do?
What can we do?
Let's do it all over again.
But the presentation's next week!
There's no way we'd make it in time!
And one week's not nearly enough time to make the same thing again.
But it is enough time for something simpler.
How is that gonna help us beat the jazz band?
Yeah, it'll probably be an uphill battle, but...
...we haven't lost yet!
Didn't we say that we'd do our best for Nagase too?
She'll surely come back to us.
And that's one of the reasons we can't give up here.
Just think about it.
The only problem here is that
.our stuff won't look as good.
Then all we need to do is focus on
.the content and how we present it.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
Yeah!
Moping around isn't gonna help us!
We must press on!
I'm gonna defeat the weak-
hearted me of a minute ago!
Wow, Yui! You're so cool!
Cute, not cool.
All right, then.
Let's forget about finding out who did this for now and get to work.
Sure, but I'm going on a witch hunt
.the moment we finish the presentation.
They could run to the depths of Hell for all I care, but they can't hide.
But we need to mark a suspect and take measures so they can't do this again.
We'll be fine if we take our
.work back home with us.
Also, we'll probably need
to report this to Goto—
Nagase?
You're not getting away with this!
You went and got other people involved in this!
Apologies just aren't gonna cut it now!
Shall I make you cry?
Shall I make you scream?
How should I make you pay for this?!
What? What's wrong?
Did you receive a thought transmission from Iori?
You two stay here.
Shouldn't we have had Kiriyama
and Aoki come with us?
Nah, I wanna settle this
.with just the two of us.
Her thoughts earlier weren't
exactly pretty, were they?
You can say that again.
Hello? Fujishima?
Thanks. I owe you one.
What'd you get from her?
Setouchi's number.
What do you want?
You're in danger.
I'm sure you know why.
I-I don't know anything.
I had nothing to do with it.
There you are!
You're dead!
Don't do it, Nagase!
Hold on a sec, Iori!
Don't try to stop me!
I won't let her get away with this!
She'll pay!
She'll definitely pay!
Get out of here, Setouchi!
Now!
Don't stop me!
Don't stop me, please!
I'm sorry!
I'm so, so sorry!
It's all my fault!
I'm sorry!
Why did it end up like this?
Hey, Iori.
Can we try and talk things out again?
I'm not letting you run away this time.
Remember what I said last time?
I said I wanted you to tell me what you kept hidden in your heart.
But thinking back on it, I realized
.that it was too arbitrary.
Let's do this the fair way.
I want you to give me some of your pain.
And I'll give you some of mine in turn.
I'll embarrass myself to the
.point where I'll wanna die.
So regardless of how
.much you're against it,
tell me why you're rejecting
.the people around you.
Didn't I do the same thing to you?
You got a problem?
I totally do!
Actually, this is totally illogical!
I'm talking to Iori here!
Get the hell out of here if all
.you're gonna do is complain.
Anyway, now I'm gonna talk
.about something embarrassing.
Not to mention, I'm gonna do it
.in the presence of the guy I love.
Nothing else could even come close
.to how embarrassing this'll be.
As you know already, I love Taichi.
I love him so much that he's recently started showing up in my dreams!
Hold on a second. You're
embarrassing me here!
And this happened just the other day.
I went and had a dream about doing something erotic with Taichi!
But then I woke up, so we didn't
.get to finish what we started.
To illustrate, we were doing it in this position!
My heart was pounding out of
.my chest when I woke up.
My chest hurt like someone had
.just punched a hole through it.
But I was also heartbroken that it ended.
I got so frustrated I thought about Taichi as I—
Stop!
What the fuck are you saying?!
Oh, come on! You did the same thing!
Holy shit, I'm so embarrassed. I'm gonna cry.
How about it?
It ended up being a bit half-assed,
but it was a pretty damn
embarrassing story, wasn't it?
You were right.
I really am selfish.
At first, I tried to set the two of you up,
but later, I started saying I loved him.
Now I've realized that there's nothing I can do about this anymore.
Back when I sought logic in anything and everything,
I never would've come to terms with this conclusion.
I can now, though.
I don't have to rely on logic, rationality, or objective proof anymore.
It might not be much compared to others,
but I have some self-belief now!
You got a problem with that? Feel free to tell me.
I'm well aware I'm being impudent here.
So you can go ahead and do the same.
Don't bottle it all up inside.
That's enough.
Stop with all of this stuff, please.
What the heck was that?
You're fucking retarded!
Such an embarrassing confession.
I'm moved to tears here.
And I'm sure that if I gave in to that
impulse and oh-so-tearfully apologized,
there'd be a very emotional
ending waiting for all of us.
But too bad. That just isn't gonna happen.
I'm done with this shit!
I'm tired of it!
I can't keep playing some
tragic heroine anymore!
How many times do I have to
lay my feelings out bare?!
How many times do I have
to be torn to shreds?!
When will this stop?!
What the hell is Heartseed?
How the hell does this
possessing people thing work?
Everything related to it
is so damn fucked up!
How many times do I have to suffer?
I'm done with this!
I can't take it anymore!
Yeah, of course.
It must be hard.
I had no idea you were that cornered.
Sorry about this. You haven't done anything wrong.
But you know, you could just rely on us!
We'd do anything to get your usual self back—
Listen to me! I told you that's not it!
What do you even want me to be?
I can't do this anymore.
"What do we want you to be?"
What do you mean?
Nagase,
you can just be your usual self.
You can make the people around you happy by just being yourself.
And they'll all love you—
I just said I can't do it anymore!
Nagase.
It's impossible for me.
Nagase...
I can't be what you all want me to be.
I can't be someone who
.makes everybody happy.
I can't be universally loved.
I can't be that amazing a person!
What were we burdening Iori with?
Wasn't Nagase Iori a more normal, average girl?
In truth, I'm a cold and gloomy person.
But I used to pretend to be more cheerful.
Everyone found that pretense of mine fun and, most importantly, so did I.
But I've grown tired of acting out that idealized self.
Maybe I could've handled it just
.fine if I was living a normal life,
but then this Heartseed nonsense showed up,
.took me over, and nearly killed me.
Right when I thought I'd somehow made it through, he showed up again!
I was absolutely terrified, but I
.did my best to put up a front.
Loads of shit happened that left my life in pieces.
That's when I got the chance to rewrite my past.
I considered it, but I threw that chance away in the end.
I did my very best,
but I can't keep doing it over and over again!
This time, I started transmitting my thoughts to people.
The prospect of being called a liar because of the disconnect between what I think and how I act terrified me!
But I didn't know what to do.
Things just got so messed up.
I wanted to handle things better, you know.
I don't care, you retard.
Huh?
You called me a retard too,
...didn't you? Well, guess what...
You're a retard!
A stupid, foolish nincompoop!
Sure, we may have unwittingly
.asked too much of you.
But why'd you have to try and live up to all of that? Why'd you have to push yourself?
You're just a fucking retard!
Are "I can," "I can't," and "I'm gonna run away" your only options?
Can't you learn to relax and take things easy?
Bottling it all up inside until you explode is the worst possible way to do things!
Nobody gives a flying rat's ass
what happens to you!
It's your fucking life!
Live it as you damn well please!
Where're your two cents, Taichi?
I...
I said I loved you, and yet I
.never knew you really were.
How could I not get rejected like that?
But now I know both sides of you,
and I'll say this so I can
get through to the real you:
I still love Nagase Iori.
How can you say you love someone when they're not the person you thought they were?
Who cares?
Sure, you're not the person I thought you were,
but I want to be your friend regardless,
and I think you of as a friend.
That's what's important.
That's all we need.
Could you give me some time?
I had no idea Setouchi was that much of a bitch.
Dude, you were the one who went nuts back there.
Well, it's kind of a stress buster, you see.
What was it again? The Student Cultural Society?
Gotta feel bad for 'em.
We messed up their room quite badly.
What's the big deal? All it had was paper.
So it was you guys!
You fucking bastards!
Wh-Who the fuck is this—
You fucking—
Help me deal with her.
Help!
Connecting Hearts
Inaba!
Taichi!
We'll save you!
If anything happened to you...
Let me just say this:
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
I am lost and confused
and yet I know that someone is holding out their hand for me
Inside the little box I locked
was the taste of a path I thought I knew
One by one I soothe my wounds
and again jealousy, ardor, coldness, light,
rejection and hope,
all become one and I stand screaming helplessly
My feelings are like melting chocolate, black and sweet
My dreams have long since turned to ash
I am weak, and ringing fills my ears and I hear nothing else
Please find me
mi     chi     ra      n      do      m
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
Frankensteiner!
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
Tune in next time!
Yaegashi Taichi
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get points from the judges
A bonus extra for the SCS paper
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
How about
curry doria?
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Inabaaaan!
Cheep
A map that shows
recommended places
around school
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Inaban's white rabbit
Universal Studios
sounds good too