Meet Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
Sadly, her life will last only
until next spring.
Although we were sent to make certain
that her destiny didn't change,
we ended up transforming her
into a 16-year-old girl, Full Moon.
Mitsuki somehow managed to make
her doctor and manager
believe the story.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Huh?
What's that?
You haven't forgotten anything?
No!
It's good that you're being released
from the hospital so soon.
Please, come in.
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji!
Thank you for taking such
good care of us.
O-Of course.
Mrs. Koyama also said to
give you her thanks.
Is that so?
How do you feel?
I feel great!
Doctor, thank you for everything.
Still, keep your transformation
a secret from your grandmother, okay?
Ah, yes.
And...
Him too.
Y-Yes.
Well then, take care of yourself.
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji, once our preparations
are done, we'll come say goodbye to you.
Oh no, I have an examination now,
so please don't bother.
It seems like that doctor doesn't like me.
N-No way! That's your imagination!
Well, I guess it can't be helped
if he doesn't like me.
I'm a Death Spirit,
he's a doctor.
I was surprised by how much
your grandmother was worried about you.
Oh really?
Grandma...
She's that concerned about me?
You should think about how
you inconvenienced others!
Starting with Dr. Wakaoji,
then the nurses, everyone was so busy,
but they're looking for you!
I'm so sorry!
Indeed... Be careful from now on.
Umm... Grandma, how are you feeling?
The heat got to me a bit.
There's no need to worry.
I see.
Excuse me.
Congratulations on your release
from the hospital, Mitsuki.
Thank you, Ms. Oshige.
You can work again after
you've settled down a bit.
Thank you.
And remember, you'll have to make
some apologies when you return.
Yes.
Well, I'll be in touch.
Okay.
Hey, ya little brat!
Why isn't there an air conditioner
in this room!
Because it's not good for my throat.
Besides, we're elevated,
so there's a breeze. Isn't it cool?
It's not cool!
More importantly...
I wonder what Meroko is doing.
I don't know.
Takuto, are you still angry?
Hey? Aren't you angry?
It's her fault that you didn't
make the audition!
I'm sure that Meroko had
her own reasons.
Th-That's true.
But it's Meroko's fault that you...
But, thanks to her, I was able to tell
Dr. Wakaoji and Ms.Oshige the truth.
Y-Yeah well...
All that's left is for Meroko
to come home.
Meroko... I wonder where she went.
I didn't do anything wrong!
I only fulfilled my duty as
a Death Spirit!
What's wrong with that?!
That stupid Takuto!
Hello.
Yes, yes.
W-What is it?
Is Mitsuki home?
Yes.
We all came to visit her!
We were surprised to hear
you were in the hospital.
But we're glad you've gotten better.
Yes. Thank you.
Wow, your garden is big!
You even have a pond!
That's awesome!
Hey, can I go look a little bit?
Sure.
Ms. Tanaka.
Ma'am...
Do we have guests?
Yes, they are all Mitsuki's friends.
This is the first time so many
have come to visit.
I'm surprised.
What?! A school ghost story?
They say it appeared in
the gym of our school!
No way!
At night, when nobody is in the gym...
a basketball...
S-Stop it!
I have a thing about stuff like that.
Mitsuki's a chicken.
With only this much.
But...
I'm sure that ghost is lonely.
So it's waiting for someone to
come and play with it.
What?!
After all, you can't play basketball alone.
- You sure can't!
Could that, by any chance, be...
Meroko?
Don't bother coming out.
Don't overdo it.
Okay, thank you for coming today.
See you again!
- Bye-bye!
What a dreadful experience!
Hey, Takuto.
Huh? What is it?
It's about Meroko.
You're still talking about that?!
Meroko might be at school.
I don't want to hear it!
Oh, Takuto!
Jeez!
I'm tired of it already.
Are you here, Meroko?!
Oh, shoot!
Oh, I can't get out!
Are you okay, Meroko?
I'm fine.
What? Takuto didn't say anything?
That's right, he wouldn't tell
me even when I asked.
Th-The reason is...
The reason is...
It's okay if you don't want to say it.
It's just...
Without you, Meroko, it's like...
There's something missing,
like something's different.
When it's not the three of us...
If it's not the three of us like before,
it's lonely.
So, let's go home together!
I want to go home too.
I want to go home, but Takuto...
I think that deep down
Takuto wants you to come home.
You think so?.
It's okay with me if
you don't come home!
Why!
Because, I got to be
alone with her at last.
In short, you're
in the way!
I-It's no good!
Takuto prefers it without me!
What?
Anyway, I can't go. See you!
Meroko!
Jeez...
Jeez! It's hot.
So hot!
I'm hot.
R-Rejected!
Hey, I haven't said anything yet.
Anyway, it's going to be
about Meroko, right?
Oh, you know?
Umm... I want you to go and get Meroko.
Now she's at school.
Listen, why do I have to go
and get her?
If she wants to come home,
she can come home herself.
What?! She can?
Th-That's Meroko's problem.
Why should I care?
I see. Yes, that's right.
W-Wait a minute!
Did Takuto really say it was okay?
That's what he said!
B-But...
Come on!
But I don't know what
to say to Takuto.
You can say, "I'm back!"
But I don't think Takuto will say,
"Welcome back."
Not that again.
At this rate,
things will stay like this forever.
Is that okay?
It's...not good, but...
Wow, the sky is so blue!
And the clouds are so white!
It's beautiful.
Hey Takuto, come look!
I'm not interested.
Besides, for Spirits of Death,
it doesn't matter if the sky is blue
or the clouds are white!
Oh, is that so?
Yes, that's so!
Meroko, come here!
Jeez!
The both of you!
Hello, Tomoe?
This is just a hypothetical question.
What do you think you should do
to help good friends make up?
An opportunity.
An opportunity? What kind?
Anything is fine.
If you create an opportunity
after that it's up to them.
An opportunity...
Mitsuki.
How long do you plan to
be on the phone?
Long phone calls are troublesome
to the other party.
Y-Yes.
Hello, Tomoe?
That's fine.
Really? Thank you very much!
Just be careful about starting a fire.
Prepare a bucket full of water.
Yes!
Excuse me!
Fireworks with friends...
That sounds like fun!
Oh, please excuse me.
I got excited despite myself.
There's nothing to apologize for.
Yes, that's true.
Oh, shall we do something nice
for the children?
Do as you please.
Yes!
Fireworks with Death Spirit power?!
Yeah, I prepared
a fireworks set anyway.
But I want really big ones.
That's fine.
Please.
Fireworks with Death Spirit power?!
Yeah! I want big flashy ones.
Hmm... Well okay.
Hello.
Oh, come in.
- Good evening.
- Please excuse me.
Good evening. Mitsuki's waiting.
Well, come this way.
W-What's this?
It's streaming somen noodle!
Yes, please eat all you like.
- Wow!
- How wonderful!
It feels so quiet and elegant!
Hey, hey, ginger goes with somen.
What? I like mayonnaise dressing.
Welcome!
Oh, Mitsuki!
Cute!
Lovely!
You look pretty, Mitsuki.
R-Really?
Thank you for inviting us today.
Don't mention it.
Everyone, I'm going to start
streaming the somen now.
Okay!
Caught it!
Oh, I missed it.
It's lit!
Light this one too!
I wonder if things will work out.
- Oh no!
- No!
Everyone, this way!
R-Rain, at a time like this?
It's unlucky...for it to rain.
No worries.
It's just a shower, it'll stop soon.
I hope so.
But isn't it great
that you made a lot of friends?
Yes, thanks to you,
Takuto and Meroko.
You know, when my CD came out...
There were times like that.
And I wondered
what was going to happen
when Meroko transformed into me and
made a bargain sale of the CD's.
That really got me.
But that was good.
Yeah.
You're trying to bring the conversation
around to Meroko, aren't you?
Saw through me?
Well, that's okay.
But when I got out of the orphanage,
you and Meroko were my first friends.
That's why, the two of you are
such important friends to me.
I want you to make up.
- Oh, the rain stopped!
- Lucky!
We can continue
the fireworks!
Let's do it!
Hazuki...
Let's do fireworks that shoot in the sky!
Yeah. Let's do it.
All right!
Now!
- Go!
Oh, that's cute!
It's a rabbit and a cat!
W-What's that?!
I only did a rabbit.
That girl...
I get it.
Hey, Meroko!
Takuto...I...
You can't...forgive me.
Well...
Wait!
Don't just decide how other people
are feeling by yourself.
So, do you forgive me?
That thing.
Let's do that thing.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah!
It's presumptuous to ask who we are!
It's us! The Death Spirit duo
who fools crying kids!
Takuto!
Meroko!
Together we are,
Green Onion Ramen!
Wow!
Look at that!
I'm so glad.
What, Mitsuki?
Oh, so glad...
So glad that they have
green onion ramen fireworks!
Or something.
What are you saying, Mitsuki?
What am I saying?
I wonder...
- Good night.
- Good night!
Be careful!
Mitsuki.
Did everyone return home
after having fun?
Yes.
That's good.
But Mitsuki, you're still recuperating so,
get warm and go to bed soon.
Oh, yes.
That's all.
Grandma...
What is it?
Thank you for always being
concerned about me.
Takuto! Meroko!
I have a feeling
that from now on,
Grandma and I are going
to get along just fine!
Is that right?
Of course!
Man! I'm so frustrated!
That girl came back...
Madoka Wakamatsu!
Hey! Why do you always
make her an enemy?
She might actually
be a nice person.
She can't be!
I'm sure she's the one
who destroyed Mitsuki's costume!
Anyway, this is no time
to be talking about that!
She's returning to work for the first time
since her release from the hospital.
We have to support her.
Next time on Full Moon:
"A New Inspiration."
- Look forward to it!