Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Hey, Kagami.
Do you like chocolate wafers?
I do...
Really.
Then here.
Enjoy!
Oh, thanks.
Thanks a lot!
I have more!
I have even more so help yourself!
Wait a sec.
Why do you have so much?
Well, you know those toys that come with snacks.
I can never seem to get the one I want...
...so I end up buying a whole bunch.
Yeah...
Some people just want the toys and ignore the snacks.
To Each
Her Own
Fox.
Um...
Squirrel.
Dog.
What are you babbling about?
Oh.
Just wondering what kind of animals everybody might be.
I like to play tricks so I'd be a fox.
Based on her image, Tsukasa would be a dog.
Yu-chan's like a small animal so she'd be a squirrel.
I see.
So you probably want to say that I'm a tiger or wolf or something.
Nah.
You get lonely really easily so you'd probably be a bunny.
Plus, your pigtails look like bunny ears.
That kinda feels embarrassing...
...so stop.
This is fun!
Me?
A bunny?
What about everyone else?
Cousin Yui is hyperactive so maybe a leopard.
Iwasaki-san is all cool and suave so maybe a hawk.
Yuki-chan has that whole white feel...
...and then she just shouts fluffy for some reason...
...so probably a sheep.
Fumoffu.
Nah...
Miyuki-san has to be a cow!
Around there...
That's what an old man would say...
We were at Konata's place yesterday...
...and saw some of her writing from grade school.
My...
Is that so?
But you know...
Konata may look like a sloppy person...
...but she actually saved that stuff.
Dad told me to keep that stuff safe.
But the real surprise...
...was the list of her dreams for the future.
Veterinarian and lawyer...
Regular jobs like those.
Really.
Well...
The way her dream changed
every year was definitely Konata-esque.
When you look at those...
...you can tell what kind of games and manga I liked at the time.
I get it.
That's what it was.
Back to that again.
Then again, some people put down bride for their ideal job.
That's not even a job.
That's cute!
No.
And like, Tsukasa...
I'm talking about you.
R-Really?
This is why airheads are hopeless.
Airheads tend to not realize they're airheads.
It's not an issue of being an airhead!
That may be true.
Just so you know...
That includes you, Miyuki-san...
Is something the matter?
Miyuki-san.
How bad is your eyesight without glasses?
Under 20/200.
Really...
I heard somewhere that eating blueberries is good for your eyes.
Indeed.
There are also carrots, which contain vitamin A.
Green-yellow vegetables such as spinach.
Pork, which contains vitamin B.
And items containing protein such as sesame seeds and liver...
...are said to be good for your eyes.
Also, laster surgery is the subject of much attention.
But I'm not brave enough to try it.
And I've seen shows about eyesight training on TV.
You know a lot.
Well, I've only named a few of the many options.
But why hasn't your eyesight gotten better if you know so much?
I haven't actually used any of the methods I know.
Why not?
Well...
I wonder why...
You should give it a try!
Like that eyesight training thing.
Right now?
Well...
First, you close your eyes.
And open them really quickly!
Then you look left, right...
...up, and down...
...without moving your head.
Miyuki-san!
Your head!
Your head is moving!
Wh-Wha—
Huh?
H-Huh?
Th-That's strange...
You can stop now...
I may have ended up exhausting my eyes...
Won't that make your eyesight even worse?
Hey, Kona-chan.
What's moe?
When you put it that way...
It's definitely used to express that you like something...
...but I don't really know the specifics.
What?
So you use it without knowing the meaning?
I'll just say that anyone who
understands the general meaning is hardcore.
Not that it really matters...
...but I kinda understand.
We've got dogs from all around the world!
Otay!
Puppies are so cute!
Dad.
Let's get a dog!
Hey, Tsukasa.
That's easy to say...
...but can you train it, walk it, feed it...
...and take care of all the other things?
And puppies and adult dogs look pretty different.
Are you prepared to care for a living being instead of an object?
Y-You're right...
I need to think it through...
B-But you sure know a lot about it, Sis.
That's 'cause, yeah...
I'm also pretty simple...
So I went and looked stuff up.
Look, Konata!
You like this artist, right?
Read it.
Fine.
You're such a pain.
Your face is really close.
Stare~
Um...
Do you need something?
I was wondering how far you'd gotten.
Did that Osano person already show up?
No.
That's still beyond my limits.
Come on.
Read faster.
There sure are a lot of elections this year.
It's killing me.
Really?
What's with the gloomy faces?
Students should go home and study.
Teacher.
We were talking about how there have been too many elections.
Where did that come from?
Election coverage messes up the
schedule for regular programming!
The first airing of this one show was late by four hours!
And then they have updates in the middle of the program!
And the L-shaped ticker just makes the screen smaller!
But you know...
Election coverage is educational in terms of current events...
You shouldn't keep going on about anime.
Besides, air times change even without elections.
Stuff like K-1...
...pushes back the regular programming.
Don't you like martial arts?
Konata
I have experience, but I'm not that interested!
Nanako
Even anime has special programs sometimes, right   ?
—
Nanako
My honey   !
Konata
But they don't run overtime and create
problems for the following show so it's okay!
Nanako
Bah, a college applicant
should worry less about that
and study! !
Konata
Gotta finish with a power attack
—
Sorry for the wait.
Kona-chan doesn't have an umbrella.
You could at least check the weather forecast.
Maybe I should be like guys and just not care and go home.
But I wonder why boys don't mind getting wet.
Because they don't have to worry about bras showing through.
I get it.
It makes sense...
...but don't just blurt it out loud.
Don't you have any shame?
So...
One of you lend me an umbrella.
Well...
We go home together...
...so I guess we can make do with one.
Thanks so much.
You don't leave an umbrella at school?
But you leave all your textbooks here.
Well...
I had one here...
But I used it once, and I haven't remembered to bring it back.
It's not a daily routine or anything.
So you only remember if you've made a habit of it.
Hey, Suzume!
Wait up!
Oh, yeah.
When you wear a raincoat and galoshes...
...you look pretty lame.
That's true.
It makes you look like a kid.
So why is it so attractive in art?
Like I would know.
Yo, Konata!
Good morning!
Er...
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
I got in trouble 'cause my cell phone bill was too high!
I rarely use my phone so I only
have to pay the monthly access charge.
Mont
Really...
Economical, isn't it?
So you say...
...but if you barely use it...
...the monthly access charge is already a waste.
Don't sweat the small stuff, Kagami.
I got a message.
Please buy eggs on the way home.
Understood.
I'll go buy some...
...on the way home...
...with Sis.
Hey.
You're talking with your parents, right?
Doesn't it end up more polite when you're using text messaging?
Well, I pretty much know what you mean.
It'll change once you get used to it.
How long have you used this?
Maybe a year.
How long before you usually replace it?
Isn't two years about right?
That's around when the battery starts dying.
I'm going to double...
No, triple that time!
Just you watch!
I don't get the point.
I take good care of my possessions.
I make them last.
You're not even using it.
Yeah...
Some people splurge on their hobbies...
...but pinch on everything else.
Sorry, Sis.
Can I borrow your world history textbook?
Again?
Geez, you're hopeless...
Here.
Be more careful next time.
I'll return it later.
Your sister's pretty careless.
She sure is.
That's why I have to be the responsible one.
But maybe it's that...
She has somebody to rely on...
...so she lets loose.
In other words, your existence allows her to be that way!
That sounds really convincing...
Hiiragi.
What time is it?
There's an alarm clock right in front of you.
There is.
A-A victim of Hiiragi's legendary morning violence!
Just to be clear...
It fell and broke.
Tsukasa.
You can read manga...
...but you should read the newspaper every once in a while.
It's good to know what's going on in the world.
Um...
Th-The newspaper's hard to read...
I can't tell where the next line starts.
Thought it might be something like that.
You there.
What is it?
Could you call Kobayakawa-san for me?
Tell her the third-year, Izumi, is here.
Y-Yes.
Kobayakawa!
A third-year, Izumi-senpai, is here!
What is it, Big Sister?
Man...
It's so fun how they're suddenly
polite when they realize you're older.
So cute.
I wish I could be tall like you, Iwasaki-san.
I wonder why there's such a big difference.
I can't say for sure...
...but it may be because I drink lots of milk.
I see!
So it's the result of your daily efforts!
No...
Life isn't so simple...
PAT
I was trying for growth of a different kind...
Since it's raining...
...we're gonna play dodgeball in the gym today.
You seem to be the type to be the
last person standing, Iwasaki-san.
Since you look strong.
I actually end up being one of the
last ones left if I'm on the near side.
Maybe it's 'cause I'm hard to hit since I'm small.
They both survive...
I'm not even that good at dodgeball.
...but for very different reasons...
I'd kinda feel bad if I hit Kobayakawa-san.
But I don't really understand it myself.
That's too bad.
We're on different teams.
Looks like we're together.
Iwasaki-san looks like she's good at sports...
...and she won't hold back so it's scary.
Head......... Out of the question
Upper Body..... A strong hit might
make her feel sick
Lower Body..... She might fall and get
hurt
But what if I let
someone else do it...
I got placed on the outer side...
...so it's okay.
That's good to hear.
Iwasaki-san's really a nice person.
So Kobayakawa-san is attacking?
And Iwasaki-san is on the inner side?
So I'm recei—
Er...
I mean defending.
I was attacked by infirmary staff...
Are you okay?
You sure are amazing, Iwasaki-san.
You hit one target after another.
Really?
Your movement and reflexes are great.
Not particularly.
Oops...
Is she mad I made a big deal about it?
No.
She's embarrassed.
Really?
That makes me feel better...
But it's hard to tell...
I see...
So she's the type that's easily misunderstood.
So people who don't really know her...
...get a different impression...
Have you gone on any trips after you got here?
I went on a pilgrimage to all the sacred places.
Sacred places?
Yes.
I visited Japan's three most sacred places.
You mean like Kamakura, Kyoto, and Nara?
No.
Akiba in Tokyo.
Nipponbashi in Osaka.
And Osu in Nagoya!
And I also visited some sites around here.
You mean like Tokyo Tower and Asakusa?
That's wrong!
Nakano...
...and Kichijoji!
Um...
What's wrong?
I think some dust got in my eyes...
Are you okay?
Tell me if it gets to be too much to bear.
I'm okay.
Good situation, isn't it?!
No!
I shouldn't look at my friends with perverted eyes!
Hello!
Hey!
Come on in!
I'll go get drinks.
So many books...
This is all we have...
So Hiyorin once had such a phase...
Kill me now...
Really, just kill me...
And this would be now.
Oh, sh—
You can tell she's improved.
You're right.
She's really good!
This picture kinda resembles Iwasaki-san.
Takarazuka Revue, huh?
Huh?
Is that me?
Is this like a fairy tale?
Please let me see it when it's done.
No!
I shouldn't draw my friends in perverted ways!
Tamura-san.
Shall we go to Maiden Road?
That was the plan.
What's Maiden Road like?
You don't know?!
Neither do I.
Good grief.
Maiden Road, huh...
Maiden Road...
...is a street west of
Sunshine 60 in Ikebukuro, Tokyo.
Maiden
Road
Many stores sell manga,
anime, and character goods.
It's as popular as Akiba in
terms of attracting hardcore fans.
However, unlike Akiba...
...the customers
are mostly female...
...which is why it was
named Maiden Road.
In other words, it's a
gathering place for fujoshi.
Fujoshi?
Written as rotten girl...
Pronounced fujoshi.
They're rotten?!
Well...
That's one way to look at it...
Y-Y'know!
The three-second-rule! The three-second-rule!
If it's under five seconds...
...there won't be any bacteria!
What?
We didn't say anything.
My beloved meatball...
What happened to the three-second-rule?
Well...
Just let me say that it depends on the situation.
SMIRK
Good lucky!
Okay!
Let's have another blast today!
We've managed to make it to the
eighteenth episode of Lucky Channel!
Okay!
You all know who the navigator is by now!
Akira Kogami!
And...
Yes!
Akira-sama's assistant...
...working hard again today...
Minoru Shiraishi!
Well, today's theme...
...is the introduction for all of the new characters...
...who have joined the regular cast!
All of them!
Too many!
First, the addition to the Izumi family...
Konata-san's cousin.
Yutaka Kobayakawa-san.
And her classmates...
Minami Iwasaki-san.
Hiyori Tamura-san.
Patricia Martin-san.
In addition!
We have Kagami-san's classmates.
Misao Kusakabe-san...
...and Ayano Minegishi-san.
It's gotten rather lively!
As you may have already noticed...
It's blocking me.
...the new characters have been appearing in the opening...
Hey.
I said that it's blocking me!
How many more characters are they going to introduce?!
It went flying!
We're on the eighteenth episode!
What happened to my appearance?!
That's right, Akira-sama.
Didn't you just make an appearance?
That adorable image of you in a raincoat and galoshes.
Yeah.
What to say...
Last week...
...I was able to talk with our guest, Anizawa-san...
...and he told me that an actor needs initiative!
And presence!
Indeed.
Your appearance today...
...brief as it was...
...was screaming to me, "Akira Kogami is here—
You sound passionate.
Hey.
Yes?
Hey!
Ah, no.
It's nothing.
Oh, no!
It's time to say goodbye.
So there you have it.
We're waiting for you to send us any
questions or comments about the show!
Hey.
Who is it?
You can direct them to our home page or the radio show!
Then bye-bee!
Turn that thing off!
Then good work!
Was it a message?
No.
No, it wasn't!
Was it a message?
N-No way!
Of course not!
Who's it from?
Uh, it was from my parents.
About what?
Well, they wanted me to go visit...
What was your reply?
Uh, you know...
Say it.
Well, basically...
I've always been looking...
...for my partner in destiny.
I'm sure you're the one.
Though I've got no proof to show.
When I see your smile...
...this ordinary life...
...magically starts to shine.
Like you cast a spell on me.
You're the one who taught me...
...the joy and suffering of love.
No matter how long the road ahead may be...
...the two of us need not fear.
I'm so very happy...
...I could spend this special day with you.
I'll protect you for eternity...
...with everything I have...
I promise you...
Okay.
Kinda screwed up on the falsetto.
Sorry.
It was touching!
Touching!
Shankya.
That's so old!
Next Episode
John Lennon
Coolest man in the world
「
」
Che Guevara
Shoot, coward...
You are only going
to kill a man
John Lennon
Coolest man in the world
「
」
Che Guevara
Shoot, coward...
You are only going
to kill a man
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Hiyori here!
Patricia here!
Reality
Patty.
Are you used to your job yet?
Yes!
Perfectly!
With Patty around...
...first-timers can probably have a fun time without being nervous.
No.
I don't handle first-timers.
Really?
I only serve people who've visited lots and paid lots!
It's store policy.
Th-That's pretty harsh...
Next time:
「To Each Her Own」
2D has Substance.
Look forward to next time!