A boat beneath a sunny sky,
Lingering onward dreamily
In an evening of July?
Children three that nestle near,
Eager eye and willing ear,
Pleased a simple tale to hear?
Long has paled that sunny sky:
Echoes fade and memories die:
Autumn frosts have slain July.
Ever drifting down the stream?
Lingering in the golden gleam?
Life, what is it but a dream?
We've got a Capital Craze again today!
What the hell are you doing?!
Try not to hit the whole area!
They're more spirited today than ever!
Damn outsider thinks this is a theme park or something.
I've just about had it with her arrogance.
Got'cha, Doc Shoko!
Hey, why are you on our channel?
See, you're giving me a chance to exercise!
Thought I'd repay you!
You're pissing me off!
Give us back the hammer first!
It's Bishamaru's!
How's it looking?
Still more after us!
Christ, man! We can't give up yet!
So, folks, will you make me another after I return this one? Yeah, right.
Where the hell is your sense of decency?!
'Scuse us!
Thanks for the food!
How nice it is to be young.
Hey there, Sis!
'Sup?
Only some boring small fries!
Shoko, send Bishamaru! Come on!
Hell will sooner freeze over! That's cracking a nut with a sledgehammer!
That hurt.
What bravado...
What's so interesting here?
So what are you doing there?
I think I know just what it is.
What is it?
Going to chase skirts so early in the morning?
Let me make it up to you now.
Will you, I wonder?
Have I ever lied to you?
Thanksies!
That's some serious perseverance.
I've seen enough.
It feels like a real festival every day.
What are you doing, you idiots?!
Over there is Yase! It's sealed off!
Give it a break, Sis.
Consider a written apology.
But it's not my fault! It's those siblings!
All right!
Watch my special move!
See you tomorrow!
You got him good!
I bet Shoko's furious.
When isn't she?
Anyway,
today we can celebrate another glorious vict—
Go home.
Welcome back.
You two are retards! Drop dead!
CAPITAL CRAZE COMIC
Hey, you listening?
Sorry for taking away your beauty sleep.
Are you going to pay attention?
No worries, man.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Think on your actions, Lady!
Do you really get it? Do you?
We heard it was a festival day so the situation may have gotten out of hand.
Yes, exactly!
Don't you lie to me!
For you people it's a festival all year round!
What?!
Dumbass! You stupid, crazy monk!
Stow it, morons!
Um, say something!
Eat him whole!
I need to go to the toilet.
Urgent?
I'm about to pee into my pants.
What did you do until now?
Hold it in.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Next time this happens you're starving for three days.
Some would call that child abuse.
Yes, it pains me too.
Oh, and whip the room into shape.
We do our best hunting them down every day.
Myoe is such a slave driver.
PlasticModel
I'm just telling you not to provoke them if you can help it.
Also, in what world is your rampant destruction "hunting"?
For how much longer will I have to put up with the cultural differences here?
Be patient until we find the rabbit.
Huh?
Good news, then. You can go home.
Take your brothers and get out of here.
Hop to it.
Food! Food! Food!
I love how you guys get along.
They can be really damn annoying, though.
No sweets before dinner!
Why the sullen face? Today the stars are looking good.
Now, aren't they in high spirits?
Evil spirits have been dispatched. I'm tired.
Hate to hear it...
is what you'd expect me to say?
Isn't this good enough? You grew close to them.
I envy you.
Want me to impart that honor on you?
No, thanks.
Don't be like that. Decisions made here are absolute.
Right?
Yeah.
I know.
No idea what to do with the crazy girl, though.
I've gone crazy from pondering that.
They're lovely! That little tomboy's so cute.
I'm expecting great things from them.
Don't paint them so demonic.
Weren't you good at handling girls like her, Myoe?
You're flattering me. I'm not even close to you, Yase-Doji.
This reminds me of that wonderful time you two fought.
You talk like you weren't a part of it, Kurama.
Professor Sarcasm speaking there.
Enough of this banter.
If she catches us we're in for another lecture.
We will meet again soon.
I can't wait! I'm so excited!
She's completely useless.
It's enough to let her fool around.
She's not a queen or something.
Why not make her one?
We're walking on dangerous terrain here.
Are you scared?
You've always been a crybaby.
Unlike you I've changed out of my baby diapers.
Just to switch them for adult ones?
No need to worry.
You are both little boys.
Leaving that aside, today is still the anniversary.
We should celebrate it.
Well then, let us pledge upon the one who came first, my siblings.
Among the three of us...
...there shall be honor...
...and no secrets.
By our great mother's and our own names,
let us follow the Ten Flawless Commandments!
We're off!
Koto!
Call me if something is wrong.
Sure.
Do you think we should pity the plucked flower?
Then again, isn't withering pitiable as well?
Miyakoi-no-Kifune has been captured.
Don't bother feigning ignorance.
You've seemed fishy all morning.
Get it out if you're up to something!
So, what are you scheming, Head Monk?
There, there, don't cry now.
When is she coming back?
I wonder. We'd have to ask.
I can't stand it!
Whenever she wants to.
You three should get along.
You'll see her soon.
Get it together!
Uncle! Uncle!
There are charms for you here.
Only tonight, not tomorrow.
Those who have faith should take one on their way home.
Light a candle as an offering.
Will you light a candle?
No money?
Nope. Only the cheats take money.
Whose shrine is this to begin with?
It's the Capital God's, the Capital's!
Frankly... I don't really know either.
Maybe someone important from long ago?
Do you know? Hey, tuck that away!
Haven't the slightest!
A safe travels deity, maybe?
I heard you can pray for anything here.
See, my grandma said...
Big ears, like this! Right?
Like a rabbit! Right?
The Capitol God? Oh, you're talking about Lady Koto!
Yeah, her memory is being lost to the ages.
You can see her at the assembly hall today.
Lady Koto, that is.
This beauty is Lady Koto.
She left this place a really freaking long time ago and hasn't come back.
Righ—
What if we can never go home?
What are you— Why would—
Yeah. No matter how you look at it, Lady Koto is the rabbit.
No!
We can't be sure yet, can we?
But this was the first black rabbit!
I wonder... Would a picture do as well?
That's it!
We'd still be stuck here.
That's why I think it's impossible.
Come on!
You two!
Be stingy and the gods get stingy too.
They say money even buys you passage out of Hell.
So this is Hell?
You didn't know?
Don't be mean, Koto. Consider the feelings of the demons here.
And saints as well.
Do you really care about going home?
Yase!
Koto! You were such a little tomboy again this morning.
You saw me?
Of course!
I'm your fan!
Don't you want to see our parents again?
Parents?
I came here for you.
I don't want to be separated from Koto.
Same as you, I guess.
What are you talking about?
Huh? What?!
You should've used this earlier.
This is boring. Ain't my style.
What's that? Do you have something in store?
A great birthday party. For you!
Koto!
What is th—
Welcome to the Assembly of Three. I greet you.
What are you two thinking?!
I told you we should celebrate it in style.
No birthday without the birthday girl!
Hey,
today isn't even my birthday.
Really?
That's not true.
Dammit.
Ever since you've come back...
...the Gion festival took place every day.
You've got this all wrong!
I didn't come back — I want to go back!
Here's the Saito newspaper right off the press!
Is Kyoto's Koto
Mirror Kyoto's
Lady Koto?!
What the hell is going on?
You don't like it?
Is Mirror Kyoto's Lady Koto Mirror Kyoto's Old Rabbit?!
Is Kyoto's Lady Koto Kyoto itself?!
What the hell?!
Is Mirror Kyoto's Koto Kyoto's Old Rabbit?!
You have got to be kidding me!
Accepted artwork
Accepted
artwork
I don't even have boobs!
You got it.
The soul is what matters.
Indeed.
All who bear wishes come here.
Your Tanabata wish has been granted: advance 5 spaces.
This is the Capital after all.
Full moon night. Ill omen of misfortune: go back 10 spaces.
Wasn't it the Mirror Capital?
Carpe diem!
You had too much fun: miss the next turn.
It is the Malice Capital.
Crazy
This is the Crazy Capital...
Sutra
The Holy Capital...
Border
The Borderlands Capital...
Kyoto... Kyoto...
I have no idea what the hell is going on!
Every joke must hold some meaning.
How is a meaningless child useful?
We would like to stake something on your childish potential.
This is some crazy game they are playing.
Looks like standard fare from Bishamaru.
Goodbye, Koto.
Hold it!
I haven't agreed to this yet.
This is not the decision of the Assembly!
Obey the rules and the one who came first! Kurama!
This is an exam according to the rules. You know that too.
Don't you want to meet Mom as well, Snakeheart?
Mom?
Now I'm tired of waiting for my turn.
I suspect your actions will lead to our reunion anyhow.
Ah  It's Sis!
Um   We can't get out.
I think you understand it, Koto.
Jesus, those idiots are going nuts.
So, what now, Inari?
I like to think I'm human.
I'm definitely not your mother.
But I can feel for you when you want to see your family.
That's why I'll play along this one time.
Don't! Don't do-
What an obstinate man.
Goddamn... Get the fuck out of my damn way, demon!
How are you going to make me, human?!
You were a big help, you know.
But I think it's not nice
to push your expectations on kids.
Moral of the story: don't trust adults.
Sorry, I'm the trusting kind!
Hold it right there!
You've gotten boring. This is stupid.
I'll stuff your mouth, demon!
Quite the fight between siblings.
Ah    Why can't she crush it?
Um   He's cheating!
A    Using cheat characters isn't fair!
Looking charming there, Princess.
You filthy human!
This is pissing me off.
Let's try this.
Ah   Do it, Koto!
Um   Aye, finish off yonder thing!
There's something I've been dying to know for a while, Myoe.
You've done nothing but complain.
Still, in the end you took care of them as if they were the crown jewels.
There are supposed to be no secrets between us, Myoe.
Which is the one you'd miss?
How do you like my special attack?
Sudden kill!
Idiot.
Idiot...
Wait, time out! Time out!
Did it all go to waste?
Is this enough for you?
Ah   Let us out!
Let's keep this a secret.
Um   Let us out!
Ah    Let us out! Let us out!
Um   Let us out! Let us out!
Feeling down, Shoko?
Stop that, it hurts!
You're such a mess.
You could never live together in peace even as children.
It's your fault you let her roam around.
But I'm happy I get to meet you again, too.
I've waited for so long!
A virus?
What you say will come to pass.
Your words are my power.
Look! Mommy's here!
Sis!
Tell me now, my Queen, my Mistress.
Your wish is my wish.
...want to...
I want to go home!
Koto!
You grew into such beauty, Princess!
And you aged, Kurama.
You're as beautiful as ever, Koto.
Thanks.
A woman kissed me! A woman kissed me!
Poor you.
You grew tall. Can you sleep in an empty bed now, Myoe?
Leave me alone...
You have so many kids.
They ain't mine!
Koto...
I'm sorry.
It looks like I misunderstood something.
Can we get along?
Come on.
I'm glad you're back, Lady Koto.
We've waited for your return.
Welcome back!
I don't really get it.
Me neither.
I'm back.
Save
Don't Save
We want to go home too. Please!
Huh?
You can't go home anymore, Koto.