oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
Happy New Year's, everyone!
We hope that
you will continue
to support us
this year
too.
A
Bag of Gold
The new year's always so quiet.
It feels fresh and new.
Saying "new" always makes it sound like a new beginning.
Kind of like a new show or a new sale.
Or like a newlywed or newbie.
They sound so innocent and pure!
Not to mention new shop designs and new games.
Makes me want to look into them.
Sometimes I can never figure out what's so new about them.
Take New York or New Orleans for example.
Heck, even the news isn't really new.
Everything's updated faster online, and there's less editorial bias.
Newborn puppies, new MLP episodes, cute newts!
Newts aren't "new".
Oh, right!
Huh? What's up, Marii? You look down.
You know damn well what's up!
"Too"? Seriously, "too"?
"Too"?
A new show on Toonami?
No!
This isn't the season to be breaking watermelons in two, you know.
Of course not!
I'll beat you too a pulp, you toothless bastard!
That's two "too"s!
And this?
Too close.
Eve's costoome.
Listen to me! That's not it at all!
Then what? What's this "too"?
Why'd I only get to say the "too" in our new year's greeting?!
Ah, the one we gave earlier?
Oh, just that?
No, it was totally un just!
But who can we rely on besides you?
That's right. Being last is a great responsibility.
I'd be so nervous, I'd end up saying "this year ooh" at the show's...
climax...
Yeah, it'd be mortifying to accidentally say "this year ooh" at the show's...
No one but you could deliver the last "too" that well, too.
Too true.
Really?
But isn't one syllable cutting it a bit thin?
What are you talking about? More doesn't necessarily mean better.
A certain someone with a two-syllable name works a lot harder than that five-syllable guy.
Yeah, that's actually a good argument.
Don't forget Jugemu, who had a very long name,
but never did anything much besides hitting other people's children.
Oh right, the Master sent us these mystery envelopes as a New Year's present.
We should each choose one.
Considering how meager the contents tend to be, they're more like envel-nopes, really.
Is that so?
It's more about just sending your regards.
The Japanese are modest, after all.
Well, I definitely wouldn't expect the Master to splurge on presents.
He said he got us something nice this year, though.
Really? Then I'll—
What are you doing?!
You go last here as well.
But whoever chooses first is better off!
Then let's decide with rock-paper-scissors.
The winner chooses first!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay then, Marii goes last.
C'mon, gimme one more chance!
Then let's do a ghostleg lottery.
Marii's number five.
That makes her last.
She heralds the end of the show like a cock crowing at dawn.
She might've been a bird in her previous life.
Anyway, let's choose our envelopes!
Wait a minute! If I choose last, I'm bound to get the worst one!
You can't say that for sure.
The thickest one might just be full of 1,000 yen bills,
and the thinnest one could have a 10,000 yen bill.
That's true.
And being the "last man standing" is associated with luck.
Okay, I'll be the last.
Okay, then I'll go first.
This thin one's gotta be a 10,000 yen bill!
Now!
That's what you get for going first!
You really think someone as stingy as the Master would give us 10,000 yen?
Then I'll go next!
If the envelope's thick, it doesn't matter what kind of bill it contains!
She's so cute!
Ah, youth...
It's full of 10,000 yen bills?!
I-I'm happy for you, Kigu.
Sure.
Um... Then I'll take this one.
B-But this one...
This is a 2000 yen bill!
You can't use these in vending machines,
and some shops won't accept them anymore either!
There are infinite possibilities!
Why are you so preoccupied with unimportant things like thickness?
Don't worry about the details. Just accept your fate.
Eeny meeny miny moe, catch a tiger by the toe!
Central Japan Railway Company
One stock certificate
This isn't a bill at all.
It's a stock certificate!
And it's for JR Central Japan!
One stock's worth like 600,000 yen!
Just how lucky can you get?
It's the last envelope!
Go for it, Marii!
It's just a few friggin' coins!
Oh?
You left that one on purpose, didn't you?!
Not all coins are low in value, you know.
There are memorial coins worth up to 100,000 yen as well.
That's an impressively low possibility.
It could be a foreign coin.
Foreign?
It could be a 500 won coin.
How much is 500 won?
At the current exchange rate, one won is about 0.08 yen.
So that'd be about 4000 yen then?
No, 40 yen.
It's that little?
But you can also use it in place of the 500 yen coin.
You can't anymore! That's a crime!
A while ago everyone was doing it.
It doesn't necessarily have to be won. It could be any coin from around the world!
Or...
It could be a key!
I win!
It's gotta be the key to some modern apartment!
That's quite a long shot, even for her.
Is she the proprietor of a Ginza club during the economic bubble or what?
How big do you think it is?
6 tatami? 8? Maybe even 10?
Don't you know any other units?
I'll bet it's the key to a dungeon.
It must be full of frightful monsters!
Scary!
Perfect!
That means there'll be all kinds of treasure hidden there too!
Of course.
A chest full of 500 won coins!
It's not gonna be in won!
Either way, I doubt there's a key in there.
A camera?
Oh, we should say something for the people watching via satellite.
Marii, you should go last.
Me again?
The last word is the one that really sticks in your memory!
Really?
Happy New Year's, everyone!
We hope that
you will continue
to support us
this year
too.
You asshole!
Marii's New Year's envelope is gone!
Marii...
No good. She's closed her heart off to the world.
I can't help but wonder what was in her envelope, though.
I think...
it really was a key after all.
The key to Marii's heart.
Don't just end the segment like that!
Won.
My name is...
Marii.
I was following a cute kitten
and ended up getting lost.
I remember a story from long ago.
A story of a city full of the dreams and wishes of children who could never grow up.
Could this be Akiha—
This is the Protector shopping street.
It's Sugamon's realm!
A
Totter
Isn't it Akiba?
I even put on a maid uniform!
Maid uniforms aren't the norm in Akiba anyway...
Look, a maid!
A maid!
You might go straight to heaven if you touch a maid!
They're maid in heaven!
Where should I touch her?
Her boobs, of course!
They're next to her heart!
Hey, stop!
A
Mongolian spot
Sugamon's buttocks
Stop it!
Why are the shops selling so much animal-related stuff?
This Fuji shirt looks lucky.
Mt Fuji
This Kannon shirt seems like it'd bless you.
Should we get it? We can only wear it around here, though.
The keywords are "auspicious", "blessing" and "only here".
We have to be careful with our words or we'll be in trouble again.
Then what should we talk about?
Health, I guess...
My shoulders are so stiff lately...
My back hurts.
Sometimes I see a pink elephant.
That's a hallucination.
This dialog drains the little energy I have.
Then how about we eat eight-eyed eels to get our vigor back?
Eight-eyed eels are so scary!
Eight-Eyed Eel
They're good for your vision, right?
Because they've got a lot of eyes?
They're not really eyes, just gill holes.
My eyes met with the soy-boiled carp's!
That reminds me of my granny who made me eat soy-boiled grasshoppers, saying it's good for the teeth.
Grasshopper
I had to eat bee larvae too.
Bee larva
That's nothing.
I had to eat soy-boiled fly larvae!
Fly larva
That creepy, slimy sight when you open the rice cooker...
Stop!
Just be quiet!
Kintarou Candy
Look, Kintarou candy!
That brings back memories.
It shows the same face no matter how much you cut off.
It's always your face no matter how much you cut off.
It's always Kukuru's face no matter how much you cut off.
Doesn't sound like sweets.
Kougan Temple
Now for today's main event, the Thorn Protector.
Once a servant swallowed a thorn,
but a charm from this temple saved her.
A
Image Charm
Tokyo
Sugamo
If you pour water on it, you can use it to cleanse a part of your body.
That's not the Thorn Protector,
but the Washer Kannon.
Really?
Many people make that mistake.
I feel tricked.
Thorn
Protector
*This  image   idol   is
withheld from public
view,   so   it   cannot
be displayed.
But now that we're here, let's just wash ourselves anyway.
Will you pour it on your eyes, Gan?
She has to pour it on her heart.
Where should she pour the water then?
Her heart, of course!
Hey, you have to pour the water on the Kannon statue, not the person!
Really?
Now even Gankyou is a bit—
What's the matter, Marii, my dear?
Marii... my dear?!
What happened to you, Gan?!
Are you kidding me, four-eyes?!
Don't be so mean, Marii.
Don't fall, Marii.
The weather's so nice today!
I'm so happy!
The Thorn Protector's blessing is truly astounding!
I'll pour it on my boobs!
My ass!
See, it bothered you...
My head!
A
The
Statute
Books
My heart.
I don't feel different.
Yeah...
Why did only Gankyou get blessed?
Get real.
You're all so naive!
A
Turtle and Ginseng
Mukian
I didn't think it'd be this much fun.
I sort of feel we didn't raise our girl power, but rather our hag power.
Oh well, they say eating soft-shelled turtle gives you softer skin.
But isn't it inevitable that we age and go all wrinkly?
Our shoulders, back and knees will start to ache...
Our vision will fog up...
That's what it means to be human.
Whatever will be, will be.
You got it.
That was very relaxing.
This is a very mature discussion.
Acting like good adults every so often is nice.
My vision just fogged up...
You've got vapor on your glasses.
Sugamo Protector's Shopping Street
Thorn Protector hall entrance
A
Bouhatei Tetora
I bought this cat because you said it'd live a thousand years,
but yesterday it died!
I see.
Yesterday must've been its thousandth birthday.
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Is It Over Yet
It's April...
It's April.
It really is April.
What are you saying?
It's M—
Take the hint!
A
April
Monday
Very lucky day
Today is the 40th of April.
Why?
If it becomes May, Kukuru will get the May blues!
Oh right! I can't believe I forgot about that.
Sure is April right now!
They're expecting me to get the May blues again.
April! April! April!
Her expression's getting darker and darker!
If this keeps up, it's just a matter of time!
What can we do to cheer her up?
Kukuru, let's play poker face!
Hey, hey, let's play poker face!
You lose if you laugh!
Th-Then how about this?
It hurts!
Still not enough?
How about this?
Watch out!
She's so close to showing symptoms!
Is there any other way to cheer her up?
Oh right, we're rakugo performers!
We're pros at making people laugh!
That's right! Let's do rakugo!
Who will?
Marii, of course!
The weather's been so nice recently!
This is the month of carefree breezes, May—
April! April!
Sure, I'm prone to depression,
but it's not like May is especially bad.
Kukuru's monthly mood
High
Low
I feel bad that they're expecting the May blues from me...
She sighed!
It's a symptom!
Wh-Who cares about the May blues?!
She said it...
Satsuki and Mei are both May kids!
So the May blues is a sickness that lets you see Totoro!
That's so nice!
They do say manga artists start to see mystical beasts as their deadlines draw close.
White crocs.
Green cats.
And the mysterious assistant who shouldn't even be there,
Yamashita.
I'm scared! I don't want to start seeing Yamashita!
I've never seen Totoro or Yamashita.
I don't even feel worse than usual in May...
May's no worse than usual?
Does that mean there's June lows and April slumps and August blues too?!
There could be, in this day and age.
People are labelling everything a sickness.
Anyway, we can't let you suffer alone!
Let's share the suffering!
I'll take the June lows!
Huh?
We should divide the monthly blues between us!
I see! Then I'll take care of the November blues!
February blues!
December blues!
All right! We've used our girl power to divide up the suffering,
but what exactly do my June lows involve?
Well, since it's the rainy season,
could it be some nasty lower-body infection?
We're still not certain that Marii isn't a cross-dressing boy,
so it's definitely possible!
It is not!
You'll just have to show your revolting crotch rot to a doctor.
I don't have any revolting crotch rot!
Well, it's June, so the damp weather might make you gloomy.
Gloomy?
Like when you're still brooding about old grudges.
They hid my shoes in grade school...
They used the corner of my eraser...
They laughed at the window shutters on my house...
They wrote the lyrics to that song by Alice on the underside of my desk...
I'll never forget them!
I think you'd be better off with the June lows.
Decided
june lows
But if I take the June lows, what about you?
That's right.
I'm so full of love I can handle anything!
Let me take the toughest one!
Which one would be the toughest?
September, maybe? That one sounds pretty hard.
Yeah. No one wants to go back to school after summer break.
It's tough.
Some people even stop going to school completely.
Decided
september blues
Why?
Ssh! Don't ask!
Eh? What am I supposed to take, then?
The other months don't seem so bad at all.
February
Chocolate
January
Snow fights
April
Hiking
March
Flower watching
August
Mountains
July
Sea
November
Baked potato
October
Halloween
You're the only one who has that much fun all year round.
December
Christmas
The only hard one sounds like the May blues,
but I'm not the kind of person who'd get that either.
You think so?
Usually, the more cheerful you are, the easier it is to get the May blues.
In that case, you'd better be careful, Marii.
Don't be stupid. I'm okay.
Ya—
Yamashita!
Let me ask, just to make sure... Yamashita isn't really there, right?
Nope.
What do you mean, Yamashita?
Does this mean I've got the May blues?!
After that day,
I would see Yamashita every now and then,
and each time it only added to my suffering.
Don't you think that's enough?
Just a little more.
A
May
Monday
Very unlucky day
She's quite adhesive.
Instead of feeling down, she seems to enjoy it.
When...
When is May gonna end?!
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
I'm Buratei Marii.
What kind of bread can't you eat even though it really is bread?
The answer is: rotten bread!
The ninth performance of Joshiraku,
Buttoufu, the Bear of Ueno, and Sleeptalk
A
Buttoufu
The Bear of Ueno
Sleeptalk
will be there for you to watch!