Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Reflection Room 1
They finally let us go...
My neck hurts after sleeping on that hard floor for so long.
Weren't we supposed to have the advantage after taking down Angel?
Why are you topless?
What the hell's with those guys?
Under First Contact Bridge - Passageway
Next time they come we'll pay them back like we usually do to Angel.
They're ordinary students so we can't.
Though it's pretty weird.
What is?
Ordinary students have never sent us to the reflection room before.
You mean Angel was keeping them in check?
Maybe.
NPC actions are generally supposed to be models for how we should act, but their emotions are exactly like any normal human.
No matter how weird someone acts, they're supposed to think it's normal.
So basically,
you're saying this shows they can go farther than that?
That would seem to be how the acting student council president is reacting.
He's more bothersome than Angel. She never turned the tables on us.
What should we do, Yurippe?
Let's take him down with sex appeal!
What kind of sex appeal do you have?
What was that? Have you seen these?
I can tell just from your shirt.
You think that's the same as touching them?
Their absolutely exquisite form?
How the hell should I know?!
How shallow-minded.
So, how should we proceed from here?
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
Time to decide, huh.
We'll experiment a little.
For now, attend classes and do whatever you want during them.
Just try not to get in the way of the ordinary students.
That's all. Dismissed.
Alright!
Otonashi-kun.
I want you to take this.
Isn't that pretty valuable equipment?
Why are you giving it to me?
Just take it.
Angel won't get in the way anymore.
Last night was proof of that.
Now the problem is the acting student council president.
What will he do if we screw around with the school?
Study Block A — Classroom
I'm so nervous...
Eating snacks in the middle of class...
I ate one!
I just ate one!
I never thought I'd ever eat snacks in class like I want to!
If it gets through, it's mine!
Too bad.
Ouch! Are you serious?
Riichi, chitoi, dora, dora, oyaman.
Dammit! It's all going to Hisako!
Just wild heaven.
Losing to a girl...
What shame!
You lot there, could you be a little quieter?
Ah, sorry about that.
Sensei!
I need the bathroom!
You again?
Go ahead.
What's she doing?
She's playing a student that needs to go to the bathroom every minute.
What an idiot.
What are we going to do?
Just sitting here's fine.
Though, look over there.
Sensei, bathroom!
Yeah, go ahead.
What an idiot.
That's enough!
Here comes Naoi Ayato-sama.
I need the bathroom!
Oh crap!
Let's beat it!
I'll be back.
What are you doing?
It seems you can't hear me.
That's fine.
Take him to the reflection room.
What the hell are you telling me to reflect on?!
You were blatantly sleeping in the middle of class,
and then you threatened an innocent student.
You've got some nerve asking that.
Quite commendable, in a way.
The hell did you say?!
Dammit, are you running away?!
Hey!
I'm right here! Come right at me!
Where do you think you're going?!
Is there really any point in keeping this up?
Main Dining Hall 3rd Floor — Rear
Whoop.
Hey...
Are you hungry?
Not really, it's not even lunch yet.
I see.
The cafeteria has this ridiculously hot Mapo tofu that no one dares order.
When I tried some, it was surprisingly good.
So yeah...
How about I... treat... you...
What are you doing?
Oh okay, let's go!
Main Dining Hall Interior
It really does look scary.
So freaking hot!
I heard you're normally supposed to eat this with rice...
Really?
"Really"? Isn't this way too hot?
Not really. It's just...
Just?
Delicious.
I see.
So it's not that you particularly like hot food, just that Mapo tofu is your favorite food?
What's wrong?
I like Mapo tofu?
Well, even if you ask me...
I never realized it.
Tachibana-san.
What are you doing at this time of day?
Can't you tell?
We're eating.
Eating during breaktime is a violation of school regulations.
I forgot.
That's right, it's a violation of school regulations...
There's no mistaking that she knew.
It's pretty scary what her favorite food can do to her!
Take them.
Dammit!
Simply eating Mapo tofu during breaktime shouldn't warrant this!
And where is this, anyway?
It's like a prison!
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey, this isn't the time to do that!
What else can we do?
Doesn't this seem strange to you?
Throwing us into this jailroom?
We're supposed to reflect on our actions, so there's no helping that.
Still!
How can you sleep in this sort of situation?
Good night.
She seriously went to sleep.
What was that sound?
An earthquake?
A battle?
They're here to save—
Oh right!
I had this!
Yuri, we're trapped!
It's broken...
Piece of trash!
...shi-kun?
Otonashi-kun?
Can you hear me?
Otonashi-kun!
I can hear you!
Hear me out and believe what I'm about to tell you, Otonashi-kun.
Listen carefully, Naoi Ayato isn't an NPC.
He has a soul.
He's a human just like us!
No way...
It makes sense.
As the former vice-president, he was supposed to be a paragon of student life.
If that were the case, he should have accepted his life and disappeared.
But I discovered that he'd been beating up ordinary students under the table.
He acted like an exemplary student publicly, but in the shadows he was doing terrible things.
That's how he maintained his balance in this world.
No way...
And when Angel lost her position, he obtained the freedom to do what he wants with this world.
I don't know what his objective is yet, but we've started battle against him.
It's a terrible fight like you've never seen.
He knows we won't harm ordinary students, so he's using them as shields and hostages.
We have no choice but to submit.
It's turned into a one-sided massacre.
Our friends are falling one after another.
I think Angel's been imprisoned somewhere.
We went to the reflection room to find her, but she wasn't there.
I think they put her in a different place, one not so easy to release her from.
And so I thought, maybe you're with her right now?
Otonashi-kun...
Get Angel out.
We need her to stop this terrible fight.
There's no time left.
Come to the grounds.
I'm heading out now too.
Be careful!
Dammit!
Why am I here at a time like this?
Wake up, Tachibana!
Help us!
My friends are in trouble!
That's a strange thing to say.
Aren't we the ones in trouble?
Yeah, I know that well enough.
But I'm sure you can do it!
Please!
Everyone's counting on you!
Guard Skill: Hand Sonic.
Can you get through the door with that?
No good, huh...
I didn't create it with offense in mind.
It's meant for self-defense.
Self-defense?
Didn't create it with...
Oh yeah!
Do you remember when we first met?
You stabbed me through the heart and killed me.
Because you asked something weird.
Yeah, but I mistook you for an enemy because of that.
I don't have my memories,
so I don't really have any reason to fight you.
If I still had my memories...
If I hadn't asked you that stupid question...
Maybe I'd be your friend in this world.
There's no one like that.
It's fine if there are, right?
There are none.
Even if there were, they'd all disappear.
I see...
Anyone who befriends her would live a normal school life and eventually disappear from this world...
I see.
It's almost funny.
That's just too sad, too pitiful...
What kind of system is this?
Hand sonic, version 2.
It's a thinner form for higher speed.
Version 3.
Inelegant, isn't it?
It's pretty cool!
But I can't open the door with this either.
Does it have any other forms?
Yes, version 4.
I tried to shape it like a flower, but maybe it looks too cute?
No, it looks pretty threatening...
That might work...
Could you try something?
Hand sonic version 2.
Version 3.
Version 4.
It'll work!
Let's hurry!
What on earth is this....
Hinata!
Are you okay? Hinata!
Running straight to me first...
Are you...
Now's not the time for jokes!
How did you get out of there?
I broke the door.
I thought I'd made it tough enough.
I order you as the acting student council president to go back.
Tachibana, you see this?
You know that this is just not right, yeah?
Hand sonic.
Are you rebelling against God?
For I am God.
Has he lost it?
Doing all this...
You fools.
Did none of you realize that this is a world that chooses its God?
I remember when I was alive.
Everyone here had a cruel life.
Why?
Because that is what gives you the right to be God.
As one who lived through such a terrible life, I also earned the right to become God.
And now I have reached that point.
And what will you do after becoming God?
Bestow eternal rest.
On us?
By massacring us?!
Only because you resisted.
You all had the right to become God, but you bound yourselves to your lives and kept struggling.
God has been decided.
And so I will bestow rest upon you.
Yuri!
What the hell do you intend to do now?!
What do you want?
You're going to rest in peace now.
You remember Iwasawa's guitar?
In her past life, she was robbed of her voice and her dream to sing.
She died miserably, with a terrible family.
But her dream was granted in this world.
And so she disappeared.
She was able to rest in peace.
And now you're going to follow her.
It'll be a nice dream.
You don't know my past!
I don't need to know.
I didn't just spend all that time preparing just to remove Angel from power.
Hypnotism.
Now, close your eyes.
You're going to enter a blissful dream now.
Even in this world, you can dream of a happy place.
No way...
No way!
That's...
Those kids...
No, this is wrong...
Don't make such happy faces!
I couldn't protect you!
I let you die one by one!
One by one...
until none of you were left!
You know,
I'm happy you're my sister!
No...
No!!
Stop that!
Don't get rid of her with some fake memory!
Our lives were real!
Not a single moment of them were fake!
Everyone lived the best they could!
We carved those memories into ourselves!
Memories of living as hard as we could!
No matter what kind they were, they're the life we led!
Erasing them in the blink of an eye like that...
Wasn't your life also real to you?!
My brother died.
We were born to a famous potter,
Sign: Naoi
my older twin brother and I.
My brother showed talent from a young age.
They proclaimed him the heir to the name.
I on the other hand, stayed in my room every day, playing alone,
living a meaningless life, getting no attention from anyone.
"The one who died was you."
That's what they told me.
Yes.
I am alive and I am my brother.
I traded places with my brother.
I was the one who died.
And then a meaningful life began.
Removed from the world to recover from the injury, my rehabilitation was strict training.
This is shameful!
Days of father yelling angrily at me.
Making garbage like this!
My training grew more and more severe.
My brother was just too far from my reach.
But I persevered to turn my life into something meaningful.
I didn't want to go back to a life of playing alone.
I won an award at an exhibition.
It was nothing compared to what my brother could have done,
but it was the best result I could have produced in my position.
What?
Are you crying?
Absurd.
Yes.
It is absurd.
Don't bring me shame!
Honestly. What are these results?
I was glad.
I thought I would stay with my father and continue my training,
and then become the best potter in Japan!
My father became bedridden.
They said there was no hope for recovery.
He couldn't spin the wheel anymore.
He couldn't teach me pottery, and he couldn't scold me anymore.
When I fed him, he would smile kindly.
All meaning to my life...
I couldn't maintain the workshop, and I couldn't be independent.
A life taking care of my father...
God!
The one who died was you.
I really was the one who died that day.
It was my brother who had worked so hard every day.
And here, I'm my brother.
It was always my brother and father.
My life was a fake.
I was not in it.
Your life was real too!
You worked hard!
You struggled as hard as you could!
Didn't you?!
Like you would know.
I know!
Because you're here too!
Then, will you acknowledge me?
What else could I acknowledge?
The one in my arms is you.
You're not here?
You're nothing but you!
They're just persimmons, you know.
Got it! I beat my brother!
What are you thinking? It's a persimmon.
But good job, Ayato.
Those were the words I wanted to hear the most.
Those words that acknowledged my existence.
Sign: Ayato
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
Monster stream.
You're finally into it?
That's stupidly huge!
Carnival of despair.
Shall we go with Tornado?
God cannot fall.
O! S!
Basically he's an idiot.
Overdrive is passive.
There'll be trouble if you make light of us!
You can regain your lost memories too.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
What do you mean?
I can't die...