Quit jokin'!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Bon, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me!
I don't want to listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
My feet feel heavy.
It's just like the first time I climbed this slope.
Kaoru-san...
Would you like this onigiri?
What? I'm fine.
I'm already stuffed.
Just eating half a bun isn't good for your health.
Then... I'll take it.
This is good.
What's in it?
Let's see...
Clams boiled in soy sauce...
I shouldn't have said that! Stupid, stupid!
Me and my big mouth!
Say, Ricchan, I can't help but notice
that you're on really good terms with Nishimi-san lately!
Tell me the truth, are you two going steady?
Y-You're mistaken!
My-my, she's blushing!
You don't have to hide it from us!
We're on your side!
No, I said you're mistaken...
U-Um...
Honestly... it's not like that.
Mukae-san and I... are just friends.
So... please don't get the wrong idea.
Crap. What did I butt in for...?
This is a surprise...
Nishimi-san, you hardly ever talk and I had you pegged as unapproachable.
For a second, I thought you were gonna' flip your lid.
M-Me too...
Hey, tell us something.
What's the trick to getting good scores on tests?
Yeah, I wanted to ask the same thing.
Oh, I don't...
Oh, we've put him on the spot...
Huh?
What do you know? I don't feel sick at all...
Hey, Bon...
Don't ignore me!
Would you just listen to me, you blockhead!?
Wow, what a pad, Yamaoka-kun!
And set apart from your house...
This is where we're gonna practice every day from now on!
Huh? Kawabuchi-kun, you look kind of glum.
Don't tell me you're having second thoughts?
Don't be stupid.
Once I decide I'm gonna do somethin', I see it through.
That's the way to be.
We better hurry up an' decide what songs we're gonna do. What's it gonna be?
Well, I wanna get the Spiders in there.
And the Ventures, of course. And then...
Hey, what about the Beatles!?
What's with all the different genres?
I think the girls will dig it more if we play a variety.
That isn't what you said before!
Ryunosuke...
We just got a roll cake.
Why don't you share it with your friends?
Mama! Don't bug us!
Ah, Okaa-sama!
We'd love to have some roll cake.
Let's discuss this over a snack, okay, Ryunosuke-kun?
Kawabuchi-kun, aren't you coming?
Nah.
I'm gonna stay here an' practice a little by myself.
Oh...
Pops...
What are you doin' wearin' a tie on a hot day like today?
Oh... I'm in mourning.
For who?
John Coltrane.
C-Coltrane died!?
You didn't know?
Well, I guess it's only natural that a rock and roller wouldn't get word of it...
Please don't bust my chops about that, Pops.
That aside, have a look in the shop.
There's a real dish in there that looks familiar.
Y-Yurika-san...?
Oh my. I haven't seen you in a while, Sentaro-kun...
I heard that you're going to be in a rock band for the school festival.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yurika-san... Chet Baker...
If you're interested, wanna hear it?
Sentaro-kun... I...
Please... don't say anythin'.
I can't...
Because... I...
W-Who's down there!?
Oh, sorry.
Didn't mean to interrupt, Sen-bou.
Jun... nii...?
Don't mind me.
Keep goin'...
Dammit! I forgot to tell him about Junichi!
Yurika-san!
Hey, Sen-bou.
Your woman forgot something.
Sen!
That packed quite a wallop...
What are you lookin' at me like that for?
You're not satisfied with one punch?
Wait, Sen.
Junichi has had kind of a breakdown...
Jun-nii-chan...?
What's wrong?
Tell me, what happened? Sentaro...
Wait, Sentaro!
Eh... now...
I'd like to decide on the members of the committee for the festival.
I'm open to volunteers or nominations...
Okay!
Then I nominate Nishimi-san and Mukae-san!
I'm sure those two would take responsibility and do a good job!
I think that's a good idea, too!
No objections here!
East High School Festival
Talent Show Sign-Up
Oh, the brass band...
Could you write down the
representatives' names and program?
Um, could I have an application form?
Here you are.
This is okay!
I'm sorry, Kaoru-san.
The new term's just begun and you've been saddled with this busy job.
Actually... since I was always transferring from school to school,
I never had the chance to take on a responsibility like this.
It's more fun than I thought.
Kaoru-san, have you talked to Sentaro recently?
No.
Then... you wouldn't know about it.
The other day at the shop, Sentaro punched Jun-nii-chan.
I didn't see it myself, and I don't know what it was about...
...but I heard Yurika-san was at the shop that day.
Could you two bring the completed applications to the student council office?
Sure. I'll do it.
Kaoru-san, stay here at the reception desk.
Sure...
Oh, Rikko, good timing.
You're on the committee, right?
Do me a favor an' copy this info onto the application, would ya?
Forget it!
The reception desk is in the materials room.
Go over there and fill out the form yourself.
I can't accept a scrap of paper.
Fill out a form.
Did they really get into a fight?
Is he taking it all on himself and suffering in silence?
Hey...
That band name.
In katakana, it shouldn't be Za,
it ought to be "Ji Olympus".
Za is fine.
No, it's not.
No, that isn't what I want to say!
Se...
Excuse me! Is there still time to sign up?
Yes.
Thank goodness!
Za -Olympus
Ji -(The) Olympus
Somewhere in my heart, there was still a little hurt and regret...
As the festival drew closer, I became busier with my committee duties,
and before I knew it, the distance between me and him had grown.
I even looked back fondly on that silly conversation.
but they seemed so long ago.
18th
School
Festival
And at last, the day of the festival arrived...
SCHOOL
FESTIVAL
Next is The Olympus!
I'm gonna go to the front!
I can't wait!
Are you ready, ladies?
1-2-3-4!
Look at him smile, say "Hey-Hey, Boy!"
Which of the girls now is he gonna chase
Kaoru-san...
After this festival is over, you two will be playing jazz at our place again, right?
Um...
You're not going to watch from inside?
Things are... awkward between me and Sentaro-kun right now.
It's my fault...
I gave in to loneliness
and betrayed him in the worst way.
What the...?
Ah, you!
You're on the committee, right? Follow me!
What happened?
The electric amps suddenly cut out!
No good...
The main electrical system's fine.
Sorry, but could you help look for the cause?
We'll split up.
Boy, what a bummer, huh?
Hey, second-year!
You can't do anythin' without electricity, so quit actin' big!
I bet you just wanted to show off your fancy shmancy electric guitars!
Rub your money in our faces!
Why don't you get off the stage!?
Th-That's not what...
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but him an' I are poor and the instruments are borrowed.
He may be a flashy guy, but he's got a real goal.
So, interruptin' just to amuse yourselves...
Won't you give it a rest, you senpai.
Kawabuchi-kun...
You're actually a nice guy.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
"Actually", huh? I'm always nice!
Ow! Y-Yes, of course, of course!
B-But I really am surprised.
I never thought you would join the band...
Yeah. I was gonna refuse at first.
But I changed my mind after Matsuoka told me he wanted to become a star
so he could support his parents and brothers.
I know how it feels, wantin' desperately to be of use to your family.
U-Um... Kawabuchi-kun, would you consider staying with the band?
Nah. This was a one-shot deal for me.
Jazz is more up my alley.
Besides...
I'm keeping my important partner waiting.
They can't fix it, huh?
Guess I'll go...
No, don't leave!
Wait! Wait!
Please!
Don't panic.
I'll keep them occupied for a little while.
You be ready to go on as soon as the problem's fixed.
What's he doing all of a sudden?
He's wearing an armband, so he must be on the committee...
This song...
Can we get it all back?
Hey, what's goin' on!?
Kawabuchi-kun...
But... it sounds totally different than it did then...
It's like two princes arguing good-naturedly as they come back home...
Bon!
What the heck!?
They're running away!?
Cool...
18th
School
Festival
My body feels light...
It's as if I've been born again...
I feel...
like I've got wings on my feet...
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.