Taroumaru, don't lick me like that!
You'll wake everyone up
if you fuss like that.
Wait, huh?
Oh, no! I'm late! I'm late!
Gotta hurry...
Let's go, Taroumaru.
Yuki
Resource room
Bedroom
Fire Hydrant
Lately, I just love going to school!
Morning!
And my favorite part is...
School Living Club
#1
"Beginning"
Made it!
Where are you going, Taroumaru?
School Living Club
In here!
Good morning, everybody!
Kurumi
Oh, good morning.
Mii-kun
Yuki-senpai, good morning.
Morning, Yuki-chan.
Rii-san
You slept in a bit this morning.
Oh, it was nothing.
That wasn't a compliment.
Don't start first thing in
the morning, Kurumi-chan.
Why do you have a shovel out this early?
You're so naive.
This weapon had the highest kill ratio
in the trenches during the first great war.
Mii-kun, what're you reading?
Please don't call me Mii-kun.
Listen to me!
Oh, yeah. Get a load of this!
She's not listening.
I almost forgot about coming to
club and nearly left to go home!
Close call.
But Megu-nee stopped me in time.
Meat Sauce
I see. You'll have to make sure to thank her.
Yeah!
Senpai, you're too forgetful.
What's wrong, senpai?
That smell...
Spaghetti!
I quit.
With meat sauce.
Rii-san, I love you!
Jeez. Get the other plates, please.
Okay!
You can't stay on the desk. Over here.
D-Don't feel bad...
Taroumaru...
Don't be naughty.
Whoa, what is it, boy?
Taroumaru's hungry, too.
Oh? Let's get your breakfast, too.
I'll help.
Taroumaru's still just a puppy...
Growl
Guess I'll lend a hand.
Wait!
Huh?
Rii-san
Kurumi-chan
Yuki
Is everyone ready?
Mii-kun
Let's dig in!
Om nom
T-Try to savor it a little.
Like Miki's doing.
Delicious.
Please don't stare at me, Senpai.
Sorry...
Yuki-chan, chew your food
thoroughly before you swallow.
R-Roger.
Delicious.
You don't have to be exactly like her.
I hate you, Senpai.
F-Forgive me, Mii-kun.
Burp
I'll practice until I get it down.
Please don't!
Yuki-chan, isn't it almost time to go?
Oh, yeah! I'm the class helper today!
Gotta run!
You didn't finish your food.
Now she's inhaling it.
What did I just say?
School Living Club
See you later!
And thanks for breakfast!
Take care.
Lately, I just love going to school!
I know it sounds weird,
but school is awesome.
The physics room has these weird devices.
The music room has beautiful instruments
and intimidating portraits.
In the communications room,
all the school's your stage!
We've got everything.
We're like our own country!
You won't find a place
this weird anywhere else.
Takeya-san.
We love school so much, we want
to live here day in and day out.
Takeya Yuki-san!
Megu-nee!
Megu-nee
That's Sakura-sensei, if you please.
Takeya-san, no running in the hallway.
How many times must I tell you?
Sorry about that...
I didn't notice you since you
don't really stand out much.
I'm class helper today,
so I've gotta run! See ya!
I don't stand out...?
And safe.
Slump
Sup, school-dweller?
Coming from the club room today?
Yup.
And yet you're barely on time every morning.
Coming in at the last second is thrilling!
Who's on duty today?
The blackboard hasn't been erased!
Teacher alert.
Okay, from today on I'll
start trying harder!
She perked up fast!
I guess that's just like you.
Class helper, lead us off.
Okay!
Stand!
Bow!
Be seated.
Zzz Zzz
She fell asleep fast, too.
Takeya-san. Takeya Yuki-san.
Morning...
We're in class!
Right, good morning, ma'am!
One more time and you're
staying after class.
Roger!
Yuki-senpai!
There.
Yuki-senpai! Hey, Yuki-senpai!
Mii-kun, we're in the middle of class!
You're one to talk.
I'm sorry.
Cute little protege you've got there.
Umm, Sensei.
I don't feel good. Can I go see the nurse?
Yes.
Thanks!
Hey, you seem fine to me!
Senpai?
You scared the heck out of me, Mii-kun.
Sorry.
And it's not Mii-kun.
Are you nervous?
Look, just because I'm an upperclassman...
I'm not nervous about anything.
I have no reason to be nervous around you.
Anyway, we've got an issue.
Taroumaru's gone missing.
Uh-oh! We gotta find him!
Yes.
Taroumaru!
Not here, either.
M-Mii-kun, they're having class!
I've been calling and calling for him,
but he won't come.
Hmm...
Well, Taroumaru doesn't like
you that much, Mii-kun.
I-I don't think he hates you or anything!
Taroumaru's a smart dog. I figure
he's probably scared of you is all.
I'm scary?
Maybe not scary, more like...
I can do this
You've got the aura of a powerful,
capable woman.
I see.
Lazy Lazy
I don't have your lazy,
lackadaisical aura...
Right!
My lazy aura...
Hey, wait a second!
I'm joking. Now let's hurry.
Oh, good.
What?
You look more relaxed now.
I told you, I wasn't nervous to begin with.
Really?
I'm just worried about Taroumaru.
I see.
Leave everything to me.
That way!
There he is!
Taroumaru!
Don't scare Mii-kun like that!
Senpai!
Lazy aura! Lazy aura!
Freeze!
Running him down won't help!
I-It's fine! That's a dead end.
Where'd he learn to do that?!
Home Economics
He's over there!
Why are you closing the door?!
We're in big trouble.
Come on.
W-Wait!
Mii-kun, they're in class!
We're from the School Living Club.
We've come to fetch our dog.
Mii-kun, he's back in the hall!
Hey, Taroumaru!
How does a dog that small climb so fast?
Taroumaru's talented.
This is no time to admire him!
Sorry.
Hurry up.
Roger!
Gotcha!
Taroumaru!
Wave Wave
Be a good boy and come here.
Okay?
What are you guys doing?
Kurumi-chan?
Zoom
Were you chasing Taroumaru?
Yup! What are you doing
up here, Kurumi-chan?
And with another shovel...
What do you mean? I'm working.
You know, with the horticulture club.
Oh... sorry.
It's fine.
It's not her fault.
My aura is the problem.
Ooh-rah?
Found him!
Okay, I've got this!
What are you gonna do with the shovel?
Don't worry. I won't use the sharp edge.
Oh, all right, then.
Wait, that's not all right!
Taroumaru!
Here, boy!
Whoosh
Hold still, you!
Taroumaru.
No stepping on the crops.
Rumble
Sweet! Nice, Rii-san!
The School Living Club charter!
Recite!
Right.
School Living Club members
not only attend classes
but live their whole lives
at school, so as to...
As to...
As to grow closer to the school's
many departments, and with them...
Foster self-governance and independence,
and set an example for all to follow.
Yes, very good.
I'm sorry.
It's fine, but you bothered the
horticulture club members a bit.
Sorry, everybody!
Sorry!
Err, sorry.
You're an upperclassman.
You need to be more responsible.
Oh, Taroumaru!
He's over there!
Take care, horticulture club!
Goodbye!
Behold, my senpai power!
This time...
She's still not in lazy mode!
Physics Lab
Not there...
Senpai!
Music Room
Broadcasting
Don't lick me like that!
Aw, nuts!
Wait...
Senpai!
School Living Club
Hardtack is so yummy.
You think?
Though, you can't just have one.
It tastes like... survival.
Now that I can agree with.
Taroumaru?
What, you want a bite of hardtack, too?
It's your fault I'm so tired.
I'm the one who's tired here.
I can't believe he can open doors.
We'll need to keep him on a leash now.
He's too talented for his own good.
Taroumaru's very sharp!
Right?
D-Don't feel bad.
Chasing down dogs during class...
This will definitely come
up at the staff meeting.
I'll have to write another apology letter.
Hey, we didn't have any
casualties, it's all good.
I'm a casualty!
I apologize.
It's fine. Just try to be more careful.
I guess Taroumaru really
wanted to go for a walk!
Who was supposed to take him yesterday?
You forgot your duty, didn't you, Senpai?
Yuki-san...
I apologize.
Apologize to Taroumaru, not me.
You're right. I'm sorry, Taroumaru.
I'll make up an excuse for why you missed
class. Just make sure to do your homework.
Okay!
What's wrong?
I don't see my backpack...
I left it in class!
She's always in such a happy mood.
Thoughtless is more like it.
I think it's nice.
Same here.
I...
Stare
What's up?
Forget something?
Not exactly...
Umm...
It's just... I love you all!
Where'd that come from?
Like how I forgot about the club
and almost left to go home,
but I didn't forget about all of you.
We know.
That was it.
I'll be off, then.
What now?
You think Senpai will be okay by herself?
Probably, yeah.
Are you going with her?
Yes.
There you are!
You all better?
You went to the nurse, right?
Playing hooky?
No fair.
No, no, Taroumaru ran off.
Who's Taroumaru?
A boy?
Well, he's not a girl...
What's he like?
Let's see...
He's got a necklace just like yours!
A choker? He's got good
fashion sense, at lease.
And this morning, he jumped on me
and tried to pull my skirt off!
He'll walk in during class
and jump up on my desk.
Sounds dangerous...
But that's what makes him so cute.
Cute?!
What the hell is this Taroumaru?!
A dog. The School Living
Club takes care of him.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
The School Living Club has everything.
Taroumaru can get anywhere.
He uses his front paws to open doors!
Are you sure Taroumaru's a dog?!
If you don't keep an eye on him,
he gets into all kinds of places!
When you're holding him,
he makes the cutest little face.
It makes me want to squeeze him so tight!
Senpai!
Oh, Mii-kun!
What's up?
Umm...
Huh? Yeah, she's in the
School Living Club, too.
Right, Miki-chan became Mii-kun.
Yeah, Mii-kun's super smart.
See you later!
Sorry about that.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Mii-kun, you seem tense.
Nervous?
Not at all.
You don't have to be on edge
just because I'm older.
I'm telling you I'm not.
What did you want?
Rii-san made me come.
She said you'd probably start talking to
people and forget about your homework.
Come on, I'm not that bad.
I'd hope not.
Oh, no! I did!
Gotcha, just kidding.
The window's open...
Next Time!!
Taroumaru's so adorable!
And smart.
He sure is.
He can open doors and slip off
his collar in an instant.
That's not good!
#2
"Memories"
Next time on Episode 2 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Memories!"