Hoplà.
All right, perfect!
Sheeeeit, we was worrying about you!
Sorry man My B
Their won't be no problem if them plays with this pace.
Guess so
You let out the sixth graders for the extension, huh?
Yeah.
We're on da same view.
We wanna to see how strong y'all really are.
I don' want to admit it, but it's the best choice
for the team, considerin ya'll niggas got hops
If you's insist that much, we have no choice but to go full throttle.
U-Um...
You say it first, Wilt
Nah man, You say it first, Larry
Y'all niggas better start talkin reall fuckin soon
D-Do your best... d-during the extension.
W-We're cheering for you, you know.
Yeah whatever
Y-Yeah.
Yo alright, everynigga gather up!
There be something I'd like ta fix before the match begins.
Aight...aight, it's a plan
Yeah, I'll call my people
Got it.
All right! Let's go full throttle!
Make sure ya don't burn out early on.
We're depend on you.
One year ago, it would have nevar
crossed my mind that we all be fightan together like this.
Oh~! I'm very happy that we's getting better and better at ape-hoop.
Let's make all dat shit a reality!
Dem things that we learned so far will be our weapons.
No matter how ya like it, ya only got 3 minutes.
Give it your all!
Sure!
Y'all niggas been waiting for dis
Let's continue from right where we left off.
Hey, do you wanna like, not hurt me this time?
Oh? How about you grow a pair?
Faggot
wh-wha? n-no, y-you too
Dirk!
Got it.
Here I go.
Kareem!
Got it.
LeBron!
Oh~!
Nice, LeBron!
Check out my tits, nigga, I'm the hottest shit around
Excuse me, but are you motivated at all?
Huh? Wha? Yeah, I am
Why so nervous, boy?
Stop pissin in the sandbox
If you wanna play with the big dogs
I'm not—
Just go home, kid
Don't hold back. Give it all ya got.
I'm goin full throttle.
Look! A distraction so I can take the ball!
do u think im like 6?
Fool me once, shame on you
Nice shot, Vick!
Atta boy!
It's a duel.
Hoplà.
Look, I'm fine.
Number 13, your accidental nip slip caused an erection.
Please, contain yourself on the bench
Fool me twice, I won't get fooled again
Isn't that a song by The Who?
Don't you dare speak band name of Roger Daltrey
She dare defile his name, I cannot forgive her.
No, really, what's the name of the band?
The...who? The hell's this son of a bitch talking about
No, I think that's the name of the band, the Who
I dunno, I don't listen to shitty Britbong bands
Yeah.
If I hit a Grand Slam, we could win the Stanley Cup
I can't mess up the trajectory
And going by the angle of the moon and the sun
I'll need ~1.7 niggawatts of power to make it
Hey good job Dirk!
Dirk sure is good at basketball!
Yeah!
Wow Dirk is a girl!
This is the Fire Works.
But not only Dirk has grown.
I'm on defense duty at Eminem's school o' hoops,
so I'm not going to let you go no further.
Dirk!
Everyone knows how much LeBron-chon is striving.
She's showing off her badonkadonk in hopes of finding a mate
Kareem!
We done worked so hard and now reach up to here.
I ain't not stepping back, not even an foot.
Prismatic Bud.
Her boobies are rectangular!
Hell yeah, Kareem!
Ain't they getting gooder and gooder?
Listen up, make sure to light them up!
Arty can't hit them unless you do your job!
Okay.
She'll hit them from afar with a HE shell
She's Ice Age, LeBron's Ballin' Academy's key member.
Here.
Not less from what expect from Eminem's School O' Hoopi;
they're shooting no matter the distance
It's a real competition, huh?
They goin' full throttle
But we're not exactly losing, either.
Besides, there's an ace in LeBron's Ballin' Academy
I'll leave it to you, Kobe!!
You aint nevar gettin past me
lol
Don't laugh at me!
Haha, oh god I'm sorry, but you're fly's open
If I, by any chance, hadn't met
the people from LeBron's Ballin' Academy,
I'd still be out inna street sucking dick for cheeseburgers
So,uh, thanks
Well...
I still\i0} suck dick for cheeseburgers
I'm going full throttle, so I hope you'll lose.
no u
Because it's not just me who wants to win this match.
I know it since I'm one with the team.
Amazing! You're amazing, Kobe!
Kobe, you're my Shitty Gift; an irreplaceable treasure!
Eli, here!
Drew Brees-Sempai!
Only thirty seconds left.
Clutch time.
LeBron!
Chris!
Kareem!
I will fight with full power, as a member of Eminem's School o' Hoop
I'm absolutely not going to
fumble this one!
Since we need to be connected...
for the last shot.
Kobe!
Go, Go Kobe Ranger!
I won't let you secure the victory!
She came back from such a distance?!
Eminem's School o' Hoops isn't going to lose like this!
Not counting.
50-9001; Eminem's School o' Hoops Wins
You did it, Wow!
How great!
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry I didn't make it in time.
nah it's cool
It was fun!
Yeah!
Oh~, true, true.
Hey...
Um... well...
It was fun!
It was fun for me, too...
but I want to get an overall win,
so let's play basketball in middle school again, Kobe!
Yeah. I also want to play a match against you again.
I'll leave it to you, Anne!
Okay. I'll take responsibility and see them off.
It's annoying but the sixth graders were pret-ty good
Yeah. We need to work harder.
I wonder if we can do that.
Yeah nah, probably not
Sooner or later.
TL Note: Oui means I surrender in Frog
Oui. We will succeed.
Could we talk about that matter?
Yes.
Um, what about Charles Barkley?
I dunno, I'll probably end up blowing him
Thanks.
I can't create the same bond those girls did...
Sorry I couldn't let you win yet again.
Whatchou talkin about?
Oh~, s'all good in the hood, brotha
You always be givin us da support we need
We done did our best out there, no doubtin that
S'just that Eminem's School o' Hoops is OP as fuck
I know, but this's out last game 2gether
Damn shame you had to lead us into defeat
Besides...
Besides, dis ain't the end
We gon' be playin ape-hoop in Middle School, then I'll drop out
and go to the NBA and play with all mah niggas
Then fuck a supermodel and contract chlamydia!
Oh~, we'll make you so satisfied by sharing STD's
Even in middle school and in high school...
You'll always be our coach.
Everyone...
Damn. Why is everyone crying?
The sun's in my eyes!
The wind took it!
Oh~, these r tears of joy
I wonder why.
I also...
I also think that we'll be connected through ape-hoop
As long as there's ape-hoop
Oh come over here you nigger!
Big Brotha!
ooga booga!
soz 4 makin you come
Nah it's cool, mang
Kobe?
There's a little something I wanted
to ask you once the match was over.
Whoa!
What are these?
Each star is a fallen brother
I hope I get to be up there some day
I'm glad you remember it.
Um, which stars are you looking for?
Which one's Trayvon?
Shit, I mean Tray-gone
Our fallen brother
May he be in Heaven
Half an hour before
the racist cracka ass police
and the horridly obese man, George Zimmerman
take his sweet, innocent life
No mercy was had that day
Our sweet jolly todder-like Trayvon was ripped from our hands
Flashes of MLK Junior and a thousand slaves been whipped
went through baby Trayvon's mind
And a chorus of angel were heard as he ascended into heaven
May we all take a lesson from that incident
TL Note: 5 is more den 4
and nevar 5get the tragedies
bb i don't have any idea what the HECK ur talkin about
but how bout you swing your rear by my place
and we go to town on baby makin'
Okay.
Kobe, you're the best.
It's morning, Charles!
Wow you're so fucking cute god damn!
Good morning!
Damn shawty you be lookin' fine this mornin!
Thanks dad
I;s hoping to show it to you before anyone else.
It looks really good on you. You're really fuggin cute
Thanks dad
I see. So Kobe and the otheres are one parole again
It really makes me think...
My Kareem...in jail!
Well, we can't stand in one place, either.
That's right, Charles!
The male basketball club has been revived.
We can meet starting next week.
Sheeeeeeeeeeeit really?
Yeah dawg, 4 realz
But why?
I've gathered signatures and handed in an application to the student council during the break.
I'm the vice president starting this year!
Hey, that's great!
THANKS OBAMA!
Now, since that's settled, let's practice!
Yeah!
I hope that you'll leave this building today and remember our great Lord and Savior Biggie Smalls. His spirit lives one in each and every one of us.
God bless his soul, and yours too
All right! We're playing today, too!
Oh, you're pretty enthusiastic, huh?
It'll be our first time playing basketball in middle school.
Oh~, eight grade's over!
I'm looking forward to it.
The first time, huh?
I remember my first time, it really hurt
Come to think of it, why did you start playing, Kobe?
Huh?
Momma said food stamps aren't enuf
Actually, my mother—
Kobe! Charles Barkley!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Okay!
And she even said we'd be playing with balls more...
Mom's an asshole!
It's empty...perfect.
Alright! Only eight thousand five hundred sixy two left!
Ay bitch...you lookin at me?
just fug off b4 i pop a cap in your tight, scrawny ass
Basketball?
Yeah. Basketball.
Amazing!
It's a sport where a bunch of slaves run around
The team throwing in the most wins.
Can I also play basketball?
Are you a nigger?
I thought so
nig...ger?