Mario...
If it weren't for you guys, Mario wouldn't have been released.
Everything's on the house tonight.
Drink as much as you like.
Yeah!
Man, he's such a tough cookie.
At least we got that settled for now.
It isn't over yet.
Haven't you forgotten something, Turtle?
What?
Women, man! Women!
Introduce me to some women!
A-All right!
I get it, so calm down!
I see, I see.
Don't worry.
Well, miss, can you find him someone cute?
Sure thing.
See ya.
And good luck, Uncovered.
Hey, isn't this place...
You gotta get to know a woman first.
Learn here and get some experience.
Got it?
Mister, come right in.
Sorry to make you wait.
R-Right...
Now, should we begin, Mister?
Turtle!
Gramps, seconds on the noodles!
Coming right up!
What's up?
You showed up out of nowhere, Mario.
Oh, I know!
Are you here to take me to a movie?
Who am I kidding?
You don't like movies.
Hey...
You've heard from Joe, right?
I'm... getting married.
I'm sorry.
I meant to tell you.
The man I'm with is really nice,
and he cherishes me.
I think I can get by with him by my side.
I'm going to be happy—
As the rain started to pour,
Mario couldn't suppress his feelings.
"I love you."
"I won't let you go."
"I won't lose you to anyone."
His young heart was bursting.
It's already been eighteen months,
but I can't forget about him.
Yet, I'm going to marry.
You can't do that, Mario.
You can't choose a woman like me.
You just can't.
It doesn't matter.
I love you.
I can't think about anything else.
Setsuko's tears flowed because she knew...
that the blinding love she shared with Mario...
was like a unique, bright firework that would never rise again.
Thanks for the meal!
Man, it's pouring.
Hey, Turtle.
U-Uncovered...
Sorry about that.
Don't get so mad.
Are you kidding me?
I almost did it with that granny!
All right, I get it.
I'll take you to a proper place next—
What was that for?
You two are completely soaked.
Well, why don't you play with me?
Turtle, cash.
Cash, man! Cash!
I'm gonna be a man this time!
I'm sorry.
You're so young.
Setsuko?
Setsuko!
Where are you, Setsuko?
You sure about this, Mario?
Isn't Setsuko getting married today?
Yeah.
I guess I'll go show my face there.
That's all?
That's all you're going to do?
Mario...
What a beautiful bride.
Truly.
Her parents look quite happy.
Well, of course, they're proud that their daughter's getting married.
Setsuko, you like Bro, don't you?
I can tell just from watching you.
I want you to welcome him.
Bro... died.
I love you.
I can't think about anything else.
Farewell, Setsuko.
Cheers!
Okay, let's drink till we drop in celebration of Setsuko's happiness!
Is he okay?
I dunno.
All right!
Then let's drink because I've become a real man!
Congratulations!
Cheers!
Though he did it with a pro.
Shut up!
They're all women, man!
See ya, Mario!
Yeah.
I drank too much.
It's freezing.
Tokyo?
So, are you going?
Yeah.
Really?!
A friend of mine is opening up a store in Shibuya,
and he's looking for a good bartender.
But...
Don't worry about this place.
You're still young.
Go hone your skills in Tokyo.
Tokyo...
Turtle and Joe both work in Tokyo.
I see.
You're leaving too.
What's wrong?
Gonna feel lonely without anyone to play with?
Yeah.
Then come to Tokyo with me.
You're not working, anyway.
That's it!
I can totally do that!
Thank you for coming!
Hey, Yokosuka!
Bring some sake!
Coming!
Man, you're so useless.
We're all tired after performing on stage.
You should've prepared some sake before we finished.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
Don't say that, Charlie.
By the way, Yokosuka...
can you change the strings on my guitar?
Sure thing.
Go buy me some cigarettes, too.
Okay!
"No matter how much they exploit me, I can take it."
"I'm going to become a singer."
Just as a caterpillar turns into a butterfly,
Joe knew that this was the only way a disciplinary school grad could become famous.
Great work on stage today.
Have a good night.
All right, I can still make it.
Ow!
Sorry.
Turtle!
That hurt.
Where are you rushing off to, Joe?
I'm going to a jazz café in Akasaka.
Wanna come?
What the hell, Joe?
Aren't we here to drink?
I can't learn anything as just a gofer for that band.
I need to see other bands and performers...
or I won't be able to be a star.
The vocalist's not here?!
I'm sorry, I can't reach him.
Are you kidding me?!
We're up next!
How are we gonna do anything without a vocalist?!
Go find him, right now!
Excuse me.
If you'd like...
I can lend you my vocalist.
If you don't mind, I could sing for you.
I'm Yokosuka Joe, and I'm an assistant for Five Lemons.
I could do a couple of songs before your vocalist arrives.
Who's that?
Who is that boy?
I don't know.
Joe...
It's finally here.
This is my chance.
Hey...
You're gonna sing that song on a big stage one day, right?
Good luck, Joe.
Let's start this party!
Get everyone in on it too!
In this morning full of dreams,
don't look so blue.
Set yourself free and dance!
This party's free and easy, so let's rock tonight!
He's freaking good!
Is he really just an assistant?
You're kidding.
He got these customers screaming for him already!
Scream your soul out tonight!
Raise your voice!
"Yes!"
"The crowd is watching me,
listening to me."
"It's a one-in-a-hundred chance for a disciplinary school guy like me,
so I'll put my life on the line for this opportunity."
Joe sang to take his first step towards stardom.
Good morning!
Um...
Is something wrong?
What's wrong, Yokosuka?
It's too early to sleep just yet!
It's a million years too soon for you be on stage when you're just a gofer!
And that band's our fucking rival!
I-I'm sorry.
Man, give me a break.
Hey, let's go.
Sorry, but you guys go ahead.
Sure thing.
Do whatever you want, Mickey.
Hey, wipe the blood off.
So, how was it yesterday?
How was the stage?
That was your first time on stage, right?
I heard people liked you.
Everyone in front of you is bewitched and looking at you.
They're all listening to you.
I love that moment.
It feels so great. That's why I'm a vocalist.
Didn't it feel great?
Yes.
Hey, Yokosuka.
Have you ever drunk mercury?
Did you know?
You'll lose your voice if you drink mercury.
You know...
I hate it.
I hate it when I'm not the one getting the attention.
So please, Yokosuka,
don't get in my way.
I'm the vocalist.
If you try to steal my place,
I'll have to take away your voice.
I...
I won't... ever sing again.
It looks like they beat you hard.
You shouldn't be rotting away in that second-rate band.
Joe, I can turn you into a big star.
Three months.
In three months, you can be a star.
You just need to do what I say.
Trust me.
Okay?
Meg...
We have no relatives.
Our only option is to be used by others.
You're right, Meg.
Our parents abandoned us,
and this is the only way we can survive.
I'm ready for anything.
Joe.
Okay.
"If I can be a star, I'll take it for three months or even six months."
"This is the only way that we siblings can attain happiness."
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Joe gets an opportunity.
Turtle rejoices.
Joe must break all ties with his friends.