He came to visit me sometimes...until recently.
Long time no see, Kida Masaomi.
What is this?!
They disappeared after an altercation with another gang.
And you can't just go ask Orihara Izaya, can you?
You dragged me back into this...
Damn it.
Damn it!
So, your friend was hospitalized?
Who'd you hear that from?
I saw it from my window.
You came to visit every day.
So, your friend's a girl, right?
She has a nice body and wears glasses; that lack
of balance makes her an attractive high schooler.
Do you like her?
Yeah. I'm smack dab in the middle of
a love triangle involving her and my friend.
It'd be a love square if you included me.
We're done, finished, canceled, closed up.
Right?
Then why do you keep visiting me?
Have you decided you want to return to how things were?
Sorry, I'm going home.
You'll come back, Masaomi.
I mean, you always do.
So I'm fine no matter how many girls you fall in love with.
In the end, you'll show a much stronger
love toward me than any of them.
I didn't have to listen to know what she was going to say.
She always repeats the same thing;
that I'll return to her no matter how many girls I date.
And, more so than any of them, you'll love me on a much higher level.
However, I didn't want to hear the words that would come next.
I mean, that's what Izaya said.
I succumb to the illusion that I'm God when I look
at it like this, which feels pretty good, you know.
Three-way fights are great.
Moreover, all three leaders are friends with each other.
God attack!
The sweeter the honeymoon, the higher the flames
of despair rise when it all comes crashing down.
Look! The pawns are like garbage!
Now, what do the cards say about the non-pawns?
Kadota's group, Shinra, Simon...
Umm...I guess Shizu-chan's the king after all.
Celty's the queen, I suppose.
Then who's the joker...
Meh, whatever.
This has gotten fun, hasn't it?
You think so too, right?
I heard that she didn't die.
How fortunate.
It'll all work out as long as she's alive.
Izaya...
You're pretty smart;
you understand that you're the reason she ended up like that.
It's laudable that you haven't succumbed
to your emotions and tried to punch me—
Bingo.
It's only natural that you'd channel your anger towards me.
Since I was obviously trying to insult you.
So, she's unconscious?
I hope she wakes up.
Or maybe you hope that she'll never come out of it.
What are you trying to say...?!
You know....
You're scared, aren't you?
You figure that if she wakes up,
she'll blame you for the rest of your life.
But, let's assume that she dies.
Wouldn't you feel guilty for the rest of your life that you killed her?
In other words, your feelings of guilt are
meaningless whether she lives or dies.
You can't run away.
The past will be only too happy to chase you—
In absolute, complete, and total earnest.
Do you know why?
Because it's lonely.
The past and memories get lonely easily.
I don't believe in God.
Because he doesn't have a fixed form.
The past certainly does exist, even in a world
where the future doesn't have a fixed form.
Even if it's been colored by misunderstandings and delusions,
a person's past can't be anything but
the truth as long as he believes in it.
If that's what you base your actions...or your way of life on,
isn't that like being a deity?
I don't understand what you're trying to say at all!
Yeah, you do...
You can't run from her anymore.
Your feelings of guilt towards her will become
your past, and she'll become a deity to you.
Well, that should be fine, right?
Since you like her...
I see you've recovered wonderfully, Anri!
That's great; Anri and her eros are safe!
"Eros" is going too far, Masaomi.
But I'm really glad you're okay. I really am.
Uh, umm...thanks, you two.
You don't have to thank me.
I'm happy as long as you and your eros are okay!
The same for me—except for the eros thing.
Hello?
I see.
Got it.
I'll be right there.
Sorry! Something just came up with my friend!
Oh, really?
If you want to hate someone, hate my friend to your heart's content!
Hate doesn't cost anything, and it doesn't cause me any harm!
It's a perfect "two birds with one
stone," it's "many wives for one man!"
"Many wives for one man?"
See you tomorrow!
I wonder if it's really that important?
Don't you think Kida's been acting strange lately?
Really?
You're sure it's not all in your head?
I've never told Mikado about my
involvement in the Yellow Scarves.
Where he is and this place are both realities to me...
But I feel like an incredible distance separates them...
We fought every day.
We'd stay connected to each other only if we continued to fight.
I wanted someone to affirm my existence.
It was then...that I first met Saki.
That yellow cloth looks really nice.
Huh?
You're much cooler than the rumors make you out to be, Kida Masaomi.
What?
How do you know my name?
Do you have ESP?
Are you Itou the ESP user?
If you really can read people's minds like that, I'm going
to put you in my bag and take you home with me!
Oh, you... That's just too weird!
But, it's not me. Someone else has ESP.
Eh? Who is it?
There's a girl with ESP here?
Anyway, he's an amazing person.
He knows everything.
It was also the time...I met someone I didn't want to.
Hey, nice to meet you. You're Kida Masaomi, right?
And who might you be?
I'm Orihara Izaya, an information dealer.
This girl's something like my disciple.
I'm not her boyfriend or anything, so don't worry.
I hope we get along.
Shogun!
I told you to just call me Kida Masaomi, not "shogun."
B-But, "Kida" still sounds kind of...
We don't know anything about the Dollars.
We have some members who used to be a part
of them, but no one knows who's at the top.
They couldn't identify who it was during
their first gathering six months ago...
Are they planning on making a move?
Apparently their leader issued a statement
saying he wanted information on the Slasher.
So, I guess it wasn't true that the Slasher is part of the Dollars.
Even so, something about this is definitely fishy.
Anything else?
Well, Horada got attacked by the black biker, but...
Who's Horada?
It was a while ago, but the black biker attacked us while we
were making fun of some weird guy for wearing a white gas mask...
The black biker...?
Yeah, it was covered with something
that looked like black oil or whatnot...
Just who is this black biker...?
There's a rumor that it's involved with the Dollars...
Well, whatever...
By the way, you guys are older than us, aren't you?
Y-Yeah, well...
Don't drag in any more adults.
We're done for once we have people's names
getting out like Mr. Whoever from Whatever Group.
We're just little brats!
No matter how many of us there are, we can't win
against adults, and we're done for if we get used by them!
Just like...Orihara Izaya used me...
Stop it!
Hey!
Whenever I was even the least bit troubled,
Saki would always say, "Just ask Izaya."
We'd ask for his opinion on certain things.
I made it so that you both benefit...
Everyone thought he was annoying at first, but
things actually went well when we did what he said.
I didn't believe him.
I figured I wouldn't get any closer to him than need be.
Izaya's really amazing.
He knows everything and he's never wrong.
So, would you die if he told you to?
Probably...
I took pity on her.
I wanted to release her from Izaya's bonds.
I wonder if we can say that we're dating?
I wonder...
So, why do you hang out with me?
Because I like you.
Did that Izaya guy tell you to like me or something?
Yeah. Only at first, though.
Izaya doesn't interfere with people's love lives.
So, why do you still like me?
Because you're cool.
No, maybe it's because you're cute?
What about you?
Do you like me?
I guess I'd like you if you stopped your zealous devotion to that guy.
I can't help that.
It'd be nice if you'd overlook at least one of my faults.
You know your own faults?
I guess.
Although I don't plan on fixing them.
If you have a fault, you should fix it.
I'll even help you.
And so, we started dating.
When I was dating Saki, there was no one to keep me in check.
I was serious, and the Yellow Scarves were even
more serious when it came to fighting the Blue Squares.
They fought dirty.
They'd attack small groups with large ones,
and they'd lay traps so they could win fights.
They injured over one hundred of my compatriots.
Everyone was scared.
And so was I.
I was scared that I'd have to disband the Yellow
Scarves and lose my sense of belonging.
So...
You should ask Izaya about it.
I relied on someone.
On him...out of fear...
Welcome!
I kept telling myself it was for my friends' sakes.
Let's take our time talking about it.
His information changed the Yellow Scarves drastically.
It wasn't just information about the Blue Squares...
He even gave us specific information on how to fight.
Our position as the weaker party was quickly reversed.
Izaya, you truly are amazing!
At some point, I'd lost my apprehension about him.
Moreover, we were winning...
I enjoyed our victories.
But...
Kiiiiida Masaomi?
Who's this?
It is nice to meet you.
I'm Izumii, the leader of the Blue Squares!
We're holding a trivia tournament today!
Question one: we've asked a special guest to join us; whoever could it be?
Here's a hint; this person's very, very, very, very important to you!
Hey!
Time's up! Or so I'd like to say, but an image
of someone flitted across your mind, didn't it?
Then bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo!
What have you... What have you done with Saki?!
Question two: What could your precious
girlfriend possibly look like at this moment?
Question three:
That was the sound of what bone breaking?
Here's a hint: I don't think she'll be walking any time soon!
Last question: If you don't come to the parking garage
where you trapped us last time within the next 20 minutes,
what in the world will become of this girl?
I regretted it.
I'd been naïve.
No matter if I said, "We were still middle schoolers,"
Or, "This is just the continuation of a backyard brawl,"
It wasn't.
This was war.
Moreover, I was the one who started it.
Pick up!
Please, pick up...
The person you have dialed—
What the hell?! Damn it!
Izumii, the girl passed out.
How boring.
We just broke one of her bones in a couple of places...
I ran.
All I could do was go there.
I'd go there...and kill everyone who made Saki scream like that!
The person...
That's why we're going to knock the
leader of the Yellow Scarves down a notch.
I told you I'm not taking part in this.
C'mon now, I heard we kidnapped his girlfriend.
She's just a kid, but she's still pretty womanly!
You can have some fun with that, right?
You kidnapped her?
Alright, I'll head out right now.
I knew it! I knew this—
Tell this to Izumii when you wake up:
"So long, you bastard."
I couldn't move anymore.
What I'd felt earlier had just disappeared.
Why did my feet freeze in place...even
though I knew Saki was in danger?
Why...?
Why am I so scared?
I thought I could do anything if it were for Saki's sake...!
I was a powerless...middle schooler.
Won't she die at this rate?
Not like we care, though.
She's not bleeding, so she should be fine.
Hello!
Well, well, well—
Whoa, so you really did kidnap her!
Oh, it's just you, Yumasaki? Where's Kadota?
In reality, this girl would end up in
pieces, unlike in the movies or manga.
That got me thinking.
Huh?
I believe that if a hero were to appear and save
her, just maybe the world would turn into 2D,
and I'd become a superpower-wielding world savior,
and I'd be all over the girls like, "Oh my,
tee hee," and, "honk honk, heh heh heh."
And so, to realize my dream, here we go!
He's still as weird as ever.
And so, it's time to implement my "let's turn reality
into a happy ending for a 2D heroic story" plan!
Hurry!
Kadota, you asshole!
We probably shouldn't move her too much.
We should get her to a hospital fast.
Are you two really okay with this?
We follow you, Kadota, so we won't have any
lingering attachments to the Blue Squares.
Honestly, I'm not good at dealing
with people like Izumii and Horada.
They're always like, "I second that."
It would've been cooler if you'd thrown it out the window.
I don't like littering.
Saki finally woke up.
Thanks to her testimony, Izumii was arrested, and
the weakened Blue Squares were forced to disband.
Hey.
Huh?
You're Kida from the Yellow Scarves, right?
Um, who are you...?
How should I explain...
My name's Kadota.
Ah, I just heard that you betrayed your gang to save Saki.
Um...thank you very much.
Well, we're on our way back from visiting her,
but she said you haven't come to her room yet?
That's none of your concern, is it?
She asked us to tell you something.
She can see this whole area from her room.
She says, "Thanks for always coming to visit me."
I told her that you were held up by the
Blue Squares and got there a little too late.
She wasn't mad at you or anything.
See you.
Why...?
Why did you tell her that?
When did I ever tell you to do that?!
I would've told her the same thing even if you'd said not to.
You know, don't you?!
That I...ran away...
My legs froze up...and I couldn't move...
Yeah, I know.
By the way, you're still running from her.
Are you telling me...to lie to her?!
Even though I abandoned her and ran away?!
Hey, don't get carried away.
If you remember the guilt you felt at running away,
then at least bear the discomfort that comes
with lying to her for the rest of your life.
That'll be your atonement.
If you still don't want to lie to her,
then face her head on and don't run away!
I'll forgive you for running from your past.
However...
At least don't run from the present or the future!
Oh? Did you just say something cool, Kadota?
That was awesome! I'm going to
call you Poey the poet from now on...
In the end, I just couldn't do it.
I tried. I went there numerous times...
To simply tell her, "Let's break up."
But I couldn't do it.
I left the Yellow Scarves.
Have you already decided on a high school, Kida?
I'm going to take the exams for Raira Academy, since it's close.
I kept typing words in praise of Raira Academy.
I was lonely.
When I talked to Mikado, I felt at ease.
You should...
Come too.
And so, I reunited with Mikado.
I also met Anri.
I thought that my peaceful life as a high schooler would continue.
And yet...
Damn it!
You...You dragged me back into this.
I had absolutely no intention of returning.
You can't run from her anymore.
Your feelings of guilt towards her will become
your past, and she'll become a deity to you.
He was right.
That's why I'm here.
I'll defeat the Slasher, who hurt Anri and my friends.
I'll defeat the Dollars if the Slasher's with them.
I won't freeze up any longer.
This time, I'll definitely...
Who's there?!
What's wrong?
A girl was spying on us!
Someone's chasing her as we speak!
A girl?
Maybe she's with the Dollars!
I want to talk with her. Don't be too rough with her.
Yes, sir!
I'll go this way!
I shouldn't have been hesitant at all...
That's why I returned. That's it...
Yet, why...
Why is anxiety rippling throughout my body?
Why...?
Why...is Kida...?
The girl runs.
She runs as fast as she can...
...to escape the shadow that's chasing her,
to escape the horrible truth she's discovered.
Next Time: The Blue Dynasty is Dead.