What's this? Just scenery?
Hey, ain't this the beach we're on now?
Looks like it.
Shinpei!
Or Mio? Or maybe a completely different person?
Whatever, I'll just talk like yer Shinpei.
Shinpei, if yer watchin' this,
that means I'm dead.
Ya just wanted to say that cliched line, didn't ya?
Y'seen right through me.
Well, duh, I know myself!
Oh, get over here!
Let's get in the video together.
Wha—
Is this good?
Maybe a little to the left?
Ushio and her Shadow are together?
What in the world is she doin'?
Shinpei.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to tell ya.
Only me 'n' my Shadow can unlock this phone.
Which is why my Shadow should be next to ya right now.
Oh! Can ya tell which one's me?
Hey! I'm talkin' here!
Gotta be the left. Or is it the right?
I'm me.
No, I'm me!
I'm me!
Th-They sure get along.
No, no, no. I'm me!
It don't matter!
We're both me.
Huh?
I'm sure you figured it out by now,
but she ain't evil like the other Shadows, so don't worry.
She's yer ally, Shinpei. I guarantee it.
Ya can ask my Shadow the details later.
But I wanted to leave ya a message directly with my own words.
That's why I'm recording this video.
Where do I start?
Right. Everything started with Shiori.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
July 17th
It weren't nothin' as harmless as a look-alike!
I was walkin' home 'n' it felt like someone was followin' me!
Flow, My Tears
That's just some creepo!
Be careful. Did ya tell Totsumura?
Totsumura ain't no help! 'Sides, it had to be her!
Hey, Sis, is this the cream for Dad's athlete's foot?
Yep, that's the one.
Ya never take me seriously!
I'm gonna charge ya double!
What's up? Whatcha talkin' about?
Forget it! Thanks fer shoppin'.
July 18th
Lookit that, Mio.
Who are ya?
Ah! Stop!
She ran.
A Shadow...
It weren't nothin' as harm—
The Shadow?
Yeah. I'm gonna dig into this look-alike of yers.
Huh? Ya finally believe me?
Yup! So no need to worry anymore.
The Omoto Beach clean-up is now finished!
Thanks to y'all's help, the beach is clean and we can reopen it tomorrow!
The trash we gathered today will be burnt in our next Omiokuri ritual.
All right, everyone, I'll see y'all on the 24th for the summer festival!
Bistro Kofune
Rock, paper, scissors!
One, two, shoot!
Yay! I'm goin' first!
Hey, Sis.
Ya think Shin will come back this summer?
Huh?
He can stay in Tokyo the rest of his life for all I care!
Don't gimme that. Ya love him.
Ya love Shin, don't ya, Sis?
Wha—
As if!
Hey!
Move! I'm takin' a bath first! You little—
Oh, Sis...
I wonder what you're up to nowadays, Shinpei.
What am I thinkin'? Who cares about him—
Welcome home.
Mio—
Who the hell are ya?!
Yer not even tryin' ta listen, are ya?
Did ya follow me from Omoto Beach?
I'm Kofune Ushio!
What's wrong with goin' back to my own house?
Th-Then why were ya hidin' in here?
That's 'cause I saw ya with Mio.
Do ya...
know about the Shadows?
What?
Yer the Shadow!
What? The heck's goin' on here?
Hold on a sec.
If Shadows really exist, then...
That must mean Shiori's Shadow is somewhere on this island too!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Shiori said the first time she saw a Shadow was on Mt. Takanosu, right?
We need to get to the bottom of this.
Fine. I'll just deal with ya later, then.
Why are ya followin' me?
Yer the one followin' me.
I promised Shiori that she wouldn't hafta worry about no Shadows no more.
Make any funny moves, and yer deader 'n dead!
Got that?
Ain't no leads 'round here, huh?
And we're outta time fer today.
Gotta head down before it gets too dark.
C'mere!
Keep out
Look.
There's a path up ahead.
Don't that sign make ya wanna go in some more?
Ya totally get me!
I see!
This is Sou's family's old clinic!
Hishigata Clinic
The old clinic has been rumored to be haunted for as long as I can remember.
All the islanders are too scared to come near it.
Eek, scary!
Ghosts are the one thing I can't stand.
Yew too, huh?
Ya sure don't look scared ta me.
Are ya really gonna go inside?
Ain't ya scared?
I am, but it's weird...
Reception
Pharmacy
I feel like I've been here before.
Wh-Who was that?
Someone out there?
Th-This is a Shadow?
Its face—That's my face!
Look out!
The heck was that?
Lemme go! Dammit!
What is this?!
Damn it!
Let go of her!
Ya! Damn! Monster!
What's goin' on? It didn't stab my leg, so how?
Oh, I get it.
I see! So a Shadow's weakness is...
Yeah, I got it.
My body just gave me a pretty clear answer.
I'm...
not human!
Yer not gettin' away!
My real body's the shadow on the ground!
The projected body...
is a weapon used to protect the main body!
What did ya just do?
I—
That was freakin' amazing! It was super cool!
I know, right?
Wow! It healed!
I only copied yer right leg's data.
Is it really like data?
It's hard to explain in words, but basically, yes.
But the copied data will eventually disappear, I believe.
By erasing the original,
the copy becomes the original.
Erase? Like kill?
So ya gotta kill me or yeh'll die?
The instinct to do it fills my brain.
Under normal conditions, I would've had to kill ya.
My God!
So that's what they meant by yer dead if ya see yer Shadow.
Shiori's in danger.
We gotta do somethin'.
July 20th
Which is why my Shadow should be next to ya right now.
What would Shinpei think if he knew I was a fake?
Oh! Can ya tell which one's me?
Hey! I'm talkin' here!
It don't matter!
We're both me.
Ushio, the two of ya tried to save Shiori together, huh?
I remember.
I remember now!
Yer memories...
are back?
Not just my memories, my power too.
Yer power?
I want y'all to see my last moments. The truth of that day.
So I'm gonna replay the past from my memory data.
Let's go back to that private beach on July 21st.
Summer Time Rendering
Th-This is...
Hey, Shinpei.
L-Look at that!
Thank goodness it's sunny out!
I know, right?
This is the perfect weather fer studying.
Ya mean fer swimming!
Hey, Shiori!
Ya still need that to swim? So lame!
Big talk from someone who can't eat his mushrooms, Hamaji!
Not eatin' mushrooms don't make me lame, so I'm all good!
That's...
Yeah, it's us on the 21st.
Crap! I gotta stop 'em!
Hey, y'all!
Ya can't.
This is a video of the past,
and we're just watchin' the replay.
We can't touch or talk to 'em.
Ain't that right, Ushio?
Damn it!
Where were ya at this point?
Follow me.
One, two, three, four, five...
I think my stomach does stick out a bit, after all.
Geez, stop it! Ya know I'm conscious about that.
So ya copied her swimsuit here?
Just watch.
I can't get close to Shiori like this.
I've got an idea.
Can ya become this?
Yeah!
Gotcha!
Well?
Perfect!
I turned into her seashell necklace and had her wear me.
She took off the real necklace and put 'er away in her pool bag.
Hey, Mio!
How can I be a great swimmer like ya?
I wanna learn how to swim.
Ya can totally do it.
I'll tell ya what, I'll open up my swimming class today just for ya!
Do ya wanna learn how to swim?
Yeah!
Shiori...
I like yer spirit!
I swear I'll protect ya, no matter what happens!
Huh? What was that, Ushio?
Ya proposing to me?
What?
What's the matter?
Akari said she pooped.
Oh my.
Nuh-uh! I said I gotta go poopy!
I can't hold it!
Ya need someone ta go with ya?
It's okay, I'll take her.
Shiori?
What's up?
Shiori's gone!
Look, Sou, over there!
Ushio! I sense a Shadow under the water!
Tokiko, watch Akari for me!
Sou!
On it!
Shinpei, did ya see what happened to Shiori?
N-No.
I'm sorry.
This is just a memory,
so I can't show what no one saw.
Stay back!
Don't come any closer, y'all!
Leave this to me!
Sis?!
Ya idiot, Ushio! What are ya think—
Hold on, Shiori!
There!
Shiori's Shadow!
Okay, let's do this!
Right, leave it to me!
Stop.
That girl is mine. Don't take her.
I can't move?!
I'm so close to the surface too!
Shiori's gonna die!
Go! Hurry! Save Shiori!
Ushio!
Idiot!
What're ya spacin' out for?!
Just go!
How the hell am I supposed ta pay ya back fer this?!
Go... me...
Stop.
I told ya to stop.
Faulty.
They're coming.
Lucky you.
Shiori!
Sis!
Ushio!
I'm sorry, Ushio.
I couldn't protect Shiori.
But I—with Shinpei's help, I'll wipe out the Shadows!
I'll save everyone from the summer festival on the 24th!
Then maybe that'll pay ya back...
just a little!
Ya will. Ya will pay her back.
It pretends to be knocked out, then completely replaces Shiori.
Yeah.
That's unforgivable! Damn monster!
I wanna kill that thing now with my own hands.
Yeah...
It's already dead.
Hey! How can ya be so damn calm?!
But...
I did what I had to do!
Shinpei... I'm sorry.
Who had to do what now?
Found ya.
H-Hey, Ushio. This is a video, right?
Ya said we can't talk or interact with it, didn't ya?
This is crazy! This ain't part of my memories!
This is bad.
End the video, Ushio!
I've been looking for ya for a long time.
Ya won't escape again.
W-We're back?
Shinpei, yer arm!
There's a mark where she grabbed me!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Into the Darkness