Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, everyone,
do you have a pet at home?
A pet that you feed and take on walks.
They can be quite troublesome.
But still, they're adorable, aren't they?
After all, they're a member of the family.
No matter how much he's against it,
I'm not gonna give up this time
either! Not gonna! Not gonna!
Yaritai koto wa nani
Sou kikareru tabi
Aoi sora miageta
Kotae wa only my heart
Honto ni daiji na kotoba
wa kantan ni wa iwanai
Hikari ga yubisasu
basho e to hashiridasu yo
Dakishimetai mono nara
nakitai hodo mune ni aru
Egakitsuzukete yuku kitto take it someday
Shiroi kumo ga nagareru
chiheisen no mukou ni
Naranderu mirai wa itsumo soba ni aru kara
Kaleido Stage's Cinderella is a must-see.
In the show, the performance
of a trio of newcomers
as the fairy godmothers was
fascinating during the climactic scene.
We will be watching these
girls in the future.
We will be watching!
Yes, watch us!
The paper's praising us!
We did it!
We did it! We did it!
We did it! We did it! We did it!
Wow! I'm so happy!
What's this?
This is... a baby seal?
"The Amazing Seal."
He must have gotten
separated from his parents.
Poor baby.
Well, I'll be gone for just a bit.
Please take care of him, Fool.
What?! Take care of him?
What am I supposed to do?
For the time being,
I shall try reading your fortune!
The upright Hanged Man.
This card represents ordeals or sacrifices.
It may bring misfortune.
Yes?
Oh, can you see me?!
You are wrong if you think
you can be a Kaleido Star
just because you can see me!
Good morning, Sora.
Sora?
I'm hungry.
I wonder if she left for
the dining hall already?
A misfortune is befalling me.
What's with this paper?
They're praising the fairy godmothers.
They have no eye for talent.
It's like, if I were doing it,
they would've praised us more.
Hey, you'll hurt her
feelings if she hears you.
Oh, that would be like, awful.
I should be careful.
Oh, you're right here. Sorry.
Sorry.
Let's see...
Good morning.
Oh, good morning, Ken.
Something bothering you?
I was just wondering what he would like.
He?
Yeah. I met him this morning
when I was jogging on the beach.
He's cute, round, chubby,
small, and he's very hungry.
What type of guy do you like?
Guy?
I'm not talking about any guy. He's a seal.
Se... Seal?
Yes.
Please don't tell me you brought him home.
Well...
You brought him?
But he was hungry and I felt sorry for him.
So I'm not allowed to keep him?
Come with me.
Oh, okay.
But, he's still small, and
he's probably just a baby.
He was weak, and he looked
like he could die at any moment.
So I wanted to do something for him.
Seals eat fresh fish.
Thank you.
You have to return him to the
sea once he recovers, all right?
Okay.
Huh? It's open.
Thanks for waiting.
It's time for your meal.
What are you doing, Fool?
I can't believe this! He's not here!
I'm in trouble!
Rather, it is I who am in trouble.
No, he's not there.
Maybe he went back to the sea.
No way!
Are you looking for him?
So he's your friend.
Oh, Jonathan!
What?! Who's Jonathan?
It scared me.
This little guy was
scooting down the hallway.
He was dragging this.
Sorry about that.
Isn't he adorable?
Is there any way for me to keep him?
What?!
Keep him?!
Didn't you just promise to
let him go after feeding him?
I think Jonathan could be
a mascot for Kaleido Stage.
Right, Jonathan?
Oh, I'm in trouble!
I've got lessons to go to!
Would you please look
after him for a little while?!
What?!
Hey!
She does everything in her own way.
Well, that's what's so
great about her, though...
Good morning!
Did you read it? Did you read it?
I did! I did! I did!
The paper!
You there! Quiet down!
Yes, sir.
This is a message from Kalos.
Although the paper praised your performance,
the Triple Illusion is far from perfect.
Do not get carried away and lose your focus.
That's all.
Why can't he say that to us himself?
I heard that Kalos will
be in Seattle for a week
to attend a meeting about a new production.
A new production?
It seems to be the meeting for
the next production after Cinderella.
Big projects like these
take time to prepare for.
Really? I didn't know that.
So basically, we'll be fine as
long as we don't make mistakes.
Right.
Let's practice hard for our Triple Illusion.
Yeah.
All right, just you watch, Kalos!
I'll make you burst out laughing!
That's not it.
What's this? What the hell is this?!
Jonathan!
Who?!
Um, I found him at the beach.
I'm sorry for scaring you.
What are you thinking?
Well, he was hungry
and I felt sorry for him, so...
You can barely perform your own duties.
There is no way you
can look after an animal.
But...
Take him back right now!
Sorry,
I took my eyes off him for just a second.
No, it's okay.
I asked some veteran staff members,
but they said that Kaleido Stage
has never had any animals.
That seems to be Kalos's policy.
Maybe it's a good thing this
happened while Kalos was away.
You can't keep him, Sora.
But he's still just a baby.
I don't think he can survive by himself.
He's small, but he'll
eat quite a lot of food.
The cost of feeding him won't be cheap.
I'm getting a performer's pay now.
And I'm going to start
a part-time job tomorrow.
What?!
Part-time job?
You have lessons during the day
and performances in the evening!
Sora, now is the most important time for us.
I know.
I know that, but...
After my parents died, I was all alone.
If no one had opened their arms to me,
I'm sure I wouldn't be here right now.
That's why I can't abandon him.
You can call me a hypocrite,
but I just can't abandon him.
Don't worry,
I'll work harder than ever on my performance.
Thank you for letting me use your bath.
You're welcome. But are you really okay?
Yup. Good night.
Good night.
I'm home.
How do you like it, Jonathan?
I'm sorry to keep you
in such a cramped place.
The inside of the drawer is also cramped.
When I have time off, let's go to the beach.
The beach! Wearing bathing suits
is a great way to breed intimacy.
Just the two of us, Jonathan!
She treats me worse than animals.
All right.
--That is all for today's lesson.
--Thank you.
Sora!
What?!
There she goes.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your Pirate Pizza.
Two orders of the Chef's Special,
Linguine Bolognese.
--The main entrees are sea bass and lobster.
--Signorina, here's today's pay.
Yes, thank you!
But are you really sure you want
fresh fish instead of money every day?
Yes, he eats a lot of
fish, so this will help.
Well, I have to go now.
He must really love fish.
Here!
That's all.
You still want more?!
Yeah!
Job well done.
Thanks.
Wasn't our timing for the
cross jump just perfect today?
Yeah, I wish Kalos could have seen it.
Kalos just had to be gone
when we did it right.
Anyway, Sora, are you going
to work after this again today?
Yeah.
You've been working
non-stop for a whole week, right?
You shouldn't push yourself too much.
Don't worry, don't worry.
You broke one again?!
Break another one and you're fired.
I'm sorry.
I have the day off tomorrow,
no performance or lessons.
Just hang in there a little longer.
I'm home.
What was that?!
Sora?!
Well, I just missed dinner.
So I ran out of energy and I got dizzy.
That's not "dizzy"!
Okay!
--Here.
--That's why I told you not to push yourself!
Sorry.
What's this?!
You were working this many jobs?!
No wonder you collapsed.
But Jonathan eats so much.
And he gets hungry really fast.
Look, that's it.
Anyway, this has to go!
What?!
You won't give up even if we try to stop you.
So we have no choice but to help you.
Hold on.
I think it can be done if we take turns.
Yeah, I agree.
No, this is Jonathan's and my problem, so...
This is our problem too!
Mia...
Isn't that right?
Oh, I just remembered something!
Juggling contest?
That's right.
This is an annual event held on
the outdoor stage at the beach.
All the jugglers who are confident
in their skill participate in the contest.
The contest is...
three days from now.
People who want to participate
must register by 9 AM
on the day of the contest.
Can anyone participate?
Yes.
Wow!
What?
The first prize could pay for a
whole month of food for Jonathan.
Then we have no choice but to participate!
Oh... But I...
What's wrong?
Are you worried about something?
I've never juggled.
It could still be okay.
That's right, we have three days.
Really?
Yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
You think so?
That's right!
The level of competition is high,
but as they say, "You've
got nothing to lose."
Miss Sarah!
Oops... Sorry.
Let's start a crash course!
Yeah!
What?!
The upright Wheel of Fortune.
A messenger for good fortune?
Him? Impossible!
Sora! I have great news!
If you win the juggling contest,
a month's worth of food for Jonathan...
Look, look. Here, here!
--Oh, so she already knew.
--A little more.
Yes.
--Not like that.
--Oh, no.
--Do it more rhythmically, like this.
--Okay, okay.
No, I can't do it!
Do it faster!
Oh! If I can't even do something like this,
I can't expect to become a Kaleido Star.
I didn't think you were that bad.
Did you know there was a cast
member who tried to keep a dog
and got fired by Kalos for it?
What?!
My dad said that Kalos
is coming back Monday.
Wow!
Jonathan, you're better than Sora!
Jonathan, you're good! Very good!
Great! You're great!
Oh...
Hey, Jonathan, do it one more time.
One more time.
It looks like he won't
do it unless he feels like it.
He acts just like a big star.
Not too bad.
If Jonathan can do it, I should be able to...
All right.
In that case,
let's go for the crowd pleaser.
Now, the juggling contest
is getting more exciting!
Next up are regulars you already
know, Mr. and Mrs. Pumpkin!
Ooh, they're veteran performers for you.
--Wow! They're the best.
--They're pretty good.
It could be difficult for Sora's team to win.
It's me.
Yeah. I got back a day early.
Sora is?
This costume is tight.
That's because it's a rental.
Don't miss the timing to
bring out the balls, Sora.
I know.
Once Mia and Anna finish juggling...
--Well, next up are three
very attractive sisters,
--Okay.
--Anna, that's a bit too much.
--Really?
--the Jonathan Sisters! Here they are!
It's our turn!
Finally, it's Sora's group.
We need them to do their best.
Sora!
She blew it.
Shoot!
Oh, no!
Hey, hey.
Jonathan?
Jonathan!
We were saved by Jonathan.
Anna!
Bravo, Jonathan!
Kalos...
Isn't he supposed to come back tomorrow?
What should we do?
I'll go.
I cannot allow you to work part-time.
Nor can I allow pets.
Keep your attention
focused on performing onstage.
That's all.
You can go now.
I'm not losing my focus.
In fact, when you were
away, we did a perfect...
This discussion is over.
I'm not going to abandon Jonathan.
Who?
If I abandon him,
Jonathan will die.
If you cannot abandon him,
then you should quit Kaleido Stage.
No, I won't!
What?!
What is it?
Boss, you have a guest.
Okay. I'll be there soon.
I told you the discussion is over.
Not yet.
That's enough!
I think the show has
nothing to do with Jonathan.
It does!
Listen, get rid of him!
If you have time for something
like that, you should practice more!
Understand?
Of course, I will.
I will work harder than ever for the stage,
so that all the papers will come to see us.
I think Kaleido Stage exists
to make people happy when they come see us.
But abandoning Jonathan
in exchange for that...
I think there's something wrong with that.
Although I can't say what exactly,
I still think there's
something wrong with that.
Kalos.
Jean.
Jonathan... Everybody...
Kalos, now I understand why
you let Sora join Kaleido Stage.
It was my biggest mistake.
How about it?
Why don't we take care of the seal here?
That way, Sora can quit her part-time jobs
and there won't be any worries
about how he'll affect her performance.
I'll let you handle this, Jean.
Let's build a gigantic
swimming pool for Jonathan.
Dad!
Sora, Kalos gave you permission!
Did you hear?!
Thank you so much!
All right!
Isn't this great, Jonathan?
When you sabishii toki doushitemasuka
Never say sonna no wakannai
Nemuru asobu magazine mekuru
Sabishii toki wa sabishii yo
Mienai denpa ga kyou mo
tulututu machi ni tobikau
Anyway kokoro no bekutoru
so many reason hanashiteru
Jiyuu ni sora o tobitai keredo
Hane o hirogeru basho ga nai
Demo shinjiteru
Katachi no nai mirai ga aru yo
Katachi ni shitai watashi ga iru
Kanashikutemo machigai demo
Omou mama fly to the free
"Next Kaleido Star"
They don't appreciate my performance
because the audience isn't
sophisticated enough!
And so, a talented diabolo
girl, Rosetta, has come.
Amazing...
She is truly the world champion.
But she looks sad somehow.
The stage is supposed to make
the audience happy with our smiles.
That's why I wanna see
Rosetta smile no matter what.
I wanna! I wanna!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Girl Who Doesn't Smile."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...