AAH!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: A STRANGE PHENOMENON
STRUCK OUT OF THE BLUE.
- THIS ARMOR'S PRETTY FANCY
FOR AKIHISA'S LAME AVATAR.
- I KNOW.
HE PRACTICALLY LIFE-SIZE.
- MM-HMM.
- GUYS, EXCUSE ME!
HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
THIS THING AT ALL?!
- YOU MEAN ITS NASTY HEAD?
YEAH, WE HAVE.
NOW GET IT OUT OF MY FACE.
IT'S CREEPY.
- I GUESS THAT THING'S NOT GONNA
RUN ERRANDS FOR ME, IS IT?
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE WORRIED
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE HERE?!
- HEY, LOSERS!
- HOW IS EVERYONE THIS MORNING?
- HEY, WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
AND HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
- AAH!
- ( laughs )
- I'M SORRY.
SEEING YOU LIKE THAT
FREAKED US OUT.
- OH, NO,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M SORRY I SCARED YOU.
- GOOD.
I MEAN, IT IS YOUR FAULT.
SO THANKS FOR THE APOLOGY.
- THINK IT'S JUST HIM?
I WONDER IF THE REST OF OUR
AVATARS HAVE CHANGED TOO.
- THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
- MM-HMM.
- All: SUMMON!
- ( hisses )
- WELL, THAT'S RATHER ODD.
- THEY'RE OBVIOUSLY
TURNING INTO MONSTERS,
BUT I THINK
THEY SOMEHOW REPRESENT
WHAT OUR TRUE NATURES ARE.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
I WONDER WHAT MY REAL NATURE IS.
I BET HE SYMBOLIZES
MY CHIVALROUS SPIRIT.
- AKIHISA, DON'T FOOL YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW THE TRUTH.
- OR MAYBE IT MEANS I'M STRONG
OR EVEN THAT I HAVE A BIG
SWINGING SWORD,
'CAUSE I'M SO MANLY.
- DOUBTFUL.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A HEAD.
THAT PROBABLY JUST MEANS
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
- WHY?!
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO BE SO CRUEL?
YOU CAN'T DROP
AN HONESTY BOMB ON ME.
THE SHRAPNEL HURTS!
- Fukuhara:
TRUTH CAN BE
THE MOST PAINFUL
OF SHRAPNEL.
- YUUJI'S AVATAR
DOESN'T REALLY LOOK
ALL THAT MUCH DIFFERENT
THAN HE DOES.
- IT'S A DOPPELGANGER.
- WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU SAYING?!
THIS IS THE NASTY MAN-BEAST
KNOWN AS YUUJI SAKAMOTO!
HE'S ALMOST AS MEAN AND VICIOUS
AS HE IS UGLY.
- WORLD CUP IN YOUR FACE, SUCKA!
- YOU'RE OUT OF CONTROL, YUUJI.
YOU KICKED MY AVATAR'S HEAD
LIKE IT WAS A SOCCER BALL--
WHAT KIND OF PIECE OF CRAP
FRIEND DOES THAT?
- SERIOUSLY, AKI,
DON'T BE SUCH A GIRL.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD THE SAYING?
YOU KNOW THE ONE.
"MY FRIEND IS A BALL."
- IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE: "THE
BALL IS MY FRIEND"!
- ( growls )
- ( all screaming )
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- HE'S A WEREWOLF.
- WAIT, DOESN'T HE
NEED A FULL MOON
TO DO THAT WHOLE
TRANSFORMING INTO
A MURDEROUS BEAST THING?
- MAYBE JUST SAW SOMETHING
THAT WAS ROUND.
- ( roaring )
- MY FRIEND REALLY IS A BALL.
- ARE YOU TWO GONNA
SUMMON YOUR AVATARS?
- OH, SURE, I GUESS WE CAN.
'KAY.
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR!
SUMMON!
- ( giggles )
- PLEASE DON'T LOOK AT HER!
AVERT YOUR EYES!
SHE'S HIDEOUS!
HIDEOUS!
- DON'T WORRY. EVERYONE ALREADY
KNEW WHAT YOUR TRUE NATURE WAS.
- NO!  I-- IT MAY BE TRUE
THAT I'M A BIG GIRL,
BUT THEY'RE NOT BIG ENOUGH
TO BE MY CALLING CARD.
- STOP!  DON'T SAY ANOTHER WORD.
IF YOU DO, A CERTAIN SOMEONE
IS GOING TO GET HURT,
AND THEN HURT ME
IN THE PROCESS
OF MY WRIST GETTING
SNAPPED OFF!
- YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
YOU WANNA SAY,
GO AHEAD AND SAY IT.
- NO!
- RIDICULOUS.
MIZUKI, DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR HAVING SUCH A NAUGHTY BODY.
- WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
THAT'S SO MEAN.
- WHY ARE YOU CRYING? I SAID
NOT TO TAKE IT THE WRONG WAY.
FOR ONCE, I DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT MINE.
SHE'LL BE UBER CUTE.
SUMMON!
( grunts )
- Aki: I CAN'T LAUGH.
IF I DO, I'M A GONER.
- AKI?
- YEAH?  WHAT IS IT, MINAMI?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THIS AVATAR?
I MEAN, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IT'S TRYING
TO SAY ABOUT ME?
- UH, I'M NOT SURE.
OH!
DAMN IT!  OKAY...
WHAT CAN I SAY OTHER THAN
SHE'S TOTALLY FLAT?
I GOT IT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE
IN COMMON.
YOU'RE BOTH--
WELL, YOU'RE REALLY...
HARD.
- I'M HARD?!
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?!
- Fukuhara: IT'S A FACT.
THE TRUTH HURTS.
- YOU BETTER GET AWAY FROM MY
SUGAR PIE NOW, YOU FILTHY PIG!
- OH, WOW, SHE IS CRAZY.
- WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE, TOUCHING HER LIKE THAT?
YOU ARE DISGUSTING!
TAKE THIS, CREEPER.
- SHUT UP,
YOU BASTARDS ARE TOO LOUD!
- HEY, I KNOW YOU...
( stammers )
WAIT, WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
- I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
TRYING TO MOCK US!
- WE ARE TSUNEMURA
AND NATSUKAWA,
YEAR THREE, CLASS "A."
- OH, YEAH,
THE TSUNEKAWA DUO, SURE.
- I THINK I'VE HEARD THAT
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
THE TSUNEKAWA DUO.
- QUIT DOING THAT TO OUR NAME!
- Fukuhara:
DURING THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL,
THE TSUNEKAWA DUO...
BLAH BLAH BLAH...
THEY'RE JERKS.
- YOU GUYS NEED TO
KEEP IT DOWN.
WE CAN HEAR YOUR RACKET
ALL THE WAY
FROM THE YEAR THREE CLASSROOM,
AND CAN'T STUDY.
- OUTRAGEOUS. AND A LIE.
- WHAT?
- THIS IS CLASS "F" ON
THE THIRD FLOOR, MORONS.
YEAR THREE, CLASS "A" IS IN
A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT BUILDING
AND ON A DIFFERENT FLOOR.
- INDEED, IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE
WE WERE BEING THAT LOUD.
- YOU PROBABLY GOT BORED
OF STUDYING,
AND WERE WANDERING AROUND
WHEN YOU HEARD
AKIHISA'S STUPID,
SILLY VOICE.
SO YOU DECIDED TO TAKE IT OUT
ON ALL OF US, RIGHT?
- DID YOU JUST RANDOMLY
BLAME ME FOR THEM BEING HERE?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER!
GAH!
THE FACT STILL REMAINS YOU GUYS
ARE ALL ANNOYING AS HELL.
- WE GOT YOUR NUMBER.
YOU'RE THE TOOLBAGS WHO
GOT SUSPENDED FOR STARTING
A PEEKING REBELLION.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO IF THAT MESSES UP
THE SCHOOL'S REPUTATION,
AND OUR COLLEGE ENTRANCE
EXAMS IN THE PROCESS?!
- WHAT DO THEY WANT YOU TO DO,
SAY YOU'RE SORRY?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
THEY PROBABLY WANNA
HEAR THAT FROM YOU.
- Both: WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE BOTH OF YOU!
- Aki and Yuuji: OKAY, YOU'RE
KIDDING US NOW, RIGHT?
- IT'S TIME WE TAUGHT
YOU MISERABLE IDIOTS
A LESSON ABOUT RESPECT.
YEAH, AND THE MATH TEACHER'S
HERE. PERFECT TIMING!
- Both: SUMMON!
( grunt )
AAH!
- NO WAY!
- WHAT THE--?!
- I'M GONNA BE THE FIRST ONE
TO TAKE THAT JERK DOWN.
SO DON'T GET IN MY WAY,
OR I'LL TAKE BOTH OF YOU OUT!
- I DON'T CARE IF
YOU'RE OLDER THAN ME OR NOT.
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO ATTACK AKIHISA.
NOT ON MY WATCH.
- MIHARU?
AND WHAT'S KUBO DOING HERE?
- THEY'RE LIKE,
THE SAME CREATURE.
- LOST GODS.
MONSTERS LOST
ON THE PATH OF HUMANS
WHO TRY TO GET YOU
TO BECOME ONE OF THEM.
- SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
- ( grunting )
- AAH!
- NO!
- THE TIME HAS COME.
LET'S FINISH THEM OFF!
- STOP RIGHT THERE!
- All: IT'S THE PRINCIPAL!
- Yuuji: IT'S THE CRAZY OLD HAG!
UH-- OH.
- YOU'LL PROBABLY WANT
TO SAVE YOUR REMAINING SCORES
FOR THE EVENT YOU'RE ABOUT
TO BE PART OF.
- WHAT EVENT?
- WAIT, AREN'T YOU
FORGETTING THAT YOU NEED TO
TURN OUR AVATARS
BACK TO NORMAL FIRST?
- YEAH, LIKE THIS, THE BEST
EVENT WE COULD COME UP WITH
IS A HAUNTED HOUSE.
- WELL DONE.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE PRETTY
GOOD INTUITION FOR AN IDIOT.
WE'RE HOLDING THE FIRST EVER
COURAGE CONTEST
BETWEEN GRADES,
USING OUR AVATARS!
- All:
WHAT'S A COURAGE CONTEST?!
- BASICALLY, YOU SCREWED UP
THE SYSTEM AGAIN
ON THAT LAST TUNE-UP, RIGHT?
- THIS WILL BE FUN.
PERHAPS I SHOULD HAVE YOU GENTS
MANAGE THE EVENT.
NOW THEN,
YEAR TWO AND YEAR THREE...
WHICH ONE OF YOU WANTS TO BE
THE GHOSTS AND GOBLINS?
- WE'LL DO IT, BECAUSE
WE'RE OLDER, AND SCARIER!
- PLUS, THERE'S STILL
THAT LESSON IN RESPECT
THEY HAVE TO LEARN.
- THE YEAR THREE STUDENTS
WILL BE THE GHOSTS AND GOBLINS.
AND YEAR TWO STUDENTS
WILL HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO BRAVE THE HAUNTED HOUSE.
- Fukuhara: RULES FOR THE
COURAGE CONTEST BETWEEN GRADES.
OOH...
CHALLENGERS WILL BRAVE THE
HAUNTED HOUSE IN GROUPS OF TWO.
WHEN THE CHALLENGERS SCREAM
OR MAKE NOISES
LOUDER THAN
A SET SOUND VOLUME
WHILE TRAVERSING
THE HAUNTED HOUSE,
THEY SHALL BE DISQUALIFIED
IMMEDIATELY.
CHALLENGERS WILL FIGHT
AVATAR BATTLES
WITH HAUNTED HOUSE INHABITANTS
AT FOUR SEPARATE CHECKPOINTS.
IF THEY WIN, THEY WILL CLEAR
THAT CHECKPOINT
AND CONTINUE TO THE NEXT.
IF THEY CLEAR ALL
FOUR CHECKPOINTS,
THE CHALLENGERS WIN.
HOWEVER, IF ALL THE
CHALLENGERS ARE DEFEATED,
THE HAUNTED HOUSE INHABITANTS
WILL BE THE VICTORS.
- HA, YOU KNOW,
I DON'T THINK JUST COMPETING
IS ENOUGH, DO YOU?
- MAYBE WE OUGHTA DECIDE ON A
PENALTY GAME FOR WHEN THEY LOSE.
- ALL RIGHT, BOYS.
SHUT UP.
I NEVER SAID YOU COULD MAKE UP
YOUR OWN RULES.
THIS IS AN ACADEMY EVENT.
- YEAH, BUT--
BUT WE ALWAYS DO THAT.
- ALWAYS DO WHAT?
CRY LIKE A GIRL?
AS LONG AS YOU TWO POSEURS
ARE AT ONE OF THOSE CHECKPOINTS,
YOU'LL EVENTUALLY BE ABLE
TO FIGHT US ONE ON ONE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- VERY GOOD POINT.
- WE'LL BEAT YOU DOWN
WITH EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT!
- HUH?  HUH?
WHY ME?
WHAT DID I DO?
- Tsunekawa Duo:
BAKA AND TEST!
- ( students chattering )
- ( dance music playing )
- EVERYONE LISTEN UP.
WE ENTER THE HAUNTED
HOUSE IN GROUPS OF TWO.
AND I'M THINKING WE NEED TO
HAVE GUYS PAIRED UP WITH GIRLS
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
- BUT IF THE GIRL GETS SCARED
AND SCREAMS,
WON'T THEY GUY END UP
BEING DISQUALIFIED AS WELL?
- NOT AS LONG AS
HE DOESN'T SCREAM.
PLUS, THIS SHOULD MAKE THINGS
MORE EXCITING ANYWAY.
ALL RIGHT!
GO AHEAD AND FIND A PARTNER.
- BRO, WHAT'S THE TRUTH?
- AS IF YOU DON'T ALREADY
KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT.
HER NAME STARTS WITH AN "S"
AND ENDS WITH AN "OKO."
- YOU SHOULD PAIR UP
WITH ME, YUUJI, OR ELSE...
WE GET MARRIED NOW.
- ( murmurs )
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
MIZUKI?
- I, UH-- IT'S JUST--
- IT'S JUST WHAT?
- I'VE ALWAYS REALLY
HATED GHOSTS
AND SCARY STUFF LIKE THAT.
SO I'M AFRAID
THAT I MIGHT SCREAM.
I DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONE
WHO MESSES UP OUR
CHANCES OF WINNING.
- Both: UH...
- NO, THAT'S OKAY.
IF YOU'RE TOO SCARED,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PUSH IT AT ALL.
- YEAH!  IT'S COOL.
SO, LIKE, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE ALL HAVE SOMETHING
WE'RE SCARED OF.
EVEN ME, SO-- SO YEAH.
- WE'LL DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO KEEP YOU FROM GOING IN THERE.
THAT WAY YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE AFRAID, OKAY?
- HUH?
OKAY.
- HOW DARE YOU,
AKIHISA YOSHII?
MARK MY WORDS-- YOUR DAYS OF
BEING A FILTHY PIG ARE NUMBERED.
- HEY, MIHARU?
- WHOA!  WHAT?!
WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO ME?
- CALM DOWN.
PARTNER UP WITH ME.
- ALL RIGHT, LET ME HEAR
WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY.
- AND SO, THE COURAGE CONTEST
BETWEEN GRADES GOT UNDERWAY.
- THEY WORKED REALLY HARD
ON THIS.  FREAKY.
- YEAH.  BUT ALL OF THIS STUFF
IS STILL SUPER FAKE.
IT'S NOT REALLY THAT SCARY.
- ( both gasp )
( screaming )
- ( both screaming )
- DISQUALIFIED.
( screaming continues )
- THOSE YEAR THREE STUDENTS
DON'T MESS AROUND.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY
MIGHT BE TOUGHER
THAN I ORIGINALLY THOUGHT.
- DAMN IT.
WHY'D I GET STUCK PAIRING UP
WITH A DUDE?
- DON'T HATE ON ME BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT POPULAR WITH GIRLS.
- EXCUSE ME?
AREN'T YOU THE ONE
WHO ASKED TWENTY GIRLS OUT
AND GOT REJECTED BY
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM?
- SHUT UP!
ALL THOSE GIRLS
DIDN'T REJECT ME, OKAY?
MOST OF IT WAS BAD TIMING.
- YEAH, I'VE HAD
BAD TIMING TOO, ASS!
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I'M NOT POPULAR!
- YEAH, NO JOKE.
- DON'T BE A JERK!
- WHY DON'T YOU SHUT THE HELL UP
AND QUIT COMPLAINING?!
- DISQUALIFIED.
- YOU LOOK TOTALLY AWESOME.
THEY'RE GONNA FREAK OUT FOR SURE
WHEN THEY SEE YOU LIKE THIS.
- FABULOUS.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M OFF TO GO GIVE THOSE
PATHETIC DELINQUENTS
THE SCARE OF A LIFETIME.
- AAH.
- UH--
MIKAMI, ARE YOU HURT?
LET ME HELP YOU BACK UP.
- YEAH, OKAY.
THANK YOU.
- HEY, DID YOU SEE SOMETHING
WEIRD ON THE SCREEN JUST NOW?
- WHAT?  WEIRD LIKE WHAT?
- ( gasps )
- ( groans )
- I'M RIGHT HERE, MIKAMI.
THERE IS NO NEED TO WORRY,
MY DEAR, I'LL PROTECT YOU.
- ( groans loudly )
- EVERYTHING IN HERE IS
SO OBVIOUS ANYWAY.
- ( both scream )
- ( all screaming )
- DAMN!  THAT LITTLE BASTARD
HAS GONE TOO FAR!
- NO!  THEIR WAY OF WINNING'S
AS DIRTY AND DISGUSTING
AS THAT DIRTY, DISGUSTING FACE
ON THE SCREEN!
- THAT'S SCARIER THAN A GHOST!
- I'M GONNA HAVE NIGHTMARES NOW!
- ( screaming )
- HOLD ME!
- ( screaming continues )
- ALL STRIKE UNITS
DISQUALIFIED.
- AH, DAMN IT ALL!
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO NOW?
HOW CAN ANYONE GET PAST
THAT DISGUSTING FACE?
- LEAVE IT TO ME, GUYS.
- Aki and Hideyoshi:
KOUTA, NO!
- YOU NEED A PARTNER FIRST.
I DON'T MIND GOING IN.
- LET'S DO THIS THEN.
I'LL SHOW HIM A THING OR TWO
ABOUT TERROR.
VICTIMS...
HERE I COME.
( cackling )
HEY!
( gags )
- All: YEAH!
( cheering )
- THAT WAS A DIRTY TRICK!
- SMILE FOR THE CAMERA!
DON'T YOU WANNA LOOK
YOUR BEST?
- WE'RE GOING TO PUT
THESE PICS UP ONLINE.
- NO!  YOU'LL--
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
JUST YOU WAIT AND SEE!
- BYE, BYE!
SO LONG!  LOSER.
- ( bell rings )
- WELL, LOOK WHO
FINALLY MADE IT.
- I GUESS WE MIGHT AS WELL
GET THIS OVER WITH.
- Both: SUMMON!
- CHECK THEIR AVATARS.
THEY LOOK AWFULLY BIG
AND STRONG, DON'T THEY?
IT'S ADORABLE.
- I SEE THAT.
LET'S ROLL.
- SUMMON!
( giggles )
THEY'RE NO MATCH FOR US.
- All: WHOA!
- HECK YEAH!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY DID IT!
- HEY, YUUJI, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- WELL, I DIDN'T HAVE WHAT
I WOULD CONSIDER A CLEAR VIEW.
BUT I THINK THE FACELESS
ONE TOOK A SPLIT SECOND
TO GET TOTALLY NAKED.
BEAT UP ALL HER OPPONENTS,
AND PUT HER CLOTHES BACK ON.
- WHY DID SHE HAVE TO TAKE OFF
HER CLOTHES?
- WITHIN THAT SHORT PERIOD OF
TIME, KOUTA'S NOSE BLED,
HE STOPPED THE BLEEDING
AND PERFORMED HIS OWN
BLOOD TRANSFUSION.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKIN' ABOUT!
AT THIS RATE, THEY MIGHT
ACTUALLY BE ABLE
TO CLEAR ALL THE CHECKPOINTS.
- YEAH.
I DOUBT IT.
IT'S ABOUT TO GET ROUGH
IN THERE.
- THE NEXT CHECKPOINT SHOULD BE
COMING UP PRETTY SOON, RIGHT?
- I THINK SO.
( gasps )
- KOUTA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WELCOME.
MY NAME IS AOI KOGURE.
AND I'M IN YEAR THREE,
CLASS "A."
I'M ALSO A MEMBER OF
THE TEA CEREMONY CLUB.
- HUH?
- NO.
- FOCUS, KOUTA,
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN HER!
- RIGHT.
- ( giggles )
OF COURSE YOU ARE, SILLY.
SURPRISE, THOUGH.
I'M WEARING AN ENTIRELY
DIFFERENT UNIFORM
UNDER THIS ONE.
- YOU SNEAKY LADY!
- PERHAPS.
REGARDLESS...
I BELONG TO ANOTHER GROUP TOO!
THE RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS CLUB!
- ( murmuring, screaming )
- YOU'RE BLEEDING EVERYWHERE!
SOMEBODY HELP US!
HE'S GONNA BLEED OUT!
- Boys:
WE'LL SAVE YOU, KOUTA!
RHYTHM GYMNASTICS!
- THIS IS BAD NEWS, YUUJI.
WE BETTER GRAB A CAMERA
AND HEAD IN THERE IMMEDIATELY!
( screams )
- I'M SORRY, AKI...
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- I THINK SOMEONE HAS HAD
FAR TOO MUCH EXCITEMENT.
- I DID GET THE GIST
OF THE SITUATION, THOUGH.
AND LUCKILY
I HAVE ANOTHER PLAN.
- I DO NOT LIKE THIS.
I HATE HAUNTED HOUSES
AND ALL THE STUPID
THINGS THEY STAND FOR.
- WHO'S THERE?
OH, IT'S JUST
A COUPLE OF GIRLS.
- GOOD CALL, MAN, DIRTY CHICK
TRICKS WON'T WORK ON THOSE TWO.
- YEP.  AND DON'T FORGET,
YUUKO IS FROM CLASS "A."
- ( chuckles )
AREN'T THEY CUTE?
OBVIOUSLY,
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
TILL NEXT TIME.
I'LL LEAVE THEM TO YOU BOYS!
- ON IT!  SUMMON!
- LET'S IGNORE HOW IT LOOKS.
HIS SCORE'S NOT THAT HIGH.
- SUMMON!
HOW COME YOU GET TO BE
A SEXY CAT GIRL,
AND I'M JUST A PLAIN OLD CAT?!
- MAYBE IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH YOU ALWAYS PLAYING COY.
- WHAT?!  WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- ( device trilling )
- OH, NO, HE'S GOT HER!
- THANKS FOR THE CONCERN,
BUT I'M GONNA BE FINE.
I'M NOT THAT WEAK, YOU KNOW.
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY...
I DETEST BUGS.
- ( cheering )
- Yuuko:
THAT WAS A PIECE OF CAKE.
SHALL WE MOVE ON?
- Hideyoshi: ABSOLUTELY.
- ONE SEC, MY DEAR HIDEYOSHI.
- Both: HUH?
- CRAPOLA.
- I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
SPARE A WORD.
I'VE BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME
FOR THIS MOMENT.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON,
AND I DON'T WANT TO.
JUST MAKE IT QUICK, OKAY?
- I'LL GET STRAIGHT
TO THE POINT.
- TO WHAT POINT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HIDEYOSHI KINOSHITA...
I, UH-- WELL--
SEE, THE THING IS...
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU!
- ( gasps )
- ( all murmuring )
- Aki: THAT DAY...
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I HEARD HIDEYOSHI SCREAM.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kids: EVERYONE'S SONG!
- Tsunemura:
"SUN AND SUNFLOWER."
WHENEVER I NOTICE, MY EYES
ARE ALWAYS FOLLOWING YOU.
AND NOW,
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I'M ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR YOUR SMILE.
I DON'T KNOW THE WORDS TO
DESCRIBE MY FEELINGS,
BUT I STILL WANT TO TELL YOU.
I LOVE YOU, HIDEYOSHI.
I'M SERIOUSLY
MADLY IN LOVE WITH YOU.
- GUYS, I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I SCREAMED SO
LOUD AND FOR SO LONG LIKE THAT.
- COMPLETELY UNDERSTANDABLE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, REALLY.
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY WHO
WOULDN'T SCREAM
UNDER THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- Hideyoshi: THANKS.
I NEVER THOUGHT--
I MEAN, WHO KNEW
HE'D START READING
A POEM HE WROTE FOR ME?
- I THREW UP IN MY MOUTH,
IF THAT HELPS.
- All: MM-HMM.
- WE HAVE TO STEP UP OUR GAME!
AND WE HAVE TO DO IT SOON.
- HEY, ARE YOU LOSERS WATCHING?
- ( all scream )
- THOSE BASTARDS!
- ARE YOU TOO SCARED OF US?
IS THAT WHY YOU HAVEN'T
COME IN HERE YET?
HEY HEY, YO, IT'S YOUR TURN
TO SAY SOMETHING NOW.
- HA, YEAH!
HIDEYOSHI, I--
- ( all whimpering )
- HEY, YOSHII!  SAKAMOTO!
YOU JERKS THERE?
- HOW LONG DO WE HAVE TO WAIT?
COME IN AND SEE US!
- DON'T TRY TO HIDE!
GET YOUR BUTTS INSIDE!
- ( both laugh )
- STUPID POET!
- THEY ASKED FOR IT!
IT IS ON NOW!
- Fukuhara:
QUESTION THIRTEEN.
TAKE A MOMENT TO CHECK
YOUR ANSWERS SO FAR,
AND INDICATE HOW SATISFIED
YOU ARE WITH THOSE ANSWERS.
- Aki: I'M PRETTY SURE
I WROTE MY NAME RIGHT!
- WELL, KUDOS TO YOU.
- NEXT EPISODE!
BAKA AND TEST
SUMMON THE BEASTS!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.