I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
Even if your feelings have been shattered,
even if your wishes are out of reach...
please don't forget the kindness of those around you.
One person's been supporting your heart,
and many more are waiting to see you smile.
So fill yourself with your feelings,
and put your wishes on the line.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Dimensional distortion confirmed!
It's rapidly increasing in size!
At this rate, a dimensional dislocation
will occur in less than thirty minutes!
The Garden's power source is similar
to the Jewel Seeds, the Lost Logia.
She's overloading the reactor to make up for the output she's missing!
She was planning on a one-way trip from the beginning!
Chrono-kun! Where are you going?
I'm heading to the scene.
If we don't stop this at the source...
I'll go with you!
Me too!
Understood.
Arf, stay with Fate.
Y-Yeah.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Chrono, Nanoha-san, Yuuno-kun, I'll be there shortly.
Until I arrive, you three are to focus
on arresting Presea Testarossa!
Understood!
Episode 12
When Our Fates Are Sealed
When Our Fates Are Sealed.
There's a lot of them...
This is just the entrance.
There'll be even more inside.
Chrono-kun, what are these things?
Simple robots programmed to attack
any enemy within range.
I see. That's fine, then.
You don't need to waste your
time on enemies of this level.
Stinger Snipe.
So fast!
Snipe Shot!
Break Impulse.
Don't just stand there! Let's get going!
Yeah!
See that hole? Don't step
in any of the black spaces.
It's imaginary space.
No magic whatsoever will work inside of it.
That includes flying magic,
so if you were to fall into it,
you'd be pulled down by gravity,
and never escape.
I-I'll be careful.
We'll split into two groups here.
You two head to the top floor
and seal the energy source!
What about you, Chrono-kun?
I'm going after Presea.
That is my job, after all.
I'll carve a path for you, so you two...!
Yeah!
Blaze Cannon.
Chrono-kun! Be careful!
I'll also be heading out.
I'll put up a Distortion Shield within the Garden
and suppress the growing
dimensional distortion.
I'm worried about those guys, so...
I'm gonna go help out a little too, okay?
I'll be right back.
And then, when it's all over...
no matter how long it takes,
you'll return to the Fate
I know and love so much, okay?
Because from now on, you're free to
use all the time you have for yourself.
Mother never smiled at me even once...
I wanted to live... because I
wanted Mother to accept me...
No matter how often she told me I wasn't good enough,
or what bad things she did to me...
I just... wanted her to smile at me.
Even though she's so clearly abandoned
me now... I'm... still clinging to her.
Arf...
Arf, who's always stayed by my side...
I've probably made her so sad, since I never
listened to anything she had to say...
And that girl in white
I've run into so many times...
She's the first person to
see me as an equal,
and face me so directly,
with such honesty...
We've met, and fought... so many times already...
And she's called out my
name countless times...
Time and time again...
I wanted to continue living because
I wanted Mother to accept me!
I thought that was the only reason to live.
I thought that if that wasn't possible,
I might as well stop living!
I can't just throw away
everything that's happened, right?
I can't even possibly think...
about running away now.
For me...
For us... nothing has begun yet...
I wonder if that's really so, Bardiche?
Maybe I haven't even truly begun yet?
Get set.
That's right... you've always been
by my side too, Bardiche.
You don't want to let things
end like this either, right?
Yes, sir.
I don't know if we'll be able to pull it off,
but let's do our best together, okay?
yodonda kuuki nukedaseru you ni oshiete kureta yo ne
You taught me how to escape from this suffocating air
komiagete kuru shizuka na negai
A quiet wish surfaces inside me
Recovery.
jibun o torimodosou
I'm going to take myself back
Nothing has even begun between us yet...
aoida sora no hate kimi no manazashi
As I look up to the other end of the sky,
omoiyari no ame ni utarete kieteku
your gaze disappears under the rain of compassion
That's why, in order to start anew as my true self...
Let Me Down tomaranai
Let me down, I won't stop
I have to put an end to
who I've been until now.
Shake Up hajimete kidzuite yudanete Take A Shot
Shake up, now I see! Trusting you, I'll take a shot!
miwatashitara kimi ga ite
I raised my head and met your gaze
tamerau koto naku tatakau imi wa
Now I can fight without hesitation
azayaka ni sakihokoreru you ni
so that I can bloom in vivid colors,
yowai kokoro to mukiau koto
and face my weaknesses
Damn it! There's so many of them!
It'd be fine if that were all of them, but...!
doko e muite mo doko e mukatte arukeba ii nante
I didn't know where to turn, I didn't know where to go
I need to do something about this!
jibun no michi mo kimerarenakute tadazumu boku ga ita
I just stood there, unable to choose a path
Nanoha!
haruka naru mirai ni kibou tayasazu
I can't lose hope for the distant future
Nanoha!
Thunder Rage.
kumo ni kakurete ita togirenai yuuki
My unbreakable courage was hidden in the clouds
I Have Drive yobi sumase
I have drive, awaken it!
Get set.
Take Off furuete mezamete tazunete Pave The Way
Take off, shaken up and woken up, called upon to pave the way!
Thunder...
Rage!
mayowanai de kimi to yuku
I won't hesitate to go with you
doushite tomadoi tsudzukete kita no
Why did I ever hesitate?
Fate?!
hareyaka ni kachihokoreru you ni
So that I can overcome my past with pride,
musuu no negai tsukamitorou
let's grab countless wishes with our hands
It's a big one.
It has a strong barrier!
Yeah... and those things on its back...
But... if we fight it together...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go, Bardiche!
Get set.
Us too, Raising Heart!
Stand by, ready.
tsuyoku yasashiku tsubasa ni kaze o
Strongly, gently, give wind to our wings
Thunder...
Shake Up hajimete kidzuite yudanete Take A Shot
Shake up, now I see! Trusting you, I'll take a shot!
ushinau mono nado nai
I have nothing to lose
Buster!
furuete mezamete tazunete Pave The Way
Shaken up and woken up, called upon to pave the way!
Divine...
hareyaka ni kachihokoreru you ni
So that I can overcome my past with pride,
Buster!
musuu no negai tsukamitorou
let's grab countless wishes with our hands
Here goes!
So, they've come.
But they're too late now.
Right, Alicia?
Alicia...
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Fate-chan!
Fate! Fate!
Fate!
Arf...
I'm sorry for worrying you.
I'll finish things here.
After that, I can finally start anew... as the true me.
Just a little longer...
You can head to the power core
from that elevator over there.
Okay! Thanks.
And Fate-chan, you're going
to where your Mother is?
Yes.
I... um... I can't say it very well, but...
Good luck.
Thank you.
Chrono's heading there by himself!
If we don't hurry,
we may not make it in time!
Fate!
Yeah!
Amy!
Nanoha-chan and Yuuno-kun have
successfully made it to the power core
and Fate-chan and Arf are heading
to the lowest level of the Garden.
It'll be fine. We can do this, I'm sure.
Yeah.
I'll take care of defense.
You concentrate on sealing them, Nanoha.
Yeah. Just like always, right?
Yuuno-kun, you've always been by
my side... protecting me, right?
Sealing Mode.
That's why I can fight.
Because I've always had
that warmth at my back!
Let's go!
Divine Shooter! Full Power!
Shoot!
Presea Testarossa.
This is the end of the line.
I am suppressing the
dimensional distortion.
The power source will soon be sealed,
and my top Enforcer is
heading this way now.
The forgotten capital, Al-Hazard...
The hidden technology that supposedly
lies there may not even exist.
It's nothing more than a legend.
You're wrong.
The path to Al-Hazard lies in the
interstice between dimensions.
As soon as dimensional space is shattered,
the brilliant glow that surges
forth from that interstice...
must certainly reveal the path!
That's an unlikely bet you're taking.
What do you even plan to do there?
You say you wish to reclaim your lost time
and rectify the mistakes of your past?
That's right.
I'll take it all back.
The past and future that belong to me and Alicia!
I'll regain it all...
It was never meant to be this way...
not any part of this world we're living in!
The world... is always filled with things
that were never meant to be!
Since the beginning of time,
for everyone... that's how it is!
Do you plan to run away from a reality that
wasn't supposed to be? Or will you face it?
It's up to you!
But no one has the right to
interfere with other people's lives
just because of their own selfish grief!
Mother!
What did you come here for?
Go away. I no longer
have any need for you.
I've come to tell you something.
I...
I... am not Alicia Testarossa.
I may just be a doll you created.
However, I... Fate Testarossa...
was given life and raised by you.
I am your daughter!
So what? You expect me to think
of you as my daughter now?
If you...
wish for it...
If you wish for it, I will protect you from
everyone and everything in the world.
Not because I'm your daughter...
but because... you're my mother!
Ridiculous.
This is bad!
Captain! You can't stay there!
The Garden is going to collapse!
Please return to the ship!
A dimensional dislocation won't be
able to occur after the collapse!
Chrono-kun and the rest of you, please escape too!
There's no time left before
it completely caves in!
Understood!
Fate Testarossa!
Fate!
I'm going... to Al-Hazard!
And I will regain everything!
Both my past, and my future!
I will regain the single happiness I once had!
Mother!
Fate!
Let's go together... Alicia.
We won't be separated this time...
Fate!
Everyone, please! Escape! Hurry!
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
The incident is
finally at an end.
The conclusion is upon us,
as is the time for farewells.
But an ending is always...
the beginning of something else.
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 13
Call My Name
Final Episode:
Call My Name.
Lyrical Magical,
we'll see each other again, right?