We can't do this.
Sorry. Imanity's finished.
Wh-What do you mean?
After all that buildup?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't expect it to be set in Tokyo.
I can't do anything here.
It's our home,
but we're the away team.
We can't help you, so I'm sorry,
Is this your world, Masters?
but please handle this yourselves.
We can't do it.
You are incredibly popular.
So popular that girls from
all around the world are after you.
But in your heart,
there is only one woman you love.
Nonetheless, if faced with too many
temptations, your love will waver.
Can you make it through
all the temptations
and convey your feelings
to the one you love?
Living or Dead Series Side Story:
Love or Loved 2:
Hit Her With Your Bullet of Love!
Living or Dead Series Side Story:
Love or Loved 2:
Hit Her With Your Bullet of Love!
Kill
ing Gi
ant
Kill
ing Gi
ant
Kill
ing Gi
ant
Kill
ing Gi
ant
Can you hear me?
Welcome to the game world.
This fictional field is where
our contest will take place.
Wait.
Yes?
Let me confirm something.
This is a fictional place.
It doesn't really exist.
In other words, it's a virtual world
you invented for your game?
That's right. Why?
Don't scare me like that!
Damn it!
That brought back
some deep-rooted trauma!
Don't make misleading stuff like that!
Why are you so upset?
Damn you, old man!
Do you have a problem with the level?
Of course I do! Why the hell
would you use this place, of all things?
Is this psychological warfare?
You trying to screw with me?
This is a science fiction level very popular
among the youth of the Eastern Federation.
That is the only reason
it was chosen, but don't worry.
It's a game, so to an extent,
you will be safe.
That explains why
I can be out in the sun.
Shiro! Calm down! This isn't Tokyo!
It only looks like it! It's just
some place they dreamed up!
That's right. This is a game,
*
just like Pers*na,
or Stein's G*te, or Akiba's Tr*p!
As long as we're in a game, we're fine!
A game?
Okay. Got it.
All right. We're fine now.
Let's get started.
Allow me to explain
the rules to you all, then.
First, please take note
of the box at your feet.
You'll use those guns to
shoot the NPCs who chase you.
We're shooting them?
Through careful aiming
and well-timed detonations,
you'll make them
fall in love with you.
*
Isn't that G*l Gun?
The girls who fall in love with you will
give you their love power and disappear.
The ammo fired from the
love gun is your own love power!
So this is called the "love gun"?
Lame.
However, if Izuna shoots one of you,
you'll become her love slave!
I love Izuna!
I love
Izuna
<3
I love
Izuna
<3
Can't you just say,
"you'll join her side"?
But even as girls from
all over the world look your way,
your one true love will not!
Your goal is to reach her with your love power
and have her fall head-over-heels for you!
That concludes the explanation!
So basically, I just have
to reject every girl I see?
Who do I think I am?
In other words, Izuna wants a harem ending
with the four of us, but we're after her only.
That's correct.
One last note: magic cannot be used
in the virtual world, so do be careful.
Well?
Would you like a more detailed
explanation of the rules?
Nah. I'll figure them out as I play.
Let's try this.
Firing the love gun
depletes your love power.
Defeating NPCs restores your love power.
What is going on? This is too creepy!
If an NPC touches you,
your love power depletes,
and if it runs out,
the NPCs will leave you alone.
Huh? What's wrong?
However, you'll no longer
be able to power the love gun,
which means you can't fight.
So what happens if you
shoot an ally, old man?
You can restore love power
to an ally who has run out.
You can also save companions who
have been turned into Izuna's love slaves,
but the one shot temporarily becomes
...a love slave of the one who shot—
Master!
Oh, my sister!
I had no idea such a cute, beautiful girl
was so close to me this whole time.
I wish I could gouge out
my eyes in shame.
...Bro, we can't. We're sibli—
Jibril!
I love you!
Shiro?
Are you rejecting your brother's love?
So this is the "love triangle" and "NTR"
I saw in my master's books!
Shiro! My beloved Shiro!
I don't even possess the emotion
of love, but somehow it excites me!
Jibril, you'll be punished later.
Oh, forgive me, Shiro!
I see.
When you're a love slave,
I couldn't hold back my curiosity!
you lose all ability to defend or control yourself.
I found you!
You all left me on my own again!
...That's horribl—
Sora! My prince!
Steph, do you understand
the rules so far?
Love doesn't need rules!
Even if I don't know them, our love is eternal!
Of course you don't.
So put this here, and this here,
...Oh, my...
My heart is pounding!
and then pull your index finger in.
...Huh? What am I—
I'm so beau-ti-ful!
I thought so. It bounces off of things.
I'll never let myself go!
That's the key, Shiro.
I'm so cute!
Leave it to me.
Also, even though we're in a game,
our stamina doesn't
change much from real life.
Keep your running to a minimum.
Yeah.
Okay,
let's go, you two!
Looks like it's finally getting started.
Can you see it, Fi?
Yeah, I can.
I'm borrowing your eyes, Clammy.
The Werebeasts must hate this magic.
It's hard to maintain this spell,
but I'll do my best for you, Clammy!
The Werebeasts' strength and speed are said
to push the limits of what's physically possible.
How can one fight
against such a fearsome race?
Show me, Sora.
Hey, Izuna.
When's the last time
you thought a game was fun?
Damn it!
I knew it!
That's what makes this game special!
This is all the motivation I need!
Target: NPC's cotton panties.
Cotton max thickness: 1 millimeter.
12 o' clock.
Distance: 20050.
Firing angle: 93.
300 meters per second.
Acceptable targeting error:
within 0.5 millimeters.
But I can do it!
Fire!
What?
Damn it!
I failed!
Why?!
This race is beyond saving.
Fools, every last one of them.
Why the hell are you having fun? Please.
If you lose, many people will be unhappy,
so you have to win!
...But if you win, your opponent...
Yes! Bra destroyed!
Hand bra for the win!
Of course I've never
thought it was fun. Please.
...These footsteps...
Is that Shiro?
She's coming this way.
Shiro, you're mine.
I missed!
That's impossible!
What?!
This can't be happening!
I'm sure you're surprised
right now, Izuna.
We've played first-person shooters
against the best players in the world,
but I'm not the one
who holds all the records.
That would be Shiro.
Futile.
Her terrifying powers of calculation
allow her to grasp her enemies' movements,
and her firing intervals
and dodges take into account
everything from her understanding of your
movement patterns to how fast you can fire,
almost verging on precognition.
It feels like your bullets
are passing right through her,
and hers are tracking you
like guided missiles, right?
This is insane! Please.
I have to run! Please.
Hi!
I'm so glad you could join us.
...It's the Flugel...
Jibril!
A bomb to blind her.
Huh?
Oh, right! I can't fly!
Jibril!
I can't dodge it!
Master!
My master, please come back to me!
I see.
She can use her clothes as a shield.
What's going on?
The king and queen are amazing!
Imanity's winning!
Did you see that, Fi?
Indeed. I saw it through your eyes.
Shiro's firing skills are amazing,
but that was even more impressive.
Yes. I can't believe she was able to sense
and dodge Sora's shot before it was even fired,
when he was so far away
and completely silent.
...That must be...
That must be the Werebeasts'
sixth sense, I suppose.
Don't be stupid.
That's not a sixth sense.
She straight-out saw the future.
...So...
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
They must be cheating.
This game is a scam!
I see. A cheat you can't prove.
If they say it's a sixth sense,
there's nothing you can do.
So they are familiar
with this kind of game.
More than we are, in fact.
...But...
Izuna!
They're in the corridor below you.
Shiro is exhausted and can't move.
Take them out now!
You don't need to tell me. Please.
No matter what
little tricks they may have,
there's no way they can win.
So now we're finally
on the defensive.
Jeez.
I'm counting on you, Shiro.
We weren't able to
finish this at the start,
so now we'll have to wing it.
Wing it?
We're trying to play a fair game against
cheaters who know the game inside and out?
...That means...
Your luck just ran out, Sora!
I'm getting you back for all you've
done to me, and for my dear Izuna!
You're so mean, Jibril!
Where did you go? You left me!
It was a bad idea to bring her along.
I won't let you go anymore!
I'm smiling?
And my heart is pounding so loud.
When's the last time
you thought a game was fun?
Shut up! Please!
Shiro, what's our next strategy?
Jibril, shut up!
Master, maybe this really is impossible,
even for Shiro.
No, she can do it.
If there's something I can't
do in a game, Shiro can do it.
That's always been true,
and it always will be.
...Bro...
Do you believe in me?
Has your brother ever doubted you?
...Okay, Bro...
...this time...
it's your turn, okay?
What?
...No—
Shiro!
Shiro?
It's over, isn't it?
I don't understand why
Shiro protected you, Master.
Yeah.
Well, I do, so don't worry.
It's not that Shiro
couldn't find the answer.
That was the answer.
It was blank.
In other words, us.
Everything, including Shiro's joining
the enemy's side, is Blank's power.
In other words, it's up to me to complete the magic
formula that will lead us to the promised victory.
That's right, isn't it, Shiro?
Jibril.
Fight Izuna to buy me time.
...Th-That's fine, but...
You don't mind if
I just happen to beat her,
do you?
I might as well tell you.
That's a death flag, right there.
What?
No need to hold anything back, then.
That makes this easier.
Where did she go?
Hello there, my sweet puppy.
I'm feeling a distinct sense of déjà vu.
The last time I challenged
the Eastern Federation and lost,
were you perchance my opponent?
Master told me to buy time,
...but since we're both here...
let's have some fun.
Throw every cheat you've got at me,
and embarrass yourself
to your heart's content.
No, damn it!
Going to a different area
isn't going to help!
What the hell am I
supposed to do, Shiro?
I need to run to the roof.
No, she'll be ready for that.
Either way, she'll catch up to me soon.
Wait. Something's not right.
Why isn't Shiro running after me?
If she were running, she'd have
any number of chances to defeat me.
Keep your running to a minimum.
Yeah.
Wasn't I the one who told her that?
If I get this wrong,
it's going to be rough.
...But, well...
Okay, Shiro.
Your brother's just about had it.
This is a tough game for a guy
who never leaves his room.
Your brother can't
make a mistake now!
...Shiro, the one thing you'd never expect...
You never thought I wouldn't
try to dodge at all, did you?
I love you, Bro!
I love you too.
Now, Izuna!
That took way too damn long. Please.
This is why you saved your strength
and didn't run, right, Shiro?
I love you, Bro.
...Impossible...
Sora just shot her.
How can she still fight?
Her panties are gone!
It can't be!
Was it really only
her panties that got hit?!
You finally figured it out?
Shiro was never on your side.
She let the shot hit her shirt button
and pretended to be under my control!
They fooled me!
But that doesn't mean anything.
It'll take more than that!
When's the last time
you thought a game was fun?
This is fun!
dare ni mo ienai
With a loneliness
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That I could share with no one, I was crying all alone
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, deep inside our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshiyatte
We pushed away the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura wa kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furun deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By finding and piecing together the fragmented expressions
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuite ikun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
As we pray to the sky
douka eien ni
For this moment to last forever
Rule Number 10
We're almost there! Give your power to Blank!
Ready!