Over 100 years ago, natural
predators of humanity appeared.
There was an insurmountable gap
in power between them and mankind,
and as a result, the humans
soon faced utter annihilation.
The survivors responded by constructing three
walls—Wall Maria, Wall Rose, and Wall Sina—
which graced them with 100 years of peace.
However...
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
The Whereabouts of His Left Arm
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑤
The absence of the elite Survey Corps
was one of the reasons for
the substantial casualties
sustained in Trost District
during the Titan assault.
Just earlier that morning, the Survey Corps had
departed for an expedition beyond the walls.
A Few Hours Ago
They're here!
It's the main force of the Survey Corps!
Commander Erwin, please give
those Titans a good beating for us!
Look! It's Lance Corporal Levi!
They say he's as strong as an entire brigade!
Damn, what a racket.
I wonder if you'd still get this much praise if
they realized how much of a neat freak you are.
Just beyond this wall...
lies a world of Titans.
I wonder what kind of Titan I'll meet today.
If only I was lucky enough
to run into an Abnormal!
There's already one nearby.
Huh, where?
Right here.
Onward!
To survey the lands outside and secure
a base of operations beyond the walls.
As the epitome of human skill and intellect,
the members of the Survey Corps
were given this mission.
Their survival rates were higher than
ever due to their resourcefulness,
but whenever troops were
dispatched into Titan territory,
more than thirty percent
of them never made it back.
The gap in strength between Titans
and humans was simply that great.
Just... watch...
you bastards...
Mankind will eradicate you.
In the end, we'll be the ones who survive!
You bastards... will be destroyed...
by Lance Corporal Levi!
One to the right.
Another two to the left.
Lance Corporal, I've gathered reinforcements!
Petra, you go free the injured soldier below.
Everyone else attack the one on the right.
I'll take care of the ones on the left.
Lance Corporal!
Don't worry!
I'm not trying to hurt you.
Too slow!
Now's my turn!
There!
See? Didn't feel a thing, did you?
Ripe for the picking.
You all look ridiculous.
Quit moving.
You're making it difficult for me to get a clean cut.
Disgusting.
Lance Corporal, I can't stop the bleeding.
Lance... Corporal.
What?
W-Was I... useful to... mankind?
Or am I... going to die...
having achieved nothing?
You've contributed more than enough.
And you'll continue doing so.
I'll carry on your will, and it will grant me strength!
I swear to you, I shall exterminate
the Titans no matter the cost!
Lance Corporal, he's no longer...
Did he hear everything I said?
Yes, I'm sure he did.
He's resting so peacefully, after all.
That's good.
Levi!
We're withdrawing.
Withdrawing?
There's still more we can accomplish here.
Did my men die for nothing?
The Titans are all heading north toward the city.
It's the same as five years ago.
Something's happening in the city.
The wall may no longer be intact.
Damn it...
Damn it!
This... This wasn't supposed to...
We're no longer the weaklings
we were five years ago.
We trained to become soldiers.
We believed we were soldiers.
All so we could beat them.
All so we could survive and protect.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Help me.
Mom...
Mom!
Help...
Why did this happen?
Why are we robbed of everything?
Our lives and our dreams...
Why?
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it all!
Hell if I'm gonna give up!
I'll exterminate them!
I won't spare a single one.
I'll make sure of it!
I'll exterminate them...
from this world...
I won't spare a single one!
More! More!
I'll kill more!
I want to kill more!
More. Way more.
I'll kill you all.
Eren?
Eren!
Eren, can you move?
Are you back to yourself now?
Tell us everything that happened!
I'm sure they'll understand!
Armin?
Hear that? He said, "I'll kill you all."
Yeah, no doubt about it.
He wants to devour us all.
What's going on?
Why are their swords turned toward us?
They're weapons for killing Titans with!
Why are they looking at me like that?
What's... going on?
Currently
Disclosable
Information
The Current Survey Corps Part ①
The Survey Corps' main objective is to scout the area
beyond the walls. But since the fall of Wall Maria,
its operations have extended beyond that
Currently
Disclosable
Information
The Current Survey Corps Part ②
Its duties now entail establishing supply bases and
maintaining routes for large troop movements in
the second plan to recapture Wall Maria.
Within Wall Rose
Recruits are to maintain their
equipment and wait for orders!
So that's how we refilled our gas
and got out of Trost District.
I see.
I'm really sorry.
We requested supply support for
you guys multiple times, but...
We finally got our hands on some too.
S-So the people that aren't here are all...
Yeah.
Even Mikasa?
N-No, I thought she came back
later with Jean and the others.
Jean! Don't tell me Mikasa is injured.
Hey, what's wrong?
We were ordered to keep that confidential.
I can't say.
Confidential?
Seriously?
Although it's not something they
can keep under wraps for long.
It's only a matter of time
before everyone finds out.
That is, assuming people live to hear of it.
A defensive wall of flesh
using the Titans themselves.
The engineering squad has outdone itself.
But we still can't let our guard down.
This is the front line between us and
the Titans, as well as the edge of a cliff.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Our mission is proceeding smoothly,
but I'm worried about the safety
of my comrades in the vanguard.
A messenger headed to HQ earlier
with a deathly pale expression.
Right, but we need to devote
ourselves to interception,
just like we've been trained to.
I heard the three kids you rescued five
years ago have all become recruits.
They're also in the vanguard.
Yes.
My apologies.
I shouldn't have brought that up.
They're safe.
They're strong kids, and each one
has their own means of survival.
One has advanced combat skills,
another has tenacious strength of will,
and the last has a sharp mind.
They're safe.
Alive and well for sure.
Recruit Jaeger, as well as
Recruits Ackerman and Arlert!
Your present actions are treason!
What do you have to say in your defense?
Any attempts to mislead or escape will be met
with a bombardment of high-explosive shells!
This is no bluff!
Let me be frank!
What are you?
A human or a Titan?
What kind of question is that?
Why are they glaring?
It's as if they're looking at a monster.
Is that what they see me as?
I do not understand that question!
Feigning ignorance?
Damn monster, I dare you to try that again!
We'll blast you to pieces in an instant!
We won't even give you time
to show your true colors!
True colors?
There are plenty of witnesses!
We all saw the moment you
emerged from within a Titan!
Mankind has allowed strange creatures
like you to get past Wall Rose!
Even if you're part of the Training Corps,
which is under the King's authority,
the risk you present is too serious to ignore!
No doubt about it!
There's a chance the Armored Titan that broke
through Wall Maria could appear again!
Mankind once again stands
at the brink of extinction!
Understand?
We cannot afford to waste
further troops or time on you!
We'll just bombard you lot
with high-explosive shells!
True, their defiance is all but subtle.
Furthermore, I doubt they'll
give us any useful information.
As you said, this is a waste of troops and time.
Captain, now's our best chance!
We can kill him now while
he's still in his human form.
My strength lies in slicing off flesh.
If I'm forced to demonstrate,
I'll show no hesitation.
If any of you wish to experience this personally,
please feel free to approach me.
Captain, that's Mikasa Ackerman,
one of us elites in the rear guard.
Her skills alone make her as
valuable as a hundred soldiers.
Losing her would be a
devastating loss for mankind.
Hey, Mikasa, Armin!
What's going on?
Mikasa, what's the point in fighting with them?
Where can we escape to within
the confines of these walls?!
Regardless of who it might be,
I won't let anyone kill Eren.
That's reason enough.
We need to convince them!
None of them understand the situation,
so they're being controlled by fear!
Am I the only one who sees me as a human?
Damn, I can't remember what
happened before I was here!
I feel so sluggish that I can't stand,
and they'll kill me if I don't watch my words.
Getting killed by humans is ridiculous!
What's this about anyway?
I emerged from within a Titan?
What're they talking about?
What does that mean?
Wasn't that all a dream?
But if it wasn't, that means
the arm I lost before grew back!
Just like a Titan's!
That's impossible.
Why did this happen? Why?
I'll ask you once again!
Just what are you?!
In any case, I can't afford to answer wrong.
It's not only my life that's on the line.
That's right. I've always...
been the same as you guys...
I'm human!
I see.
Don't think ill of me.
There's no other way.
No man can prove...
that he's not a demon, after all.
Eren, Armin, we're going up!
Stop!
Eren.
When I return, I'll show you the basement
that I've always kept a secret.
Keep this key with you and
never let it out of your sight.
And when you look at it, remember.
Remember that you must go to that basement!
Your memories will be
affected by these injections.
So it's pointless for me to explain now.
Listen.
Recapture Wall Maria and go to that basement!
This power should prove useful then!
Your memories should teach you how to use it!
Eren!
Upon reaching that basement
you'll discover the truth!
It'll be a hard and unforgiving
journey, but you must succeed!
If you want to save Mikasa,
Armin, and everyone else,
you must learn to master this power!
Did that do it?
Dear lord...
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba
Eren is not the enemy of mankind.
Armin stands up for him, risking his life.
But the Garrison, which abandoned reason in fear,
decides to execute Eren.
Response
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑥