The universe had a
beginning, but has no end.
Infinite.
The stars, too, had beginnings,
but their own power
leads them to their destruction.
Finite.
History dictates that it is the
wise who are the most foolish.
One could call this a
final warning from God,
to those who can still resist.
Okarin!
Let's go.
Prologue
to
the
Beginning
and
End
Initiating infiltration of the building.
El. Psy. Congroo.
There aren't many people here.
As I suspected,
the Organization may be interfering...
What's going to happen here?
You came here, without even knowing?
A time machine...
Professor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
Amazing!
Professor Nakabachi has
surpassed the rest of us scientists,
and is ready to announce
the invention of the century.
I'm going to pay careful
attention to what he has to say.
An earthquake?
No, from above?
What's this?
You called me here for this?
There aren't many left of this series,
and Mayushii's out of 100 yen coins!
Don't act so spoiled, Mayuri.
Even though I've known you since we
were kids, I'm not lending you any money.
I'll teach you how harsh life can be...
What's this?
It's not painted?
M-Metal...
It's a metal...
A metal Upa!
Is it rare?
Really!
Then you can have it.
Are you sure, Okarin?
It's Hououin Kyouma.
Thanks, Okarin.
I said it's Hououin Kyouma.
Professor Nakabachi's press conference
will now begin in the 8th floor's hall.
In the handouts, you can read about
the time machine's basic design.
I will use this conference as an opportunity
to discuss the fundamental theory behind it.
Scientists all over the world...
Received Mail
Time:
Sender: Mayuri
Subject: My Upa...
I think I dropped my metal Upa,
so I'm going to look for it.
Currently, there are over ten major theories of possible methods of time travel,
Basic design of the time machine...
and they've been examined from nearly every possible angle.
Doctor!
What is it?
You know exactly what!
What is this "time machine theory" of yours?
Kerr black holes?
World lines?
You stole all of this from John Titor!
Titor called himself a time traveler,
and posted this theory on the Internet back in 2000.
Don't try to claim you didn't know!
How rude!
Of course I know about him!
Don't compare my
theory to that fraud's!
Then why don't you explain
the differences between your theories?
Hey, you...
Titor, huh?
Come to think of it, there was
similar stuff in the John Titor books...
Who are you?
That's what I'd like to know.
What?
Back there, you were
going to tell me something,
weren't you?
Back there?
About fifteen minutes ago.
I don't have the slightest idea...
Makise... Kurisu?
You had a paper in
Science Magazine a while ago.
I'm surprised you know of it.
Are you a university scientist?
You!
Are you an agent
from the Organization?
Organization?
What?
I just wanted to ask you...
There's no need for me to answer you!
It's me.
I've been caught by
an Organization agent.
Yes.
Makise Kurisu.
Who are you talking to?
Yeah, no problem.
I'll get out of this somehow...
Huh? It's turned off.
I'll tell you a secret.
That's a special cell phone,
for secret missions.
If anyone but me
touches it, it turns off.
I see.
You were talking to yourself.
I'll make this brief.
What were you going to tell me?
About fifteen minutes ago.
You were trying to tell
me something, weren't you?
It seemed like it was really important...
I've seen through your tricks.
Girl genius, when next we meet, we will be enemies.
Farewell.
Wait!
What was she talking about?
She met me?
Date: 2010/07/28 12:26
Sender: sg-epk@jtk92.x29.jp
Subject: (No Subject)
Attachment: IMV001
Received Mail
Okarin!
Mayuri!
What were you doing?
I messaged you, didn't I?
I can't find my metal Upa.
I even put my name on it...
You dropped it?
I think so.
Give up.
On auction sites, a metal
Upa goes for 10,000 yen!
10,000 yen...
Find it!
My lab is almost entirely out of money!
Even if I find it, I won't sell it.
With 10,000 yen, we
could acquire the parts
for a new future gadget...
I said I'm not selling it.
What was that?
Run outside!
Hey...
Is someone there?
Makise Kurisu...
What?
Someone's been stabbed...
Okarin!
What's wrong?
You're pale.
I saw a dead body...
On the 8th floor!
Looks like someone stabbed Makise Kurisu.
To: Daru
Subject: Trouble
Send?
Wh-What?
What's going on?
Here you go, Okarin!
What is this?
What's what?
The people... Why did
all the people disappear?
They disappeared?
They all disappeared!
All the people here!
Right in front of us!
I don't know...
You have to know!
You saw it, didn't you?
Right?
I didn't.
What are you talking about...
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
is a trivial matter with little glamor for you
Even trapped in the past and lamenting the future
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
The dreams that stretch into "infinity" and the future we imagine
are vain privileges we allowed ourselves
"Finity", that's what the two hands of the clock show
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
and protect your smile
And once again, a solitary observer
is sucked into a time loop without sadness
Hey, you there!
Can you see us?
Why don't you answer?
You, on the other side of the
monitor, with the dumb expression!
Never mind.
This is the Future Gadget Lab.
I'll introduce our staff.
First is Lab Member 001,
founder of the lab and
Insane Mad Scientist...
Myself, Hououin Kyouma!
Okarin is cuter.
Silence!
Okabe Rintarou is the name I
use to deceive the general public.
Lab Member 002,
the lab's lone female member,
whose hobby is making cosplay outfits,
Shiina Mayuri!
It's me, Mayushii.
And Lab Member 003,
Super Haker Hashida Itaru!
It's "Hacker", not "Haker". Hurr.
We three.
Isn't it time to give up?
Don't expect too much out of software you bought at a 500 yen wagon sale.
Listen well.
Future Gadget Lab
CRT
TV
Work-
shop
To get to our lab, go down Chuo Street,
and turn left on Kuramae Street
at the Suehirochou intersection.
We're in a multi-use
building, in the first alley
before the traffic light.
The goal of the Future Gadget Lab
is to revolutionize the
world's ruling structure...
To create inventions
which will bring chaos.
Do you understand?
If you understand,
then tell us your secrets!
Hey, do you think we look
like a video game to that Alpaca Man?
Don't you think the
concepts of what's real and unreal
are a little beyond him?
Then are your 2D girls like that, too?
That's different.
Those are mai waifus.
No one cares about your wives.
But isn't that an interesting proposition?
If we did exist solely inside a monitor,
do you think there's any way we could tell?
No.
That was fast.
Thus, this discussion is pointless.
We'd do much better to spend our time
thinking of ways to
fight the Organization
and destroy the world's ruling structure.
That delusional crap again? Fail!
Silence, Super Haker!
I am the Insane Mad Scientist, Hououin...
Kyouma!
That's your backstory, isn't it?
My, my... Daru.
You shouldn't go hiding in your shell.
You should listen to
what others have to say.
So, this is today's "you're the last
one I want to hear that from" thread.
Anyways, it looks like the
news chopper's arrived.
This object, thought to be some kind of satellite, crashed in Akihabara, Tokyo,
Special Report
Where did it come from?
A mysterious satellite appears!!
around 12 o'clock today.
What was that?
This morning, Mayuri and I left the lab for the radio building,
to attend Professor
Nakabachi's press conference.
But the next thing I knew, a satellite had crashed into the building.
And not just that...
Me?
Yeah... You saw the
satellite crash on TV and said,
"The Organization has
finally made its move!"
So the two of us came to see it.
Canceled?
Don't you remember how angry
you were this morning? Saying, "he got cold feet and ran off!"
Professor Nakabachi's press conference!
It was at 12 o'clock, at the radio building!
No, it wasn't, man.
And a good thing, too...
If it had, that satellite
would have flattened you.
This discrepancy in memories...
Is it the Organization's memory control?
Right...
This is the choice of Steins Gate!
That again?
That Stein-whatsit makes
no sense, you know?
Daru, get me Future Gadget #1!
Alpaca Man got mad because you changed the channel.
Darn you, Mr. Braun!
Making us use this piece of crap...
He gave it to us for free, didn't he?
Daru, get the TV!
I refuse.
It's hot today.
And like,
don't think I'm strong,
just 'cause I'm fat.
That's not something to brag about!
Mr. Braun!
I told you to call me Tennouji.
I'd like to ask you to
fix this immediately...
You broke it already?
You don't have enough
love for the Braun tubes.
1,000 yen to fix it.
If anyone's at fault here, wouldn't it be you, for giving us something defective?
Is that how you address your landlord?
I'll pay the repair bill.
Mayuri, you should give up on this guy.
But Mayushii is Okarin's hostage!
Hostage, huh?
Is this broken as well?
Repair bill's 2,000 yen now.
You don't like it, take it back.
What will you do?
It's me.
The Organization's finally
gotten to that stupid baldy.
I'm encountering sabotage.
Here you go.
You really do like Dr Pepper, Okarin!
It's an intellectual drink,
for the chosen ones.
The cicadas are really
loud, aren't they?
Daru!
Now that the Organization
has begun using Mr. Braun to sabotage us, we're putting the plan into action.
We're backed into a corner!
The plan? The what now?
The plan is the plan!
What else could it be
but the introduction of
Future Gadget #8 to an
actual combat situation?
Oh, the Phone Microwave.
(name subject to change)
How do you use a microwave in combat anyway?
It'll be nearly three and
a half years since we'd met.
Second year of high school...
We were in different classes and barely spoke,
so it's more like two years?
The details don't matter.
Anyway, it's been that long.
Please reach the point
where you can keep up with my conversations already.
That is.... Im-po-ssi-ble.
Actually, want to try again?
It's all set.
Mayuri, bring the bananas!
You're making gel-banas again?
It's such a waste!
If we're stingy, we can't win against the Organization!
We don't need to win...
You know Mayushii will
bring the bananas, right?
I know.
This is R-E-N-G, the Phone
Microwave. (name subject to change)
You can manipulate the timer here.
Please press the pound key,
and then the number of
seconds you wish to time cook.
One, two, zero, pound.
Pretty turntable, isn't it?
It goes in the opposite direction.
Opposite?
Might be important!
When you think of what's
happening at the quantum level,
and you apply Hund's rules...
I'm sure it... isn't.
It isn't?
Nope.
Hasn't changed.
It doesn't get warm,
and it doesn't get cold.
Mayushii's Juicy Fried Chicken #1 froze...
Well, something involving Steins Gate is at work here! That's clear, anyway!
That again?
Daru, don't you want to try eating this?
No, I don't.
Then we'll give the honor to Mayuri.
The gel-bana was soft and squishy.
And it had no taste.
You ate it?
Mayushii?
Say, "your banana is soft and squishy."
"Your banana is soft?"
Don't make her say that, pervert!
I-I'm melting...
It hasn't been ten minutes
since we left the lab.
When the summer gets hot, I don't
want to go any farther than Feyris's.
I wish they'd just hold it
at MayQueen Nyan Nyan.
They're not going to hold a
university lecture at a maid cafe.
If they didn't take
attendance, I'd never go.
It's so cold.
I'm alive.
A satellite fell, didn't it?
That again?
You're not going to the
radio building to see it?
Probably too many onlookers to see anything anyway.
I'm reading the reports on @chan,
from the people who went.
"Work Temporarily Canceled."
Another giant thread?
Oh, right. Back then...
Give me your cell phone.
Why?
Just do it!
That's a violation of privacy! Not allowed!
I sent you a message!
A message about Makise
Kurisu being stabbed.
Oh, the one from last week?
Last week?
It was split into three messages.
I thought it was spam!
See?
Okabe Rintarou
(No Subject)
Sent on July 23rd, 12:56...
"Looks like
someone stabbed
Makise Kurisu."
See?
Last week... Let me check my sent folder.
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
It's not here!
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Daru
Re:
(No subject)
What is today?
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
The... The 28th.
What's wrong?
The message was sent to the past...
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten