Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
Korokun
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Rika-chama
Tressflin
Saoen
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetters
ThaEagle
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
I guess we'll be practicing with just the mouthpiece for a while.
Is there a problem?
No!
Well... you see, I was just thinking "I want to learn how to play as well as Rio-senpai as soon as possible," so...
My ways are Spartan.
Yes, ma'am!  Please teach me properly!
Next is breakfast.
The cafeteria is that way.  You head over there first.
Yes, ma'am!
Feels rough and rugged.
We'll be friends starting today, all right?
Oh!
Good morning!
You suck!
Wow!
Actually, this had been prepared as a welcoming meal for you last night.
Just a little something for you.
Thank you very much!
Oh, that's right, Rio, did you bring down the dried fish from upstairs?
No, I wasn't told about it.
That's strange...
Come on, Noel, you can do it!
If you're gonna nap, at least eat first!
Can-do, right...
Can't you try any harder?!
I am.
That's... Rio-senpai's...
Hurry up.  The food'll get cold.
To start off, allow me to formally introduce you to the members of Platoon 1121.
First, our Platoon Captain.
I'm Second Lieutenant Phylicia Heideman, the tank commander.
Let's have a great time together!
I look forward to working with you.
And this is...
Hey, Noel.
'm Kannagi Noel...
Well, this is Corporal Kannagi, the driver.  She also serves as our engineer.
Pleased to meet you.
And lastly...
Private Second Class, Suminoya Kureha.  I'm the gunner.
And listen up.
I may be younger, but I still have seniority over you so you'd better listen to what—
Finally ran out of steam, huh?
You did your best, Noel-chan.
Well then, let's start eating, shall we?
Huh?
But...
Whatever, I was done!
Now then, it's time to eat.
Thanks for the food!
Oh, this is so good!
That bacon is homemade.  Eat a lot, all right?
Yes, ma'am!
Both as a soldier and trumpeter, the body is your most important resource.
Eat well and build yourself up.
I'll give my all.
Kureha.
Y-Yes?!
When you're finished eating, show her around the base.
Understood.
Attention!
I'm really busy and don't have time for this, but since it was an order, I've no choice but to show you around.
R-Right!  I hope we work well together, Kureha-san!
Don't refer to me so familiarly, Private Second Class Sorami!
My apologies!
Um...
Private Second Class Suminoya, ma'am!
That's better.
So first off, face the national flags and the platoon...
Salute!
Our 1121 Platoon currently consists of five members.
Broken down: one Second Lieutenant, one Sergeant Major, one Corporal,
and two Private Second Class, for a total of five.
Yes, Private Second Class Suminoya, ma'am!
We may only have the minimum required to count as a platoon, but that just means...
that all of those gathered here are elites.
Understood!
Given to our platoon were:
one tank,
one heavy machine gun,
two light machine guns,
four rifles,
and five handguns.
With only these resources at our disposal, our mission is to maintain the national border of all of Trois, Seize!
Um...
P-Private Second Class Suminoya, ma'am, I have a question!
Very well.  I permit you to speak, Private Second Class Sorami.
If I, um... If my memory serves correctly, beyond Seize is...
It's certainly true that No-Man's Land exists beyond the mountains.
However, Helvetia's borders extend only up to here, so this is our national border!
The front lines!
An important position!
As such, we must never fail in our vigilance.
Through the night, the five of us take shifts.
Sleeping while on watch is strictly prohibited!
And this here is the only hotline in this city that connects to the capital.
Meaning...!
If this rings, something serious is happening!
So if that goes off, everyone is woken up and we immediately initialize the first level of security alert!
Is that clear?!
Yes, Private Second Class Suminoya, ma'am!
On the second floor are the Captain's quarters and the tactics room!
Normally, entrance is...!
It's really as you please, but...
make sure you knock first!
This is the bathroom.
Heating water for the bath as well as cleaning duties are all done on rotation.
Also...
Bathing is done in order of rank.  Am I right?
No.
After all, it's more fun if everyone gets in together, right?
Captain!
What are you doing?
Cleaning the bathroom.
Isn't it Noel's turn today?
But she just looks so tired...
For the Captain to do this herself, it sets a bad example for the new recruit!
I'll do it myself later, so you just keep being serious and Captain-like please!
Now, take a good look at this!
This is the main battle tank that's been granted to us here of Platoon 1121.
An autonomous moving tank, Vector-Type Zero, the Takemikazuchi.
She's so much bigger than the one used in training!
This is one of the so-called Zero-Generation tanks, after all.
She's a legacy from a former age, with no more than ten like her left in the world.
I've heard of them!
I've heard they're really amazing tanks!
But her legs...
She's being repaired.
There aren't enough parts.
W-Well, it's true that the maintenance manual wasn't preserved and that we can hardly find any of the parts...
But...!
Because Noel is working hard on her for us, she'll turn out all right!
I won't let you call her useless, got it?!
I'm sure she will...
someday she'll definitely...
Don't make fun of us.
We're lax.
It's certainly true that our platoon is lax...
And also that we're called the "burden platoon of Seize," nothing more than decorations!
We're a pink branch of the army, yet we don't even having a working tank.
But...!
Kureha-chan.
The tour is complete!  You're dismissed!
Seems they're getting along quite well, doesn't it?
Are they?
It's reminiscent of the two of us when we first met.
Guess so.
Still, I'm a bit troubled.
Last night, after you went to put Kana-chan to bed...
Captain!  Why was the girl assigned part of communications?!
Wasn't the new recruit supposed to be only either a loader or a driver?!
It can't be helped.
Headquarters sent her here.
Things often happen not to work exactly the way we'd hope.
But...!
There, there.  It's okay.
Rio will continue to love you, just as she always has, up til now.
Of course, so will I.
Despite appearances, she's a sharp girl.  She might've picked up on something.
I see.
I guess something will need to be done, huh?
It was there.
Huh?
What was?
A ghost?!
Yeah.
That's just silly.
Knowing you, you were probably half-asleep, Noel.
I thought so.
"I thought so," what?!
I saw it, too.  The ghost.
It was by the barracks, right?
Yeah.
Don't you start in on this, too!
Huh?
But they're normally there, aren't they?  The ghosts?
I just told you not to say stuff like that, didn't I?!
Noel!  You cut it out, too!
If you're an engineer, go and investigate scientifically and then report back!
Don't wanna.
Why not?
'Cause I'm scared.
What are you saying?!
Ghosts don't exist!  They don't, they don't, they don't — absolutely don't!
I hold the same opinion as you.
Right?
Yeah.
Things like ghosts don't exist.
They don't exist!
Absolutely, positively!
Absolutely, positively don't!
Yes!
Go and do a thorough investigation of the place!
If you actually encounter it, sound your trumpet!
We'll send you reinforcements!
Why?
Excuse me, Private Second Class, ma'am.
What is it, Kana— Private Second Class?!
This is kind of...
exciting, isn't it?
The thunder is like a steady, marching beat and all...
This is a mission!
We're not playing around!
Listen, Kana— Private Second Class Sorami!
You go first!  I'll be your backup.
Right!
Okay then, press forward!
This area has supposedly been this way since before this place became a bastion.
What was it before?
There's no way for me to know something like that, is there?
Hurry up and get a move on!
Right.
They're ideograms.
I wonder what they say.
If you can't read it, then quit looking.
Wouldn't it be wonderful to be able to read it, though?
It's probably just some silly thing from a long time ago anyhow.
Hurry up, let's go.
Aren't you... scared?
Nope.
You dimwit.
I mean, after all, ghosts are entities that protect us, right?
Huh?
In the village where I was born, we hold a festival every year to welcome and thank the ghosts.
What kinda countryside did you drop out of?
Ghosts are things that possess people,
drink their blood,
move corpses,
and do all kinds of bad things!
T-That was dangerous, you know.
Rats can carry all sorts of horrible diseases, and...
What?
So you really are scared, aren't yo—
Are they gone?
Looks like it.
Hey, Kureha.
Private Second Class, ma'am?
I was thinking...
this place might have been a school, don't you think?
What?
Even in the capital, they don't have schools this big.
But in the past, there were more people here, right?
So I'm sure that in the past, this building was filled with children around our age,
studying together...
Oh!
What, what?
What?!
I'm sure they taught music here as well!
Even though it wasn't part of the military?
I mean, look!
It hasn't changed.
Even if I can't read their words...
D-sharp.
The sounds don't change.
What are you doing, going off in your own world like that?
W-What?
Hey, Kureha-chan! It's just wonderful, isn't it?
What is?
All of it!
Huh?
The city of Seize,
this bastion,
everyone in this platoon, everything!
We're just an insignificant little troop in the middle of nowhere.
Our tank doesn't work,
and they forget to resupply us a lot of the time, too.
And our missions are all superficial.
We're all so lax, and...
But you love it, don't you?
What?  What?  What is this?!
It's here!
No!  Wait up, Kureha!
Kanata!
Wow... amazing.
Of course it was!
I'm the gunner after all, for my beloved wonderful, just wonderful platoon... Platoon 1121!
So this is the true form of our ghost, huh?
What part of this looks like a ghost?
Hey, you.
You look a lot like that thief from yesterday, don't you?
You little...!  I'll eat you!
Stop that, Rio.
You shouldn't threaten an injured creature.
But!
I'm sure this little one doesn't have any other place to go, either.
And what was the emblem of our platoon again?
If you eat her, surely you'll be punished.
Right, Shuko-chan?
She even named it...
But I think that's wonderful.
You almost died yesterday because of this thing!
But thanks to her, I was able to have a great adventure today!
Right, Kureha-chan?
What are you talking about?
That was nowhere near what qualifies as an adventure!
Well, well.  I guess majority rules.
No.
These are Captain's orders.
But next time you steal food, you'll be punished, okay?
Got it?
Wow...
That was Rio this morning, right?
If it were Kanata every morning, I'm sure we'd get complaints from the citizens.
I'm sorry.
That's your seat, Kana-chan.
Kureha-chan?
I just happened to come across another chair that matched ours.
I-I didn't do it for your sake or whatever.
Thank you!
Hey!
What are you guys doing?  That's dangerous...
Ugh, cut it out!
Yeah, dangerous!
What are you guys doing?
Breakfast is...
Next time, A Day with the Platoon: Rio Runs!