Precure Love Link!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Cure... Heart...
A new Precure has been born!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Dundundun!
Cure Heart's Secret Identity is Exposed!
Hey, since when was there another one?
She may be a new recruit.
Talk about a pain...
Why you—
This chick...
I'm light!
What are you doing?
My body's moving heart-wrenchingly fast!
Guess I jumped too far.
Got you!
You threw me off!
No, you did!
Now I'm mad!
Selfish!
Just kidding, Selfiselfiselfiselfi!
If you fight any more,
your friend here might fall head over heels for you.
Wait, you can do that?
Man, you're dim.
The entire world revolves around King Selfish!
So we can use any underhanded tricks we want!
You're the dim ones!
That girl and I aren't friends or anything of the sort.
If you think that girl
would throw her life away to save mine,
you're gravely mistaken!
What did you say?
Self!
What?!
Cure Heart!
Cure Sword!
Self!
But why?
You don't need a reason to help people!
Self! Selfyself Seeelf!
Selfyselfalling!
Selfy!
Help me!
This should give birth to an excellent Selfish!
Could it be that the Selfish wasn't going berserk by choice?
Maybe it was forced into that form and didn't know what to do!
If so, I have to help!
This light...
The Cure Lovies...
Sharuru, let's go!
Sharuru!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love looooove!
This girl... purified a Selfish...
She did it!
Ha ha, you got wrecked!
Quiet, you!
It flew away.
That's a Psyche, a human heart.
Heart?
Everyone has self-centered feelings budding in their hearts.
People try not to give in to those feelings,
but the Selfish strengthen those self-centered thoughts and turn them into monsters!
I see...
Hello there!
I'm Cure Heart!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I thank you for saving me,
but don't let it go to your head.
As I said before,
you and I aren't friends or anything of the sort.
But we fought together, so we're partners!
We're practically friends!
You can't fight with that attitude.
Huh?
When they attack with their full strength,
will you be able to protect those dear to you?
Hey, wait!
I still need to ask...
Um...
How do I get my regular clothes back?
Why didn't you team up with her?
If you have a partner, we can search more—
Be quiet, Dabyi!
I don't need a partner!
Mana!
Aida!
Are you all right?
No injuries?
What about that crab monster?
Eh, I don't really know...
Huh?
But dude, this elevator hall...
wasn't it totally busted up?
I-It might've been!
Maybe it was all a dream?
Well, you're safe, and that's what counts.
Let's return to the bus.
Yeah!
I'm beat!
I knew today would have way too much to deal with!
It most certainly did, Happy Prince.
Who's that?
Long ago, on a street corner far away,
a statue with eyes of sapphire, buttons of ruby,
and a coat of gold stood in the image of a prince.
The prince asked a favor of a swallow.
O Swallow,
give to the impoverished citizens of this town
one piece of my body each!
A fairy tale?
Yes.
You've always been just like that prince, Mana.
You always try to make other people happy,
no matter how much it wears you down.
Aw, it doesn't wear me down much.
But there's something you still haven't told me.
What? How'd you know?
I haven't been your friend for ten years for nothing.
Tell me.
Well, as long as you don't flip out.
The truth is...
I transformed into a Precure.
Come again?
A fairy from the Trump Kingdom gave me a mysterious power.
I used that power to transform,
and I fought a bunch of selfish people!
Well, I chased a white rabbit down a hole,
and exposed the truth of a hidden world.
I'm not lying!
Mana!
Welcome back.
Welcome home!
I'm home!
Oh, welcome, Rikka!
Welcome.
Nice to see you.
Mana, we'll continue this tomorrow.
Huh? Wait!
Are you sure you want to go without dinner?
I'm fine!
Goodbye!
Wait, Rikka!
diner
Pig's Tail
Thanks for the food.
Seeya, Mana.
Thank you for coming!
I figured Rikka would've been the one person who'd believe me...
Then again, I barely believe it myself,
so of course nobody else would.
What've you been muttering about all day?
Guess I'm at that age where you have tons of problems.
Times like these call for piping hot food!
It's...
Your daddy's own special omelette rice.
Now, eat up!
Don't mind if I do!
It's so yummy!
Nothing gets my heart racing like this!
Now you're finally back to normal.
Huh?
I don't know what's been on your mind,
but if you're not brimming with energy, we all worry.
Not just your mother and I,
but your grandpa and Rikka, too.
You're right.
Daddy, can I ask you for something?
Meow!
What do you need at this hour?
Peach buns!
Daddy steamed them!
Wait, I'm coming down!
I'll be honest with her
Rikka should understand then.
You must not speak of the Precure's secret...
Huh?
I'm here!
Mana?
Who are you?
Heheheh...
Ta-dah!
They multiplied.
I'm Raquel!
I'm Lance!
We're all fairies from Trump Kingdom!
Hello there, I'm Aida Mana.
Oh yeah, I need to explain Precures to Rikka,
so you all can help.
You can't tell her that.
Why not?
You can't tell anyone about the existence of the Precures!
The Selfish will dye more peoples' hearts in darkness!
The only ones who can stop them are...
the le... legendary...
Warriors!
Yeah! The Precure warriors!
And you're one of them, Mana!
I understand that, but why can't I talk about it?
The Selfish plan to extend their dark rule to this world!
Anyone you tell the secret to will be dragged into the fight!
When they attack with their full strength,
will you be able to protect those dear to you?
I get it.
I won't say a thing.
Thank goodness!
I can't drag Rikka into something this dangerous...
Good.
I'm off!
Have a nice day.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Did those two fight or somethin'?
Beats me.
Thanks for last night's snacks.
Huh? Oh, how were they?
They were great.
Too bad we couldn't eat together.
Mana...
Wh-What?
I still don't know what you've been hiding.
But if you ever want to talk, be honest with me.
I'm always here.
Good morning!
Mornin'!
Good morning.
Top of the mornin'!
Mornin'...
The prez looks bummed out.
She oughta do that more often.
What's up?
I gotta spill it!
Wha?!
I can't hide anything from Rikka!
I'll tell it all!
Y-You can't!
Rikka!
You wanna drag your friend into this fight?!
Frickin' A, I'm late!
And now I get stuck again!
I ain't gonna make it!
If I could change the lights to how I want 'em,
I could totally make it in time.
Nah, I shoulda just woken up earlier.
Aw, just change the lights.
Who was that?
I'm here to grant your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
How dare you cross my road!
Stop!
What's that?
This street belongs to me!
You need to lie for her sake!
But...
Aah!
Stop!
That's...
President!
Mana!
It's a Selfish!
Self!
Don't worry, everyone.
I'll figure something out!
Rikka, hide everyone in a safe place!
What about you?
Mana, what will you do?
I'll stop that traffic light!
You Happy Prince!
Huh?
Even that prince statue standing on the corner
needed a swallow to give out his gold to the people!
Won't you let me be your swallow?
Rikka...
Help me!
Yeah.
This road belongs to me!
Huh?
Here goes!
Self!
Everyone! Run away while you can!
Who dares roll balls onto my road?!
Me! Right here!
Mana!
You shall pay!
Let's go, Sharuru.
H-Hey, you're not gonna transform right in front of your friend, are you?
I am.
You dragged yourself into this from the start.
Right, Rikka?
Mana?
I have no idea what's going on!
Let's go!
Sharuru!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Oh poor traffic light who knows no love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race!
Huh?!
Selfish!
I transformed into a Precure.
We've been friends forever,
but there's no way you can ask me to believe this!
There's just no way this can be happening!
This road belongs to me!
Stop!
Mana!
I'll stomp you to a pulp!
I can't move...
Mana!
Get up, Mana!
That's a...
Push Me
What's that?
Why you!
Please Wait
I have to hurry!
Hurry...
Hurry and turn green!
Hurry!
Got you!
Why you, this road belongs to—
Now, Cure Heart!
Self!
Sharuru!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love loooove!
Something got in my way again.
Huh?
What did I...
Really Mana, why do you always take on all this trouble?
You've just started running for reelection.
I said I was sorry!
Since I apologized, can you carry your own bag?
Have you reflected on your actions?
Totally!
Then I will.
I'm glad you told me the truth, too.
Thanks.
Rikka...
Rikka!
She got dragged into it in the end...
The other fairies are going to be mad!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Rikka, let's be Precure together!
What are you talking about?
I don't have your endless enthusiasm...
Don't worry!
I turned into one, so you can too!
And you'd look great in a Precure costume!
Mana, disguise or not, it's a no.
Besides, I don't have the confidence to be a Precure!
So no way.
Come on!
Dokidoki! Precure:
The Ultimate Partner Has Arrived!
Cure Diamond!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!