Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Eh?
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
We saw a shooting star the other day...
...but Kagami was telling us that repeating your wish three times is totally unrealistic.
Shooting stars are nice.
I hardly ever see them.
It's hard to see the stars from our house.
Oh, that's right.
Your house is downtown.
I would probably be too distracted by it...
...and then forget to make a wish.
Simply looking at the shooting star, getting dazzled by it's beauty,
and filling yourself with its bliss...
It certainly feels like there is such a myth that could make your wishes come true.
Your candidness is what dazzles me!
The Various Ways to
Spend Christmas Eve
Winter break is around the corner.
Though we have finals before that.
Do you have any plans for winter break?
Not really.
Which reminds me, we haven't traveled lately.
I went to Asakusa the other day.
Hm, when did you go?
Ah, you know how trains make you sleepy in the winter?
You missed your station?
Huh?
But isn't that in the opposite direction?
Apparently, I slept until the last station...
...and missed my station again when the train turned around.
When I finally realized it, I was in Asakusa.
Whoa there.
There has to be a limit to how many stations you miss!
But it wasn't entirely a bad thing.
I was able to go on a little vacation to Asakusa.
Though that's not something you should do during exam week.
And I thought I saw a high school girl in a sailor uniform with a machine-gun walking across the platform...
I wonder what that was...
You'd better not be telling me she was making a hit.
And you know how they say, "Kids who sleep more, will grow more."
How so?
There is someone that's even better than that, though!
My dad pulled an all-nighter and then went to turn in a manuscript.
He got on an early-morning train but missed his stop,
then it reached the end and made a U-turn,
so when he woke up, he'd already missed his stop...
...and this happened a few more times.
He started to wake up when he got close to his station,
Patrasche...
but he still ended up missing it.
I can't go on anymore...
He was so tired and just wanted to go home and sleep, but he couldn't for a while.
Wow...
To top it off, when he finally woke up,
he didn't know which direction he was going anymore.
Unbelievable.
When I fall asleep on trains, I always wake up before my station.
That's amazing!
How do you know when to wake up?
Maybe she has an internal alarm clock.
Though it seems to be broken on other matters.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're always snacking on stuff.
Shut up!
But when the seats on a train are warm, it makes you really sleepy.
That's true.
It's like a sunny winter afternoon,
where you're just idling in your seat next to the window,
taking in the rays.
What's this?
Covering for each other?
T-That's not what I meant.
The other day, when I tried to wake you up on the way back,
"Hey, wake up,
we're here."
"Just 5 more minutes,
I promise."
You said that in your sleep.
And everyone around us started laughing.
I had a friend who said that in class once.
Geez, you two really are similar.
Eh!?
You're grouping us together!?
But I wonder why it's 5 minutes?
Well, if you were to wake someone up...
...and they were like, "Just one more hour!",
you would probably get mad.
Well, that's true,
but putting aside sleep,
whenever you say a time, the first thing that comes to mind is "5 minutes".
Like, "Wait 5 minutes!"
I suppose.
Maybe because it's not too long and not too short.
Though it feels long when you have to wait 5 minutes for a train.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess so...
But when it comes down to it,
the people who say "5 more minutes", are the ones that never hold to it.
You know they say not to use your cell phone or put make-up on the train?
But it's a lot more troubling when the person next to you falls asleep on your shoulder.
Yeah, sometimes they're so heavy that...
...you would rather be standing up even after all that effort to find a seat.
And when you see a sickly elderly head coming...
Sometimes I try to push them off, as if I were to say, "Lean the other way!"
But no matter how many times I straighten them, they would fall back into the same position.
Yeah, yeah.
It's so mysterious.
When I fall asleep,
there's always an old man on this side...
and an empty spot on that side, so I try to lean towards the empty spot,
but for some reason, I always end up leaning in the wrong direction.
I guess there's just one side that feels more comfortable.
When the person next to me starts leaning over,
I begin to hunch over like this,
but when I do that, my elbow hits my side.
Don't count on those guys being asleep.
Really!?
Then, bye-nii.
Good-bye.
You know how some people...
...take the inbound train home...
...and others take the outbound trains home from school?
Yeah.
Don't you think the inbound group seems a little more erudite than the outbound group?
Yuki-chan, you're part of the inbound group.
But...
Now, now...
We unrefined should be heading home now.
Wait, this is the station before mine.
Yo!
Hey~
I couldn't get any studying done at all yesterday.
Really?
Surprisingly, I got a lot done this time.
If I do say so myself.
How much studying did you do?
Only four hours.
A whole four hours!
Huh?
Kagami, you can breeze through almost anything, can't you?
Well, I do study quite a bit.
Just between the two of us.
Yep, you're pretty competitive at times, Kagami.
Well, I guess it's just my pride as the older sister.
I always feel I have to be one step ahead of Tsukasa.
Though I often say how there's no "older" or "younger" between us.
I guess I had that feeling in the past.
I wouldn't call it a competition between you and Tsukasa, though.
Oh, well...
I guess so.
How dare you, you're just like Kona-chan!
It's almost Christmas!
I wonder what presents I'm going to get this year...
You still get presents...?
Kona-chan, how old were you when you stopped believing in Santa-san?
Santa Claus doesn't exist?
Oh my~!
Since Santa never came to Kona-chan's house,
her dad gave her gifts in his stead.
So, she thinks he's out there somewhere.
That old man must really want to show his good side to his daughter.
Hey, Hiiragi!
Oh!
Hiiragi-san, the printout from the other day...
Oh, yes, yes.
And then, Hiiragi-chan.
Hiiragi!
You dropped your pencil.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, Kagami!
Oh.
Kagami-san, here's the printout from the other day.
Oh, yes, yes.
And Sebastian just smelled so bad!
Kagami, you dropped your handkerchief?
Oh my~
I think I spend too much time in Tsukasa's class...
My cavity started hurting recently.
My, how awful.
I don't like the dentist either.
Yuki-chan, you went to see the dentist about your tooth the other day,
is it better now?
Dentists usually spend a lot of time on each tooth and on top of that,
when they finish one, they move onto the next and repeat the procedure,
so it takes a while.
So I unintentionally ran away.
After making up a number of excuses.
What should I do?
She makes it sound so cute, but she's doing some pretty crazy stuff!
Konata!
You want to go have a blast with everyone on Christmas?
Oh, I'm sorry, but I'm busy on Christmas.
Oh, what's this?
A guy?
Hm, something like that.
You have plans to go somewhere with your dad?
No, I told my dad that I would be home late.
Don't tell me...
Are you really going on a date with your boyfriend?
When did you...?
I hate to spoil the mood, but it's just my part-time job.
Oh.
But most of the customers are guys, so I wasn't lying.
I thought you managed to get ahead of us.
That surprised me!
For Christmas, we have a special event,
and we dress up like Santa Claus.
You really like that kind of stuff, don't you?
Yep, but you know...
For New Year's, you two also cosplay as shrine maidens at your own shrine.
Don't call it cosplay.
It's really nice of Santa-san to give us presents...
But ever since I was little, I thought he was totally trespassing.
Don't contemn something with holy origins.
What a blasphemous kid.
And yet...
Santa is the one who is supposed to give dreams to little kids,
so what does that say about the men who come to this little kid seeking dreams?
Hm?
You just insulted quite a few people there.
By the way, is it okay for you guys to celebrate Christmas in the first place?
Well, we used to receive Christmas presents on a regular basis.
And we do enshrine a plethora of gods.
We regularly go to temples to pray...
And we've sung in the church choir before as well.
I see...
That sounds really peaceful.
Ah, but...
Yes?
A fellow shrine maiden said...
...that she wanted to wear a wedding dress for her reception.
I wonder if that's okay...
Doesn't it get complicated if you take it that far?
Yahoo!
It's gotten chilly lately.
Oh, welcome Nee-san.
What are you watching?
Oh, a detective drama.
Is it interesting?
Not really.
It was just on.
All right, I got it!
The culprit is that guy!
Wait a second, Detective.
There are still some loose ends in this case.
There's nothing strange at all!
The mystery is solved!
Who do you think you are, Mr. Outsider!?
Geez...
This is why police are useless.
But aren't you one of them as well?
Why do we have to get a phone call right now?
The suspect is about to confess.
How do you know?
Watch.
I see.
So you were the criminal.
No use hiding it now.
Why does the ending to every two-hour drama has to be a cliffhanger?
Maybe it's because people can't make up their minds until they skirt the edges?
Yahoo!
How are ya?
Nee-san, evening!
What are you watching?
Oh, a movie of a popular detective drama.
My dad borrowed it.
The crime doesn't happen in a conference room!
It happens on the scene!
No, no, never happens.
Something this passionate never happens.
So you're going to deny this one, huh?
I don't think the thief intended to steal the receipts.
The chief was pulling the strings.
Better luck next time.
You've seen a case like this!?
Speaking of which, in detective dramas, they usually give pork cutlet bowls to the interrogees...
...but I heard that's not allowed.
Well, it's fiction, so they make up a lot of stuff.
Eh!?
Then police commissioners don't really have granddaughters like that?
Eh, the commissioner's granddaughter?
I don't think I've ever seen her.
I would at least want Mai-chan to exist, to give me hope...
What a hollow wish.
There sure are lots of cases where adults go after children.
I agree.
I've been thinking...
If you taught those kids martial arts, then crimes like that would decrease in frequency.
I heard Oyama-sensei has, through rigorous training,
attained the power to knock down a cow in one blow!
And he has a quota of twenty bears per day!
Is that so?
But doesn't that put you right back at the beginning?
Because when the kid grows up, he becomes an adult.
And the adult is strong, too.
U-Um... it's that.
You know how if you practice martial arts,
your way of thinking becomes enlightened.
Ah, I see.
But...
I have a good example of someone who walks a crooked path in spite of practicing martial arts right here.
H-How rude!
Oh, Yui-neesan's little sister,
or rather my other cousin, is entering high school next year.
She has a fragile body,
Konata-neesan!
but she's so sweet, pure, and simply adorable.
I see...
But if we go buy that definition of a strong body and straightforward mind...
Those cute eyes suddenly seem to be hiding something very shady underneath.
I don't think everything can be defined by martial arts like that.
Look at you.
This year's almost over.
Every year when December comes around you think that the year went by so quickly.
Tsukasa, are you guys going to help out at your temple as shrine maidens again?
I guess...
Come and draw your fortune again.
With the sacred lottery... whenever you draw your fortune and get a bad one, it really stings.
But if you draw a really good fortune,
it feels like you've wasted all of it on something so trivial.
Well, that's why some say that an average fortune is the best draw.
All right, here's an early present from your teacher.
I'm giving you your report cards!
Kona-chan, how did you do?
Here you go, keep up the good work!
Sensei, I don't want this present!
This Santa rewards only those who have put forth the effort!
You better give up.
It comes with a little bonus homework over winter break, too.
What kind of Christmas cakes do you guys want this year?
When you go to the bakery, they have so many wonderful cakes...
...that it's fun just looking at them.
What happens to the cakes that aren't sold by Christmas?
Perhaps the employees take them home.
But if there's no one to take it home,  I guess they just have to toss it.
You know, marriage age often gets compared to a Christmas cake.
Yep.
Like how the 25th is the endpoint.
Once you're past the 25th, a Christmas cake becomes just another cake.
After one night, the decorations don't look as colorful and are not nearly as appetizing,
so you lose all interest.
I was talking about Santa-san the other day with Kona-chan,
but how old were you when you stopped believing in Santa, Yuki-chan?
You seem like someone who believed in him for quite a long time, like me.
I believed in Santa-san, too.
When I was little, I tried to send Santa-san a thank you letter.
And I did some research.
I asked my mom and dad about him, but I didn't learn much.
So when I did some more research,
I came across phrases such as "Santa Claus exposed" and "Santa's origins".
Therefore, my dreams were shattered at a pretty early age.
Ah!
Miyuki-san, how did you do?
Let me see!
That's Yuki-chan for you...
I could never get grades like this.
I feel kind of annoyed about losing...
Yuki-chan is one of the top students in our year, so there's nothing we can do...
We're no match for her.
No, I don't really care about the grades.
But her bust size.
Look, they're huge!
I'm kind of hungry.
Maybe I'll make a cup of ramen.
Is it ready yet?
These three minutes feel so long.
I'll kill some time with this today.
And before you realize it your noodles are all soggy!
Yep, yep!
The excess hot water in my cup yakisoba dried up!
You guys...
She told me she was going to be late,
but this is too late!
I don't want her to make a habit out of it,
so I should lay down the law every once in a while!
As the man of the house!
I'm home!
Konata!
Come in here!
Do you know what time it-
Merry Christmas!
This is my Christmas present to you, Dad.
It must have been so cold at this hour!
Want some hot tea?
Yay!
I do! I do!
Dad's so happy he could die!
Hey, everyone!
Yui-neesan is home!
Nee-san, you reek of alcohol!
You shouldn't drink and drive!
I parked the car somewhere and had a drink at a place nearby.
Listen to me!
It's Christmas Eve, but when I go home, my husband isn't even here!
Our plans for tonight...
Nee-san, how about you go to your own home instead of ours once in a while?
Oh, hello?
Yui, it's me.
I wanted to quietly come home and surprise you, but it was locked...
Are you at home now?
I'm coming home!
I'm coming home right now!
I'll fly through the stop lights!
No, you're not supposed to break the law.
I'll give you a ride.
I could use a little break.
Maybe I'll log in for a bit.
Hm, Sensei's online.
Sensei, let's just party until dawn...
One moment please.
Christmas
Cakes
It's not a leftover...
It's not a leftover!
Kuroi Nanako
Because I bought you.
27 years old
Single
I came to the manga club here last Sunday.
I'm amazed that you still come here considering the expensive transportation fare.
I can't believe you do this all for points.
You must really like this stuff.
Do you even use the rewards you get with your cards?
Nope.
I don't.
Thought so.
It's hard to use that kind of stuff.
Yep, yep.
It'd be such a waste to use.
Their value would go down, you know?
So that's how it is, huh?
Oh well.
Ah!
No!
Yes!
Didn't you get shocked by the static electricity?
Nope.
Eh, why not?
Maybe it's because you have weird waves all inside of you...
Since you spend most of your time in front of a computer.
Don't you hate winter for that reason?
And you can get shocked just by touching someone's hand.
Oww!
Maybe you guys actually don't get along well with each other.
Oh my.
What are you doing?
I wanted to see it again!
Ooh!
Stronger!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
I'm the navigator, Kogami Akira!
Believe it or not, Lucky Channel has reached the eleventh episode!
And finally, on this eleventh episode,
we have some wonderful news you've all been waiting for!
U-Um...
We received lots and lots of postcards from everyone.
You're so motivated today.
Affectionately saying that they want to see Akira-san in the series, too!
Hello!
Next week, I, Kogami Akira will be-
I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Shut up!
I'll be in the actual series!
But my introduction...
To Izumi Konata-san from Saitama and everyone else...
...who submitted a postcard to Newtype to support me,
thank you!
Wow~
You're going to make an appearance in the series, too, Akira-sama?
What's with that,
"Oh, you're finally showing up in the series at episode 12?"
"I was in it ages ago! Ho ho ho!" kind of attitude?
N-Not at all!
It's a great honor to be able to support you in the actual series as well!
Huh?
You talk about appearing in the actual series...
...but all you did this episode was pick up a measly handkerchief!
It's the most dangerous when you start thinking...
...you have what it takes to survive in this business!
You better remember that if you don't want to disappear right away!
I-I'll keep that in mind.
Eh?
After hearing news like that, you can't wait till next week, can you?
You want it right now, don't you?
Everyone's probably trembling...
Rather, quaking with excitement in anticipation!
Hey, let's value the fans' opinions here...
...and broadcast it right now!
We can grab some other thirty minute slot, right?
I-I don't think that's possible...
As a small request from me!
But we should probably stop here.
If you have any questions or comments, please send it here...
...or to our radio show.
Bye-nii~
Bye-nii!
Ah, what should I do?
It would be bad if I stole the lead role, huh?
That's correct.
But it's happened in the past where main characters' friends or rivals...
...ended up becoming more popular than the main characters themselves!
Huh?
A-Akira-sama, what's the matter?
Are you...
Yes?
Talking about yourself?
Are you letting it get to your head...
...because you've been a little popular lately!?
T-That's not true at all!
Don't expect it to last!
Not at all!
You probably thought you won first in the fan votes!
What are you saying!
Quit messin' with me!
That's impossible!
P-Please listen to me!
And next we up is a duet from Tsukasa and Miyuki-san.
Yuki-chan, let's stand up front and sing.
Okay...
Who would have thought Konata would choose the song for Miyuki to sing...
It's amazing...
I know lots of songs, you know.
So it was an anime song!
Believe it or not, anime songs come in handy in situations like these.
Konna koto ii na dekitara ii na
こんなこといいなできたらいいな
This kind of thing is wonderful! It would be so wonderful!
Anna yume konna yume ippai aru kedo
あんなゆめ　こんなゆめ　いっぱいあるけど
This dream, that dream, there are so many of them!
Minna minna minna kanaete kureru
みんなみんなみんな　かなえてくれる
Every single one of them, will come true!
Fushigina Pokke de kanaete kureru
ふしぎなポッケで　かなえてくれる
His magical pocket makes them come true!
sora wo jiyuu ni tobitai na
そらをじゆうに　とびたいな
I want to fly freely through the sky!
Hai! Takekoputaa
「ハイ！　タケコプター」
Yes! Take-Copter
Not even close!
An An An tottemo daisuki Doraemon!
アンアンアン　とってもだいすき　ドラえもん
Ah ah ah, I love you heaps, Doraemon!
Shukudai to...
しゅくだいと。。。
Homework, school...
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Tsukasa here.
The other night, I got really hungry in the middle of the night,
but it was so late,
so I was debating whether or not I should eat.
And I decided it would be okay if it was just a little.
And then I went to the kitchen...
where I remembered I had some leftover snacks,
and opened up the freezer...
What, time's up already!?
Next week: "Let's go to the Festival"
「Let's Go to
the Festival」
Look forward to it!