This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
I'm sorry! I couldn't find it.
You couldn't find "Dead at Dusk"?
I think I took it to the countryside during summer break and forgot it there.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Then give us a hand with the poster.
Poster?
Yeah, something cute and exciting.
I gotta head off for a bit.
She... remembered its title.
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
Wildfire
Chitanda, Mayaka,
don't forget the cooking contest starts at eleven.
Roger!
Sorry, Fuku, I got roped into helping draw a poster at the Manga Lab.
Huh, really?
Well then...
If we put you last...
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
you won't have to be there until 12:10.
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Wildfire
11:30 Vanguard
11:50 Main force
12:10 Captain
At least one dish per person
Apron           shirt
No talking to the cook!
Secure ingredients within the school
Got it! I'll do what I can!
Later!
I gotta go to a General Affairs meeting,
so I'll go on ahead.
Sure looks like he's enjoying himself.
Meeting room
Please take that to the gym.
Understood.
Shoe bags for visitors
By the way,
aren't you going to take a look around?
Things keep coming up.
I've seen a few bits here and there, though.
Did something interesting happen?
Something interesting?
Oh, the Go Club were struck by a mysterious thief.
They stole a few stones and left a note claiming responsibility.
Ah, I see. The Go Club.
Yeah. Though I think it was just one of their members having fun.
Actually,
I heard from Okano that a similar thing happened to the a capella choir as well.
Really?
Yeah, someone nicked a juicebox from their cooler.
Did anyone claim responsibility?
I heard there was some weird note.
This is starting to get interesting.
What's that big grin for, Fukube?
Oh, nothing.
Classics Club Anthology
"Hyouka" issue #46
On sale
Classics Club Anthology
"Hyouka" issue #46
On sale
Today I'll really do my best!
Out of Sight, Out of Mind
Now Screening
Class 2-F's self-produced movie:
Leaflet: 50 Yen
Out of Sight, Out of Mind
Very well.
So you can help?
Yes.
Thank you so much!
You can thank me if it sells.
So, how many of them for how much?
They're 200 yen each. We have...
200 copies in stock.
That's a lot.
Owing to a clerical error.
But I wanted to try and sell them anyway.
I... I...
I'll take twenty at 50 yen below the retail price.
That way, we can sell it for 200 yen together with our leaflet.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Give me a sample.
Oh, that's what you meant!
Sorry, I don't have it with me.
Make sure you bring it with you from now on.
That way people will know exactly what you're asking for.
Irisu!
Irisu, you're really good at asking for stuff, right?
Please teach me how you do it!
I guess so.
Listen well!
Whatever you ask for,
the key is to make the other person want to help you.
Make them want to?
To do that you have to satisfy them mentally.
There are a number of means to that end, but in your case I'd recommend
setting expectations.
Expectations?
Yes. Make the other person believe you expect great things from them.
Make them believe?
If you can do that, the rest will go down easily enough.
Go down?
Yeah.
But don't make it seem like the problem is too big.
Not too big.
They should feel like it's just a minor issue for them, but quite an important one for you.
Oh, and one more thing.
If possible, hit them with everything at once in some isolated place.
Yes.
Now run along and bring me those anthologies.
Yes...
You helped me a lot!
Trick or treat! Yay!
Who are you?
We're doing door-to-door sales for the Sweets Lab!
Want some biscuits?
How much?
It's 100 yen a bag, master.
What's this? It's so cool!
Just think how this'd improve our sales pitch!
You can have it for two bags of biscuits.
We're offering that pistol alongside the anthology.
Really?
Boom!
Then, here!
And as a sign of the pumpkins' gratitude, this too!
Weak flour
Flour?
Yay! Yay!
Trick or treat!
Amazing speed!
The Poster-Drawing
Battle Royale!
The Manga Lab's
most treasured artists!
Witch Girl vs
The Panther!
The Manga Lab's most treasured artists, huh?
That's nice.
Done.
Mayaka!
Yeah, let's do this!
Cooking Club                     Competition
Where's Mayaka?
Looks like she's still pretty busy.
Is she?
Let's believe in her.
Hey, Fukube!
This is Suhara.
He's a chef's son.
Now isn't that amazing.
Do your best, 'kay?
My best, huh?
All right, let's see the entrants!
Number one, Team Delicious!
Number two, Team Fata Morgana!
Number three, Team Astrology Club!
Number four, Team Classics Club!
Here are the rules! Each team consist of three people and each person has 20 minutes.
After your 20 minutes is up, you must switch with the next person!
You're not allowed to talk to the person cooking,
so please be careful!
What are you going to cook, Fukube?
Thanks for asking!
I'm making a Fukube-style seafood rice bowl!
I think we need to cook the rice ourselves.
So will you go last as the captain?
No, I'll go first as the vanguard.
If that's the case, I'll have to make something else.
So it doesn't matter when I take the stage.
I'm counting on you.
Each team member must make at least one dish!
You may collect your ingredients from the table in the middle! First come, first served!
If anything you need should run out, you may also collect ingredients from within the school!
Now, vanguards!
Ready your swords!
All right!
Then let's begin!
Wild!
Fire!
Fire...
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
The Wildfire has begun to blaze!
I'm looking forward to seeing what the teams cook up for us!
Oh, Team Classics Club are removing the heads and guts from the dried sardines one by one!
What careful attention to detail!
What do you think, club president?
It's an important step, vice president.
Team Fata Morgana have gone straight for the clams!
I guess he's making radishes in miso.
Wait, Fukube, that won't do!
You haven't peeled the radishes!
No! I can't talk to him!
The radishes!
Peel...
the skin!
Fukube!
Did he understand?
He's peeling the rings one by one?!
The water! It's boiling over!
Team Classics Club look like they'll need some time!
Is that a Möbius strip?!
Done!
Um...
We still don't know what the teams are making!
Team Classics Club, our eyebrows rise in doubt!
I know! It's pork soup!
Look at that! Team Delicious!
It's that must-have, meat sauce!
I won't make it at this pace.
Vanguard members, your time is running out!
Five! Four!
Three! Two! One!
Change element!
Sorry, I only managed to make one dish!
It's okay! Leave it to me!
You're up, Chitanda!
Now that's amazing!
Team Classics Club's main force!
A perfectly executed paper-thin slice!
Witness the true form and beauty of radish!
A cut so clean, it'd purify the dirtiest of rivers!
Amazing!
She already finished a whole other dish!
Ah, that's the Chitanda I know.
The Classics Club member washes the rice almost ritualistically!
They only have six liters of water, but she uses it without hesitation!
A sacrifice to bring out the divine flavor of the rice!
Team Astrology Club, what is your main force doing?!
What's that?! What dish is that?!
Raging fire!
Meanwhile at the Classics Club,
is that giseyaki I see?
What a delightful local flavor!
Hiromi!
I've never even heard about that before.
And Team Fata Morgana!
Their brill teriyaki is nearing completion!
Brill-iant!
Team Classics Club's giseyaki is done!
This makes me hungry!
Just who is their main force, anyway?!
The daughter of the rich Chitanda family of farmers,
Miss Chitanda Eru!
Remember her!
Meanwhile, Team Astrology Club continue with their avant-garde cuisine!
The darkness will swallow you!
Team Classics Club!
She added cooked potatoes and starch to the mortar!
She's making potato mochi!
We've got a pro in the Classics Club!
But this might be bad!
Bad? What?
Classics Club, talking to the cook is forbidden!
No good. She's not getting it.
We've just passed the forty minute mark!
Switch over to the commanders!
Fukube, how was it?
Wonderful, Chitanda.
I didn't know you were such a cook.
I do enjoy cooking.
Wonderful.
It's just that...
Just what?
We've got no ingredients left!
Sorry, Mayaka.
It's time for the last round now!
I'm done!
Excuse me!
Team Delicious is preparing apples for the dessert!
Is he making rabbits out of them?
There's still no sign of the Classics Club's captain!
Team Delicious is now making flowers for the rabbits!
The Classics Club's captain is still missing,
but Team Delicious are preparing dessert!
Mayaka!
Look!
A girl who isn't in school uniform!
Could this be Team Classics Club's captain?
Mayaka!
It's the Classics Club!
Team Classics Club's captain has shown up at last!
Looks like Team Classics Club's facing one difficulty after another!
They're fresh out of ingredients!
If they're unable to make anything, they will of course receive zero points!
They were in the lead until now, but what will happen next?
This is all?
Team Classics Club's captain has picked up a small onion!
Now what?
But what is she going to do with it?
Can't she think of anything? She's standing still!
What now, Classics Club?
If you can't make anything, you're out!
Now what?
What can I do?
What is Mayaka going to make with so few ingredients?
I can't stop thinking about it!
Whose fault is that, now?
The Classics Club's captain is paralyzed with indecision!
Look! Team Fata Morgana's made an omelette!
Think! Think!
Could this be the end for Team Classics Club?
Something... There must be something!
Is Team Classics Club finally out of moves?
They have a mere ten minutes left!
Can they do anything but wait for the timeout?
Satoshi!
Did someone just call your name?
Huh?
Listen!
The Astrology Club are frying bananas in broth—
Really?
Excuse me!
What?
Could you keep quiet for a second?
Satoshi!
It's Oreki!
There! In the club room!
Satoshi!
What's he doing?
SatoshI! Come here!
Under the window!
Hurry!
Fukube!
Okay.
What?
Catch!
Nice catch.
But... what is this?
Team Classics Club's vanguard has returned!
Mayaka!
What?
What a fortunate turn of events!
Could that be flour?
That's within the rules!
Please continue!
Got it!
Seven minutes left!
All teams competing in Wildfire have entered the endgame!
Team Classics Club is on the move as well!
How will they handle this extreme handicap?
I can't stop thinking about it!
Look at that! She took the heads off the shrimp!
What's she trying to do?
Shreds in batter.
I see!
Shreds in batter!
Just five minutes left till this Wildfire burns out!
Hey! Cooking Club!
The least you could do is give us a ladle!
Now that the Classics Club has their ladle,
their captain continues with the next step!
She's catching up! Team Classics Club is catching up!
Can she pull off this daring comeback?!
It's a shred-fry rice bowl!
Are Team Classics Club gonna make it on time?!
Just one minute left!
You're running out of time!
She's got it!
And it's on the bowl!
Three!
Two!
One!
Time's up!
Yes!
Hooray!
Mayaka!
Nice job!
What's up?
Nothing!
And now, it's time to announce the results.
The winner is...
Team Classics Club!
I'm exhausted.
It's a bit underdone.
No! Considering you had no time or choice in ingredients, you did great!
But I had no ladle!
If only I'd had a ladle, I could've done it perfectly!
It took at least a minute for them to bring it...
I was so stupid.
I should've realized there was no—
We're very sorry!
We were sure all the utensils were there.
I guess we should've checked one more time.
I thought something was missing. I should've asked...
Excuse me...
Don't worry about it.
There!
Look!
What?
The Cooking Club has lost their ladle.
Juumonji
Another note!
The Cooking Club has lost their ladle.
Juumonji
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Juumonji
Next time: The Juumonji Case.
The Juumonji Case