The Student Who Sucks
At Storytelling
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ore wa tandoku de seigi katsudo o shiteiru
I'm a lone cyborg working to uphold justice
saibogu, Genosu toyuu mono da!
My name is Genos
Kosoku sekkin hanno...kuru
I detect a high-speed object... approaching!
Kazoku no ada o utsu tame ni
For the sake of avenging my family
Hakase ni moratta kono karada
I took this body from the doctor
Ima koso warumono haijo seyo
Now is the time to eliminate evildoers
Kono atsuki honoo de
With these red-hot flames
Tsuyosa no hiketsu ga shiri takute
"Wanna know the secret to true strength?"
Nikki ni shirusu no sa
I write in my diary
A kaki kaki kaki
Ah scribble, scribble, scribble!
Toire no soji mo nikka desu
Toilet scrubbing is also in my daily routine
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
Ore ni wa taosaneba naranai shukuteki ga iru n desu!
I have an arch-enemy I must defeat at all costs!
Saitama sensei, ore o deshi ni shite kudasai!
Saitama-sensei, please make me your disciple!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
Wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch ah March