Taromaru...
2. Supplies
One month of supplies is prepared for the predicted
number of 15 survivors. An infinite supply of electric
power is provided by solar panels, and water via the
rainwater filtration device.
3. Relief Supplies
Supplies                      painkillers, antibiotics, first-aid kits.
Each kit                       supplies for three people.
4. Entrances
It says there's medicine down there.
Who's there?
Yuki-chan?
Yuki-chan?!
What's wrong?
Mii-kun!
Mii-kun, get in the club room!
Senpai?
Hurry!
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
Scars
We're okay. The door's locked.
So they can't come in.
W-we're okay.
We're gonna be okay.
At this rate...
That's right. We have to get the medicine.
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
The medicine...
If it works on people, it'll work on Taromaru, too...
Yuki-senpai.
What?
This isn't like you.
Mii-kun?
Please, just say something stupid like you usually do.
Tell me something fun.
Huh?
"Something stupid"?
You're so mean, Mii-kun!
Really?
Is that the biscuit you should be
showing your senpai?
Do you mean "respect"?
Yeah, ri-spect!
Let's go on a field trip when Kurumi-chan feels better.
I wanna swim in the ocean
with everyone, not just a pool.
And I wanna eat grilled potatoes with you in the fall!
And then in the winter,
I wanna go ice skating and skiing!
I hope we get good snow this year!
Okay, let's see, then I'll go biking with Kurumi-chan,
and shopping with Ri-san,
and you and I can go eat something really yummy...
Oh, with Taromaru, of course!
And Megu-nee, too...
Megu-nee...
Mii-kun?
I'm gonna go.
Don't leave this room, Yuki-senpai.
Mii-kun, I'm coming with you!
No way!
Wouldn't it be sad if Taromaru came back
and nobody was here waiting for him?
It looks like they won't come this way
if the lights are off.
Lock the door as soon as I leave.
Okay?
See you, then.
Miki Naoki, heading out.
Mii-kun...
I think I should come, t-
No way!
I didn't know it was so heavy...
Kurumi-senpai...
was always carrying it...
If I'm infected, don't hesitate to do what you have to.
Promise me.
Sports Festival
When: Right now!
Place: The whole 3rd floor!
Let's hustle
Now that I think about it,
I was given so many wonderful things.
Opening Ceremony
Festival Program
Beautiful Scavenger Hunt!
Ultra Ball Rolling
Great Ball Toss
Lightspeed 3-Legged Race
Lightning-Fast Sprint
Fun things,
warm things,
Are you okay?
hope...
I can't lose now.
Please, help me...
Kei!
Do it calmly, but quickly!
Don't freak out, but hurry!
Hey, Ri-san.
Ri-san?
Sorry, were you asleep?
What's up?
Nothing, I just kinda wanted someone to talk to.
I'm kinda surprised those two in the back
can sleep with my crazy driving.
They were really tired.
Let's let them sleep.
Man, we really messed up Megu-nee's car.
I hope she'll forgive us.
It's fine.
I'm sure Megu-nee would understand.
Are you really okay with not stopping?
It's close to the mall, right?
Your house?
Hey, I was thinking.
Hm?
All those things wandering about oustide.
Yeah.
You think they're still conscious?
Umm...
What do you think, Kurumi?
I don't think they are.
Why?
Because it'd really suck if they were.
I've seen acquaintances and friends, and others, too...
But that's just it.
There's nothing we can do.
That's why I really want you to remember
that promise we made.
You're the only one I can trust to do it.
Right.
I'll keep my promise.
Taromaru...
You're Megumi Sakura-sensei, right?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Miki Naoki, a new member
of the School Living Club.
I've heard a lot about you from the others, Megu-nee.
You're kind, and you're always there for everyone.
You didn't want anyone to get hurt.
That's why you've stayed down here this whole time.
But...
it's alright now!
Yuri-senpai plays the big sister to everyone,
and is always planning ahead.
Yuki-senpai is always so full of energy.
She really keeps us going.
Kurumi-senpai...
Kurumi-senpai is always there to help
when we're in trouble.
If it weren't for you, Megu-nee, I wouldn't be here.
Right now, the four of us are supporting each other.
And we're doing our best to live here at school!
So please...
Rest in peace.
Alert. Alert.
Due to loss of power, the emergency shelter
has switched to emergency power.
The medicine should be down here...
Yuki
Kurumi                           Ri
Medicine
These handprints...
First Aid Kit
Painkillers, antibiotics,
experimental medicine for first-stage Infected...
This is it!
We can save Kurumi-senpai with this!
Sakura-sensei...
Yuki
Kurumi                           Ri
We're going to save Kurumi-senpai!
please live on
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Wait!
Where are you all going?!
Hey, wait!
Don't leave me behind!
Takeya-san?
What's all the ruckus about?
Megu-nee!
Don't call me Megu-nee.
It's Sakura-sensei, remember?
Right!
Come on, hurry up and get to class.
But everyone else is...
They're all in the classroom.
Oh!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What was that just now?
No!
I don't have time for this!
Was that...?
I've gotta hurry up and get this medicine
to Kurumi-senpai, or she'll...
Where can I get through?
This is just like the room back then.
Why?
I thought I got away from all of that.
Is this the end?
Am I going to die here, alone, in this tiny room?
I can't get out.
Nobody's coming to save me.
It's just like when I lived at that mall.
I don't wanna die like this!
Someone!
Someone please, help me!
Kei...
I'm sorry.
Taromaru...
Kurumi-senpai...
Yuri-senpai...
Yuki-senpai...
What's wrong?
I have to go.
I have to go, or the School Living Club will be over!
I see.
Then go to the broadcasting room.
The broadcasting room?
Then you can save Miki-san...
no, you can save everyone.
Okay, got it!
It's heavy!
This way.
Nobody's here now.
I heard a really loud siren earlier.
I think that's where they all went.
Hey, Megu-nee?
Will I see everyone again?
Or is this...
Huh?
We've made a lot of progress, but we're a long way off
from guaranteeing ourselves an escape route.
You're right.
The first floor seems like it'll take some time.
Are you alright?
I'm sorry.
Nobody's blaming you for anything.
I'm clumsy, and weak, and just get in everyone's way.
I'm just a big bother.
That's not true.
There are things you can do
that nobody else can, Yuki-chan.
Like your beautiful smile.
It always cheers us up.
You mean it?
Of course!
You always cheer me up, Yuki-chan.
I'm sure everyone feels the same way.
So promise me, alright?
Promise me that no matter what happens,
you'll never forget to smile.
Because I'll always be watching over you, alright?
Always?
Yes.
Okay, I'll do my best!
I'll work really hard!
Do you really have to work hard to smile?
That's true.
Yeah, huh...
Yuki-chan.
Megu-nee!
Let go of me!
Yuki-chan, stop!
Megu-nee's still out there! We have to hurry!
No, you can't!
Megu-nee!
Yuki-chan.
You're almost to the broadcasting room.
Are you alright? You're not afraid?
Actually... I'm really scared.
But you know, I've always tried to ignore scary things,
and caused a lot of problems for everyone.
I can't keep going on like that.
Or I feel like I'll lose all the things
that are important to me.
And I'm a lot more scared of that...
Yuki-chan.
Don't forget the promise we made, alright?
No matter what happens.
Yeah.
I won't forget it, Megu-nee.
Megu-nee!
Bye bye, Megu-nee.
Bathed in the crimson light
What were you thinking of?
I thought you were beautiful as you tried to brush it off
Tears welling in your eyelashes
I always thought
That these days would go on forever
Without a doubt
The sky we looked up at
Looks upon us from so far away
We just gripped each other’s lost hands
Quietly, without ever changing
I’m not lonely anymore
I just keep moving towards the other side of the ending world
I can see our sunrise
I can see it
So smile
Next Time!
The super fun sports festival!
The field trip!
Swimming on the roof!
They're all such precious memories!
Next time on School-Live's final episode:
"Graduation"
Graduation
Everyone write 100 pages!
I can't write that many!
See you!