Dojinshi exhibition and sale event...
It's mostly where individuals
buy and sell their books.
The participants work hard
every day for each of their purposes.
If there is someone
that realizes their dream...
...there are also those
that are thrown into reality.
This is the story of those that
live in that type of dojin world.
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
So as for me, I was reflecting on it...
...and taking in my manager's lecture
with my body and soul, but...
...one of my bangs was slightly
touching the tip of my nose.
It was really itchy!
So my manager
saw that face and said...
..."What's with that face! Do you have
some kind of complaint or something?"
So then I didn't think
and accidentally said...
..."I'm sorry the hair was..."
I totally forgot, but...
...there was some suspicion
that my manager had a toupee.
Of course I was fired.
Man, I was planning on
buying a bicycle too.
Tsuyuri?
Sorry. I was asleep.
What, you weren't listening to
any of that story just now?
I was listening.
After that, Najimi, you went
into the pool naked and...
Where did that story come from?
You haven't been listening!
More like, Tsuyuri, you have
been looking really sleepy recently.
Yeah, I didn't sleep last night either.
An all-nighter?
What were you doing?
The truth is...
Oh, is it something perverted?
How did you know?
It is definitely pretty perverted.
What, are you serious?
Really? An all-nighter...
When did you find a person
to do those kinds of things with?
What? I'm doing it alone...
Doing it alone?
To the point that you're losing sleep?
A-An all-nighter?
If you have interest,
you want to help me?
Help you?
Next station, Yurigaoka.
Next is Yurigaoka.
It's not yuri!
Please excuse me.
Next station is Ouizumi Academy.
Well, Tsuyuri...
I like you as a friend, but...
...I can't imagine a relationship
more than that...
This is Ouizumi Academy.
I'll see you...
I'll pay you.
Hey, you shouldn't be doing such things!
How much do you want?
It's not that type of problem!
What about 20,000 yen?
The train is departing.
First Edition
My First XXX
What a horrible face.
I couldn't sleep last night.
What were you doing
pulling an all-nighter?
Leave me alone.
Well, I'll ask again, but dojinshi?
Yes.
Aren't those manga that you draw
on your own using manga characters?
That's what it mostly is.
By the way, there are a lot of people
that draw perverted manga.
I'm mainly into sexual assault.
Sexual?
Then by perverted stuff and
being sleep-deprived, you meant...
Of course I was working on my manga.
What about the part-time job?
I wanted you to be a salesgirl for me.
More like, what did you think it was?
You came this far...
Father, Mother...
I am still okay.
You do not have enough funds.
Please pay the sufficient
amount at the window.
Are you okay?
This is the club's space.
Club?
That's what a group
of people that do dojin are called.
There are a lot of clubs that
are run by individuals. Like me.
Really?
Does your club have
a name or something?
Panty Revolution.
What?
Sorry. It's not going into my head at all.
Let me hear it one more time.
Panty Revolution.
Panty Revo...
Don't worry about it anymore. I got it.
Comic Festival has now begun!
Najimi, hurry and put the books out.
Yeah...
Enforcement Bloomers
New book
I'm leaving for a little...
Huh, where are you going?
Restroom.
Me too.
No. Najimi, you're watching the table.
That was the reason
why I asked you to help.
When I come back, we'll switch.
See you.
Hey, wait a second!
Sample - New
Excuse me...
This new book...
Can I look at it?
Huh?
Ah, yes, go ahead...
This...
No, it's not...
Uh, how much is this?
Um...
About how much do they run around?
Oh, nothing! Then...
Two...
It's 500 yen.
There you go.
Thank you very much!
You're happy when your book sells, huh?
Yes, very much.
It's calmed down a little.
You helped a lot. Thank you.
No problem. When I think I could get
a bicycle because of this, then...
Oh yeah, I have a question, but are
you able to make money with dojinshi?
When you become a major company,
you sell copies in the thousands, so...
...I hear there are places
that make about 10,000,000.
10,000,000?
I want to work hard
and be able to sell more.
T-Tsuyuri, about
how much is your profit?
300 copies sold out, and if
I subtract everything, about 50,000 yen.
I think it's going to end up
about that much today too.
What?
If Tsuyuri pays me for helping her out,
her profit's going to be...
This is a nice book.
One copy, please.
Thank you very much.
Also, may I have you that
looks great with a beret on?
Will it be carry-out then?
What?
I will be dining here.
Well, whichever way, the answer is no...
You are more lovely
for not falling the ordinary way.
What's the matter, Sora?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just kidding.
Justice.
Sora.
Justice? Then you're...
Oh, Najimi, it's you.
What a coincidence.
What do you mean, coincidence?
Justice, who is she?
Najimi. She's my childhood friend, Sora.
More like, what are you doing here?
Justice? Are you possibly
from the major company club?
You know of me?
I'm honored.
What, major company?
You're not participating
with the club today?
I am doing my own shopping right now.
Hold on, Tsuyuri.
You said if you're in a major company, there
are places that sell copies in the 10,000s, right?
Yes.
Justice, what about you?
This time around the
3 new books all sold out, so...
In total, 30,000 copies.
If it's 1 book at 1,000 yen,
you could buy an apartment building.
We're distributing at 100 yen, though.
But that's still 3,000,000 yen!
The printing cost is 2,900,000 yen.
Then with the miscellaneous expenses,
pretty much nothing is left with me.
What do you mean by that?
But, I'm satisfied if the readers are happy.
I don't need the money.
Justice, you are so cool!
Thank you.
Stop spurring on your success...
But that is amazing.
If I work hard on it,
getting rich quick isn't a dream, right?
To think there was big business
in a place like this!
Dojinshi and its tremendous power!
Najimi?
If this business goes well...
That's right, if it goes well...
...I can eat my fill of really good food!
No!
Why am I talking about something
on such a small scale like food!
No, it's not that! If this goes well...
...I can get dessert with it too!
Hey, hey, could you buy this too?
Sketch book
That's right.
First of all, is dojinshi something
that you can write all of a sudden?
I've never drawn outside
of a class in school, have I?
Senpai's Through Pass
You drew this, right?
Ah, yes.
It's possible.
What?
Thanks to you, an infinite chance
of opportunity has opened for me!
Th-Then you'll buy one from me?
No.
What's the matter?
You will only be able
to laugh right now!
No, the one that's
laughing is you, Najimi.
I, Najimi Osana, declare right here!
I'm going to make
a lot of profit with dojin!
I can see it! I can see it!
My future!
It's dangerous, so please get down!
Dojin Work
It's starting! It's starting!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
It's finally started.
We need to get someone
to cook some red rice for us.
You just thought of
something strange, didn't you?
2nd Edition
The Naked Princess