So Ra No Wo To
Ready forward.
Advance!
Advancing.
Enemy sighted.
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Distance 800.
Gunner, load HE round!
R-Roger!
Loading complete!
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
Boom!
Target hit!
All right. Signal the
forces to our rear.
One enemy unit destroyed.
Follow me!
Roger!
One enemy unit destroyed, huh?
Nice work!
We're not there yet.
Filicia, it's Claus!
My... Then let's have tea.
Good work, everyone.
Mountain Hiking
- The Ends of the World
Shuko's doing a lot better!
Her wound has healed,
but she's stayed here.
Well, this place is wonderful, isn't it?
Hey!
How can she be that
active in this heat?
Yeah...
This is from HQ.
I need your signature here.
Here you go.
And here are some letters
and packages for you.
Kana-chan!
Yes?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
This is for you!
Thank you!
It's from my mom!
And for you, too, Noël.
From your beloved Professor.
Professor?
Yes.
His family name is Pro.
His given name is Fessor.
They're very common
names in Sept.
Mr. Fessor, huh?
It's wonderful that you have
friends from so far away!
I'm sorry.
It was a joke.
Oh, come on, Noël.
I believed you for a minute.
Take Claus a present.
OK!
Rio.
The usual.
Throw it out.
So, what did HQ say?
Excuse me!
What's wrong, Kureha?
Major Claus... Here!
This year's, huh?
Yes!
U-Uh, th-thank you
for everything.
Don't worry about it.
It's my job.
Major.
Here you are.
Roger.
I'll take care of the place
while you're gone.
Gone?
Good luck out there, Private.
Thank you.
Everyone, we're going on
a field trip tomorrow!
Yay!
A field trip, she said!
Isn't that great, Noël-chan?
Aren't you psyched?
A field trip... Filicia?
Just walking would be boring,
so we're going to have a game, too.
Game?
You all know that there are
old-era observation devices
placed on the south side of Seize.
You know, the border between
us and no man's land.
Three of them are up for their
regular maintenance check.
I'd like you to look at them
all on your trip.
That's...
That's a mission!
No, it's just a field trip!
Even if they're broken,
we can't do anything about them.
Noctur-type observation devices
are a complete black box.
It's impossible to disassemble them.
So it's a field trip.
So this is what he meant by
"Good luck out there."
But just walking isn't
good enough!
Thus...
You'll be carrying those!
You're feeble.
Listen, the way to carry these is by
putting your weight forward...
Wow!
I... I can't move.
Screw up.
Like you're one to talk!
You really are such good children.
You did exactly what we thought you would!
Argh...
Listen! When carrying
a heavy pack,
first, you lean back.
Then...
Once the weight of the pack
is completely on your back...
Pathetic.
Stop talking...
And do it!
Yes, ma'am!
OK! Then Filicia and I
will proceed straight to the goal point
on the map to wait for you.
If you really think you can't
go on, blow your trumpet.
We'll come to look for you.
OK?
And there are wild animals
on this mountain.
Should you encounter one,
I'll leave it up to you.
You have permission to use
your weapons if necessary.
Got it?
OK, guys. Have fun!
Face right!
Advance forward!
Advance!
Now then...
OK, the rest is up to you.
Roger.
Heavy...
Heavy! Heavy, heavy!
Kureha-chan, don't say that.
The more you say that,
the heavier it gets.
Noël, how much farther?
Noël!
Hey, Kanata!
Found it!
Yahoo!
Wow!
Functioning normally. No issues.
What?
We found that one easily.
Let's keep it up!
Yeah.
What's wrong?
No, just...
I was just thinking, it's been protecting
the town, all alone, this whole time.
Now then, Noël,
where's the next one?
Let's see...
We're here now, so...
That mountain.
Th-Th-That mountain?
Someone do something
about these bags!
Heavy...
I knew it. The captain and
Rio-sempai both hate me!
I know it.
That's why they're doing this!
Heavy...
Hey, say something, Kanata!
It's not like you not
to say anything!
Hey!
Shut up!
What?
I can hear you...
I can hear you!
Hey, Kanata!
What's wrong?
She's broken?
Wow, amazing!
It's so cool down here!
And so pretty!
Break time!
I don't care what anyone
says. It's break time!
I've decided it!
First in!
Not fair!
This is good!
I'll get you for that!
Take that!
Just for the heck of it.
Noël, you...
A fish!
Hey, Kureha-chan!
Wow, this is fun!
Yeah!
No, it's not!
You're not taking this
seriously enough.
It's a field trip.
You have to enjoy it!
Did you forget about
those ten-ton sacks?
This is training!
But Filicia-san...
Get a clue already!
She's evil.
The devil herself!
But she's got blonde hair
and her skin is so pretty!
That doesn't mean anything...
Kureha doesn't understand.
Understand what?
That's what's good about her.
Right?
No!
You guys must know
some other Filicia!
Geez! Someone do something
about these goody-two-shoes!
Time for food! Hooray for food!
We're soaked...
It'll dry quick in this sun.
Wh-What?
Our food's gone.
Was it a boar maybe?
What?!
In the countryside back home,
they tear up fields all the time.
But there's a lot of food for them in the summer,
so you normally don't see them.
There's a bigger problem.
What?
The compass is gone.
What?!
I wonder if it was OK
to leave those bags.
We've gotta focus on reaching
the goal now.
Are we going the right direction?
The first device was here.
Here's the river.
We're on the mountain with the
second device at its summit.
So we just need to head upward.
OK! We'll get there,
no matter what-
Hungry, huh?
I wonder if there's anything
we can eat...
There is!
Bayberries!
Can you eat them?
Yup!
They're sweet and a little
sour. They're good.
The sounds made a chord!
But we can't get up there.
It's dangerous.
You think so?
We should hurry.
They say Major Claus once
crossed a desert in a tank,
for three days and nights, with no food,
to take out an enemy fortress!
We'll be fine!
Yeah?
You've never heard that?
They call him the Desert Wolf.
He's amazing!
Wow... Claus-san is?
So let's do our best!
But the bayberries...
No whining!
Found number two!
A boar?
Where's the last one?
It's getting pretty dark.
So we'll have to keep
checking our direction.
Is this really the right way?
Probably.
What do you mean, "Probably"?
I can't be one hundred percent
sure without a compass.
Then what? We've come
all this way for nothing?
That's not what I'm saying.
If the compass is that important,
you should've kept it with you!
Hey!
Let's not fight here, guys!
It's your fault for playing
in the river.
Huh?
That's right!
You're not taking this seriously!
What did you mean, field trip?
You're such an airhead,
smiling like an idiot all the time!
That's why we're in this mess!
Don't you understand that?
Hey!
There it is!
Yahoo!
Hey, wait!
Kanata!
Sheesh... I guess they'll be all right.
Goal!
We did it!
We did it, Kureha-chan!
I get it, I get it, so get off me!
I can't breathe...
Look.
No Man's Land.
This is the end of the inhabited world.
Good work!
Captain, I'm sorry!
We didn't complete our mission!
What mission?
Huh? But...
I told you, it's a field trip.
But...
We just wanted you to see this.
These are the signatures of
those who came before us.
All the fortress maidens came
here at least once.
And they saw this...
The end of the world.
This is history, isn't it?
It sure is... Can you
walk a bit more?
There's one more thing
they've left us.
You're late!
Rio-sempai?
What happened?
Here!
Bayberries!
I feel alive again.
So, did you win?
Don't ask.
But it was worth the effort...
Kanata's Day Off - Hair Braiding
Next time:
Kanata's Day Off.
Hair Braiding.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.