Saturday, April 4th.
The height of spring.
Corona House
Everyone knows it's the season to start anew.
I, Koutarou Satomi,
will be living on my own, now
that I've gotten into high school.
This is my best friend, Makkenji.
His name's Kenji Matsudaira, making "Makkenji."
I've been stuck with him ever
since elementary school.
This is Kasagi Shizuka-san, my landlady.
Supposedly we're the same age,
but she's managing this apartment complex.
Looks like she was cleaning
up the yard for us.
And this is the apartment
that will become my castle
for the next three years.
Room 106 at Corona House.
No security deposit or money put down.
No fees to use the common area, either!
Plus, the rent's only 5,000 yen a month!
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
I see, you're all moved in?
If you had anyone help,
make sure you thank them.
Sure.
How are things on your end, Dad?
They relocated me for
my job out of the blue,
but stuck me in a dorm for singles.
I can get meals here, and take baths.
No problems for the foreseeable future.
I see.
Well, this is a good opportunity.
Find someone nice.
Well, I forgot I have some stuff to clean up.
Better get going.
First day of
Kindergarten
Well, that's okay.
Anyway, talk to you later.
Good night, Koutarou.
Night.
You should take a day off
since you just moved.
The invasion begins!?
I need to save some money for this spring.
Didn't your dad leave you some?
I should try not to spend that.
That's why I searched really
hard for that apartment.
It is pretty impressive that you found
a place like that for 5,000 yen.
But aren't you worried?
You know, there's rumors that there's ghosts.
There wasn't anything last night.
Even if there was, I'm not
giving up on that place.
Hey!
Satomi-kun.
There's not enough people at site B.
Could you head over there?
Sure, not a problem.
Site B... Site B...
Koutarou.
Hm?
Am I just hearing things?
Ouch...
Where am I?
Koutarou.
I've been waiting for you for so long...
Countless days and nights.
And within those repeating
states of slumber and consciousness,
I wonder just how many times
I dreamed of this moment.
Koutarou, we've finally met.
Ow...
Um, so what happned there?
So get this, Landlady...
This guy hit his head at
work and passed out.
What?! Are you okay?
Yeah, the doctors said that
there's nothing wrong,
other than this bump here.
Well, that's good, but
don't go and worry us like that, Satomi-kun.
Er, Satomi-san.
Why did you change that?
Well, you're a tenant of mine.
Yeah, but I'm going to be your
classmate starting today, too.
Exactly. There's no reason to have
to choose your words with this guy.
But you definitely need to
choose your words better!
Satomi-kun, what are you
doing on the way back?
Sorry, Landlady.
I have something to do, so I'm kinda...
Oh, that?
You'll be alone with the beautiful president.
If you think that all men are
only after women like you are,
you're way off-base, Makkenji.
Sorry. See you later.
Sure. Later, Satomi-kun!
He's part of the Knitting Society.
Huh?
He already chose a club to join?
He was invited during the school
acceptance announcements,
and decided to join right away, supposedly.
I thought he was going to
continue with baseball, but...
Satomi-kun, I've been waiting for you.
Sakuraba-senpai, thank
you for having me here.
Ow...
Hm?
I see.
So, it was you I saw at
the hospital yesterday.
I never would have thought
you'd be at the same hospital.
For my whole life, my body's always
been a bit on the weak side.
I go in for periodic checkups.
Just in case, you know?
rou
I see.
Well, if you see me around
somewhere, feel free to say hi.
Especially now that I'm officially
part of the Knitting Society with you!
Club Entry Form
Are you sure about this?
Joining this club, I mean.
Hm?
I thought there were tons of people
who'd love to have someone
like you on their sports teams.
There's something I want to do.
Because of that, I'd like to learn how to knit.
Well, I'm not great with my hands,
so I'm not sure how long that'll take, but...
Got it.
In that case...
Right.
Club Entry Form
Let's start tomorrow.
Sure, Sakuraba-senpai!
I'm back.
Hm?
So, you're back!
All right... Today's the day!
I'm going to make a ton of
noise while it's still light out!
He didn't notice last night
or the night before that,
but now's my chance, while he's awake!
Now be surprised, my dumb friend!
It's mysterious!
Huh? Wait...
What are you doing in my room?
What?! You can see me?
Of course I can!
How did you get in here?
Why?
No way!
You're touching me...
You're touching me!
Go back to your own place!
That's weird...
Did I not lock the windows?
Hey!
What was that for?!
Y-You...
I was waiting for that reaction!
It's weird you're able to talk with me,
but that also saves me a lot of trouble.
Wh-What are you?
I'm Sanae.
Sanae Higashihongan.
I'm the ghost who lives here!
I see.
A ghost, huh?
So, what does a ghost want with me?
This is my house,
so I want you to leave!
Don't be selfish!
This is my home! It took
a lot of work to find it!
I won't hand it over that—
You're resorting to violence, now?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Take this!
Poltergeist attack!
Hey!  If that thing had hit me, I'd be dead!
You're so dumb.
That was the point!
Now, I'll finish you!
I knew it. Sacred items keep you at bay.
And my grandma sent me a ton of them!
I've been living here longer than you!
So get out!
I refuse!
I'm trying to make
things easier on my dad,
so I'm not giving up this cheap apartment!
Ow, ow...
Ow...
Who... are you?
I'm...
Um...
Yurika... um...
I'm the princess of love and courage!
Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika!
I'll protect the peace of this town!
Cosplay?
Oh, I see.
No! It's not cosplay...
The glass...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to,
I was just in a hurry!
I can't pay you back, though...
I don't have any money.
Why were you in such a hurry?
Ah, that's right!
This room is in danger!
Danger?!
Yes...
Gathering in this room, right now...
are large amounts of magical energy!
Magical girls will come to use it for evil!
So, please, run away from this place!
Right now!
Huh? What?!
Um... open up!
Please, listen to me!
If that's the backstory for your
cosplay party, hold it somewhere else!
That's right.
We're busy!
I don't like this, either!
This outfit doesn't hide my
chest or butt all the way...
but, the Magical Land says
I have to wear it proudly!
Please! Believe me!
Believe me!  Please, believe me!
Want to call a temporary truce?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Will you believe me?
That I'm a magical girl, I mean?
Sorry, but that's a little tough.
There's no such thing as magic.
Please!
I'm Karama!
I'm Koroma!
N-Now what?
I'm sorry for startling you.
W-Who are you?
A pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kiriha Kurano.
A descendant of the Earth People,
and a member of the Kurano clan,
masters of oracles and incantations.
The Earth People?
Oh, wow! How cute!
Basically, the underground people.
Um, so basically you're
a descendant of people who
moved underground centuries ago,
and recently you found the location of
a shrine that's important to your people,
and that's this room?
That's right.
So, Koutarou, would you give us this room?
We want to rebuild the shrine.
I see.
I understand, but...
Hey, that's not how you treated me!
Of course not.
She's not acting the way you did.
And be quiet, you guys!
I'm sorry!
By the way...
If you're willing to leave, we'll thank you.
Gold bars?
No, no! You can't have this room!
That's right!
You can't!
Very well, Kiriha-san.
I see, Koutarou.
Thank you.
Why are you getting greedy all of a sudden?!
No! I couldn't take something this valuable.
But, if she's being so nice,
I have to at least consider it...
Yes.
Now we can move on to our next goal.
Karama!
Koroma!
It's time to invade the surface world!
Invasion time!
If we can activate the shrine and
gather lots of etheric energy,
we can make many ether weapons.
Hold it!
What do you mean, invade the Earth?
Don't worry.
We'll treat you as an honored guest, Koutarou.
That's not the issue!
Forget it!
I'm not giving you the room!
Well said.
I refuse as well!
Me, too!
Shut up, you cosplayer!
What about this, then?
Do you really think this will break my will?
We endured being underground for a millennium.
But, how long can you endure?
Hey!
Why are you being all perverted in my room?!
It's not the time for that!
The magic power...
Again?
There better not be another one of you!
How... How rude!
W-What?
Don't fondle them, jerk!
Sorry! Ah!
"Sorry" isn't good enough!
You fondled my noble breasts
out of sheer lust, didn't you?
It was an accident!
I wouldn't deliberately touch them,
they're barely there in the first place!
Barely... there?
Well, that's true.
If he was going to fondle
somebody, it'd be her.
You want to?
No!
And yours are even further
out of the question!
How dare you, neanderthals?
Blue Knight!
Activate anti-personnel pulse
laser and sonic impact cannon!
As you wish, my princess.
I'll kill you all right now!
Karama! Koroma!
On it!
Etheric Field! Maximum Power!
Wipe them out, Blue Knight!
As you wish, my princess.
What is this?!
You can regret your insults when
you've been blasted to dust.
Blue Knight!
As you wish, my princess.
What are you doing to my room?
What?!
You can't lay a finger on
me, you neanderthals.
Yeah?
Special move, Sanae-chan Tulip!
Nice job, Sanae!
B-Bear?
Don't look!
How rude!
Stop it!
A bear!
Stop!
It's a bear!
Stop it!
If you surrender, I'll forgive you.
Do you really think a princess of
the Holy Fortorthe Galactic Empire
will bow her head to
some outland barbarians?
Blue Knight!
Transform into Final Attack Mode
and fire a limited blast
from your Genesis Buster!
As you wish, my princess.
Emergency alert!
Ultra-high energy readings
fifty meters above us!
Looks like an antimatter cannon!
That's bad, we'll all be destroyed!
What?!
It's huge!
No! I don't want to die!
You're already dead!
Hey, Tulip!
Stop it!
Blue Knight.
Begin firing sequence.
As you wish, my princess.
Hey, I said stop!
Please stop, ma'am!
Don't try to stop me, Ruth!
Princess Theiamillis!
Destroying this entire planet is a
violation of the treaties
on intergalactic war.
But, they said I was flat-chested...
Your task is to make the life form at
these coordinates swear loyalty to you.
This will cause you to fail!
Do you want to be the fastest
failure in the history of Fortorthe,
and bring shame upon your mother?
Blue Knight,
turn off the Genesis Buster.
Satomi-san, what is going... on...
The room is a mess!
You guys!
Yes!
The next time you damage this building,
or cause trouble for the neighbors...
Yes?
You're going to regret
the fact that you're alive.
I understand the situation.
A ghost.
An underground person.
An alien.
And a cosplayer.
And you're all fighting over this room.
It's hard to believe, but
I guess I don't have a choice.
But, I order you as the landlord
to resolve this all peacefully.
If you can't...
You're going to find eternal peace, right now.
Sign this, please.
Corona Convention
My signature indicates my willingness to abide by the agreements above.
Satomi Koutarou
Sanae Higashihongan
Kiriha Kurano
Karama Koruma
Theiamillis Gre Fortorthe
Ruthkhania Nye Pardomshiha
Yurika Nijino
The treaty is now officially in effect.
You know what'll happen
if you break it, right?
Approved
No matter what anybody
says, this room is mine!
I won't let anybody have it!
Who is that landlord?
How could she hit me?! I'm a ghost!
That hurt...
But...
Yes.
My shoulders feel much better.
Next episode: More Invasions?!
Eh? Huh?