My apologies for the wait.
I have been rather busy this evening.
You're hardly to blame, considering the situation.
It will be difficult to cover all that up.
Yes, perhaps...
This is too extensive for the Church.
We are accepting any aid proffered towards this effort.
Now then, Father...
Regarding my request, what is your decision?
The matter of the reward offered for the defeat of Caster...
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
Thank goodness...
Now, once I get the Command Seal for killing Caster,
Diarmuid and I will be truly connected.
My right hand's gone...
My right hand! My right hand!
I need it! I cannot call Diarmuid otherwise!
I won't be able to make him care for me!
My right hand...
My right hand. My right hand.
My right hand! My right hand!
Hand...
My hand...
I have secured Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri in the new city.
I removed the Command Seals by taking off her right hand.
Fine.
Get out of there now.
Lancer will return soon.
Roger.
I saved Matou Kariya...
Without doubt, he could threaten my master.
There is no excuse. This is an act of rebellion.
But what is this?
It is not regret...
Could this be excitement?
It's true that the Servant Lancer played an important part in the defeat of Caster,
a fact multiple eyewitnesses can corroborate.
Then I have the right to receive one of the Command Seals?
About that...
Kayneth Archibald,
I am unsure whether it is appropriate to consider you a Master at this point.
My contract with Lancer was executed jointly by my fiancée, Sola, and myself.
Is Sola not the one currently both providing the prana and caring for the Command Seals?
That is true.
I have temporarily given her the Command Seals.
However, the rights of the contract still lie with me.
First off,
the petition submitted to the Church to be a Master was filed in my name.
Very well.
The rights are yours.
Now, Kayneth...
Extend your hand.
Take, and drink.
This is my blood, given to you, for the salvation of all peoples.
The blood of contract!
I hope you will continue to fight a noble battle, as a Master.
Yes, of course.
I'm down to a single Command Seal.
My situation remains dire.
I cannot allow the other Masters to gain an additional seal!
Lady Sola!
You incompetent imbecile!
Useless, bumbling fool!
You fail to protect even a single woman?
Some fine chivalry...
I am grievously sorry.
Even if she was only a substitute,
you failed to protect your own Master!
What are you good for as a Servant?
I'm amazed you had the nerve to return here alone.
I am afraid, my Master, that Sola and I never had a proper contract.
We could not sense each other's presence.
And so you should have taken special care!
Master, Lady Sola lives yet.
She still supplies me with prana.
Irrelevant!
If you are not properly her Servant,
and if you cannot discern her location, it doesn't matter!
Sola, I should never have given you those Command Seals...
I could not dissuade her.
I share the responsibility.
I can't believe you have the nerve to say that.
Don't try fooling me, Lancer.
You were the one who encouraged Sola.
Never, sir!
It's just as in the legend...
Are you truly incapable of seeing your lord's fiancée without attempting to seduce her?
My Master, please retract those words.
So you don't care for that, huh?
You're only a beast. You swore eternal loyalty,
and then gave in to lust!
Milord Kayneth...
Why...
Why will you not understand?
I...
I wished only to defend my honor.
To fight in noble battle with you.
Don't speak to me like that,
Servant!
Understand your place.
You're nothing but a ghost, granted life by magic...
You dare lecture your Master?
Absurd!
If you are so dissatisfied, use your precious pride to resist my Command Seal.
You'll never win.
You Servants are mere puppets, and here is your mechanism.
Milord Kayneth...
Master..
What?
You still have something to say to me?
No, that isn't it.
Something is approaching.
It's just as Kiritsugu said.
There are traces of a magical barrier.
But it's strange...
It hasn't been properly maintained.
It's falling apart...
Everywhere...
I did not expect you here, Saber.
My...
My ally found this place and informed me.
They claimed you were to be found here.
You would not happen to know where my Master's fiancée is, would you, Saber?
I do not.
What of it?
No.
Forget it.
In any case, are you certain about this, Saber?
You did not come all the way here to talk, I'm sure.
But after that technique you used on Caster,
you must have depleted quite a lot of energy.
No more than the other Servants.
None will be fighting further tonight.
They will focus on defense.
That is why we won't need to worry about being interrupted.
Dawn nears,
but I believe there is no better night to finish our battle than this one.
What say you, Lancer?
Saber...
The only thing that still grants my heart peace is your pure fighting spirit.
Her attacks are too weak.
Saber, you...
You will not use your left hand?
Don't get the wrong idea, Lancer.
If I were to use my left hand here,
the shame would certainly dull my blade.
Against your spear,
that would be fatal.
Saber...
Therefore, Diarmuid,
this is my best chance to defeat you.
Pride rests in the blade of chivalry!
I...
I am glad that I was able to meet you.
I am the first spear of the knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Here I go!
Splendid!
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain, accept your challenge.
Come, then!
Why does he not win?
If he has no certain path to victory, he should escape with his Master.
Right now, our highest priority is to rescue Sola...
Why can he not understand even that?
That useless servant...
Him of all people?
This is a Self-Geas Scroll.
A magical item used by magi to form an unbreakable contract.
Binding Spell...
Affected Party: Emiya Kiritsugu.
The Crest of the Emiya Family orders the following.
The pledge is to be obeyed by the Affected Party
upon fulfillment of the conditions described herein.
Pledge:
Kiritsugu, son of Norikata, the fifth heir to the house of Emiya,
will be forever forbidden from harming
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri
or intending them to come to harm.
Condition...
The curse of the Geas theoretically cannot be removed by any means.
Even if you forfeit your life,
it will bind your soul as long as the magic crest exists.
It's true that if I do what's written, he cannot kill me.
But...
Under these conditions, my fight...
...will end here.
The Grail.
The pride of house Archibald, as well.
He asks me to throw it all away?
Sola-Ui...
Use all your remaining Command Seals to force your Servant to commit suicide.
The conditions have been fulfilled.
You want to win...
You want to win so desperately?
You desire the Grail that badly?
You have crushed... my sole remaining wish...
And yet!
You feel no shame at all?!
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive you for this!
Inhuman monsters who have ruined the honor of a knight,
let my blood taint your dreams!
Let the Grail be cursed.
Let the wish it grants bring disaster!
And when you fall into the pits of Hell,
remember the rage of Diarmuid!
Are you now bound by the Geas?
Yes, the contract is complete.
I cannot kill you.
Not myself, anyway.
Kill me...
Kill me, please...
Sorry.
But I can't, according to our contract.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I finally understand what a terrible man you are.
I believed our paths to differ,
but that our goal was mutual.
I was a fool to think this.
Until now,
I placed my faith in Irisviel's words,
and thus did not doubt you.
But now,
I can no longer believe that your desire for the Grail will be anyone's salvation.
Answer me, Kiritsugu...
What is the true reason you desire the Grail?
Even should my sword win the Grail,
if that means I must yield it to you...
I...
Answer her, Kiritsugu.
This time, you owe her an explanation.
Come to think of it,
this is the first time I have shown you the way I kill, Iri.
If you only eliminate a Master,
the Servant may make a contract with another party.
So I had to eliminate the Master and Servant simultaneously.
Kiritsugu, speak to Saber, not me.
She needs to hear your words.
No.
Honor, glory...
There's no point in speaking to someone who abides by these ideals,
yet does not hesitate to kill.
You would even insult chivalry to my face, monster?!
A knight cannot save the world.
Knights call certain methods of fighting good and others evil,
acting as if there were some nobility to the battlefield.
Such illusions, created by heroes throughout history,
have led countless young men to their bloody deaths, all for the sake of glory and honor.
They are not illusions.
Even the act of taking a life must be regulated by laws and ideals.
Otherwise, every war would bring Hell onto this world!
And there you go.
You heard her, Iri.
Our Heroic Spirit believes a battlefield to be preferable to Hell.
What a joke.
It's Hell itself.
There is no hope on a battlefield.
There is nothing but unspeakable despair.
Just a crime we call victory,
paid for by the pain of the defeated.
But humanity has never recognized this truth.
For that, we have to blame the dazzling hero,
who, in every era, has blinded the people with his legendary deeds,
and kept them from seeing the evil of bloodshed.
True human nature has not advanced a step beyond the Stone Age.
Then, Kiritsugu...
Is the reason you force Saber to endure such humiliation because of your hatred for the Heroic Spirits?
Of course not.
I don't allow private feelings to interfere.
I will win the Holy Grail and save the world.
And I will wage that war with the most appropriate weapons at my disposal.
Justice and righteousness cannot save the world.
I care nothing for them.
Kiritsugu...
Do you fully understand?
If you commit evil out of hatred for evil,
rage and hatred will merely birth new conflict.
Emiya Kiritsugu, I do not know what betrayed you,
nor what has caused you to despair so.
But your rage and sorrow are found only in those who once sought justice.
Kiritsugu, in youth, your truest self wished to be a hero, did it not?
A hero to save the world.
You believe in that... You desired it more than anyone.
Or am I wrong?
I will end this ceaseless cycle.
And the Grail is a means to that end.
I'll ensure that the blood I spill in Fuyuki will be the last blood humanity will ever shed.
If that means I must stain my hands with every evil in the world, I don't care.
If that will save the world, I do it gladly.
Kiritsugu has left, hasn't he?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!
Episode 16
The End of Honor
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
This cannot be allowed!
An alliance? Now?
Let me tell you the truth behind the Holy Grail War.
I accept.
Die, to make his dream a reality.
Such a boring ending.
Next Time:
The Eighth Contract
Goodbye, Father.