When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Good morning, Miss!
Come now.
Please get up!
What the heck? It's still
late night 32:00 o'clock.
Let me sleep a little more.
Please do not say that.
It is a pleasantly warm day outside today.
Why not go out for once?
I will pack us a lunch.
Mr. Rice Ball. Mr. Rice Ball.
High School Girls Ultra Quiz!!
And look, there are spring-like
events being held everywhere.
How about trying this one?
High School Girls Ultra Quiz.
To participate, you have to be a pair
of super-best friend high school girls.
This is stupid.
Who are these fools who sign up
for these things willy-nilly?
What a shame.
It says they welcome
last-minute participants.
And the prize is...
M-Miss?
If I win this, I get this?
This... This...
...will be mine?!
All right, I'll enter!
What? Why?
So that's what's going on.
How about pairing up with me?
How 'bout it? Ya'll do it, right?
Ya will, right? Awesome, right?
What? You're in Osaka?
At the Nanba Grand Kagetsu Theater?
Damn it! She hung up on me!
So Sakuya was a no-go.
Then I'll try Isumi next.
No, not happening.
Who can I pair up with?
Why don't you just enter, Hayate?
I have several high school
girl outfits ready to go.
What?!
Ooh, I hadn't thought of that!
I-I will go look for someone
who might pair up with you!
Damn, he got away.
Wow, a quiz contest, huh?
I wonder if entering something like
this will make a good youthful memory.
Wait, one of the prizes is...
An all-you-can-eat ticket to Mo-Para!
Shabu-shabu All-You-Can-Eat Ticket!!
Can't
show you!
This might be good!
Imagine it! Poofity-poof!
Poof! Poof!
Poofity-poof!
Just kidding!
Totally just kidding!
In my wildest dreams,
if ⁯I do say so myself...
But...
If I do win...
Maybe I could invite him.
Maybe I could invite him...
B-But...
Who...? Who...?
Who should I enter it with?!
Ow, that hurt...
Hayate!
Miss Nishizawa! P-Please pardon me.
I was lost in thought...
Th-This is...
Ah! This is...!
What good, good timing you have!
Huh?
Miss Nishizawa.
Y-Yes?
Won't you please enter
this quiz contest together?
Y-Yes.
Thank goodness! Miss Nagi will be pleased!
Huh? What?
In this episode, I will be serving
as a famous host of the Heisei Era!
Tima!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Quiz! Written as "Foe"
and Read as "Friend"!!
Shine! Jump out! Shake your hips! Come on!
The 4256th High School Girls Ultra Quiz!
Now, with the hard-to-draw crowd
of several tens of thousands watching,
it's begun!
I am Teruo Mikiri, host and narrator, and...
...Demonking Abe!
Here to bring you the event, tima!
Incidentally...
Do any of you remember me, tima?
Hey, don't try to hog all the attention.
Please forgive me, tima.
And now, here come the participating pairs.
End of Century
Empire
10,000 pairs, who have gathered
from all across the nation, tima.
Which pair will fight their
way through this quiz battle
and win the crown of victory?!
I can't wait to see, tima!
Vice President/Secretary
Aika, why are we here right now?
I thought that you might
like shabu-shabu, Chiharu.
Protagonist/Hammy
Why do I have to end up in this
with the hamster?
That's my line!
This is like being
handicapped from the start.
Suck it up! Suck it up, me!
Well, my abilities alone will be
more than enough to win this,
so I don't care whether I'm paired
with a hammy or a sausage.
If I can't put up with this,
what'll I do when I get a job
and my boss turns out to be
a sexually harassing bastard?
Or actually, this is the very first favor
that none other than Hayate
has asked of me, after all.
All right, let's win this quick
and take the trophy.
Once I win, I'm going to
have shabu-shabu with Hayate!
What are you saying?!
I will never permit that!
What?!
If you want to eat, eat alone,
in solitude with a lonely heart.
Not happening. You can tell me no,
but it's too late now.
No way I'm backing down! No way!
Hayate and the trophy are both mine!
Hayate's having shabu-shabu with me!
I made up my mind.
This year, I'm going to pursue Hayate,
even to the ends of the Earth.
They both seem to be
full of fighting spirit...
And now, let's get started with Stage 1!
Your first hurdle is your typical
"true or false" quiz, tima!
Please move to the area that
you believe is the correct answer
to the quiz questions we give you, tima!
2-choice questions are a piece of cake!
At any rate, we have to win this first...
Question 1!
Question 1
Naturally, Ishikawa Station
is in Ishikawa Prefecture.
A trick question right off the bat!
Or so they want us to think.
They're testing how trusting we are.
True, of course!
This way! It's false!
What?!
I have a feeling it's true!
Grr! Do as I say!
The pair fighting over there,
please hurry up and
choose your answer, tima.
Don't drag me down already!
Question closed!
The correct answer is...
...false!
It is actually a station name
in Aomori Prefecture!
Pairs who got it wrong, goodbye, baby!
See that?!
If you've played the Momo-Tetsu game,
it's an easy, common knowledge question!
If you know the answer, say so first!
Question 2. Between
chimpanzees and giant pandas,
the one who weighs less
at birth is the giant panda.
They say it's "giant" so
the panda probably weighs more.
False!
This is true! No mistake about it!
It's false! Don't get in my way!
True! Just come with me!
It's that pair again...
I'm telling you it's true!
Okay, and the correct answer is...
...true!
Bye-bye to the false pairs!
See? I told you.
Giant panda babies are 15cm long,
weighing just 90-130 grams.
I saw it on Animal Planet.
Then say so first!
Question 3
Question 3, a Japanese sake question.
For delicious warm sake,
the recommended temperature for
perfectly warmed sake is 40 degrees Celsius!
That's not a question
for high school girls, tima.
So what?
Go call the agency
if you've got a problem with it!
Please don't, tima!
No one's moving.
Legally-speaking, sake's something
high school girls don't deal with.
Oh, yes, yes, I forgot to mention this,
but every pair in this
contest can use a lifeline!
Oh, this is totally ripping off "Who Wants
to be a Millionaire", right, tima?
The temperature for perfectly
warm sake is 40 degrees Celsius.
True
False
Hell if I know
There! There, there!
That rule sounds so tacked on.
However, you can only use one
kind of lifeline just once, tima.
Think carefully.
Telephone!
Ooh, the Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair
has gone straight for the telephone!
No willpower, tima.
H-Huh?! Wh-What should I do?
I'm suddenly being put on the spot?
But I know the answer.
The correct answer is...!
Yes?
The correct answer is false.
Perfectly warmed sake
is approximately 45 degrees Celsius.
That's my Maria!
I knew I could count on you!
Incidentally, the temperature of sake
is divided into 6 levels.
Super hot, hot, perfect, lukewarm,
skin temperature, and barely warm.
What about my role?
Okay, the correct answer is false!
No one got it wrong! Darn!
You saved us, Maria!
Thank you!
I wish you luck.
So, on to Stage 2!
Next up is the familiar scatter quiz!
Questions will be scattered from above.
Pick one up and answer it, tima!
The time limit is 5 minutes.
Just answer one question
to move on to the next stage, tima!
And now... GO!
GO!
All right, I'll go!
What? That's okay. I'll do it.
Shut up! You can do this!
Oh, yeah, bubble popping!
Once you get started, you can't stop.
Wait, she's already gone!
I'm just telling you to stay out of my way!
Huh? What happened?
I-I got a cramp in my leg.
Oh, really!
But running isn't really my thing.
Nothing!
Moron Moron
Too bad, you got nothing, tima.
What?!
I mean, most of the envelopes have
nothing, so do your best, tima.
Oh, man.
Get running. You have no endurance.
Are you in any position to say that?!
Just go!
Yes, yes, yes.
Nothing
Moron!
Nothing! Nothing! Nothing!
I-I think I might be done for...
I am not giving up!
Huh?
For Hayate!
Until I have my hands
on that victory trophy!
Though my leg may be cramping!
You're right! Shabu-shabu with Hayate
is waiting for me beyond this suffering!
Still saying such impudent things?!
Hayate likes shabu-shabu, too! I'm sure!
Trophy!
Shabu-shabu!
One minute left, tima!
Crap!
Please!
Okay. Nothing!
I mean, here's your question.
That's confusing!
Now, here is your question. What's
the minimum fare on the Yamanote Line?
Um, two-thousand...
Th-The current fare in 2008 is 130 yen.
That is correct, tima!
Piece of cake.
Behold the latent power of the ordinary!
And now, on to Stage 3!
Locked room escape quiz, tima!
If you can escape from
that room within 3 minutes,
you will gain the opportunity
to answer the quiz question.
Hmm, I suppose it wouldn't hurt
to leave this to the commoner.
Huh? It won't open!
And the window, too!
And the floor, too!
None of it seems likely to open!
As long as we can get out,
I'm not picky about how we do it.
That's the commoner.
Well, I'll be escaping
one step ahead of you...
Huh?
What?!
A h-high rise?!
20 seconds left!
What'll we do? What'll we do?
Key! Key! Was there a key somewhere?
Good grief, you really are totally useless.
I don't see one, I don't see one.
What'll we do? What'll we do?
Let's see, the typical escape methods
for these Crimson Room-esque games are...
First, you take this and do this...
And you'd find something
like this around here...
And once you do this...
You open this thing here and you get this...
And when you do this with it...
No way!
Oh, it opened!
You have successfully escaped, tima!
Congratulations!
Congratulations! And now,
here is your question.
You're kidding!
What is the world's first video game console
that was released in 1972?
Um... "Brain Age..."
It's the Odyssey!
That is correct, tima!
Next up, we are finally at the last stage!
So you repaid the debt
you owed me from Stage 2.
In the end, it just means this
is a piece of cake
as long as we have my brains.
When the last stage is over,
will the goddess of victory
bestow her smile upon them?
Oh, Mr. Mikiri,
you just sounded exactly like the narrator
we always hear in the show, tima.
Quit it with the "tima"s! It's annoying!
And their triangle love with the butler!
Will this bring a subtle change
to their relationship? Or maybe not?
For now, it'll be continued
in the second half.
Tima!
The carotid artery. (Kei-doumyaku.)
Even if you eat, don't go to sleep right away!
(Kuttemo sugu neru na!)
Do you all wanna go to New York?
I do!
Pay your own way.
I ain't got money!
Now, let's bring out our
magnificent finalists, tima!
Our first team...
...is these two!
"We're friends who even
take baths together."
It's the Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair, tima!
Don't introduce us like that!
Who leaked that information?!
And the second team!
"We were originally supposed to have
more scenes in the 3rd half-season."
It's the Aika Kasumi-Chiharu Harukaze pair!
Gack! The vice president
and secretary of the student council?!
It seems we have survived
being eliminated somehow, Aika.
So it seems, Chiharu.
And finally, the third team.
"We eat the strawberry
first on our shortcakes
"and the pickled bamboo
shoots first on our ramen."
You do?
Well, something like that.
The favorite to win! It's the Hinagiku
Katsura-Miki Hanabishi pair!
What?! Even Hinagiku was in this?!
Hey, I came along because you asked me
to help you choose a gift
to celebrate your relative
getting into school.
What's going on here?
Um, that is to say, the prize is the gift...
As long as we have Hina,
our victory is assured!
Hina!
Looks like we'll get
some good footage again.
Rah! Rah! Miss!
Miss & Nishizawa
Go for it! Go...
I can't see!
Pardon me. I'll be more careful.
Okay, ignoring the cheering squad
that's getting more attention
than the participants...
The final stage!
Don't Slip Now, Speed Quiz Round, tima!
Get an answer right
and the slides will go up bit by bit
for the other pairs, tima!
The last pair to keep
from sliding down will win, tima!
Well, with Hina,
I've got an army at my back...
Oh, right, she's already
out of it at this height...
I-I'll be okay.
A-As long as we stay at this height.
We're going to answer
every question, all right?
No getting things wrong either,
okay? Okay? Okay?
This is a battle I absolutely cannot lose!
We've come this far! We can't lose now!
And now, Question 1!
Question 1
In Japanese, it's "I think, therefore I am".
In Latin, that's...
"Cogito ergo sum".
Correct, tima!
Next question!
The true taste of coffee is...
A barista.
Correct!
According to quantum theoretical thought...
Schrödinger's cat.
The Treaty of Mersen.
The Sarashina Diary.
The two-crop system. A theremin.
A backward pivot throw.
So strong! The Katsura-Hanabishi pair
is overwhelmingly strong!
You're doing good!
You answer some, too.
Aika...
To be honest, I have
about reached my limit...
Y-You, too, Chiharu?
Yes, then...
Shall we fall soon...
Oh, but she's gone already!
In that case...
...I shall join her!
The Kasumi-Haruka pair has dropped out.
Meanwhile, the Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair
also looks to be struggling
quite a bit, tima!
Th-The next one...
We have to answer it!
Question!
Father's least favorite...
It's mine!
Papa-ya!
Yes, but...
Now, name four other tropical fruits.
Kiwi, mango, pineapple, durian.
Correct yet again, tima!
This is bananas!
Now, what will you do,
Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair?
They're at quite a nice angle, tima.
You lose if either one of you fall, tima.
Don't copy me!
I think this might be my limit...
Maybe. Maybe.
This is nothing!
For Hayate!
I will win and get the trophy!
Come to think of it, Little Nagi's
been going on and on about the trophy...
Can't show you!
Oh, come to think of it,
the trophy shown on the flier...
...might've looked somewhat like Hayate.
Little Nagi...
I've reached my limit!
Hayate...
What?!
F-Fight it.
You're going to win
and get the trophy, right?
Let's try hanging in there
just a little longer.
Hammy...
With the two of us together,
I'm sure we'll be invincible!
Yes, I understand! Let's do our best!
And now for the question!
What kind of dumpling goes silent
when you look at it?
This is it!
Me!
Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair, go ahead.
"Mitara shhh (if you look, shhh)"...
So it's mitarashi dumplings!
Correct!
You did it!
Among the episode titles for Japanese anime,
what was the longest ever?
Leave it to me!
The 187 character long title
for Episode 26 of "School Rumble".
Correct, tima!
That's my Little Nagi!
A bronze statue!
"Matango"!
Sam!
Color flashing!
Impossible! I'm being put on the defensive?!
Never mind that. How are they
pressing the button in their position?
That's all fine and good, but...
I'm... just...
Go for it! Call for it! Fine weather for it!
Hang in there!
Now, will the next one settle it?
Koyuki's, the cake shop known
for their ultimate seafood cake!
How much does one
of their cream puffs cost?!
Me!
You two are in no position
to be able to push the button,
but what is your answer?!
Um...
As I recall...
200 yen a piece!
Correct, tima!
Well, that's about as far as we get.
Adieu!
Aww...
That was one heck of a fall...
The Katsura-Hanabishi pair has
suffered an unexpected defeat, tima!
And so, victory goes
to the Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair.
I'm surprised you remembered the price.
Same to you.
Well, you did well for a hamster.
I guess you were pretty gutsy
for a delicate rich girl.
That's right! The trophy!
Can't
show you!
Shabu-shabu All-You-Can-Eat Ticket
What should I do with this?
Maybe I'll go with my family, after all.
Miss Nishizawa!
H-Hayate...
Really, congratulations on your victory!
You fought magnificently out there!
I think I might be a bit
embarrassed to hear that.
Th-Thank you.
Not at all. I should be
the one to thank you.
Thank you so very much.
I hope we can continue to work
together in the future, Miss Nishizawa.
Yeah, of course!
Hayate, I guess it might
still be a long way off
before my feelings reach your heart.
But even so, I can still...
...keep my gaze squarely
on you like this, right?
Right?
What are you doing, Hayate?!
We're leaving! We have to celebrate tonight!
Yes, Miss.
Oh, wait.
What is it?
If you've got something to say,
make it quick, hamster.
Hey, if you feel up to it,
how about the three of us
go eat shabu-shabu now?
Or something like that...
Miss.
Yes!
I swear, this meat is paper thin.
It's shabu-shabu, so of course it's thin!
What did you say?! I came
because you asked me to come!
What was that?!
Now, now, I will skim
all the scum off the top.
Incidentally, shabu-shabu is very healthy
and also great for middle-aged
people living alone.
Shabu-Shabu
Next time, they will battle the 150
million yen we'd totally forgotten about.
Can't
show you!
More like, that was a lot
of dialogue in this episode, huh?
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Try saying my name. I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Time flies. This is already Episode 50
of "Hayate the Combat Butler".
The story is finally
coming up on the climax!
Will Hayate be able to defeat the Great
Super-Dimensional Evil Butler General?!
Um, we'll have to see about that...
By the way, this song is your
character song, isn't it, Miss?
Yes. Actually, the next episode
will be our last Butler Report.
I must take the anchor position, after all.
So, the fan service shot is of me, too.
This is improper, Miss!
Not to worry. For the next episode,
we'll prepare a fan service shot
of you bathing in a cross-dress outfit.
What?!
Well, see you!
Preview
What? Something important
the Miss had ordered?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Yes. Might I ask you
to go get it from the store?
I understand. I will go right away.
Don't be in such a hurry!
Huh? Why?
I just suddenly don't want to
see your face anymore!
What?!
Mister Ayasaki, I would like to give you
this gift of 150 million yen.
I would like to poach you for my company.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler"...
"Spring."
Spring
Don't be such a stranger, Hayate!
I will protect the Miss!