The future is unknown...
Human life is like a continuing story from someone’s imagination.
The way Samsa woke up as a gigantic insect…
That day, they suddenly transformed into sukas!
Suka!!
It would be great to go back to your childhood and have fun～
Even if you can’t return to your, childhood you can still have fun right?
By Kazumi.
Alright. Any questions?
Yep!
Oh? Asuna-san raised her hand! That’s rare.
Alright, Asuna-san.
Hey Negi, why are you teaching us now?
Looks like we’ll be distracted for a while. Please bear with us.
That’s not what I meant. Do we really need to have class while we’re in the magic world?
Yeah!
In any case, let’s look for a way to get out of this magic world!
What are the two of you talking about!?
In this dire situation, Negi-sensei, with his wonderful personality is still doing his job for us!
Don’t go “eeh” in front of me.
Excuse me…
Oneechan!
Sensei! I forgot my homework!
Oneechan, you’re not my student…
I forgot it! Should I stand in the hall?
Oh, come on...
I　will take the bucket now!
Oneechan……
I’m going now…
Nekane-san is really popular in the class, huh?
That counts as popular?
A lesson?
When we came to this world,
I don’t think we have to stop working on investigating the situation.
They just said it themselves…
If they want to, just let them do whatever they want.
Master, it has been 3 minutes.
I see
Thou shall wait.
Let 5 more minutes pass.
These cup noodles only need 3 minutes.
How naïve.
The longer instant ramen is cooked、
The fatter it becomes,
And the better it is to eat.
I think 3 minutes is more than enough!
If you wait longer it will go bad.
Please follow my eating style today.
These are the last cups of garlic noodles!
Let me eat it the way I want it!
Isn’t garlic poisonous to vampires?
This level of poison is just a small sting. It is actually nice to eat!
If you leave it longer, it will be even nicer to eat.
No! I will eat immediately!
Is that so…
If that’s the case…
The only way is to do it by force!
Takamichi! We’re in trouble!
Give it back!!
What’s on, Negi-kun?
Everyone has…
All of a sudden, everyone became like this…
It’s not because you’ve tried to activate the contracts?
No…
Everyone switched to Suka mode!
The card expiry is in 3 patterns.
29 people have been transformed at once.
The probablility of all changing into the suka mode is 1 out of 68,630,377,364,883.
I don’t think this is something you should get excited about.
Once the spell expires, they will return to normal, naturally.
Sensei! Let’s play!
Let’s play! Let’s play! Let’s play!
Eh, please wait everyone…
Not only do they look like children, their minds have become childish as well!
Anyway, I have to check up on something.
Everyone turned into Sukas! What a sight!
Everyone has become Sukas-suka.
Is that so-suka?
Mana-chan wins!
We’re in trouble!
Asuna and Haruna are having a shoot out!
A SHOOT OUT!?
Go get em! The big helmeted Evil Weevil!
Don’t lose! White-spotted longhorn beetle!
Come on!
Yes!
My red butterfly will join the battle, too, aru!
What in the... They're just insects…
Kids do cute things don’t they?
Doki doki…
Cat! Cat!
Frog! Frog!
I’m twisted, mya.
If it's children, you call it simple-mindedness.
Is this called simple-mindedness too, myaaa?
W-Well… you can’t call it evil intentions… either.
Do you guys know?
If you use a straw to blow air into a frog, it will swell up!
Let’s try it!
Whoa!
Woah! It's true!
Akira-chan is amazing!
Pure sphere!
Akira-san!!
Are you alright? Akira-san?
Yep! I’m alright!
Hey you, I’m not alright…
In a good way.
No, in a bad way...
Yaaa… I wanna sit on it too!
Don’t play dangerously, okay?
Uaaaah!! Hey! Hold on a second!
AAAAAAAH!!!! MY STAFF…!!
Ah! Haruna-chan is writing something!
Broke…
Everyone’s so cold hearted eh?
Even so… My staff…
Doki doki…
There’s one stick lying down…
After that… the stick… and then another stick…
Negi-sensei! There's trouble!!
What is it this time, Asakura-san?
That!
WAIT!!
She was just playing with insects a while ago!!
They’ve changed their minds already!
Don’t chase it!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Aniki, it’s broken!
AAH, THAT'S RIGHT...
Asuna-san!!
Capture successful!
There doesn’t seem to be a problem…
AAH! ANIKI!
What is it this time?
Cave exploration, de gozaru!
YEP!
It’s dangerous! Don’t go inside!
One more blow!
Landing successful!
One more time!
Me too!
YOU WILL NOT GO!
Aniki, babysitting is horrible isn’t it?
This is a squid.
Aaaah, troublesome, troublesome…
Aah, that was surprising…
We lost…
Soft and Fluffy~
Anyway, how long should I be standing here?
I don't know.
Hey, Hey!
When I realized it, I turned into a chibi form!
The magic world is amazing!
And so, since I’m in chibi form,
there are no sexy shots for today!
Too bad…
It’s tasty, huh?
It is tasty.
Did you know, Secchan?
What is it, Kono-chan?
If you can find a koala with eyebrows, you will live happily!
A koala with eyebrows?
Happiness..
In that case, we will always be happy if…
What is it, Secchan?
N-Nothing! Kono-chan!
Yeah?
Yeah! In order to offset it, I’ll just draw…
I can’t do it…
What is it, Secchan?
N-N-Nothing, Kono-chan!
It’s tasty, right?
It is tasty.
The Chao Castle is done!
It’s as splendid as 100 meat buns!
Waaah! I’ll also build a castle!
Done!
Ahh! Nice!
That’s a nice dog house!
I wonder what kind of dog lives in it? Bark! Bark!
It’s a castle…
Ahaha! It’s so fast!
Aniki, can you still go on?
I’m still alright! This is…
Rollin’, rollin’, rollin’…
Are you really alright, Aniki?
I’m alright… I’m alright…
Which one do you want, Yue-san?
Umm… Err… Doki doki…
What is it?
Umm…
I want one from over there…
Oh, over there eh?
Alright, which one, Yue-san?
Err, actually I think the ones over there are better.
Alright.
Nodoka-san, what’s the matter?
Why are you hiding here?
Umm...
Yes?
Negi-sensei...
Can you read me a book?
Alright.
The venue under analysis apparently is...
under the influence of increasingly powerful magical power coming from external sources, I believe.
It takes a considerable amount of magical power...
to make around 30 people transform for such a long time.
That’s something not anyone can do.
Anyway, you said that fatter noodles taste better right?
How about this?
Takahata! Is this a one in a million pinch?
Neapolitan sauce… Neapolitan sauce…
It's daddy! Daddy!
Ah, honey, you are early today!
Welcome home, daddy!
Come! We have just made dinner!
I also helped out making it!
A playhouse, eh? Makes me want to go back to being a child too.
Work is tiring, huh, honey?
Take it easy, okay?
Daddy! Listen!
Today something interesting happened at school!
Ah, so healing…
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
Would you like a cup?
Yes, please.
Ahh… A family is good~
Oh? Aren’t you going to eat?
Ah, Itadakimasu.
You aren’t eating!
Why aren’t you eating?
You didn’t put it in your mouth.
You are only pretending to eat!
But, this is… soil…
But I made it with lots of love…
If that’s the case, my croquette is not nice to eat either!
By croquette, you mean… this brush!?
Our relations and love have faded, before nobody knows, didn’t they?
You won’t review our family life anymore, right!?
Uaaaaah! Daddy hates me!
No… that’s not what I intended…
Then, eat it.
Come on!
That day, the brush tasted really painful.
I don’t think brushes taste good any day.
I guess so…
Alright, there we go.
I think making so much food would be quite troublesome, huh, Aniki?
Why is it that even I have to make food?
We have no choice…
He can’t do it all alone.
My, that’s not how you do it, Negi.
You turn on the flame later.
If you put the vegetables into the water first, then the meat won’t get cooked.
Oneechan?
Can I help you with the cooking?
Ah, yes.
Itadakimasu!
All the little ones eat like adults, don’t they?
Luckily this doesn’t happen all the time…
I want seconds!
Alright. Please wait a minute.
Seconds here too, de gozaru!
Seconds, aru!
Alright, alright.
Aah, I’ve spilt.
I’m working on it, please wait!
Me too, desu!
I take that back. They’re nothing like adults.
Motsu, haven’t you eaten today?
I have, but I still feel hun… gry
A brush?
Not this...
Don’t be choosy! Eat it!
It’s not that I don’t like it.
Then, what is it?
It’s not peeled properly.
This girl…
But you see Satsuki-chan, this is done by Eva-oneechan for you!
Really?
Yeah!
Then, I will eat it.
It’s nice, right?
Oneechan…
Ah! Cold!
Here. It’s lemonade.
Oneechan…
Alright, pass out the drinks to everyone!
Okay!
Oneechan, you’re amazing after all…
I can’t babysit everyone that well…
That’s not right, Negi.
I’m not babysitting them.
I’m having fun with them!
Oneechan?
Yeah, that's right.
Alright.
Today, you’re not a teacher. You are their friend!
Friend?
Hey, what are you guys doing? Get off your butt!
Negi-kun, come and play!
Come on!
Have fun!
Okay!
Everyone! Let’s have fun!
We’re back!
Haa… He’s asleep.
He’s tired.
Ahh! What a lovely face!
Cute!
Ugh, he'll catch a cold sleeping here...
Thank you, Asuna-san.
Geez, it’s so troublesome to babysit kids.
And so, all the little ones’ playtime has come to an end.
BUT! That reason is still in the dark. The adventure in the magic world has not ended!
Please wait for the next episode…
Let's go!
When you are mad, when you are sad, whenever all that happens, it’s alright to eat.
Next time,
"Even if you say, 'When you're big, you have a big appetite', that really isn’t the case."
By Satsuki.
Aaaah! I’m full! I’m so satisfied!
There you go!
Why is this happening!?
I think it was just a matter of time…
Why me…
Anyway let’s all play with straws!
Not again…
You're so popular, mya.
Bon soir?
What the heck is this!?