When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Hakuou Academy's beach class involves...
...traveling on a private jet.
Since Hinagiku is afraid of airplanes, she won't be participating.
But don't worry.
Stay tuned.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
What? Is it the summer vacation episode?
Due to scheduling issues, they swapped episodes eighteen and twenty.
Not many participants for a beach class.
Why?
Because the cost was through the roof.
It's not because we wanted to reduce production fees.
And this is Hayate's first airplane trip.
But he was in a helicopter before, wasn't he?
Oh, well...
Thank you very much, Milady.
It's so pretty.
What is?
The ocean of clouds.
Katsura-chan, come check the "kumoumi" out with us.
"Unkai".
"Unkai"?
Unkai = "Sea of clouds". The Student Council Trio use the wrong reading of the kanji.
You write "kumo" "umi", and you read it as "unkai".
After the vacation, I'll put it on the kanji test.
Unkai... Unkai...
Sir Taiga.
I am thirsty.
W-Would cola do?
Yes.
Okay.
Hi-Himuro.
It is nice and cold.
Another, please.
Right away!
Nonohara, can I take a seat now?
Sir, didn't I tell you?
You did.
What did I say?
"The best way to prevent economy syndrome is to jog."
Say it again.
"The best way to prevent economy syndrome is to jog!"
Then keep running!
Nonohara-kun, keep it down.
Yes.
Milady, thank you for paying the cost for the beach class.
Hayate, it's better if you don't thank me for the money while you're airsick.
I'm sorry-
A tropical resort island with white sand that surfaces in the middle of the southern blue ocean.
That's Hakuou Island for you.
Hakuou Academy's private island for beach classes.
We're here.
Make sure you don't fall behind.
There!
Get on already.
To your right, you'll see-
I think I saw unrelated screenshots there.
Looks like screen capture maniacs will have to keep their eyes open this episode.
Welcome to Hakuou Academy's Hakuou Island,
reserved for beach classes.
Who are you?
Pardon me.
I'm the newly-appointed butler and the manager of this island, Schmidt hen Bach.
Call me Schmidt.
Ah, I see.
Yes.
I will do my best to create your fun summer memories.
All right, best regards to you.
Best regards.
Then let's show you your rooms.
Looks like we have a triple.
Is that because we're dumb and dumbers?
I don't think that's quite the case.
Which bed do you want, Himuro?
Man, that was heavy.
Sir.
It's not heavy! It's not heavy!
Not heavy at all!
You have the main room, Milady.
Klaus-san and I will be in the guest room.
I'll see you later.
I don't mind being in the same room.
Everyone change into your swimsuit.
Gather up in pool-wear!
Before we get in the ocean, we'll warm up in the pool.
Start stretching.
All right, let's get in the pool, shall we?
Sorry to make you all wait.
Schmidt! What the heck is that?!
Synchronized Swimming Manipulation Machine.
Synchronized Swimming Manipulation Machine?
Let's get this started.
*Press*
Zan***to Moon Attack!
Hey! Why is he in front of me?
Hey you! What do you think you're doing to Milady?
This is part of the attractions for creating fun memories.
Please watch for a while.
Okay...
Music, start!
Schmidt! Stop this!
How does this become a fun memory?
Hi-Himuro!
Don't worry about me!
Nonohara! H-Help me!
Sir!
I don't remember raising you to be such a weakling.
Y-Yes!
Are you all right, Milady?
Yeah, no problem.
But that Schmidt...
He said he'll make fun summer memories for us,
but he's the one having fun.
Yes, I think so, too.
Wh-What are you doing?
Please create a fun summer memory with your master.
And last is...
*Press*
Bravo. Bravo. Bravo. Bravo. Bravo.
Were you able to create fun memories?
Of course not!
It's noon.
That was the chime for lunchtime.
A gorgeous barbecue is set out by the beach.
Yay!
Katsura-chan, save the punch for after lunch.
I guess.
But, before that...
It's boring to eat lunch in your school swimsuit, so I prepared some nice swimsuits.
I'll take this.
I'll take this, then.
This I'll get this.
However, I'll be selecting them for you.
Leave the changing to me, too.
Lan**lot dewa arimasen!
He's enjoying himself.
He's enjoying it too much.
Daidai-iro tte Orenji?
Daidai-iro tte Orenji? = Is daidai color the same as Orange?
Jibun de kangaenasai.
Jibun de kangaenasai. = Think for yourself.
Segawa Izumi.
Hanabishi Miki.
Asakaze Risa.
Katsura Yukiji.
Lady Sanzenin Nagi.
And, Sir Oukouchi Taiga.
Hey now... Why is he saved for the last?
Besides, we've had enough of this already!
So, lunchtime.
This bikini...
It's very erotic.
Schmidt's taste is a little strange.
Yeah? I like mine if you ask me.
Everyone, I've prepared this so the lunch will be a fun memory.
Create.
He's up to something again.
No way...
Live alligator to feed on!
Obviously, it's still alive.
Create.
Right when Hakuou Island was echoing with screams, Isumi was...
...trying to go to the beach class and getting lost again.
*Sniff, sniff*
*Bark, bark*
Peter! Hey, come here!
There's someone buried here.
Must let the old man know.
Meanwhile, Hinagiku was...
...enjoying the vacation in the city.
Très Bien.
We're airing from Ikebukuro today.
Let's DC Challenge!
You there!
Me?
You're really good.
This program requires very skilled techniques.
It's challenging the limitations of the hardware.
After the rampage, the alligator returned to the wild.
Hayate and everyone learned the value of life.
Humans, alligators, corals, seagulls.
They are all precious crew members of the spaceship Earth.
Take care, alligator!
Don't ever get caught by humans!
Find a good wife and create a nice family!
Make sure to use your wife's house when you have family reunions!
So good!
I can't eat any more...
But I want to eat another one!
After lunch came free time.
All sorts of marine sports were being created.
Segawa Izumi, Hanabishi Miki,
and Asakaze Risa met the blue ocean.
They met it.
They met it, too.
Men!
Island of Heat. Katsura Hinagiku.
Coming soon.
You won't go play, Milady?
I enjoy myself most when I'm doing this.
I've brought you a drink.
Thank you.
Create.
Merci. Create.
He's a good butler if he doesn't do anything.
Hey, this is good!
How do you like it?
"Like" what?!
We'll now go on an undersea cruise.
We can't see anything, though.
Create...
Don't try to change the subject.
It must be Diana's doing.
Sir?
Let's keep walking.
Yes, Milady.
And then it was suppertime.
Dinner at the hotel was gorgeous.
But that has nothing to do with her.
Tent Mura...
Tent Mura = Tent Village
Ranchuu...
Ranchuu = Roundfish
F-First kiss?!
Hakuou Academy's beach class's dinner was formal.
To Hakuou Academy's beach class.
Create!
Oh, you all don't seem to be enthusiatic.
I don't want this kind of beach class!
Neither do I.
I want to go home.
I don't like it, either.
Three stooges.
Three stooges?
Ah, sorry.
I agree with the three girls.
Schmidt, we don't want to be forced into your fun anymore.
Excuse me, but Katsura-Sensei, I'm only trying
so everyone can create fun summer memories.
And that effort is what's troubling us.
Himuro-sama.
Schmidt, your troubles create a negative effect on my master.
Nonohara-sama, you too?
Milady?
If everyone wants to go home, then I'll go home, too.
Then let's all head out, shall we?
Oh yeah, put the leftovers in some Tupperware, will ya.
I'll take it to go.
I won't let you.
Schmidt...
Get out of the way.
A summer beach class comes with a haunted house.
So that it'll be a part of your fun summer memories,
I've had these people come from all over the world!
The fun is only starting.
It's showtime.
Milady!
Hayate fought for Nagi.
I-I'm counting on you, Nonohara!
Nonohara made Azumamiya fight.
Taiga protected Himuro.
Klaus sprayed insecticide.
You find them in shops during summer.
Tama... used insecticide, too.
Create your fun summer memories!
How can we?
Everyone, let's go home.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
What a horrible beach class.
It is Hakuou Academy, after all.
Hey, Katsura-chan, this plane's flying over mountains.
It's not headed to Hakuou Academy?
Hey, where are we headed to?
If you don't like the beach class, I'll create a mountain class.
Schmidt?
Where are they headed to now?
Next time, we'll fight against summer memories.
Hello, this is Maria.
Our guests today are Aizawa Sakuya-san's butlers,
Makita-san and Kunieda-san.
I'm Makita.
I'm Kunieda.
We haven't seen you two in the show for a while, but what do you usually do over the weekends?
I bought a guitar a while back.
I can play E fine.
But F is...
By the way, I'm Makita.
Clean the room, I guess.
Oh, but when I finish, I tend to start reading books.
By the way, I'm Kunieda.
I see.
Thank you very much for coming today.
See you next week.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
What's up, yo? I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
What? We're back to your song?
According to a ranking, my song placed higher than Hinagiku's, but I'm pushing it again just to be on the safe side.
I see...
Now is the time to prove who
the heroine of Hayate no Gotoku is!
That's the Milady I know.
Your stubbornness is increasing.
Hayate. In Sanzenin Nagi's dictionary, the word "lose" does not exist.
Bye bye.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku...
Saki's been acting strangely recently.
Looks like she's worried about something.
Saki-san's going to her
Coming-of-Age Ceremony next year, huh?
By the way, what was your
Coming-of-Age Ceremony like, Maria-san?
I'm still a fresh seventeen year old.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Saki-san's Personal Business (National Ver.) 2007
Come to think of it, nobody celebrated my birthday.
I don't mind it though, really.
Let's get ready with Hayate next week, too!
RELEASE!