Sam, I've told you, haven't I?
We don't need hard drugs in Melanie Square.
P-Please wait, Tony-san.
I didn't have a choice.
Brother Ben insisted on selling them.
Like I care about your situation.
This territory belongs to us, the Stone Family.
Towards those who neglect to obey my rules, even if it's the president or the first lady, I will show no mercy.
That's as far as you can go.
Old man Gant.
I'm taking that guy with me.
You don't mind, do you?
Do as you please.
Your "stick to the old ways" attitude hasn't changed, I see.
You're probably the only mafioso that still won't allow hard drugs in Las Vegas.
I just want our Melanie Square to be a clean playground.
The city won't have a way to make a living if we bend to the new powers.
Don't be so arrogant, you little snot-nose.
You're not working to fulfill anyone's expectation after all.
You're hurting my ears.
"Stone head" Tony, huh?
Papa!
Duke, you came?
Sorry for coming so sudden, Tony.
Eva.
We just went to see a movie in the Square.
Papa, you haven't forgotten, have you? We're going to the amusement park the day after tomorrow.
Of course I haven't forgotten!
There's no way I'd forget a day where I'm to play with you.
Yeah.
Tony, can I have a moment?
That bastard again?
We should settle this once and for all.
Let them know what happens if they don't comply.
Understood.
Miss McCunnen.
This is Richard Harrington.
I'm here today expecting a favourable answer.
We will provide you with the maximum profit of the deal.
I see. That's not a bad deal at all.
But my answer will not change.
Why?
Don't make me explain it all over again.
Melanie Square is our family's territory.
Those who live here, those who make a living here,
everyone is my family.
I will never sell them out.
So that's the way it is.
Go home and tell that to your boss.
Or do you want to hear the answer from a bullet and go home as a corpse?
It seems that you people still don't know how fearsome we, the Inferno, can be.
What?
We'll wait for three days.
This is your last chance.
I have faith that you will change your mind.
Tony Stone.
What an arrogant bastard!
What's with his attitude, Tony?
He creeps me out even if it's only a bluff.
Lutz, Rob.
Investigate everything about Inferno's background.
I think there's more to them than just a sprung up organization.
Understood.
Are you ready?
Anytime you want.
Even when you have succeeded in grabbing hold of your opponent's weapon, it's not over.
Understood.
Splendid.
Even though you were nothing in the beginning,
you've reached your potential now.
It's because I have a good coach.
There are two missions I want you to take.
Are you up for it?
Two?
I'll give you the details in my house.
Come with me.
House?
This is your house, Miss McCunnen?
That's right.
Although it's a bit too big for someone living by herself without a family.
Lizzie is out handling a different case tonight.
More importantly, please tell me about the mission.
The first one is for you to be my bodyguard for tonight and be my company.
I told you, didn't I? That Lizzy isn't here.
This mansion's security is perfect, but even only as a formality, I want someone to be here.
Why does an executive like you always have only one guard?
Do I need someone else?
And the second mission is for you to have a look out for a certain mother and son.
Understood. If that's an order.
Don't do that.
You're not a doll.
You need to know why you must watch them so closely...
...or the meaning of it all, okay?
You're unable to find out anything useful about Inferno?
Y-Yes.
I've gone through all the information sellers and informants I could find,
but they all gave inconsistent information.
There's even words that they have involvement with the Vellucio family.
There is also Cervantes Family and of course, even the Bloodies name popped out.
What the hell is that?
Lutz, since when did you become such a useless bastard?
Sorry.
Stop it, Anton.
They properly did their job.
What do you mean?
Inferno raised their power in a short amount of time,
did a lot of things,
they have executives that never show themselves to others,
then there's the information from Lutz and Rob...
If you think it through thoroughly, the answer will appear on its own.
They are a special family that is highly connected to the west coastal families.
What?
That attitude of that guy supports all of this.
The only way for us to keep on living is to wag our tails before Inferno.
And he knew that.
Boss, are you saying that we have to give them Melanie Square?
You've got to be joking.
Wouldn't you do what you could to protect everyone in the Square, no matter who the enemy might be?
Anton, prepare a meeting with Inferno as soon as possible.
However, give them a condition.
Tell them to bring their boss.
Tony, you can't be...
We'll negotiate.
A negotiation, that is.
From what we know of their organization system, I don't think they'll bring their real boss.
However, that won't be a problem.
That'll do just fine to pick a fight.
But if we do that, they'll retaliate for sure.
That's right. Not only the square, but your family will be in grave danger.
I'll leave that part to you guys.
You must protect them.
Let them feel the pain for laying their hands on such a troublesome opponent.
So that mother and son's fate will be decided based on what they do.
That's right. Even if it's...
... will you do it?
Tell me.
Not because you're just following your order.
Give me your answer.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Alright.
Thank you.
No problem.
You seem to have become used to it.
To blend in with the sheep, you need to wear sheep's skin.
What did the fifth person we passed look like?
A Caucasian man in his twenties,
wearing a dodgers hat, with a black shirt.
By the conversation he had on his cellphone, it seemed he was separated from his friend and was trying to find a place to meet.
Correct.
Even when you wear the sheep's skin, never lose the wolf's sense of smell.
That's another thing you taught me.
Wait up.
Fine, I'll buy it for you.
Well then, Duke. I'll see you later.
Okay, Papa.
Tony, please be careful.
Brother Anton said the preparation is all set.
Let's go.
Stone heads, what are you up to today, all dressed up like that?
Old man Gant... This is none of your business.
Just listen, don't do anything that would cause civilian casualties.
If that happens...
I know.
The mansion is heavily guarded by Abel and Bark.
It's the safest place in Las Vegas tonight.
What about Inferno?
Soon.
I assume I can leave this case to you, Miss McCunnen?
Yes, it's also concerning our future.
I will pay them my respect.
Thank you for your concern.
But as someone in charge of this district, my situation is a bit complicated.
We want to take Melanie Square for ourselves without turning it into a battlefield in the process.
Please do us the favor.
Miss McCunnen.
Please be at ease.
With our two trump cards, most games are ours to win.
We just got a heads up from Rob.
The meeting will start soon.
I see.
Please be at ease, there are no unusual movements in the area.
If nothing happens tonight, it's our victory.
This is unexpected.
A fine woman like you is an executive of Inferno.
Everyone's surprised at first.
I hope you're not just an accessory.
We told you to bring us your boss.
I won't say I'm Inferno's number one.
However, I have been granted full authority over this matter.
Just as she said.
Please don't make rude remarks.
Get your hands off Melanie Square.
Do you really think we'll settle for that?
We'll return the debt eventually.
That's the code of the mafia.
There is no need for that.
We only want Melanie Square.
Those who live there couldn't find their place in society and toil in the shadows.
It's a haven for the fallen ones.
But...
they're our family.
We never betray our family.
That would go against our principles.
Stone headed, living by the old ways, just like your nickname... Isn't that right, Tony Stone?
Would you say the same thing even if your real family was in danger?
If you do that, you could lose everything.
Would you be alright with that?
I will ask you one last time.
Will you give Melanie Square to Inferno?
No.
You're late, Phantom.
What's this?
Get down! It's a sniper!
Return fire! Kill him!
It's no good! It's too far away!
Zwei, it's your turn.
What?
Is our boss okay?
The deal is off.
Boss and brother Anton are fine, but...
Rob and Lutz are...
No way...
Anyway, Nee-san. Please stay with Duke.
I understand.
What a crazy bunch of people.
Inferno.
Mama...
Duke, you haven't gone to sleep?
Listen, the onii-chan I saw at the amusement park...
Eva! Eva!
You're wonderful.
You are...
...wonderful.
As a tool...
or as mere equipment...
we only have to perform our function.