Let's see...
What should I do with these?
I might as well have some fun...
Huh?
What's up, Yuuji?
I hear they're gonna host something.
Host something?
Fumizuki Academy sponsored...
Treasure Hunting...
Orienteering Competition?!
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Fifth Period
Maps and Treasures and Striker Sigma V
Akihisa Yoshii has found some gold.
Man, I haven't eaten like this in forever.
It all looks so good!
Fumizuki Flour is every bit as delicious as I thought it would be.
Tastes just like bread!
I'd have no complaints if I could just get some jam...
You have no room to complain in the first place.
I guess flour digests pretty quickly...
Fox Phi. Kisaragi Land's mascot character.
Welcome
By the way, it's very popular with the kids.
Isn't this Kisara-
I already explained it in the narration.
Whoever lost this is probably looking for it right now.
I guess I'll just leave it here.
I can't find it... I can't find it...!
Morning, Hazuki.
What are you doing here?
Oh! Good morning, Mr. Stupid!
I'm looking for something I lost.
Lost?
I lost my Phi strap.
It's a limited edition... They don't sell it anymore.
Oh, that? It's right over-
Jesus, what now!?
Phi!
What's the matter, Yoshii?
Mr. Fukuhara!
Great timing!
Gimme permission to do a summon!
Why, exactly?
It's an emergency! Just hurry up!
I guess I might as well. Just remember, this is an exception.
All right!
Summoning Being...
Summon!
All righty! Grab that strap!
Save Phi!
Are you okay, Yoshii?
Mr. Stupid!
Christ... That damn feedback system...
What the hell is your problem?
Good morning, Mrs. Principal.
You scared the hell outta me!
Don't use Beings to wreak havoc like that!
I wasn't!
I just wanted to pick that strap up...
This is why you shouldn't be playing with toys.
Hey, you don't have to put it like that!
Your summoning permission has been suspended.
Beings are absolutely not to be used for violent purposes.
Violent!? I was just doing that for-
Summoned Beings are not toys for idiots!
Are you frustrated? Why not try proving that you're not an idiot, then?
You might just be able to get your hands on what you want, too.
Sorry, Hazuki...
It's okay...
Hazuki...
So that's what the principal meant.
The prizes are written here.
Free meals for a year!?
Coupons for new video games!?
Sounds pretty awesome.
It also mentions "secret items"...
A Phi-Noin-Ain limited edition strap set?!
The hell, Akihisa?
I want this! This! This! This!
Why on Earth do you want that?
Who cares?
So how do we win those prizes?
This is a map of the school grounds.
We're gonna search for them using this?
Not to brag, but I'm awesome at finding treasure in RPGs.
And these are the test questions.
What?
The answers to the questions on these represent the coordinates for the checkpoints.
We then exchange tickets for prizes at said checkpoints.
That means...
We can't get 'em if we don't answer the questions correctly?!
It's also first-come, first-serve.
If you run into another team,
you have to settle it with a Summoning Battle.
I'm being cockblocked by everything!
Wait a sec... I just need to get on a team with Himeji!
Back to your seats.
I'm gonna announce the teams for the orienteering competition.
Who's in my team...?
Yuuji and Hideyoshi!?
Himeji and Minami are in a team with Voyeur!?
I grouped all of the troublemakers together.
I don't even want to know what you guys have in mind.
Hey, that's not exactly fair!
Hideyoshi is cute, so whatever...
but Yuuji is completely useless!
And you're not?
You have the entire school day to search.
This is no laughing matter!
So take it seriously.
There are three questions in each set, huh?
The answer to the first one is the x coordinate.
Y coordinate for the second.
And z for the third.
Or, in layman's terms, which floor it's on.
Hey, check this out! They're all multiple choice.
This'll be a snap.
You're good at multiple choice?
How can you not know my specialties?
Whatever. Get a load of this!
Man, I almost believed you for a second, too...
For math, I use the Striker Sigma V!
For modern Japanese, I use the Problem Breaker!
And Shining Answer for history!
They're all accurate beyond belief.
Do you always just leave things to chance?
Don't treat them lightly!
Just watch.
Do I have to?
Roar, Striker Sigma V!
All right!
I got the answer!
X coordinate: 652.
Y coordinate: 237.
Z coordinate: 5.
Target locked on! It's over there!
Wow, it's floating.
Go fetch it.
This is weird.
Did they make a mistake writing the problems?
It's your fault, dumbass.
Found it!
Awesome! It's a prize ticket.
Looks like we drew first blood.
Hooray!
It looks like our x and y were correct, at least.
I told you! Striker Sigma V is awesome.
You're more "amazing" for actually believing it works.
We can redeem this for a year's worth of free desserts!
Let's split them between us.
I'll pass.
Are you on a diet?
I'll take this if we manage to find it, though.
A premium ticket to Kisaragi Grand Park?
Oh, I see! You want to go with your boyfriend!
No, he's my husband.
I just felt a chill down my spine.
You have my sympathy.
I can't answer anything besides math!
You're pretty smart, Tsuchiya...
I skipped everything except health.
Ignored
Done!
Wow! Let's go there!
These coordinates...
Female Changing Room
I get to walk into the girls' changing room legally...
Okay! Let's look for the prize!
It's a changing room, sure...
but no one is changing!
Of course not.
We need to tidy this place up...
We're not afraid of the guys seeing it, so it's pretty much a mess...
There's no reason to come here unless it's in use.
What's wrong, Tsuchiya? Are you okay?
I'm fine... This is nothing...
Tsuchiya!
I won't lose here!
Amen...
All right, let me take a look...
at how those idiots are doing.
Pierce the heavens! Problem... BREAKER!
The coordinates point to around here.
Our classroom?
The hell is this?
Not the prize, at least.
Weird... maybe I should try condensing it more?
Just cross out everything.
Um, you found it?
This is yours?
Yes, that basket...
Yoshii, uh...
What's up?
Do you like sweets?
Yeah, I love 'em!
Thank goodness! Actually, I woke up early today to bake some chiffon cakes.
Wow! I didn't know you could bake cakes.
Uh, just a sec!
Nice work, Problem Breaker.
You've struck gold.
You were such a good guy.
I'll never forget you.
Don't act like I'm about to die...!
I think it'd be nice if you could all eat some of it.
Here you go.
There's four of you, so there's not enough to go around...
Three chiffon cakes. Four people.
Only one of us will live to see tomorrow.
Welcome to the first annual...
...power level competition!
We'll decide it with rock paper scissors!
Yeah!
This is a battle of life and death.
Mizuki and Tsuchiya are sure taking their sweet time...
What are they up to?
Dammit! One more problem and my head's gonna explode!
Don't worry.
Miharu?
I'm over here.
I've solved them all!
What are you doing?!
Please look at the answers I slaved over for you, Sissy!
Once I compared the coordinates with the map,
I discovered that the prize was hidden in your bra!
Please prepare to surrender your body and soul to me.
I'd rather die!
Just let go of me!
No way! The coordinates don't lie!
The Ministry of Education agrees! Don't even bother trying to argue!
You've made a mistake!
Then let's make an even bigger mistake together.
Together!
Hell no!
You know, if they have the time to host these damn things,
why don't they use it to accelerate the course material instead?
The coordinates point to here.
This is Yoshii's shoebox!
If someone sees me here...
They're going to think that I'm sneaking a love letter into Yoshii's shoebox!
No, no. I'm just here to get my tickets.
Wait a sec...! Won't it look like I'm stealing someone else's love letter to Yoshii?
No, no. I only want the treasure inside.
I don't care what others think! I can do this!
But wouldn't the contents of Yoshii's shoebox be considered a treasure by some!?
I'll never escape this guilt!
What... What should I do?!
Does it matter?
Sparkle!
Shining Answer!
There it is.
You rock, Hideyoshi!
I don't think I had much to do with it.
Let's see what the prize is.
Failed?
So this isn't what we were looking for.
Dammit! They pulled one over on us!
How could random chance pull one over on us?
I need to change the angle of it...
I don't think that's going to increase the accuracy.
All right.
What do you think?
You actually answered it!
Are you sure it's right, Yuuji?
I don't want to end up somewhere crazy because you screwed it up.
Look who's talking.
According to Yuuji's answer...
it should be here.
Wow! There really is one!
How'd you manage to solve it?
I chose a set with problems that I could solve.
Wow, you're pretty good.
You're at the bottom of the class with regards to test scores, though...
You must've cheated!
Is it really that hard to convince you?
So what's the prize?
Let's see...
A premium couples' ticket to Kisaragi Grand Park?
All couples are invited to participate in our mock-wedding event.
Sounds pretty cool.
You should go with Kirishima.
Don't even say that!
She'd turn that "mock" wedding into the real thing!
Don't show me shit like that!
You two can go!
Really?
Hideyoshi, are you free this Sunday?
The ticket says it's for couples!
No way! Do you hate me!?
I'm a guy.
I've been rejected!
Does God hate me or something?
There's only one thing I can do at this point...
Hideyoshi, I love you!
What the hell!?
These words hold a deeper meaning!
You might not know this, but, in Japan,
there's a legend saying that you'll be blessed if you confess beneath a legendary tree!
That's not a legend.
And there's only one thing "legendary tree" could be referring to at this school...
It refers to the legendary beauty, Hideyoshi Kinoshita.
TL Note: Kinoshita can be also read as "under a tree."
In other words, you'll be blessed if you confess to Hideyoshi!
What, Hideyoshi!?
Really? If that's true, we can all confess to Hideyoshi without fear of being persecuted!
This is wrong on so many levels that I don't even know where to begin.
I love you, Hideyoshi!
Snap out of it!
Well, looks like it's not gonna work out for us after all.
This is pretty unfair for idiots like us.
There aren't many prizes left.
I wonder what the secret items are.
The Phi straps are still available!
You still haven't given up?
The only problems left are pretty fucking hard.
Or are you just gonna walk around randomly?
Randomly...
That's right! I'll just answer all of them!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to fill in every possible coordinate.
All of them?
There might be a prize at places where the x and y axes intersect!
What about the floor?
We'll just have to check all of them!
That's a lot of places to look through!
Do you know long this would take...?
This game is based around searching high and low.
That's crazy talk...
I see. That's pretty clever.
No harm in trying. Not like we can solve the problems anyway!
We'll show them how idiots do things!
Yuuji...
I'll go to the fourth floor.
Akihisa, you go to the third.
Hideyoshi, you go to the second.
Okay.
Roger that.
The janitor's closet!
Nothing.
Empty.
Female changing room
Nothing.
None.
Occupied...
The lockers.
Nothing.
None.
A dog?
The changing rooms!
Trash cans.
Nothing.
None.
W-Why?!
The women's bathroom!
Nothing.
None.
There's somebody in here.
The fish tank.
Nothing.
None.
Ouch!
Once again!
Nothing.
None.
Let me go...
One more time!
I'm using it.
There's someone here.
Thank god it's empty...
Or not!
Hi.
Dammit, we didn't find shit.
There's nowhere left to look.
No, there's one place left!
There's nowhere you could hide stuff there, though.
No way...
No one's found the strap yet.
It has to be hidden somewhere.
Found it!
I knew it!
Hideyoshi, you don't need to answer problems to-
Hmm? I found this place after solving all of the questions.
You're...
Sister! Why are you here?
The rules say that we can use a Summoning Battle to take that ticket by force.
Don't tell me...
Permitted.
Summon!
Summon.
This isn't good, Akihisa.
They're way too strong for us.
I didn't think we'd have to go up against them...
Shit... What should we do?
We're not going to go easy on you.
Ready to get your asses kicked?
See ya later.
What?
Time's up.
That means...
You're right.
Yup.
Kisaragi Grand Park
mascot strap set exchange ticket
Yippee!
Wow, look at these! There's three in a set, too!
That's great.
Hazuki is gonna love this.
What is this?
Are these the secret items?
I wonder what these do.
There's a manual.
Iron Bracelets. The activation phrase is "Awaken".
So...
What do they do?
Let's try it out.
Awaken!
This is...
No way...
Summon!
Wow!
We can summon our Beings without a teacher's permission!
The range is kind of limited, but this is still pretty sweet!
Why am I the only one whose clothes got torn?
Akihisa, is yours okay?
Uh, yeah.
That means that only dumbasses can use these.
Dumbass
What do you mean by that?!
You're a dumbass too!
Then you're a super dumbass.
Ultimate
What?
Fine, the ultimate dumbass.
What?!
The dumbass to rule all dumbasses.
What do you mean by that?!
I see.
They're still getting there.
But...
Idiots are like scissors - it's all about how you use them.
Every night turns to dawn, after all.
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Question six:
Please list the different types of medleys.
Anisong medley, oldies medley, pigeon cookies!
I like pigeon cookies myself.
Next episode: Me and Pool and Swimsuit Paradise and.
This will be on the test.