When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Last episode!
Due to the whimsical superintendent's whimsical whim,
the Butler Battle Tournament starts at Hakuou Academy.
Nonohara-san, your move takes
a little too much time to get going.
Great fights one after another.
And after a tremendous battle, the Sanzenin butler, Ayasaki Hayate wins the first round, as well!
It's an incredible battle aura.
What kind of ultimate move is he getting ready?
It's coming, Hayate!
That's right; I don't have the time to wimp out.
I have to look good in front of Milady.
Winner, Sanzenin butler, Ayasaki Hayate!
Um, I didn't do anything...
I see, you used your chi to rip his clothes up.
Good job, Hayate!
End of summary.
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet starts!
Oh, Klaus-san. What are you doing with that strange mask on?
You're the only person who noticed, Maria.
I hear a true master can win without laying a finger on the opponent.
Hayate, I never thought you had reached that level.
You flatter me.
The opponent self-destructed in that last match.
Here you go, Milady.
Thank you.
Hayate, doing this reminds us of some old memories, doesn't it?
Reminds us of what?
Hey, you haven't forgotten, have you?
That day.
So many months have passed since then.
Hayate, thank you for your hard work.
Here, you drink this.
Milady.
Since I do need you to win the tournament.
Yes.
That's Himuro-san.
Don't make a big fuss because he fits the handsome mold.
Hayate's a lot cooler.
Please...
Sir, this is far enough.
So Himuro-san's in this tournament, as well.
Okay, I will observe your ultimate attack.
Let's get this going.
The three men in black from Saginomiya versus Oukouchi's Saeki Himuro!
Three against one?
How dirty!
Don't be rude! Us men in black of Saginomiya are...
...united three as one!
Body and soul.
Shou*** Tai!
Very interesting.
Fight!
Then, here I go.
Bonjour?
U-Um, where's the Butler Battle Tournament's hall?
I am starting to feel I was yet again unable to see the moment of truth.
W-Winner, Saeki Himuro!
Sh-She's always lost...
...so we wanted the 100 credits...
...since she can't make it to school often enough.
Himuro!
Good work.
Hurry and win the battle for me!
I'm counting on you for the bonus, Sir Taiga.
W-We didn't get to see the ultimate move at all.
Yeah...
I can't afford to lose.
However, despite his high spirits...
Fight!
Kame**me...
I give up.
Winner, Ayasaki-kun!
Eh?!
Wh-Why?
Yes, the extra butlers all feared him so much from his victory in the first round that they all forfeited one after another.
The tournament kept progressing,
And the tournament's best four has been chosen.
Semi-final, first match!
The Hanabishi family! Part-time butler, Hinagiku Katsura!
The Asakaze family! Part-time butler, Kashiwagi!
My butler...
...ran away!
R-Risa-chin...
Why?
I bet she can't pay any more cash.
W-Winner, my sister!
First one to the final!
Hina, fight for me, too.
Risa.
Here's a little something from me.
What? This is a bill from the butler you hired!
I bought the Ikki***sen DVD wanting to see the main character that never comes out,
and I went over my credit limit.
You have to pay it yourself!
Is it really all right that I'm left in the best four?
It is God's will.
What? Can you even hear others speaking in their head?
The Sanzenin family butler! Hayate Ayasaki!
They're calling for you.
Yes!
The Oukouchi family butler! Himuro Saeki!
Himuro-san, why did you enter this tournament?
Why?
Because I...
...love money!
Hayate!
That guy...
He's pretty good.
Seems so.
As expected from Himuro-san.
I got dragged into his pace.
B-But...
...it finally feels like a battle!
Sir Taiga?
I see.
Attacked by a fearful beast?
I-I'm sorry. I went to buy stuff for you for your hard work but...
Yes, I'll be right there.
Hayate-kun, we'll save this for another time.
What?
Oh what the heck!
Winner, Ayasaki Hayate!
A-Again?
He got scared off by Hayate.
R-Right, since I won this match...
...I-I'm up against Hinagiku-san next.
This is going to be difficult.
Is he supposed to rejoice at the victory?
Moving on to the final.
Nurarihyon! = Goblin!
Nurarihyon!
Eee?
Eee? = Ehh?
Era kokyuu shite mo ii desuka?
Era kokyuu shite mo ii desuka? = May I breathe through my gills?
Hanabishi family, part time butler! Katsura Hinagiku!
Here!
Sanzenin family butler! Ayasaki Hayate!
H-Here!
Welcome to the final, both of you.
Those were very brave battles you fought.
I don't remember much of a fight.
Now, get ready for your last battle.
The winner of the match receives the right to fight Shion as the representative of the students.
Any objections?
No.
No, not really.
To honor you two, I will now announce the new school anthem.
It's a masterpiece I made myself, staying up all night.
A new school anthem?
This is a good chance, Hayate-kun.
You should learn how fearful that superintendent is.
I'm in this tournament to beat her.
Hinagiku-san.
Suginami no chi wo shihai suru
It rules the city of Suginami
Shiroki manabiya
The white academic building
Waga bokou
My school
Muneno enjin hi wo tsukete
Get the engine in your heart to work.
Hakuou!
Rokumega shock. Shuushokuritsu 120%
6MB shock, 120% employment rate!
Hakuou Gakuin.
Hakuou Academy!
Ochitsuke! Ochitsuite benkyou surunda!
Calm down! You must calm down and study!
Looks like everyone's fascinated by its majesty.
Hakuou!
Kuzuha-sama.
Cornelia wana.
Cornelia's trap.
See?
Yes, I agree we must defeat her.
Hakuou!
Haukou!
If we keep letting her act as she wants, then our school's doomed.
Rokumega mainichi koushin.
6MB marching down every day.
Hakuou Gakuin!
Hakuou Academy!
Superintendent!
I will definitely win against her!
But I will reject the prize, of course!
Is that fine with you, Miki-chan?
I-It's fine.
We are student council members.
We can't possibly actively skip classes.
You always are though.
A hundred credits?
I feel bad for the students who are diligently taking classes.
This school isn't your toy.
Students! I will defeat the superintendent!
And I will bring revolution to this school!
Please give me the power to make revolution in this school!
It's as you hear, Hayate-kun.
But a fight is a fight.
What should I do? She's serious.
I'm on the hot seat.
Absolutely trapped by fate.
Okay, ready?
Final round match!
Hinagiku Katsura versus Hayate Ayasaki!
Super Battle Time!
Here I come!
P-Please stop, Hinagiku-san!
There is no reason for us to fight!
You're not holding back because I'm a girl, are you?
Completely like an away game.
Hayate-kun, it's cowardly of you to keep running away.
Fight fair and square!
Hayate! Straighten yourself out!
Why are you so earnest?
Hurting others through physical means isn't all there is to being a butler.
Hayate, you of all people should know that.
Milady...
Yes.
Hayate-kun! Fight!
I'm sorry, Hinagiku-san.
I understand that you're serious about protecting the school from the Superintendent.
But I have something I must protect, too.
W-Winner, Ayasaki Hayate!
Um, Hinagiku-san.
Pervert.
But I guess a defeat is a defeat.
I was getting carried away, too.
I have more to learn.
Ayasaki Hayate-kun. As regretful as it is,
I entrust Hakuou Academy's future to you.
Is that all right with you all?
Um, please don't leave something that big in my hands.
He is our, as students, representative.
Now, accept our challenge!
Superintendent's butler, Kuresato Shion!
Wait!
Show them what you have.
Yes, Ma'am.
Let's get this started, shall we?
Don't worry, Hayate-kun. You can win.
Hinagiku-san, stop advancing the story on your own.
Hayate.
Well... you know...
I'm very happy with your fights so far, but...
I would love to see you knock out the opponent!
Looks like I can't back out now.
I will do this!
Yes, that's the spirit, Hayate!
For the school's future!
Fight!
I must be careful not to get caught up in that strange move.
It's useless, Ayasaki-kun.
Crap!
My Poetic World sends its melody directly to the brain.
You can't leave this zone anymore.
Wh-What's wrong, Ayasaki-kun?
That's...
Hayate-kun, go after her legs!
Get her off her footing!
The effect should wear off if she's distracted!
Hinagiku-san?
I won't let you!
O-Oh no! My secret...
Um, you're...
D-Don't say it!
Allow me to explain.
Superintendent's butler, Kuresato Shion is a female student in the junior high.
When her secret boots come off, she can't maintain her figure and reverts to child form.
She's become a completely different character!
I'm already an adult!
I'm not a little kid!
I-I'm a cool adult who matches Kuzuha-sama!
Shion, stop it now.
You lose.
Kuzuha-sama.
You're not so bad being small.
We'll step away for today and confirm our love.
Yes.
Um...
You seem like a toy I can play with a lot.
Y-You better remember this! I will come back for you!
SFX: Silence~
Um...
How do I deal with this?
That's how the Butler Battle Tournament ended.
There!
I said it ended.
Hey, it's a jellyfish.
I wonder if the jellyfish is edible.
So, what happened to the prize, the hundred credits?
She did give it to me.
That superintendent doesn't lie, after all.
Then...
No, we returned it.
He wasted my generosity,
since I often make him skip school with me.
Was she worried about Hayate-kun's attendance?
Thank you for your thoughts.
But I will make sure to manage school between work.
Go!
Even the battle tournament winner can't stand in a game.
I will win the next match!
Sure, bring it on.
Ready?
Shion, what do you think?
About that boy, Ayasaki.
"What"? Well...
That boy... He unexpectedly...
...turns me on.
Eh?
I've made up my mind.
I don't care about battle tournaments.
Come! League of Mysterious Dark Butlers!
We will bring Ayasaki Hayate to us no matter what it takes!
What is this League of Mysterious Dark Butlers?
And what will happen to Hayate?
Next time, we'll fight against the Gun**m freak's trivia.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Good night through good morning.
I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
It's starting to turn out like a shounen manga.
Will you be fighting against freaks every week from now on?
No, next week will be a normal story.
Looks like the anime staff is going through lots of brainstorming.
It's hard to go original.
You're right, Milady.
Don't miss the staff's futile resistance.
Basara!
Sir, my mother suggested I have a marriage meeting.
That's nice.
Oh, Mom? Get the arrangements moving at once.
Yes, by any means.
What? Saki!
Therefore, next Sunday, I will be having my meeting.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Marriage Meeting.
Did you know?
The hottest spice in the world is Red Savina Habanero.