Rin.
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Year 2
Japanese
Hey!
Year 2
Japanese
You're ganging up to make
her do things she doesn't like?!
You guys suck!
You really suck!
What's your problem, Tohsaka?
This is none of your business.
Well then...
Go ahead and do the same thing to me.
Then it'll be my business, right?
Hey.
Boring!
Here.
Year 2
Japanese
You infused too much mana at once.
Keep your mind calm.
In order to control mana,
you must first control your mind.
Lose control, and the mana will rebound back to your body.
Too much power in the wrong form will harm not only you, but those around you as well.
Strive to consistently maintain the proper flow.
That is the Tohsaka family precept.
It means to be in control and elegant at all times.
Kotone, you shouldn't keep
quiet when they do that stuff.
You need to get mad if they're in the wrong.
Rin-chan, you're amazing.
You always speak your mind.
That's not true.
I think it's normal and natural...
Yes.
It's natural.
Hold out your hands.
Father, teach me more!
How do I make something like this?
Let's see.
It might be too hard for you right now.
But I'm sure you'll be able to make it
eventually if you work hard every day.
You're the daughter of the Tohsaka family, after all.
Hey, Rin-chan.
Can you show me how to do this part?
Of course. Where?
Me, too!
Me, too.
This was on page 23 in the textbook.
You just did the math wrong here.
As for this question...
Look, it's just like this example.
Kotone.
Sit down. I'll help everybody one by one.
Okay!
Do I have to go live with the Zenjou?
Once the Holy Grail War begins,
Fuyuki City will no longer be safe.
Father, I want to help you win the Grail War.
Rin, you mustn't cause your father trouble.
Are we in the way?
That's not it.
This time, I'll need to make extra
preparations to battle under perfect conditions.
Which include securing the
safety of you and your mother.
And for that, it's better if both of you leave Fuyuki City.
I'm sure there's something I can do to help!
That's right.
I just haven't learned how to yet.
So all I need to do is study on my own.
I-I don't understand at all...
What is this?!
Geez!
Du, wer die Tür geöffnet hat, wird Freunde sein.
I have to close it.
Für die Aussage nimm meine Hand.
Wir werden in meinem Zimmer treffen.
Sind deine Arme klein, groß, schlank, steif?
It won't move!
Rin!
Jeder ist gleich.
Are you all right?
It's still too soon for you to read this book.
Some things in this world contain their own mana.
This is called a mana compass.
Normally, it doesn't indicate anything.
But if there are mana traces in the area...
Rin, try generating mana in this.
Okay.
...it does that.
And with that book...
Anything that causes a reaction like that is beyond your ability, so be careful.
I'll give this to you.
As an early birthday present.
Th-Thank you, Father!
Once the Holy Grail War ends,
we'll try some real Jewel Magic.
Then, strange occurrences began occurring.
Study period again, apparently.
Study Period
The morning news was also
talking about the kidnappings.
Serial
Kidnappings
News
In Fuyuki City, the sudden disappearances of children...
The teachers have been in a meeting all day.
In a
meeting
q
Staff Room
They said we won't have fifth period today!
Notice:
Afternoon Classes Canceled
Beware of
Suspicious-looking People!!
School News
All right!
But they said we should stay at home.
Why?
Serial
Kidnappings
News
Another kidnapping...
They said only children had been kidnapped.
Hey, did you hear?
I hear the body isn't inside the coffin.
That's... horrible.
It definitely happened in Fuyuki, right?
U-Um, I'm Kotone-chan's classmate, Tohsaka...
The person you are calling is not home.
Please leave your message after the beep.
Please be safe...
Kotone.
This is Fuyuki at night...
It's completely different from during the day.
It's really scary.
What's this?
I've never seen it react like this.
Does that mean there are mana traces all over the place?
I have to find Kotone!
Out with a kid this late?
What was that?
Oh no!
Phew.
They'd take me home if they found me.
Come on, keep walking.
Two of them?
He got another kid.
Why?
Wait. Why am I hiding?
I can't accomplish anything at this rate!
No one's here?
H-Hey!
Kotone?!
Kotone! Kotone!
Did they do something to her?
What should I do?
Something...
Huh? Are you lost?
No... Um...
You've come at the right time.
We're just about to start a party.
But we still don't have enough people.
Wanna help too?
Come on. The more, the merrier, right?
No!
What was that?
Don't you run away.
He's using that bracelet on them?!
Ow!
I have to destroy it!
Oh, so you're gonna help me, after all.
Huh? What's this?
You infused too much mana at once.
This is nothing!
Kotone!
Rin-chan...
Huh? Where am I?
There's no time to cry! Run!
Hey! Wait!
Man...
I wonder if Mister'll be mad about this.
Huh?
Where's Rin-chan?
What a relief...
I should head back.
I did it, Father.
What?
Anything that causes a reaction like that is beyond your ability, so be careful.
I can't believe Rin went to Fuyuki...
Rin!
Rin...
Rin-chan's fine.
She's just sleeping.
Kariya-kun?
What? What's happening here?
What are you doing here?
Your face...
This is the magic of the Matou family.
You offer your flesh, and your life is slowly devoured.
Our sorcery comes at this price.
But Sakura-chan is fine.
I'll definitely save her before this happens to her.
Zouken only desires the Grail.
He promised to release Sakura-chan if I win it for him.
The Grail, you said?!
Yeah, don't worry.
My Servant is the strongest.
It won't lose to anyone.
Right now, even hope causes
Sakura-chan nothing but pain.
So pray for me in her stead.
For my victory...
And for Sakura-chan's future.
Kariya-kun, you...
I'm sure the day will come when we
can all play in this park like we used to.
And Rin-chan and Sakura-chan will go back to being sisters.
So, Aoi-san.
You don't need to cry anymore.
Kariya-kun, do you plan to die?
After killing Tokiomi...
Mother?
Rin!
I was so worried!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
Kirei-sama, are you certain you wish to leave
Tohsaka Tokiomi's wife and daughter like this?
It's fine.
Continue monitoring Berserker's Master.
Understood.
It wasn't much, but I did manage to do something.
But as for whether I'm independent yet, I passed out halfway through, so...
I have a long way to go.
But that's just for now.
I have plenty of time, after all.
Someday, I'll fight as a Tohsaka Mage.
So that I'll always be ready, I'll work really hard and uphold my father's teachings.
And when the time comes,
I'll just do the best I can, elegantly.
Episode 10
Rin's Adventure
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
A king without greed is even worse than a figurehead!
Of what worth is a king who
fails to protect the powerless?
We have nothing to lose.
A Reality Marble?!
I shall kill you myself.
Wasn't your goal supposed to be world conquest—
Next Episode
Grail Dialogue