C'mon. It's an easy
question. So answer it.
What the hell is
it you want to do?
I want to become a
member of the Scouts,
and slaughter every
Titan that crosses my path.
Huh. Well played.
Alright, then. I'll
take responsibility for him.
Let the higher-ups
know what's going on.
Not that I implicitly
trust him, of course.
It's more a matter of me trusting myself
to deal with him. Kill him, if I have to.
The big wigs aren't
likely to raise a stink.
My record more than speaks
for itself, I'm pretty sure.
Good news, Jaeger.
You're now officially
a member of the Scouts.
Hey.
You think it's true?
There's a Titan
fighting on our side now?
When did you start
believing everything you heard?
More likely the
recapture plan failed.
And now refugees from Wall Rose
are going to start flooding in here.
And once those people swarm us, our
supplies'll run out in a matter of days.
Wait. So if the Wall Rose people
really do have a Titan with them,
you don't think they'd be crazy
enough to bring him in here, do you?
Hey. Have you
heard the good news?
The military
has a Titan on the team!
Can you
believe it? Who knows?
We might even be
able to retake Wall Maria!
Finally,
humanity has a Savior!
Saviour, huh?
Since the dawn of history,
commoners have always been a rash lot.
These rumors get any more out of
control, we'll have a revolt on our hands.
Not today. This
so-called "Savior"?
We'll make an
example out of him.
I'll be damned if he's
allowed to join the Survey Corp.
Form ranks!
All hail to the Premier!
Damn, hot day.
Commander Pyxis.
You're the C.O. of
the Garrison Regiment.
And I'm the Commanding Officer
of the Survey Corp and the Scouts.
Some people might disapprove
of our meeting like this.
Ha! You're as straight-
laced as your reputation.
Nothing untoward here. We just coincidentally
bumped into one another while out for a morning stroll.
Protocol doesn't prevent us from
chatting under the circumstances.
You are aware the Military Police plan
to take custody of Eren Jaeger, I presume.
Yes. I received
word yesterday.
They plan to hold
a deliberation on the matter.
Hm. The decision has
been left to Premier Zachary.
Whether Cadet Jaeger's future lies with the
Scouts, or in the hands of the Military Police.
Zachary? You mean
Premier Dhalis Zachary?
The Military Police.
The Garrison Regiment.
And the Scouts.
All three fall
under his jurisdiction.
His decision will be
based entirely on one factor:
Is Eren Jaeger's existence a
benefit or a handicap to our survival?
If deemed
detrimental, Jaeger will be
executed
without a thought.
Right then
and there, if need be.
I, for one, do
not want to see him die.
However, many in the Garrison
Regiment, I'm sad to say,
are fearful of Eren's unique
ability. My hands are tied.
The most I can do is avoid
agreeing with the M.P.'s.
Do the odds favor you?
No, they don't.
And yet, we do have
a proposal prepared.
Whether it
will work or not,
all depends on
how the debate unfolds.
You mean, you're
going to play it by ear?
Our job is reconnaissance
beyond the walls.
Playing things by
ear is all we ever do.
Ha!
You're not so uptight
after all, it would seem.
Thank you for the pleasant
conversation. And good luck, Commander!
A debate over Eren?
What for?
I'm not really sure, but, it might
be about what they plan to do with him.
And what does that mean?
It means...
they may not let him live.
Cadet Mikasa Ackerman. And
Cadet Armin Arlelt. Hop to!
Sir!
You're ordered to attend and act
as witnesses at today's deliberation.
'Scuse me. I gotta pee.
No, you just went.
Then can I have some water?
Hey!
You're not getting a
thing, got it? Damn monster.
Monster. I guess he's
not too far off the mark there.
Frightened
of me or not, though,
I don't deserve this.
Except how
can I blame him?
I don't even
understand what's going on.
On the bright side, at least these
guards haven't tried to kill me yet.
When I think back,
they weren't afraid of me.
Even after
everything they'd seen.
I wonder what
they're doing now.
And all the others.
I wonder what happened to them.
Just hang on
a little longer, Eren.
We'll keep trying
to sort all this out.
I've been
in here so long.
What's been happening
outside of these bars?
I'm... I'm not going to spend
the rest of my life like this, am I?
So then, you're Eren?
Are you well?
How're things?
I'm really sorry
you've been waiting so long.
But here's your
chance to finally get out.
Uh.
One thing. You'll have to
put these on for me, okay?
My name is Zoe Hange.
I'm a section
commander for the Scouts.
This is a fellow
commander in the Scouts,
Miche Zacharius.
Uh...
Oh. Don't mind him. He makes a habit
of giving new people a thorough sniff.
Tends to laugh
through his nose a bit.
But I don't think
he intends it to be derisive.
Quirks aside, he is
a skilled section commander.
Oh, poo! Sorry. I've just been prattling
on with the small talk, and now we're here!
Well,
I'm sure it's fine.
It's probably better
if I don't explain, anyway.
Hey! Hold on!
It might seem
callous, but remember...
we've all put our
faith in you, Eren.
Best of luck!
Wait!
A courthouse?
I was in the basement
of a courthouse this whole time?
All right. Move it!
On your knees. Now!
Why're all of these
people here, just staring at me?
Somebody gonna explain
what the hell's going on?
My friends.
All right. Shall we begin?
Your name is Eren
Jaeger.
And as a soldier, you have sworn to give
up your life when called to,
for the good of
the people. Is that correct?
Yes.
As an enlisted soldier during a time of war, military
doctrine demands your tribunal be held as a court-martial.
As Commander of our armed forces,
this matter is left to my discretion.
Thus, I will decide
whether you live or you die.
I knew it!
Any objections?
No, sir.
Your astuteness is
appreciated. Let us proceed.
As expected, covering up your
existence has proven quite fruitless.
And unless we publicly disclose your
existence one way or another,
we risk the outbreak of widespread
civil unrest.
A choice must be made.
And the regiment that takes custody
of you will determine your fate.
The Military Police...
or
the Scout Regiment?
To begin. The Military Police
will now present their case.
Thank you.
My name is Nile Dawk.
I am Commander
of the Military Police.
Our recommendation, following a thorough
examination of his physiology,
subject Eren Jaeger should be disposed
of immediately.
We acknowledge that Jaeger's ability played a
part in turning back the latest Titan incursion.
However, as has been stated, his mere existence
is creating a swell of rebellious sentiment.
For the greater good, after we have gathered
all the information that we can from him,
we would see him made a
fallen warrior of humanity.
Unacceptable!
This verminous fiend has
defiled the mighty Wall...
Another deranged
Wall Cultist.
Five years ago,
everyone ignored them.
Now they've
actually got some clout.
And now I'd like to hear the
Scout Regiment's proposed plan.
Yes, sir.
As the commander
of the Survey Corp,
I, Erwin Smith,
propose the following:
Let Eren join our
ranks.
Reinstate him as a full member of the Scouts, and we
will utilize his Titan ability to retake Wall Maria.
That is all.
Hm? Is that it?
Yes. With
his assistance, sir,
I'm certain we
can reclaim Wall Maria.
Ergo, I believe our top
priority is perfectly clear.
Quite bold. Assuming you were given clearance,
where do you plan to launch this operation from?
Commander Pyxis.
The wall in Trost District has been
completely sealed, is that correct?
Yes. I doubt its
gate will ever open again.
We'll depart from
Calaneth District, to the east.
From there, we'll
make for Shiganshina.
A new route can be
establish as we proceed.
But that's ridiculous! Our time and money
would be better spent sealing up all the gates!
They're the only parts of the Wall
that the Colossal Titan can break, right?
Let's reinforce the blasted things
and wash our hands of the entire affair!
Shut your mouth,
you spineless merchant dog!
With a Titan on our side, we
can finally return to Wall Maria!
We can't afford any more of your childish
antics, or your delusions of grandeur!
Squealing louder
won't help your case, pig.
While we're
bolstering our defenses,
do you think the Titans
are going to stand idly by?
And when you say "we can't afford," do you speak
for anyone other than your fat merchant friends?
Do you pigs even
realize that most of our people
are struggling just to survive
off what little land we have left?
I'm simply saying that sealing the gates
is the only guaranteed protection we've got!
Hold your tongue, you
vile, belligerent heretic!
Are you really suggesting that we lowly humans
meddle with Wall Rose, a gift to us from on high?
The Wall is a miracle.
And its divinity
transcends human comprehension.
Don't you understand?
It's that cult's fault. They're the ones
who delayed the garrison's arming of the Walls.
That shows you the sick amount of support and
power they've got. I don't trust them at all.
...to pieces!
Such sacrilege!
Oh, you're
insane. Shut yer trap!
How dare you!
Order! I ask
that you save your personal
sentiments for
a more appropriate venue.
Now then Mr. Jaeger,
I have a question for you.
As a soldier, you have made a solemn
pledge to answer humanity's call.
Can you still serve
by controlling your ability?
Yes! I will, sir!
Oh? Is that so?
But this report from the Battle
for Trost contradicts that statement.
Just after transforming,
it seems you made an attempt
to crush Mikasa Ackerman.
He doesn't
even remember.
He completely
lost control.
What'd you expect? You want
me to lie in the report?
Glossing over that important fact could
potentially spell disaster for us all.
And who is
this Mikasa Ackerman?
Me! That would be me, sir.
Alright, then. Is it true that Eren Jaeger
assaulted you while he was in Titan form?
Answer the Premier honestly.
Eren's future depends on it.
Yes. All of that's true.
I knew it! He's
a wolf in sheep's clothing!
I... I tried
to kill Mikasa?
What's happening to me?
However, he also
saved my life twice before.
And in each circumstance he
was using his Titan ability.
The first:
shortly after Trost fell.
I was nearly
killed by a Titan.
But then Eren came.
He stepped
in and protected me.
The second
time: he transformed to
shield Armin
and me from cannon fire.
I implore you to take these
facts into consideration.
Objection!
I have reason to believe that personal
feelings play a large part in her testimony.
Let the record show that Mikasa
Ackerman was orphaned at a young age
and was subsequently taken
in by the Jaeger family.
What's more, our own internal
investigation into this matter
led to a most
shocking discovery.
Eren Jaeger
and Mikasa Ackerman,
at the tender age of nine, dealt with three
adult kidnappers by stabbing all of them to death.
Granted, this
was done in self-defense.
All the same, one cannot help but
question the violent nature of the act.
Knowing all of this,
should we really invest in him?
Money, manpower. Perhaps
the very fate of us all?
Maybe he's a Titan that snuck in here after
taking the form of some little child he ate?
Maybe she's one! I bet
she's not human either!
Yeah, you're right!
Dissect her too,
just to be safe!
Now hold on a second! Maybe I'm a monster
that you want dead, but you leave her out of this!
She's innocent!
Like we'd trust you!
It's the truth!
She must be
one if you protect her!
Stop it!
You're wrong.
About it all.
But you're so intent
on pushing selfish agendas,
you're blind to
what's in front of you.
Wait. What do you mean?
What does it even matter?
What am I saying?
None of you have
even seen a Titan,
so why're you so afraid, huh?
Maybe I should
just keep quiet.
No. If
they wanna kill me,
I'll let them
know exactly what I think.
There's no sense in having power if
you're not going to use it to fight!
If you're too scared
to fight for your lives, fine.
Let me do it!
You... You're all cowards!
What?
Just shut up. And put
all your faith in me!
Take aim, dammit!
Right! Yes, sir!
Huh?
Mikasa, wait!
You know, personally,
I think nothing
instills discipline like pain.
You don't need a
good "talking-to".
What you're in need of,
boy, is to be taught a lesson.
And you happen to be
in perfect kicking position.
N-Now hold on, Levi!
What is it?
It's dangerous.
What if he gets
angry? Turns into a Titan?
Don't be silly.
After all, you guys just want
to dissect him, don't you?
During the time that
he was transformed,
they say that Jaeger was able to kill twenty
Titans before he finally ran out of strength.
As an enemy, his intelligence
makes him all the more dangerous.
But I could still take
him down without a problem.
How many of
you can say the same?
Before you torment
the beast, you'd better think.
Can you
actually kill him?
Sir.
I have a proposition.
Proceed.
There's still too
much we don't know.
And no doubt, his danger
will be ever present.
As such, I suggest this:
Eren Jaeger will be placed
under Captain Levi's supervision.
And we'll conduct a recon
mission outside of the wall.
Jaeger will join
you in this excursion?
Yes, sir. Then you can look upon
the mission's results yourself.
And if he successfully
controls his ability...
Eren will have proven
his value to mankind.
Eren Jaeger will
be closely supervised?
And if he should lose control?
I can definitely
kill him, if it comes to that.
The only downside is, there's
absolutely no middle ground.
Hm. Then I
have made my choice.
Well that went
better than I expected.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
Yeah? Describe it to me!
Huh?
Sorry for all that.
But the theatrics did get
you placed in our custody.
No, I understand.
I can assure
you the pain was worth it.
We played our trump
card at the perfect time.
You have my utmost respect.
Eren, I'm glad that
you're on our team.
Uh? Me, too!
Glad to be here, sir!
So, Eren.
Sir?
You don't resent
me now, do you?
N... No. I can see that what
you did was necessary, sir.
Good. Then you understand.
Still, don't you
think you went too far?
I mean, you
knocked his tooth out!
Neat, huh?
You picked
it up? How disgusting.
This is a precious
sample I'll have you know!
Hey, just be glad people
like that aren't dissecting you.
Don't you dare
to compare me with them.
I would never
even dream of killing him.
Hey, Eren. Let me take a look
inside that mouth of yours!
Your tooth...
it grew back.
After achieving his long-held dream
of joining the elite Scout Regiment,
Eren finds the vaunted Scouts are an
eccentric band of soldiers and searchers.
A haven for oddballs,
misfits and iconoclasts.