Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
Korokun
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Rika-chama
Tressflin
Saoen
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
ThaEagle
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
That's a sound that would wake even the dead.
Thanks for the food!
How is it?
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Absolutely.  It's delicious.
Yeah.
Well... I guess it's all right.
Thank goodness!
This is a dish native to my hometown.
This miso stuff, it seems to be made the same way as soy?
That's right!
I brought a little of my mother's homemade miso with me.
There's plenty more for seconds, so please eat up!
To Treize?
Right.  The restocking notification finally arrived.
Kureha-chan and I will go to pick them up.
We're running low on ammunitions, medicines, various everyday needs, and other supplies, right?
With this, we'll finally be able to rest easy.
What about you, Noel?
You'll be going to Carl-san's workshop, right?
Yeah.
Got it.
Kanata!
Huh?
We'll be working intensively on your trumpet playing this afternoon!
Really?
You mean it?
Hm?
Bro'shom food.
Oh, dear.  You're just so improper.
If your father saw you like this, he'd cry!
Hmph.
Wike I care abouh somehing wike tha.
Here, enjoy a snack with your tea.
Huh?
Fortune cookies, huh?
You still dislike them, don't you?
It's isn't as though it's the children's fault, you know?
Hmph.
To use superstitions to extort money — that sort of thing is the same no matter where you go.
Oh, please.  That isn't true.
These are truly exquisite.
Oh, my?
But she really seems like she's adapted to everything quite well, doesn't she?  Kana-chan, that is.
Her consistent hardworking attitude is cute.
You think so?
I'll admit she's enthusiastic and earnest, but not all things are so simple that those qualities are enough to get by.
Hm?
What're you looking at me like that for?
It's a secret~!
Wh—
What's with that?  You're so frustrating.
All right then, we'll see you later.
I think we may be late coming back.
Right.
Be safe.
Don't you go causing trouble for Rio-senpai!
Right!
Departing.
Have a safe trip!
I don't expect you to get this far yet, but controlling your notes on even just the mouthpiece is fundamental.
You try it.
R-Right.
What do you think?  Of the lifestyle here at the base?
It's fun!
That's so like you, to be so assertive.
That happy-go-lucky outlook of yours... it makes me a little jealous.
Come to think of it,
why did you join the military in the first place?
That's because...
Um... I heard you could learn to play an instrument here for free...
Ah!  But I, uh... a-also understand the importance of protecting the country!
It doesn't matter to me.
Whether someone joins for money or whatever, it doesn't matter.
Those who have a clear goal when joining last longer than those who just happen to find themselves here.
Um...
You're very kind.
Then... what about you, Rio-senpai?
I...
Well, actually it was for about the exact opposite of you, I suppose.
But nowadays, that's rare.
Especially because you don't really hear brass instruments outside of the military.
I've heard one... in the past.
Huh?
Someone like you, senpai...
Kanata?
The sounds of the skies...
What's wrong...?!
Hang on!
Keep it together, Kanata!
Answer me!
No, stop!
Shh, please, just stay still.
It's hot.
It's hot, Momma.
Are you hot?
I can tell... but you'll be fine.
You'll be fine.
Mo...
Momma...
What's the matter?  Kanata?
Kanata!
Snow... I want to eat snow.
What?
I got it.  Wait just a second!
Snow... snow...
Snow, where is it...?
There's no way we have something like that here!
Calm down.
Of course, medicine!
No, that's supposed to be the last resort!
Medicine, medicine...!
Medicine... medicine...!
Got it!
Huh?
We're running low on a lot of things, right?
Damn those idiots in the supply corps!
Damn it.
What should I...
What should I do...
Damn it!!
U-Um... is there something you need?
Could it be that the children have caused you trouble again...?
I apologize for my rudeness up til now!
So... that is... please save her.
Drink up.
There you go.
Her fever is a little on the high side, but with this, I think she should be okay.
It's not some sort of terrible illness, is it?
I think it's probably three-day fever.
"Three-day fever"?!
Isn't that something only children get?
Even adults can suffer from it if they're heavily taxed.
There are many children who get it right after we take them in.
The more normal the child seems, the worse the outbreak of the fever is.
She was probably fighting it off the whole time, I'm sure.
T-Then, will she get better?
For her to be like this is just...
I think she should be just fine.
Thank goodness.
Than... ks...
Um...
My name is Yumina.
Ah!
These have been infused with medicinal herbs.  Wait a little while, then have her drink some.
This...
I'm sorry about all this.
Have no worries.
It is our pleasure and our duty to assist the people of this city.
And so, may there be countless blessings upon you all.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Ow...
I-I'm sorry!
How are you feeling?
I apologize.
I'm like miso.
Huh?  The stuff from this morning?
Not like that.  Miso dregs are...
When you make miso soup, you strain it and so some leftover beans and the like will be left — the dregs.
Leftovers, a deadweight, and such...
I've always been like that ever since I was a child...
That's why—!
I promised myself this time I'd work hard, that I wouldn't get in anyone's way...
And yet...
You're a lot more sensitive than you let on, huh?
And you're a selfish, spoiled brat, too.
I... did I say something wrong?
A bunch of stuff, you know!
Oh, that's right, senpai!
W-What?
That song you were humming earlier...
W-What are you talking about...
The one that went like this:
That's astounding.
You've only heard it once and...
It wasn't just the once.
I've heard it before... a long time ago.
I thought, "How nice it would be to play that song, too."
That's why I...
In order to learn that song, whose sounds seem to resonate in the skies...
But I guess dregs are still just dregs, no matter how much they travel.
Kanata.
It doesn't do to rely on the church for everything.
The Takemikazuchi is a relic of a former age.
And also, many things sleep inside of her.
"Many things"?
Yeah.  If you want specifics, ask Noel later.
All right, this is it.
Here goes!
This...
This song!
Shh!
This is probably what that song sounds like in its complete form.
All sorts of instruments, all sorts of parts, resonating together to create one symphony.
It's the same as a tank crew.
Commander...
Gunner...
Driver...
And communications.
Everyone combines their strengths in order to move one tank.
Not a single one is inessential.
Every sound is essential, you see.
Don't look at me like that.
It's just something that I was told.
By the person that I most admire, most respect...
To borrow that person's words... Kanata, why do you think elders and superior officers exist?
Huh?
So their juniors can cause them trouble.
It's okay if you can't do it just yet.
Just remember your frustration and how powerless you felt...
and how happy you were to be protected from those feelings.
That will be your guide someday when you, too, take up the role of protecting instead of being protected.
That's why you can cause me as much trouble as you'd like.
I got here by doing the same.
Of course, if you mess up, you'll be scolded and even punished.
But if you're frustrated, tell me.  If you're in pain, say so.
Got it?
Understood!
From now on, I'll be sure to cause you lots and lots of trouble!
N-No... I mean...
Go easy on me if you can, okay?
Oh, ugh!  I knew I should've stayed behind!
That Kanata, she got Rio-senpai to nurse her.
What, that was no big deal.
It seems like it was just fatigue.
If she sleeps, she'll be fine.
Lights were on in the Takemikazuchi...
Ah, sorry!  I used it for bit.
Were there any problems?
No.
You listened to it, didn't you?  That song.
Yeah.
Even though you said you never would again.
Somehow I just really felt like it... you know?
And?
It's a secret.
Next time, The Sky During Rainy Season: Quartz Rainbow!