I wonder if the others are sleeping well.
Tomorrow, huh?
"Getting Around at Kanyasai" The whole
school's really going all out for this.
I'll have to be sure to hit
all the good places.
Hm, let's see...
The Quiz Club starts at 1:00...
A shogi tournament, huh?
Not sure I'm up for that.
Ah, the cooking contest
is worth checking out.
Mm-hm. It's coming up tomorrow!
Kamiyama Prefectural High School
Welcome to the
Kami High Homepage
Culture Festival page here
Tomorrow, huh?
Days until Kanyasai: 1
Please, may we have good fortune
for the next three days.
May we be able to cross over this mountain.
Okay, it's culture festival time!
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Those Things Piled Up Endlessly
Morning!
Yeah.
You're up early, Sis.
You've got the culture festival, right?
That's right.
I heard you had some trouble, didn't you?
How did you know?
I just do.
Besides, it's traditional that the
Classic Lit Club's culture festival
can't ever end without there
being some trouble first.
Nobody wants you leaving us
your unwelcome traditions.
If that's the case, you could at least
leave me a good-luck charm, "Senpai."
Here!
There, you can have that.
Am I supposed to thank you?
Oh, by the way, that's out
of ink, and the nib is split.
Don't dump your trash off on me.
You're going to be late.
All right.
If I have time, I'll come down
and see how it's going, okay?
No, stay away!
It's the culture festival, Hotaro!
So it would seem.
Same old Hotaro as ever.
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
Well, sure I am.
It's the Kamiyama Culture Festival,
the hall of fame of clubs!
Ah, isn't that Mayaka there?
That's probably a Manga Club costume.
Judging by appearances,
Mayaka is on festival time.
Have you thought up something, too?
Heh, I am in the
Handicrafts Club, after all.
I'm going to go bother her.
Hey, Mayaka. Good morning.
Good morning.
You look good in those clothes.
Cut it out.
So, who are you cosplaying as...
Do not use that word in front
of respectable folk.
Roger that.
Then, what outfit is that?
Frol.
Frol? Frolbericheri Frol?
Mm-hm. I've got gloves
that I'll put on later, too.
Oh, yeah?
What's in your bag?
Oh, a little something.
Sounds kind of shady.
Mayaka, are you with
the Manga Club all day?
Mm-hm. I got stuck being a salesgirl.
And at a time like this, too.
Well, don't worry about it too much.
You can't help what's already happened.
Ah!
Now this is what I call a culture festival!
Mm-hm.
I'd heard about this, but it's
more than I ever imagined.
Wow, what is this? It's pretty well-made.
You're right.
Too busy.
Way too busy.
Hey, are you done?
Yeah, all done.
This is incredible.
All right! Let's get this party started!
Well, I have to step away for a minute.
Handicrafts Club?
Just for a moment. I'll
be right up, though.
It's quiet, huh?
Yeah.
Don't dwell on it so much.
If you keep fretting like this,
forget about Satoshi... even
Chitanda will get concerned.
Yeah, I know.
Classic Lit Club Anthology
Hyouka Vol. 46
Now on sale
Ah, good morning, Oreki-san, Mayaka-san.
Good morning, Chi-chan.
It's almost time, huh?
It sure is.
Let's give it our all!
Yeah.
Is giving it our all
going to help this, though?
Actually, there's no guarantee that
if we give our all, it will help,
but if we don't give our all,
I can guarantee that it won't help!
Indubitably.
You know, I'm just going to buy them!
Huh? Oh, that's not what
I meant by saying that!
Still, I am the one who placed the order.
How many was the order originally for?
30 of them.
How many of them actually came?
200 of them.
Galaxy!
Ah! My Saturn!
You finally showed up, huh?
Good morning, Fukube-san.
Been waiting long?
It's all right. We haven't started yet.
Guys, I'm really sorry!
This is all my fault for not checking
my email from the printers.
Everybody goofs up, you know.
You can say that, looking like that?
There's no need to place
it all on yourself.
We're all friends, right?
You can say that, looking like that?
He's right. As club president,
I should have checked it, as well.
Well, after I turned in my draft,
I'd washed my hands of it.
All of the club members should
have been responsible.
Right! That's what I think!
Mm-hm... All right.
Looks like you've finally gotten
your head on straight.
Again, you can say that, looking like that?
All right, there's no more time
before the opening ceremony.
Does anyone have any ideas
about how we can sell
the greatest number of copies?
How much for one of them?
¥200.
That's pretty cheap.
The problem is the Classic Lit
Club's lack of name value,
Hyouka Vol. 46
Now on sale
and our unfavorable location.
Elective Classroom ♪5
Yeah. In other words,
boosting our name recognition
and creating a better storefront
are most important.
Creating another storefront?
I was only thinking about how
to bring customers way up here.
You've turned my thinking
upside down, Oreki-san!
Well, I wouldn't go so
far as "upside down."
Then again, can we get permission
to do so the same day it starts?
Well... What do you think,
Mr. Executive Committee Member?
Hm... It depends on whether or not
they'd approve such a special privilege.
We could try asking the committee chairman
or the student council president directly.
Who is the executive committee chairman?
You could at least look
through the guide, Hotaro.
See? Right here.
Committee Chairman: Tanabe Jiro
First time I've seen it.
Jeez, I wish you would have
noticed the way this is set up.
So what about it?
Well? Anything stand out?
Look, the Classic Lit Club is at
the end of all the club profiles, see?
I asked a huge favor and
had them put us here.
The executive committee
compiled this, after all.
That's amazing!
It's an abuse of power.
Well, who cares? If you want to ask
the chairman, try the council room.
You're not going to ask him?
Well, I suppose I could do that.
But I don't have too much
luck with negotiating.
Is that right?
Chitanda-san, what if you do the talking,
and I'll stand by you
to put in a good word?
Please, if you would!
Very well. Let's try it that way.
She doesn't seem too eager about this.
Oh, more importantly, I'd like
to devote myself to publicity!
Is that why you're dressed like that?
This is just one part of it.
I have something else up my sleeve.
Do you have a good idea in mind?
I'm going to drop the Classic Lit Club's
name as I participate
at the events and contests being held
during the culture festival.
The plan is that by giving
a strong performance,
the Classic Lit Club's
reputation will increase.
You just want to go out and have fun.
That is a good idea!
Isn't it?
Yes!
Leave it to you, Fukube-san!
Wait, hold on.
Yep, just leave it to me!
That's a good idea. I guess
that's how we'll proceed.
Chitanda will negotiate us
a better site to sell from,
and Satoshi will publicize us.
Let's go with that for now.
But what about you, Oreki-san?
I...
Yes?
Will mind the store.
Oh, right. I guess someone
has to be here.
That's true.
Well, we should get going.
The opening ceremony roll call
is starting soon.
Right.
Okay!
I would like to proceed with
the assignments we just stated.
Let's try to sell as many copies
as we can! Our goal will be...
Hyouka!
All 200 copies sold! Everyone ready...
Hey! Hey!
Oh!
Oh.
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
Today's centerpiece is obvious.
Hey, this looks like fun.
Hm? The Quiz Club?
Hurry up and find your class.
Say, how about the Quiz Club's event?
Hey, look!
The bunny rabbit?
This is amazing, huh?
It's just like that.
I hereby declare this,
the 54th Annual Kanyasai...
to be open!
Wow! He jumped over him!
Wow! He's spinning around!
Ah, I can't afford to stay here like this.
Who wants to do calligraphy?
Calligraphy! Calligraphy!
Would you like to try calligraphy?
Huh?
Chitanda Eru
Cultivating rice is cultivating soil
If you like, you can keep it as a memento.
Oh, no... Oh, no...!
"The river from Tsukuhane..."
Got it!
"Spring has passed..."
"Though I part from thee..."
Got it!
Everywhere at once!!
The Hundred Poets Card Game Club
What do you say?
One game?
Huh?
"In the..."
Got it!
Please accept this.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Executive Committee Office
I'm finally here.
Excuse me!
What a pretty picture.
Excuse me...
Um, did you need something?
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Um, I am here to see Executive
Committee Chairman Tanabe-san.
I'm Tanabe.
Huh? Oh, you are?
Well then, please give the
Classic Lit Club more selling space.
Global action! Global action!
Excuse me! Um, I am Chitanda Eru,
Classic Lit Club president.
And you see, I have a request to make.
Please give the Classic Lit Club
more selling space!
When you ask me out of the blue
to give you more space,
I can't just offer something up.
You can't? Thank you anyway.
Huh? Wait, hold up.
I meant, as a principle.
If you have circumstances that
would warrant it, tell me.
Do you mean it?
Thank you very much!
I thought that when I spoke to him,
Fukube-san was supposed
to be helping me out.
So, when I hit the gas pedal, we go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no way, no way.
You're way too dangerous.
I'm what?
You'll cause an accident.
So that's the situation.
That does sound like a problem. Hm...
I'd like to help you out somehow,
but the same goes for
all the other clubs, too.
I can't be partial to the Classic Lit Club.
Then there isn't anything you can do.
Sorry about that.
Ah, however, if you get the other clubs
to let you leave some of the Classic Lit
Club's anthologies at their spots,
I'd have no problem with that.
That is a great way to do it!
I will consider it!
Thank you very much!
Welcome to the Manga Club
Collections now on sale!!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh, Ibara, you're here.
Kochi-senpai, good morning.
You even have a katana for yours?
Yeah. It's just a fake plastic one, though.
You should have come up with
something for your feet, too, huh?
Look at that, she decided
to cosplay after all.
And after objecting as
hard as she did, too.
She should have just done
as Kochi said from the start.
Now, there's no call for that kind of talk.
Ah, good morning.
Good morning, Yuasa.
Good morning, President.
Good morning.
Did that cost a lot?
Just the price of the belt.
Oh. If you have the receipt, I'll take it.
No, that's all right.
Nevermind that, President, can I...
Hm?
Oh, nevermind.
It's nothing at all.
You're sure?
Yes. Sorry.
It really is hard to ask if I can
put copies of Hyouka in here.
Zeami's
Hey, there!
What outfit is this you're wearing?
This? It's Frol. Ever heard of
They Were Eleven?
Wow!
I've never heard of it.
It was an old science fiction manga.
I consider it a masterpiece.
Let me borrow it sometime.
Mm-hm.
Huh? What? What are you borrowing?
A manga.
All right, everyone,
let's all get fired up!
Yeah!
Excuse me, are you open yet?
Come right on in!
We have our first customers!
Come on in!
Welcome!
Classic Lit Club Anthology
Hyouka Vol. 46
Now on sale
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
It's quiet.
Three cheers for store-minding.
I think I'll mark down the ones
we're definitely going to sell.
And given the circumstances,
let's assume the four Classic Lit Club
members will each buy two.
Add to that our advisor and the archives,
and that's 12 gone, for sure.
Well, even at just that,
I'd say we did well.
A Capella Club
Huh? Anyone seen my apple juice?
Not me.
Aw, I didn't even have any of it.
What's that piece of paper there?
Did something happen?
Uh-oh, getting sleepy.
Excuse me...
Oh, a punk!
Is he a punk?
What are you doing here?
Nothing... er, I mean,
we're selling anthologies.
You mean, all of them?
Yeah. Long story.
Okay, one, please.
Oh, he's a customer? Is he a customer?!
I'll have to be gracious...
That will be ¥200.
Aw, I can't even manage to smile.
Thank you very much.
H-Hey, you!
Yes, what is it?
Th-This! Would you mind
if I had a look at it?
You mean this?
Mm-hm. This is it! This is perfect!
Are you sure about that?
Oh, sorry.
I'm in the Clothing Club, you see.
We're having a fashion show,
and I forgot something to go in
my formalwear breast pocket!
This would be just the thing!
You can have it.
Huh?! Really?! You'd really give it to me?!
I was going to throw it
away anyhow. Help yourself.
Oh, well then, take this.
It's a priority pass to our show,
so if you bring that to
the Clothing Club room,
they'll set you up with
a top-notch ensemble.
Okay...
Satoshi's about the only one who might go.
Nah, I guess he has his own style,
huh? Well, don't need that.
Although, that is one issue sold.
Ah! I did it again!
Say there!
Yes?
Have a commemorative picture taken!
Photography Club
How would you like to take a photo?
Huh?
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Every time something catches
my interest, I come to a halt,
which is keeping me from
accomplishing my duty!
Occult Club! Occult Club!
Would you like to summon a UFO with us?
We also have an exhibit
of spirit photography.
Now displaying the Enterprise!
Industrial Arts Club
Although we're
about to hold the launching ceremony!
Come witness three months
of work go down the tubes!
Global Action exhibit here!
Magic charm, anybody?
The A Capella Club is
singing in the courtyard!
Come to the Shogi Club tournament!
See the Debate Club arguing!
Occult Club! Occult Club here! The History
Club has recreated Kamiyama Castle!
Are there a pair of glasses anywhere
that only let you see straight ahead?
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "A Corpse By Evening."
A Corpse By Evening