I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
♪ Been a fool, been a clown,
lost my way from up and down ♪
♪ And I know, yes, I know ♪
♪ And I see in your eyes that you
really weren't surprised at me ♪
♪ At all, not at all ♪
♪ And I know by your smile ♪
♪ It's you ♪
So as a reward, the turtle took him
to Ryugujo, the dragon temple.
Ryugujo?
That's right. It was like a palace.
And they gave him
a big welcoming party.
Beautiful women, scrumptious feasts,
breams and halibuts swimming around...
He spent his time
there as if in a dream.
I haven't eaten bream
or halibut in a long while.
The days passed, and before he
knew it, the time came to go back.
And as a keepsake,
he was given the Tamatebako.
Tamatebako? Is that scrumptious too?
No, it's not food.
It's a big chest with a treasure inside.
I haven't seen any treasure
in a long time either.
You two are so clueless, it's pitiful.
This is an ancient fantasy.
It's a folk tale.
Tamatebako's the turtle?
Where'd you get that idea?
I should give up the ponies.
Well... huh?
Pay up. 6,300 Woolongs.
What? Where did
that come from, huh?
Special delivery for you.
Well, I didn't order anything.
It was C.O.D.
Top it off, there's no
return address on it.
I had no choice but to
accept it and pay your tab.
Hey, hold on!
Hey, I want my money, or else!
She's a busy girl, huh?
A collection for the
life extension agency?
Or else... No, could it be...
Oh, there's just too many people
who want a piece of me!
Time for Faye's famous
disappearing act.
Don't you think it's odd?
For a woman who always
wants other people's stuff,
here she gets something for free,
and she won't even touch it?
Yeah, but she's made a lotta enemies.
Think about that.
Well, I'd better run
some tests on it.
An explosives test,
and a biochemical examination...
Nah, I'll just return it
to the freight company
and tell them I want my money back.
I'll say it was a mistake.
Whoa!
H-Hold it, S-Spike, no--
Spike!
Huh.
What the hell is it?
It's not ticking like
it's about to blow?
- Uh-uh.
- Ed's got data!
Data on the freight routing, see?
The sender is a...
nonprofit convent on Europa?
There's more, look.
Pluto Penitentiary?
Asteroid B Actors' Studio?
Uranus Observatory Number 9?
Venus Action News Network?
Forwarded and forwarded again.
This thing's been passed
around the entire solar system.
Oh, read this!
Due to the explosion
of the lunar gate,
all data encoded before 2022 is missing.
So it's an antique then.
Apparently, it's something
called a "videotape."
- An artifact from days gone by.
- Hmm...
She ran off without a word, so she's
got no complaint if we sell the thing.
You think it'll sell?
This guy's crazy for anything
from the twentieth century.
- He'll buy it.
- I can't believe it's worth anything.
The real value of a treasure like this
can't be determined by looking at it.
You'd be surprised how much you
can sell this stuff for sometimes.
Anyway, if it covers the
C.O.D. charges, I'll be happy.
- Excuse me.
- Quiet!
But it's so different here
than where we grew up.
Nothing is like it was in Minnesota.
I'm so worried.
Do you think we'll be able to fit in
here and live like everybody else?
Um, to be honest, sis,
I was worried about it too.
- But now I'm sure we're fine.
- Uh?
Because I'm here
with my own twin sister.
I'm glad, twin brother.
Well, I gotta start work
bright and early tomorrow.
- Good night, Brandon.
- Good night.
God, that was good!
Twentieth century TV was the best!
On the other hand, our dramas
are so boring, it's pitiful.
I have something to
show you you're gonna--
Hey! You-- You can't do that!
Cigarette, man! Don't you realize that
smoke can screw up electrical stuff?
Sheesh! This is why I hate people
who don't know anything.
Idiot! Idiot!
What are you thinking?!
What the hell do
you guys want here?!
What do you have against me?!
We've got nothing against you, pal.
We've just got something
you might wanna buy.
Is that a Beta cassette? Wow!
What an amazing find!
Where did you guys
get ahold of this thing?
It's a miracle it's all
in one piece. A miracle!
- Beta?
- Never heard of it?
I'll explain for your benefit.
Well, back in the
twentieth century, you see,
they didn't record movies on discs.
It was primitive.
They used these things called videotapes,
which are in cassettes like this.
They're not digital, mind you.
They're completely analog.
And they're also magnetic!
Magnetic! Wow!
You see, it's all because they used
electromagnetic signals to record.
Isn't that wild? I mean,
talk about primordial technology!
But the guys who came up with this stuff
created two standards, Beta and VHS.
The Beta cassettes
were small for their time,
and the decks didn't take much space.
Still frame and slo-mo
were almost noise-free.
And since Beta had high quality images,
smart users supported it heavily.
But that's just the beginning
of the tragic history of Beta.
No need to tell it all.
Huh? Oh man,
I was really on a roll...
Look, buddy, are you
gonna buy it or what?
There. We gotta see
what's in it, you know.
- Ohh...
- So what's wrong?
It's hard to adjust the tracking
on these early Betas.
This way? Or this way?
Um... there we go...
Huh?
The tape is messed up!
That isn't helping, Spike.
It's not? Huh.
Come on...
You can do it, boy! Run!
Yeah!
Dogs are better than ponies!
My ship works better when I kick it.
Right... you just don't
know when to quit.
Brute force doesn't solve everything.
You owe me a new deck, dammit!
You back again?
You are refusing to take responsibility
for breaking my machine!
Yeah? And how about your responsibility
for ruining my videotape?
Early Beta decks
eat tapes all the time!
Anyway, you're gonna have to pay
for the cost of the repairs!
- We'll call it even for my tape.
- No way! I--
Guy's crazy.
Ed to Beta deck.
Come in, please.
There's only one of them around.
Where are you hiding, Beta?
The Underground City Museum.
It's there in old Asia.
I'm gonna find out what's
on that tape if it kills me.
Yeah, just might.
You really think it's worth it?
Go, go, go, go!
Yes! I did it!
Oh, I wonder if all this time,
those guys were just
sucking up my luck.
Yes? Hello?
Anybody?
Hey, it's me. Hello...
Oh, it's Faye! What's up?
Hello, Ed. What's going on?
Where are you guys, anyway?
- We're on Earth.
- Huh?
- We're on Earth!
- Earth?!
What? You just took off for
Earth and left me behind?
Spike and Jet are trying
to find a Beta deck.
All right, just a little farther.
Think we're really gonna
find one at a place like this?
Well, we'll never know
unless we check it out, right?
Twenty-eight floors down.
It's not working?
No wonder it's stuck.
The cable broke.
Tell me again why in the world
we're going through all of this?
It's a lesson to remind you that
treasure hunts are always trouble.
Treasure hunts?
What treasure are we hunting?
Tamatebako, was it?
When he opens the Tamatebako,
he turns into an old man.
Now I know why.
Even if we turn back now,
we wouldn't be any younger.
This place is some Ryugujo.
Where'd that minx
run off to, anyway?
Go, go, go, go!
Well, nothing I could've done.
Races are all luck anyway.
So? Is it here?
- It's here.
- All right.
Is this it?
Yeah, that's gotta be it.
And? Which one do we take back?
Um, let's see...
Well, they say the greater
serves for the lesser.
Hmm...
- What's wrong?
- The size.
- What about it?
- It won't go in.
- Push harder.
- But it's--
- Uh, that's the wrong one.
- Huh?
- You got a VHS.
- It won't play Beta!
- Huh?!
Oh, hello? It's me.
Hmm...
Mm-hmm.
Ein, who are you talking to?
Oh, it's Faye!
Well, I'm glad I reached a life form
that's capable of speech.
What do you want?
Did any visitors show up
looking for me?
Visitors? Hmm...
I mean like scary guys
who screams stuff like,
"Gimme back my money!"
Or, "You're under arrest!"
Mmm... there was one.
Huh? What'd he say?
Something like,
"Pay me back, get even,"
"tape munch-munch
grind-grind, bye-bye!"
Huh? Oh, right.
Oh well. Where's Spike and Jet?
Disappointed and sad.
Oh, I see. Hmm...
That's how it is...
Oh well.
Listen, Ed, I guess if they're
that lonely without me,
I have no choice.
I'm coming back to the ship.
What? Another package
for that wench?
I won't accept it. Take it back!
Dammit, why should I have
to pay the shipping for her?
And not once, but twice!
This sure is a lotta packaging.
Ahh!
Beta!
- We can see the tape with this?
- Mm-hmm!
Hey, how's it going, guys.
Long time no see.
It's showtime!
Hold on.
If you wanna watch, you have
to pay the C.O.D. charges.
31,500 Woolongs.
All right, then, I won't see it.
- Oh!
- We got picture!
Ooh, what's that?
Ooh, look, what's that?
Shh, watch and see.
Uh, well, um...
We're here because, um, well,
we all decided that we'd send ourselves
a message ten years in the future.
Come on, you guys, don't laugh!
Well...
This is making me feel really shy.
Um, something I wanna say...
Uh...
Good morning...
No, wait!
Good morning, me.
Did you sleep well?
Did you wake up feeling good?
Do the light and the wind
and the smell and the sound
all seem like they're brand new
and fresh this morning?
Is each and every cell in your
whole body awake and alive now?
Today, you are who
you are today, see?
You're still me,
but you're a newer version.
Myself ten years from now...
It's so far away, it's almost
impossible to imagine.
Am I alone, or is there a
wonderful person next to me?
Well, knowing me, I'm sure
you're causing all kinds of trouble
for lots of different people.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to.
But it's all right.
That's part of life too, isn't it?
You're not perfect, but you've
got a lot to give, so remember,
I'll always be cheering you on.
And now, a big cheer
from my heart.
Let's...
go...
me! All right!
Do your best, do your best,
don't lose me!
Let's go, don't lose,
Do your best!
I can't remember...
Don't you lose, don't you lose,
me, me, me!
Go me! Yay!
In your time, I'm no longer here.
But I am here today.
And I'll always be cheering
for you, right here.
Cheering for you, my only self.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
You know, I'm starting to get tired
of us doing all the previews like this.
Once in a while,
can't we have someone else?
Huh? Oh! Hey, you're perfect!
All right. Here, you try
doing it this time.
Really...
Oh, so that's how it is...
Wow, this is gonna be
an interesting episode.
Next episode: "Wild Horses."
Whoa, he talked!