It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
What's yer name?
Original
Kofune Mio.
When were ya born?
Who gave birth to ya?
Yesterday, at the wake, Mother scanned Mio, and
later that night,
I was born in a cave.
This "Mother" of yers.
Is she Haine in Shiori's form?
Yes.
Did ya cut the brakes on Mio's bike?
Were ya trying to kill me?
Nurse's Office
It didn't matter if ya died or not.
I just thought it would be easier if ya got hurt and had to go to the hospital.
Easier to kill Mio at the hospital and replace her, ya mean?
Yes.
Dr. Hishigata is a Shadow supporter, after all.
Were those Haine's orders?
No.
I just wanted to do it, but I failed.
I had no idea they were going to make a Shadow of Mio.
Don't worry, Tokiko.
I have no idea why I wanted to kill her anymore.
Haine created ya in order to search for Ushio's Shadow, correct?
For the traitor, yes.
I can't copy people.
Can ya do the same?
There are two types of copying.
Transformation—replicating something with your own body.
And childbirth—splitting off a part of your body to create a new Shadow.
Childbirth...
Us "children" can only birth one human Shadow each.
Children?
Haine can give birth multiple times.
But her body is weak, so it's not easy for her.
The grand-children I create cannot give birth.
Day 1
But all Shadows can transform repeatedly.
Day 2
Whether it's childbirth or transformation,
Day 3
Day 4
if a human was copied, then the original must be erased within a week,
Day 5
Day 6
Day 7
or the body will turn to mud and vanish.
I only have six days left to live,
yet I don't particularly care at the moment.
That's about it, I suppose.
Sorry, Shin.
I don't know anything very useful.
Th-That's okay.
Th-There's nothing for ya to apologize for!
Whoa, whoa, this is a Shadow yer talkin' to, Sou.
Oh, well... But—
Sou?
Damn it!
This is throwing me off!
Haine needs to consume a large amount of people in order to recover.
She is likely creating an army of children for this purpose.
Dad and I were helping Haine to recover for my mom's sake.
We brought her food and stuff,
but it was all a lie.
They have a different goal in mind.
Dad knows everything, eh?
Friggin' jerk.
So he's okay with all of us dying?
Dad...
There's a lot I'm still having trouble accepting.
But it seems Dr. Hishigata knows what Haine's true plan is.
I'm supposed to be meeting him tonight at 10.
Okay.
Our next objective is decided, then.
To the Hishigata Clinic.
I'm bein' eaten alive!
So many mosquitoes here!
Protect Mio, please.
Is that an order?
An order, huh?
I guess it is.
Shin,
are ya scared of me?
Yer really far away.
W-Well, I'd be lying if I said I wasn't.
Do you realize how many times you've killed me?
But those were in different timelines.
I personally haven't killed anyone yet.
Can I ask ya a question now?
S-Sure.
Did ya get a girlfriend in Tokyo?
A girl—
Girlfriend?!
Wh-Whaddya think yer askin'?!
It's a little suspicious when Shin slips outta his local accent from time to time.
Don't ya think it's weird?
I don't have a girlfriend.
And people in Tokyo couldn't understand my Wakayama accent.
So, when in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Well, that was just a joke.
Have ya ever thought about why I don't call ya "big brother"?
Listen, I'll protect Mio like ya ordered.
But you're the only one who can really protect her, Shin.
Sh-She makes no sense!
What's with her?!
C'mon, let's move it, Shin!
R-Right.
Hishigata Clinic
It's unlocked.
What the heck is this?
All of our stuff is gone.
Our rooms were empty too.
The desks, beds, closets—everything.
Miss Nagumo, is this...
Indeed.
Fortunately, I don't see any human-shaped stains.
Only furniture was erased.
Perhaps there was something here they didn't want found.
But the objects seem to have been erased haphazardly.
It's as if they knew something here needed to be erased,
but they didn't know its location.
That is my impression.
This has to be Dad's work!
The fact that he's not here is proof enough!
Plus Mom's missing.
What the hell is going on?!
Shinpei!
So ya sensed a Shadow in the clinic, Ushio?
Yeah.
Ow, ow, ow!
What's yer deal?
Stop squeezin' so hard!
Yer cuttin' off the circulation!
Are ya scared?
O-Of course I am!
I hate hospitals at night!
I hear something.
It's not working. So, this sound...
It's like something's caught in the basement door.
Bullet holes, huh?
There are traces of a fight.
Be careful.
The Shadow is going below us.
What's in the basement?
The morgue.
Th-The morgue?
Don't worry.
The only body down there is yours from when Dad swapped it for the funeral.
I see!
There's no reason to be scared if it's my own body, then.
Is that how it works?
Fear means your survival instincts are working correctly.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Shadows are scarier than monsters.
Gird yourselves for what is to come.
It's Mom's wheelchair.
What's it doing here?
Behind ya!
Morgue
Did ya see its face?
No...
I-It's empty.
Is...
this for real?
This was below the whole time?
It's gone.
Was Ushio's body here?
Yes.
If Ushio could have scanned it,
she would've been able to recover.
Someone must have realized that leaving it until tomorrow wouldn't be wise.
Wanna retry?
No, we gotta keep moving.
We need to find Sou's parents.
Got it.
Toki, what is this hall?
It's a path that connects to Hiruko's cave.
There's an entrance down here too?
We'd go through here to reach Haine's nest and bring her food.
It's a different route from the one under the old clinic.
I can just barely sense a Shadow.
Perhaps the one from earlier went through here.
Stay close, everyone.
It's coming up ahead.
Mom?
Summer Time Rendering
What's going on?!
Stop! D-Don't shoot!
But yer Dad's being killed!
Ushio!
It's all right, Sou.
I'll bring her back.
Dad!
He's not breathing.
Lemme take over!
Dad!
Don't ya die, dammit!
Ya don't get to go without answerin' fer anything!
I won't allow it, ya hear?!
Wake up! Dammit, Dad!
Sou?
No more hiding things.
We're family, aren't we?
Chitose—
How's your mother?
I cut her link with Haine.
She should wake up in a bit.
I see.
You've already reached this place.
So, Haine...
must've thought I'd tell you everything.
There's no point in hiding things.
All we have to do is scan ya, after all.
Tokiko, kill them.
Dad!
Kill them!
If you do, Haine will trust me again.
Yer wrong, Dad.
That won't happen.
The Shadows have no intention of keeping their promise to us.
You disappoint me, Tokiko.
Get back, Sou!
Your gun's too close!
Doc—
What... the hell?
You're...
Sorry to disappoint.
I wonder if Shin and them will be okay.
Don't worry, Ushio and Miss Nagumo are there.
And don't forget about Shadow Mio.
That's what I'm worried about the most.
I still don't trust her.
I'm surprised ya let her copy ya, Tokiko.
When a Shadow copies someone, they get to see everything.
Body and soul, right?
Right.
I wanted her to see the deepest parts of me.
G-Geez!
How can ya say that with a straight face?!
I don't want to hide anything anymore.
Mio!
Do ya trust me a little now?
Yeah, you saved us.
Really?
Go ahead and copy me if ya need proof.
Absolutely not.
I don't wanna know what's in yer heart, Shin.
Sou!
Ya shot Tokiko!
How the hell could ya do something like that?!
Kill them.
Ya bastard!
What do ya think human life is?!
Kill...
Ain't ya a doctor, Dad?
A doctor ain't supposed to be talkin' about killing people!
Right?!
Not gonna talk now, huh?
Forget it.
Do it, Mio.
I can't copy him.
He has immunity.
I see.
So, we just have to make you talk.
Wait!
That shouldn't be!
You can't copy me?!
A Shadow of you was made and then died.
People in that situation gain an immunity, and they can't be copied again.
No... Impossible!
I can't create a Shadow anymore?
Pretty much.
Doc?
Chitose...
Then... why did I...
Negoro.
Doctor, I will be taking my leave.
I've already completed my primary objective.
She's out of range!
Doctor, I have a message for you from Shide.
"The Hishigata family has served us well.
But that is at an end.
Thank you for your hard work."
I also have a message for Ajiro Shinpei.
"It would appear you survived somehow.
You're an annoying cockroach.
Yet, you are powerless to stop us.
Everything will be over in two days."
Wait, ya jerk!
Stop!
Ya don't have to chase her.
But!
She was using yer body as bait to lure us in.
She purposefully told us the time limit to provoke us.
It's over if we take the bait.
But, Shinpei!
It's so frustrating!
The Shadow we saw earlier in the hall was her!
Calm down, Sis.
Shin is the one feeling the most frustrated.
Ya can't just act on instinct and expect things to work out.
Anger, frustration—
View them objectively, and they become weapons.
Shinpei...
Dr. Hishigata, is there any point in staying silent now?
My daughter...
Call the real Tokiko here.
Are you awake?
Sei.
Wh-Where am I?
Chitose, I'm going to show ya my memories just like I've done to the doctor.
I'm sorry, Chitose.
Sou's mom had no idea she was a Shadow.
Nor of how she was created.
I know you're trying to stop the ritual.
But is killing Haine really the right decision?
What do you mean?
Killing Haine means all Shadows will die!
In other words, you'll be killing your Ushio as well!
Ushio...
It's fine, it's fine!
I was supposed to die two days ago, anyway.
Living this long is just lucky.
It's like I'm in bonus time, y'know?
And if I can use this time to save everyone, I want to.
So defeating Haine will solve everything?
That's good to hear!
In that case, I'll gladly take her down!
She's right.
I'm ashamed of myself for hesitating.
Right?
Right.
Dr. Hishigata.
What is Haine trying to do by reviving?
She only wishes to return home.
To her hometown, across the vast, deep ocean.
Creatures of this world cannot reach it.
It's only possible for Shadows.
Haine's only going to bring Shadows with her.
The family that she hand-picked.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
Th-That can't be!
It's possible if her power returns, that is.
But even now I still see visions of you
It's an eternal country where time doesn't exist.
Chitose and I were supposed to become Shadows and live there forever.
In reality I only have vivid memories
And in the end, Sou and Tokiko were going to become Shadows too.
To play in my head over and over again
Is that why ya don't care if we die?!
How selfish can ya be?!
Are ya stupid?!
Even if it's all just a lie
All this for that?
Please be close by my side
You're so selfish and self-absorbed.
Right next to me
I don't know what to do with ya.
Thank ya for saving me.
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
Chitose...
But we must end this now.
I wanna go back
Sou, Tokiko.
I got to watch so much of yer lives.
I'm very happy.
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Chitose, wait!
If you die, I'll have no reason to live!
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
No, ya have yer children.
And ya have the islanders that depend on ya too!
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
Shinpei is correct.
It's not over just yet.
Ya can still make things right.
True to myself
But it's too late for that
What's in there?
The patient records Tokiko and I hid.
I diagnosed everyone here with Capgras delusion.
The shadow sickness, endemic to this island.
But the truth is that it's actually a list of Haine's food.
Shinpei.
Your parents' name are in here too.
But Mom and Dad—their boat sank during an expedition.
It was an accident.
They discovered Hiruko cave and were going to go public.
So they were killed.
It was made to look like an accident.
Shide killed them, and I replaced the bodies and transported them to Haine.
I'm sorry.
What?! Ya think that's all ya need to—
Do ya know Shide's real identity?
Yes.
Take a look at this photo.
Shide is Haine's guardian and the first child she ever gave birth to.
His original name was Hishigata Shidehiko.
The founder of the Hishigata Clinic, as well as its first director.
Next time
Decision