Goodbye!
Let's go, Kii-chan.
Yeah!
Nothing's changed, at all.
You've been here before?
Yeah, ten years ago.
Anyway, let's go, Koutarou.
Right.
Letting himself get seduced just like that...
Satomi-sama needs to
remember he's your knight.
He's being drawn in by Kiriha's sex appeal.
He has Sakuraba-senpai, and he's still...
I'm not letting him get away with this!
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Someday, With Them...
This hasn't changed, either.
What's wrong, Koutarou?
Ah, nothing.
Is it okay for them to be
messing around over there?
Spin, spin!
I'm dizzy!
I told them they could have the day off.
Isn't this risky, since they usually hide?
I'm sure no one will notice
them, given our location.
I see.
Koutarou, let's go to the next one.
Yahoo!
Stare...
2 Adults
Are you sure this is what you want to see?
It looks like a movie for kids...
Yeah. I wanted to see this.
I see.
Well, I don't think I mind.
They went into the theater.
It's dark in there.
Will Satomi-san and Kiriha-san...
You're imagining too much!
What now?
Should we head in, too?
No need for that.
I prepared a surveillance drone
specifically for this situation.
I'll have Ruth set it so it'll
notify us when they leave—
Where's Ruth?
That's weird.
She was just here.
Hey!
Look at this!
Rhinoceros beetles?!
This is...
"Beetle Warriors: Rhinoceros Man Hero Show"
This is terrible!
A whole bunch of rhinoceros beetles!
Whatever evil tries to challenge us,
we rhinocerose warriors will fight them!
Rhinoceros Man Number One!
Rhinoceros Atlas!
So this is where you were, Hercules-chan.
Huh?
I've been so worried.
I thought you'd been multiplying!
Why is Ruth-san here?!
Are you one of them, too?!
She's going to ruin my part-time pay!
I have to deal with her!
Sorry, but I'm taking you down!
Rhinoceros Beetle!
Wait!
That was pretty good.
I'm glad.
We got a reprint of the old pamphlet, too.
Pretty cool.
Hm?
This is...
The same as mine, huh?
I got this from the person
I liked a long time ago.
So, you came here with the
person you liked ten years ago?
Koutarou, let's go on that next.
Kii-chan!
There!
Hey, be more careful.
Kiriha-san.
There.
Hey, be more careful.
You're not a kid.
Sorry.
You're right. I'm not...
Hm?
I have to do what I need to do.
Koutarou, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
It all started ten years ago.
I got into a fight with my
father over something minor,
and ran away from home.
Ran away from home, huh?
Doesn't sound like you.
I was a kid back then, too.
And I'd lost my mother, so
I guess I was a bit unstable.
I see.
You lost your mother, too, didn't you?
I left home, and headed towards the
surface, which was forbidden to me.
And that's when I met him.
I don't remember his name,
or what he looks like.
What I do remember is that he
was about the same age I am now,
and that I called him "Onii-chan."
The places we went, and the
feelings I had at the time...
So, we went around the park today because...
That's right, because of
my memories with him.
You really liked him, huh?
He was my first and only love.
I was taken right back underground,
and haven't seen him since.
I see.
That's why when it was decided
we'd invade the surface,
I volunteered to be the commander.
Wait, you're invading because you
want to see your first love again?
That's why I needed to
recommend we invade peacefully.
I didn't want to drag this town,
where I met him, into a war.
But, wait...
You said you wanted Apartment 106
to mass produce weapons, right?
That was in order to get you to resist.
Huh?
If I had taken Apartment 106 at that moment,
there was a danger things
would have turned into a war.
It would give credit to the radicals
that advocate military action.
But, if I forego the
invasion of Apartment 106,
that radical faction would
probably take action on their own,
and try to invade the surface.
That's why I can't win or lose
the fight over Apartment 106.
You have to maintain
control over Apartment 106
until I'm able to peacefully
take over this city.
I see.
It finally makes sense.
You really are too kind to invade.
Guess I couldn't keep it hidden.
Anyway, if you would have
just told me earlier,
I would have helped you out.
I see...
I'm sorry, Koutarou.
I was deceiving you purely for my own gain.
It's fine.
But, you know, I guess I feel a little bad.
I think any guy would have fallen for you
if you were hitting on them seriously.
Koutarou...
You really are a guy, after all.
I'm a young guy, it's only natural!
If you actually meant what you were
saying, I think any girl would be happy.
Ruth...
Ruth.
Ruth!
Your Highness...
Everyone...
What happened to me?
You don't remember?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Nothing! Yeah, nothing, don't worry about it!
It was terrible.
You were using a fly swatter
to get some rhino—
Well, all of our guests had
a great time, so no problem.
Yeah, no problem!
Right.
This next?
Doesn't seem like your kind of thing.
Or maybe it is, huh?
You're making it sound like
I'm some sort of tomboy.
I don't think I like the sound of that.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
You rode this with that guy, too?
No.
You must be as tall
as this sign to ride
I couldn't because of that.
I've always wanted to ride it.
Today is the day that dream comes true.
Dream, huh?
Yeah, but Kiriha-san...
Huh?
An earthquake?
What's going on?
It couldn't be...
What's that?
W-What?
It's a subterranean submarine
of the earth people.
I knew it'd be you, Tayuma Shijima!
Tayuma, what are you trying to pull here?!
Oh, Commander.
I'm here to regain the glory and honor of the earth people,
instead of the inept
leadership of Kiriha Kurano!
Withdraw your soldiers, Tayuma.
I'll forgive the fact you brought
a subterranean submarine.
I'm afraid I will be unable to do that.
Kiriha-san!
I'm fine, Koutarou!
Stand back.
Who are these guys?
They have guns!
From the situation, I'd imagine
they're with Kiriha...
They don't seem to be
on the same side, though...
That Koutarou...
Always getting tied up in something annoying.
Your Highness!
I'll go, too!
Huh? Where's Yurika?
Whatever.
I'm a magical girl of love and justice.
It's my job to protect everyone.
First I need to use my magic to
get people to stay away.
Tayuma, do you understand what will
happen if you point your weapons at me?
Of course, I plan on telling Chief Daiha you
were betrayed and killed by a surface-dweller.
That will get our citizens
riled up for the invasion.
So, you'd even use my death...
You're going to die for
the glory of the earth people.
You should be honored.
Fire!
Kiriha-san!
Sis, sorry we're late!
Karama, Korama, disable their guns!
Roger!
Shock, shock!
The Kurano family's prized
automated dolls, huh?
But I have something, too!
Come to me, Jack-o!
What now?!
It's an Shijima family earth combat doll!
We're not losing to some earth doll!
We're not real haniwa dolls if we lose!
Tayuma, do you wish for war no matter what?
There's a more peaceful—
A peaceful takeover is a joke!
You've forgotten the greatness of the earth people,
and cozied up to the surface-dwellers!
That's not—
That's proof enough!
I know you're obsessed
with that lump of metal!
That's right.
I'll destroy that first, and
make it your gravestone.
Jack-o!
Erase everything!
That's enough!
This is a place for everyone
to make memories!
And what about it?!
You won't be able to invade the
surface if you don't understand that!
Kiriha-san understands.
That's why she's trying to merge
with the surface and this town.
It's not about weapons, but hearts and minds!
Koutarou...
You're—
Koutarou!
Why are you concerned
with a surface-dweller?!
Jack-o, do it!
Great work, Theia!
You're supposed to say, "You
saved me, Your Highness!"
Ruth!
Right, Your Highness!
Perfect, Ruth-san!
How come you didn't act like that with me?!
Take that!
You guys really shouldn't try
to lay your hands on my tenants.
Take this, Koutarou!
My Knight,
here's your sword!
Thank you, Theia!
No need to thank me.
Who are you guys?
My invaders and landlord!
Tayuma, this is the invasion I desire.
Leave this to me, and return underground.
And I'm saying that's not enough!
Jack-o!
Second Form!
You want to fight to the end?
In that case...
Karama! Korama!
Right!
I thought this might happen!
I'm not going to hold back.
Kiriha-san, we're going to help, too.
Right. Thanks!
Here I go!
Take that!
And that, and that!
You look like you're standing still!
Blue Knight.
T-That's not good!
Let's end this.
Damn it...
How underhanded...
Koutarou, I'll be your eyes.
You can praise me later!
No problem!
Right there!
Damn you...
You still plan to fight, Tayuma?
If I could have sacrificed you,
the people of the earth
would have chosen fighting.
That's what I thought.
But, the sacrifice didn't have to be you!
It can't be!
What is it?!
He's trying to self-destruct!
Karama, Korama!
Create an etheric field at maximum power!
I don't care if you burn out your circuits!
Right!
Too late!
I wonder if my magic made it in time...
No way...
How could you defend against
an explosion that big...
It seems like the goddess of
creation isn't on your side.
I'm going to start a war...
I'm going to become a hero!
I don't like hurting people.
However, I'll take up arms to
protect those I care about.
Goddess, forgive me.
What are we going to do about this?
I'm sure the government will
manipulate the information for us.
They'll say the ground suddenly
fell in, or something.
They will?
They want to hide certain things,
even if they know we exist.
Guess we'll have to go on that
roller coaster another time.
Koutarou...
Will you go on a ride with me another time?
No.
I think you should go on that roller
coaster with your first love.
Koutarou...
If you really did come up
to the surface just to see him,
then we should find him!
I'll help you out, too.
Thank you, but you don't
have to do that for me.
It's not about me "having to".
We're friends, right?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Koutarou Satomi,
you're my best and only friend on the surface.
I'm telling you earth people
are really here this time!
Come on guys. Let's go.
We still haven't gotten our
different colored suits, though.
We still haven't resolved
me wanting to be red.
Huh? There's no signature from the
earth people anymore, is there?
I want to see Lord Baron Devil again!
Whatever.
It's almost Christmas.
I wonder what I should get Satomi-kun.
Wait a second!
I'm going to have you do all sorts of stuff
at the big event at the end of this year!
Next Episode: Invasion Going Well?!
I'm not going to wear that!
Huh?