Morning, Run-chan.
Morning.
Are you wearing your panties?
Of course! I'm completely awake right now!
Come on. Let's go.
Run-chan...
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Man, carbonation is the best way to wake up!
Usually it's coffee.
Really? This bubbling feeling makes me blink and wake up in a flash.
Is that how it works?
Nice shot.
Hey, you know, I haven't seen Tooru at all today.
She has day duty today, so she'll be busy all morning.
Oh, really? It feels like she's always with us. It's kind of quiet without her.
You're right. But day duty is day duty.
Hey, wait...
What is it, Nagi?
Hey, do you feel like seeing them?
See what?
First years. And Tooru.
Classmates
Oh! Look! These scribbles!
They're still here!
They're carved into the wall.
Come on, let's go.
Wait for me!
Man, it feels like forever since we were here.
It wasn't too long ago, either.
Oh, isn't this Tooru's classroom?
I wonder what Tooru's like in the classroom.
Maybe they're all scared of her.
Actually, Tooru's a very good student.
No way!
She's always going berserk around us!
That's right! I always saw her as swinging around a bat, covering the room with blood...
I don't think she would...
Sensei, here are the handouts.
Thanks as always.
The number of boys wasn't right on the original, so I corrected it.
Is that okay?
Oh, really? I guess I made a typo.
Thank you so much.
No, it was only natural.
To-o-ru!
"It was only natural," you said! You're so nice!
Dependable, huh?
Come on. Come on.
Why are they here?
Excuse me...
I forgot my textbook. Can I read along in yours?
Sure.
Thank you!
Sorry, I forgot my contacts today, too.
I see...
I can't see...
Too close...
Thank you so much.
You're a lifesaver.
Not at all.
My name is Yutaka.
You know, I've always wanted to talk to you.
But I never had a chance...
I see.
I hope we can get along, Toorun!
Toorun
Let me treat you to some juice as a sign of our new friendship!
Wait, what did you call me?!
Oh, Tooru?
What's wrong?
Oh, what a nice surprise!
Isn't this a bit too tight?
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
What's up with Tooru?
No idea.
Thanks for waiting, Toorun! I brought more drinks!
Wait, Toorun?
Where are you, Toorun?
Excuse me for a moment.
Yes?
You have a pretty forehead. It's very nice.
Run is talking to a weird-looking guy?
Oh, thank you.
And... what is with that shirt pattern?
Could you tell me where the nurse's office is?
That way.
I see. Thank you.
See you again.
Nagi-chan!
Hey, who was that?
The new school nurse.
He got lost.
Oh, is that it?
I thought he might have been dangerous.
And he said, "You have a pretty forehead. It's very nice."
Isn't that kind of weird?
Oh? A new school nurse?
He looks kind of dangerous...
School Nurse
Satou Sensei
But he's the type that girls kind of like—
He's talking to her again!
Thank you again for earlier. You were very helpful.
No, don't mention it.
Come by the nurse's office sometime.
I'll keep a special bed just for you.
Sensei, you're too funny.
Come by anytime.
It feels like something's moving—
What are you?
Don't act friendly with Run-chan.
Oh, so your name is Run-chan?
Can I call you Run-chan, too?
Sure.
I see. Run-chan.
Very cute. Run-chan.
You kind of look like an urchin.
How does Uni-chan sound?
She looks kind of down.
She kind of just helped an enemy in need.
But your forehead is very cute, Run-chan.
Thank you.
Yes. So very... So very...
Get away from Run-chan!
Sorry, it's time for my medicine.
Oh, he's sick.
Oh, right! Look at this!
Ta-da!
No music, no life!
Oh, you got the limited edition color!
Oh? Did I?
Man, I really want one...
Sure is high tech.
What kind of music do you listen to?
Let's see...
I'm still living a no music life.
So you haven't put anything on it?
I tried to do all sorts of things, but I couldn't get music into it. I think it might be broken.
Like that.
MD Stereo
It doesn't work...
And that.
Cassette Deck
It doesn't work
And even that.
Like a TV
hit at a 45 degree angle
Right?
But nothing really worked.
What was that last one?! Hey?!
You took it apart?!
I thought it was broken, so—
You think an amateur could fix one of these?!
You could do something else, like take it to a shop!
Calm down, Nagi! It's not yours!
If it were mine, I would take you apart!
Don't worry. I'm not broken, so you don't need to.
That's not what I mean!
It turned on!
What a relief.
Run, you need to use a computer to put music on it.
What?
I don't have a computer.
Then why'd you buy one?!
Excuse me, but where do you go every break?
I won't let go until you tell me.
I-I-I-I was just kidding, Toorun! Wait!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry! Are you mad at me?
I'm not.
It's all stretched out...
It'll go back when I wash it.
No. We can use it like this.
What?
Now, where do you want to go? Yutaka will take you there!
Run-chan!
Oh, right.
She has P.E. next.
It feels like they'd reach, but I know they just won't
What do I need? What don't I have?
I don't need to look, I already know
Just a little courage and a push
(I miss you) If I called you right now,
(do you hear me) I could meet your voice
(hold me real tight) But I want to hold you so much
(don't you feel me) I might just die if I did
(I miss you) I want to see you right now
(this ain't right) It's not exactly what you'd call love,
But without you there's just no point
So I want to hold you tight (never get enough)
Run-chan...
In the end,
Tooru put music on it.
Occupied
You know...
It's pretty weird for us to wear bloomers in this day and age.
You're right.
Other schools use shorts.
Bloomers are just another pair of underwear.
We put on underwear on top of another pair?
Underwear on underwear.
Nagi?
Taking a class in underwear is just plain weird.
They're not panties, so it's not embarrassing?!
They're freaking embarrassing!
You're more embarrassing than wearing bloomers!
When you shout it like that, it sounds like you like it.
Start your warm-up exercises.
Hey.
What is it, Yuuko-chan?
Are we supposed to pull for this one?
Wasn't it push?
Oh, right. Then on three.
Let's do this!
One, two.
What are they doing?
Looks like we were supposed to pull.
Looks like it, Yuuko-chan.
We're doing this one right!
You look like you're having fun.
Keep fooling around and you might get hurt.
Don't worry!
Oh?
What's wrong, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing.
Right. Now for the next question.
Toorun is watching Yutaka?
No question about it!
Something for Yutaka?
Out of the way.
Okay. Who can solve this problem?
You look eager to.
Huh? Yutaka?
Yes. Come up front.
Toorun!
Yuuko-chan!
Try putting it outside instead of tucking it in.
The uniform?
Not wearing any.
Nagi-chan, look! Yuuko-chan isn't wearing any!
Run! Don't shout!
So that's what happened, and you're wearing your P.E. uniform.
Don't tuck it in?
I don't think it's what you want.
This is...
a normal one piece dress!
You're good at this!
A compliment!
Toorun!
Isn't that...
Alright! Let's start class now!
We'll start with warm-up exercises, so pair up.
Toorun!
Please pair up with Yutaka!
Oh. Miporin.
You're going to pair up with me, right?
Yutaka wants to pair up with Toorun...
You'll pair up with me, right?
Let's go over here.
Miporin...
Hey, Yuuko, do you have a band-aid?
What's wrong?
Get hurt?
No, I scraped my knee when I fell down during P.E.
That's not good! We need to disinfect it!
We're going to the nurse's office!
Washing it off and putting a band-aid on it is good enough.
It's not. What if it gets infected?
It's fine. And class is going to start soon.
That's why we have to hurry.
Hey, wait—
I said it's fine.
I said it's not.
Did something happen?
Excuse—
Yuuko-chan?!
I'm so sorry! I never thought anyone would be right there...
It's okay. I had an attack and fell down.
Thank you.
Yuuko-chan! What happened—
I'm sorry, Sensei. I didn't know...
Don't worry about it.
In fact it was an honor to be stepped on by you.
Excuse me, but it seems like you like Run a lot.
What do you like about her?
Let's see... How she can just talk to anyone like that,
and how she doesn't have any ulterior motives.
Right...
And... she can cause pain without knowing it,
and her forehead is pretty,
and her forehead width is the best,
and her forehead...
This nurse...
Thank you very much.
Come by anytime.
Looks like class already started.
Thanks for coming with me.
Don't mention it. You can't take scrapes lightly.
Got it. I'll be more careful.
But I wonder if Nurse Satou is okay.
What about him?
He was on the floor earlier.
You think he'll be okay by himself?
I guess it's a bit worrying...
Oh, right!
That nurse is dangerous!
What's dangerous about him?
That nurse...
ha-has some weird interests...
Oh, that.
He said that my forehead was pretty!
He does seem dangerous.
Right?
Oh, whatever.
Toorun, can you help me with this?
Okay. What part do you need?
All of it.
Then I'll explain from the beginning.
Please.
Tooru-san is really nice.
Yeah.
How can you not understand?!
I've been repeating it over and over!
I'm sorry! You do this here, right?
No! Wrong! You do this!
I would have given up a long time ago.
But I thought that...
No, you do this here!
Definitely.
Do you understand?
Not at all.
Yutaka.
Oh, Miporin.
Yutaka, you've been bothering Tooru-san too much recently.
Sorry about her, Tooru-san.
You don't need to mind her.
Help me!
She's too much trouble.
Come on, let's go.
Don't bother Tooru-san like that! If you don't understand, ask me first!
It's kind of lonely now that she's gone.
I didn't think that! I didn't think that!
Tooru! Wait, Tooru!
No! No more!
Did something happen to Tooru?
Don't know.
Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy! Mercy...
I'm not lonely.
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
So, Yutaka and Miporin are main characters!
And it's almost summer.
What? Summer already? Isn't that a bit too quick?
There are a few circumstances behind it...
We need to have a swimsuit episode and a hot springs episode...
No, I don't think we have hot springs.
But before we change into our swimsuits, there's that painful tradition...
On the next A Channel: Kilograms.
A diet, huh?
Something that Yutaka's nice body will never need!