When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Screen Text: "While walking outside, harm befalls the local residences"
Screen Text: Sada
What movie is this, Milady?
It is very avant-garde.
When I rented a video from Wataru,
this looked interesting, so I borrowed it, too.
Apparently I'll die if I don't show it to two other people within one week.
What? Isn't that the same curse as that circular movie?
Such an unscientific thing can't possibly exist.
You have a childish side to you, don't you?
Oh, right.
Allow me to explain just in case.
The circular movie is the famous Ri-
No! Don't say any more than that.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Although it's the Obon festival now,
the season for ghost stories, did I react too much?
Because it's Obon, no one's watching.
From here on, we're working the cel artists into the ground.
Damn Nagi... She's past the return date again.
I understand that O****'s works
require more than one viewing to understand...
Hey, that circular movie's gone.
Someone actually rented that fake copy?
Saki, Nagi's overdue with the rental, so give her a call, will you?
What's with her?
It's been a week since, but nothing has happened.
It's as I told you.
Spirits do not exist in this world.
You're right.
Maria-san's amazing.
She looks so mature;
I bet she doesn't have anything she's bad at.
Oh, I just remembered we have watermelon.
Would you like to enjoy some?
Then let's give it to Milady, too.
Actually, I already took some to Nagi, but...
No, this won't cut it!
Isn't there a more striking name?
I'm going to find a new genre with horror imbedded.
I see. When it comes to manga,
she gets engrossed in it too much.
Although that's what's good about her.
Give one to me, too.
Wataru-kun, what are you doing here?
Well you know, Nagi's been overdue with her rental again, so I'm here to bug her.
Right, what was that strange movie?
I noticed it was missing from the shelf, so it was Nagi who took it.
It's a fake version made when the authentic one was popular.
I didn't think someone who would want to watch that crap existed.
I mean, Sa**ko doesn't even come out.
If I remember correctly, something like this comes out when you watch that movie.
Yes, if something like that existed, it would be gross, but...
Don't you agree, Maria-san?
Huh? Is something wrong?
Saki's been acting strangely recently.
Looks like she's worried about something, but won't talk to me about it.
Seriously, just because she's twenty now, does she want to say a thirteen year old isn't reliable enough for her?
Saki-san is going to
her Coming-of-Age Ceremony next year, huh?
Coming-of-Age Ceremony?
Oh, so you'll be twenty when June comes?
Yes.
I should get you something to celebrate, then.
What do you want?
That kindness is enough for me.
You always wear that maid outfit so...
What me to buy you a furisode?
Furisode: An elegant kimono for unwed women.
Do you mean that, Sir?
When you become twenty, you'll need one for your Coming-of-Age Ceremony, too, right?
What? You don't need one?
No, I didn't mean that.
Then I'll look forward to it without too much expectation.
Could she be upset because I forgot about her birthday and didn't give her the furisode I promised her?
Hey, are birthdays and Coming-of-Age Ceremonies important?
Well, I think so.
By the way, what was your Coming-of-Age Ceremony like, Maria-san?
Huh?
Eh?
Right. Maira-san's only seventeen, so she hasn't had hers yet.
Yes, I am still a fresh seventeen year old.
And yet, Hayate-kun...
What made you think I have had my Coming-of-Age ceremony?
M-Maria-san, you're acting strangely.
I'm not acting strange.
Excuse me, I just remembered something I need to do.
Really, what's wrong with Maria-san?
Coming-of-Age Ceremony...
I guess I'll ask Saki personally.
Hey, Saki.
Could the reason why you've been sighing be because I forgot about your birthday present?
Come to think of it, nobody celebrated my birthday.
I don't mind though, really.
I can't do anything about the time that's passed, but I think the lost trust can be rebuilt!
So what do you need from me?
I want to give you a present!
Don't need one.
Who'd ever give you a present!
When you ask others for a favor,
"watch what you say," says Haman****.
Yes, Sir...
Really, it's better for her to play with
her friends than draw manga all day.
Let me go make some tea for the two.
So, what's this present thing about?
Well, you see, I want to give a furisode to a certain person,
but I don't have a clue what's good.
Hmm, a furisode as a gift, eh?
I see, so you've finally...
Go to this store.
It's pretty cheap, and you can find variety of furisode your girl would like.
R-Really?
Thanks a bunch, Nagi.
I'll go right away!
But don't buy something too cheap!
Let me ask just in case, but how much does an average furisode cost?
Don't worry, it's cheaper than buying two Fe***ris.
How could clothes be more expensive than a Fe***ri?
Don't make fun of a commoner's sense of money!
Stop shouting.
The chair I hit you with cost more.
What kind of furniture do you have?
Besides, if a man decides to give a present to a woman,
it's natural to pay that much!
You're worthless if you can't!
Y-You may have a point, but...
Where do I find such money?
Although it's not carved in stone, we are engaged.
So no interest and pay me back when you make the money.
Now, it's up to you.
So bright!
Holy Onmyouji!
What's going on here, Maria-san?
Something is  wrong with you.
H-How so?
N-Nothing is wrong.
Th-This is...
What's going on?
No!
Please! Nothing but that!
I cannot handle that black rustling creature!
I didn't know Maria-san had this side to her.
I am sorry; I lost control of myself.
But I just cannot stand them.
Don't worry.
Even if it does appear, I will protect you, Maria-san.
R-Really? You really will?
Yes.
Roach...
What?
N-No way!
H-Hayate-kun... What was that?
Please don't worry, Maria-san.
Roach!
Roach?
Cock Roach Roach Roach Roach.
Ima aini yukimasu.
Ima aini yukimasu. = We'll come see you soon.
Su... Suusuu surun desu.
Su... Suusuu surun desu. = I... I feel a chill down my spine.
I didn't know Sir was worried about my birthday.
Compared to that, Grandma won't even call me.
Allow me to explain for a moment.
Kijima Saki's grandmother is the legendary housemaid,
Kijima Rei.
In order to find her missing daughter and son-in-law,
Saki's parents,
at times, she wandered around the world with Saki.
At times, she protected the president from assassination.
At times, she closed cases that would have been filed away forever.
And at times, she liberated oppressed citizens by serving delicious cuisine to emperors.
However, the legendary maid is already sixty-two years old.
Her life was about to end in the middle of the Sahara Desert.
Grandma! Grandma!
Do you plan to die here?!
Are you the legendary housemaid, Kijima Rei?!
This man is the President of
the Tachibana Group, Tachibana Enkyou.
Kijima Rei and Saki were saved by Enkyou.
A resonance between hearts that's neither friendship nor love blooms between Enkyou and Rei.
In order to repay the debt, Rei fights against evil and criminals.
And, a fated encounter came to Saki, as well.
Her encounter with Wataru.
His too-young-to-be-a-mother mother didn't give much attention to him.
Saki swore to his lonely face...
...that she shall repay the gratitude of saving
Kijima Rei back by raising him to be a wonderful man.
Have some tea.
To Saki, it felt like two souls forsaken by mothers were calling to each other.
I serve tea better than you do.
But Wataru was very skilled and could do everything himself.
He was so much more thorough than Saki.
Could I possibly guide him to become a wonderful man?
For your reference, Saki's parents still live in Ueno.
They are not lost, so don't worry about it.
It's a dead end!
Please hold on tight.
Hayate-kun...
What a nice day.
On days like this, it's best to walk around creating the original language of flowers.
Target spotted!
Jet St***m Attack!
Attack!
It's getting away!
Another round of Jet St***m Attack!
Roger.
Jet St***m!
Attack!
How dare you step on me!
We should be fine, since we've come this far.
On what basis?
Hayate-kun.
That was nothing.
No, that!
Damn you're persistent.
I'll protect Maria-san.
Butler Kick!
I will not forgive you if you touch Hayate-kun.
Ow...
Maria-san.
Hayate-kun.
Are you all right?
I talked big saying I'd protect you, but I got protected instead.
That is not true.
You did protect me.
Maria-san.
Oh no, what if that thing attacks Nagi?
Milady's in danger!
I was surprised I did not get lost for once, but it seems as though we have a guest.
Isumi-san, you were here?
Did you see the black rustling creature here?
That child already left.
She exterminated it?
What's the ruckus here?
Hey.
So you've come.
Did Wataru give you a call?
He didn't?
He must be embarrassed inside.
When you buy a present, you have to use your own money.
When I bought something with my savings, I could afford only a yukata.
My, what a cute yukata.
I-I-Isumi!
Sorry. But why are you here?
Nagi said there's something important you need to tell me and that you had a present waiting,
so I should go to your house right away.
Could the present be...
...that?
No, this is...
Then what's the important thing you need to tell me?
That Nagi, doing the extra unneeded favor...
But this is an unexpected opportunity.
I'll give this yukata to Isumi and tell her my feelings.
My feelings...
Isumi!
Yes?
I got ahold of an extra DVD box of Cha***ion, so I'll give you one.
Oh my.
So what's the important thing you need to tell me?
It's about the acting by Hagino-san, the main character.
Unlike Ryu** Asakura, his acting is cheerful and worth a watch.
Have a good watch when you go home.
Yes, thank you, Wataru-kun.
Sir?
What are you doing out here?
Yeah, well...
Hey, what's this?
Um, I felt bad for forgetting about it, so...
I can smell the scent of a female that's not mine.
Huh?
You didn't possibly bring a girl in while I was away and...
...do anything naughty...
No!
It's a present for you! This yukata!
Eh? Why?
Well, since I didn't have enough money, I couldn't buy a furisode,
and I had forgotten to get you a present for your birthday.
And I thought that's why you were down recently.
I was wondering what color I should get for my new cell phone.
Huh?!
Oh well.
Good grief. It wasn't a present for Isumi.
I see.
And did you lend him the money, after all?
No, he said it's pointless unless he buys it with his own money, so he bought a cheaper yukata instead of a furisode.
One that's about fifty thousand yen.
Fifty thousand?
That's not cheap at all.
By the way, that circular creature didn't appear.
See, it's all made up.
You're right.
Yes.
What was that?
Did a missile come flying from somewhere?
It's a fireworks show nearby.
Fireworks, eh?
Can't miss these in summer.
All right, let's go out, Hayate.
Yes, Milady.
The grilled squid is the best thing in the summer.
You look great in that yukata.
Thank you very much, Sir.
Maybe a new misunderstanding has arisen.
Come on, hurry.
It's beautiful, Hayate.
Yes.
Roach.
Next week, the dragon and the hamster go head-to-head for their loved one with their pride at stake.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
I'm the Red Cross Killer, Sanzein Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
It's really getting hot these days.
Today's temperature at noon was over 30 degrees Celsius.
Please don't make things up.
We don't know if the broadcast date will be really hot or not.
The broadcast date differs depending on area, too.
Rather than that, what I want to say is
on a hot day like this, the best thing to do is sit...
...in a chilled room playing MMOs while listening to my character song.
You can't spend such an unhealthy summer vacation.
Bye bye.
All right, summer vacation starts today!
I'll play MMOs and watch anime and draw manga and fool around to my heart's content!
I think you do those even on school days.
Even though the summer break's started,
I don't feel cheerful at all.
I wonder what Hayate-kun's doing now.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
I Like Books, but Sing It, Great Submarine Castle.
Hey, you're the burglar hamster from sometime ago.
Who are you calling a burglar hamster?
The sign of the guardian guides me.