Since when were you...?
Water sploosh.
You know this?
I think I know, I don't think I know.
I don't think I know that I know.
I think I know
even though I don't think I know.
Which is it?!
Hey!
Hey, Spike, where the hell are we?!
- Isn't it Earth?
- Earth?
Hey, this ship was headed for Mars!
Why the hell are we on Earth
all of a sudden?!
- I don't know.
- Shit, this isn't funny.
While we're wasting time, our fugitive...
It was the first big one in a while.
- In any case, why the hell are we on--?
- Jet.
The women are gone.
Listen, if you lead me
to that "water sploosh" place,
I'll give you something good.
Good thing? What?
Something very tremendously
wonderfully good.
wonderfully good!
Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
This!
Water sploosh!
I knew I shouldn't have trusted you.
Hey, I found Ed!
Ed has been found?
What? You know them?
...35 point 38 point 0, 35 point 48
point 1, 35 point 48 point 2...
This! This! This!
- Hey, can I have your nails?
- Nails?
I'm collecting them! Can I, please?
Just the pinky will do!
...35 point 52 point 3, 35 point...
This! This!
- Come on, can I have it? Please?
- What are you guys?!
Hey!
Ed?!
Is that really you... Ed?
I'm sorry about that.
That's the best way
to make the kids listen.
It's all right.
Is Ed from this place?
She wandered in about five years ago.
Before I knew it, she was eating with us
as if it had always been that way.
And about three years ago,
she wandered away...
as if she was a cat or something.
I was wondering
how she was doing nowadays.
But I didn't think
she would suddenly appear.
All right, it's time to eat!
Dear Lord, up in the heaven.
Never mind the rest. Let's eat!
Let's eat!
I have to get going now.
What, you can stay longer, right?
- I'm actually looking for something.
- Ed knows where it is.
We just came here for food.
You...
You have to give me something good!
Oh, yeah, Ed.
There's something good
in the desk drawer over there.
- Something good?
- Go get it.
Something good!
Inside that drawer.
Not that.
Yeah, that. Open it!
Her father.
Whose?
He came looking for Ed
about two months ago.
He said he forgot
that he had put her in an orphanage,
and that he had been looking for 7 years,
hopping around the world.
I hope she will be able to meet him.
People have to cherish
what ties they have.
Yeah!
Are you Faye?
Impossible.
Really?
It's me, Sally Yung!
I was in your high school
graduating class!
Are you all right?
I was really surprised.
I thought you were a ghost.
You look just like you did back then.
You know, they say ghosts appear
in places where they have regrets.
Oh, yeah, I remember now.
You were put in cold sleep
after that accident.
- That's why you still look the same.
- Accident?
Faye... you don't remember?
I...
Grandma!
Grandma, we gotta go back now.
Is it that time already?
Do you know who this is?
I bet you don't know.
- Actually, she's--
- A ghost.
Goodbye. Take care.
Hey, you guys! What's with
the course change without asking?!
Our plans have all been screwed
because of it!
I don't appreciate
you doing things on your own!
You want to smell something really good?
What's with them?
What are they being so secretive about?
Leave them alone.
Maybe they're too hungry
for their own good.
Humans go insane if they don't eat food.
Fifty million?
I see. Pretty big.
"Appledelhi Siniz Hesap Lutfen."
Would you like one, Mackenroe?
That's McIntire.
No, thank you, Mr. Appledelhi.
You sure? Eggs are good.
As they say, power and charge.
That's what's important, Macintosh.
That's McIntire.
Why is it that you can't ever remember
your assistant's name?
Don't worry
about the small things in life.
- Hurry, Macky-Mike!
- That's McIntire!
Watch where you're going!
Hey.
Sorry.
Sorry?
I...
I have to go.
Going out? Where are you going?
I finally remembered where I belong.
Where you belong?
You have someone waiting for you, too.
You have somewhere you belong.
You should go look for it, too.
That's the best thing, you know.
This one is a piece of cake.
Fifty million is right there!
If they can eat sukiyaki filled with meat,
then they--
Faye went out.
Again?
Where the hell did she go this time?
"A woman's heart
and the skies of Ganymede," was it?
You're Appledelhi?
Can you come along with us?
Cooperate with us
if you don't wanna get hurt.
Who are you guys?
Don't interrupt our work!
Work?
What does this Earth need
to regain a peaceful peace?
This Earth of wild chaos!
Is it the cosmos?
That is a map! A map!
Yes, happiness comes
in the form of a map!
We are creating maps to save the Earth!
A map?
But meteors fall often
and change the landscape.
That's why we're globetrotting.
We're chasing after every meteor.
Until every single meteor falls to Earth!
Enough with the excuses!
You!
I wasn't expecting someone this adept.
- Is that you, Ed?!
- That's enough! Stop!
Françoise!
How's that? And that, and that?
This is father-person.
Father?
Your father?
She had such a thing?
This is Spike-person and Jet-person.
I see.
No, father. Good people.
Oh? I see.
Thank you for taking care of my son.
Or was it daughter?
Oh ,well. It's all right either way.
That's a token of my appreciation.
Then, Ed, were you the one
who put the bounty on...?
Fifty point zero, zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero?
Only 50 woolongs?
So, you wanna come with me?
Hurry, Michael-duck!
That's McIntire!
Hey, wait!
Father!
He's gone.
Hey, it's dinnertime.
Spike, dinner.
You can't come with me, Ein.
Ed is going someplace far, far away.
I might not be coming back.
So, Ein, you should go back home.
Do you want to come with Ed?
Let's go, Ein!
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
Everything has a beginning and an end.
Life is just a cycle of them.
With unwanted endings, becoming an adult
is to experience the inevitable finale.
It's been a fast trip for Bebop,
with only two episodes left.
But make sure you pay close attention
to how it ends.
Next episode:
"The Real Folk Blues Part 1."