A... ki... ra...
That was nasty, Aki-lovely.
I'm shaking with fear!
I have to... continue battling.
Huh?
Selector battles...
Oh?
What's your wish?
I want Ulith's wound to heal soon...
Leave it to Rurun!
Aki-lucky...
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
Hitoe, are you okay? Does it hurt anywhere?
Mom
Re: Sorry for Making You Worried
I'm just glad you're all right.
Be sure to come home
early next time so you don't
inconvenience Kominato-san.
I'm fine now. I was mostly just surprised back there.
I'm sorry. It's my fault...
No, I'm sorry, too.
You went through so much because of me...
Don't say that!
And Iona-san had to recall all those bitter memories, too...
How softhearted can you get?
We were originally created by Mayu.
So you have every reason to say that
we're the origin of all Selector battles.
But wasn't it actually just Mayu who—
And you girls have every right to hate me!
So why are you saying all that...
I can't forgive that girl Mayu... or at least I shouldn't.
But you know, my life was really painful before I became friends with Ruuko and Yuzuki.
Whenever I went for a stroll through town, everyone I saw around me seemed to be having so much fun,
and it felt like I was the only one in the world who was alone.
But when I heard what Iona-san said,
I understood how Mayu couldn't even tell what it meant to be alone.
Oh.
That could be it, I guess.
What do you mean?
Mayu's... true wish.
Her true wish?
There's something that bothered me.
Why did Mayu make the rules for
Selector battles the way they are?
The winner gets her wish taken from her
and is sealed inside a card.
That's an awful thing, but it doesn't exactly feel like revenge.
You know...
It's fine when we're all talking like this,
but it gets really lonely inside the card.
Really, really lonely.
Maybe Mayu wants everyone to know how that kind of loneliness feels.
Yuzuki...
I'm so sorry I made you feel like that! I'll hold you tight from now on,
even when I go to sleep!
It's fine! It's fine!
C'mon, stop doing that! You're making me sweat!
Iona...
I can't believe it.
Even with all those things you girls went through, you can't bring yourselves to resent Mayu.
Well, that's not entirely true.
But I guess we feel that way
because of Tama and you.
I mean, if you two are Mayu herself,
I can't really imagine her to be such a bad person.
Tama... and me?
You're both our friends, aren't you?
That's why I believe that Mayu will understand us if we speak to her from the bottom of our hearts.
My heart is aching.
It must be because I embraced this feeling even though I reign the darkness.
But as much as it pains me, it also warms me.
I want to keep holding it close.
It's strange!
It's so strange!
It's all so strange!
Kuro's not the same anymore.
Selector battles need
radiant light and deep darkness.
Let's burn this useless LRIG card of darkness.
Okay, Shiro?
That's some preferential treatment, huh...
A private hospital room for a mere scratch?
Guess that comes with the Urazoe name.
Are you okay, Ulith?
This'll heal in a matter of days.
Say, mind if I ask you something?
Iona passed through many Selectors' hands
as the LRIG of Darkness.
Where have you been before you ended up as Ruu's card?
Well...
All I remember is being with Ruu.
I forgot about Mayu and everything that happened before.
But when I met Ruu,
I felt like I was born just so I could meet Ruu.
I see.
Now I know how Mayu feels.
Mayu wanted to dispose of you like the vomit you are.
She was disgusted by that hypocritical desire
for the light that constipated her bowels.
That's why she put you into Ruuko's hands first.
After all, she's a terrifying girl.
The girl who can destroy it all.
Chiyori? What are you going to do now?
What do you mean?
"I know the truth behind the battles now,
but that won't faze me!"
"I'm gonna go look for my next battle straight away!"
Wouldn't that be your usual script now?
Such evil.
Huh?
I finally get what these Selector battles are all about!
Win or lose, all that waits for you is hell.
And someone like you wouldn't think twice throwing a person down into that inescapable, incessant hell!
Well, you've got to protect yourself.
Come on, don't you remember what you said?
Your wish is to enter the world of WIXOSS, right?
That's perfect then, no?
Guess you're right...
But if I lose again, I won't be able to battle anymore.
Well, just turn your brain off.
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it.
Guess you're right...
By the way, weren't you a human too, Eldora?
What was your wish?
Huh? Oh...
I forgot.
You're lying!
You bet I am!
I just don't want to tell you, Chiyori.
What was that?!
It was nothing much.
Yeah, now that I think about it,
my wish was nothing much, really.
But I was pretty serious about it back then.
In any case, we need to speak with Tama-chan, right?
But will you be okay meeting Ulith, Hitoe?
Good point.
Ruuko and I can go without you.
It's okay.
After all, this is to meet Tama-chan. That's—
New Mail
1 Message
Maybe it's Ulith!
Please battle against me!
Huh?
I don't care who my opponent is, just please battle against me!
W-Wait a second! Chiyori-san,
if you lose one more time, you...
Justice will prevail!
So, I'm... evil?
You still don't understand anything even after we've met Fumio?
Well, then...
How about doing it with me?
Hey, battle me.
I sense an unusual evildoer aura...
A-Akira-san!
Sure, alright.
Huh?!
Let's get this show on the road.
Hey, Eldora! What are you thinking, making a call without your Selector?
Oh? So you're scared of losing?
Heck no!
Alright then! Onwards to battle!
I'm gonna bring this one home!
No!
We can't let this happen!
Stop!
Wait... Wai—
Wait the hell up!
You little goddamn...
Akira-san's... not coming after us... right?
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Why are you getting in my way?!
But—
If you really want to battle, then we won't stop you.
But you could be a bit more careful choosing—
It doesn't matter a bit who we choose.
Yup! No matter who it is, I'm gonna win, y'know?
Oho! Pretty bold, coming from a girl with two losses to her name.
Hmph! Once I win, it's gonna be bye-bye, Eldora!
Now that's good news if I ever heard some!
Wha—?! Why you...!
I'll... battle Chiyori-san.
Huh?
What?!
Chiyori lost twice already! One more, and...
You know what that means, don't you?
Her wish will be reversed.
Hitoe?
I understand.
I'm doing this because Chiyori-san can only lose once more.
Don't tell me you're planning to gift her a win!
No.
Before my wish was reversed with
my third loss, Midoriko said to me...
Hitoe! Please, throw me away!
Midoriko... Even at the cost of her chance to be human again,
she wanted me to stay together with my friends forever.
My wish... I thought it was something I needed for my happiness.
But Chiyori-san's wish is...
Oh, just shut it!
You're taking the words right out of my mouth!
Once I become the heroine of the WIXOSS world,
you'll get what you deserve!
You think so? C'mon, bring it!
I see. If visiting Fumio wasn't enough
to stop her, then we might as well...
If Chiyori-san wins, then it's another story.
But if I win, I can prevent her wish from coming true.
The thought of what would happen to her if her wish was reversed is bothering me, though.
Chiyori-san's wish is based on her attachment to WIXOSS.
If it's just a matter of her forgetting about WIXOSS,
then it shouldn't make her situation any worse.
Argh! Now you've made me mad!
I'm gonna win for real! Our way's coming to an end with this last battle, Eldora!
Sure, sure...
Um?
I'm okay with fighting you, Chiyori-san.
Yay! It's a battle!
Finally, finally!
May the first step towards the birth of WIXOSS's new heroine be engraved in the history books today!
Let's begin.
That's what I was waiting for!
Open!
A battle field... is opening.
Looks like there are girls other than us
who are seeking battles at this very moment.
Are you going to battle?
Doesn't it hurt?
Well, of course it still hurts a little.
But the pain will soon fade.
I'm going to win the battle.
I've gathered enough wins, so just one more will make my wish come true.
I'll become a LRIG again.
And you...
will come outside and inherit Urazoe Iona's body.
I'll... turn into Iona?
You want to be Ruuko's friend and equal, don't you?
Isn't that what you wish for?
If so, our interests should be mutual.
If we win the battle, this body will be yours.
You can be friends with Ruu.
Not as a LRIG, but as a fellow human being.
Here we go!
Chiyori Moonlight Chorizo!
That move's got a real name, too!
Not half bad, Chorizo.
Are you okay, Yuzuki?
Of course!
After all, we definitely can't lose this battle!
Yuzuki. Grow!
Eldora and Yuzuki are both strong!
But the match is decided already.
Yeah...
Yuzuki's deck is red and has cards with the ability to burn her opponent's Ener.
The odds are totally stacked against Chiyori-san...
Chiyori probably doesn't know that.
But there's no way Eldora, as a LRIG, is unaware of it.
Wait...
N-No, I'm losing...
I'm totally gonna lose if this keeps up!
Chiyori! Your command!
B-But...
What does it matter if you lose?
Huh?
You're going to retire from Selector battles and go back to being a normal girl.
Eldora-san...
I knew it. Eldora was thinking of the same thing as Hitoe!
She wants to save Chiyori-san from the suffering of these battles.
Wh-What are you saying, Eldora?!
Excuse me!
Well, it's probably a tad bit weird to ask this during a battle,
but would you still be friends with this girl even I lose?
What?!
She's dressed all funny now, but you wouldn't believe how plain she looked back when I met her!
H-Hey! Eldora!
Th-The card spoke...?
My name is Eldora.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
So cute!
She's super cute!
Shh!
Hey, look here! It's so Eldora!
Trying to mimic me?
Seeing girls wearing matching clothes is totally creepy.
Oh, come on. If you hate it so much, then wear something else, Eldora!
I'm just paper, so no can do!
Then I'm gonna draw you
some clothes with my marker!
Time to draw!
Stop it! W-Wa—
She can be a handful, but I was glad she became my Selector.
She might be a bit soft in the head,
but she's not a bad person at all, really.
Eldora...
You were planning to lose this fight from the beginning, weren't you?
E-Eldora?!
I thought we couldn't win, that's all.
Not like LRIGs can sway the end results or anything.
That's mean! You didn't tell me anything about that!
There's that evil Eldora again!
Sure, evil. I'm evil, like you said.
And that's why
we shouldn't be together.
I was glad I became your LRIG, but only at the start.
You're so thoughtless, stupid,
dim-witted, and hopelessly carefree.
Eldora?
And I...
just want you to stay like that, y'know?
Eldora...
Alright, Yuzuki-san. Let's get this over with!
What's gonna be your next move? Orochi?
Look, you've got enough of them Eners,
so you might as well drill it home with an Art!
Hold it!
Chiyori?
It's... it's not over yet!
Get working, brain!
You better come up with a way to turn the tables!
If you don't, I...
I'll be separated from Eldora!
Ah! I got it!
Check their Life Cloth with Spell: PLUS RUSH!
Direct damage with Arts: Cloth Crush Flash!
Chiyori, that attack—
Go!
is meaningless.
Our attacks aren't as much as touching Hitoe-san right now.
If you don't pull a Scylla within three turns, Hitoe-san will win.
Eldora-san...
Now hold on! You better not pull any obvious losing moves here.
I want to turn back into a human, y'know?
But that won't ever happen as long as I'm stuck with a scrub like Chiyori.
Eldora...
Let's keep trucking on, Chiyori!
You still have a chance to win if you turn over a Burst.
Turn End.
Orochi! Echidna! Attack!
Eldora!
It's your turn now, Chiyori...
No... No! Eldora!
I'm not going to forget...
Turn End.
I'm never, ever going to forget!
Listen, Eldora!
Once I enter the WIXOSS world,
I'm making you my subordinate!
Orochi. Attack.
Eldora!
Chiyori...
Hurry...
This is the last turn.
No... No...
Chiyori!
Chiyori.
I really did love you.
Turn End.
That's it.
All that's left for us is to wait for the finishing blow.
You're late, Aki-lovely.
That ain't me.
I'm Aoi Akira now.
The one who will beat and save you.
That
Parting
is
Abrupt
Aoi Akira.
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
Shut up... Shut up... Shut up!
What's that? It's wrong.
It's definitely wrong!
Otherwise, that's absolutely and completely wrong!
This warmth is limited.
This
Warmth
is
Limited