The Vajra Giant, Bishamaru!
The Vajra Giant
Bishamaru
The city of Kyoto is bathed in light.
To the evil shadows who disturb
the city's peace, take this!
With a mighty punch!
Punch!
And a thunderous kick!
Kick!
But you must never forget, no no,
the righteous controller—
controller—controller—controller—
Gone.
Gone, gone!
Gone, gone, gone!
Gone, gone, gone, gone, gone, gone, gone, gone!
It's gone!
Kyouso Giga
What is?
Shouko,
the Scientist, Raves and Panics
the Scientist, Raves
Shouko,
the Scientist, Raves and Panics
the Scientist, Raves
My controller, you nincompoop!
Shouko,
the Scientist, Raves and Panics
the Scientist, Raves
Shouko,
the Scientist, Raves and Panics
the Scientist, Raves
Out of
service
Miyakoi
How are you today, Shouko?
In the pits.
Call the Four Symbols.
Miyakoi
Looking for something again?
The Four Symbols Appeared!
Azure Dragon Aoi
White Tiger Haku
Vermilion Bird Shushu
Black Tortoise Zakuro
Ready to search, ma'am!
Yeah, get to it.
What's that?
A replacement.
Once you install the OS, it'll be the same.
You nitwit.
This is why I told you to put a GPS tracker on it...
Why would I need that?
It's not like I'd lose it.
Not here... Not here...
Besides, I remember having it yesterday morning.
Yesterday, before noon...
March Diner
Time to eat!
De'ishus!
Don't talk with your mouth full.
Elbows off!
I want more tsuyu!
Go get it yourself.
Did someone knock?
Nobody's home!
Bring me the Three Stooges.
It's Shouko-chan.
The gamer girl!
Ah, the geek.
Shut it!
Where is my controller?
Don't think I'm not wise to you!
What happened?
I can't understand a word you're saying! Did you hit your head?
You blithering stooge!
If you wanna play, do it
outside!
Kurama Temple is currently conducting an impromptu safety inspection.
Kurama again?
Notice from Kurama Temple
This Area
Under Inspection
What is it now?
We ask for your kind cooperation in this matter.
Under Inspection
Thank you
for your cooperation
Once again:
Inspection 1 hour only!
Kurama Temple is currently conducting an impromptu safety inspection...
The human districts are always loud and chaotic,
but there appears to be a bigger ruckus than usual today.
Yase Douji?
Look at the lot of you,
running around playing all day.
Do people of Kurama Temple have nothing better to do?
Well pardon me!
If I may inquire, are you preparing for another tea party, Yase Douji?
I'm sure it's lovely to be a shut-in
with no cares and plenty of money!
Hey! You there, bird!
Excuse me, Yase Douji.
Hold it right there!
Left at next intersection.
Intercepting.
All right!
Ushiwaka
I-It's not mine.
Darn it!
Where did it go?
Where is my controller?
Yes, hello?
Is this the March Diner?
Yes.
Oh, no. It was our pleasure.
Actually, there's something
I'd like to inquire about...
Saba Kaido
Bar
Cheers.
Aw shucks, thanks guys!
Good work!
Especially you, Fushimi! Very impressive!
I always knew you could do it if you put your mind to it!
By the way, how?
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Wake
Cry
Saba Kaido Bar
Don't tell her.
She'd snap at me.
Let loose. Let loose.
Yeah, let loose! Anything goes!
Con-trol-ler! Con-trol-ler!
See, aren't you glad I put that GPS tracker on?