When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
We'll be going now, Maria-san.
Have a good day.
Oh yeah, Maria.
If you have time, can you rent these DVDs from Wataru's place?
I will. It's cold today, so take care of yourself.
No worries. The battle plan is already made.
It really is cold today.
Huh? Where's Milady?
Hey, eyes front! The wind will hit me directly, otherwise!
What?
You're very clever, Milady.
Good morning, Hinagiku-san.
What's wrong with you, spacing out like that?
Hinagiku-san!
I'm sorry. Something was on my mind.
Could it be that the Superintendent, the walking hazard producer, started something again?
Oh no. The Superintendent should be down on a southern island, enjoying her vacation.
Kuzuha-sama, say "Ah..."
We didn't have to come all the way here just to eat rice cakes, did we?
It's for the sake of good luck.
Th-Then what could be bothering you?
Well, Onee-chan gave me a New Year's allowance.
WHAT?!
Katsura-sensei gave you a New Year's allowance?
She came over yesterday and left this on my desk.
Although, there was only ¥500 inside.
¥500?
Oh, that little?
That's a fortune!
I've only gotten azuki beans or peanuts.
Good morning!
Hey there. If you chitchat too long, you'll be late to school.
I'm going to arrest you, you know.
Bad boy.
Sh-She's totally different from usual!
Did you all know there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
K-Katsura-sensei is acting differently than usual!
She looks dazzling.
What happened to you, Onee-chan?
What's wrong, you three?
No, how should I put it...
Your total change is getting to us.
Did you perhaps eat grass
from the turf or a laughing mushroom?
Why do you ask that?
"Why?" Obviously that's because...
It's just... It's just that today's a very special day for me.
Special day?
The morning staff meeting is coming up soon, so I'll see you later.
This is...
Katsura-chan's quitting?
Yes. That seems to be the case.
What should we do?
What's so funny?
Because that's totally impossible.
Yukiji would never quit being a teacher.
Yeah. Where would she live if she quits from here?
But she's been acting strangely since this morning,
and she said today's a special day or something,
and she even gave Hinagiku-san a New Year's allowance.
Maybe she's planning to quit from Hakuou
and go somewhere far away.
No way!
If what you said is true, I'll go shave my head.
I'll change my name to Men Taiko.
Mentaiko = Spicy egg roe
Then I'll change this anime's title to Yamabiko no Gotoku!
Yamabiko = The echo you hear back in the mountains
You have no right to!
But, if you actually saw her letter of resignation, then I'd be convinced.
Exactly.
N-No way!
It was true?!
If you had picked it up, you should have said so!
Katsura-chan!
Hey, do you need something?
You're not going to call it quits as a teacher, are you?
It's a prank, right?
Tell us it's a joke!
Yeah, calling it quits.
Are you serious?
Yes. Today's the last day.
Today?! Isn't that too sudden?
I'm sorry. It was a little hard to bring it up with you all.
You're joking right, Onee-chan?
Hina.
What is there to do after one quits being a teacher?
There are plenty of things to do out there.
Go on a journey or even start a new life.
Why? Why did you not tell such an important thing to anyone?
She's right, Katsura-chan. You're being such a stranger.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Why didn't you even ask for a little advice?
I'm a fully-grown adult, so why should I come looking for advice for something like this?
Don't worry. It's a conclusion that was reached after much thought.
Katsura-sensei!
I apologize for surprising you all.
But...
Goodbyes come suddenly and unannounced.
Sadly, life is filled with sudden goodbyes.
You'd never find dandelions in the winter.
Oh Marilla, when you're truly sad, tears don't come, do they?
Sudden goodbyes...
But in exchange, I'll never leave you.
I'm sorry, Matthew.
But not a single tear is coming out.
You idiot, Onee-chan!
I don't care about you!
You can go die on the street of nowhere!
H-Hinagiku-san!
Hina...
Hina. It's about time you came home.
Hey, look at how much New Year's allowance I got.
I got some, too.
This is from Daddy, and this is Mommy.
This is from Grandma, and this is Grandpa.
Hina.
Oh, Onee-chan.
I just remembered that I haven't given you your New Year's allowance yet.
Stick your hand out.
Here.
You'll have to let me off the hook with that this year.
But in exchange, I'll never leave you.
Really?
Of course, full course!
I'll give you a piggy back ride, so let's go home.
Yup!
Onee-chan, you liar!
Rukkorasetto.
Rukkorasetto = Up I go.
Toshi niha katenai none.
Toshi niha katenai none = Looks like you can't beat growing up.
I never thought Katsura-chan would really quit.
I still can't believe it.
Despite everything we've done to her,
she's taken care of us a lot.
How do we fight against homework and tests from now on?
Looks like everyone's very shocked.
But there's something I don't understand.
This is too much to be one of her spur of the moment things.
Yes, but the truth is the truth.
I wish I could attend one more of her world history classes.
Yeah, yeah.
Right, the next homeroom period will be the goodbye with Katsura-sensei.
Oh yeah, homeroom!
We'll now start the homeroom period.
Let's see, today's agenda is...
Yes! Katsura-sensei!
I have a question regarding the rise and fall of the Frankish Empire, so could you give a lecture?
I request the Reconquista events that happened in Spain during the Middle Ages.
What were the four historically important apples?
Is it true Pythagoras was allergic to horse beans?
Is it true that an Englishman invented the ready-made curry pack?
We have so many more questions, so please answer them all.
You guys...
All right, you got it!
Yay!
We've got to enjoy Yukiji's last class.
Listen, this is an important part.
1806, Continental Blockade!
Make sure you remember it.
Katsura-sensei's lecture goes at a good tempo as usual.
She looks like a she doesn't have herself together, but she's actually good at teaching.
By the way, did you know that Napoleon was into fortune telling.
She even tells us things you don't learn from textbooks.
It's a simple thing where you hold a coin
in your left hand and flip a crepe in the frying pan.
He did that five times and failed the fifth one.
This was in 1812. The year the French invasion of Russia failed.
After this class...
We won't be able to experience it anymore...
This is important, too, okay?
Make sure you review it from your textbook later.
By the way, the reason Napoleon keeps his right hand in pocket is-
What? Why are you crying, Segawa-san?
You idiot! Don't cry!
No, this isn't tears. It's hot water from last night's bath.
Huh?
I get it. So you've all finally understood that history is made with tears on top of tears.
Meetings and farewells. And then yet another meeting.
The links between people are what make history.
Yes!
The character "people" is made
with two people supporting each other!
Yes! People can't live alone!
Can't...
Live alone...
If Onee-chan were to disappear...
No one in this world lives alone.
Even if they are far apart,
they're always connected by their hearts.
That's what I believe.
I want you all to understand that, too.
Please don't forget.
Tears are the sweat your heart perspires.
And love is the work your heart does.
That's the end of the lecture.
Thank you, everyone!
Don't go, Onee-chan!
Don't quit, Sensei!
There are so many more things we want to learn!
So many more things we want to do, too!
Sensei!
If you leave, my life-threatening experiences will decrease, and it won't be as enjoyable as it has been!
What are you all saying?
Do you still plan to leave us?
At least stay until we graduate!
Please promise us!
"Promise?"
Maybe this is...
Hey, everyone?
Sensei! Don't quit!
Thank you, everyone!
I'm so happy to know that you all cared about me so much!
Being a teacher was so much harder than I'd thought.
Sorry. And there's one more shop to visit, too.
Please get up.
So I gave my letter of resignation to Katsura-sensei.
Letter of resignation?
Would that be this?
Yes, that.
Sorry, I forgot to turn it in to the Superintendent.
Thank you very much!
Seeing your class, I was able to learn how amazing the bond between students and teachers can be.
Everyone! Forgive me for not noticing your love!
What is going on?
This is so touching.
Um...
What is it?
Um, we're having a storm of "Why?" in the class.
Were you quitting, Yukiji?
Why would I quit?
Then what was the unnatural dazzling smiley aura you were emitting from the morning about?
Ah, that'd be because it's been such a lucky day since the moment I woke up!
Shut up.
Saeki Nobuko-sensei's fortune telling for today!
Congratulations! You Scorpios have the best luck!
Especially those who are of blood type B,
love alcohol, and have a long pinky toe nail.
It's your luckiest day that comes only once every twelve years.
None of this is ever true.
Th-The tea stalk is standing!
Twin egg?!
They all have eyebrows!
It's the angel!
D-Double red sea bream!
That's how it went!
Don't you think it's amazing?
Makes me so happy, super happy, out of my mind, you know?
Wh-What did you say?
Look at these. These are the proof.
No wonder Napoleon believed in fortune telling.
I apologize for all the confusing reactions my stupid sister has caused!
Looks like we jumped the gun, too.
I knew something was strange from the start.
What were all the tears we shed for?
You will have to make up for this.
Yeah! Do fifty years worth of our homework!
What did I do?
I'll never believe in fortune telling!
That's how the unwed female teacher's heart rotted further.
Oh, then what's the meaning behind her giving Hinagiku-san the New Year allowance?
The mystery to that has been already solved.
Damn it, why don't you all just bring spears or guns for all I care, damn it.
She really needs so much attention.
One day, I will actually give you
a New Year's allowance, all right?
When is "one day?"
Next year.
Actually, I don't have much confidence that I can.
Three years...
Ten years?
I'll definitely give you one ten years from now.
Let's see, Pirates of the Beach and Man Spider 3.
Here we go.
Thank you as always.
Remind Nagi to pay attention to the return date.
I will.
Maria-san.
Please take these with you.
But...
Please don't worry. My grandmother sent a whole bunch.
Th-These are...
These are still being manufactured?
Actually, where is Saki-san's grandmother now?
Hey.
What should I do...
While I couldn't decide if I should send a New Year's card to Hayate-kun or not, the New Year's already come.
Besides, didn't I set this year's resolution to become a mature woman with confidence?!
No, I'll do it tomorrow.
Ow.
What's this?
You picking a fight with us?
What should I do? Am I going to be killed?
Are you listening to me? I'll beat you up or else!
You'll be dead meat if you look down on us!
Why do I always fall into pinches like this?
You've got nerve picking a fight with us.
Ah, that's right, you are Nishizawa-san, right?
Hayate-kun's friend, correct?
Thank you so much for letting Nagi sleep over last year.
It's nothing.
As you can tell, she's a difficult girl in some ways, but I hope you'll be good friends with her.
Y-Yes.
Oh, who might these people be?
Are they your friends, Nishizawa-san?
Why does it look like that to you?
What the hell are you?
A maid?
Just because you're a little cute maid, don't try to ignore us.
I'm sorry, I don't understand the Cre*in language.
We're speaking Japanese, asshole!
If you look down on us, even if you're a cute maid, we won't forgive you.
You are quite inelegant to try to grab a female's chest without cause.
Wh-What was that?
A simple self-defense move.
Although, I can only use it as a surprise attack.
You bitch.
You won't get off the hook now!
I suggest you stop.
You will not leave with just injuries otherwise.
Shut up!
See?
No! Help!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes. Thank you very much.
That's all right.
On another note, this.
You dropped it.
T-Th-This is nothing!
It's nothing.
I hope this will be a good year for you, Nishizawa-san.
Oh yeah. If you'd like, take this with you.
I'll see you again.
Nishizawa-san wishes to become like her.
Did anything new happen at school?
Nothing really.
How about you, Maria-san?
No, nothing in particular.
I wonder why. All of a sudden I feel like eating marshmallows.
Next week, we'll fight against sine, cosine, and tangent.
Katsura Yukiji's
Butler Network!
Hey there. It's your sexy teacher, Katsura Yukiji.
Listen, everyone; my character song is finally done!
I got nervous over my first recording,
but I did my best for the sake of my fans.
What are you doing, Onee-chan?
Oh, Hina, you were here?
Don't give me that.
We rehearsed last night regarding what to do here together, remember?
Did we?
Anyways, Hina's singing in my song, too, so make sure you buy it.
See you later!
Bye bye.
Does he have any weaknesses?
Weaknesses?
Manga or anime main characters usually come with weaknesses as a default setting.
Do they?
The debt-ridden butler's weaknesses, eh?
All right, leave it to me. Guys like that have surprising weaknesses.
Next time, Just like Dogs, Rats, and Bulldogs.
I have a good idea.
What's your plan?
That's...
Next time, come with equipment equipped.