I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
Kida-kun! It's really you?
Lately, there aren't as many color gangs.
They picked a fight with Saitama,
and a bunch got arrested.
I'm Sonohara Anri.
Nice to meet you all.
Harima-san!
Sorry! I mistook you!
You swore you'd become a
true Ikebukuroian, right?
Overcome these trials!
I've found you!
My love...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
I'll give it back. I'll give it back!
Please forgive me.
Advertising
False
This is bad.
Really bad...
It's my fault, Celty.
I took a stupid job!
The job was supposed to be over quickly.
And just by chance, it appeared.
Inhuman!
Monster! Monster! Monster!
You heard words coming from the wound?
It called me a monster.
How rude!
I prefer the term "naughty lady."
What is it?
What if it's an alien?
Celty...
Am I supposed to laugh at that?
A-A monster!
Let's go!
It sometimes seems this town is made
of jokes, whims, and coincidences.
SinSong-san joined the room.
strong
human
wish
love
wish love human
Is wish I do strong person so human love is.
Wish is is I do so so so
I
I, so, wish
...
strong, human
wish
I, love
so
And this situation is probably
one of God's whims or jokes, too.
Here I am, walking home with
a top-class glasses-girl,
one of the top five of
the thirty-seven girls
I fell in love with during the
entrance ceremony...
And then that clod shows up.
Sucks.
It must've been hard back there.
Oh, yeah.
This isn't working...
Man, I didn't think you'd
get to her before me.
That's not what happened!
No way!
Mikado!
But it worked out fine.
If I were in your position,
I wouldn't have let that chance go.
The two of us would be speaking
of love together in West Gate Park.
So yeah, go out with me!
Kida-kun?
Um, I-
Oh, you don't need to answer right away.
I'm waiting for responses from seven girls,
and I'm still figuring out
which I want to date.
Sonohara-san, don't worry about him.
You'll just get tired.
And he may look like a playboy,
but he's actually not.
Even when he goes to pick up girls, he-
Hey, Mikado!
This guy, Ryuugamine Mikado,
is my best friend.
He's from the country and has only been
in Ikebukuro a few days.
He's very naïve, but strangely
stubborn somehow,
the kind of guy you can't just leave alone.
And this pure boy and I find ourselves
in a surprising love triangle...
Is this what they call youth?
Ow...
You two are good friends, aren't you?
Yes, we are.
Not that I don't wish to be rid of him...
As for how this happened,
it goes back to the day of
the entrance ceremony.
Yagiri Seiji.
Nice to meet you.
Then, Yagiri... Get to your seat.
No.
I don't think I'll be able to come
to school for a while.
No, I may never come back.
This is an extremely important
matter to me.
I don't have time to spend
on you people.
Goodbye.
Hey, Yagiri, wait. Wait!
I was thinking it takes all
types to make a world,
when Mikado told me about it.
Wait!
And that was the moment I fell in love!
Cute smile and great boobs.
Wait, she wasn't smiling.
I said to leave me alone!
Wait!
Excuse me...
Something wrong?
Anyway, she found herself at the very top
of my candidate-for-girlfriend
list, and today...
Hey, Sonohara.
Heading home now?
Yeah.
Hey, Sonohara...
Is something bothering you?
Are you being bullied or caught
up in some trouble?
No.
If something happens, tell me right away.
I'm fine.
I see.
Come to think of it, has Harima
not come to school yet?
Even though you're finally
in the same class...
It was tough, getting them into your class.
Saitou-sensei, from your middle school,
told me to take good care of you.
So don't worry.
I know. I'll take you home today.
You heard the Slasher struck
again in Ikebukuro, right?
Nasujima-sensei, are you sexually
harassing a student?
Wow, you're flirting with
the poor little class rep?
If that's not sexual harassment,
I don't know what is!
Or maybe it's more like sexy
хорошо, am I right?
Note: Russian for "good." Can be used to describe a "good-looking man."
Sometimes written as "horosho" in English.
Kida, don't be stupid!
Sonohara, don't get the wrong
idea and spread any rumors.
Does she look like the type who would?
Th-That's true.
Thanks!
I'll take care of spreading
the rumors, so don't worry!
Totally heroic...
Aren't I awesome?
She's gotta be in love, right?
Kida-kun? Sonohara-san?
Did you seriously just show up now?
Here you go.
All yours.
Thank you.
Seriously, though, be careful.
That Nasujima... Most of it's just rumors,
but he really did go after one student.
What?
Her name's Niekawa Haruna,
a year ahead of us.
She transferred in during
second semester last year,
and they say it almost got out
that she was dating him.
Seriously?
Either she dropped out on her own,
or Nasujima threatened her,
or she transferred schools.
I don't know.
But if something happens,
Mikado and I will take care of it. Won't we?
Yeah.
I don't really understand what's going
on, but I'll do whatever I can.
Come on. You need to be like,
"I don't know what I can do,
but the power of love will aid me,"
or something like that.
Otherwise you're not a man.
That's not nice.
It's how this works.
Anyway, about what happened earlier...
Those girls bullying you,
they're from your middle school, right?
H-How could you tell?
Just from how they were talking.
Some strong girl saved you then,
but now that she's gone,
the same girls are back.
What was it again?
A friend of yours went missing?
So you haven't found her yet.
It's Harima Mika-san from
our class, isn't it?
They're treating it like she's
just absent from school,
but since before the start of school,
she hasn't come home once.
"Friends Forever"
Isn't this something for the cops?
I was contacted on my cell phone,
from her house.
She said she was going on a journey
to ease her pain, so not to worry.
Ease her pain?
Something happen?
Well, um... Don't be surprised, OK?
After these past few days,
not much would surprise me.
Harima-san is a stalker...
I see. So that guy you were
talking to earlier...
Mika-chan was stalking him...
No, she was deeply in love with him,
and she left on a trip because
he rejected her.
Gotta leave that to her family, then.
If it gets to be too long,
they'll contact the cops.
Was she close to you?
Why are you asking her that?
We were always together, yes.
He's got good intuition, actually.
I'm not really the social type,
so I don't get along with people well,
but she always dragged me along.
I felt bad when she chose the
same high school I did.
I—
You may be thinking that she
just didn't want to lose
someone who made her look better,
but you shouldn't say it, Mikado-kun.
I know.
What?
That she kept me around
to make her look better.
And I used her, too.
It was easier to live,
being dependant on her.
I thought I couldn't live
any other way.
But now, I don't think I really
need her anymore.
I'm used to it.
Her being gone, I mean.
The reason I became class rep is because
that's the job she wanted...
I figured I should do it in her place.
I thought if I could be class rep,
I might be able to overcome her.
It's not fair, is it?
I think it's more so to say
that to someone else.
It's like you're trying to
earn forgiveness for it.
You're right to want to
aim higher than her.
So, I think, maybe you should
have more pride in yourself.
Uh... Um...
You're right.
Thank you.
I actually like this aspect of him.
Kida-kun!
Man, you fail.
I fail?
What? The toughest in Ikebukuro?
Yeah, the toughest.
You with a magazine or something?
Like, what do you mean,
toughest? Hilarious.
Wouldn't that be like,
the guy on the black bike?
Yeah, I know that guy.
He's got no head, right?
No way!
Also, the Slasher.
Oh, that. Yeah.
But wouldn't the strongest
be the Dollars now?
The Dollars?
Yeah, the Dollars!
OK, then I'll be off.
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
See you, then!
Bye-bye, Anri-chan!
I was thinking, maybe that Yagiri-kun guy
and Mika are together, after all.
A stalker and her victim?
Maybe she kidnapped him or something.
I see.
Searching for someone... What do I do?
Ignore it.
She said she was fine now.
Maybe you'd need some
kind of organization...
Like the Dollars.
Mikado, don't tell me you want
to join the Dollars... Do you?
No way!
Seriously, give it up.
Color gangs are the kind of thing
you do in your youth,
and end up regretting later in life.
Yeah, but we're still young.
I was pretty down before Mikado
came to Ikebukuro.
I am who I am now because, well,
of a lot of people's help, including his.
He's just arrived in Ikebukuro,
and the city's too much for him.
It's incredibly dangerous.
I could cool him off. But looking at him,
with his eyes shining, I just can't.
So I'm trying to stay with
him as much as I can.
But honestly, I'd like to keep him away
from the darkness of this town.
And me, too...
Bang.
I promised myself I'd never
go there again.
Laila Medical University Hospital
SinSong-san joined the room.
stronger
strong love wish
wish is want
more strong love want
want to love strong person
want I mom mom
mom mom mom
mom mom mom mom
SinSong-san has left the room.
<Kanra>
A troll, you think?
Tanaka Tarou-san has joined the room.
Setton-san has joined the room.
Kanra-san has joined the room.
<Setton>
It was like an alien.
<Tanaka Tarou>
It might be laughing.
<Setton>
Scary.
<Tanaka Tarou>
You know, it was going
"haha" (mom).
<Setton>
No, I'm not scared of aliens. Just...
Setton-san has left the room.
SinSong?
Maybe those kanji could be read "Zaika."
Like "commodity"?
I'll look into it later.
Anyway, Celty, got a job for you.
From Shiki-san of the Awakusu again.
It's not great, but will you take it?
Another transporter job?
Yeah. Exactly.
But you have to get the thing back, too.
I didn't ask what it was.
Actually, it's better for both
parties that I don't.
Understood.
Anyway, about the goods,
the guy who's got them keeps moving.
But we've got a good idea
of where he hides,
so you should be able to
find him pretty quickly.
Roger.
The Slasher keeps showing
up, so be careful.
Slasher?
Yeah, the Slasher.
Showed up again.
They say it just shows up, beats 'em up,
and then leaves them alive.
That's not really the strongest, then.
The strongest would have to be...
Simon, the Russian sushi guy.
Or that info broker who
moved to Shinjuku.
Orihara Izaya.
Or maybe him!
Heiwajima Shizuo!
Which color gang is the strongest?
That'd be the Dollars.
They don't have a color.
The yellow ones were big
up till last year, though.
Yellow?
Yeah, the Yellow Scarves.
I heard they had a full-on fight
with a gang called Blue Square,
but it ended up crushing
both of them.
Nah, I hear they're back.
Step right up and order!
Engawa!
Scallops!
It's cheap! It's cheap!
Actually, don't you see
a lot of them lately?
See what?
The yellow ones, right?
You saw 'em, too?
Yellow ones. You can't mean...
The Yellow Rags!
Yellow Scarves, right?
Yeah, those guys!
That was Hermes, right?
No, they were wiped out in
the fight with Blue Square.
Yeah, their boss backed down.
Welcome!
Would you tell me about the Dollars?
Pardon?
A friend of mine's trying to get involved
with them, and I want to stop him.
Why ask us?
There's no one else I can ask.
Can't ask Orihara Izaya
about that, yeah...
We don't know much about them, either.
I'll tell you what we know, though.
Sometimes, this town feels like
it's going to swallow me up.
So, Mikado, I won't let you go there.
Mikado?
Sorry.
It's gonna take more than that...
You can tell we're Yellow
Scarves, can't you?
Yagiri-kun!
Huh?
It's not Harima Mika...
I don't know who you are,
but don't ruin our love escape.
Love escape...?
Let's go.
But who is that?
Kida-kun?
You really Yellow Scarves?
Of course we are.
I'm asking 'cause I don't know.
Why, you...
K-Kida-kun!
Hey, Mikado, why are you...?
M-Monster!
Let's go!
Man, you had me worried.
So did you!
In the end,
I guess I did, huh?
I may be the one who's dependant on him.
Ever since Mikado came here,
I feel like my false bravado's becoming real.
I might be able to see her now,
without running away...
Yes.
Even I feel that way sometimes.
I didn't think you'd come here again...
Izaya-san.
Hey.
How's he doing?
He comes by sometimes.
At least, up to there...
I'm back.
Haruna, did you eat?
Haruna?
<Kanra>
Yeah, so I banned the troll.
<Setton>
Now it'll be peaceful.
<Tanaka Tarou>
I hope so.
<Kanra>
Come to think of it, yesterday some of the
Yellow Scarves got hit by the Slasher.
<Tanaka Tarou>
What are the Yellow Scarves?
<Kanra>
Think the Slasher works
for the Dollars?
<Tanaka Tarou>
No way!
There might be a war brewing.
<Kanra>
Everything that happens in this town,
though it might not look it,
on some level, it's connected.
It all holds some terrible truth
beyond our knowledge.
But...
Morning!
Good morning, Sonohara-san...
I know it's a bit late to realize this,
but I guess I don't mind this relationship.
Even if some day, the dots connect,
and something, unseen to us now,
goes out of control,
I believe that our relationship
won't change.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Active
Interest
The Dollars?
I can't tell you much.
I can tell you about the now-legendary
Kazutawno incident.
Next time:
Active Interest.
But don't call me Dotachin.