Madam?
Please hurry.
Another intruder.
They're waiting ahead of us.
We'll run into them if we go this way.
Understood.
Then let's circle around to the north side.
Madam?
The one who's coming is...
Kotomine Kirei.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
Kotomine Kirei?
Maiya,
your order from Kiritsugu
was to protect me, right?
Yes.
But...
But what?
We cannot let him get to Kiritsugu, no matter what.
Is that what you're thinking?
Madam.
You...
What a coincidence...
I was thinking the same thing.
Kotomine Kirei...
He probably represents the biggest threat to Kiritsugu.
We'll stop him here!
Understood, Maiya?
I apologize.
But please prepare yourself, Madam.
Yes.
Don't worry about me.
You do your job...
What you believe to be necessary,
not what Kiritsugu told you to do.
Yes.
Is there something else?
No.
The human heart...
It's so strange, isn't it?
You repeat an attack you know to be utterly futile.
Scalp!
Was Volumen Hydragyrum's autonomous defense defeated?
No... Faced with his feeble attacks,
I simply lowered my guard.
I shall take defensive action more quickly and efficiently.
You are a disgrace to magi everywhere.
You low-class piece of garbage!
To have drawn my blood...
He'll pay for that with his life.
Now that he understands how powerful this is,
it won't work again.
Next time, he'll put all his prana into defense.
No...
That's what I need him to do.
An illusion?
Maiya, no!
Madam... No!
Woman, this may surprise you,
but I haven't come here to defeat you.
I know that,
Kotomine Kirei.
I know what you desire.
But I will not allow it.
You will never reach Emiya Kiritsugu.
We will stop you.
Here.
Madam!
He is an Executor... An expert at hunting magi!
Normal magic won't suffice to stop him!
Kiritsugu taught me more
than how to drive a car.
He taught me how to live. And to survive!
Shape Ist Leben!
Madam!
It won't be that easy!
Maiya!
Please!
No...
You bastard...
I'm honestly stunned
that we have made so little progress.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds that Noble Phantasm,
matters are unlikely to improve.
I see... So that's it.
But if you plan to knock the book from that blue freak's hands,
you'll need to pass this wall of monsters.
Lancer... How about an all-or-nothing bet?
It feels a bit shameful,
but there's no glory simply in fighting these things.
Very well.
I'm in, Saber.
I shall clear a path.
We have but one chance.
Lancer, can you ride the wind?
I see now.
Easily done.
Have you said your prayers?
Tremble... Despair.
There is a limit to the numbers
that even superior skill can defeat.
It must be humiliating, right?
You will die, suffocating amongst monsters,
attended by neither honor nor glory!
There can be no greater disgrace for a hero.
That beautiful face...
Make it twist in pain for me, Jeanne!
Strike Air!
Prepare yourself...
Pierce...
Gae Dearg!
Damn you...
Damn you, damn you, damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
Damn you!
How did you like that?
Had she still the use of her left hand,
this would have been the result.
Prepare to die.
Monster.
Pathetic.
I did not participate in the Holy Grail War
for this kind of battle!
Where is he?
There you are...
Rat.
You can't really expect the same trick
to have any chance, can you?
Dirty proletarian!
Your earlier attack was but a fluke!
It was a simple, improbable coincidence.
I'll see that you understand the difference.
I shall not let you die easily.
I shall use healing magic to regenerate your heart and lungs,
while I rend every inch of your flesh.
In pain and despair,
you will die as you suffer.
And while you die, you will curse them...
You will curse the cowardice of those who hired you!
You will curse the Einzberns for disgracing the Holy Grail War!
Fervor Mei Sanguis!
I knew you'd do that, fool!
You're wasting your time.
What unbelievable cowardice.
Lancer...
Is something wrong?
My Master is in danger...
It seems he left me here, and breached the castle himself.
I'm certain it is my Master's doing.
Lancer, hurry onward.
Rescue your Master.
Knight, you have my thanks.
Worry not.
You and I have sworn to settle matters as befit knights.
Let us share in that pride.
In the end,
did all go as Kiritsugu planned?
Your origin lies in cutting and tying, kid.
To cut and tie...
It's a little more nuanced than simply destruction and regeneration.
If you cut a thread, and then tie it,
the thickness will be different where you originally cut it, right?
In that sense, it means irreversible change.
I've powdered some of your ribs and put part in here.
Your origin will materialize in anything shot by this.
It's especially powerful against magi.
If they use any magic against it,
your origin will destroy their Magic Circuits,
which will then reconnect improperly.
The more powerful the magus,
the more of their Magic Circuits will lose control and short out.
Naturally, they won't recover,
either as a magus or human.
This is for your Mystic Code, the origin shot.
I've made sixty-six, in total.
Don't waste them.
You understand how easy it would be for me to pierce you now, correct?
Master of Saber.
So that's it...
I shall not let you kill my Master.
And I shall not kill Saber's Master, either.
Neither she nor I
wish to end things like this.
Never forget this.
The reason you still live
is for the nobility shown by the King of Knights.
Woman, I ask you a question.
It appears that you challenged me
to protect Emiya Kiritsugu.
So, by whose order did you fight?
If you lack the Command Seals,
then you are not the Einzbern Master.
Most likely,
you are a homunculus, charged of being the Grail Vessel.
Someone like that
could never be stupid enough
to risk the front lines of the fight.
So I ask again...
By whose will do you fight?
Kirei...
Caster, as well as Lancer and his Master
have all left the forest.
Saber will arrive shortly.
My lord, it is dangerous here.
I see...
So it's red, after all.
It couldn't be that these women challenged me of their own accord,
in absence of another's orders?
Impossible.
Emiya Kiritsugu is like me.
Alone and empty,
understood by none.
He must be like that.
Irisviel...
Irisviel!
Wake up.
Saber...
No!
You must stay awake!
I'll call Kiritsugu.
Be strong until then!
Where is Kirei...
The enemy who was just here?
He escaped.
If I'd only been a second faster,
this would not have come to pass.
What about Maiya?
She is badly wounded, but she will survive.
I'm more concerned about you.
You've lost so much blood...
Irisviel?
What is this?
You carry Avalon, Iri.
But this Noble Phantasm heals its bearer's wounds.
I think you should carry it.
No.
Without its original owner, Saber, nearby to supply it with prana,
the scabbard won't work.
You'll be the one with Saber from now on.
You should have it.
Keep it within you, as a Conceptual Weapon.
Additionally,
never tell anyone about it.
Indeed, not even Saber herself.
From the moment you touched me,
I felt Avalon's power.
Thank you, Saber.
Kotomine Kirei...
That Executor is dangerous,
just as I imagined.
No, even more so.
We were lucky today,
but I don't know what will happen next time.
All I know for certain
is that I can't let him get to Kiritsugu.
But...
I'm not the only one who's protecting Kiritsugu.
That's right, isn't it?
Maiya?
Next time, we'll win for sure.
We'll both protect Kiritsugu, okay?
Episode 8
Magus-Killer
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
My Master was nearly killed!
Elegance is required, even in battle.
I cannot agree to that.
Give me the Command Seals...
Lancer isn't so wonderful a man!
Next Time:
Lord and Servant