“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
I-I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
Whoa! Kida-kun! Is it really you?
We've also been seeing a lot less of the color gangs lately.
During a gang war with Saitama a lot of 'em got nabbed.
I'm Sonohara Anri. Nice to meet you.
Harima-san!
I thought you were someone else!
You've pledged to become a fine Ikebukuroan, therefore, you can overcome this obstacle and show them all, Mikado!
I found you! My love!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
Please forgive me.
Bait and Switch
I've had it.
I've really had it.
It's my fault, Certy. My fault for taking on such a boring job.
The job should've taken care of itself. But then, that thing came out of nowhere...
Not human. Monster. Monster. Monster!
You heard a voice coming from the wound?
It called me a monster.
How rude. It should have at least said "devil woman."
What was that thing?
What if it was an alien?
Certy... am I supposed to laugh at that?
M-Monster!
Let's go!
They say this town is full of jokes, coincidences and the whims of others.
Likewise, this situation must be a whim of God, or perhaps one of his jokes...
Of the thirty-seven girls this guy's had a crush on since he first saw them during the entrance exams,
he is now walking home from school with one who ranks in his top five, just like you'd see in a drama on TV...
...and now, his awkwardness is holding him back. What a sight.
That was pretty bad, wasn't it?
Yeah.
This just won't do.
I sure was surprised back there. Seriously, I didn't expect you to run off like that.
Run off? Don't say that.
No way. Mikado!
I'm glad you did though. If I was in your shoes, I wouldn't have let a chance like that go either.
A chance for you to go to Nishiguchi Park on a day like this, sitting and talking about love.
So, will you go out with me?
Wha– Kida-kun!
I–
You don't have to answer me right away. There are seven girls that I'm waiting an answer from,
and I'm still considering which one I want to date in the end.
Sonohara-san, don't take him seriously. He'll only wear you out. Plus, he's only joking, so it's nothing to worry about.
Even when he tries flirting, in the end–
Hey, look! Mikado!
This guy, Ryugamine Mikado, is my best friend. He's a country boy who just came to Ikebukuro a couple of days ago.
He's simple and knows nothing of the world, but can be really stubborn at times. I just can't leave the guy alone.
This "pure boy" and I are part of an unexpected love triangle. Is this the so-called "springtime of youth"?
Ow!
Hey, Kida-kun!
You're... good friends, aren't you?
Yeah. We are.
We wish we weren't, though.
I give, I give, I give!
How did things become like this, you ask? It all goes back to the day of the opening ceremony.
I'm Yagiri Seji.
Nice to meet you.
Well, Mr. Yagiri, please take a seat quickly.
I will not.
I don't think I'll be able to come to school for a while.
No, I may not come at all anymore.
It's a matter of great importance to me.
I don't have time to chat with you all.
Excuse me.
Hey, Yagiri! Wait! Stop right there!
Mikado said later on that there are all sorts of people in this world, and that's what I thought too, however...
Wait! Stop right there!
Wait!
That was my big "fall in love" moment!
Yagiri-kun, there's gotta be something–
A cute smile, and a heart-throbbing chest!
Don't ask.
B-But, you skipped the first day of–
Well, she wasn't smiling, but...
I said, don't ask!
Wait!
Hey, what's wrong?
Anyway, that girl shot right to the top of my girlfriend ranking list, and today...
Hey! Sonohara!
Going home?
Yes.
Hey, Sonohara. Is something bothering you? Are you being teased, or are you in some kind of trouble?
No.
If there is, tell me right away.
I'm all right.
Is that so? Speaking of which, Harima hasn't come back yet, has she? Even though she's in your class now.
I worked so hard... to put the two of you in the same class.
Ever since you were in middle school, I've been told over and over by Saito-sensei to take good care of you.
So you have no reason to refuse. That's right. I'm going to walk you home today. You know, right?
About the slasher showing up in Ikebukuro again.
Nasujima-sensei, is that sexual harassment?
You know, the "real" kind of sexual harassment that makes innocent, young girls cry out loud?
Or rather, is it "sexy harassment"?
Kida! Quit fooling around! Sonohara. You won't take it the wrong way and start spreading rumors, right?
Does she seem that shallow to you?
You're right. I'll leave it all up to you.
If anything, I'll be spreading the rumors, so don't worry!
I guess I have a "hero of justice" in me too, don't I?
Look at me. I'm so cool! She's gotta fall in love with me!
Kida-kun? And Sonohara-san.
What a great time for him to show up.
Sorry for the wait!
Here.
Thank you very much.
Still, I really think you should be more careful.
More than half of the rumors about that jerk Nasujima are just rumors, but it's true that he's done things to his students.
There's one girl named Niekawa Haruna who's two years older than us.
Last year she changed schools, apparently because she thought people would find out she'd been seeing Nasujima.
Really?
Although, I'm not sure what made her transfer– if she left by herself or if Nasujima threatened her into leaving.
Well, if anything happens, Mikado and I will do something about it. Right, Mikado?
Yeah. I'm not sure exactly what the situation is, but I'll do whatever I can.
Idiot! A man is supposed to take the focus away from himself by saying something like:
"There's nothing I can do, but by the power of love, I will do it for you!"
Isn't that contradictory?
It's the rule.
More importantly, about what happened before...
Those girls who were teasing you knew you from middle school, right?
How do you know?
Judging from the way they were talking, I thought they had to be. It's like you'd been saved by a tougher kid in middle school,
and now that that person's gone, they came back for you.
Yeah. What's her name? Your friend who stopped coming? The one they haven't found.
It's Harima Mika from our class, isn't it?
Mika-san has been absent from school, but since just before our opening ceremony, she stopped coming home as well.
Then we should let the police take care of it!
She left some messages on my phone and one at her house, saying, "I'm taking a short vacation for a broken heart."
"Don't worry about me."
For a broken heart? What happened?
Well... Can you try not to be surprised when you hear it?
I've pretty much stopped feeling surprised after the last few days.
Harima-san... is a stalker.
I see. It's the guy you were questioning earlier, isn't it?
Mika-chan, who had been following him around... no, courting him, got rejected, and now she's on leave for a "broken heart."
That's something you should just leave to her family, and if it comes down to it, you should tell the police.
Were you good friends with her, Sonohara-san?
Why does he even ask?
We were always together.
I guess he does have good intuition, in a weird way.
I've always been kind of awkward, in social situations too, but it was Mika-san who used to pull me through.
She went out of her way to pick the same high school as me, and I can't describe how grateful I am.
That's...
"...just because she wanted to keep you around in order to make herself look better."
Even if that's what you're thinking, you can't say that, Mikado-kun.
I know.
What?
That she wanted me around in order to make herself look better. I had also been taking advantage of her, though.
It was easier to live my life depending on her.
I thought I couldn't go on living if I didn't.
However, now I hardly think I need her that much.
I've gotten used to her not being around... and to being the class representative.
Harima always wanted to do it, so I thought I'd at least do it in her place.
I felt that if I became the class representative, I could leave her behind.
I suppose I'm dishonest for doing it.
I think it's more dishonest to come out and say that to people. It looks like you just want someone to forgive you for it.
Striving to be better than Mika was the right choice. So why not puff out your chest and do so openly?
You're right. Thank you very much.
This is what I like about this guy.
Kida-kun!
You're so uncool!
What do you mean, uncool?!
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Right. The strongest.
Do you work for a magazine or something, oji-san? "Strongest" has bit of a ring to it.
Well, I'd say the strongest is that black motorcycle guy.
I know. He's headless, right?
You're kidding!
And, after that is... maybe the slasher guy?
It's gotta be!
But right now, the strongest in Ikebukuro has to be the Dollars, wouldn't you say?
Dollars?
Yeah. Dollars!
Well, I have to go now. Thanks for everything today.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Bye-bye, Anri-chan!
I just thought of this, but aren't Yagiri-kun and that Mika girl together?
You mean the stalking victim?
Maybe Yagiri's been kidnapped by her.
I get it.
I wonder if we should go looking for him or something.
Leave it alone. She said we've done enough, didn't she?
We'd need an organized effort, wouldn't we? Like the Dollars.
Mikado... You don't want to join the Dollars, do you?
No, of course not.
Seriously, give it up. Those color gangs are the result of youthful folly, and they all end up regretting it later.
Yeah, but we still have some youthful folly left in us.
Before Mikado came to Ikebukuro, I was feeling really depressed.
I can go around feeling the way I do now because of, well, thanks to several people I guess, but that includes Mikado.
He just came to Ikebukuro, so he's still feeling the excitement of the city.
He doesn't see the danger around him.
I could pour cold water over his head, but when I look at him with his shining eyes,
I can't bring myself to do it.
And so, the least I can do is try to stay close to him when I can,
but if possible, I want to keep him away from the darkness that can be found in this town.
I have also...
...made up my mind never to go there again.
Don't tell me we're getting spammed?
It's like an alien.
Maybe they're laughing.
Scary, huh?
Look! "Mother, mother..."
No, not that I'm scared of aliens,
or it.
Tsumiuta? Or maybe it's Zaika?
Zaika?
I'll take a look at it later. Right now, Certy, it's time for work. It's for Shiki-san from the Awakusu Club again.
It doesn't sound like it was planned very well, but will you take it?
Smuggling again?
Yeah, smuggling.
Although, they want you to start the job at the destination of the goods, and we haven't heard what the goods are either.
Or should I say, it's better for both parties if we don't know.
Got it.
And about the goods, apparently the people who stole it keep changing locations.
We know their usual hiding spot, so you should be able to chase them down.
Got it.
The slasher's been showing up a lot recently, so be careful.
Slasher?
That's right. The slasher. I hear he's shown his face again.
He doesn't kill people. He just wounds them and leaves.
You can't call him the "strongest" for that. The strongest guys in town really have to be...
Simon, from the Russian sushi place.
He moved back to Shinjuku, but there's also that informant guy.
Orihara Izaya.
Well then, it's gotta be him.
Hewajima Shizuo!
The strongest color gang? Right now, that's the Dollars!
The Dollars don't have a color. Until last year there were a lot of yellows running around, though.
Yellow...
Yeah, they're called the Kokizoku.
I heard they had a brawl with the Blue Squares and both sides destroyed each other.
No, I heard they're back together.
Hey! Keep the orders coming! Halibut, scallops! It's cheap!
Speaking of which, don't you see them a lot?
See what?
Yellow stuff, right? Haven't you noticed?
By "yellow", you don't mean...
Hyokinzoku!
It's "Kokinzoku"!
Yeah, that! The contemporary Hermès.
No. The Kokinzoku were supposedly weakened after a battle with the Blue Squares.
That's right. Their boss supposedly left.
Hey– Welcome!
Can you tell me about the Dollars?
My friend's about to stick his nose in their affairs, and I want to stop him.
Why do you ask us?
There's no one else I can ask.
You mean you can't just ask Orihara Izaya?
No. We don't know that much about the Dollars either. I will tell you everything I know, though.
Sometimes, it seems like you're about to get swallowed up by this town.
That's why, Mikado, I'm not going to let you go in there.
Mikado?
My bad.
What are you talking about?
Can't you tell by looking? We're Kokinzoku!
Yagiri-kun!
Huh? It's not Harima Mika.
I don't know who you are, but don't get in the way of our elopement.
Elopement?
Let's go.
But who is that girl?
Kida-kun.
Are you guys really Kokinzoku?
Yeah. Of course we are!
I'm asking 'cause I'm not so sure.
You...
Kida-kun!
Wait, wait. Mikado! Why are you here too?!
M-Monster!
Let's go!
You had me worried, man!
That's my line!
In the end, maybe I'm the one who depends on him.
That's right!
Since Mikado came, I've felt like my mere bravado has turned into true courage.
Maybe now I can face her without running away next time.
Yes?
And the more I feel that way...
I was starting to think you'd never come...
Izaya-san.
Hey.
How's your boyfriend been?
Good. He comes by sometimes. But only in front there.
I'm home! Haruna, did you eat your supper? Haruna?
Oh, I banned the intruder.
Then it should be peaceful here again.
That would be nice...
Oh hey, I heard yesterday that some Kokinzoku got killed by the slasher.
What's "Kokinzoku"?
You think the slasher is one of the Dollars?
What? Really?
This could turn into a war, couldn't it?
At first sight, the things that happen in this town seem to be random and disconnected,
Yo!
but there probably is a connection somewhere.
Good morning, Kida-kun.
However...
Good morning!
Morning, Sonohara-san.
Good morning.
Perhaps they hold a distorted truth which is inconceivable to all of us.
I realize now that I'm perfectly comfortable with the way this relationship is.
Even if one one thing leads to another, and that exposes something I didn't know about,
I believe that our relationship can go on without changing.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next episode
Durarara!!
On the Move
Dollars? They're nothing special, if you ask me. Anyway, I'll tell you the details of the beyond-legendary gang.
Next time: On the Move. Just don't call me "Dotachin."