"Time: 15:47"
So, whoever loses this rock-paper-scissors match
is gonna go declare war on
Class D. No problems, right?
Plain old rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Let's make it so that it's okay
to use psychological tactics.
Then, I'll use rock!
Then if you don't use rock... I'll kill you!
--What?!
--Rock-paper-scissors!
Well then, get going.
No way!
Don't worry, Akihisa. Many Class D
students like good-looking boys.
So they won't give you hell.
I see. Then I'll definitely be okay, huh?
But you're ugly, so...
How rude! My good looks span all 365 degrees!
You've got an extra 5 degrees there.
So it's actually 5 degrees.
I hate you all!
Okay then! We're counting on you!
"Time: 16:05"
Now no one will marry me!
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
"Time: 10:30"
"Fumizuki Academy"
As planned, starting this afternoon
an ST War between Year 2,
Classes F and D will take place.
Good. I like idiots who never learn.
Is there a chance they can win this time?
"Episode 11" "Rivals, Love Letters, and Blitz Tactics"
Well, about that...
What is it?
About Yuuji Sakamoto in Class F...
His scores have been going
down in each periodical test.
What?! And they're trying
to beat Class D like that?
Seriously, they're taking it lightly.
Do they think ST wars are just a game?
No, Principal...
--Please look at this.
--Hm?
"Time: 14:35"
"Year 2, Class F"
Clear away anything that'll be in our way...
or we won't be able to move
around if they attack us in here.
If we win, we'll exchange our cardboard
boxes with Class D's desks, right?
So we'll say goodbye to these boxes, huh?
So we'll finally have a decent
classroom. Let's do our best, Himeji.
Yes. Let's do our best, Yoshii.
"Surprised Akihisa"
"Love Letter"
I wonder... if that's a
love letter to Yuuji after all...
"Misconception"
But Yuuji's got Kirishima...
"None of your business"
It sure is hard to give it to him, isn't it?
Excuse me, but if you put
captions, it reduces my part.
"Year 2, Class D"
That stupid Class F has
declared war on us, Class D.
They're after our classroom equipment.
"Class D"
Teach them that their classroom
is just what idiots deserve!
Let's start the strategic meeting.
Calling it "strategic" is too dramatic, Yuuji.
We've got Himeji, so it'll be a piece of cake.
Yeah, Himeji's strength
is Class A level, after all...
No! That's too optimistic.
Class E lost because they didn't
know that Mizuki Himeji was in Class F.
However, the same tactic won't work on us.
Our classroom is located at the
end of the new school building.
Class F is in the old building.
Since the fighting power will be
spread out due to the large battlefield,
we'll be at an advantage
since we have better scores.
If Himeji marches in there alone,
she'll receive a concentrated attack,
and so she won't be able to reach their rep.
Then what will we do?
We'll go with Blitz tactics this time.
The Force Recon unit will charge the
enemy's trenches and confuse the rear
in order to create an opening
in their defenses. Then, Himeji...
Yes.
You make a fierce attack on their
center in one shot using that opening,
and bring down the Class D Rep, Genji Hiraga.
Okay!
If we divide our strength, we can't win.
Forget defense, we'll put
everything into our attack!
We'll attack in one shot
and win before we can lose!
Offense is the best defense!
They'll put all their energy into
attacks, so they'll have a weak defense.
However, Sakamoto's score
is in the bottom rankings.
As long as there's no one guarding him,
we can bring him down with one blow.
Don't put up with their
cocky attitude! Crush them!
"Time: 15:30"
And thus the war began.
"War Commencement"
Okay, let's begin the war!
Yeah!
Akihisa. Command the
front lines as the unit leader.
What? Me?
Yeah. You're the key to this operation.
I've come up with a tactic unique to
Class F. Use it to confuse the enemy.
Okay!
Snakes...
Summon!
We got beaten.
What? You came back?
You thought I'd die?! Five of our
people were sent to the remedial class!
Muttsulini, show us the enemy's student list.
--Hm?
--Akihisa, what was the enemy's lineup like?
This, this, and this one
were on the front lines.
The rest were... Oh?
Where're the guys' pictures?
I don't have those.
I see. Many of them aren't good at math.
Then, shall I go charge them?
I planned that way from the start.
We've already secured the
math teacher Mr. Hasegawa as well.
What did I sacrifice myself for then?!
Sugawa! Prepare for the special mission.
Roger.
"Time: 15:46"
Everyone, make a sortie!
Let's start the operation!
Mr. Hasegawa! Please give us approval!
I approve!
Summon!
Here I come!
I won't lose against Class D in a math fight!
You jerks!
vs. "Math"
Those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
Ugh! Iron Man?!
Ah! I don't wanna take
the demon's remedial class!
That's not a remedial class! It's torture!
It's also respectable education!
I'll make you ideal students
whose hobby is studying
and who look up to Kinjirou
Ninomiya. So prepare yourself!
All right! Let's break through
the enemy's line of defense!
Class F's Shimada has
entered the new school building!
All right! Now's our chance!
Capture Mr. Hasegawa!
What?!
Some enemies laid in ambush in the
bathroom. Mr. Hasegawa got caught.
It's their trap.
Then what'll happen to Minami?!
"Math"
Ah?! The math field is...
This is bad!
That's the classical
Japanese teacher Mr. Takenaka!
I approve the fight in classical Japanese.
"Math"
"Classical Japanese"
Oh no! That's the subject I'm bad at!
Leave the matter to me!
Sugawa!
Buy some time!
Okay. Let's stick it out, Minami!
But how?!
Ah!
So it's you, honey... It has to be you, honey?!
M-Miharu?!
It's true that I can't be a fighting
puppet that follows his orders!
Huh?
I'll bring you down, honey! Summon!
To think that lovers are
fated to fight each other...
As I thought, you and I are
connected by destiny, aren't we?!
I can't fight in classical Japanese!
I'll help you!
Kinoshita!
Your attention please.
This is an urgent message for
the math teacher Ms. Funakoshi.
That's Sugawa!
Ms. Funakoshi, Akihisa Yoshii is
waiting for you in front of Class D.
What?
Math teacher Ms. Funakoshi,
a 45-year-old single woman.
She's a spinster who missed her
chance to get married. It's rumored
that she asks students to date
her in return for school credit.
Yoshii says that he wants to talk
to you about something important,
not as student and teacher but as man and woman.
Please hurry to the Class D classroom.
Sugawa!
Ah! It's Ms. Funakoshi!
What?!
You're amazing, Unit Leader
Yoshii! You really are the man!
To think you'd sacrifice
yourself for the class...!
Everyone! Don't waste
Unit Leader Yoshii's death!
Yeah!
Sugawa!
You were too optimistic, Hiraga!
We've had another math
teacher secured in reserve!
Muttsulini! Remove Mr. Takenaka!
Roger.
Teacher... your wig is slipping.
Ahh! I'm leaving to attend
to some urgent matters!
"Math"
"Classical Japanese"
Now!
Ms. Funakoshi! Please approve!
"Math"
I won't lose any more!
Take... this!
vs. "Math"
The path is clear!
It's your turn, Himeji!
Okay! I'm summoning my Avatar! Summon!
But you're a little too late!
Emergency!
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
"Do not open it carelessly"
"Do not open nonchalantly"
"Academy Discipline Reinforcement Week
Don’t rip off Move, old hag!!"
The spy cameras have detected
enemies. You're surrounded!
There he is! It's Sakamoto!
He's unguarded! Now's our chance!
Don't be so hasty. I'll take you on now.
"Time: 16:18"
Humph. He made a fool of us.
"Yuuji Sakamoto, Year 2, Class F Rep"
"Periodical test scores for each subject"
Looks like he wasn't once called a whiz kid for nothing, huh?
Can't be! I heard your score was at the bottom!
Isn't that information outdated?
Well, I didn't put the latest score
in the info I had Muttsulini leak, so...
Okay then... Here I come!
Wh-Why...?
I'm sorry.
There's no enemy before me.
"Time: 16:25"
"War Over"
There's no enemy before me.
Okay, Idiot Test.
We did it, Yoshii!
I never thought that Yuuji was studying.
This is just the beginning.
Our real goal is Class A!
In order to achieve that,
we'll bring down Class B next!
Class B... The class with that Nemoto?
"(Curse!) Congrats"
As soon as our after-war recovery
tests are over, we'll declare war on Class B.
So, Akihisa. There's a
task only you can carry out.
"Middle"
"Idiot"
Is there anything you want to say?
I can't believe you fell for it so many times.
Argh!
They're just Class F. And they're
declaring war on us? How amusing.
I think we'll teach them a few lessons.
Are you gonna be okay, Kyouji?
Class F defeated Classes E and D.
Are you afraid of Class F, Yuuka?
Don't make me laugh.
No matter how hard Class F tries,
they can't defeat us, Class C.
Then it's all the more true that
they won't defeat Class B, right?
Yeah, but...
However, they keep winning.
There's gotta be some trick to it.
If so, we won't do anything
risky like fighting them head-on.
Kyouji...
Just wait and see. I'm not an idiot, you know.
I'll pay them back for
what they did the other day.
So that's the strategy.
Everyone, fight with all your might.
If you do, we can win for sure!
Yeah!
"Time: 17:28"
Well then, dismissed!
"Dismiss"
"Temporary"
See you.
Was it really okay not to exchange
our equipment with Class D's?
Yeah, I'm sowing seeds for later.
Sowing?
Just look forward to seeing what blooms.
"Time: 17:31"
What's this?!
This is terrible... Who did this?
Probably Class B students.
They tried to hinder our recovery
tests by breaking our pencils, huh?
What a petty thing to do.
How bland...
--Ah!
--Hm?
What's the matter, Himeji?
Ah... no, nothing.
Ah!
How dare Nemoto...
I won't forgive him no matter what!
Calm down. Don't lose your head.
But...!
If we beat them in the ST war,
that'll be enough payback.
But if we lose our heads, we can't win.
That's also part of his strategy.
"Time: 14:51"
And thus the showdown foreordained to happen
between Classes F and B began.
Let's start the war! Brace yourself and fight!
Yeah!
Everyone! Charge!
Here they come!
Humph, they sure are stupid.
Do as we planned! They
have no chance of winning!
Charge!
Dammit! They're too strong for us!
Do we really not stand a chance?
That's just what you'd expect
from Class B. They're strong.
Yoshii!
Himeji! I thought it wasn't your turn yet...
Sakamoto said to use this when you're in a bind!
Yuuji did? This is...! Okay!
Everyone, listen good!
Class B Rep Nemoto has a girlfriend!
What?!
Class C Rep Yuuka Koyama is his girlfriend!
On top of that, his lunches
are being prepared by her!
What?!
When the outrageous fury reaches its peak,
the inquisition group FFF
delivers merciless slaughter
that makes things like the
demon's remedial class seem pleasant.
Unforgivable!
"Inquisition Group"
How dare he alone be happy!
Do you understand the pain felt
by those of us without a girlfriend?!
What the heck's with these guys?!
They're dangerous! Defend with all your might!
The tides of war have changed! Charge!
What's with these guys?!
Aren't they afraid of the remedial class?
What's the matter?
These Class F guys are desperate.
They took quite a few of our
comrades with them when they fell.
Hm... Maybe it's time to
take out a little insurance policy.
"Time: 15:21"
Those who died will be given a remedial class!
Sugawa... I won't waste your sacrifice.
It did... help to calm my fury.
So you still had a grudge against
him about Ms. Funakoshi, huh?
Our group has shrunk. Let's change formation!
Yeah!
Those who've been weakened,
go take the recovery test!
Ah, Hime--
That's... Nemoto!
Why did you mess up our classroom?
Do you have any evidence that we did it?
That's...
We did it and there's evidence, too.
Unforgivable! I'm summoning my Avat--
Oops, that was close.
Ah!
Aren't I considerate, showing
the evidence even though I did it?
Oh no...
This was an unexpected bonus.
A love letter in this day and age? How cute.
Please give it back to me!
I wonder what's written in it.
Oops. I think I'll keep it to enjoy later.
You're such a...
Really, I don't have to do this to win the war.
But this is in lieu of insurance.
I'll give this back to you
when the ST war is over.
That is if I didn't change my mind.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Did you run from a fight?
If so, I'll beat you up with two fingers.
Yuuji, I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I want you to remove Himeji from the battle.
Did something happen?
I can't tell you the reason.
If you say so, that's fine.
But...
...the task that Himeji was
going to carry out... is yours now.
Okay.
Launch a surprise raid on
the enemy's headquarters.
You can pick the method.
Can you do it?
I'll try.
No! I'll do it!
That's the spirit, Akihisa.
"Time: 16:28"
Also, Yuuji...
What is it?
"Time: 16:29"
Akihisa... Are we really gonna do it?
If I am to launch a surprise raid on
Class B myself, this is the only way.
But you won't get summoning approval, right?
Not to worry. I have this.
Awaken!
Go!
This is nothing!
Wh-What's this?
I'm not done yet!
Are you okay, Akihisa?!
I'm okay. This is nothing.
No matter what happens...
I'll make this plan succeed for sure!
for Himeji's sake, too!
There he is!
You thought that I'd keep myself defenseless?
Your surprise raid has failed!
Gotcha!
Muttsulini!
What?!
We'll fight in Health and
Physical Education. Summon!
vs. "Health and Physical Education"
C-Can't be...! He jumped
in along with the teacher?!
Iron Man Nishimura, who's
in charge of remedial classes,
can not only approve fights in all the subjects,
but he is also outstanding in sporting ability.
Geez...
The war is over! Class F is the winner!
"Class F Win"
What a shame, Nemoto.
Sakamoto...
Now, I've got a proposal to
make to all of you in Class B.
Under normal circumstances, we'd exchange
our cardboard boxes with Class B equipment.
But if you meet our condition, we
can make an exception and excuse you.
Condition?
Nemoto! If you wear this and follow my orders,
I'll excuse your class from the exchange.
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
Why would I do such a foolish...
Everyone in Class B will make sure that happens!
We promise! Leave it to us!
We'll do everything in our
power to make him wear it!
Hey! I won't wear something like...
--You'll pay for this! Stop it! Stop it!
--Is this what you wanted?
--You don't have to take off my underwear, do you?!
Yeah!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
The end of the school day is bliss
If I am to put it into words, "It's really angelic!"
My peace was shattered
by a sudden announcement
Talking about the make up test. "This is Hell!"
While my friends and I were
sharing funny stories, I said,
"There's no way anyone is that stupid"
But the truth is, deep down in my heart
I was shouting, "That was me!"
About that "Monthly Parking"
sign you see in the parking lot
I thought it was the name of a company...
All this time...
Sticking to your idiocy can be cool
Is our common sense nonsense?
We don't need rules in this world
It's dog eat dog food! It's social upheaval!
Look!
The sun that rose from the west is setting
Run home! It's dinner time already.
Let's go home! Let's go home!
Here you go, Himeji.
Thank you very much, Yoshii! I'm really glad.
Uhm, Himeji... That letter...
Yes. This is that unhappy chain letter.
Just because it was
taking forever for me to mail it,
I caused everyone trouble, didn't I?
Himeji!
I had hardships because of this letter...
but I experienced many happy things, too.
So I don't need it anymore.
I don't think I should
depend on this letter anymore.
I want to tell my feelings
directly with my own words.
I can't do it yet,
but there is one thing that I can do now.
Yoshii...
What is it, Himeji?
Can I call you Akihisa?
What? Well, that's... You see, those
FFF guys will get upset, so Hideyoshi...
Is it okay, Akihisa?
Yeah!
Yuuji, why are you obsessed with the
ST war? Do you want nice equipment?
I'm not interested in things like desks.
I want to prove that academic ability
isn't all that matters in life. That's all.
So, Shouko. Don't hold back.
I know. I'll fight in earnest.
Question 12.
What do you call the last scene in a story,
such as a novel or play,
where things get resolved?
Final boss battle.
You don't have enough experience points.
Next Episode! "Love, Courage, and
Our Battle Has Just Begun! (Temporary)"
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"