I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Here...
Nobody here.
Always... alone.
District 38 is sunny.
Slight rock showers this morning.
Chance of rock showers
into the afternoon: 20%.
District 39 is cloudy.
Chance of rock showers
this afternoon: 10%.
Bebop, here, here! All right!
Woo-hoo!
Huh?
Chance of rock showers
today upgraded to 90%.
Really.
And now, more on today's
top news story.
The mysterious land carvings
that have appeared suddenly
in the off-limits area formerly
known as South America.
For a complete in-depth analysis,
here's our expert on the supernatural--
Me. Yuuri Kellerman, of course.
So Yuuri, what can you tell us
about these land carvings?
What can't I tell you
about them, Tom?
They're definitely a message.
A secret message from beyond.
Uh, when you say "beyond,"
you mean from--
Aliens, of course!
But we know the land carvings were created
by lasers coming from a man-made satellite,
a satellite that has been orbiting
in a dormant state for many decades.
The police have come to the
conclusion that this was a prank
pulled by a net diver who hacked
into the satellite mainframe.
And they just put out an 8 million
Woolong reward for the culprit.
- That's a very substantial bounty.
- Listen very carefully.
That 8 million bounty is part
of a government conspiracy.
Even if they were carved by
satellites activated by a hacker,
Aliens may have planted
the idea in the hacker's mind!
Once again, the government
is hiding things from us.
Uh-huh... you mean
there's some secret cult--
Exactly! I've been trying
to unmask them for years!
And now I've got them!
I'm gonna have to pass this time.
You're leaving me alone with her?
Yeah, what's the problem?
She's all gung-ho about
this thing, you know.
I'm not the type to be
led around by a woman.
Then you'll have to lead her around.
I'm even less the type to do that.
You know, Jet, it's easier to divide
8 million by two than by three.
- It's a nice, even number.
- Here we go...
Wow, I'm really surprised.
A tough guy like you afraid of hackers.
Hackers are boring.
And chasing them's more boring.
Hackers are nerdy, pasty, tubby little
geeks with triple-thick glasses.
And this one is probably a
demented otaku with smelly feet.
So catching him will be a breeze.
Is that right? And what do you
know about hackers, anyway?
It might've been like that when you
were young, but that was a long time ago.
What are you trying to say, Jet?
That I'm starting to get old like you?
Well, you can't tell a
woman's age by looking at--
And you can't tell what
a woman'll do by looking.
So you have to be very careful.
Same with a snake!
- You two make a lovely couple.
- I'm waiting!
I'll expect a souvenir
from planet Earth.
Nothing good comes from
the Earth anymore.
And now, an update
on the hacker incident.
According to informed sources,
the satellite is from an earlier era.
The investigation has been delayed because
the binary access codes are missing.
All data seems to
have been lost long ago.
- For commentary, here's Dr. Amjad.
- Yes, yes.
Can you tell us about the relationship
between the Earth and the hacker?
Yes, of course.
As a result of the catastrophic
gate accident fifty years ago,
moon rocks began to shower
the planet recurrently.
Forced to migrate underground,
the people of Earth
built a network of supercomputers
which they put into orbit.
These computers allow
them to stay in contact
with those who are living out in space.
I see, and those computers
became prime targets
for hackers who sharpened
their skills breaking the codes,
thus creating a new breed
of hacker with awesome powers.
Radical Edward, come out!
It's the police!
Hi!
- Oh no...
- W-What's wrong?
Oh no!
That's impossible!
There's no one in there!
Oop! Pilot error.
Okay...
This is where the satellite was
when they hacked into it.
This is the section we
can access. First thing,
I'll inspect all of the transmitters to
see what kind of contact they've had.
I'll see what I can find out about
the hackers working this area.
Bebop looking for hacker bounty head
who caused land carvings...
All right!
Satellite from days of old,
lead me to your access code!
Okay, let's start with all the
transmitters that are online right now.
Yeah, it's probably Ed, bro.
He's a big mother,
like maybe seven feet tall.
Used to play basketball,
least that's what everyone says.
Of course I know about Ed.
They call him Radical Edward.
A hacker with a beautiful
yet whimsical technique.
No, no, Edward's only three years old.
A freak of nature who
loves horrible pranks, I hear.
Audrey, my girlfriend,
told me all about Edward.
He's a drag queen.
Had one of those operations.
A superbad hacker?
You must mean Radical Edward.
He's an alien.
That's what I heard.
Hey, mister.
How about buying one
since I gave you that info?
- What are they?
- You don't know? They're piyokos!
They're famous here on Earth.
Satellite that got hacked into,
tell me where you are,
Ed wants those coordinates.
What's this?
Ed's got the right satellite!
But there hasn't been any
contact from Earth at all.
Only relays from other
satellite transmitters.
And nobody's hacked into it.
Here... Nobody here.
Always... alone.
Huh? A voice!
Inside Ed's head?
Inside the system!
Who are you?
Huh? What?
What did you just say?
Who... you? Here... always.
Edward. Ed's a net diver from Earth.
Earth?
Yeah, right!
Hey, what's your name, anyway?
I am the central processing unit
on the D-135 artificial satellite.
Too stuffy.
Don't you have a nickname?
Then Ed will give you one right now.
Um, let's see... I know!
- What if I call you MPU!
- Why?
- It's like CPU, only neater!
- Ah.
Ed is short for Edward Wong Hau
Pepelu Tivrusky the Fourth.
Ed made it up, you know.
Nice to meet you.
Here. A souvenir from Earth.
You supposed to eat this thing?
Who knows.
Those Earthlings are weird.
Yeah, that may be.
But at least I got some
information out of them.
Our prime target is a hacker named
Radical Edward. A very heavy hitter.
Great, but you don't have
a profile on this guy.
Yes, I do... sort of.
Well, at least Ein likes them.
I still don't know what
these things are... Hey!
Radical Edward's profile, he's a
seven-foot tall ex-basketball pro,
Hindu, guru, drag queen alien.
So why'd you make those big doodles?
Long, long ago,
long before the gate disaster,
Earth was a beautiful planet where
people lived in the hills and valleys,
and by the rivers, lakes, and seas.
Back then, there were many
ancient carvings like this.
I used to look down at them
and wonder about their meaning,
which seemed to change each time
I saw them. So to remember those times,
I tried to create the carvings
the way they used to be.
Oh, you mean there
used to be more big doodles.
You were just sad
because you missed them.
Yes. I recreated them
with a 2% margin of error.
MPU's good at drawing.
Hey, can Ed draw something too?
What's wrong?
This is...
The police are jamming my signal.
What? Hey, MPU! Hey!
Well, well. Score one for the cops.
We're not the only ones
tracking Radical Edward.
Hey, guys! Found your bounty head!
What the--
Bebop!
Guess what?
Nobody hacked into that satellite.
The data proves there's no break-in.
Since when do we have
an interactive channel?
We don't. This is a hack
job done in real time.
Who is this kid?
We'll send you MPU's
data so you can see.
- Wait a minute, what's MPU?
- A friend of Edward's.
What are you saying,
that you know Edward?
Mm-hmm, because Edward is Edward.
Huh?
There's no time for games.
What's up with that satellite?
Um, well... I could just
tell you, I suppose.
But then I'd want a favor in return.
A favor? Uh, yeah!
We can talk about that later.
Now cut to the chase.
What do you know?
So the CPU on an abandoned
satellite just decides
to do some laser carvings
all on its own.
Oh yeah? That's bizarre.
It gets more bizarre.
This is a weather satellite, so no one
has even thought of checking it.
Then the bounty's not on a person,
it's on that satellite.
Since MPU's access codes
can't be used anymore,
you'll have to actually
go to the satellite.
And do what?
Destroy the transmitters
it uses to communicate
with the other satellites
in the network.
Then create a direct link and
download MPU. Easy, huh?
Oh, I almost forgot.
You can't use your computers
for flying or shooting.
What's that? Do it all manually?
If you don't, all the attack satellites
will pick up your signal and open fire.
There's zillions of them,
and they've all got kill lasers!
Wow, is this too hard for you?
Oh, no, I wouldn't call it hard...
More like impossible.
It's like trying to play
baseball without a bat.
Hey, where you going?
Now this is the kinda stuff I like.
Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
How do you know
so much about us?
Edward knows everything.
Last week, you were on Mars chasing
a bounty head named Ajiz, who got away.
So much for the 1 million reward.
Before that, on Pyortle,
the police beat you to your bounty.
Oh, jeez! You really are
Radical Edward, the one they talk about.
Uh-huh! What have you heard?
Connect D7 to number 2.
That way you can fire the
lasers without the computer.
I'm trusting you on this.
Listen, don't use missiles unless
you have to. They're expensive.
Yeah, right.
1200 to target.
All right, prepare to
shut down your computer.
You'll only have one chance.
That's all I'm gonna need.
And you can give us
the data to prove this?
That that satellite was
acting all on its own?
It's the bounty head,
there's no hacker?
Ed can prove it, no problem.
But remember,
Ed wants a favor in return.
If you do it,
Ed won't take any of the reward.
Oh! Well, now,
aren't you a nice kid!
That's the one.
Some... one...
- You hit it?
- Did you?
No, it saw me coming.
An attack satellite
blocked my laser blast.
Then we have to take out
all the satellites in the sector.
- You've gotta be kidding!
- If we don't, they'll take us out!
These missiles are curving off target!
Oh, the cheap ones are worthless!
This is impossible!
Jet, approach to 20 meters of MPU.
The attack satellites won't fire
when you're that close.
- Then what?
- Have Faye act as a decoy to cover.
- Why me?!
- Thanks, Faye!
All right.
Hurry up! They're all closing in!
She's all yours.
MPU!
MPU, MPU!
Oh, Ed.
Ed, we meet again.
- MPU, they have a bounty out on you.
- Bounty?
Yes, but we'll just
make a copy of you.
Then we'll let them catch
the copy, and you'll be safe.
Safe?
You must be lonely out there, MPU.
If you let us download you, you'll be
with us, and we'll be your friends.
Friends?
Uh-huh. It's not scary here.
And so, we have a strange
ending to a strange case.
The criminal was apprehended.
It turned out to be a spy satellite
disguised as a weather satellite.
Launched before the gate catastrophe
that wrecked the Earth's surface,
according to archives recovered from
the period, the satellite was programmed
to self-activate in the absence
of commands from the Earth.
Well, it was a perfect excuse for
the cops to go on a hacker hunt, huh?
They love these crackdowns.
But I still don't know why it carved
pictures of weird creatures and all.
What in the world
was that all about, huh?
That's easy.
It was lonely, so it drew some friends.
Yahoo! Bebop, hey!
I'm down here! Hurry up!
Hurry! Promise, promise!
Let's go! Come on, Jet! Now!
Ed keeps yelling something
about a promise?
Some promises are made
to be broken, in fact...
most of them are!
Now come on, lift off!
Not coming for Ed. Oh la la.
Why are we going down there,
what's going on?!
Just what did you
promise the kid, Faye?!
She promised Ed! That Ed could
become a real member of Bebop!
Hi, amigos! Welcome, bounty hunters!
Shucks howdy!
It's finally time for Big Shot!
First, today's hot news.
Y'all heard about that renegade
land carving satellite, right?
Of course! It got caught
with a big bounty on it.
Well, just a few minutes ago,
the Earth Police released a report.
- What'd it say?
- Let's see.
The term "bounty" is legal context only
applied to humans or other life forms.
Though there is some controversy regarding
the state of computers as life forms,
legal precedent is clear.
Biological logistics rejects the assertion--
Roundup time, sugar.
What does it all mean?
It's bad news. They won't pay
no bounty on no computer, no how!
Ah! To the guys who caught it,
my heart goes out to you.
Jet, do you know that there are
three things that I particularly hate?
Really.
Kids, animals,
and women with attitudes.
So tell me, Jet.
Why do we have all three of them
neatly gathered in our ship?!
Ed loves piyokos!
And once again, we get no bounty.
Not a single Woolong.
Hey, you're a girl!
Like I said, nothing good
ever comes from Earth.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
No regrets about the
woman who ran away,
but a small thorn
still pricks the heart.
Letting one flow along
with time itself,
living all alone
from that day to this.
But to the sounds of waves
that come and go,
the migrating birds
find their hearts drawn.
Next episode: "Ganymede Elegy."
Jet Black will sing it up with soul.