Oh no! What should I do?
This is the worst pinch
Green Onion Ramen's been in!
Takukto and I are split
right in the middle
on whether or not to let Mitsuki
go to the audition.
My handbook says that
her life will be in danger
if we let her go for it.
And Takuto's feelings seem to be...
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
I have to go...
to the audition.
I won't let you go!
What's with the silly stunt?!
Look at this!
Audition?
Right.
So don't go transforming her
and helping with her audition.
I didn't want to say it,
but something about you and
that girl is similar.
You're sure to recall the time
when you were human if
you associate with her any more.
You know what'll happen then, right?
I love you.
I never want us to part.
I don't want you to turn
into a ghost, Takuto.
I'm tired.
I want to rest just a little.
The whistle's gone.
What should I do?
Now I can't contact Takuto.
Takuto.
I don't want you
to turn into a ghost, Takuto.
- Mitsuki!
- Huh?!
Something's wrong.
Oh, Takuto!
Ma'am!
It doesn't look like
she's in the main house.
Ma'am!
I'm okay.
I just got a little dizzy.
How much worry does
she have to cause me?
To think she'd sneak out of
the hospital in her condition.
- Hospital? Did she collapse?!
- Please lie down.
You haven't slept at all.
No!
I won't let you go.
I won't let go, even if I die.
After all... I was serious when
I confessed my love for you.
But...
It's your 57th time, so...
No matter...
No matter how often I confess
my love, I mean it each time!
Takuto , you jerk!
Oh!
No!
Oww...
Oww!
Are you okay?
Takuto is worrying about me.
It hurts and I can't get up!
Well, your only redeeming
quality is robustness.
So you're okay, right?
Wha—?!
What do you mean by "robust"?!
See? You seem okay.
Oh no.
Since it's come to this,
it's time for my trump card!
If you're not going to listen to my advice,
I'm going to report
everything that's happened to
the Division Chief of Death Spirits.
It's punishment.
Go ahead and tell
if you want to.
Takuto!
Even if backwards letters
appear in the handbook,
or if I'm punished by
the Division Chief of Death Spirits,
today, I have to go.
Why?!
Why are you putting so much
of your heart and soul into this?!
I don't know why myself.
But I can't leave her,
so it can't be helped, right?
I feel that if she becomes
unable to sing, she'll really die.
You're awful.
You're awful, Takuto.
Since it's come to this,
I'll stop that girl from going to
the audition by any means necessary!
I'll interfere!
Where in the world did she go
in that condition?
A whistle?
Dr. Wakaoji.
Has anyone from
her home contacted us?
Her attendant, Ms. Tanaka,
did earlier.
And?
She hasn't gone back home yet.
She dropped the whistle?!
Yes. I have a place in mind,
so I'm going to try looking for her.
I appreciate it.
...clear, continuing from yesterday...
today looks to have the
highest temperature of the summer.
And now, let's get the traffic report from
Miss Kawada at the traffic center.
Miss Kawada?
Yes!
I fell asleep here.
I'm cold.
Takuto hasn't come.
So I guess there's no chance now.
Eichi...
Mitsuki, we can only see
one side of the moon
from the earth.
Really?
A moon that's so beautiful.
But on the backside,
there are many marks from
meteorites that have landed.
It hides its wounds
and keeps shining.
When I first met you,
I thought it was
the perfect name for you.
Eichi, I won't cry.
I won't cry until I see you.
If she sneaked out of the hospital,
there's only one place she'd go.
It has to be the audition venue!
She's not on board.
Good morning.
Oh! Morning, Madoka.
Thank you for yesterday.
I had a lot of fun.
Me, too.
I got good vibes from you yesterday.
I'll do my best today.
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
Okay then,
shall we start the camera test?
All right!
- Please pick up, Mitsuki.
- Okay, Madoka. Please stand here.
Where am I?
Where should I go.?
I can't move anymore.
Oh my, what's wrong with this girl?
It's probably TV or
something, isn't it?
These days, there's a lot of
reality show filming.
I'm sorry I'm not a good girl.
I bet he's worried about me
sneaking out of the hospital.
The audition is looking impossible.
Everyone...
Takuto... Meroko...
They supported me so much.
And I haven't apologized yet.
Why do I like you so much?
My tears are falling...
Here, I just wanted to sing.
I wanted...to see...Eichi.
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki, hang in there!
She's not breathing.
Open your eyes!
Please open your eyes!
Mitsuki!
Eichi?
Takuto?
That was you just now?
What're you doing?!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What're you doing sprawled
out in a place like this?!
Oh! Umm...
- This way!
- Oh!
H-Hey...
Hold it! Hey!
Umm...
Are you in any pain?
Huh?
Oh yeah.
No, not at all.
Good.
What time's the audition?
Let me see.
It's already 11:00?!
What should I do?
The audition's already started!
Oh no.
Hurry. We can still make it.
What?
You're going to have
Eichi notice you, right?
Then don't give up!
Right!
I won't let her
make it in time.
No matter what!
Oh!
What's wrong?
Don't look!
M-Move away from there, quick!
My shoe's caught
and I can't get it out!
- Then...
- Don't look!
I'm sorry!
Did it hurt?
Takuto!
Does it hurt?
No, I'm totally okay.
Good!
Just a little further.
Yeah!
I'm just getting started!
Mitsuki!
A-Are you okay?
Look at her face!
Meroko!
I'm seeing stars in front of me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, somehow.
- Huh?
- What?
No way!
Mitsuki!
Takuto?
That was a close shave.
Oh no!
Is this also TV?
There sure is a lot of filming!
Safe.
Think again.
It's Full Moon!
Full Moon is here!
What?! Full Moon?
Full Moon?
Then, the filming before was...
O-Over there!
W-What should we do?!
- Run!
- Okay!
This way!
An idol wouldn't be in here.
But just in case...
We somehow shook them.
Th-That over there!
Huh?
The studio is in that building.
Okay, let's hurry!
Oh, over there!
She's going into the building!
Have we been found?!
Wait up!
Hey! Wait!
Man, thank goodness.
Oh!
Oh... I-I'm sorry.
But...you see...
I wonder if that'll be
my first kiss...
But, it wasn't unpleasant at all.
Well, I'm sorry it was me!
Huh?
Too bad it wasn't
a certain someone!
When you get right down to it,
it's your fault for collapsing
from shortness of breath.
You...You don't have
to say it like that!
Well, don't worry about it.
That was just CPR.
Well... Umm...
It wasn't a kiss, so...
it won't be your first kiss.
It stopped?
Why?
When we only have
a little further to go!
Is this Meroko's doing?
There's no way that
a half-baked Death Spirit can beat me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for forcing a question
on you that you didn't want to be asked.
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, don't give up.
You've decided to keep at it
until Eichi notices you, right?!
Right.
But, we won't make it in time.
I'll get you there in time.
What?
Meroko!
Go ahead and tell the Division Chief
of Death Spirits if you're going to!
No matter what happens,
I'm going to help this girl!
Got it?!
Takuto...
Let's go.
Okay!
How beautiful.
Even if they're replicas,
even if they're not real,
they're really beautiful, Takuto.
You'll be okay on your own
from here, right?
Right.
Good! Get going!
Okay!
Thank you very much for waiting.
And now for the announcement.
The Mermaid Tear image character
will be Madoka Wakamatsu.
No...
She couldn't make it
to the audition.
That means our assignment
was completed. And that's good, right?
No, it's not!
What do you mean by that?
We've done enough!
It's not necessary to
do her any more favors.
No, not yet.
She won't run away from
everything after this incident!
Singing is not something
she'll give up on so easily.
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Singer's Voice That Can't Be Heard."
- Look forward to it!