Why can't I do it right?
Really...
Noel-chan?
Did you bring your wallet?
Yes.
ID tag?
Handkerchief?
Yes.
Tissue paper?
Map?
Yes.
Compass?
Field rations?
Yes.
Helmet?
Gun?
Grenade?
She was kidding, Kana-chan.
Geez, you really scared me.
You would have known right away if you were thinking rationally.
That's so mean, Rio-sempai.
Those two are getting along really well together, aren't they?
And Rio is acting like an overprotective mother.
All right, here's the list for today.
Listen up.
Your mission today is to go to town and purchase the items on that list.
Got it?
Yes!
Well then, drive safely and be on your way.
Yes.
Commencing departure.
Come back soon!
We're having pot-au-feu for dinner!
Don't stray anywhere.
She's just like a mother.
This is the first time that we're going to town together, isn't it, Noel-chan?
But, this almost feels like my first time in town...
Wonderful!
I wonder what that is?
It looked completely different during the festival.
This is a very calm and peaceful town.
The first one was Nue, the proud roof decoration of Trois.
Its purpose is warding off evil spirits.
Following that, a drinking fountain.
It was modeled after the twelfth Archduke of Helvetia, Akira Arcadia II.
We've arrived.
Oh! What we saw earlier?
Yes, I was instructed to drive safely.
Thank you.
I get it now.
Noel-chan is really well informed.
Hey girls,
could you make up your minds if you're coming in or not?
You're obstructing my business.
The Oba-san from the festival!
Onee-san.
No pressure, as usual.
You kids just can't take a hint, can you?
Then at least call me Naomi.
Naomi-san...?
So, the the next shipment will be next month?
By the way, does she know?
You're a bunch of unusual girls as always, huh?
Even though you're soldiers-
Excuse me...
W-What?
About that...
You were completely captivated by it when you arrived, right?
Do you like it?
Um... M-May I touch it?
A-flat.
This is a fish, isn't it?
What is it called?
Well, that's...
It's not a fish.
Why?
That's a dolphin.
It's closer to a human than a fish.
Back when there were living creatures in the sea, it was a marine mammal.
The sea?
It lived in the sea?
How lovely.
That old guy sure is good at making these things.
He doesn't look it, but he's quite a romantic.
Do you know the person who made it?
There's a big factory outside town.
All of our glassware comes from there.
I would love to see the place where they're made.
That's not a problem.
What is?
We're going there after this.
I see.
You're having Takemikazuchi's parts made at the glass factory.
Yes. Even Naomi is collecting accessories from the old era.
But, you're really amazing, Noel-chan.
You can repair such a complicated machine in a blink.
In a blink?
Unlike me, I'm having a hard time just memorizing the bugling signal codes.
It's not really that difficult...
That's because machines do not... betray you.
Noel-chan-
Here!
Your balance is ¥2,750,000.
What? Do we get that much back?
That's a mistake.
The balance is ¥2.75.
You're the same as always, Noel-chan.
Here's your change.
She's right.
The morning bugle recently... was that you?
Y-Yes.
I'm still terrible at it, sorry...
That's fine. I like it though.
It... well, somehow wakes you up completely.
Stare...
I was just thinking that I must improve quickly, so that I won't bother the people in town.
Seiya, that's unfair!
Is that so? Come and get it then!
Kanata, I...
Ouch!
Sorry-
Yay, you knocked into someone.
I'm so terribly sorry!
Oh, you are...
The girl from the festival!
That clumsy Onee-chan!
I'm so relieved.
You seem to have recovered completely.
You murderer!
Seiya-san!
These people are not responsible for your parents' incident, right?
They're all the same.
I hate soldiers!
Get out of our town immediately!
Playing that awful bugle every morning; it sucks!
Hey, Seiya!
I'm truly sorry... for his rudeness.
I-It's fine.
That boy is a war orphan.
Because of that, when he sees soldiers, he indiscriminately...
Noel-chan.
I'm fine.
It's true that we are soldiers.
So...
Noel-chan...
That's true. We are soldiers.
I did recite the Paradore's Oath when I enlisted.
I thought I understood that, but...
Geez, what am I saying?
It's something that I've understood from the very beginning.
I'm not going to start speaking hesitantly now.
That's right!
To be fully prepared in case something happens, I must improve quickly.
Everyone would be in trouble if there was no bugle call, right?
We can see it now.
That's the glass factory?
You're amazing, Noel-chan.
This is the first time I've seen a building this big!
This didn't work either, huh?
Is spherical aberration the problem?
And I was so sure that I got the refraction right.
I-I'm the new recruit, Sorami Kanata.
It's an honor to meet you!
Yeah.
And, well... I...
So, how was the timing before the error occurred?
The seek time barely fluctuated.
The distortion of the image during shutdown was less than previously-
Sorry!
The boss doesn't notice anything else when he's engrossed in work.
But, he's really amazing, that old man, Carl.
He's an amazing mechanic, one of five given the title of Meister in this country.
He's won competitions everywhere, and has even presented his work to the Archduke.
Maria, move your hands not your mouth!
Yes! Sorry, boss.
I'm not even worthy of that title...
I'm way out of her league.
What is that?
Takemikazuchi's optic sensor lens.
That's the original.
I need two of them for the repairs, so I've commissioned for its duplication.
But, it's not going well.
Even though it's so pretty?
In addition to silicon dioxide aggregated in the engine,
these are composed of sodium oxide and magnesium oxide.
This defines the chromatic and circumference aberrations.
In other words, it corrects the image distortion.
But, we do not know the proportion of the compounds.
It's a magical product from the previous era, after all.
I thought glass was just pretty, but it's quite complex, huh?
In Seize,
it's possible to gather silica deposits,
so many small workshops that specialize in industrial art objects have gathered here.
Even this factory was originally a workshop like that.
But, when the war intensified,
the military increased the demand for glass products.
This factory prospered because of the war.
Kanata, I like machines.
Yes.
But, there are times when machines hurt people.
Even Takemikazuchi must have killed many people in the past.
Do you think machines are scary if they have killed people in the past?
Yeah.
But,
I think the people who used the machines to kill are scarier than the machines themselves.
Even this bugle,
it sounds bad when I play it, but when Rio-sempai plays, it sings beautifully.
I'm sure it's the same for a tank, isn't it?
And just a while ago, Rio-sempai let me hear a song from Takemikazuchi.
It made such beautiful music.
I'm sure it's a good tank, that Takemikazuchi.
That's right. Next time, let's-
Noel-chan.
Let her sleep.
She must have worked all night again.
Noel-chan works really hard at repairing Takemikazuchi.
I know.
This little lady is a true mechanic.
If she wasn't, I wouldn't have accepted such a troublesome request.
Here,
put this on her.
Thank you very much.
By the way, you guys stopped by Windmill, didn't you?
How's Naomi-san doing?
Right!
She said that your boss is a wonderful romantic.
That's what she said, huh?
That's great isn't it, boss?
Shut up!
Get back to work right now!
Whoa! He's mad.
Work, work.
But, is the technology from the past really so amazing?
Yes, it is.
But, the boss always says...
"No matter how amazing, it was made by humans like us."
"There's no way we can't make it!"
You also agree, don't you?
Yes... that's what I'd like to say, but...
I see.
Certainly, Rio-san's bugling is different from yours.
I've always worried about it.
How I can be like Sempai?
I believe that I've been practicing as hard as I can.
Even my lips... well, see how swollen they've become.
But...
No matter how I try, Sempai's sounds elude me.
I guess I really don't have the talent...
Ojou-chan.
Yes!
"Talent" is the worst excuse used by those who give up.
Hand me that.
I don't really know about bugles, but...
I do know of a mistake that young people often make.
Ojou-chan, you're forcing the sound out, aren't you?
Look, I wasn't trying to create a shape like this.
The glass itself wants to be formed in this shape.
Thank you very much, Carl Oji-san.
Let the sound itself reverberate as it desires...
Morning...
It feels like the sun rose sooner just for her.
She's a craftsman in her own way, too.
That's a great sound.
Really?
Glass is comprised of dust and impurities,
and depending on its content, the sound subtly changes.
Even if we cannot hear the difference,
those with sharp intuition could definitely define it.
I'll have Kanata find the closest sound,
from all the samples that we've made so far.
That way, I could probably...
"Now, go listen to their voices, Ojou-chan."
"Okay!"
Noel-chan sure has changed a lot since she arrived, hasn't she?
Really?
Yes.
You did it!
You did it, Noel-chan!
Thank you.
This is the first time I've seen Noel's smile.
Next:
Mountain Hiking - The ends of the World.