Owner.
One more cup of coffee, please.
Um...
Actually, I...
I have a favor to ask of you!
What?
A favor?
Yes.
This is my problem, so I shouldn't be asking for your help...
but could you listen to what I have to say?
Well, if I only have to listen...
Hyouka
Great!
Troubled Descendant of the Classic Literature Club
I had an uncle named Sekitani Jun.
Would you help me remember what he told me?
I don't really understand.
I'm sorry! I jumped the gun...
I'll explain everything.
My uncle went to India seven years ago,
and went missing.
Sign: Japanese Citizen Gone Missing
When I was a little girl, I was very attached to my uncle.
He would answer whatever ridiculous questions I had.
It was like he knew absolutely everything.
When I was in kindergarten, I learned that he was in the Classic Literature Club,
which made me very curious.
I suppose it's because it rhymed with the basic mixture kelp we always had in home.
Was that a pun?
One day, I asked my uncle something about the club.
That was the only time he was ever reluctant to answer my question.
He was reluctant?
Yes.
I kept nagging him until he finally caved.
When I heard his answer, I...
What happened?
...cried.
I don't remember if I was scared or sad,
but I broke into tears.
You cried?
My mom was shocked, and rushed by my side,
but my uncle didn't even try to comfort me.
Only the shock of the event remains in my memory now,
and I can't remember any other details.
It started to bother me when I became a middle schooler,
and I started to wonder why my uncle was reluctant to tell me,
and why he didn't comfort me.
I think I've done everything I can do.
I even approached the introverted Sekitani Family as best as I could.
But I couldn't find anything to help me remember.
That's why I thought the Classic Literature Club was my last hope when I became a Kamiyama High student.
So that's what your "personal" reason was, huh?
Unfortunately, I didn't know the club was on verge of disbanding.
I asked around in the staff room,
but no one knew what happened when my uncle was a student 45 years ago.
So why are you asking me  for help?
It's because...
...you might be able to come up with a conclusion beyond my imagination!
Like with the locked door or book mysteries...
and the recruitment note too!
I know you'll lead me to an answer!
You give me too much credit.
They were all just luck.
Let me bet on your luck, then!
It's too much effort.
I can tell that this problem will eventually turn into a life-changing revelation for Chitanda,
but does she really think an energy conserver like me would want to take part in it?
She must be joking.
Why are you asking me for help?
There must someone more useful that can help you.
You just have to use the wisdom of the crowd.
Why don't you ask your friends?
Oreki.
I'm not the type of person who goes around telling people about my past.
This isn't something I could just tell anyone.
Sorry.
I know I'm being unreasonable.
I know I shouldn't drag you along with my quest for lost memories.
Even so,
you're far less cooperative than my uncle, but you've come through for me too!
Sorry  for being uncooperative.
You might've just reminded me of my uncle.
We have three more years left of high school.
Just take your time looking for clues.
I want to reclaim my memory before my uncle dies.
Before he dies?
Yes.
Legally speaking, if someone's whereabouts are unknown for seven years,
they will be declared dead.
I see.
My uncle's family had planned to settle this matter too.
They're also planning a small funeral for him.
That's why...
I want to keep what he told me in my heart...
...for the funeral.
I'm sorry.
"Houtarou,
"It's not like you're interested in anything else, right?"
I can't bear that responsibility for you.
That's why I can't tell you that I'm accepting your request.
But I'll remember what you've told me,
and if I ever come across any hints,
I'll definitely let you know.
If you're having trouble analyzing the information,
then I'll help you out.
Okay.
If that's fine with you, then I'll help you.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Right.
Living a high school life isn't all fun and roses.
Take the midterms for example.
First term midterms have started in Kamiyama High.
All club activities are on hold during this period.
The Classic Literature Club is no exception,
but we weren't doing anything in the first place, so it doesn't really make any difference.
Library
We shouldn't be forced to change our routine either, but...
there was nothing we could do without access to the room.
First Term Midterm Examination Schedule
Modern Lit.
Social Science
English I
Math A
Math I
World History B
Science
Classic Lit.
First Term Midterm Examination
Math I
World History B
First Term Midterm Examination
Science
Okay, time's up.
The midterms are finally over.
What a drag.
"Dear Oreki Houtarou,
"I'm currently in Istanbul.
"I didn't really plan it out, so I'm suffering from jet lag after visiting Japan.
"so I haven't taken a tour of the city yet."
What's she up to now?
"This journey is really interesting.
"I'm certain that I won't regret these days when I look back in ten years.
"By the way, how's the Classic Literature Club?
"Did you get more members to join?
"There's something I thought would be important, so I'll include it in this letter.
"Are you interested in making an anthology?
"Our club used to make one for the culture festival every year.
"Is the tradition is still going strong?
"I figured that you might not know how to make one.
"You won't find our anthologies in the library.
"You should be looking for it in the club room.
"There's an unused drug safe inside,
"and the archives are inside.
"It's not locked.
"I'll call you when I get to Pristina.
"Best regards,
"Oreki Tomoe."
A drug safe?
Your timing couldn't have been better.
Shouman
When everything shines under the sunlight, lush green fills the view
Hyouka
Geography Storage Room
Really?
Yes.
I brought her letter too.
I see. A drug safe, huh?
It's not here.
Right, I didn't see one!
Wh-Where are the anthologies? Where are they?!
Come on, calm down, Chii.
"Chii"?
Chitanda, the letter only says the drug safe is in the clubroom.
My sister graduated two years ago.
The clubroom changed while she was gone.
I see.
So that's why.
So do you know where it was two years ago?
I asked our club advisor.
It's in the biology storage room.
Oh?
You're actually prepared today.
I only increased my efficiency.
You're really excited about this.
That's not true.
I'm never excited.
Let's go, then!
By the way, where's Fukube?
Oh, he's with the Sewing Club.
He said he's researching on the latest summer fashion trends or something...
Oreki!
Huh? It's locked.
Is anyone there?
Sorry about that.
I locked the door.
Do you want to join the Wall Newspaper Club?
No, that's not why we're here.
This is the Wall Newspaper Club's room?
That's right.
This smell...
Is it cologne?
No, it's air freshener?
Did you need me for something?
Um... I'm the leader of the Classic Literature Club,
Chitanda Eru.
You're Tougaito, right? From Class 3-E.
How do you know my name?
I saw you at the Manninbashi estate last year.
At the Manninbashi estate?
Wait, are you Chitanda from the family of farm owners?
Yes. Your family has been very kind to my father.
Uh... Likewise.
I see, Chitanda family's...
What's bothering him?
So why are you here?
Right!
I heard Classic Literature Club's archives are stored in the biology store room.
This room used to be the Classic Literature Club's room, right?
Y-Yes.
I think it was back when I was a freshman.
So...
So have you seen the anthologies?
Uh... I haven't.
I see.
Thank you for your help.
Don't leave!
Please! It should be in this room.
Please let us search inside.
Sorry, but I told you that I haven't see it.
But...
Let's go back.
Don't you think something fishy is going on?
I do.
Don't leave, then!
I'm sorry, but please look elsewhere.
But we have information stating that it's in here!
If it's not in here, then we'll have to search the entire school!
The entire school?
No way in hell!
We won't take very long,
so please let us search inside.
I'm begging you too.
I don't want outsiders entering here.
But this is a classroom before it's a clubroom.
Who are you?
Ibara Mayaka of the Classic Literature Club.
Fine.
Go ahead.
But don't go snooping around everywhere.
Where are other club members?
Oh, they took the day off.
I was thinking about the article for the June issue.
Kami High Monthly Report Vol. 496
Juniors field trip
General assemby
Student Council Elections
About community service
One article per day
Plans for June
It's called Kami High Monthly Report.
We've been around for a long time, and we've published about 500 volumes.
It doesn't look like it's in this clubroom.
So it wasn't here...
What should we do?
Oreki?
Tougaishi.
Did you take anything in or out of here when they changed rooms?
Now that you mention it, I remember carrying a few cardboard boxes.
Cardboard boxes?
Yeah.
That means...
But it's going to be pretty difficult trying to get our hands on it.
I guess I can try to corner him.
Sorry, but there are so many things in this room.
I think searching this place is going to take some time.
I want to get our club advisor for a thorough search of this place.
Is that all right with you?
No, it's not.
I told you not to snoop around.
But we won't have any more clues if it's not here!
I promise we'll put everything back in place.
Pleas-
I said no, god dammit!
But...
I'm busy.
Thorough search my ass!
Your stupid anthologies aren't here!
Got it? Now get lost!
Bingo.
Tougaishi.
We're interested in what's inside the drug cabinet.
What?!
The anthologies should be inside.
We won't bother you as long as we can find them.
By the way, we have to stop by the library now.
If you find the anthologies while we're gone,
can you leave them in the Geography storage room for us?
The door's open.
A-Are you... Are you trying to...
Trying to?
Fine.
If I find them, I'll bring them to you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Hey, freshman.
You haven't told me your name yet.
Oreki Houtarou.
I do feel bad about this.
Hey, Oreki.
Why are we waiting here?
Energy conservation.
What's that supposed to mean?
By the way, Chitanda.
What is the Tougaito Family known for?
Let's see...
They're very influencial in secondary education,
and they're a family with many members working in the field of education.
No wonder.
It's been five minutes.
Let's head back.
Oh, there they are.
These are the anthologies.
Hey, Oreki!
How did you make this happen?
Did you know something?
Well, I just threatened him a bit.
Threatened him?
Ibara, how good are you at keeping secrets?
Why do you ask? I'll keep it secret if you ask me to.
I see.
Let's take it from the top.
He was clearly alarmed about us when he came out of the room.
You're right.
What about the inside of the room?
The windows were open and he had the fan on,
but the setup would've blown his manuscripts away.
Maybe he just wanted to ventilate the room.
Yes.
Why did he want to ventilate the room?
To elaborate, why did he go through the trouble of locking the room and setting up infrared sensors for...
S-Stop right there!
What do you mean by infrared sensors?
Oh, I saw small, strange boxes on the hallway walls.
I assumed the thing with an antenna was the receiver.
When someone walks by,
it probably sets off an alarm.
I can't believe you actually figured that out.
It's basically just analyzing your surroundings.
The question is, why would he take such precautions and try to ventilate the room in a hurry?
To get rid of some smell?
That's the most logical answer.
He smelled like air fresheners too.
The smell you want to hide that much would be...
Cigarettes.
When you're the son of a family known in the field of education,
then you have conceal illegal activities no matter what.
I see.
I'm sure Chitanda would've noticed it right away if she didn't have a cold.
Hold on!
Where were the anthologies anyway?
They were inside the safe. Where else?
Oreki!
I-I'm not trying to tease you.
The drug safe was under the makeshift table.
He must have hidden his cigarettes and lighter inside.
That's why, when I asked him for permission to search the place with a teacher,
he panicked the way he did.
You really are a weirdo.
Why are you saying that to the epitome of the average person?
Guys!
Sunflower!
Satoshi.
We found the archives for the anthologies.
Huh?
Oh, you're right.
Wow, this is how it was?
They sure look handmade when they're 40 years old!
What's up, Chitanda?
It's called stencil printing.
More accurately, it's printed by a mimeograph machine invented in the Meiji Era.
What's up?
I guess schools still didn't have Xerox machines in school in the '70s.
Oreki...
Look, this one was printed using a photocopier.
Come here.
Oh, this one is...
This is it.
Hyouka...
Volume two?
This is the one I found when I was little.
I brought it to my uncle,
and asked him what it was for.
You remember it now?
Please take a look inside.
Things about my uncle are written inside.
Something must have happened.
45 years ago, in this very club.
"The Cultural Festival is upon us once more.
"It's been a year since Sekitani graduated.
"In a single year, he turned from a hero into a legend.
"Unfortunately, all our disputes and sacrifices,
"and even his smile are starting to be covered in sands of time.
"Actually, it is probaly for the best.
"We mustn't remember,
"because it was not a heroic tale in any way.
"All objective accounts are gone,
"and everything gradually turn into a piece of classic literature from a historical perspective.
"As our records may one day become a piece of classic literature to readers of the future.
"October 13th, 1968.
"Kouriyama Youko."
The "last year" they refer to is 45 years ago.
In that case, that Sekitani in the Classic Literature Club must be my uncle.
Sekitani
The answer to my question was also related to the club.
You have enough clues now.
But I just can't remember.
I'm so close... I'm so close, yet...
What did he tell me on that day?
Sekitani
What exactly happened to my uncle 45 years ago?
All you have to do is check.
But it says his tales shouldn't be remembered.
Maybe the answer would only lead to sorrow.
Some things are better left unknown, right?
Even if it's something that happened 45 years ago?
Are you sure?
I am.
It's written right here.
"Everything gradually turn into a piece of classic literature from a historical perspective."
It means we'll only find the facts.
Right.
Besides, it says "last year" in volume two.
so all we have to do is check volume one...
Wait, what?!
All of them are here except for volume one!
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね　見つけてね
Please come and find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
芽生えてた温もり　暖かくて戸惑う
I'm at a loss to this warmth growing inside me
こんな気持ちをまだ　あなたは分からないの
You're still oblivious to my feelings
その視線には意味なんて別にないはず
I'm sure your gaze doesn't mean anything
だって友達にしてるのと同じ
Because you look the same way at your friends
明け方に消えてく　小さな願い星
The tiny wishing stars disappear into the dawn
夜の間だけの魔法
Our magic only lasts until daybreak
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
Next week: "Glorious Olden Days of the Classic Literature Club."
Glorious Olden Days of the Classic Literature Club