Oh, are you here to see Kamijou-kun?
Y-Yeah...
I'm sorry, but the date of his examination was moved up, so he's in the rehabilitation area right now.
I see... thanks.
She sure visits a lot, doesn't she?
Yeah, but I'm glad she does. That patient is difficult to handle.
I hope she's cheering him up.
He was a violin prodigy before the accident, right?
Even if he were able to walk again...
it's likely he'll never be able to play an instrument with those fingers.
Out of all people, why did that happen to Kyousuke?
No matter how much I move my fingers, they don't do any good to anyone.
Why did that happen to Kyousuke instead of me?
If I use my wish to heal him, what would he think?
Would he just tell me thank you? Would that be it?
Or do I want him to say something more?
I'm... a horrible person.
Now that I think about it, back then I still didn't know anything;
just what it meant to wish for a miracle, and what it would cost.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll continue walking upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでく
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 4  There are such things as miracles and magic
yesy: the most trusted name in madoka
we're doing it live
This show is brought to you by the sponsors you see here.
Is that a mole?
There, I got it.
Madoka?
Huh?
If you don't hurry up and eat, you'll be late to school.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong, Nee-chan?
W-Was the food bad?
No, it's good.
It's really good.
Because I'm alive, I get to experience my dad's great cooking...
And, like, I kept telling Yuuka and she still didn't get it.
She was almost crying, like, "Huh? What? Did I say something weird again?"
I was trying so hard not to laugh.
Sayaka-chan, about yesterday...
Sorry. Not right now. We'll talk later.
That's totally weird, right?
Yeah, that's kind of...
While it's true that our understanding of a woman's prime childbearing age is based off of scientific evidence,
○
The Indicative Mood and Subjunctive Mood
i  )   uses rains / will cancel, and
ii )  uses had / would buy.
These two sentences are not demonstrating
the difference between past and present.
i) says "rains tomorrow" and is referring to
something that could happen in reality.
ii) says "if I had a lot of money" and is not referring to
something that's actually happening.
The Indicative Mood:
Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is probable.
The Subjunctive Mood: Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is not
consistent with the facts.
The Indicative Mood:
Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is probable.
The Indicative Mood:
Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is probable.
The Indicative Mood:
Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is probable.
The Indicative Mood:
Indicates the speaker's
judgment that the statement is probable.
using this to estimate a woman's age of marriageability is a huge mistake.
Thus, women over thirty plainly still have the chance for a loving marriage.
Which means that you shouldn't be using the past perfect here, but rather the present progressive tense—
It kind of feels like we're in a different country now.
School, Hitomi-chan—nothing's changed since yesterday. But it feels like I'm surrounded by strangers.
Nobody knows what we know.
Nobody knows about the witches or Mami-san.
We know, and nobody else does.
It's like we're living in a different world, seeing different things.
Sayaka-chan...
It all changed a long time ago.
We should've realized it sooner.
What about you, Madoka?
Do you still want to become a magical girl?
Yeah... That makes sense.
I know it's not fair... It's pretty selfish for me to back out now,
but... I just can't...
Just remembering how she died... I can't breathe.
I'm so scared.
I hate this.
Mami-san was really kind.
As an example of the resolve we'd need to fight, she...
Hey, Kyubey, what'll happen to this city?
Who will protect everyone from the witches now that Mami-san's gone?
This has been Mami's territory for a while now, but now that there's no one here, the other magical girls will act.
Others hunting for witches will come here soon.
But they're just after the Grief Seeds, right? Just like that transfer student.
It's true that Mami was a rare breed.
Normally you'd be less inclined to put yourself in danger if you didn't stand to gain something from it.
Everybody wants to be rewarded for their actions, after all.
So that means...
But I think only another magical girl would really be able to criticize that.
I understand how you two feel.
It's unfortunate, but I can't pressure you into it.
I guess this is it.
I need to go search again for girls who need my contract.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
Me too. I'm sorry for getting you involved.
It was short, but it was fun being with you, Madoka. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Tomoe
Mami
British Tea Life
A Tea Magazine
for the Modern Adult
I'm sorry I'm so weak...
I'm sorry.
Homura-chan...
You're blaming yourself too much for this, Kaname Madoka.
Huh?
There's no one who can criticize you for your choices.
If there was, I'd never forgive them.
You listened to my warning.
Yeah.
If I had listened to you sooner...
That still wouldn't have changed Tomoe Mami's fate.
But you were able to change your own.
I'm happy I was able to save at least one person.
Y-You know, Homura-chan... You seem like a veteran, but in a different way from Mami-san.
That might be true. I won't deny it.
Have you seen a lot of people die like yesterday?
I have.
How many?
Enough to give up on counting.
I wonder if her room will stay like that forever.
Tomoe Mami only had distant relatives.
I'm sure it'll be a while before anyone reports her missing.
No one... will notice that she died?
That's just how it is.
If someone dies in there, there is no corpse left behind.
She'll be deemed forever missing in this world.
That's what happens to magical girls in the end.
That's horrible...
She fought alone to protect everyone, but no one even realizes it...
That's terrible.
That's the contract we made to receive this power.
It's not for anyone else.
You keep fighting for the wish you made for yourself.
Even if no one notices, even if no one remembers you at all, that's just how it is.
I'll remember.
I won't forget Mami-san.
I never will!
I see.
Tomoe Mami's lucky to have someone who thinks that.
Enough to make me jealous.
I won't...
I won't forget you, either!
I won't forget how you saved us yesterday!
Homura-chan?
You're too kind.
Huh?
Don't forget that kindness can sometimes bring forth an even greater sadness.
Mobile Ringtone Download!
Claris' new single: Connect.
On sale starting February 2nd.
Everyone please listen!
Kalafina/Magia.
What are you listening to?
La Fille aux Cheveux de lin. (The Girl with the Flaxen Hair)
Oh, Debussy, right?
That's a pretty song.
Everyone thinks I don't listen to classical music. I mean take a look at me.
So sometimes people get really surprised when I know the name of a song and stuff.
It's so unexpected, people really start to respect me for it.
It's because you taught me all about it.
If you didn't, I probably would never have had the chance to really appreciate this type of music.
Sayaka, you...
Huh?
What is it?
Sayaka, are you making fun of me?
Why are you still making me listen to music?
Are you trying to harass me?
Well you like music, so...
I don't want to listen to anything anymore!
I just sit here listening to music I can't even play anymore!
I just... I just...!
I can't move my fingers anymore.
I can't even feel pain.
My hand is worthless!
It'll be okay.
It'll all work out.
If you don't give up, I'm sure someday...
They told me to give up.
They told me to give up on performing again.
My doctor told me personally that with current medical science it just won't happen.
I won't be able to use my hand again.
It won't get better unless there's a miracle or someone uses magic.
That's possible.
Miracles and magic do exist.
I think we could be friends with Homura-chan if we just talked.
I wonder why she ended up fighting with Mami-san.
Huh?
Hitomi-chan...
Hitomi-chan!
Didn't you have practice today?
That's what happened to that woman from before!
Hitomi-chan!
Hey, Hitomi-chan!
Oh, Kaname-san, good day.
Wh-What's wrong?
Where are you trying to go?
Where? Somewhere much better than here, yes.
Hitomi-chan...
Oh, I know. You should come with me.
Yes, that would just be wonderful!
What should I do?
Isn't this...
If I could just get a hold of Homura-chan...
No, I can't! I don't know her cell number.
That's right. I'm worthless.
I couldn't even run this one small factory right.
There's no place for me in this world anymore. Not now.
Listen up, Madoka. If you handle these things improperly, some of them can cause terrible things to happen.
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
Super Wash
For toilet cleaning, steri-
lization, and deodorization!
r Wash
er Wash
Everyone here will die.
Don't get it wrong, okay?
No!
You can't do that!
You musn't interrupt them.
They're performing a holy ritual.
But that's dangerous!
Everyone here will die!
That's right! We are all going on a journey to another wonderful world!
Do you understand just how wonderful that is?
Our living bodies are holding us back.
Kaname-san, you'll understand soon!
Let go of me!
Powerful Bacteria Killer
GET WHITE
Danger Do Not Mix
Powerful Bacteria Killer
GET WHITE
Danger Do Not Mix
Powerful Bacteria Killer
GET WHITE
Wh-What should I do...
What should I do?!
N-No!
This can't be happening!
No! Someone save me!
I wonder if this is a punishment of some sort...
I'm sure this happened because I'm weak... because I'm a liar.
That's why... I'm being punished.
Sayaka-chan?
This is the end!
Man, sorry about that.
That was close, wasn't it?
Sayaka-chan... you're wearing...
Huh?
I guess you can say I had a change of heart.
It's fine.
I did fine for my first time on the job, didn't I?
But...
You...
Hmph.
Pretty late, aren't you, Ms. Transfer Student?
I didn't expect you to come, of all people.
I heard Mami kicked the bucket.
I came all the way out here, too.
I mean, what gives? This isn't what you told me.
Sorry, but there's already a new magical girl in this area.
She just made a contract not too long ago, though.
What the hell? That really pisses me off.
But, you know, I don't think I want to give such a great spot to a rookie.
What are you planning, Kyouko?
Isn't it obvious?
All I have to do is... beat the crap...
out of her.
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光がときを超えて
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ壊すだろう
Now that you've drank every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干した君が望むものは何？
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
I want to see you, smiling with the power to destroy even God,
子供の頃夢に見せた古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic you showed me in my dreams when I was young.
神さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
that now lays in my frightened hands.
思いだけで頼るすべて
This wish will awaken that light.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Connect
Bluray and DVDs on sale soon!
Included
That means you get to look at cute Madoka as much as you want from every angle!
Episode 1
Original
Ending
Episode 2
Version
Spe|cial
Included
Original Drama CD directed
by Urobochi Gen
Episode 1 and 2 Original Ending Version
Now you just have to buy it!
God, Sayaka-chan...
On sale starting March 30th!
Illustrator Kobayashi Jin
I'm flying high!
Magical Girl Sayaka-chan will do everything she can to protect Mitakihara City!
Episode 5      There's no way I regret anything
There's no way I regret anything.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: limitbreakingcat
Timer: euronymous
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Encoder: Miku
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
goof
euronymous