I'm starving!
Sorry!
Really, I swear!
Yes, that's right.
Not at all.
It's my job as class representative.
Hey, over there!
C'mon, hurry!
Move, move!
Oh, sorry!
I'm hungry! I'm so hungry!
What?
I won't be able to wait until I get back to the classroom!
Shortcut time!
I'll wipe off my indoor shoes after!
Wha—
Hey, hey! Are those—
Th-These are... bread crusts!
These Are Bread Crusts
You still eat as much as ever, Futaba!
Yeah, this is me holding back, though.
Really?
Actually, I wonder how you eat so little, Hayama.
Is that enough?
My body is more efficient than yours.
Want to eat some of my side dishes?
Can I?! Yay!
You can have some, too.
What is the matter with the two of you?
Why are you eating here, too?
How bothersome!
Amazing!
You just said "desu wa"!
Wow, a real rich girl!
All right, now.
Time to "hold back."
Really, now, what is the matter with you?
Oh, we haven't introduced ourselves yet.
I'm Hayama.
I'm doing Class 3 the favor of being their class representative.
"Doing them the favor"...?
This is Odagiri Futaba from the same class.
Nice to meet'cha!
I-I am Nishikawa Youko from Class 2.
I know.
You're famous, you know.
Famous?!
Fine, telling a student not to touch me
with their filthy hands was not proper.
I haven't heard about that.
And I am not secretively eating alone
because nobody will eat with me after that.
Er, we weren't asking.
Hey, you don't have friends?
My, you are direct!
I do not have similar interests, and I do not
know what to talk about in the first place.
We're talking just fine right now, though.
Right?
This is nice, huh.
It's pretty fun to eat outdoors.
U-Um...
Oh, the first bell.
Huh?
Oh, no!
I'm done!
See you, Yoko.
See you later.
Huh? U-Um...
Oh, bread crusts are yummy when you
deep fry them and sprinkle sugar on them.
Fry them and use sugar?!
I have never heard of that.
What kind of recipe is—
Hurry, let's go!
Our teacher is strict about being on time.
We have English next, right?
Yup.
Did you do your homework?
Hm?
What odd girls.
Still...
...that may have been my first lunch
with others since I came to this school.
So this is their class?
I sorta got sleepy...
I so hear you!
Nishikawa...?
What's she doing?
I made it to the flash sale on time again!
Oh, bread crusts are yummy when you
deep fry them and sprinkle sugar on them.
Hm, do I have any sugar left?
All right, lunchtime!
You're getting a little full of yourself
Whatever do you mean, Nishiyama?
I know you badmouthed Kondo to the teacher yesterday!
All I did was deliver the printouts to him.
For Kondo, the one on duty, since she
didn't do her job for some reason.
Huh?!
A-Anyway, I want to settle things with you!
Follow me.
All right.
Don't be too hard on her.
I don't take orders from you!
Um, I was talking to Hayama, actually...
I wonder what they'll think?
Say, you two...
I-It's not as if I was expecting them!
And now I can eat lunch alone, like usual.
Alone...
Aw, that sucked!
Futaba...?
You said you wanted take a shortcut.
Well, I didn't want to keep Yoko waiting.
Hayama!
Sorry, Yoko.
Did you wait long?
Y-You're late!
Five whole minutes late!
Sorry, a nuisance picked a fight with me.
What?! Are you all right?
Yep!
She cried at the end for some reason, though.
I wonder if something was wrong?
Huh?!
Best not to ask.
What?
Is it a perv?
Like a stalker?!
Yamaji!
You know him?
He's a former family servant.
I sincerely apologize!
What— Yamaji?!
I was laboring under a misapprehension.
I thought that was just a whim yesterday...
So he was here yesterday, too?
But I would accept a whim!
After all, it's a miracle for Miss Yoko to make school friends!
Wh-What does that mean?!
For you, a ruined shadow of the
rich young lady you once were,
yet unable to let go of your upper-class
attitude after the company's bankruptcy
due to your pampered upbringing,
to make friends with normal commoners
at school must surely be a miracle!
I-I see...
Th-That's not how it is!
Yamaji's exaggerating!
Please take care of Miss Yoko forever!
As her school friends!
Well, shall we eat?
Huh?
Hayama...
E-Er, listen, my—
Isn't it nice to be outside?
It's so much fun to eat surrounded by nature.
My—
Oh, I knew you couldn't really make friends!
Yamaji!
How horribly noisy they are!
I'd at least like to quietly enjoy a book during break time...
These loud voices aren't ladylike at all.
How can I be social with such people?
Hey, Yoko! Hey!
Futaba!
Her smile is so bright!
Wh-What is it?
Um, I forgot my math textbook.
Can I borrow yours?
My class doesn't have math today so I didn't bring it.
Aw really?
Shoot...
I'm sorry!
In the old days, I would have had a servant fetch it at once!
Oh, no, it's not that big a deal.
Later!
Phew, I'm starving!
I'm sorry about before.
About the textbook?
No worries, it's my bad for forgetting it.
And she hardly pays attention
in class anyway, book or no book.
Right, right!
Sheesh, Hayama, you say the
rudest things with no hesitation!
Oh? Didn't I speak the truth?
Okay, lunchtime!
Time to eat!
Wh-What is that?
Huh?
You don't know what white bread is?
Yes, but why are you eating a whole loaf?!
Buying more than one thing is too much work.
That's the issue?
Are you having bread crusts again, Yoko?
Yes!
Look how many you can get for such little money!
I was so moved the first time I saw these!
But don't you need more nutrients?
Not to worry!
Now they're perfectly nutritious!
Um, not really...
My poor Miss Yoko!
Him again!
Yamaji?
I'll have to call the police if you keep trespassing.
Oh, I'm authorized to be here.
I refill the school vending machines.
It's a side job.
Oh my.
That's fine, then.
No, stalkers are not fine!
That is unfair!
What about my quietly watching her unseen
from the shadows makes you think I'm a stalker?!
You're the real deal!
I'm just concerned for Miss Yoko.
No sooner had I taken over my late grandfather's
position as servant than I was suddenly let go...
I'm so worried about how the young miss
will get along among the common folk,
I have to keep an eye on her.
She has such an explosive temper,
and when she doesn't get her way,
it triggers a chemical reaction.
Yamaji!
Miss Yoko, take these!
They're clearance goods from my job,
but they're not quite expired yet.
Yamaji, you...
Uh-oh, my next job is waiting.
Goodbye!
Huh?
If he pities you that much, he should give you cash.
I bet he's barely making ends meet, too.
Honestly, I can't believe him.
Pudding
Does he think these will make me...
Make me feel...
Yoko.
Drat!
Now I've been mortified, thanks to Yamaji.
I've finally made friends.
I have to make sure not to turn them off me.
Miss Yoko, here is today's expired food.
Please, take it.
Why does he have to do this during lunchtime?!
Th-Thank you.
I'll take my leave now.
Keep a cool head, Yoko.
Don't jump for joy and make them think you have no decorum.
How wonderful! It's cheese!
Good for you, Yoko.
Yeah, cheese is healthy.
So, you two, what are your favorite foods?
White rice.
Not bread?
Bread kinda feels like a snack.
I like rice better.
Then why not pack your own lunch?
No time in the morning.
What's your fave, Hayama?
Me?
Why, it's mille-feuille!
I like salted fish paste, is there a problem with that?!
No problem...
Oh, yeah, that stuff is good!
Goes nicely with rice.
What's yours, Yoko?
Cheese?
I need to give an answer they won't think is strange.
Something commoners would accept...
Right now, I like pudding!
Pudding?!
But that would be gross with rice!
With rice?!
Are normal people's favorite foods
things that pair well with rice?
I need to answer right...
H-How about pink codfish flakes?
You like them?
Mayonnaise!
At least that's the truth...
Are you sure you used to be rich?
Wh-What now?
At this rate, they might start to hate me.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
They were so happy about
the fried bread crusts, after all.
Hayama!
Futaba!
Today I...
...I made rice balls!
I thought she and bread crusts were exclusive.
I can cook if I try!
Wow.
I can't make them.
I wouldn't mind sharing, if you'd like some.
She can't mean balls of just rice, right?
Erm...
It really is just rice.
You said you liked rice, Futaba.
R-Right!
Rice balls are surprisingly complex, huh?
Lots of different possible fillings...
These have no fillings.
None?!
I wanted to use salted fish paste,
since Hayama likes it, but it was expensive...
For my sake?
But in rice balls...?
Getting the salt level in the rice right is tricky, too.
I forgot to add the salt!
D-Did I fail again?
I thought they'd be happy...
But now...
Let's dig in!
Thanks, Yoko.
I'm gonna have seconds.
L-Listen, please don't force yourself...
Rice is tasty, huh?
Hayama...
Futaba...
Go on, Yoko, you gotta eat too!
You can have one of my Vienna sausages.
Thank you very much!
I'm having thirds!
Futaba!
Central Shopping Arcade
You shouldn't do anything for me in return, really.
S-Since we're...
...friends...
...and all.
Don't be shy, Yoko.
Yeah, since we're friends.
They were free tickets anyway.
I have a family member who wins this stuff a lot.
Oh, it's here!
Healing Waters
A bathhouse!
Nothing better than a bath for we Japanese.
You said it.
And this one smells nice.
This is great.
It's been so long since
I could stretch my legs out in the bath.
But...
...to heat enough water for a bath this big...
How much must the utility bills be?!
Just have fun!
Sorry, I lost it a little.
To think they were even willing to bathe with her...
I was so worried, but I think Miss Yoko will survive!
Why don't you come out?
No, I can't waste Hayama's kindness...
Stop worrying and have fun!
A-Another hour... no, at least half a daaay...!
You'll get dizzy!
You're gonna boil into Yoko soup!
I can keep going!
Yoko!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a daily bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each her own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
And so my tumultuous school life began.
This new dog eat dog world is full of trials,
such as understanding how to spend break time!
But from now on, I won't lunch alone!
Whooshhh
Shall we eat indoors when it rains?
Fwooshhh
Yes...
Next: Nothing Good for You is Tasty