I found you.
You were my friend.
You were that girl.
I cared for you.
I loved you.
We took that picture together, didn't we?
We drank my mother's
honey ginger milk and sung the song of love.
Why didn't you tell me?
You're burning up. You must still be feverish.
Only the bear who killed my mother could have that pendant.
Why do you have that?
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
The Past: About 20 Years Earlier
HISTORY
I was once an unwanted bear,
abandoned in the world of humans.
I found you.
That was my first encounter with him.
You have no need to worry, for this academy is my box.
He loved boxes.
Listen closely, Yuriika.
This world slowly but surely
taints that which is untainted.
But look.
With this, the flower will remain eternally untainted.
In this world, only that which is untainted has value.
You are devastatingly pure, Yuriika.
You are special—
my one and only precious treasure.
I entered one of his boxes.
It filled me with happiness.
Inside his box, I was a precious,
special, and untainted existence.
I was no longer an unwanted bear.
Until that day came, that is.
I chanced upon a new incredibly untainted existence.
I must go.
Wait... wait, my precious person!
Don't abandon me!
Gyarl!
Bear Shock!
It was then that I understood.
Precious things are meant to be stored in boxes. Otherwise,
they will leave your sight forever.
They will become tainted.
From today onward, this shall be my box.
Why do you cut them so?
If I don't cut them while they're untainted, I can't place them in my box.
Why do you place them in your box?
To protect that which is precious from being tainted by this world.
The box allows me to remain special.
That which isn't special—
That which is unwanted, won't be found—
I found you.
You... found me?
Yes.
So free it from your box.
If you don't open your box, see it
with your eyes, and touch it with your hands,
it will be as if that which is precious doesn't exist.
As if it doesn't exist?
I am empty. The world is invisible.
Open your box, and show me your precious things.
With that, Reia and I became friends.
Reia imbued my invisible world with color.
She helped me find many more things to hold precious.
Reia tainted herself alongside me.
Reia.
I...
I love you.
Reia, do you love me?
Yes, I love you. I really do.
We'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes, friends forever.
Reia.
Happy birthday.
Yuriika.
It's a symbol of our friendship.
A vow to never forget love.
So long as you don't forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as you don't back down on love, even if you were to lose something, you won't become invisible.
Reia, I love you.
I love you with all of my heart.
But I knew.
I understood that Reia's love was not the same as mine.
Knowing that all too well, I indulged myself in that sweet and fleeting dream.
The Past: 17 Years Earlier
HISTORY
Her name is Kureha.
It's written as "red feather".
My goodness.
She really loves this pendant.
I see.
Over here, Kureha. Say hello to your mother's precious friend.
See? Didn't I tell you?
You should have put all your precious things into a box.
Outside of a box, they will
be tainted and lost to you forever.
You've lost Reia's love.
It is because you foolishly left your box and
became tainted that she was stolen from you.
For babies are, without question, the most pure and untainted existences on this planet.
I...
...will back down on love.
My tainted self is empty.
I am invisible.
No longer am I a precious being to store in a box.
Thus, I turned myself into a box.
An empty box to fill with something as if to sate my hollow self.
Just that single wish.
In this ever-invisible world,
the stars fell, and the Severance Barrier was created.
We can no longer return.
And then...
Reia...
Reia! Reia!
Sate me! I'm all hollow, so fill me!
I'm going to die of loneliness! Please, Reia!
Save me!
Reia!
Take this pendant with you.
That's a good love charm. It will surely protect you.
Why did you give that pendant away?
Do you love that girl?
I don't! But that girl is Kureha's—
Oh, I see now.
That's all you think of our symbol of friendship, gyarl.
You abandoned my love!
Grind... gyarl... grind... gyarl...
I ate Reia to store her within the box that is myself.
Now I will be sated!
Or so I was certain.
Even after eating Reia, I remained starved.
My hollow was not filled.
When I saw it, I questioned
Yurishiro-san without a second thought.
And her answer?
How did she respond?
Well...
Flashback
That pendant disappeared the night my mom was killed by a bear.
Why do you have that now?
Because I...
After that, she simply said she couldn't tell me now.
When I went to check on them this morning, they were gone without a trace.
What's this?
Undeniable evidence of their identity as bears disguised as humans.
The one with Reia's pendant,
Yurishiro Ginko, must be the one.
The bear who killed my mother?
Yes, there's no doubt.
It can't be...
That bear approached you as a child and became your friend
all so that she could kill Reia, your most precious person.
You mustn't expect love or friendship from them. They must be excluded.
Excluded...
That's right, believe in my words.
You stole Reia's love from me.
It is time to atone with your body.
You can no longer escape.
Tsubaki Kureha, you will become my bride-in-a-box.
Flashback
To
Cri
bear
mi
"Yurishiro Ginko.
I know about the grave sin you committed. You..."
Hey, Ginko. Don't you think it's about time we cross the barrier and go back home?
Even if your love is true, once she finds out you're a bear, growl...
Kurechin won't forgive you.
Promised kisses only exist in fairy tales.
Kumaria-sama may be the Goddess of the Barrier, but her job is to separate bears and humans.
She would never allow you to be friends.
I forced you to abandon your kiss.
You can't redo the past, growl.
Even after committing a grave sin?
I know what you did, Ginko.
Let's just go home!
Once Kurechin finds out,
she'll never give you her love.
At the same time, you can't share a
promised kiss without telling the truth.
Let's go home! Even if you back
down on love, I'll always love you!
It doesn't matter that I've lost my promised kiss forever. As long as you're by my side...
Lulu, I...
restricted number
Hello.
Is your love true?
Yes.
It's true.
This is a challenge from the Severance Barrier.
Tsubaki Kureha, if your love is true, then come to the rooftop at once.
The bears are awaiting you.
I know.
She was my friend... I loved her...
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will exterminate the bears!
Wait... wait, Ginko!
You can still love Kurechin, growl...
Don't abandon me!
Ginko! Ginko!
Entrust your body to the humans, and your love shall be approved.
Forgive me, Lulu.
Ginko!
How cool.
However, was this really the best method?
Don't sweat it. Now we'll see
whose love is true, nice and clear.
Shiny shine!
I still find this to be cruel.
Order, please.
We are that which exists in the gap between man and bear.
Everything is at Kumaria-sama's discretion.
That is sexy.
How long until the downpour? Shabadadu.
The time has finally come.
Come to me, Tsubaki Kureha.
I abandoned my bearmanity and became a human for you.
Flashback
I inquire of you, bearfendant Hakonaka Yuriika:
Will you give up your box?
Or will you back down on love?
I won't give up my box. I'll back down on love!
Please turn me into a human.
I want to watch over Tsubaki Kureha's growth.
Reia's love exists within that girl.
I wish to sate myself as a box through her!
Will you have no regrets?
You shall be eternally unable to escape your fate as a box.
Reia gave my love to another cub as if it were nothing!
I won't forgive her!
Understood.
I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Lily, approved!
Bear Dark!
Yuriika-sensei?
I've been awaiting you, Kureha-chan.
But why?
She's over there.
Yurishiro Ginko!
That girl is the bear who killed Reia.
Take our revenge.
Mom's revenge!
Yurishiro Ginko betrayed you.
She called herself your friend to deceive you.
She stole the person most precious to you.
Kureha.
You killed my mother...
I didn't eat her, growl!
Then explain why you have her pendant!
She gave it to me as a good love charm.
A good love charm?
I am a bear.
And in spite of that, we were friends, growl.
But then, out of nowhere,
we became unable to stay together.
You began to think one-sidedly
that bears are the enemy of man.
And why wouldn't I?
Bears are the enemy that kill people... that killed my mother!
You're wrong.
You found me when I was an unwanted bear.
You approved of me and gave me your love, growl!
That's nonsense!
I'll never forget the love you gave me back then.
I won't back down on the love I felt that day.
That's why I crossed the barrier.
To meet you once again
and become true friends with you.
True... friends?
Don't listen to her lies, Kureha-chan!
She's nothing more than a man-killing bear!
She killed all the girls in your class!
All to protect Kureha from the Invisible Storm.
I won't forgive those who try to exclude Kureha.
I am a bear. That's all I can do.
It can't be...
Why didn't you listen?
Bears have neither love nor friendship. They are but tainted beasts!
That is their true nature!
Delay no longer! Shoot it to death!
But...
Do it, Kureha.
I finally understand.
The promised kiss that
Kumaria-sama spoke of was your bullet.
Growl.
I shall accept it as a crimibear.
That will prove that my love is true.
It's the only method to become your true friend.
Why are you hesitating? Hurry and deliver punishment upon that crimibear!
Bestow upon me the promised kiss!
Flashback
The promised kiss...
From me to you?
And from me to you.
With this, everything shall awaken, and everything shall change.
What are you doing?
I can't... shoot her.
Enough foolishness!
Even if I kill that girl, Mom won't come back.
Nothing will change.
You mustn't forgive her! Shoot that man-eating bear with your judgement bullet!
But that girl...
Ginko saved me from the Invisible Storm.
She dove into the flames and risked her life to protect Sumika's letter.
You fool! That crimibear is simply pretending to be untainted!
Even so!
Kurechin!
Lulu-chan?
Kurechin, I know.
I know what Ginko did to Sumika-chan.
That's right, Ginko committed a grave sin.
What Ginko did to her was—
I shan't...
...forgive the bears!
I will exterminate the bears!
Is your love... true?
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger