Full Moon Wo Sagashite
Searching for a Full Moon
Toosugiru koi no michi shirube
The road to love is far too long for me
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
There's no way for me to love you anymore. Nope, Nope!
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one...
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
...where I can tell you how I really feel
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
I wear my favorite clothes every day...
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
...so that person will turn his gaze towards me
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
"I like you"  If I could bring myself to say it out loud...
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
...I would even be able to talk about love with you
Anata no haato ni tsutsumaretai no ni
I want to be tucked in your heart...
Doushitara tsutsunde kureru no
...and I will do anything to get there
I LOVE U wo anata kara kikitai
"I love you" Those are the words I want to hear from you...
Kissu suru shunkan no chikai kokyuu wo
...and my breath will quicken when we kiss
Anata wo mane suru atashi wa ichiban kawaiku naru hazu
The me who is performing for you... is the most beautiful of all