Reiji...
My apologies for arriving late.
You are...
Uncle Daisuke's...
Hey, Mom...
Is this about your dad?
A lot of people mentioned Dad and Uncle Daisuke...
I knew we'd have to talk about this eventually.
But that time came sooner than I expected.
The truth is your father isn't dead.
He's still alive.
He lives in an unimaginably cruel world.
Mom...
...are you okay with that?
Back then, I wanted us to live together.
I didn't mind giving up my life for that.
But...
I'm glad things are the way they are.
By leaving me behind,
he was able to keep his memories of me.
The only precious thing in our hearts that we can rely on.
He longed for how we live now.
But that's something he'll never reach.
A place that can only be thought of from far far away.
A place that can only be reached in dreams.
If I had followed him instead,
his wishes would have been destroyed.
I'm living the life that he wanted to live.
Just being together is not real love.
Mom...
Daisuke was the son of your father and his previous wife.
He endured everything because he had a little sister who was living the life that he dreamed of.
That's what he told me.
I...
I have something to tell him.
Jeez...
She definitely has my blood.
Crap... I can't find them without any clues!
Is this Fujieda?!
Yes, Elen saved me.
I'm back home now.
That's great.
Reiji...
Elen and Cal are going to kill each other.
I overheard their phone conversation.
She said it'll be at some place that they both know at 3am.
A place that they both know?
And also... Cal must be in a lot of pain.
She has no one to talk to.
Reiji, I'm counting on you to take care of them.
Okay, don't worry.
I'll definitely do something about it.
Fujieda...
I'm really sorry about what happened this time.
It's all my fault.
Don't say that. I don't mind at all.
I'll forget about it by tomorrow.
That's why I'll always be here to welcome you.
I love your smiling face.
If you can be that happy, it must mean that this place is right for you.
Thank you.
Really, thank you.
Fujieda, I-
I'll wait for you.
I'll always wait for the day when you'll return to this city without any worries.
That's why this isn't goodbye.
Please be safe.
All right.
I'm off.
Listen up. Don't go easy on them just because they're kids.
Are you going to kill them?
I'll be right there.
I've sworn to prevent Mio from getting hurt ever again.
Do you think this is what she wants?
This is the one promise I made to Daisuke.
How selfish.
You people are always like this.
Shiga, the one who shot Daisuke was...
What's the point of all this?
There's no point.
I'm doing it because I can. That's all there is to it.
What will come of this?
Nothing at all.
She'll die and I'll burn out.
The end.
That's all.
Is that everything you desire?
Of course! What else could I wish for?
And what about you guys?!
What have you accomplished while you've been alive?!
What'll be left after you die?!
Nothing at all!
And just like that, everyone dies like pieces of trash!
Correct.
And that will also apply to you one day.
You'll have no proof of your existence nor a meaning in life...
...and die.
Quit joking around.
Don't compare me with you guys.
I'm the almighty Phantom!
I've finally found the thing I'm better at than everyone else.
I found a way of life that people can't look down upon.
This is all I am...
What I do is to take away and destroy.
I don't want to have it done to me anymore...
I thought you'd be here.
"I think this is the best choice."
Do you really believe that?
Yes.
You can't kill Cal.
No, I can and I will.
I'll bear all her anger and sadness.
I'll be the saddest person in this world when she dies.
I can mourn for her.
So let me kill her.
No, you'll lose for sure.
I'll never let myself lose you.
Elen...
You're the only one who can't do that.
Because you're gentle.
Because you won't be able to kill her.
I'll stay, too.
The two of us will definitely be able to defeat her.
You have to understand this!
This is the seed I've sown!
If I don't settle this here, I'll always be bound by my past.
I won't be able to free myself.
Elen, leave first!
I'll come right after!
Where can I go without you?
I don't even know where I came from...
I don't even have any memories!
What should I do to free myself?
What good is freedom built on the deaths of others?
Tell me! Please!
Let's go find it together.
I'll definitely return to your side to fulfill that promise.
Reiji...
Elen won't be coming.
Why are you here?
This is my duty.
To protect that girl?
No, Cal.
To kill you.
I've sacrificed countless people up until now.
I've tricked countless people,
used them and killed them in the end.
Just for the sake of staying alive.
You've got quite the nerve...
You're right, Cal.
Your anger represents justice.
You don't need to bring this to court.
Just use your gun to bring judgment upon me.
Not by anyone else, but by yourself.
If you're stronger than me,
then I'll be punished.
Just the way I want it.
I won't let you interfere.
Get her!
If you really want to have a match, then this is the perfect choice.
That's...
You still remember?
This is our karma.
My guidepost up until now.
This thing always reminds me of who to hate and who to kill.
A duel.
When this song ends, we shoot.
Okay?
You're the only one...
...who is still alive after hearing this song, Reiji.
What? Did you fall asleep?
I had a dream about back when we were in Los Angeles.
What kind of dream?
What would've happened if we hadn't seen each other after the place got blown up?
That's so stupid!
As if you'd make a stupid mistake like that.
That would never happen.
There's no way we'll be separated.
If that really happened, I would go look for you.
Even to the ends of the Earth...
That's impossible.
I'm a hopeless idiot.
Why am I thinking of such things?
It might not be so bad to think about things from time to time.
It might not be so bad...
At least something like that can happen in a dream...
Is this where Judy Devens passed away?
Why are you so strong?
This is this only way I can answer you.
Oh...
Then I can still have you all to myself at the end?
That's great...
I don't need anything else...
Do you have to sacrifice yourself for such things?
What do you mean by "such things"?
Is there something better?
I think we had other ways to live our lives.
If we had met some other way, we might have been able to live happily ever after.
Yeah...
We just messed up somewhere, that's all...
That has to be it.
I'm glad I met you.
I'm...
...satisfied...
...and happy...
Cal!
Cal...
CAL!!!
Phantom, you monster!
I really don't understand this.
Mr. Shiga, I thought you were smarter than this.
Why didn't you just leave it to us?
You bastard!
You've been watching this whole time?!
It's time for the final act.
There's no place in the cast for you unrefined stage props.
If you want to stay, then please do so.
Please feel privileged to be able to see my best work.
The concerto of the strongest ghosts.
Now then, who will respond to the curtain call?
I will kill.
I will kill in order to live.
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
In my wrongful life where I couldn't fulfill any promises,
there is still one promise I want to fulfill.