When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Hayate is a little sleep deprived these days.
And the reason would be this.
I love you, Brenda.
Why are you here? Why did you wake me up?
Why do you try to speak love to me?
W-W-W-What? Don't look at me like I'm delicious.
He'll eat me!
Stop it... Don't eat me...
It's an afro.
I don't taste good!
Afro. It's an afro.
I'm not seasoned enough!
It's an afro.
What? It was all a dream?
Afro. It's an afro.
That looks like an afro.
Afro.
What?
Afro?!
Sorry to interrupt, but what are you showing off, and to whom?
Oh, you're behind me.
And who are you?
Nabeshin. He looks great in an afro.
Nabeshin. Apparently he owns four red jackets.
Nabeshin. He was asked by Kawaguchi
to make an appearance and actually came.
Nabeshin. So many things we can say about him.
The number of girls he scored with is-
Um, this opening is old.
I never knew that!
This is the current opening.
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
I see. So that's the one you use now.
I want to redo it with this.
Think of the work required to fix the pictures.
Um, the subtitles are done.
Ah, right.
Then let's ignore the script and get this going.
I really can't tell if he's motivated or not.
I'll be forty-three this year.
So what?!
Sign: Mysterious Woman
The machine between my legs roars! It's a Walther P-30!
C-Could that be?
You're right, Ayasaki Hayate.
Right, Mikako?
Something like that, Director.
It all seems to be like a prearranged deal.
So die.
You got that from Ameyoko, didn't you?
How'd you know?
I see a sticker for Nakata Sto** on the grip.
Seriously?
Oh, you're right. It's so cheap.
Nakata Sto**. That's...
But I'll still shoot you.
Listen to my narration!
Is there a problem with not being able to handle hot food?!
I-Is he serious?
He's fast.
And he's insane.
Um, what are you doing?
Sorry, I have a deadline for a rough draft due. And next week is shooting.
A rough draft for an anime?
Something like that.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself, have I?
I hear it's a valuable business card.
Watanabe Shinichi.
Nabeshin in short.
Yup. I produce and direct anime.
Butler is a part-time job.
So don't get in my way.
Get in your way? You're the one who picked a fight with me.
And then you go to sleep?
Nabeshin-san! Please wake up!
Don't go to sleep in the middle of a show.
Sorry. I didn't get to sleep at all last night, too.
An all-nighter?
Last night was on a swing in a park-
Why Kawaguchi?!
And the reason why Kawaguchi is hopeless is-
I never asked anything about Kawaguchi-san.
Nabeshin-san. What is it this time?
I-I'm hungry.
Working in a park in the middle of the night?
So I heard.
And what a meaningless afro.
It really is worthless.
He's almost worth being a protected species.
I must protect him.
It goes there?
Seconds!
Yes, sure. Don't worry about
your metabolic syndrome and eat.
No worries.
Can I say one more thing?
Keep going.
Can I invite my wife and daughter?
S-Sure.
They're already here and eating.
Don't mind us.
Thanks for the food.
You finished that really fast, didn't you?
It was good stuff.
The dessert tastes good, too.
Tastes good.
And where did that good-looking maid go?
Maria-san?
She's a busy person, I'm afraid.
I thought I'd show her the DVD episode of
"Wel**** Newly Weds" we were in as thanks for the food.
Although we weren't newly wed at this time.
Why don't at least you watch?
I don't care about that.
What do you mean "that"?
I'm a little busy, so excuse me.
Hold up, Hayate-kun.
Please give an explanation of "that". In Kansai dialect, please.
We'll smack ya!
Sorry!
This is what Hayate thought.
I can't keep this going!
No, this is horrible! It's cheating!
And, this is one of my works.
Wow, so nostalgic.
No, no, I got carried into their pace.
Let's put an end to this already!
And this is the bucket type laundry machine we got from "***come Newly Weds".
It's so useless.
What is up with them...
Let's do it, win it, Kobayashi!
I will do it, in a reverse manner!
No... At this rate not only this mansion,
but the entire anime will get taken over.
Lululu~ Excel~ Lalala~ Excel~
All right, let's go!
I'm sorry.
Lululu~ Excel~ Lalala~ Excel~
Please forgive my husband.
Please.
Just like how tuna die if they don't keep swimming, he dies if he can't stay the focus of things.
Lululu~ Excel~ Lalala~ Excel~
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's not much of an apologetic gift, but...
Please accept these.
What are these?
It's really not worth much, but they're his Comike items.
You're giving them to me?
Please buy them.
At the listed cost.
I don't need them!
And madam!
It's enough! It's enough! It's enough! It's enough!
Hayate-kun.
Look at this.
Please, just leave!
Tama!
Excuse us.
Afros...  Afros...
Hayate-kun.
Afro returns!
It's only a wig.
She's been calling you.
Hayate! Where are you Hayate!
Thanks for having us!
I heard Isumi is on her way to the mansion.
Isumi-san is?
Yes, and alone, too.
Alone?
Yes. I got a letter from Isumi's place, so I'm sure.
Isumi-san always gets lost.
Where am I?
Knowing she gets lost, why does she always leave alone?
That's an easy question.
She thinks she's well-managed and independent.
SFX: Sparkle
I'll be fine the next time.
...is what she thinks.
But she gets lost all the time anyway.
So she's actually...
Actually?
Stubborn.
I am actually a stubborn girl.
Where am I?
And she's lost as always.
Oh no. Oh no.
SFX: Sparkle
But I'll be fine today.
SFX: TA~DA
I have a cell phone with me today.
If I use this, it will tell me where I am now and which way I have to go.
This is what the girl thought.
I don't see a number pad.
Stare~
The newest model: 240 Mpixel, anti-blur camera. One-seg. And comes with mp3 player, but there is no keypad.
At a closer look, it looks like it'll open.
Yes, this will open! It is made to open!
Open sesame!
Open sesame sesame!
Open sesame salt!
This cell phone is broken.
It's your head that's broken!
Sakuya. It hurts.
Why? Why can't you make a call with a cell?
What are you? A ******zuka? Have you quit thinking?
******zuka.
Isumin kikku
Isumin kikku = Isumin Kick
Kun kun kuntama ii nioi
Kun kun kuntama ii nioi = Sniff sniff. What a good smell.
Seriously, your entire day is a joke.
So, what are you doing here?
I won't tell a person who smacks others' heads with a paper fan.
What?
By the way, Nagi's house would be that direction.
I was just thinking of heading that direction.
Oh, sorry to bother you, then.
But, can you make it there?
Can't even use a cell phone.
A princess without any sense of direction?
Don't worry. I'll take you there.
I do not need you to help me.
Yeah, yeah, I gotcha.
Please save us!
No! I can't! I can't!
Please save us.
No! I can't! I can't hallucinate in the middle of a city.
I can't let things like this happen for the sake of everyone's future.
Calm down, Sakuya.
This fish is not an entity of your hallucination.
But you don't see a fish like this in a fish market.
It is a type of Tochigami.
Tochigami = A deity that dwells in a property's ground.
Tochigami?
It's harmless.
But...
As expected from Isumi-sama.
You freaked me out.
So, how can I help you?
Yes, you see...
I want to ask for your help in phantom busting.
Phantom busting?
He's a phantom himself!
Absolutely not!
A phantom is tampering with our lake and we're really troubled.
We feel doomed like fish on a cutting board.
Good reference?
Let's go, Isumi-san.
This place will soon get eaten by the *** of Decay.
A god that says something that boring should just die.
Don't say that!
Hold on, Sakuya.
It's a phantom strong enough to create trouble to a whole land.
No matter how boring a god He may be...
Boring god?!
...it still bothers me.
Even if He's uber-boring?
Even if He is uber-boring.
Thank you very much.
I'll ignore some of the harsh words. Thank you very much.
A nice afro. A charming afro.
What is that annoying afro?
Please watch the first half later.
But Isumi's taking her time like always.
Um, should I go look for her?
Yeah, if you would. Please.
Isumi is weak, so I'm worried that she might have gotten caught up in something strange.
Man, we got caught up in something really strange.
I kinda knew you had strange powers, though.
Is the reason why you always get lost because you have to deal with phantoms like this all the time?
Yes, I do get bothered by them two or three times a year.
Then that's not the reason.
But he's not a phantom.
He's a Tochigami.
A fairy, if you will, created by nature.
If you call this a fairy, the image of Tinkerbell falls to the pits.
Then what's a phantom?
Phantoms are those that gained a spirit.
Gained a spirit?
For example, it's said that when cats lick lantern oil at night for twenty years, they gain a spirit and turn into a monster cat.
When humans gain a spirit through some method,
they'll turn into an Oni.
And those that gained a spirit are referred to as phantoms.
Then the phantom that's giving this guy trouble is...
Yes.
Since He's a Koi, the koi herpesvirus must have gained a spirit and become a phantom.
Koi = Carp
So I call it-
Phantom KHV!
What the hell is that?!
Hey, you!
Koi?
What did Phantom KHV do to you?
"What?"
Umm...
SFX: Blush
S-Served me on a plate alive.
What's the blushing for?
Getting served on a plate alive is...
It was when I was synchronized swimming.
And you'll go right into the reflection?
Carp's synchronized swimming.
What are you doing to me?
No, stop!
No, don't! Don't strip me like that!
I told you not to.
Crap, I forgot wasabi.
Wasabi, wasabi.
It's my chance!
Now's my chance to run! I can get away if it's now.
My body feels light.
Phantom KHV tried to eat you with wasabi?
Yes.
Unbelievable.
If it were me, I'd have made soup.
Oh no, please stop.
Anything but that.
Stop synchronized swimming in the soup!
Do you like synchronized swimming that much?
Do you love it?
Can't you control yourself?
Only a little.
He is a Tochigami despite his appearance,
so I don't think the paper fan's a good idea.
It's animal abuse picture-wise,
so I think you might get punished for it.
Sign: Portable
But maybe she'll be happy.
Tell Nagi what happened, and she might be able to use it for her manga's plot.
I cannot do that.
Why not?
It's so interesting. You don't find stories like this often.
To Nagi, who fears darkness so much, I cannot tell stories like this.
Now that you mention it,
when did she get so scared of the dark?
I don't remember her being like that when she was young.
Something happened, didn't it?
I didn't intend to make her cry like that.
I'm scared... I'm scared...
So I won't hurt my friends anymore.
I like your determination, girl.
Th-That voice is!
So it's him?
That's right. The koi herpesvirus that gained a spirit.
I'm the Great Phantom of KHV!
He has the same naming sense as you.
No. He added "Great" to himself.
It's him! He's the one that tried to serve me on a plate alive!
In fact, he did!
You think a helper like that will let you to win against me?
Shut up, you An***man's enemy!
I'm not An***man's enemy!
I'm the Great Phantom of KHV!
Bye bye virus.
I have things to do, so let's keep this short.
I'm turning on my work mode.
She's heartless once she's like this.
Don't underestimate us.
I see. They're viruses, so they can multiply.
Looks like this will be a big task.
Yeah.
Then I'll blast the big one, so in the meantime, Sakuya, you handle them.
Huh?
Don't worry. KHV can't infect humans.
SFX: Sparkle
Stop the sparkle! It's not a matter of infecting humans or not!
Besides, you just made a statement, didn't you?
I won't hurt my friends anymore.
You said that!
You're full of energy, so you'll be fine.
You moron! I am pretty sensitive, you know?!
Hey, where did that carp god go?
Oh.
Great Phantom-san, Great Phantom-san.
They just said that you're a knockoff of Hyou**zoku's Black ****.
That moron! What's he saying?
We're not knockoffs!
We're inspired by them!
It doesn't matter!
Anyway, we won't let you guys live!
I'm cornered in only after a few scene cuts.
It'll be over in two more cuts.
Watch out!
Debt-ridden butler.
Are you all right, Sakuya-san?
That's indeed the Hayate-sama I know.
Wherever there is a person in need of help, you appear like a gust of wind.
Reinforcements, eh?
But what difference is there with one extra kid?
Why are these people wearing knockoffs of underling suits?
We're not knockoffs!
So what exactly are these strange people?
They're not people; they're phantoms.
A carp asked Isumi to exterminate them.
Take this!
Super M spread uniting!
I got cornered really quickly, too.
We're in big trouble!
Hachiyou Rokushiki.
Isumi-san?
Away and begone.
What?
Then that strange thing that happened a while back was all Isumi-san?
Please keep it a secret from Nagi.
Let's now go to Nagi's house, shall we?
Yes.
And Isumi-san, this way.
Seriously, I can't let my eyes off of her.
No! I don't want to be served alive! I don't want to be soup either!
What? Everything's over?
Yay! Now I can do synchronized swimming again!
Just go do it.
Oh, so you're finally here, Isumi.
Good work, Hayate.
Well, thank you.
Can you get tea for all of us?
Yes, right away.
Hey, can I ask one thing?
That last thing, if that was your power, I think you could have won even if I hadn't lured the enemy.
What's the truth there?
I can't tell that to a person who hits others' heads with a paper fan.
So that's what you were getting back at?
You think of me wrongly, Sakuya.
Don't lie to me!
I hate the way you talk!
They get along well, don't they?
They are friends after all.
What the heck! What the heck!
You're no longer my friend!
We're done!
I reject you!
Friends, huh?
You're pretty good, Afro.
You, too, Koi-san.
Friends!
That's right, you have to take care of friends and afro hair.
Next time, we'll yet again fight with a familiar looking hot butler.
Carp soup from sashimi I found on the street!
Thanks for the food!
I am Nabeshin yay yay ya.
An afro looks good on me yay yay ya.
I don't like evil afros!
Nagi and
Hayate and
Nishizawa Ayumu's
Butler Network!
Oo! Ya! Tah! It's Sanzenin Nagi.
It's Ayasakai Hayate.
It's Nishizawa Ayumu.
You've never failed to show up in this anime, Nishizawa-san, but we hardly see each other in the actual show.
Yes. I'm so envious of Sanzenin-chan.
But there seem to be fans of yours out there, so we have a service shot prepared.
It's a super borderline shot.
What? I never heard that!
Hayate-kun, you can't see it!
What?
But we don't have time to show it, so we'll save it for next time.
Bye bye.
Autumn is the season of culture, right?
Therefore, next week will be an episode of Hakuou Academy's Culture Festival.
We as student council members will do our best to make this festival a success!
Now, Hayata-kun. We leave the rest to you.
O-Okay.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Why?! School Festival Part One.
Did you know? Pacific saury used to be a fish from which only oil was extracted.