Attention!
I will now brief you about the operation for retaking Trost!
I shall now introduce him.
Eren Jaeger of the Cadets!
He's the product of the military's top
secret Titan transformation experiments!
He will transform into a Titan, pick up
that giant boulder near the front gate,
carry it to the breach in the wall, and block off the hole with it!
Your mission will be to protect him from the other Titans while he's carrying the boulder!
When this plan succeeds,
it'll be the first time we've ever reconquered land from the Titans!
Compared to what's been taken from us, it may be a small thing...
But it will mean mankind has finally managed an attack on the Titans!
Eren, don't you recognize me? It's Mikasa!
I'm your family!
Dodge, Ackerman!
What's up with him?
He's just a stupid Titan like all the rest!
We're changing our objectives.
Until Jaeger can be retrieved, we'll protect him from the Titans.
He represents a precious possibility for mankind. We can't just abandon him.
Where am I?
Oh, I'm at home?
Jean!
Why isn't he using his 3D Maneuver Gear?
Don't tell me it broke!
I'll sort this out myself!
Mikasa! What happened to the plan?
It failed.
We can't leave Eren behind, so everyone's fighting!
But with this many Titans,
we're bound to get wiped out!
From the back of the head to the nape of the neck...
One meter vertically. Ten centimeters horizontally.
Eren, answer me!
Even though you knew hell was raging outside the walls...
Why did you ever want to see the outside world?
Why, you ask?
Because I was born into this world!
Eren!
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
Basic Needs
Defense of Trost (pt 9)
Dammit... Now I'm holding up the others.
Will this really work out?
Squad leader, this is all we can handle!
We're the only ones left!
Let's fall back to the rock!
Report!
Five Titans incoming from the gate.
I can't just sit around waiting for the Titans to piss off!
Jean!
It must be his Maneuver Gear!
What?
C'mon, you bastard! I'm in a hurry here!
Jean, calm down!
Marco, what are you doing?!
Jeez, what a drag!
Crap! Why is the trigger so hard to pull?
Jean!
What are you doing?!
That's my line!
Fly away already!
You guys are insane!
My line again!
I think I just died like three times over!
Look at that!
Eren!
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren won!
He's trying to do his job now!
If he can just make it to the gate, we win!
Listen well!
We must defend Eren until he reaches the gate, even if it costs us our lives!
Don't let any Titans get near him!
Keep them all out of the way! We must support Eren!
You two, go to Eren!
This is an order! Got it?
Yes, sir!
Mitabi's squad?
What are they—?!
The Titans aren't paying us any attention!
We've gotta get close enough that they can't ignore us!
Look! Over here!
Turn around, or I'll shove my sword right up your stinkin' ass and bleed you to death!
Now! Two of them are after us!
Run! Run to the buildings!
No way! Staying on the ground is suicide!
Without horses or buildings, we can't fight!
No... It's the only way we've got left.
Everyone follow their lead!
Armin, we're going too.
This way! Come over here!
My body...
It feels like I'm being crushed...
Mikasa? Armin?
What are you doing?
If you stay down there, the Titans will eat you!
Hey! What are you waiting for?
Come and get me!
Hey!
No! Mitabi!
Why did you ever want to see the outside world?
When we're born, all of us are free.
People who deny that, no matter how strong they are, don't matter.
The fire water, the continent of ice... I don't care what!
Anyone who saw such things would be the freest person in the entire world!
Fight!
Who would value their life over something like that?
However terrifying the world may be...
It doesn't matter!
However cruel the world may be...
Fight!
Watch out! Titans!
I'll handle this!
Out of the way!
Go, Eren!
Fight!
Everybody... didn't die in vain.
Today, for the first time, mankind triumphed over the Titans.
Yellow signal flare confirmed!
The operation was a success!
Send in reinforcements now!
Rescue the elite troops!
Currently Disclosable Information
History of the war with the Titans (pt 1)
According to the oldest existing records,
the Titans emerged 107 years ago.
Subsequently, most of mankind was eaten by the Titans.
Currently Disclosable Information
History of the war with the Titans (pt 2)
Mankind tried using cannons against the Titans,
but their durability and vitality
overwhelmed all human combat techniques.
The remaining Titans are coming! We have to climb the Wall!
I'll withdraw as soon as we've recovered Eren!
Armin! How's Eren?!
He's feverish from the unbelievable heat in here!
We need to get him over the Wall right away!
Part of his body is still fused with the Titan.
I can't pull him out!
We'll have to cut it then!
Hold on!
Eren! Armin!
Mikasa...
That's...
The wings... of freedom!
Hey, you kids...
What's the situation here?
After that, the Recon Corps and the Garrison's engineers came rushing in,
and Wall Rose was freed once again of the Titan threat.
It took an entire day to eliminate all the Titans trapped inside Trost.
During that time, the fixed artillery was constantly spitting fire.
While the high-explosive shells eliminated most of the Titans,
the Recon Corps mopped up the leftovers.
They even successfully captured a 4-meter Titan and a 7-meter Titan.
However, 207 soldiers were dead or missing in action,
and 897 were wounded in battle.
Though it was mankind's first victory against the Titans,
far too many lives were paid in exchange.
Hey...
Is that you... Marco?
Cadet!
Do you know his name?
I wasn't going to look, but...
I can't believe it. Not him.
Marco... What happened?
Someone must've seen his last moments.
Who is he? If you know, tell me now.
Don't you understand, Cadet?
Two days have passed since the gate was blocked.
Yet we're still collecting the corpses.
There's a risk of an epidemic breaking out.
We must prevent a secondary catastrophe.
We don't have time to mourn our fallen comrades just yet.
Do you understand?
The 104th Training Corps...
Leader of Squad 19, Marco Bott.
Marco, huh? Glad we know his name.
Let's move on.
What... is that?
A Titan puked it up.
They have no digestive organs,
so once they get their fill of humans, they throw up like that.
No way...
Shit... We'll never be able to identify anyone like this.
I'm sorry.
Apologizing won't fix anything.
Let's hurry and put them to rest.
Do you have any questions?
Chief Erwin, the top leader of the Recon Corps.
And Captain Levi...
Um...
Where... am I?
As you can see, you're in an underground dungeon.
You're currently in the custody of the Military Police,
but we finally got permission to see you a little while ago.
That key!
Yeah, it's yours. I'll give it back later.
The basement of your house,
Dr. Jaeger's house in Shiganshina, holds the secret of the Titans.
Am I right?
Yes. Probably.
That's what my father said.
You have amnesia and your father is missing...
Awfully convenient, don't you think?
Levi. We've already concluded he has no reason to lie.
There is still so much we don't know yet,
but for now, I think the most important
thing to inquire about is your intentions.
My... intentions?
To return to your house, we must retake the Shiganshina District of Wall Maria.
It would take drastic measures to seal the broken gate.
We'd need your Titan strength.
Our fate rides on a Titan, it seems.
The Colossal Titan. The Armored Titan.
They are probably just like you.
Your intentions are the key here.
The key to freeing mankind from this despair.
I'll...
Exterminate them!
I'm going to kill them all.
Every single fucking one...
Answer the man, scum.
What do you want to do?
I want to join the Recon Corps,
and kill as many Titans as I can, sir!
Oh? Not bad.
Erwin. I'll take responsibility for him.
Tell that to the higher-ups.
Don't get me wrong. It's not like I trust him.
If he betrays us or goes berserk, I'll put him down without hesitation.
Upstairs shouldn't have a problem with that...
Nobody except me is suited for the job.
I'll accept your application to the Recon Corps.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
The time for dreaming is over.
Eren awakens to find himself locked in a dark underground cell.
Now, he must face a court martial to decide his fate.
Can't Look Into His Eyes
Prelude to the Counterattack (pt 1)