Mom! What's with your fabulous pose?
It is not a "fabulous pose".
It is the incantation for the Reverse Path spell.
It is a form of meditation that can imprison any and all oddities.
You sound like some transforming superhero!
Okay, can I be the monster of the day?
I am no transforming superhero.
I am a Tsukuyomi priestess.
But Tsukuyomi priestesses are good guys, right?
You really are a hero!
Your reasoning is indeed sound.
Here we go! Reverse Path Spell!
Shouting is unnecessary. The pose is different too.
This way's cooler!
You look strong and you can scare your enemy!
Twoarr!
Is that so?
Twoarr?
You're not loud enough!
Do not make light of me! Witness the true power of your mother!
Twoarr!
What is it, Sasami?
Is something the matter?
I love you, Mom!
Such a weird child.
Twoarr!
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 7
I forgot how to speak
Life hasn't always been good for us.
Long ago, Tsurugi had no motivation.
She was always tired and her head was in the clouds.
Kagami never laughed or talked to me,
and even the smallest noises scared her.
She always seemed to be fighting something invisible.
So I smiled.
Because I had to.
It was hard to smile when kids at school got mad at me or made fun of me.
It was difficult,
but I had to keep smiling.
I couldn't do anything else, so I pretended to be really happy,
hoping that I could drag Tsurugi and
Kagami along and make them smile too.
Even when they told me I'm annoying or scolded me,
I did my best not to hate the world.
You idiot!
Useless simpleton!
Once we started hanging out with Mamarin,
Tsurugi and Kagami's faces became more gentle and they even started smiling.
With all the ruckus that's been going on, I
thought our hearts were finally free of burden...
But now none of that means anything.
Tsurugi was thrown into the underworld.
Kagami was beaten up so badly she can't even move.
But I'm fine. The only one who's fine is me.
That's why I have to go.
I'm scared and I can't stop crying,
but at least I can keep walking forward.
If wishes can come true, then please, gods!
Let me fulfill their wishes!
Huh?
Do not move.
I am mending your body.
I can't move...
It appears you have neglected your health.
You need more fat on your bones, otherwise you will lose all strength and die young.
What's going on? My head feels fuzzy...
I numbed your consciousness with drugs.
It would be undesirable for you start to using the power of Amaterasu.
But why? Where am I?
This is where the Tsukuyomi shrine lay.
The shrine itself might not exist anymore,
but this land is the perfect spot for to dedicate
yourself to training away from the vulgar world.
I shall purify it and raise a new barrier
so that it will be the hidden home to
the Tsukuyomi priestesses once again.
I shall pose the question to you again.
We have reached an utmost compromise.
Do you vow never to consider escape ever again,
and to fulfill your duty as a Tsukuyomi
priestess for the sake of the world and mankind?
No.
Why?
You swore that you would return to being a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Just... to stop you.
So you lied?
You... drugged me...
I... don't wanna do the stupid job that got you killed...
I finally got out...
I finally made friends...
So you've chosen to abandon the duty the heavens bestowed upon you?!
I don't want it!
I shall reeducate you as my time permits.
No... I don't wanna...
I don't wanna work hard anymore!
I see.
In that case, you leave me no choice.
Ever since you were little, you have thrown up many times.
If I administered drugs through your mouth, you might regurgitate them.
Thus, I administer them directly into your stomach.
I left your consciousness intact so you could answer my question.
However, once this drug spreads, you will be left completely unable to think.
I have no further questions for you.
No further words will come from you.
And as a person, there is nothing further I expect from you.
It is a shame, Sasami. A shame indeed.
I am disappointed in this fool as well.
It was always a spoiled dimwit.
Not only did it allow the Tsukuyomi shrine to be destroyed,
but it acted on its own accord and consequently failed.
Unredeemable.
You have no value if you can not fulfill your duty.
However, the Tsukuyomi blood must not vane.
Therefore, you have only one thing to desire now.
Bear a child, Sasami.
That child shall inherit the power of
Amaterasu and become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
As soon as the inheritance is
complete, you shall begone from here.
My body was weak and I could not bear many children, therefore you have few relatives.
Use him.
No...
No! No! No!
I care not for your tantrum.
Bear his child and give birth to a new Tsukuyomi priestess.
I will educate that child and return the world to how it is meant to be.
No! No!
Can't it... Can't it be Brother?
Out of the question.
It is not a Tsukuyomi anymore.
It is a criminal who committed a
terrible crime by helping you escape.
It is in no way related to the Tsukuyomi name anymore.
Also, I believe that man wanted to help you.
It came here earlier and made a ruckus
demanding to see you, so I cleaned it up.
Purify your body first.
Burn incense, perform the ceremony, and pray for a child.
Oh, are you dead on the inside? Well, that does not matter.
As long as your body is intact, I do not care.
I explained to Sasami about her final duty.
She calmed down when I told her you died.
She likes you quite a lot.
You filthy monster. So vexing.
I would kill you if I could.
Are you really going to turn Sasami into a tool to give birth a new Tsukuyomi priestess?
Do you have no motherly love left in you?
When I crawled back from Yomi, I ceased being a human.
I am a Tsukuyomi priestess before I am her mother.
Sasami truly loved you.
I am aware.
But that is a trivial matter...
...my Brother.
Awaken from concentrated sleep.
Verifying damage.
Status of self-regeneration: 38%.
Approximately seven hours until fighting capability returns.
Sasami...
Are you worried about me, Meat?
We're up against the strongest Tsukuyomi priestess to have ever existed,
and she has the protection of the lord of the underworld.
Without proper preparation, Tama will end up like me.
The lord of the underworld, the hero god, the manifestation of storms: Susanoo.
Susanoo flat out rejects Amaterasu's order and oversight.
He is chaos and rebellion.
There is no opponent as formidable as him.
I'm glad I had this GPS-like feature.
I don't care if you're a Tsukuyomi priestess or the hero god himself!
Don't you underestimate the Yagami sisters!
The rest is in your hands, Tama...
I have to go and save Sasami!
That scared me!
That's Ms. Tsurugi's sword!
Great timing!
This sword's a lot duller than it looks!
Okay, now I can get ou-
This is nothing!
Sasami's scent...
This way!
This room!
Sasami! Sasami, it's me!
I'm here to save you!
Sasami!
You don't have to worry anymore!
Whatever may come, I'll protect you!
Bro... Brother...
Alive...
Yes!
I'm alive, Sasami.
Don't cry anymore...
Brother!
Ouch!
I don't get it!
This was supposed to be the part where she hugs me and shouts, "I love you, Brother!" and kisses me on the cheek.
You're late, you moron!
You idiot! Retard! You're useless!
You're trash! Junk! Good for nothing!
Everything will be okay, Sasami.
I'll protect you.
Brother...
Did you think I would let you get away?
I did not expect them to break the barrier with a long distance throw.
The divine blade Ame-no-Murakumo is powerful indeed.
A defensive sacred sword that purges
and purifies any and all that is wicked.
But...
All they have done is send you the
weapon. They have yet to show themselves.
Does this mean that those evil gods still cannot move?
Beat it, Mom. I'm not going to have a child.
The pointless Tsukuyomi bloodline dies with me!
That's my decision!
This world has been twisted by mankind.
I'll return it to the state of primordial chaos before the age of legends!
That's how the world is meant to be.
Even if you beat me, hurt me, brainwash me, or force me to become your tool,
you can never break my soul.
I used to try so hard that I threw everything away.
I tried not to notice the happiness
and fun that was within arm's reach.
What did the world give you in
exchange for doing your duty, huh Mom?
You only got death and pain!
You have no right to speak.
If you do not try and just fool around, others will be forced to work harder.
You do not realize that and merely look for the easy way out.
You stomp on the values that you were born with.
I will not acknowledge you as my daughter!
You know... I really loved you, Mom.
You hardly ever smiled, but you were always kind.
I thought you were so cool, protecting the world and all.
You were my hero.
The Tsukuyomi shrine used, buried, and killed you! And I'll never accept them!
I don't care how great they are or what grand goal they have.
Being a Tsukuyomi priestess is stupid.
We're humans, not gods! We can live happily even if we're powerless!
Words will not move the dead.
This was SO FAR AWAY! Jeez!
I had to save Mamarin, but I didn't know where to go!
Last time I came here, I just followed Kagami!
I didn't know the way and I got lost!
I just kept walking, but I ended up back at the school...
I tried asking a policeman for directions, but all I knew was that it was in Kyushu.
He thought I was making fun of him and got angry at me!
I wasn't being a bad girl!
I won't let you get away!
You hurt Tsurugi and Kagami! I'll get you for that!
I'll go home with Mamarin!
Such incredibly reliable help you have.
Give me this, Mamarin.
Tama... what...
Gods are omnipresent.
The higher their divinity, the more they are present in the world.
Their existence is first recognized
when humans acknowledge them.
But in the gaps of that recognition,
they conceptualize then rematerialize,
thus enabling them to teleport.
I'm only a grade schooler! I have no idea what you just said!
But I know this isn't about who's
smarter! It's about who tries harder!
What?
She made the divine sword teleport and
appear in the same space as the other sword!
What's going on?
According to the legends, the Ame-no-Habakiri is more fragile than the Ame-no-Murakumo.
Here, Mamarin.
Mamarin called you Mom!
Dummy!
Mamarin cried!
You're her mom! Don't be mean to her!
She ate me?
What could eat gods?
I see, so you are a new god?!
A god of the new age to take over the old ones?!
Impossible!
You wanted to end the legends from ancient times unmatched in beauty, o Sun?!
I will not recognize new gods!
Th-This is...
the Reverse Path spell?!
A form of meditation that can imprison any and all oddities...
Sasami, how dare you?!
I am your mother! I gave birth to you!
You treat me as an oddity?!
I'm sorry, Mom.
Go back to the underworld!
Sup, mommy dearest! We meet again.
Let's have a little chat about your daughter's future.
Enough of this folly, you evil gods!
What will happen to the world?!
I must return this land to how it is meant to be,
or I will not die even if I am killed!
Sorry, Tama.
I won't be back for a while. Take care of stuff while I'm gone.
Sasami! Sasami!
I don't wanna talk.
Sasami!
You should at least eat!
I...
I'll eat it later, just leave it there.
I got it!
He got it?
On today's menu is my forte, my special ramen!
You should eat it before it gets gooey.
The dessert is my love!
I'll pass on that dessert. Take it back with you.
I see. That's sad.
He got it again?
Oh, by the way, you got a delivery. I'll leave it here too.
I'll be downstairs. Just yell if you need me!
Tsurugi
Incoming Call
Tsurugi?! Hello?
Hey, it's me!
Be careful with bank transfer scams!
I had a little accident and I gotta pay the consolation money.
Think you could you transfer me about 500 grand?
Why're you trying to con me?
Wait, aren't you in the underworld?
Yeah, I'm altering the radio waves to reach all the way.
It's pretty tiring though. Let's keep this brief.
Okay...
I'll be back after I beat some sense into this cocky piece of shit who calls himself my little brother.
Take care of my sisters until then, okay?
As for your mother...
When I dragged her down the slope of Yomi, she was on the brink of falling apart since Tama took a few bites out of her.
She didn't get completely erased
though, so she might return eventually.
Not for a while though.
That's all.
End call
Calling
I see...
End call
Calling
Don't worry about it much.
Guess that's impossible, huh?
But this is the path you chose, and you even faced your mother with sword in hand.
It'd be rude to just give up and stop now.
Look up and keep walking forward. Make that your promise to Tsurugi!
Okay. I'll try my best.
A little more. After a little rest, I'll do my best again.
Calling
Yeah, but don't overdo it. Just do your best.
Oh, by the way, she dropped something stumbling down the slope of Yomi.
I sent it to you. Hope you get it soon.
Laters!
End call
Calling
The call has ended
End of call
Ehime Mikan
Sasami@Unmotivated
I'm back!
Welcome back, Tama. I'm happy to see you're fine.
I'm a bit tired!
You had quite the journey before the big battle, didn't you?
Thanks for your hard work.
You really can do it if you try.
Anyway, since you're here already, you should sing too!
Our sister's still away in the underworld and Sasami's depressed, so there's no one else who can sing.
I'll sing along too.
Really really?
Then I'll do my best!
You smile at me with a disappointed look.
Hey, let's go home together.
I can hear your voice.
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony.
I can't do any more!
That's all I can do!
Hey Kagami, were you actually singing?
I was.
If you didn't hear me, turn up the
volume on your TV and listen again.
It's much easier when you help, Tama.
Someone praised me!
You're really convenient.
Preview
Unmotivated@Ranking
It's time for the Unmotivated@Ranking.
Those who tried the least
Here's a ranking of the most unmotivated things.
In 3rd place:
Third Place
The arm in those crane games.
The arm in the crane game
Try harder.
Try
Harder
In 2nd place:
Second Place
Those ballpens that stop working
even though they still have ink left.
Second Place
The ballpen that stops working though it still has ink left
You're unmotivated, aren't you?
You're
unmotivated
aren't you?
First place:
First Place
This preview corner.
This preview corner
First Place
There's nothing about the next episode!
There's
nothing
about the next episode!
Next Time
Episode Eight
Next time, episode 8: Strategic Solitude.
Strategic Solitude