“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Well, keep it up, Tanaka Taro-kun!
I'll keep this in my custody as a member of the Dollars.
My, aren't we acting all high and mighty now that Harima Mika's gone?
How can this thing die?
You know, right? About the slasher showing up in Ikebukuro again.
All I can do is start fights that only I can win. Am I right?
That's it!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Welcome, welcome! Russian sushi! It's tasty! It's cheap! You eat sushi, yes?
The slasher... he's back!
How many does this make?
This is the scene where another of the slasher's crimes were committed last night.
Out of the blue, half a year ago, a large gathering took place in Ikebukuro's shopping district.
That's precisely when the slasher sightings started.
Also, amongst the youth, there's a rumor about a headless rider...
America has attempted to contact the headless rider, and is working towards analyzing the technology...
The slasher?
The headless rider.
How scary! Unreal!
In this town, things are born and things disappear every day.
And yet, nothing ever happens. Nothing ever changes.
That is... her everyday life.
A Sudden Turn
Our love is completely and thoroughly fake.
Yet, it's stronger than real love.
I love the scar on your neck. It is because of that scar that I can find true love.
I love you, Seiji-san. I love you with everything I have.
I get jealous every time I look at them.
Then stop looking.
Whenever there's a cute girl around, you look and then you raise your voice.
That's the fate that's been carved into the DNA of the male team!
I wish you wouldn't include me in that.
However, fear not. My body belongs to everyone, but my heart is Anri's alone.
I've always thought, why is Anri-san so erotic and cute?
She's not erotic. Don't say "erotic," Kida-kun.
I get it. Eroticism aside, you have to admit she's cute.
Well, I mean...
So you don't think she's cute?
She is! She's cute, but–
Really? So you admit she's cute. However, I also think she's pretty erotic. In other words, in terms of erotic-ness,
I understand Anri deeper than you, and therefore I love her more. So in that regard, I win!
What do you mean? She's totally mine!
You lose, Mikado!
About half a year ago, an insignificant event took place.
In town and at school, everyone was talking about it.
However, it had nothing to do with her. She didn't even care.
You all right?
Thank you.
Nothing ever happens. Nothing ever changes. That is her everyday life.
Good thing we had those points saved up!
Hurry up!
Yumacchi, what're you gonna do with that poster?
She's sure going fast.
I'd say she's got even more guts than before.
Yeah, she does.
I wish they'd be more secretive about something like that.
Yeah, it'd be nice if we were the only ones who knew about it, like in "Ojousama's Secret."
You mean "Nogizaka Haruka's Secret"!
You guys...
Give 'em a break. They've probably been through a lot. And so has she.
Look! It's the headless rider!
This is Celty Sturluson's everyday life. It's what she's always been used to.
Humans who are pulled into something unusual start to panic. At that moment, she would casually slip away.
That's how Celty Sturluson used to do things. However...
I've always thought that in manga and movies, guys like us are usually the pushover type of character when we're with people like you in them.
Once the protagonist arrives with his super powers, we're already dead in a pool of blood, as testimony to the bad guy's strength.
That's fine by me. It just means we're thought of as strong to begin with.
That's just something you can't get around as a director.
However, there's one thing I've always wanted to say.
If there ever was a real monster, an evil psychic, an artificial human or a ninja who came along...
There's one thing, just one thing, that I've always wanted to say to them.
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you monster.
I'll say it again. A monster like you shouldn't mess with the cops!
Celty! Welcome ba– What? What's wrong? To me, being hugged by you is like being awarded the Nobel Prize!
Well, I suppose this isn't the time to use that expression–
Hey. You're shaking. Seriously, what happened?
Celty?
I was scared. I was really scared, Shinra. The police have turned into monsters!
The police?
There were about ten police motorcycles and cars chasing me, as if they were all one creature...
It sounds like they called in more motorcycles from somewhere else to deal with you. I have heard that Hara Kinnosuke,
is somewhat of a "problem officer" who's been known to cause accidents by chasing suspects too enthusiastically.
It was scary. It was really scary. I was prideful. I'll be humble from now on, so please forgive me! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Who are you apologizing to? This timid-like Celty isn't like you at all.
I thought you'd only show me your weak side in bed–
Don't ruin the moment by embarrassing me.
Right... Okay. Well, now that I've ruined the moment, can I ask you to pick someone up for me?
No, it's not a job. He's come home... My father.
Seriously, why am I doing this when he could just take a taxi...
He's always had an interest in me.
What's wrong? C'mon.
Say something! You white freak.
You don't mean...
What's wrong, old man?
He's wearing quite the outfit, isn't he, Horata-san?
Young men. The air in Tokyo is filthy. Don't you think so?
Your filthy face in particular seems to be taking on quite an affected color, no doubt from living in this polluted air.
Hey. I think the heat's getting to the guy's head.
That's all right.
It looks like it's time to teach you the power of an adult.
You boys are protected by juvenile laws, so you could kill someone if you wanted to.
Or at least you think so, right?
Remember this,
when you're trying to kill someone,
prepare to be killed by your oppone–
I think that you're feeling the heat after all, old man. I'm already over twenty years old.
Wait a second. That really hurts, and you're standing on my shoe, so I can't run...
Your finger's poking me, it's poking me! What are you doing, Celty-kun? Hurry up and help me out!
I'd rather not save him...
Couldn't you tell that I only stuck up for myself because I saw you standing there and thought I'd be safe?!
Horata-san, this is the black biker!
What?! Are you sure, Higa?
Yeah, I am. I saw him on TV.
So you were at the Dollars meeting half a year ago, were you?
Everyone thinks that they can come traipsing onto our turf, acting all high and mighty.
What's wrong?
What the hell is this?!
Hey, wait!
Now that's the right reaction.
Good. It isn't broken. This is a gift from Shinra that means a lot to me.
Did you see that? That's the true power of an adult!
I still don't like him.
Is there really a point to this thing?
Again, what are the rules for this?
Russian sushi! Russian sushi! Manager! Oh, Izaya!
Yo. Working hard as always, I see.
You come a lot to Ikebukuro lately, yes? Since you're here, you come to the shop. We just opened the cans this morning.
The toppings are fresh!
Sorry. I would, but I've got a lot on my plate at the moment. I'll come by when I can, though.
Hey.
You can't hide an awl in a sack.
of a hanged person," I believe it is.
"You don't talk about ropes in the home
Okay, in order to find out which one of us understands Anri better, let's list all of her good traits.
I'll start with erotic-ness.
That one, out of nowhere? Quit talking about being "erotic" so much.
Those who laugh at the erotic will one day cry because of it.
I don't get it.
This was her first experience with becoming close friends with boys.
It's your turn, Mikado. What's one of Anri's good traits?
I'll go with...
Actually, she may never have had any close friends before.
"Anri doesn't have any good traits!" Is that it?
I never said that!
Then say something. Say it now! Hurry and say it!
Harima Mika had only kept her around to make herself look better, but that was okay. It was where she belonged. However...
Three, two, one. Too bad!
Now, after losing that niche, she couldn't find another place for herself.
All right! To prove how erotic and cute Anri is, let's all go flirting, the three of us!
What's the logic in that?!
F-Flirting?
It's all right. You're just a lure to make the women think, "Oh, they have a girl with them, so it's okay if I join them."
You don't actually have to do anything.
Hey, wait, Masaomi–
Right then, let's go! Follow me, comrades! Let's ride on!
Here we go!
K-Kida-kun?
Masaomi!
Are you sure this was a good idea?
I'm positive. He goes flirting alone all the time, anyway.
Seriously.
What a hassle. You really have to give shy-boy-kun this big a handicap. What a detestible man I am.
Really, man.
Let's have some fun.
She had noticed that two boys were favoring her. However...
The sunset's beautiful, isn't it?
Though there's a weird-looking cloud over there. It might rain later on, so we should be careful.
You're right.
What?
I have to go.
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
There's no real sunset to this sunset.
If either one of them confessed their love to her
now, she probably wouldn't be able to answer.
She still liked her friend, Harima Mika.
She also liked both of them just the same. She still didn't know
the difference between platonic love and romantic love.
To her, Harima Mika, Ryugamine Mikado, and Kida Masaomi...
Are you sure you don't?
We really need you, man.
I already told you. It's none of my business anymore. This isn't where I belong.
I don't want to go back... to this side again.
For real? That's tight!
There's been a lot more people in yellow recently, huh?
Yellow?
That's right. Since they're easier to pick out, they stand out more than the Dollars.
Oh, you mean the Kokinzoku?
You know them, Setton-san?
Yeah, well...
They've been around a while. Those guys.
Kokinzoku...
A gang that used to be in Ikebukuro.
They've disappeared after getting in a gang fight.
Ah, I've heard about that.
Are they back, do you think?
Ikebukuro's gotten pretty chaotic, too.
Really. Even the police are afraid.
No, really!
Don't underestimate the police.
The police?
She fell down! What a dork.
I only kicked you lightly. You must really be a total klutz.
Of course, she's a little pinworm.
What's with that face?
It doesn't look like they're even close to solving the slasher incidents.
Speaking of which, did you know?
There's a rumor that the slasher is really one of the Dollars.
And apparently that it's the headless rider?
Who said that?!
I don't think it's true, do you?
Jokes aside...
You really should be careful of the Kokinzoku.
Some of them aren't too pleased that the Dollars expanded while they were gone.
Is that so...
I see, I'll be careful.
Jeez. After Harima, you start flirting with Ryugamine and Kida, and Nasujima to top it all off?
How many people do you have to sell your body to before you're satisfied? You little whore!
Apparently you can't live without someone else to leech off of. Pinworm!
Pinworm! Pinworm!
The girl thought to herself that what they were saying was true.
That she had depended on Harima Mika, and probably still did.
Pinworm! Pinworm!
Why so quiet?!
Say something!
Or do pinworms not even have mouths?
Even now, she may have be depending on those two boys, trying to find her place with them...
You stink, pinworm! Don't come to school anymore!
Thanks to you, I lost two boyfriends!
Why are you just staring into space?!
This was how she protected herself. Nothing ever happened. Nothing ever changed. That was her everyday life.
Your place is nearby, right? Let us come over for a bit.
It's time for a little household search.
Hey! Hurry up and lead us there!
He's back!
I would like to cut you instead, for crying out loud!
You're the guy who's been trolling the forums and chatrooms for the last half a year, right?
Didn't we ban you?
I did!
But no matter how many times I try, it won't work!
Ah, is that so?
I keep banning his remote IP, but he comes right back with a different host.
Oh, so he's using a proxy?
I don't think it's a proxy, either.
It really is scary.
Nothing happens. Nothing changes. That is her...
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Durarara
Next time on
Unrest Prevails
The slasher is somewhere in this town.
Every time one of these incidents occur, the fear that is awoken from a sense of insecurity,
gives rise to countless rumors in the wind of the heavy, stagnant, night. However...
Next time: Unrest Prevails.