Lady Dyspear!
Dyspear?
That's her?
She's the one who sealed all of Hope Kingdom's dreams in the cage of despair...
Which makes her Dysdark's head honcho, right?
You are the Princess Precures?
If we beat her, then everyone'll live happily ever after!
We can't let this chance slip away!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
It's a hologram!
Know your place.
Close.
Y-Yes!
I assume you're prepared.
Please wait!
I cannot let this loss to the Precures... to Cure Flora stand!
This is my last request.
Give me one final chance to prove my loyalty!
Very well.
You are to vanquish the Precures at the price of your very being.
Right...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
A Colossal Crisis!
Precure vs. Close!
Where... am I?
Perf!
Are you okay?
Bro, just one more cookie...
She's sleep-talking...
Talking?!
Perf, are you hurt?
Bro...
Th-They're talking!
Drat.
Bonjour! Bonjour, brawk!
Meow!
Wait, Perf's a cat?!
I'm not a cat, I'm Perf!
You really can talk!
Double drat.
You two...
Who are you, really?
What's that?
Dyspairvil!
Run for it!
Where are the others?
Dyspair... vil!
Quit it!
I've got friends to find!
I don't have time to mess with you!
Dyspair!
Dyspairvil!
It's strong...
There you are, Cure Flora.
Close!
Where are we?
Where?
We're in a gigantic cage of despair
that Lady Dyspear made just for us.
Cage of despair?
This cage vastly increases a Dysdark's power.
That includes mine, of course!
Come heck or high water, this will be your doom!
You'll never escape this cage!
Because I...
will end you here and now!
I'm not holding anything back!
Fight me...
Princess of Flowers, Cure Flora!
Here I come!
I'm just getting started!
Oh yeah!
The new Elegant Dress Up Keys we found!
Oh yeah, I've got this!
Why?
Guess your precious key won't save you!
Dyspairvil!
Dys...
Pair...
Those three have been fighting those scary monsters this whole time?
Yeah.
Those are devils created when Dysdark seals a dream away, the Dyspairvils.
You once had your dream sealed away, too.
Huh? I did?
Right now, those three are fighting to protect everyone's dreams as the Princess Precures!
Haruka became Cure Flora to save your dream, too!
She saved... my dream?
Aroma! Perf! Can you hear me?
Sir Kanata!
Who is he?
The prince of Hope Kingdom!
P-Prince?!
It seems they found the new Dress Up Keys.
Yes!
But Dyspear used her magic to trap us and
the Precures inside some kind of giant cage!
What?
I've got a bad feeling about this...
The Precures are in grave danger...
I must deliver this to them!
What's that?
A treasure passed down by Hope Kingdom's royalty, the Crystal Princess Rod.
If this rod is combined with the Elegant Keys,
the Precures will obtain a new power!
That's cool!
But how do we get it here?
Like the Keys, the Princess Rod
is drawn by the power of dreams.
If it can feel the power of the Precure's dreams...
the Rod should find its way toward them.
The power of dreams?
Let's tell them!
But it's dangerous!
I can't sit back and do nothing!
And you are?
Nanase Yui.
I'm Haruka's friend.
Haruka's...
Can I trust you?
Yes!
Coiffure de merveilleuse!
Dyspairvil...
Dys?
Rage, O seas!
Precure!
Mermaid Ripple!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming!
Adieu.
Why couldn't I use my new Key?
Are the others all right?
Over there!
What's wrong?
Is that all you've got?!
Back then...
If I had just stopped you from becoming Cure Flora...
I could have had your world steeped in despair long ago!
If it weren't for you...
then Mermaid and Twinkle would never have appeared!
I've met failure after failure 'cause of you trying to protect your stupid dreams!
You kept me from getting the recognition I deserve!
What, you wanna be a princess?
More like a pain in my arse.
Well congratulations,
you're already both!
You got your wish, so lose already!
That's enough!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Hanging in there, Flora?
Barely.
Is that... Close?
Yeah.
Okay, I don't know the deets,
but I can tell things are pretty serious.
Not even the three of you combined can stand up to me now!
We're almost there!
Is that... Close?!
That's a good look for you.
Now sit still while I end it all!
Both you Princess Precures and your foolish dreams!
I won't...
let you!
Oh?
I want to be a princess! That's my dream!
The end of another's dream is not for you to decide!
Yeah.
My dream belongs to me!
Those eyes...
We won't give up!
We've only begun to chase our dreams!
This light...
Haruka!
Y-Yui?! Why are you—
You need to send the power of your dreams to Kanata!
If you do, the Precures will obtain a new power!
To Kanata?
Hurry!
The power of our dreams?
Let us try.
Seems like it's our only choice.
I'll benefit society like my father and brother do.
I'll become a world famous top model.
I'll become a true princess... the Grand Princess!
I dunno what you're on about...
but it ain't happening!
I'm scared...
He's drawing in the energy of despair!
I'll blacken your dreams with the taint of despair!
He stopped the light!
One more time!
You'll fail!
You have no dreams!
You have no hopes!
And you have no future!
What do we do?
Give up your dreams and give in to despair!
You, me, and everything in this cage will vanish in despair!
He's been swallowed by his despair!
Aroma...
What?
Take care of Perf.
Yui!
Haruka!
This is it!
Flora!
Haruka!
Yui!
What's gotten into you? Are you hurt?
I'm fine, Haruka.
I want to write picture books.
Huh?
Thank you for protecting my dream.
I know it'll come true.
Just like yours!
So, do you think my dream could help you?
I should be the one to thank you!
You've cleared away all my doubts!
I'll make my dream come true
while protecting everyone else's!
Because right now...
I'm the Princess Precure, Cure Flora!
I feel the same.
As Kaidou Minami, and as Cure Mermaid,
I'll fight Dysdark!
As Cure Twinkle...
I can't let you leave me outta this, right?
Wanna give it another go?
Yeah!
That light...
Go, Crystal Princess Rod!
This is...
It's the Crystal Princess Rod!
It's the Princess Precures' new power!
Wow...
Place the Elegant Dress Up Keys in the Princess Rods!
So that's how they work!
Let's go!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Their dresses are different!
They got new dresses!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
I am one of Dysdark's great Three Dusketeers!
Lady Dyspear!
Adieu.
It's Noble Academy!
We're back!
Thank goodness!
Yui...
I'm sorry about keeping the Precures a secret.
I just didn't want you to get involved...
I'd hate to be left out if you're going through something this tough!
After all...
We're friends!
Aren't we?
Yeah!
Let's go home!
Princess Precures...
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Kirara's a reporter?
It's rare for her to accept non-modeling work.
I get to eat Marble Doughnuts' latest creation!
Wow! It's your TV debut!
But this new idol they're debuting with me is on fire!
I won't lose!
Kirara's fired up too!
Go! Princess Precure:
Kirara vs. Idol!
The Blazing Doughnut Battle!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Mie Prefecture - Hiyori (Age 11)
Aichi Prefecture - Shizu (Age 6)