When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright and
sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Sanzenin
What? A party to celebrate my
acceptance into Hakuou Academy?
That's right! Quite the brilliant
idea, don't you think?
Well, it's not official yet,
so I feel like we're getting
ahead of ourselves.
Oh, you have nothing to worry about!
You're bound to have been accepted!
Well, to be honest...
I'm actually feeling a bit
confident about it, too.
I was disturbed in this way...
...and that way.
The teacher administering the
test played games with me...
And in the end, even the monkeys
had their fun with me...
I won't... get to go to school!
Even so, I put forth my
absolute best effort!
Yes, that's right!
All right! Go!
Yes!
In addition, I was lucky that all
the questions were multiple choice.
I'm really good at that "pick
one out of three" thing.
There, that's the one!
Whoa! You idiot!
Of all the boxes, why
did you open that one?!
Pardon me! Pardon me, Miss!
Hey, you! Stop right there!
You hardly seem good at
three-choice questions...
Yes, if Hayate had
dispassionately acknowledged
how unlucky he is at this point,
he may have avoided the comedy,
I mean, tragedy in this episode,
but then again, maybe not.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
At minus 40 degrees Celsius,
you can hammer nails with a banana!
What are you saying, Sis?
Man, I wanna eat perilla pickled eggplants.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Hey, hey! I hafta go to a party.
Hurry up, seriously
HINA!
Hina! There's big trouble!
It's turned into a huge mess!
I've told you to knock before
coming into my room, haven't I?!
Don't make us show this!
I apologize. Really, I'm sorry.
Listen Sis, knocking is
mankind's greatest invention!
The next time you forget,
I'm going to beat you for real.
For real...
Oh, Yuki dear.
I didn't know you were home.
I'm back, Mom.
If only you'd called.
Are you handling living
on your own all right?
I'm fine! Have faith in your daughter!
I'm not lavishing my
money on male companions
nor have I fallen for me-me
cons or phishing e-mails!
But I wish you'd let me see the
place you're living in just once...
I'm having an important conversation
with Hina right now!
What?
Could you just bring up milk tea
and some kind of Japanese sweets?
What?
On the double! Hurry!
Uh, all right.
Sis!
Oh!
Make it sweet! Make the milk tea sweet!
Three sugars, okay?!
You really do whatever you
feel like, don't you?
Yum! Bean jam pancakes really are the best!
I bet you'd get along with the
cat-type robot from the future.
I'm a happy girl!
So? Didn't you come here to
talk to me about something?
Daf wighf! Dere's bif,
bif, bif, pwouble, Hina!
Talk or eat! Pick one!
The Sanzenin butler actually came to
take the transfer admission test!
Wow, I didn't know.
Good for Hayate.
Hakuou's admission tests are hard.
But as Nagi's butler, I'd assume
failure wasn't an option.
I imagine he must have put
some serious effort into it.
Maybe...?
Don't you get in his way, Sis.
Uh-oh!
"Uh-oh"?
Sis, don't tell me...
Th-That's not it!
It was just a tiny prank!
It was meant to be a little joke!
I never imagined he would fall short
of passing by just one point!
Stop breathing like that!
You're spreading the Dark Side!
What are you doing, going around
ruining other people's lives?!
So basically, his not passing
is largely due to your prank
and the superintendent has ordered
you to notify him of the results,
and that's why you've
come to me. Is that it?
Yes, if you please, that is exactly it.
You're hopeless.
For starters, about the only person
we can discuss this with is...
Pardon? Not accepted?
Yes, so we'd like to deliver the
news and apologize in person.
We're on our way right now.
Yes, I'd appreciate that.
I-I'm so vewy sowwie!
I'll have you know,
I'm not coming with you for your sake!
It is only proper that the Hakuou
Academy student body president
should undertake this task.
Yes, that's my little sister!
Make sure you apologize to Hayate
properly and sincerely, got it?
Y-Yeah, I'll do my best.
I'd suspected that something
like this might happen, but...
Still, this has me at a loss...
Hey, Hayate!
Stop resisting and wear the
outfit that I tell you to!
You're the party's guest of honor!
I'm fine with what I'm wearing now!
What are you saying?!
Hurry up and get changed!
But the outfit of your choice
is bound to be a sailor uniform
or something with animal ears!
No, wrong! I've got this for tonight!
I'd rather die!
Why?!
I feel like with this atmosphere,
it's too late to be revealing the truth...
Oh, what should I do?
What should I do? What should I do?
Hey! Calm down!
Welcome, you two.
Oh, g-good evening!
H-Here! It's Andromeda cake from Okadaya!
It's too soon for that!
I had trouble deciding between this
and the turtle bread from Pantasia!
W-Well, why don't you at least come in?
Um, so where's Hayate?
Uh, the thing is...
M-Maria?
Congratulations to Miss Nagi's
Butler, Hayate Ayasaki
Hakuou Academy Acceptance Commemoration Party
What... in the world...?
Well...
Oh, Mr. Klaus.
Without an occasion such as this,
the Miss could never be persuaded
to host a social event, so...
Since she showed the slightest
interest in doing so today,
we are holding a magnificent party
to make up for how rare these are.
So that's what's going on...
And we owe it all to that boy
gaining acceptance into Hakuou!
I cannot tell you how
troublesome he has been,
but he has finally done something
of service to the Miss.
Where do you think you're going, Sis?!
Something urgent came up...
I'm not letting you run away!
He loves me. He loves me not.
Darn it, this is too much trouble!
In the language of flowers,
corn stands for trust!
Hayate and I are...!
They're dancing...
Yes...
Truly, it's almost embarrassing
how merry they are.
It must have made him really
happy that he passed.
It is wholly the result of the
thorough instruction I gave the boy
regarding taking entrance exams.
Besides, I also lit a fire under him,
that he'd be fired if he didn't pass!
Oh? Is something the matter?
N-No, my chronic peritonitis has caused
neuralgia, turning into a hordeolum...
So please don't mind me at all.
I swear! Damn that Klaus!
What I really wanted was a cosplay
party with just the two of us.
Now, now.
If it weren't a celebration for you,
I'd have skipped out long ago.
But Miss, you look quite
fabulous in that dress.
What?
You outshine every last one
of the other guests here!
Y-You dummy! You're the star of the night!
Please!
But it makes me happy to hear it.
Thank you very much, Miss.
Well, if you're happy,
I suppose I'll let it go.
Yes.
This situation makes bringing up the
subject even harder than I expected.
Given that,
please enjoy this merriment
for a while longer.
Shish kebabs!
Roger that!
Japan! It's Goh!
Congratulations to Miss Nagi's
Butler, Hayate Ayasaki
Hakuou Academy Acceptance Commemoration Party
What do you want to do, Sis?
Do you want to at least wait
until the party's over?
Yeah, at least...
N-No...
This is my responsibility!
If I don't carry it out,
I wouldn't be an adult.
Sis...
A-Ayasaki...
Oh, if it isn't Miss Katsura. Welcome!
What is the matter?
Th-The truth is...
The truth is... The truth is...!
Huh?
She has gone to the trouble of
personally coming from Hakuou Academy
to celebrate the acceptance of Miss
Nagi's butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
Now, go on! Give us a brief
speech, if you please!
Uh, um... Well...
Congratulations, Ayasaki!
What?!
Here you are! An acceptance present!
Wow! Thank you very much!
You really worked hard for this!
It makes me so happy!
Sis!
What?
Eek!
That was a counter!
That, just now, was a counter!
I thought an adult carries
out her responsibility!
Because! It's just because!
Next up, we have Miss Nagi's close
friend, Miss Isumi Saginomiya
and she will be delivering
a congratulatory address.
Um...
Miss Isumi became lost on her way over here,
but she was apparently taken
into safe custody earlier
at a souvenir shop on the shore of Lake Mashu,
so that will have to wait until another day.
Same old Isumi.
I wonder how she managed to
get off the main island...
Next, Miss Nagi's cousin, Miss Sakuya
Aizawa has sent a congratulatory gift.
Unveil it!
The title is "Soaring"!
Soaring
What about it is soaring?
Maybe it's the size or something?
Still, this is a rare party
to celebrate your acceptance.
It's too bad that both Isumi
and Sakuya couldn't make it.
It's all right.
Miss Katsura and Hinagiku are here.
That's more than enough for me.
What?
Come to think of it, why are
you here, too, Hinagiku?
Th-Th-That's because...
Come here a sec.
What is it?
Just come here.
What? Not accepted?!
Shh! Keep your voice down!
Impossible! Surely, of all people,
Hayate couldn't have...
It's the truth, so there's no helping it.
I want to let him know somehow, but...
There's no way!
How could we tell him that he didn't
get accepted after all this?!
Or rather, why did you guys
decide that he'd been accepted,
even when you hadn't received any word?!
Can't you use your influence
as student body president?!
If you're going to go there, what about
the Sanzenin family's influence?!
Now, our festivities are
in full swing, but...
What exactly is this "full swing"
from "festivities in full swing"?
Could it be a kind of lassoing?
So anyway, Hayate Ayasaki will now
offer a speech of thanks for today.
Uh, um...
So many of you have come to celebrate
tonight for little old me.
Thank you very much.
I never imagined that I might
get to go back to school...
It's really like a dream come true,
because I'd given up on it.
That I could never go back to high school.
To laugh and fool around with
my classmates at school...
Those days were ordinary, and yet,
so dazzling and precious to me.
Culture Fest
I thought that no matter
how much I wished it,
those experiences would never
be mine to have again.
But now, Miss Nagi has made
this wish of mine come true.
I am truly fortunate.
To have the pleasure of serving
such a kind mistress,
I am the luckiest butler in the world.
Hayate...
Th-Thank you so very much.
Ayasaki.
Listen to me, Ayasaki.
Yes, what is it?
Oh, Sis...
The truth is, I have some very
disappointing news for you.
Disappointing news...?
Yes.
Will she... Will she finally tell him?!
The truth is...
I know.
What?!
Hayate?
You're going to be my
homeroom teacher, right?
Huh?
Well, certainly, with you
as my homeroom teacher,
I imagine I have a pretty tough
school life ahead of me.
I feel like I might get beaten down
both physically and mentally,
and I'm slightly apprehensive,
but it'll be all right!
I think that will turn out
to be fun in its own way!
Yes, that sounds like fun!
How long do you plan to
keep fooling around?!
Whose fault do you think this is?!
B-But...
...when I look into those innocent eyes,
I just can't bring myself to say it!
Or rather...
Hey, damn you! Get a clue already!
That's right!
I'm agonizing so much over here
and he's smiling like a fool!
Argh! I'm suddenly feeling
this surge of anger in me!
Sis?!
I've made up my mind!
I'm taking the truth about his
non-acceptance to my grave!
What?!
That academy is fricking huge!
They'll never notice one fake student!
There is nothing that scares Yukiji Katsura!
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?!
It is not nonsense!
Nonsensers are gonna catch Hellers!
Um, what is this merry conversation about?
O-Oh, it's nothing.
I-It's no big deal.
That was too bad, Hayata.
Y-You three!
What are you doing here?
When we went to visit Katsy's room,
we found this on her desk.
Not Accepted
We figured Hayata would be
feeling quite despondent,
so we came to cheer him up!
It was really too bad, Hayata.
Surely, you must think there
is only darkness ahead of you,
that no good will come
of living out your life.
However, mistakes made in your youth
will prove valuable in the future!
No matter how much you get
stomped into the ground,
rise up again like a weed,
like Princess Sara!
Cheer up, Hayata!
One shot of fight to you!
See you, Hayata!
Um...
Um, I haven't quite grasped
the situation yet, but...
Not Accepted
So, the upshot of it was that I
was not accepted... Is that it?
Yeah.
I...
I see.
I'm sorry!
It's all my fault!
So roast me or boil me, do
whatever you want with me!
Or rather, just kill me!
Oh... Huh?
He's gone.
Hayate?!
Hayate!
Where did he go?
If you stay out here for too long,
you're going to catch a cold.
Nagi and Miss Katsura and the
others are worried, too.
I have done a terrible
disservice to the Miss.
What?
And to Miss Katsura and Hinagiku, too...
To all the people who
celebrated with me today...
Hayate?
It was my fault for getting really
happy and getting my hopes up!
It's stupid, isn't it?
Before I came to this great mansion,
I knew I shouldn't have
any hopes for the future.
Because that way,
I wouldn't have to suffer...
I thought I'd learned that lesson...
But as I allowed myself to be spoiled
by the Miss's kindness and
yours and everyone else's...
...I had begun to forget that
most basic of lessons...
It's better to be empty, because
you have nothing to lose.
So...
Do you think such an empty person
is qualified to be Nagi's butler?
Th-That is...
No, of course, I'm aware that
I've been a burden in many ways.
But I plan to pull myself
together more than ever
and do my best from now on.
Do your best?
What?
Oh? But the look on your face says you can't
possibly do your best all on your own.
M-Maria?
So...
Student ID
Please go here and study hard.
What?!
Th-This is from Hakuou Academy...
My student ID?!
Yes!
I submitted a recommendation for you,
and with that added,
I had them deem that you passed.
Because an empty person
who has nothing to lose
does not have the qualifications
to be her butler.
Maria...
Hayate, I think there will come a day
when you will truly be required to
use your abilities to protect her.
So, please become Nagi's first-rate butler.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll go to Hakuou and I'll become
a first-rate butler, without fail!
Yes!
All right!
I'm going to work hard!
I'll become a first-rate butler,
for Maria's sake, too!
It isn't for my sake, though...
Or rather...
I can't believe how boldly
I behaved towards Hayate!
And that was the story of how Maria
became embarrassed way too late.
If you're going to get embarrassed,
don't do it in the first place!
Next time, he'll fight the
expectations of high school girls!
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Good morn-even-noon! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I don't really get it,
but you'll be able to go to
school, after all, right?
Yes, thank you very much.
I hope to study hard in order to
acquit myself well as your butler.
R-Really?
I guess you're seriously thinking
about your future with me, too.
What is the matter, Miss?
Oh, it's nothing.
I was just meditating a little.
It's Aura Power!
Bye!
Preview
I was in high spirits,
just by getting accepted,
but I transferred with borderline grades.
Will I really be able to cut it?
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
Knowing you, you'll be fine.
In battle, you must always be
reading two or three moves ahead.
Waking up early can certainly pay off.
You get to meet interesting people.
If I make the jab that he's the most
interesting person here, would I lose?
Probably.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Samurai, the Way of the
Warrior, Van Damme in Action".
Himuro, is that enough with the flowers?
Samurai, the Way of the Warrior,
Van Damme in Action
Thank you, Little Master Taiga.
The things Ayasaki does are dangerous,
so never try them at home.