Dear Oreki Houtarou,
Greetings. I am currently in Benaras.
Belated congratulations on making it into high school.
I heard you chose Kamiyama High School.
Now that you're in high school, maybe you can take some advice from your big sister.
Join the Classics Club.
It's a club with a long history, and I was part of it when I was a student.
From what I've heard, the Classics Club now has zero members.
If no one joins this year, the club will be terminated.
As a former member, I can't bear to see that happen.
Houtarou,
protect the Classics Club, the place of my youth!
You just need to put your name on the register.
You don't have anything better to do anyway, right?
Sincerely yours,
Oreki Tomoe
taikutsu na madobe ni
Sitting bored by the back window,
fukikomu kaze ni
A breeze blew through the room
kao wo shikameta no wa
The reason I screwed up my eyes
terekusasa no uragaeshi
Was to hide how embarrassed I was
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
aimai ni unazuku tenohira no kyou
I gave a faint nod from the edge of my palm
egaiteru jibun wa sukoshi oogesa de
The "me" I was trying to be was a bit more than I was
nani ka kawarisou na ki ga shiteiru yo
I get the feeling that something is going to change soon
kokoro ni yobikakeru kimi no sei da ne
You reached out to touch my heart; it must be because of you
kumorizora nozoita yokan
I had a feeling, looking into the clouds
te wo nobasou itsu yori mo chikaradzuyoi yuuki de
I reached out my hand, with a stronger courage than I'd ever had
hikari mo kage mo mada tookute
The light and the dark are still so far away
sore demo bokura wa
But even though they are
yasashisa no riyuu ga shiritai
We still want to know how people could be so kind
ima wa dare no namae demo nai
Now it doesn't matter whose name it may be
kagayaki no kanata he
Beyond the horizon's light,
zenbu kako ni naru mae ni
Before it all becomes the past,
mitsuke ni ikou
Let's go and find out
A month has passed since the Classics Club was revived.
The Activities of the Classics Club and Its Honor
Geography Prep Room
I've grown more accustomed to the Geography Prep Room than I thought I would.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
I drop in whenever I feel bored after school.
Help yourself.
I brought these from home.
Have as many as you'd like.
Thanks.
I'm not against socializing, so long as it's not tiring.
It's barren.
When you plant two crops in the same field?
You're thinking of double-cropping.
Wait, was that a joke?
I know. Lame.
I didn't mean it like that...
Barren, huh?
Yes, it's barren!
What is?
Our time after school is!
A life without goals bears no fruit!
Thank you for the explanation.
So, is there something you want from the Classics Club?
There is.
But that's a personal matter.
I've heard that before.
I'm talking about the Classics Club.
We're a club, so we should be doing club activities.
We don't have an objective.
Yes we do.
We're going to publish an anthology for the cultural festival in October.
An anthology?
Yes!
No thanks.
It's too much work.
No, we have to make an anthology!
There are other things we can do if you want to participate in the cultural festival.
Like a refreshment booth.
Refreshment booths are traditionally banned at the Kamiyama High Cultural Festival.
And we have funds in our budget for an anthology, and our supervisor asked us to, as well.
And! The anthology has more than 40 years of history, and he doesn't want that to end.
You could have told me that first!
I'll do it, okay?
Yes!
So what sort of content are we writing?
I don't know!
Hey...
Sorry, I thought we could start looking into it now.
But I think we'll get a good idea of how to start if we can find a back issue first.
Let's look for one!
Not in here.
Maybe they're in the library.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You're coming too, Oreki-san.
Come on.
I'm not a fan of this.
It's Friday, so the volunteer librarian is probably...
Library
Oh, if it isn't Oreki.
Long time no see. Didn't want to see you.
Hey Ibara, I came just to see you.
This is a sanctuary for culture.
It's not a place for someone like you.
So you're saying it's a place for you?
That's marvelous.
As annoying as ever, I see.
If you came to tease me, then go home.
Um...
Hey Houtarou, what a coincidence!
You guys are getting along great, as usual.
I'd expect no less from Kaburaya Middle's best couple!
Shut it.
I'd rather date a slug than this sulky bum.
A slug...
And Fuku-chan, you've got some nerve to make a joke like that, knowing how I feel.
Sorry Mayaka, did that hurt you?
And you always brush me aside with a joke.
Grow up already!
What's their relationship?
She's had feelings for Satoshi since middle school.
Ahem!
Chitanda-san, this is Ibara Mayaka.
She's from Kaburaya Middle like us.
Nice to meet you.
Mayaka, this is Chitanda Eru-san.
She's the president of the Classics Club that I joined last month.
Nice to meet you too.
So what did you two come here for, anyway?
Oh, right!
Ibara-san, there's something I'd like to ask you.
Yes?
Do you keep anthologies written by clubs here?
Specifically, by the Classics Club.
The Classics Club...
I don't think so.
If they aren't out here, they might be in the archives.
I see.
Why anthologies?
We're going to write an anthology for the cultural festival, so I wanted to take a look at past issues.
So you're going to distribute it at the Kanya Festival?
I'm surprised that Houtarou agreed.
She didn't really give me a choice.
Kanya Festival?
Never heard it before?
It's what they call the "Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival".
It's not another something you made up, right?
I'm serious!
Everyone at the Sewing Club calls it that.
How about you, Mayaka?
Everyone at the Manga Society call it that, too.
Kanya?
How do you write that?
No idea. I've even asked around about it.
I'm guessing "Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival" turned into "Kamiyama Festival",
then "Kanyama Festival", then finally "Kanya Festival".
Anyway, Chitanda-san, you might find the anthologies in our archive,
but the librarian is at a meeting right now, so we can't get in.
I think she'll be back in half an hour.
Do you want to wait?
What should we do?
Wait, I guess.
You're welcome to go home.
Sounds good.
Wait, Houtarou!
Mayaka, why don't you tell them about what you told me earlier?
Good idea.
Oreki, feel like using your head for once?
No.
What might this be about?
It's about a loved book given no love.
A loved book given no love.
It's a strange story.
I was pondering it over with Mayaka since it doesn't make much sense.
Please tell me!
Every Friday I come in for duty, the same book is always being returned.
This is the fifth week in a row.
Already sounds weird, right?
This is the book.
What a pretty book!
That is huge.
Kamiyama High School
Fifty Years of History
Can I take a look inside?
Go ahead.
Oreki-san, you too!
It looks like a normal school history to me.
It seems like a very tough read.
It doesn't seem strange to me that someone might borrow this every week.
You've never borrowed a book from here before, have you?
Our loan period is two weeks.
So there's no reason to borrow it weekly.
But regardless, this book gets returned every week.
Do you know who borrowed it?
Of course.
There's a list of borrowers at the back.
Oreki-san, look at this.
It's a different person every time!
And they all returned the book on the same day they took it out!
Exactly.
For five weeks now, it's been checked out and returned on the same day.
I also know that they all borrowed it during lunch break and returned it after school.
What do you think?
Curious, right?
Yes...
I'm curious!
Let's think about this, Oreki-san!
Damn you, Satoshi...
What do you think? Doesn't it sound interesting?
You stopped me from leaving, knowing that this would happen.
You solved the mystery of that lock and that secret club so easily!
What?
Just the more interesting facets of Houtarou's life.
Don't talk about people like that.
Anyway, I'm curious!
I'm not.
I am!
I'm not!
Oreki!
Keep it down.
You too, Chitanda-san.
Yes...
That was careless of me.
Any further refusal or excuses would just be a waste of energy.
In which case...
Fine, I guess I'll think about it.
Okay!
Fuku-chan, was Oreki actually smart?
Not really.
But he's pretty useful when it comes to useless things.
You guys can sure run your mouths.
Rikka
When the air of summer starts to rise.
Hyouka
Five different people borrow this book each week for five weeks,
and then return it on the same day.
It would be easy to claim that it's just a coincidence, but Chitanda wouldn't accept that.
What's important isn't the truth, but whether or not I can appease Chitanda's curiosity.
Let's see...
If you borrowed this book at lunch and returned it after school, there'd be no time to read it.
And if you aren't going to take it home, you could just read it in the library.
Conclusion: This book isn't being used for reading purposes.
Kamiyama High School
Fifty Years of History
Which means...
How would you use a book besides reading it?
They might make a good pillow if you stacked a few together.
It'd make a good shield if you put it on your arm.
Can we try being serious here?
That's right, there must be some use that only this book can fulfill.
Do you have any ideas then?
Let's see...
You could pile them up as a weight for pickling!
I'm not even going to ask you guys any more.
Is Chitanda seriously a top student?
She seems like a complete airhead to me.
Let's try a different angle.
A
Suzuki Yoshie
Shima Saori
Yamaguchi Ryouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Machida Kyouko
Why are different people borrowing it every week?
If you look at the names, they're all girls.
One
Two
There are two possibilities.
These girls are unrelated to each other, and checking out this book on Fridays is a fad for some reason.
Two
Or these girls are in a group, taking turns checking it out and using it.
One
Two
Not a group
As a group
A fad, huh...
Maybe for fortune-telling?
You mean like...
"Your lucky item this week is the school history!"
"If you borrow it on Friday afternoon and then return it on the same day, things will go well with your boyfriend!"
How's that?
That's just dumb.
And this happened five weeks in a row.
Just throwing out ideas.
The common link is that they're all girls, and all in second year, but different classes.
Could there be some reason why they're all girls?
I can't think of one.
It's entirely within the realm of probability to get only girls if
you were to randomly pick five students from the entire school.
And girls hanging out in a group together isn't exactly rare, either.
Maybe it's some kind of message?
For example, "yes" if it's returned facing up,
and "no" if it's face down?
I don't think you could use it that way.
Look.
I see...
Returns Corner
You can't really tell whether they're face up or down.
Well, wringing Oreki's brain isn't going to get us very far.
Fuku-chan and I already spent ages thinking this—
What?
I smell something.
Really?
I don't smell anything...
No, it's definitely there.
Something quite pungent, like paint thinner...
There's no mistaking it.
Dog.
Well I guess if Chitanda-san is that sure of it, she must be right.
Which would mean...
Houtarou...
That face tells me you've figured it out.
Really?
Maybe.
Can't say for sure though.
Chitanda, feel like taking a walk?
There's someplace I'm interested in.
Alright!
Wait, I meant just you, not me.
Just me?
Why?
Well, because...
That's right, Chitanda-san!
Don't let Houtarou use you!
He's more useful the more you use him!
Careful how you say that.
Oh, I just thought that if we're going somewhere, we should go together.
Oh, well that's fine.
Let's go then, Oreki-san!
It's a pleasure to have you here.
Welcome to our humble restaurant.
There are two courses available.
Gray Course
Rose-colored Course
Which would you prefer?
We recommend this one.
Oreki-san?
Fine.
We didn't have gym class today because of the rain, anyway.
I've still got a bit of disposable energy left.
Okay!
Just how limited are your energy supplies?
Oh, shut up.
Let's go then.
Wait.
I'll come too.
I'm a bit curious.
Fuku-chan, take care of the desk for me.
I can't just abandon my library duties.
Later, Satoshi.
Have fun watching the desk.
So where are we going, Oreki-san?
The Art Room.
That's in the other building.
Right. It's far, which is why I didn't want to go.
You are seriously lazy.
What will we find there?
Let's put together what we know first.
If you consider how big that book is, there's probably no girl who'd find time to use it during break.
Break
Lunchbreak
Which means they must be using it during class.
Class
And the only class time where students from different classes would intermingle would be?
Gym or an arts class.
Class
Right.
Those girls decided to take turns borrowing the book every week before class.
I don't get why they do it every week.
The loan period is two weeks.
It’s easier to return something that big than take it home every week.
That makes sense.
What's wrong?
It's the same smell as the book!
Really?
You'll understand when you look inside.
That's what the book's being used for.
A combined class for 2-D, 2-E, and 2-F.
Paintings for an arts elective class.
The book's cover is perfect for a motif in a painting.
So it was the smell of paint!
How did you figure that out?
"How?"
It just came to me.
I was just lucky.
Library
Brilliantly done!
It didn't even occur to me that it might have been used as a motif for paintings.
How did you even figure that out?
You're weird, Oreki.
What are you talking about?
There's no one more average than me.
Well, I wonder about that...
You really surprised me though...
I'm curious about what's in your head.
Curious?
I feel like I want to open it up and take a peek inside.
There's nothing special about my brain.
It's nothing compared to the school's top student.
You're a top student?
That's right!
We haven't had our midterms yet, but she'll definitely take the top spot!
No...
Even if my grades are good, it just means I understand how the parts work.
But I'm not interested in the parts.
I want to know how it all works as a system.
I see...
Nevermind that, I find her sense of smell far more mysterious.
Oreki-san might even be able to...
Oh, nevermind. It's nothing.
Well, regardless, that was quite a fun way to pass the time.
What do you think, Chitanda-san?
It was fun, of course!
It felt like time flew by.
I spent all that time and still couldn't figure it out...
That bothers me!
I told you before, right?
He's useful every now and then.
I can't stand losing to Oreki, though!
It bothers me!
Now, now...
Different...
They're different.
I can't be like them.
Something's different.
What?
That's right.
Was it just a rare moment of genius? Or perhaps...
You can't leave yet, Oreki-san!
Why not?
Oh right, the anthology.
We have to wait for the librarian.
You sure can be careless sometimes, Houtarou.
Sometimes?
Now that's an understatement.
Ibara-san!
Good work. You can go home now.
Oh, you're back, Itoigawa-sensei.
I'm Fukube Satoshi from the Classics Club.
We're looking for a back issue for the anthology we're making.
Would you mind if we took a look in the archives?
The Classics Club?
The anthology?
You're in the Classics Club?
I see. I'm afraid that there aren't any back issues of the anthology in the archives.
Are you sure you didn't see them?
I'd remember if they were there.
I have to go now.
Thank you very much.
So she says, Chitanda-san.
That's a problem...
I'm sure we'll find them at some point.
Well, Oreki?
Do you feel better having solved the mystery?
Not really.
I see.
I guess we should just go home then.
And I did learn something today...
What do you mean?
Nothing. Just a personal matter.
That again?
Yes...
Oreki-san might even be able to...
Hello. Oreki residence...
Hello?
This is Chitanda!
Chitanda?
I'm sorry, did I wake you up?
Kind of. I thought it was maybe my sister.
So why are you calling on a Sunday?
If it's possible, I'd like to meet with you today.
A
Pineapple
Sand
I have something important to talk to you about.
She's late.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting!
So, what did you want?
Pardon?
Why did you call me out to this cafe?
But you picked out the cafe.
I'm going home.
W-Wait please!
This is my precious day off.
I can't afford to waste it playing the fool with you.
I'm sorry!
I'm just nervous...
Nervous, huh?
Are you going to confess to me or something?
Perhaps you could call it a confession...
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight's the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let's meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
mebaeteta nukumori atatakakute tomadou
I felt a growing warmth; it felt so nice that I couldn't think
konna kimochi wo mada anata wa wakaranai no
But these feelings I have, you still don't know they're here
sono shisen ni wa imi nante betsu ni nai hazu
I don't think there's anything special in how you look at me
datte tomodachi ni shiteru no to onaji
It's the same way you look at your friends
akegata ni kieteku chiisana negaiboshi
Fading into the dawn, my tiny wishing star
yoru no aida de no mahou
Magic that lasts only the night
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight's the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let's meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
Next time: A Descendant of the Classics Club and Her Reasons
A Descendant of the Classics Club and Her Reasons