She'll be filling in for Iwasawa?
You gotta be kidding me.
I'm Yui!  Glad to be working with you all!
Who's she?
You weren't informed at all?
She's GDM's new vocalist candidate.
You are aware that Girls Dead Monster is a rock band, correct?
Is she planning on changing it into an idol group?
No, I'll sing it right!
Please don't judge until after you've heard me!
At least she's got the look down.
Yay!  Everyone!
Thank you for gathering up today!
Is this some sort of performance?
Is this death metal?
Crazy baby.
I—  I'm dying—
No, I think that was accidental...
What a spaz she is.
She's the complete opposite of the cool-beauty Iwasawa-san.
I'm not too confident about having her on lead vocals for Girls Dead Monster.
How about we find someone else?
I agree.
Hey!
I was singing it right, wasn't I?!
I'm a total fan of Iwasawa-san, so I can sing all her songs!
But it wasn't really reaching people's hearts.
Not in the least.
Nope.
Damn it!
Crushing a bud of talent with poor senses of judgement like yours is just...!
And you guys call yourselves upperclassmen?!
What a noisy girl.
There's also the fundamental issue of her attitude.
So what do we do?
At least she's motivated.
She's just a groupie.
Let's leave the judging up to the band members.
Really?!
Yay!
I can pair up with Hisako-san, the guitarist!
Her godlike poses are totally awesome!
I wonder how her mind works?
I'd say she's fired.
I'd say so, also.
Did I say something wrong?!
If the band's like this, we can't run any grand operations on Ball Day.
"Ball Day"?  There's such a thing?
Of course there is, since it's a school.
So we'll sit and watch, eh?
We'll be participating, naturally.
Won't we be obliterated if we do?
We'll be participating as a guerrilla force, of course.
Listen up, everyone.  Each of you will gather people up and form a team.
Any team that loses to an NPC team...
will face a penalty game more painful than death.
Don't ignore me!
I think she's just threatening us since we can't do anything about it.
Daily training is part of our duty.  She's just enforcing it.
Otonashi.
I need you.
You swing like that?
That's not what I meant at all!  I'm talking about the team!
Let's team up, Otonashi.  We don't want to be losers in this.
Yurippe is serious.
Do you know who else to get for the rest of the team?
Leave it to me.  I've basically survived here thanks to my charisma so I'll form the best team.
You joined Takamatsu's team?!
Yeah.
I don't get it!  Why didn't you wait for me?
It makes less sense to wait for your invitation.
Besides, Takamatsu's better than you.
She's got great athleticism, too.
Damn.
Yeah, that's some great charisma there.
Whatever, it'll be a dirty trick, but let's have Matsushita Fifth join us, even if he's more of a leader than a follower.
I bet he's already taken.
No, he's waiting for me.
He's, how shall I say... a true friend at heart.
Well, that was embarrassing...
Oh, I already joined Takeyama's team.
I had no reason to say no.
Hold on just a minute!
Why?!  I had faith in you!
He said that he'd give me all the beef udon lunch tickets he gets from now on.
Beef...
He said, "A true friend at heart.  Well, that was embarrassing..." just a moment ago.
You don't have to repeat it!
Great.
We'll try T.K. next.
I'm counting on you, T.K.
By the way, why does everyone call him T.K.?
He wants us to call him T.K.
No one knows his real name.  He's a total mystery figure.
But I trust him.
Goddamn!
You're acting like T.K., you know.
By the way, what ball game are we playing?
It's baseball.
So we need seven more people.
I don't think that's possible.
Well, well.  Look who's in it deep.
Oh, let's see.  It's the suffocating death metal vocalist.
Do I even look like someone who'd do that kinda performance?!
Yes, you do.
So, what do you want?
You're short on members, right?
I'm sure to add strength to your team.
"Strength"?
Hold on.  You could take a ball in the face and the opponent pitcher would get booted for dangerous pitching style.
That works!
Welcome to the team!
Are you sure your brain didn't melt and drain out of your nose?
Hey, remember, I'm your upperclassman!
Oh, excuse me then, upperclassman.  Did your cerebrum melt and seep out from your nostrils, perhaps?
As if!
Senpai... that hurt!
It's the same for me, here!
But it does look like she has good athleticism.
Snap out of it, Otonashi!
We don't want to be considered friends with a girl who has a screw loose!
That hurt...
Yeah, but all the people you had your eyes on are taken.
Yeah, totally!  I was watching.
That's why Yui-nyan is here to help you.
Say that again.
I'm Yui-nyan!
Stuff like that pisses me off the most!
Uncle!  Uncle!  Uncle!
Let's get a move on!
Shiina-chi.
Where are you?  Come out.
What brings you here?
We searched everywhere for you.  You've got great athleticism, right?
I've never measured it.
I'm sure you're great.
Come play baseball with us.
Back then...
I've been considering why I came up short compared to the new guy.
You mean when we did the Guild Operation Parachute?
It really is something of a legendary act, how Otonashi managed to survive until the end.
I was just lucky.
I should have been superior in all aspects.
I'm sure you are.
But I am inferior to you in one way... my concentration ability.
No... I bet you have a better attention span than me.
Ever since that day, I've been balancing this broom on my finger.
She's a dumbass, isn't she?
She is, but she's a valuable asset.
This is good timing.
I challenge you, kid.
Challenge me to what exactly, while balancing a broom like that?
A baseball challenge, of course!
But make sure you two duke it out over scoring averages, got it?
No one-on-one matches!
Very well.
I won't have to balance a broom, too, will I?
Of course not.  I'll show you the difference in our concentration ability.
All right, we're good.
Got yourself another dumbass on the team!
So we've got four now...
I guess we'll have to ask him.
No one would ask him to join the team.
He's impulsive and doesn't listen to orders from anyone other than Yurippe.
So he's pretty much another dumbass.
But dumbasses are easy to use.
And look — no one's better at swinging around a long stick than he is.
So the time has come.
The time to settle our score!
Whoa, let's test a few things out first.
You'll have to show who's got better athleticism: you or him.
Why?
Strength alone won't make Yurippe notice you.
Deal.
He really is a dumbass.  He didn't even realize he's being used.
Sorry.
Looks like all the others are already taken by other teams.
We're still only five strong.  What do you propose we do?
Can't you do something about that broom?
Even if you are serious, with that you look like you're playing around.
That only happens when my concentration is broken.
How's this, then?!
What?!
What was that for?
Hey now, quit fighting.
Hinata, why don't you—
Hinata?
Hinata!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
I zoned out for a minute.
Well, what can we do?
We'll recruit some normal NPCs.
Oh, yeah!
I'll bring over my good friends!
"Friends"?
We're um...
Yui-nyansan's fans, I guess.
We're basically her self-proclaimed bodyguards.
Yui-nyan has been doing her own street lives without becoming arrogant about her talent.
They're all groupies!  Will they really be of any help?
Still, even all combined, there's still only eight.
Who cares?  We have enough.
We're playing this guerrilla-style anyways.
We'll leave the center fielder out, and have the left and right fielder move toward the center some.
Are you sure?
Homerun!
Wow.
Way to go, T.K.!
It really is a total mystery what you were doing until you died!
Don't stop dancing!
It's outta there!
Looks like the guerrilla operation is going well.
I wonder how Tenshi-san likes this.
All the Battlefront teams are moving up the ladder pretty good.
Shall we get a move on, too?
Another one...
Nobody's team will be able to move up without beating us first.
How about janken to decide who's the challenger?
The number of teams just keep increasing.
Come on.  We're students of this school, too.
Hey, you plead, too.
Let us play, damn it!
What do you think you're doing, threatening him?
My joints'll get pulled out of place!  I won't be able to hit a homerun!
No one's expecting that out of you!
If we lose here, we're bound to face the penalty game.
We need to be pumped for this first game.
You're up to bat first.
Me?
What about me?!
Calm down.
I'll bat second.
Shiina's third.
And you're batting fourth.
If you don't bring everyone home, you lose.
Very well.  That's an easy task to accomplish.
Get seven runs in, and it'll be a cold game.  Let's end this before Tenshi even gets here.
Let's do this.
Fight!
Y-Yeah...
What a lack of unity.
Play ball!
Trying to end it with a cold game, eh?
Then I'd better get on base.
Yay!
Nice going!
Is that the best you can do?!
What did you say?!
You can do better!
There's no such sport like this!
You're out!
They're dumbasses.
Jeez.
Such child's play.
Are you ready?
For what?
Bring it!
Homerun!
No way...
So, why am I the pitcher, again?
Noda hit the homerun, so now you'll have to keep their half of the inning at 0.
Who are we fighting against...?
Bring it on!
Strike!
Is that all you've got?!
How's this?!
That's nothing!
You...!
Quit playing between yourselves!
I guess stupidity isn't cured, even after death.
Foul ball!
Out!
Wow.  Dumbass.
Hinata Team: 3rd inning, cold game victory.
Okay, the Battlefront teams are steadily making their way up.
Everyone's seriously playing in fear of the penalty game more painful than death.
How hilarious.
It's famous amongst the Battlefront members how dreadful your penalty games are.
You're right.  Hey, wait!  What sort of penalty games?!
I can't comment on it, since I've never experienced one.
I've never done one, eith—
Hold on.
Seems she was successfully lured to the field.
They don't have weapons, just bats and gloves.
I wonder what kind of peaceful solution they'll try to come up with.  Let's see what they do.
Your team has not enrolled in the event.
Who cares?  It's meaningful that we take part in the event.
I'm Naoi, the Student Council Vice President.
We have formed a team for the Student Council.
We will properly eliminate the team you're a part of.
Hey, now.  A team composed of the starting lineup of the baseball team?
How do we stand a chance against this?
Look forward to getting shoved up!
You keep your mouth shut!
And it's "shot down"!
Do you need a bat shoved up your ass?!
That hurts!
The Takamatsu team lost as a cold game in the 2nd inning, followed thereafter by the Takeyama team.
Goddamn it!
Oh, man!  That's totally unfair!
We only have one team left now.  Which one was it again?
It's Hinata-san's team.
And here I wanted to make Tenshi cry, too.
Those useless lots...
So we're here.
We'll now start the final game.
How uncute.
She should provoke us a little.
Play ball!
Homerun!
All right!
Time out!
This sucks.  We can't hold off the baseball regulars.
Especially our outfielders.  They can't do shit.
Oh, I had an extra lunch ticket, so I gave it to him as a treat.
You did that for us?!
Well done!  He never forgets gratitude for food!
Now we're set with the outfielders!
Uncle!  Uncle!  Uncle!
I'll kill you later!
Great, Matsushita Fifth!
This is more like a circus than a baseball game.
Out!
Three outs!  Change!
Yes!
Change pitchers.
We could win at this rate!
They're doing pretty well.
And playing so fair, too.
Has anything ever gone so much against what Tenshi wanted before?
Serves her right.
Yurippe-san, you sound like a villain.
We might be able to win.
Final inning.  One run ahead.
Two outs, runners on second and third bases.
Time out!
Crap, I don't think I can hold him off.
Hey, could you switch pitchers—
What's wrong, Hinata?
Oh, nothing.  A long time ago, when I was still alive, something similar to this happened.
It was a really important game.
Are you shivering?
Am I?
That's strange.
What happened?
I don't know.
I don't remember well.
I used to be on the baseball team.
We were trying to go to the national Koushien finals.
It was deadly hot.
All I could taste was the dirt in my mouth.
I remember those details.
It was during one of the regional game finals.
There were two outs, runners on second and third bases.
A pop fly went to second base.
Pretty much where I stood.
But...
I don't remember... if I caught that...
or not...
Well, if I had, there's no way I would forget it.
I probably dropped it.
I can't find a damn thing to say to him.
Yeah, since he went and wasted everyone's three years' worth of effort all by himself.
He's a fucking pest.
Don't rub it in.  He hasn't moved at all.
Think he'll recover?
I'm a little worried, so I'll go talk to the upperclassmen.
Hey.
I heard the story.
Sorry, man.  Must've been tough, huh?
I bet something like this is what you need right now.
It's fine.  I mean, just try it once, give it a shot.
Okay?  It'll make you relax.
Are you... planning on being obliterated?
I mean... will you be obliterated if we win this game?
Me, obliterated?  What are you saying?
I won't be obliterated over something like this.
Finish the game, Otonashi!
No way.
A second base pop fly.
It's exactly the same as that day.
Hinata!
If I catch this, will the game end?
That... would be the best feeling ever...
Don't catch that, Hinata!
I—
I... don't want you to be obliterated!
Gotcha!
This is all for the locks you put me in!
Home in.
At a time like this...
What do you think you're doing?!
My bad!  I'll wait for the right timing next time!
Uncle!  Uncle!
Not happening!
Dammit!  We lost after coming this far?!
Home in!  Game set!
I'll never forgive you for this!
That hurts!  I'm gonna pass out!
Die!  Die!
I wish they'd both get obliterated...
Don't you know the test is starting?
I knew it'd come to me!
I resign!
What did you guys do?
The operation is nearly perfect.
What the hell is that?!
Look, I drew number one!
What do... we fight against...?
It's the final piece Iwasawa left behind.
It's a Physics test, you know...
I only need true love!
How ridiculous...
I even took away such a small piece of happiness from her...