So, Aki, how many people are going on this trip?
Yoshii Akihisa is in quite a bind.
Th-There's nine people including you. Is that too many?
If I borrow a minivan, it shouldn't be a problem;
but who are the other seven people you invited?
Th-They are—
Actually, I think you know them.
There's Yuuji,
Hideyoshi,
and Voyeur.
And the rest?
Other than them...
This is bad.
She ordered me not to hang out with girls.
I can say Kirishima is coming as Yuuji's fiancée,
but Himeji,
Minami,
and Kudou are coming too.
She'll kill me if she finds out!
So...
Who are the others?
Um, Hi-Hi—
You already mentioned Hideyoshi.
It's a se~cr~et.
Aki, please brace yourself.
I'm sorry! It was just a joke!
Tell me the truth and in return I'll give you a kiss.
The other four are aliens.
Aki, close your eyes.
Wait a second! That was so obviously a lie, right?
Humans are aliens in a way.
Wait! I'll apologize! Stop!
Stop!
I can't... I can't believe you hate me so much!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're my sister, so—
It turns you on, right?
She's a pervert!
She's a hopeless pervert!
Serious
Don't take it too seriously.
Joke
Thirty percent of it was joke!
This is bad. She's almost completely serious.
Aki, you're a bad boy for trying to deceive me.
Why did you try to lie about it?
You won't get mad if I tell you?
Not at all! As long as it's not that girls are coming,
I won't get upset or make you cross-dress!
Where are you going, Aki?
I don't want to get yelled at, beaten up, crushed, or be forced to cross-dress!
I see. You invited girls.
Th-That's not it!
It's that, um...
They've helped me study, and I would've felt bad not
inviting them since we always hang out together.
I didn't know we'd be staying overnight.
My, you're so helpless.
It's fine.
Th-Then...
Just this time, all right?
However, if you engage in any
improper activities with the girls...
I'll slaughter your entire family!
That means you'd die too.
daimondai hitori to futari
大問題、ひとりとふたり
The big question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
karafuru mawaridasu watashi no shourai
カラフル回り出す 私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
a sou ookina sekai wa kibun ga hirogaru
あ、そう 大きな世界は 気分が広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日も大好き
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当に大好き!
I really do love you
watashi no baka
私のバカ
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
星の数よりもバカだ!
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaete kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えて 君＋謎＋私は
Answer me. What does you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Me, Everyone, and the Beach!
Question 1
Today's the day of their trip to the beach.
The weather's great, Yuuji.
Yeah, it's great that everyone could come too.
I was looking forward to this so much, I could barely sleep!
Mizuki, you're not in elementary school anymore!
I bought a new swimsuit just for today!
Didn't you buy a new one not too long ago?
Um, that one is... the size is...
Do you mean, you got fat?
Weight Gain
Just a little bit! Really, only a tiny bit!
A tiny bit... too fat...
Settle on one!
It's not what you think! I gained
weight because my hair got longer!
Come on, it's because you weren't being careful.
Actually, I lost weight due to the summer heat!
That's not fair, Minami! You betrayed me!
Yeah, I got slimmer... starting with my chest.
Himeji, Shimada, you're both worrying too much.
You don't look that different.
Well, excuse me! My breasts develop slower than yours!
I don't have breasts to develop!
Don't worry about us. We know you'll eventually grow into a drop-dead gorgeous figure.
Someone as glamorous as you couldn't understand our problems, Kinoshita!
I'm a man! Calm down!
What's wrong with both of you today?
But...
I'm jealous of her boobs!
I'm jealous of her slender waist.
Indeed, Akira is a threat. I'll have to keep a close eye on Yuuji.
She's got a great figure from top to bottom. It's amazing!
I bet she'd look good in one of those
skimpy swimsuits from porn magazines!
Oh, Kouta, what's wrong?
Just car sickness.
It's a little odd to get a nosebleed from car sickness.
Aki, can you get him some motion
sickness pills from the bag?
No problem!
Huh? The zipper won't open.
One, two... There!
Great! I opened it.
Huh?
It's an old-school swimsuit. Wow.
Sis, no way!
What are you doing, Akihisa?
What should I do, Yuuji?
I just discovered there's a hopeless freak in my family!
You look like a freak with that swimsuit in your hand.
No, this is my sister's swimsuit.
I see. You've got a thing for your sister's swimsuit, huh?
You're right, you are hopeless.
You don't understand! This is unacceptable!
Sexy + Cute
Moe point +∞
School Swimsuit
Aki, you asked me to wear a swimsuit that didn't
show much skin so you wouldn't feel embarrassed.
Sorry, but no!
Compared to walking with someone your age wearing a school swimsuit,
you showing a bit of skin is nothing!
Change it! Change the swimsuit!
As your little brother, I can't let you wear this!
Are you saying I should wear something more revealing?
Exposure
Yeah, fine. Whatever.
Akihisa, don't be such a pervert.
Voyeur, the Lord of Perversion, just called me a pervert!
Don't cry, Akihisa. It's the same as when you call other people idiots.
Are you implying I'm the Lord of Idiocy?!
I guess I have no choice. I'll wear something else.
Forbidden
That swimsuit was so tight around my breasts that they were spilling out.
Wow!
What a good view!
The breeze feels great!
It's the perfect location.
All right! Let's get changed quickly and go for a swim!
Yeah!
This is my opportunity to make
everyone realize that I'm a guy.
This time I got it right and brought trunks.
This should shut them up!
Yay!
I changed inside the car!
The tan lines are different from
the swimming team's swimsuits.
Isn't this kind of sexy, Voyeur?
You can take as many pictures as you want!
I don't mind at all!
Don't get full of yourself, Kudou Aiko!
Huh?
Your swimsuit doesn't interest me in the slight—
I'm getting heat stroke.
You did your best, Voyeur. That was 28 seconds.
That's awesome! You broke your nosebleed endurance record!
Are you all right, Voyeur?
Oh no, if you come any—
The sunlight's so strong!
Voyeur!
I wish to be reborn as a bird.
No way! Don't say something like that!
So that I'll be up in the sky;
able to peep into girl's locker rooms as much as I like.
He failed to learn from what had killed him.
Swoosh. Swoosh.
So lemon juice actually goes pretty well with sugar, huh?
We're sorry!
Thank you for waiting!
Thanks for waiting.
Is Tsuchiya all right?
He's calmed down now.
Aiko.
Don't harass Tsuchiya too much.
Well, I didn't do anything!
Tsuchiya got excited because your swimsuit was so cute!
That claim has yet to be verified.
Excited?
Yup, Tsuchiya is a boy, after all.
I see.
Scissors.
Oh my God!
What the hell are you doing?!
You should get excited by my swimsuit.
There's no need for that because
both of you look really pretty!
Oh my! You called me pretty.
I'm so embarrassed!
Yoshii, thank you.
Well sorry for not being attractive!
That's not true!
Minami, you're slim, but you've
got weight where you need it.
I know, I know! My breasts are
small and my belly is plump!
That's not what I meant!
Hey there everyone! Thanks for waiting!
What are you doing?!
What do you mean?
Why aren't you wearing a top?!
Well, that's normal for a man's swimsuit.
A girl shouldn't be wearing a man's swimsuit!
Look, I'm not a girl, and...
Anyway, just come with me!
You've got it wrong! Listen to me!
Wait! Let me go!
Oh, Minami.
Did my little brother do something wrong again?
What's wrong, Minami?
Don't mind me, I know I'll never win!
Akira, excuse me for a second.
Amazing!
Sorry! Excuse me!
The beach is so cruel!
God's the cruel one!
Sorry, everyone. I'm a bit late.
Is something wrong, Hideyoshi? You look depressed.
Just leave me alone.
The beach is cruel in more ways than one.
Question 1
Fill in the blank in the following sentence with
the correct term.
In chemical substances in solid or liquid state,
molecules are held together by the (      ) force.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
( Van der Waals ) force
Teacher Comments
Correct. It is sometimes referred to as intermolecular forces.
Van der Waals force occurs between ionic bonds.
Be careful not to confuse it with Coulomb force.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
( Wandervogel ) force
Teacher Comments
I can tell you sort of remember how it sounds like.
Unfortunately, this is a force
involved in interactions between mountain hikers,
not molecules.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
( Ef ) fort
Teacher Comment
I do not mind this answer, actually.
Right
Akihisa, it's more to the right!
Left
No, actually, it's more to the left!
Front
Yoshii, go forward more!
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Right
Left
Front
Who should I listen to?
Aki, turn 32 degrees to the left
and walk 4.7 meters forward.
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Actually, do the opposite.
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7 m
They're all giving me different directions!
What should I do?
How about Yuuji?
Yuuji, how's my swimsuit?
It's okay, I guess. I saw it last time, remember?
I asked because you probably weren't paying attention.
You need to come and get a better look.
Wait, hey, don't grab on to me!
Things are touching!
Right there!
Go to hell!
Watch it!
Damn! I missed.
Sorry, Yuuji! I thought you were the watermelon.
It looked like you were aiming right at him.
Oh, come on, Hideyoshi. It was a misunderstanding!
Yeah, Hideyoshi.
Akihisa was only after the watermelon.
Now, then, it's my turn.
What's wrong? Let go of the bat, Akihisa.
Yuuji, you just had your turn and failed.
The first round is over. Now we're on the second round and I'm first.
It's only fair to go in reverse order in the second round!
Um, it'd be a waste to splatter the watermelon everywhere, so let's stop trying to split—
It's all right!
I swear I won't crush the watermelon!
Then just what are you trying to crush?
Wow, I'm tired.
I didn't even swim. Why do I feel so exhausted?
You brought it upon yourself.
Thanks for waiting!
We bought lunch.
Sorry we're late!
Was the store crowded?
No, it was...
Well, some guys hit on us.
I really hate things like that!
So do I.
Oh man, that sounds like a hassle.
Just give them the cold-shoulder.
Definitely!
Hold it. That's not how you should react!
Jeez, you really don't get us girls at all.
Yes. Yuuji, you need to worry more.
Huh? What are you—
My eyes!
I wish Akihisa would show a little more concern about us.
I know! Why don't we make him worry?
That's right.
Jeez, guys keep hitting on us everywhere!
I know! It's always such a pain to deal with!
Huh? Guys hit on you a lot?
Yes! All the time!
Seriously, anywhere we go!
But, you didn't look that used to it.
Th-That's not true! I was just tired of it happening all the time!
Yeah! A slow guy like you wouldn't understand!
That's rude! I hit on girls all the—
All the what?
For starters,
there's no way you could pull off hitting on a girl!
Exactly! That sort of thing isn't your
forte and I doubt it'd go well!
Don't try to show off!
Yuuji, you don't understand girls either. That's why you aren't popular.
How dare you say—
Everyone has things that suit them and things that don't.
A romantic relationship isn't for you, Aki.
Damn it! They're ridiculous!
It feels like they were picking on us for the fun of it.
We aren't popular? What the hell?
I know! If I get serious, getting a girl is...
Huh?
What's wrong, Akihisa?
An unbelievable sight!
Hit on...
What?
Voyeur is getting hit on.
What are you smoking? I told you not to speak gibberish unless you're asleep—
You're a photographic genius!
This is a “normal feature”.
Come on, don't be shy!
You're so cute!
Impossible! Why is Voyeur...
Yuuji...
What is it?
Is there any chance, that you and I are the only ones who aren't popular?
Don't be ridiculous! There's no way that's true!
Yeah! Of course not!
It's just that Voyeur looks quiet and harmless.
He's just a different type!
We shouldn't start jumping to conclusions!
Exactly! How dare they say we can't mack on girls?!
We'll show them what we can do!
That's the spirit, Akihisa! Let's show them how good we are!
Yeah!
Now that I think back,
I can only say that something was wrong with us back then.
I can only say something
was wrong with us back then.
Do you even know how to hit on a girl?
The quickest way is to copy the success of others; let's learn from Voyeur.
So we should go after the girls
taking the photos, right?
Yeah, one of us can say, “I'll take your picture if you'd like,”
that should make a good ice-breaker.
Mhm.
Then, whoever isn't talking can bring up more conversational material,
and everything will be smooth sailing from there.
How exactly will they decide what topics to bring up?
They'll just have to think something up.
So, it's the wingman's fault if things fall through?
Damn you, Akihisa! What's up with you sprinting like that?!
How about you, huh?!
You can follow me nice and slow!
Yuuji, I'll get the conversation going for you!
Like I'd trust you! Leave it to me!
I won't let you!
Ice
Thanks for waiting!
I'll take the picture now!
Miss!
You look pretty.
If you'd like,
we'll take some swimsuit shots.
I didn't expect her to call the cops.
Maybe taking photos is a bad way to start a conversation.
Right.
We don't have Voyeur's skill with cameras.
All right! Let's change our approach.
What are we going to do?
First, we'll compliment their looks; then
we'll get more conversational. How's that?
Everyone loves a compliment!
However, how do we compliment them?
We use comparisons.
Tell them they look like TV stars
or sports players.
After we've compared them to someone, and the conversation gets going, the rest...
will be a easy!
Thanks.
Um, you look really pretty, Miss!
Eh? Do I?
Yeah, you've got a perfect body!
I think so too! You look really great!
Oh my, you're flattering me!
No, no, that's not it!
Right! You're honestly really pretty!
Yeah, yeah! You look really great, just like a...
Right, just like...
Like a porn star!
Her right hand was definitely world-class.
I'm sure she'll become a champion.
I can even feel it in my bones.
Oh? Where have the two of you been?
Swollen faces.
What happened?
N-Nothing much! Right, Yuuji?
Yeah!
We just tripped, right, Akihisa?
Yuuji, let's get back to our swimming race!
Yeah! I won't lose this time!
We were finally about to succeed, but you went and ruined it!
No, it was your retarded comment that killed it!
You're playing innocent? What the hell?!
You want to fight it out?!
Enough, this won't get us anywhere.
You're right.
I was thinking,
maybe it's not working because we aren't sincere.
What?
It's possible we're unconsciously holding back because the girls aren't our type.
Good point. We can't fake true feelings.
Just kidding!
That's just a lame excuse.
What's the matter, Yuuji?
All right! Let's give it one last try!
Yeah, all right.
U-Um...!
Th-The thing is, we got lost.
Uh, we're looking for the b-beach. Do you know where—
Idiot! We're at the damn beach!
It just slipped out.
Her hair color changed?!
This is my real hair.
Sh-Shouko!
This is bad!
Huh?
Sorry, Akihisa.
Voyeur!
Why?!
They would've killed me if I refused.
D-Did they find out what we were doing?
Right arm, they said.
Right arm, eh? Sounds pretty painful.
I don't want to go back.
They said they'll break everything except the right arm!
Akihisa? Please don't move from there!
We have a full course of punishment ready; so prepare yourself, Aki!
I'm so sad that I'm losing my little brother!
Run, Akihisa! These three are seriously—
Akihisa, thanks for all the memories.
No!
Yuuji.
Yes, ma'am.
Kneel down.
What? But we're...
But we're in the sea.
Do I have to say it again?
Kneel down.
Question 2
Directions: Answer the following question.
What is a main component of seawater aside from water?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Salt (Sodium chloride)
Teacher Comments
Correct. As expected of you, Himeji.
Although seawater does contain many
other components such as magnesium,
the salt content is the highest at approximately 3.5 percent.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Teacher Comment
Next Episode
Question 2: What is the main component of seawater aside from water?
Tears of regret and repentance!
Tears of regret and repentance
What happened?
... What happened?
Next episode, “Me, Yukatas, and Festival Fun!”
Me, Yukata, and
Festival Fun!
This will be on your test.