Do you get it now? You're not not even close to my level.
It does seem that way.
Subarun, we may just win!
Geez! It's frustrating, frustrating, frustrating!
Cool, Hii! It's super fun!
Yeah! We may just win!
Tsubaki-chan! Hiiragi-chan!
This is something you two and only you two can do.
Something only...
we can do?
Well then. Here we go, everyone!
Yeah!
Geez! Don't move the ball so sluggishly.
Can't you pass it to me?
You know you're not gonna win without me.
Thank ya!
Let's do this!
I'm in perfect form today as well.
No one can stop me now!
You'll see how I'll stop you.
It's no use.
Not yet!
Another one?
But it's no use.
I'm still here!
Don't mess with me!
Suzuridani, number 13, charging.
How does the Twin Hell taste?
We're not afraid of you anymore!
Don't mess with me!
Seriously...
Hell yeah!
Nice, TsubaHii!
She's a beginner at basketball?!
Rena-san plays in a showy way: She's specialized in one-on-one play.
But this is a five-on-five mini basketball game,
so she can't play the way she wants.
It would be easy to destroy our strategy if they were all normal players.
But...
Man, don't get in my way!
Rena, I'm here!
Hurry up and pass.
You're annoying!
Suzuridani, number thirteen!
She's so confident in one-on-one play, that she won't pass no matter what.
I see. So she's the only one actually playing basketball now.
She gets lost as just one player among the other five.
We can't overlook that weak point of her.
Focus on!
Hey, everyone, you can stop now.
Please, Masami!
Eat it, Ashihara Rena, and choke on it.
Nice shot, Masami!
Well done!
Thanks.
But I'm not the one who should be told that.
What are you doing, Rena?
Why are you striking so freely?
Focus on!
Yeah, yeah. It got real boring.
Yeah, yeah. What's this crap you call basketball?
I win it all when I'm alone,
but it's real cramped when there are five people.
It's no fun at all.
How boring... Guess I'll go home.
You coward!
Aya, do you know who you're talking to?
To you, Rena.
Shaking off the fact that you decide whether we win or lose...
is being a coward!
Heh? You got all cheeky all of a sudden, huh?
Even though you've only just got into the basketball club.
That's right. I've entered the basketball club.
But you're not playing basketball at all, Rena.
Huh? I've been doing it for a while.
You haven't!
You're going forward creating a chance,
and letting the opponent shoot freely...
That's not real basketball!
That's because the rules are bad!
I'm not the one at fault!
Refrain from this talk here.
I'm giving a foul to the whole team.
Notice that we can win!
If you give us your support, that is.
Which one do you choose?
Winning thanks to you or losing because of you?
Well...
That's it. I won't let this talk to continue.
Suzuridani, number twelve and thirteen!
I have no choice but to let you face me.
I don't wanna be told that we lost because of me.
Okay. If you can...
Un!
I won't let you!
Deux!
You're still not there!
Trois!
You still didn't shoot!
You're awesome, Mimi!
What was that?
You did it!
It's a bit of a bad feeling.
I'm gonna stop you again!
Th-That technique?
Even though she's only seen it once?
That's amazing!
That's a real difference!
Piece of cake!
I'm still here!
Don't you think you can do it twice!
We're no match for you on a one-on-one,
but we we aren't going to lose as a team!
Yeah.
I can't win... alone.
Rena!
Got it!
Rena! Here we go!
Rena! Run! Jump!
Please!
No way!
Man... If I miss this...
it'll be so embarrassing I'll die.
Are you kidding me?!
T-That hoop..!
I'd never thought I'd see it in a mini basketball game.
Nice shot, Rena!
Good job, everyone!
You were the best!
The five sixth graders will go out on the third quarter.
However, we might make some substitutes, depending on how things progress.
So, fifth graders, don't take your spirits down until the end, either.
Okay!
I didn't think this would be how it ends up.
Me neither.
I won't ever ask you for anything, but please let me go out on the third quarter, too.
There's something that came to mind.
I think basketball...
Basketball with five players may be fun.
So, please!
Why not?
We have no complaints.
That's the view of the sixth graders' team on it.
We need all five people for winning against Keishin today.
We'll let you know what the true basketball we all fight in is like.
Well then. The players going out next are:
Miyu, Rena, Kumi, Ran and...
Aya.
The trump card against Airi-chan in the third quarter is you, Aya!
Do your best!
I-I will fight against Airi-san...
Mii-senpai!
They need two players to block Airi.
Now it's my time to shine!
You're the ace?
Then I'm not gonna let you past me no matter what!
So fast!
I'll take care of that girl.
But...
First try stopping that number five.
Then we can talk.
Hell yeah!
Here I come!
Why is it me who has to do this?
Hell yeah!
I won't let you go through!
Then I'm going this way!
...At least for pretense. This way!
Hell yeah!
Awesome!
Oh~, you've succeeded!
Yay!
Oh~!
Well then! Let's do it again!
She's annoying. Her whole aura is annoying.
Here I go.
You!
Suzuridani, number thirteen!
My leg!
Maho!
Maho-chan!
Seems like you're suffering from a cramp in your leg.
You need to rest for a while.
You can't go back anytime soon.
This is nothing. I'll be fine.
You can't go, Maho!
I'm substituting you with Kagetsu-chan.
Subarun!
You need to rest now.
Hatano-sensei, please take care of her.
All right.
I won't let you!
Nice, Kage!
She's worrying about the fouls she's got.
One more and she's out.
Even if she didn't get them, she'd probably still be unable to stop them.
Everyone concentrate! Let's go deal the final blow.
Yeah!
Mokkan!
Saki, here!
Tomo!
Nice shot! Just what I'd expect from you!
Let's try our hardest for Maho, too!
Yeah!
I'm not gonna lose! I've been practicing forever...
just so I can beat you!
I'm not gonna lose!
How's that?
What a strike!
Who would have thought she'd shoot from that edge?
I've also been practicing forever...
just so I can beat you.
I will win.
Just wait.
Here it ends!
I'm not going to let you stop me now!
This is the precious shot of me and Subaru-san.
Do it, Tomoka!
A scoop shot?!
Those two are amazing! Are they really grade schoolers?
You've got a balanced game when two aces face off.
But what a drag... They're weighed down by about how much Maho would help.
Gettan, she's coming!
I'm sorry! My leg was putting me off.
Don't worry about it, Kagetsu-chan.
Nice fight!
I'm feeling all right again.
Don't overdo it!
I'm not overdoing it. It doesn't hurt anymore.
So it should be all right, no?
Maho...
Do you distrust everyone that much?
The ten of us are fighting real hard!
We'll do the part you'd be doing.
So believe
in us...
your teammates!
Silly... do you have something to say?
I'd never thought TsubaHii would say to me something like this...
What?!
Thank you.
All right. Whether you like it or not, there are six minutes left.
Go for the win with all your might.
Subaru-san, we can still win, right?
There's still hope, right?
Of course! You can do it!
Okay!
Go! Go! Keishin!
They're finally one!
Yeah.
They're one splendid team now.
She's short!
Let's calm down and do it step by step.
Mimi!
I did it, Master!
There's not much time left!
Hang in there, Airi!
I did it!
Man, we're losing again?
You're in the way!
So are you!
The shot went in.
Only two minutes left. The showdown starts now.
Masami!
All right!
Don't you give up!!
That's right! Don't give up!
Subarun never taught us that.
That's right! Subaru-sun has taught us a lot!
Like how difficult and intense basketball s, and the spirit for it.
But Onii-chan...
never told us to give up.
We gotta win no matter what!
39-39, we shall conduct an extension.
Amazing! Everyone's so incredible!
Not just their skills, their mindset has improved as well!
Grade schoolers truly are the best!
An extension with Suzuridani...
Do your best, Tomoka!
I'll do my best!
Um, Subaru-san!
When the game ends, would you...
N-Nevermind!
Please do a good job from now on as well.
All right. Let's do our best.
As Long as You're by my Side
Next time
Yeah!