Y'all niggas get it now? You ain't got nothin' on me
Sheit, we're so far fucked
Charles, we gon' win?!
Oh-oh shit! I'm Menstruating! Menstruating! Menstruating!
Cool, Wilt! It's super fun!
Yeah! Mebbe we'll win for once!
Wilt!! Larry Bird!
I got a little plan for you nigs
A plan...
for us nigs?
Aight, here we go !
Yeah!
Geez! Don't move the ball so sluggishly.
Yo! Pass it here!
You know you're not gonna win without me.
Thank ya!
Let's do this!
I'm in da zone today, too
Ain't bein stopped by no one
I'm going to stop you.
No
Not done yet!
Another one?
But it's no use.
Look at me!
Don't be messin!
Michal Vick, number 7, Illegal dog fighting
Go back to prison!
You shouldn't be allowed back on the court!
I'm innocent!
Seriously...
Hell yeah!
Nice, u 2!
She's a beginner at basketball?!
She's not really that good, like the Harlem Globetrotters
She just dicks around and makes
cool spins and shit
In practical skill she's kind of shitty
But...
Man, don't get in my way!
Hey, I'm wide open!
Fucking pass the ball!
You're annoying!
Michael Vick, number thirteen, again with the dogs!
Really, though, she's good and all but she's got to stop the dog fighting!
But then again, she does come from the South
All the niggers down there into sick things
We can't overlook that weak point of her.
Focus on!
Hey, everyone, you can stop now.
Please, Tony!
Eat a dick, Vick.    And then choke on it
Nice shot, Tony Parker!
Well done!
Thanks you, thanks you.
But I ain't the one who should be told that.
What the shit are you doing, Vick?
Why are you striking so freely?
Focus on!
I'm bored and I want to go home
Yeah, yeah. What's this crap you call basketball?
I'm too good for you guys,
next season I'm transferring out to Chicago
So the Bears Can win da Superb Owl
fuck this, I'm going now
You coward!
Eli, do you even own a superbowl ring
Actually I do, lol
But can you even throw for an 80 yard TD?
with 5 seconds left?
Heh? You got all cheeky all of a sudden, huh?
Even though you've only just got into the basketball club.
That's right. I've entered the basketball club.
But you're not playing basketball at all, Vick
Huh? I've been doing it for a while.
You haven't!
You're going forward creating a chance,
and letting the opponent shoot freely...
That's not real basketball!
Yeah, well I don't like the rules!
Nigga, what?
Excuse me, can we pls play ape-hoop again?
I'm giving a foul to da whole team.
We can win dis!
Yeah, we ain't losin to those nerds
Which one are you choose?
Playing for us or da Bears?
Well...
Come on you two, we all know the bears won't win da superbowl
Mike and Eli, numbers 7 and 10, Yellow Card
I aint got no choice but 2 let you face me.
I'm not losin cause of you
Okay. If you can...
Uno!
Oh no you don't
Dos!
You damn wetback!
Tres!
You aliens will be the end o me!
You're awesome, Yao Ming!
What was that?
You did it!
Hell yeah, motherfucker!
I gonna stop you again!
Aww shit
We only seen this once b4
Damn nigga!
She got skills!
Piece of cake!
I'm still here!
Don't you think you can do it twice!
We're no match for you on a 1v1
but we we aren't gonna lose as a team!
Yeah.
I can't win... alone.
Mike!
Got it!
Mike! Lateral pass!
Mike! Right hook! Jab!
Please!
No way!
Man... If I miss dis...
it'll be so embarrassing I'll die.
Are you kidding me?!
T-That ape-hoop..!
I ain't never thought I done see this in a mini basketball game.
Nice shot, Mike!
Good job, everyone!
You were the best!
The five sixth graders will go out on the third quarter.
We might double up on a Tight End and go for a triple play, ok?
So you guys just sit in the dunes and try and get a hole in one.
Okay!
I didn't think this would be how it ends up.
Me neither.
I won't ever ask you for anything, but please let me go out on the third quarter, too.
There's something that came to mind.
I think basketball...
Is for fucking niggers, holy shit
So, please!
Why not?
She's all cool to us
I say just put the bitch in and have a go
We gonna need all five people for winning against LeBron's Ballin' Academy today.
We'll let you know what the true basketball we all fight in is like.
Well then. The players going out next are:
Ray Lewis, Mike Vick, Drew Brees, Pondurrr and...
Eli Manning!
The trump card against Kareem in the third quarter is you, Eli!
Do your best!
Aw man this sucks, I wanna go home
!!!!!!!!!
They need two players to block Kareem
Now's my Tiem 2 shine!
You're the ace?
Then I'm not gonna let you past me no matter what!
So fast!
I'll take care of that girl.
Butt...
First just try stopping that number five.
Then we can talk, scrub
Hell yeah!
Here I come!
Why is it always me who has to do this?
Hell yeah!
I won't let you go through!
Then I'm going this way!
...At least for pretense. This way!
Hell yeah!
Awesome!
Oh~, you've succeeded!
Yay!
Oh~!
Well then! Let's do it again!
She's annoying. Her whole aura is annoying.
Here I go.
You!
Mike Vick! Number 7
MY LEG
Dirk!
DIRK!
I'm no doctor, but I think you're pregnant.
I can smell the fetus being created before marriage
You can't go back anytime soon.
This is nothing, I'll just cut it out
You can't go, Dirk!
I'm substituting you with Tony Parker!
HeyYy!
You need to rest now.
Jerry Sandusky, please take good care of her.
All right.
I won't let you!
Nice, Tony!
She's worrying about the strikes she's got.
Three strikes and you're out!
Even if she didn't get them, she'd probably still be unable to stop them.
Everyone concentrate! Let's go deal the final blow.
Yeah!
Kobe!
Chris, here!
Nice shot! Juss what I expect from you!
Let's try our hardest for Dirk, too!
Yeah!
I'm not gonna lose! I've been practicing forever...
Just so I can beat you!
I'm not gonna lose!
How's that?
That's not even legal!
She's like a real life Dwayne Wade!
I've also been practicing forever...
just so I can beat you.
I will win.
Just wait.
I'ma end this!
You ain't stopping me!
This is the precious shot of me and Charles Barkley-san!
Do it, Kobe!
A scoop shot?!
Those two are amazing! Are they really grade schoolers?
You've got a balanced game when two aces face off.
But what a drag... They're weighed down by all that cock
Tony! She's comin' in hot!
I'm sorry! My leg was putting me off.
S'all good, Tony!
Nice fight!
I'm feeling all right again.
Don't overdo it!
I'm not overdoing it. It doesn't hurt anymore.
So it should be alrght, amirite?
Dirk...
Do you even hamstring injury?
Just let us carry the team
We're OP anyways
So believe
in us...
your teammates!
Silly... do you have something to say?
I'd never thought y'all would say to me something like this...
What?!
Thanks ya
All right. Whether ya like it or not, thers six minutes left.
Just go out there and try to touch the ball
Yo, we can still win....riiight?
There's still hope, riiiight?
Nope! You're probs gonna lose
Okay!
Go! Go! LeBron's!
They're finally a team!
Yeah.
They're pretty good, I guess
Midget alert!
Let's calm down and do it step by step.
Yao!
I did it, Mastah!
There's not much time left!
Hang in there, Kareem!!!
I did it!
Man, why're we always losing?
You're in the way!
So are you!
The ball went in!
Only two minutes left. The showdown starts now.
Dwight!
All right!
Don't you evar give up!!!!
That's right! Don't give up!
I really hope we win this
If we don't, I'd probably kill myself
Man my feet hurt, I want to go home
Mike Vick's always guarding me
I don't like Mike
We gotta win no matter what!
Oh~
39-39, we shall conduct an extension.
Amazing! Wow! All that skill!
Not just their skills, their mindset has improved as well!
Grade schoolers truly are the best!
An extension with Eminem's School of Hoops
Do your best, Kobe!
I'll do my best!
Um, Charles...
When the game ends, would you...
sfx: *Fart*
All right. Let's do our best.
As Long as You're by my Side
Next time
Yeah!