Rider?
What the hell?
What do you think you're doing
breaking the shutter open like that?
Why didn't you go through in
spirit form like when you entered?
I cannot carry these things while I am in my spirit form.
And don't whine so much.
You sound like you're some kind
of common thief or street urchin.
Well, if you aren't a thief, then what the hell are you?
Something entirely different.
A cowardly thief sneaks away in the night full of fear.
If you stride away bursting with song proudly,
then what you are is a conquering king!
Just what I needed... now get out of here!
Get lost... get lost now!
Very well... then I shall leave you to carry the spoils.
Try not to drop them.
Oh, man, why is this happening to me?
I... I don't get it.
The summoning worked, so why do I have to do all of this?
What's so important about these books, anyway?
It's important because we are preparing for war.
And one cannot wage war without having proper maps.
Hey, boy, where are Macedonia and Persia?
You can't talk to me like that!
I'm your master...
I am well aware of my status as
servant and yours as my master.
After all, we forged a pact, did we not?
Mhm.
But I'm interested in learning where
all my old territories are located.
I think they're here.
Hmm.
I spent my life conquering that
land, and look how puny it is!
Very well.
I can't wait to get started!
All right, then.
Where exactly on this map are we sitting right now, boy?
Here.
So, the other side of the round land.
Hmm.
Good news indeed.
This will guide us well in the coming battles.
Guide us well?
First, to the other side of the world,
due west, and we go as fast as we can.
And we shall conquer every land that we pass through!
I shall return to Macedonia in triumph,
and my people will hold a festival
in honor of my great revival!
Now how splendid will that be?
Why do you think you're here, anyway?
You didn't forget the Grail War, did you?
Hmm, that's right.
Speaking of the Grail, I have
neglected to ask one small thing.
What will you do with the Grail once you possess it?
Why... what's it to you what I do?
I mean, what do you care?
If you are also intent on world conquest,
then that would make you my enemy,
because the world cannot serve two lords.
Wha...
No, I don't want that!
Look, I'll tell you what I really want, okay?
I just want people to treat me fairly.
I wanna make all those idiots back at the clock
tower who never even bothered to give me a chance
to admit to me that they were wrong!
Small!
Small.
And narrow‐minded and stupid!
You mean to tell me that in this battle, your
only concern is for your ridiculous reputation?
And you dare call yourself my master?
What a terrible disappointment you are.
If you wish so desperately for
others to fear and respect you...
...perhaps you should try using the Holy Grail's power
to grow another 30 centimeters
and add a little bit of muscle.
He's supposed to be my servant!
He can't talk to me that way!
I'll show him!
I address the command seal.
In accordance with the Grail's laws,
I order this man, Iskander the Conqueror...
Calm down, Waver.
A master can only use his command seal to
compel his servant's obedience three times
and that's all.
If I use all my command seals, I won't be
able to control him when I really need to.
As long as I get the Holy Grail, it doesn't matter.
I really don't give a damn what you do after that, so...
Enough, boy!
I shall acquire the Grail for you as you wish.
Yeah, well, you seem awfully confident about that.
Do you have any idea how you're gonna do it?
So you wish to see my power... is
that what you're trying to tell me?
Well, of course I do!
You need to prove to me that I can
rely on you no matter what the situation!
I am Iskander, King of Conquerors! With
the swing of my sword, I declare my supremacy!
This is the ox chariot that King
Gordius once offered up to Zeus.
Its renowned reputation must be the source
of my designation as a rider class servant.
If you want the Grail, then find me another hero or two...
someone worthy for me to fight!
Until then, I shall entertain myself by
sitting here and looking at these maps.
That will not pose a problem, will it?
All right!
I'm not gonna lose today... you just watch!
Ah, I found one.
No way... where is it?
Oh, gee, I'm sure I didn't overlook it!
That's the very first chestnut bud today!
First point to me.
I'm not gonna lose!
Oh, there's one!
Right here!
Ahhh.
You see... I found one too!
I found my second over here.
Huh?
Hey, that isn't a chestnut branch.
It's kind of, Ilya.
That branch is actually from a tree called a wingnut.
It's almost like a chestnut,
so as far as I'm concerned, it's a chestnut bud.
Huh?
That's no fair!
No fair, no fair, no fair!
The whole time we've been playing, you've been cheating!
Yes, but your daddy can't win
this game against you otherwise!
If you keep on cheating like you've been
doing, I won't play this game with you ever again!
I don't want that!
I'm sorry, Ilya, I apologize.
Do you promise not to cheat like that anymore?
Yes, I do.
Okay then.
I challenge you to one more round.
A true champion accepts all challengers!
Indeed, I'm very honored, your highness.
Wow, I'm so high up!
What's got your attention out there, Saber?
It's interesting.
Your daughter and Kiritsugu are playing outside.
Are you surprised?
I was under the impression that my master
had a colder heart than he's showing now.
Well, I can see why you might think that.
If that really is Kiritsugu's true self,
then I am afraid I must've gravely
offended him when we first met.
Irisviel, you really don't have to laugh at me.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering if you're still concerned
with our reaction when you were summoned?
Yes, somewhat.
True, I did pretend to be a man during my original life.
But surely there was no need for you
two to be so shocked when you saw me.
I'm so sorry, but we just couldn't help it!
Your legend... I mean, King Arthur's legend
is extremely famous.
Well, if that's the case,
do you think he might underestimate my ability
simply because I am a woman?
No, never.
Not at all.
Then again, if he's upset as you think he is,
I'm certain that there's another reason.
Such as?
He's probably upset at all the
people who were around you at the time.
The selfish ones, the ones
cruel enough and uncaring enough
to force the role of King upon an innocent little girl.
It was inevitable that would happen.
I had resigned myself to that fate
when I drew forth the sword from the stone.
I believe that that upsets him
even more than anything else,
your resignation to your fate.
Well, then he forgets his place.
He hasn't the right to question
decisions made by those of my time,
including those decisions I made myself.
That's why he says nothing about it to you.
I'm afraid that Kiritsugu Emiya,
and the hero Arturia will never get along with each other.
He must've resigned himself to that fact.
He wants to use the Holy Grail's power to save the world.
That is his ambition and yours, correct?
Yes, but you must understand that
I get my beliefs directly from him.
My own desire for the Grail is exactly the same.
It is my fervent wish to save Britain
since I could not protect it in life.
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is
right and just, something to be proud of.
Our next match won't happen until you
come back from your trip to Japan, will it?
That's right.
How long do you think your work
will keep you and Mommy away from home?
When will you come back?
I should be back here in two weeks or so.
Your mom won't be back for quite a while, though.
Yeah, Mommy told me about that already.
She said we'd be apart for a long time.
She also told me that even if we don't
see each other for a long, long time,
she'll always be right here by my side,
so I shouldn't ever feel lonely.
She told me that before I went to sleep.
I'm gonna be together with Mommy,
well, forever and ever and ever!
I see.
Listen, Ilya.
Daddy?
Can you wait for me, Ilya?
Even if you're lonely, can you last till I come home?
Mhm!
Good, then I promise you I'll be home
before you know it.
Fill, fill.
Fill her up, fill.
Repeat four times.
Or was it five times?
Um, and then I have to destroy it each time it's filled.
Wait, is that right?
All right, now, fill and fill and fill and fill and fill.
Okay, that's five times.
Right!
At all three murder scenes,
officials tell us a mysterious pentagram
was found drawn in the victim's blood. Police speculate...
Do you think that maybe I went a little bit too far?
Hey, do you believe in terrible demons, kiddo?
All the newspapers and magazines right now
are saying I'm some kind of terrible demon.
But suppose demons like that
really did exist in the world.
I mean, wouldn't that be awfully rude to them?
You've gotta be pretty clear about these things.
Yo, I am Ryunosuke Uryu, and I am a demon!
Ah‐ha, I don't know if that's
the right way to go about it.
But look, I found this little baby!
It's some dusty old book from
deep inside our big storehouse.
Looks like some of my ancestors were doing a
bunch of research on how to go about summoning demons!
So, like, I've just gotta find
out if there really are demons!
Understand?
But you know, if a demon really did appear,
it would be pretty stupid of me
to just chat with it for a while
and then just send it back to
whatever pit of Hell it came from.
So, kid, if a demon does show up around here,
would you mind letting it kill ya?
I wonder what it's like being killed by a demon!
How many people get to find out?
Wait a minute, what's that?
I'll ask you, you who calls to me,
oh, summoner who manifests me
within the vessel of a caster,
I ask you your name.
Who?
Who art thou?
Um, uh, well, I'm Ryunosuke Uryu,
and I'm currently working odd jobs.
My hobby is murder of all varieties.
I really like kids and sometimes young women.
Very well, the pact is now officially sealed.
It's my irresistible desire to
possess the Holy Grail exactly as you do.
The sacred vessel of paradise, the cup
of awesome and terrible power will be ours!
The Holy... what?
Anyway, how would you like a little
snack just to kick things off right?
Here, wanna eat this kid?
Wow, that's human skin, isn't it?
Don't be frightened, little boy.
You'll be fine.
Can you stand?
All right, now, little boy.
You can leave the room through that door right over there.
You think you can manage that?
Hey, what are you doing?
Shh.
Terror has its degrees of freshness.
The more intense the fear,
the more all of the other emotions die.
Terror, in its truest sense, is not a
static state, but rather a dynamic one.
It is the sublime moment when
shining hope turns to utter despair.
Did you enjoy that?
The tantalizing flavor of fresh terror and bloody death?
Cool!
You are awesome!
You are the coolest thing ever!
Okay, look, I don't know anything about this
Grail crap, but from this moment on, I am with you.
Let's go kill!
I want you to take me out and show me
even cooler ways to torture and kill!
Ah... the name is Ryunosuke, correct?
What a magnificent omen to be blessed with
such an understanding master like yourself.
I feel my darkest dream is nearly within my grasp.
Oh, hey, I didn't get your name.
What is it?
You wish to know my name.
Let me see now, in this era, the
most common name for me would be, uh...
perhaps for now I'll just call myself Bluebeard.
The church contacted me.
They said that the seventh servant,
a caster has finally appeared.
The final servant has been summoned?
Then it's time.
Indeed.
You are to leave here now, and
head immediately to Tohsaka Manor.
And once I arrive?
The Manor is surrounded by a
number of powerful magical barriers,
but they should be child's play for you.
Are you sure about this?
I was under the impression that
you were allies with Tokiomi Tohsaka.
Don't you worry about that.
Even if it means you have to engage
Archer in battle, there's no need to fear.
No need to fear Archer, one of the three
great Knight classes of the Grail Wars?
I leave the rest to you.
Eliminate Tokiomi Tohsaka at once.
This will be easy.
You are nothing but a slimy worm. Who
gave you permission to look up at me?
No need... to fear that, he says?
You are not worthy to gaze upon me.
A filthy worm like you should face the
ground, crawl on your stomach, and die.
At last, it's time for the fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
It's unspeakably ugly.
The item I left you, where is it?
This will be fun!
Welcome!
Grant me victory in this fight!
I will, without fail.