Loitering out so late as a group...
It seems... I will need to punish you.
What is this about, Kanade?
Hey, what's going on here?
Hasn't Tenshi become harmless?
No.  That's not Kanade.
Kanade would never point a sword at us.
Goddamn it!
Yurippe!  What do you need us to do?!
Everyone, surround her and fire as one!
Huh?  Why are you commanding us?
At this point it doesn't even matter if she uses Distortion!
Right!
You got it!
Step away, Yuri!
Fire!
Damn it!
Is Kanade all right?
She's pretty deeply wounded, isn't she?
She's the same as us.
Even if it was fatal, she'll heal eventually.
What does it mean for there to be two of the same person running around?
Has this world turned out to be some kinda screwed-up place?
There is a cause.
What is it?
Remember our Tenshi Domain Infiltration Mission?
Yeah.
On her machine there was a program that creates skills, remember?
In it were several skills that we haven't seen before.
One of those, Harmonics, is what she used.
"Harmonics"?  What kind of skill is that?
Were you not looking at the screen?  It's a skill where her body becomes two.
In other words, cloning.
"Cloning"?!
In other words, it's another skill that Tenshi created herself using the software.
Still, I wouldn't say they were just alike.
Unlike this one here, she was aggressive.  Why is that?
Kanade only uses skills to protect herself.  Even her sword is made that way!
She uses it to deflect bullets.
Honestly, you all are a group of blockheads.
Excluding you, of course, Otonashi-san.
Fundamentally, we're a group of dumbasses.
Allow me to reveal one possibility.
What if the clone had been created during a time when great offensive instincts were in effect?
You mean that moment?
I see.  So she's acting out her master's sentiments from that moment.
But Kanade would never become overwhelmed with such offensive instincts.
Not that it really matters, but you really stand up for her, don't you?
Well, don't you feel bad for her?
Look, whatever.
So, what's the problem that we're really facing?
Should it be how to fight against Tenshi's clone?
You idiot!  It's about how to eliminate her.
What did you say?
But if she willingly created her,
What's that?!  Let go of me!
shouldn't she be able to willingly eliminate her?
Shouldn't we just wait for her to wake up?
Hold on.
If she were capable of eliminating her willingly, would she be here right now in bed?
I'm thinking it was an unconscious summoning.
That's why she couldn't eliminate her.
It's also why she had to stop her like that, even if it ended up as a double kill.
Hey, hey, hold on a sec.
If she can't be eliminated, that means this world's gonna be stuck with her, doesn't it?
She's overlooking us right now.
But starting tomorrow, she could pick a bloody fight against anyone who acts against the role model ideals.
Even though she's not the Student Council President anymore?
Yes.  Her goal in disciplining us has been taken over by this copy.
And she's entirely aggressive on top of that.
Just what we need.
There's not enough time even if we wanted to put up a fight.
Buy me some time.
How do we make that time?
Attend your classes, and pretend you're listening.
Don't listen to a word the teacher says.
If you take the class seriously, you'll be obliterated.
Obsess yourself with something else and make sure the clone doesn't catch you doing it.
Last through the day like that.
I look forward to seeing you all again, without anyone missing.
Sheesh.  Yes, yes, I know you split.
But is there a way to get rid of the other one?
Angel Player?
It's the manual for the software.
Damn it.  It's so thick, and everything is in English.
Like I need this under such time constraints...
Let's see...
Oh, it came up.
This must be the distance.
Not what I need.
What is this?
All right!  This is it!
It was supposed to follow this command and disappear.
Then what's the condition for the command?
Ugh, I can't figure this out.
Should I just break the PC?
You dumbass.  That's not going to eliminate the clone.
Oh, fine!  I'll just rewrite it with a program that I know!
Disappear already!  Time Wait set for 10 seconds!
Go!
Ten seconds is pretty long if you're actually waiting for it to pass.
Why can't it be set at less than 10?
All right, I think that does it.
What's this?
There's more than before?
"Howling"?
Did the clone create these?
Should I erase them?
No, I've snuck into the program, so I need to limit myself to minimal editing.
There we go.
Now, if she uses Harmonics again,
Absorb will automatically kick in and the clone will return to the host body.
Damn it...
Maybe she went out for a walk!
No, that's unlikely.
Kanade promised that she'd stay with us.
You two made such a promise?
Y-Yeah.
The way things look, I can only imagine that she was abducted.
What did you do?
"Do"?  Nothing more than rewrite the program.
If she uses the same skill, the program I added in will activate and the clone should return to the host.
Such a thing is possible?
It's only a temporary measure.
But she took action much quicker than I anticipated.
I can't do anything if the clone hides her.
What are we going to do?
Search for her, obviously.
While avoiding the looming threat of that evil Tenshi?
It's a pain enough pretending to listen to the lecture.
I wonder how long the diversion will last.
Huh, "diversion"?   You mean me?
What did you join GDM for?
Because I wanted to be like Iwasawa-san.
But GDM exists as our diversion.
No way!  We can't perform a diversion against such a scary person!
You will!
Who do you think you are?!
I'm an upperclassman!  Do you have a problem with that?!
Oh, so you're an upperclassman!  I'm so sorry!
Um, I may wet myself during the performance, but I'll do my best!
Thank you for your determination, but it isn't needed yet.
To start off, let's do what we can.
Everyone!  Gather information about Tenshi sightings.
Hey yo, check this out.
It's the moonwalk. It's the moonwalk.
It's a head spin.
Based on the information we've gathered, there's a high possibility that she's confined at the Guild.
So we'll head to the deepest recess.
That place that was totally detonated?
Yes.  The place furthest from here,
where all the traps along the way are still functioning.  The most dangerous place.
We're descending down there again?
Last time, we pretty much got annihilated.
What's there to fear?
You were the first to die...
I will continue to sing for everyone's sake, even if I wet myself.
I'll show you what I'm made of!
Any diversion would be killed by her in an instant.
We won't have any diversion this time.
We'll go in fair and square.
So we'll be fighting Tenshi as we go along, this time.
Yes.
Listen up.  Our mission is to make it to the deepest recess of the Guild and rescue the original Tenshi.
Operation, start!
Looks like all the old traps were left as they were.  Lucky.
Um, if we meet Tenshi at a place like this, I think I'll wet myself anyways.
No one cares.
Please do care!
Go ahead.
At least try to stop me!
Here she is.
Fire!
Damn, she's fast!
We still have handguns!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Fire!
We may settle this faster than anticipated.
Wh...at?
What's going on?!
That the original?
No, she's a clone, too!
Why is there another one?!
Basically, our enemy is multiplying.
On another note, he was the first to die again.
Damn it all...  Fire!
What about the one behind us?!
We don't have the time to worry about her!
We need to focus on what's in front of us!
You look busy.
Yurippe, we're running out of ammo!
There's no way to win this.
We'll close off the doorway.
Follow me!
Let's go!
Yuri!
Ten more seconds!
Those that don't make it in time will have to be left behind!
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one...
Zero!
There were two aggressive Tenshi...
This is worse than our last Parachute Mission.
Why is there a second one?
The clones can use Hand Sonic and Distortion as well, so it makes sense that she could use Harmonics.
Honestly, you guys are really lacking in the brain department.
Excluding you, of course, Otonashi-san.
Allow me to summarize the key issues for you all.
Please do.
There are two problems.
First, how many clones are there?
If a clone can create more clones, then there is no limit to the number.
So forget just two, you're saying there could be ten or twenty of them?
But wait, Yuri added a skill.  Shouldn't the clones be returning to the original host?
Shouldn't we just wait for them to disappear?
That is the second problem.
What if the clones were mass-produced before that ability was added?
Then, you mean...!
So you've finally noticed, you lowlifes.
Oh, but you're noble of course, Otonashi-san.
Listen up.  What if she anticipated us marching in here,
and stationed her mass-produced clones on the way to the Guild?
That'd be a...
Trap...
Exactly.  A trap.
We already have two on our backs.
They won't disappear, so you guys have no chance of winning.
And I'm sure there'll be many waiting for us up ahead.
So we've been trapped...
We can't even replenish our weapons.
So we're just gonna wait here to get killed?
What does she want to achieve by doing all this?
Ultimately, I imagine she wants perfect obedience.
That's her mission, after all.
So we have no choice but to go and get obliterated?
What a great way to get rid of us all at once.
Let's move on.
There's another one.
A third one...
It's a waste of bullets.
What are you going to do?
Matsushita Fifth!
Go!  Go while I'm still conscious!
Don't say things that make it sound like you were only being a good guy at the end!
Hurry up!  We need to get going, now!
Yeah.
Hang in there, Matsushita Fifth!
I leave the rest to you, everyone...
I won't let Matsushita-kun's death be in vain.
But he has proven that his method is the best way to move on.
Tenshi is small, so that's the best way to stop her from moving around.
No matter how strong Tenshi is, a judo lock will work.
It's time to utilize the judo we've learned from Matsushita-kun.
In other words, we can get by with one victim per Tenshi.
"Get by with one victim"...
And if we save the original, we can save all the victims.
Let's hurry.
There's the fourth one.
It's my turn.
Good chance and luck.
T.K.!
Hey!  Why is this turning out like the final chapter of a shounen manga?!
Never mind that.  Move out!
To show off my body... this is the moment!
Takamatsu!
I can't chicken out.
Fujimaki!
How unwise.
How unwise!
Shiina!
Just now, you've come to a sudden realization.
You're a clown.
And you see?  There's a girl in that dark corner with lonely eyes.
Oh no, you're right!
I'll make you smile—
Ooyama!
You're horrible, you know that?
You've got it all wrong, Otonashi-san.
Please listen to me, it was just some playful words.
I'll be sure to go next.
Hey, someone say something for him.
But I don't even know his name.
Let's go.
Just how many is this?
I don't know.  I quit counting already.
This time, I'll be going.
Hold on!  I'm up before you.
You stay on your feet until the last.
Why?
She's waiting for you.
I just know she is.
That's why you have to go on.
Okay?  Also, if—
If you're gonna go, get going already!
Wait for me, Senpai.
Do you like him or do you hate him?
Here we are.
Ground Zero of the Guild.
We'll be going all the way down to the deepest recess from here.
Otonashi-kun and Yui, you two look for the original.
As soon as you find her, tell her to use Harmonics.
I should be the one doing the fighting.
Don't you remember what Hinata-kun said?
She's waiting for you.
In that case, I'll fight.
You're so weak, you're out of the question.
Take me into consideration, please!
All right, let's go.
No, see, I'm actually really strong.
I hope this will be our last operation.
Yeah.
Please wait!
Huh?  Where's Yui?
I heard a very short scream from her.
Did she fall to Tenshi's hand?
Poor thing.  But we'll save her soon.
So, yet again, only we survived to the end.
Yeah.  Just like last time.
Is this the last one, I wonder?
I sure hope so.
Hey, now.  Stop standing there and search for the original.
R-Right!
Figures.
Damn, she's tough.
Plug your ears!
Guard Skill: Howling.
What is this?!
My ears!
You weren't... knocked out?
Oh, what's that?  What did you say?  I have plugs in my ears, so I can't hear you very well.
Give it up.
If you prefer, I'll slit your throat with my other knife.
There she is!
Kanade!
Are you all right?
Yes.
The Battlefront's here to save you with everything we've got.
I see.
Oh, right.  Kanade, I'm sorry to ask when you're so worn out, but I need you to use one of your skills.
Harmonics.
If you use it, everyone will be saved.
I see, okay.
Will you last even if you use it?
Yes, if it's just once.
Guard Skill: Harmonics.
It seems you rewrote the program.
Yeah.  They'll all return to her.
So that many ruthless mes will combine?
What do you mean?
The clones have their own mind.
It's not that they will disappear.  They'll simply fuse as part of her.
The many mes that attacked all of you will fuse back into her.
And do you really think nothing will happen to her after suddenly fusing so many of such like-minds?
It's time.
Wait!
Shit...
Please hang in there...
Kanade!
What will happen to us?
We've never seen Tenshi like that before.
But that was only a temporary measure.
I'd say we have a 1% chance.
Do you intend to undress me?
What the hell is this...?
Someone punch him!
Let's all survive through this!
No one's going to live through this!
Am I going to be obliterated?
Whose side will God take?
Come back!
Otonashi...
I remember everything now.