Kumagorou returned in the morning
and knocked on the old woman's door.
Knock knock. Knock knock.
"Who is it? Do you bring news of my husband's death?"
"Oh please, your husband bit the dust 30 years ago!
"It's me, Kumagorou the Fool!"
"Ah, Kumagorou. What business do you have with this old woman?"
"Skip the formalities."
"It should be impossible for someone my age,"
"but I was able to make my own delicacy!"
"Oh, that's wonderful!
"Being able to make a delicacy shows how much you've learned!"
"So, how was it?"
"I handed him the package, asked for his seal stamp,"
"and told him if he doesn't have it on hand, he could sign for it instead."
"You fool."
"That's not a delicacy, that's a delivery."
Thank you kindly for your attention.
AAAAA
Tetora
Hiraite
Thank you for letting me take the stage before you.
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
You should just read this manga as is.
Why would anyone want to make an anime adaption?
What's wrong with you?!
Why would you say that?!
This is a dialogue-heavy piece with hardly any action.
Not to mention most of it takes place in a dressing room.
So why would anyone turn a manga like this into an anime?
Well, now that you put it that way... You have a point.
AAAAAA
I'm looking for
this kitten
...said Gan.
What?
AAAAAA
I'm looking for
this kitten
Stop that! They're working so hard to animate us even though there's so little to animate!
Yeah, Gan. You shouldn't write off this project just yet.
I haven't even said anything!
Not to mention you all agreed as well!
In the event we get an anime, please leave Gan unanimated.
Hey!
Well, at least we'll have more viewers than we do readers.
Though most of them will be watching it for free.
A shopper who doesn't buy anything is just a window shopper.
But thinking about all those people watching makes me nervous!
Don't be stupid. Just act normally.
This anime is full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully enjoy how cute the girls are.
A
Normal Dialogue
But it's hard to act "normally" when you're told to.
What do you normally do?
Don't ask stupid questions!
I shop...
I read books and surf the web...
I sleep...
Does that even count?
I guess so.
I mean, sleeping is pretty important.
I usually eat and drink too.
Yeah, of course.
I breathe.
I envy others and desire things...
Yeah, of cours— No!
Be a bit more optimistic.
I live.
If you ask us what we normally do, we live.
That's too broad!
But it basically comes down to
eating, sleeping, and...
And talking. Right?
Huh? But we do talk.
Eat, sleep, and tal—
Hey girls, what do you normally eat?
Don't ask stupid questions!
But if we talk about normal stuff, it may end up normal as well.
I guess I normally eat beef bowls.
Which brand do you like best?
Let's not go into which one we like.
It'll get old fast.
But if we advertise for them, they might let us eat for free!
Free meals for life
Now that's something I think would get old really fast.
Campaign
I used to find it difficult to go to those restaurants.
Huh? Why?
There are lots of men,
and you can't look too fashionable or too casual.
You have to find the right balance between standing out and blending in.
Ah, so it's a weird situation?
You should wear whatever you'd like.
Just dress casually, of course.
Sorry for changing the topic, but we got invited to a party.
Invited?
This is actually on topic.
Look at this.
Kou○sha
100th
anniversary party
Date and time:
△th of ○、
8 PM
Place:
Kou○sha
corporation
building
12th floor
underground
Please bring
this
invit
ation
with
you
Come in
casual
wear
Come in
"Dress casually."
Casually.
How casual is casual?
Casual is so difficult.
Just because the invitation says to dress casually
doesn't mean we should actually do it!
Think of how many manga artists were humiliated because they took that too literally!
100th anniversary of Kodansha
Yeah, Marii's idea of casual is a sweatsuit.
It would be pretty tacky to show up at a party wearing that.
Why am I being pigeonholed as someone who "normally" wears a sweatsuit?!
But if everyone went to the party wearing what they normally do,
wouldn't it just turn into a cosplay party?
Students have their uniforms,
and most jobs have some dress code as well.
Yeah, those are the clothes you wear the most.
So saying "dress casually" is actually an invitation to a cosplay party?
That's so dirty.
I don't think that's quite right.
I doubt there'd be many people with such unusual jobs or interests in the first place.
I don't think casual wear would mean to come in your work clothes.
It could mean plain clothes,
but I wear something different every day.
Then shouldn't casual wear be something that you make sure to wear every day?
That's it!
Pajamas are casual wear?
That's what people wear most of the time when they're not at work.
That's true.
And I saw on TV that in China it's hip to go out in your PJs.
What do you mean?
It's like a status symbol amongst the elite who live near the city center.
But they banned that around the time of the Olympics, citing that it was bad manners.
Anyway, pajamas are definitely the king of casual wear!
So saying "dress casually" is actually an invitation to a pajama party?
That's so dirty.
I still don't think that's right.
Really? Pajamas?
Do you really wear pajamas when you sleep?
Of course! I wear pa-pa-pajamas when I sleep!
I heard it!
I sleep in the nude.
In...
the...
nude...
So Marii's "casual wear" is being naked!
That's not "wear" at all!
So saying "dress casually" is actually an invitation to a nude party?
That's so dirty!
That's beyond dirty!
Anyway, let's take off everything Marii's wearing.
Or rather...
Have her change into her casual wear.
Deal with it! We're definitely not doing it to boost our ratings!
And it's not for the sales either!
A
Buratei Marii
What are you doing?!
Oh, look. Someone got all sexy all of a sudden.
It barely even feels like the first episode anymore.
It feels real pervy just flipping this thing up.
Really?
It's not like anything changes behind it, though.
Stop it!
This looks like it should be embarrassing!
You've got enough to be embarrassed about already.
You're casually naked?
That's like the Apache *** Force!
That's a uniform, okay?!
And no one's gonna get that reference either!
One page, flip!
Did you forget that just flipping the page changes nothing behind it?
A
Bouhatei Tetora
No! Now it looks like I'm naked!
You can't do that!
A
Anrakutei Kukuru
Now it looks like I'm naked!
I can't allow that!
Someone else!
A
Haroukitei Kigurumi
Now it looks like I'm naked!
Only fairies are allowed to be naked!
A
Kuurubiyuutei Gankyou
Now it looks like I'm naked without my glasses!
Oh my.
It's like we just did all this for the first-time viewers.
Yeah, we introduced all the characters in a natural way.
Indeed.
Buratei
Marii
A natural way?!
Now for something else!
A
Heipo
What the hell?
He's not in this show!
A
Stand up Japan!
That's not a name!
That's not even writing!
A
What a lovely day. This mor-
ning I've seen dandelions blo-
oming beside the             road.
Too long!
Who did?
A
We drew it!
That has nothing to do with us!
A
Tokyo Metropolitan Ordinance
Regarding the Healthy
Development of Youths
They aren't hidden!
A
Hidden body features
It's not over!
A
The end
Bouhatei Tetora
Daatei
Harii
A
Different Clothes
Good day to you!
You're early, Kigu.
You too!
What are you listening to?
This!
What's this?
Death metal!
That was a little unexpected.
Good day to you!
What's unexpected?
Unexpected.
What is?
I didn't know about this side of you, Gan.
Are you okay? Don't try too hard.
That's mean! Do I look like I'm trying too hard?!
Well, there are these people who are like 30 kilos overweight
and wear fluffy pink and white clothes...
Those are dosuloli.
Dosuloli?
It means "fat gothloli".
There are others too, like sweetloli, prololi,
brololi, hagloli, fagloli, summerloli.
And people who just do it when the fancy takes them, like you?
Moodloli.
But all these puns must weigh heavily on your shoulders...
Stiffloli.
Now it really is as though we're...
The main act!
Established rakugo theaters are called "fixed seats".
There are only four of them left though.
More like we still have four of them.
The stage is called the "high seat".
There's no "low seat", though.
People "climb onto" the high seat, but no one talks about getting off it.
Beginners get the title of an "early seat",
then as you progress you become a "second".
Then you can finally wear a haori,
and the path to be a "true hit" opens.
Anyway, it's really hot today.
Let me fan you.
Wipe your face with this tissue.
My thanks.
I get it why a fan is a fan, but why is a tissue a tissue?
But that's not a difficul tissue!
Life is so full of persisten tissues.
Such as the Tibe tissue!
Good morning.
She's go tissues...
What are you talking about?
It kinda fits her, though.
Yeah. It really is Marii-ish.
I think so too.
Are you even trying to compliment me?
Not at all.
Not to mention, you're a rakugo performer,
so you should greet people with "good day to you" and not "good morning".
I forget about it every now and then.
But seriously, does it really matter?
I see. Well, it's not an urgen tissue.
It's the first drum.
Are you having udon or soba today?
Don't ask stupid questions!
Soba!
Udon!
Hey...
Aren't we forgetting something?
Spices?
Chopsticks?
Our order?
Whatever.
Good day to you.
A
Buratei Marii
Purr-meow! Purr-meow!
Come on, what are you saying?
You even tried to sleep on my legs.
I don't understand at all!
What are you trying to say?
Purr-meow! Purr-meow!
Purr-meow seven cups of milk right now!
Thank you for your kind attention.
A
Shouting Instruction
It's hard to ask this, but...
Do you prefer cats or dogs?
Don't ask stupid questions!
This anime is full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully enjoy how cute the girls are.
It's so stupid.
Which one? Which one?
I like both.
Me too.
Then do you prefer black tea or coffee?
Don't ask stupid questions!
Coffee.
Coffee here, too.
If I had to choose, I'd say black tea.
It has a calming aroma to it.
Actually, it contains more caffeine than coffee.
Huh, really?
Then, do you prefer your coffee iced or hot?
Iced!
Hot.
Would you prefer a cold bath or a hot bath?
Why ask that?
I'll go with hot.
I don't think I could bear an icy cold bath,
but I might be able to deal with a burning hot one.
But girls,
the real question is whether you prefer Peps—
Dogs or cats.
Which would you choose if you had to?
So once there was this woman—
If you base it on the sounds they make, I prefer dogs.
Nah, cats are way better.
Dogs are in the Zodiac and they work for the police as well.
Cats only bring bad luck. Poor things.
But dogs are looked down upon. What about the phrase "dog of authority"?
Dog of authority
Yelp of
a kicked dog
Die like a dog
But you can also say "arched like a cat", "cat burglar",
Arched like a cat
Cat burglar
Caterwaul
"caterwaul" and "purr like a cat".
Purr like a cat
Tomcat
It's usually the cats who turn into monsters.
Dogs don't do that.
They must have regrets or something.
It's not that dogs don't hold grudges,
more like they just can't stay still.
They're not meant to be ghosts.
Yeah.
There are many famous dog characters.
Cats too.
A curry-taste—
But when it comes to the sounds they make, cats are the best.
Sounds?
Dogs are only good for practicing.
Practicing?
Fetch!
Ah, performing practice?
AAAA
I'm looking for
this kitten
Yeah, performing practice.
My dog can't perform anything.
I'll bring him next time to help with your practice!
Are you sure?
Dog
Anyway, I hate the character for "dog".
Why?
Whenever I feel upset, I forget where I'm supposed to put the last stroke!
I don't!
Oh? Well then,
try staring at this for a while
and see if you can still remember which is the correct one.
I can!
Oh?
Dog
You weren't sure.
We write "dog" like this because dogs are always by our side!
When someone works with a hoe, they often have a dog close by!
Really?
I just made it up!
Dogs want to be by our side!
You're annoying.
But even then the last stroke could still go anywhere.
It's okay here...
and here and here and here and even here.
Not there! You'll impale the poor puppy!
But one of those puppies would be really lonely.
That poor puppy!
It's a whole pack!
I got attacked by wild dogs!
I just thought of a new kanji!
Big
Pet loss syndrome!
That's "big" news.
It's hard to ask this, but...
Do you prefer the mountains or the sea?
I told you not to ask stupid questions!
A traditional pun.
What?
I've had enough of this...
I like the sea!
I like the mountains. Much cleaner.
You mean, do I prefer the winter mountains or the winter sea?
No, I think summer is okay.
Summer?
But in the summer you rot so quickly!
What exactly are you talking about?
Weren't you asking whether I'd rather die on a mountain or by the sea?
How'd you manage to interpret it that way?
Well, if I had to die, I'd prefer to do it on a mountain.
I'd get frozen in the mountains,
and centuries later someone would find me,
and my sheer beauty and grace would move them to tears!
We're not talking about frozen corpses in the future.
The question is whether we prefer the mountains or the sea, right?
Well, it's not exactly a preference, but I think the sea is more primitive.
Primitive? Why?
Because in the mountains you shout,
"Yoo-hoo!"
While by the sea you shout,
"You fool!"
Right?
I see!
Though I don't think people shout "You fool!" out to sea very often.
What? Then what do you shout out to sea?
Catch me if you can!
You wouldn't shout that out to sea.
Well, you don't have to be at the sea either.
What if you try to catch crabs?
That's not even shouting.
What?
That was the shout of someone falling into a pit.
Nope.
I guess it's "You fool!" after all.
"You fool!" it is.
"You fool!"
Right, right, right?
Yeah...
I can't think of anything better.
But doesn't whatever you shout out to sea depend on the direction you're facing?
What do you mean?
You'd shout something different toward the Sea of Japan than you would to the Pacific.
There's no one to shout to across the Pacific.
Even if you were to shout to King Kamehameha, it's 6400 km away.
That's far.
The average "You fool!" travels at 340m/s.
You fool!
So how long would it take to get there?
Would it be faster if we just shouted "Fool!"?
Yeah, I think "Fool!" on its own is easier to catch than "You fool!".
But what would you shout across the Sea of Japan, where there are people much closer by?
See, you've got nothing. Why not just settle for "You fool!"?
It's not particularly meaningful, but I guess we could.
It might not be meaningful, but at least "You fool!" covers quite a wide angle.
However, "You fool!" has no style and won't solve anything.
Solve?
Oh, right!
Give it back!
Yeah, that works nicely.
Whenever you shout out to the sea, you should shout "Give it back!"
Right?
Right.
With that, you can cover pretty much every angle.
Give back our land!
Give back our people!
Give back our technology!
Give back our submarine resources!
Give back our money!
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
This is Bouhatei Tetora.
Thank you for coming tonight.
The sultry weather continues,
but if you sleep with an electric fan blowing at you,
it'll drain your energy.
So please be careful.
Coming up next, it's Joshiraku's second performance:
Backstage Riches, Three Towers and a Vow, and Cold Girl.
A
Backstage Riches
Three Towers and a Vow
Cold Girl
Those three.
Come see us next time, okay?