Romero...
I'll take you, Romero...
to the place where you wanted to be...
to the place no one can catch up to us...
at a speed that can even shake off the past...
to the other side of that place...
Truth
I can't believe you have to work this late...
I have to work whenever I'm needed.
You don't want to become an assassin any more, right?
That's not true.
I may not come home until late. So go ahead and go to bed.
No, I'll stay up.
I found a broken VCR this afternoon.
I want to see if I can fix it, so...
You can buy a new one.
That'll be a waste. It might still work.
It might still work... huh?
I guess you're right.
Come home soon.
Yeah.
Promise?
Yeah, I promise.
I don't want to be separated from you. I want to be with you forever.
If I can go back at all...
the time is now.
Whether I quit or run away,
the organization will...
You're late, Lizzie.
Lizzie?
Okay, don't move.
Lizzie...
Sorry.
Seriously, I keep causing you trouble, don't I...
I heard about you, kid.
You're that Phantom, huh?
No wonder my men were easily taken out.
What?
You don't have to play dumb.
We've got even a picture of you. Look.
Who took a picture like that?
It must've been that woman.
How's that? You're lost for words, huh?
Mr. Godo. You got it wrong.
That picture...
Listen to me before you make a fool of yourself.
I already know that you did it on orders from your boss.
I just want to get the facts. That's all.
The attacks on us... All three were...
ordered by Claudia... Isn't that right?
Are you out of your mind?
How much trouble do you think she went through
so that you guys could join Inferno?!
I don't dislike loyalty...
but that woman isn't someone you should go that far to be loyal to.
We are being manipulated by her... both us and you guys as well...
What nonsense!
Say, lady...
This isn't the first time we met at this place.
What?
Don't you remember? That was quite a memorable night.
Yeah, it's been about a year since then.
A year...
Tsk! Who are those guys?!
The shipment is...!
We did it!
It's too early to celebrate, bro.
Just step on it!
Yes sir!
I see... So that was you guys.
You allied with Scythe and...
We don't know this Scythe guy you're talking about.
It was Claudia who arranged everything.
Can't be...!
We were in a serious fix because of a series of problems.
Then suddenly, that woman brought the deal to us.
She said that she'd let us steal 500 kilograms of cocaine.
She'd arrange everything and get us some backup to help us out.
Then she asked us if we wanted to go wild in LA.
Why would she say such things?
Her terms were that we join Inferno after the dust settles,
acting as if we knew nothing.
We were baffled, too, at first,
but we were able to understand after hearing her situation.
She wanted to create her own backing within Inferno...
since as long as she's an outsider, she won't ever be able to make it big.
You know how she said we used to use a different supplier to obtain drugs?
That was a total lie.
I established the Godo Family's market in the past year
using the cocaine that we stole from you guys.
Then Claudia used Scythe...
Oh yeah... There's a fool who got the short end of the stick in that plan.
Is that the Scythe guy you're talking about?
It's me.
There was a sudden change. Scythe betrayed the organization.
He used Phantom to attack Inferno's shipment.
What?!
The organization is putting all its resources into hunting them down.
We still haven't found either of them.
That time...!
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back...
You know how to use this, right?
So she was involved in everything.
Scythe!
Because of that, we got hurt... we cried...
It seems like something rang a bell, huh?
Is that true, Phantom?!
Looks like even the renowned Mr. Phantom is no match for a woman's charms.
But there's more to this plot.
That woman was planning to connect to the Godo Family
without me and Shiga in the end.
While trying to kill us in order to keep us from talking,
she even eliminated her rival in the confusion of the moment.
Who knows what treachery she's capable of?
So this is the truth. You get it?
We were made a fool of by that woman.
I don't care about Inferno or whatever any more.
I, Daisuke Godo, can't just take being made a fool of like this lying down!
I won't believe it. I won't believe it! You filthy thief!
Son of a bitch! Where?!
Where are you hiding?!
It's that woman.
Get in, Phantom!
You go on ahead!
Phantom!
E... Elen...
E... Elen.
Can't be... You're alive...
But why?
Why, Elen?!
Why are you doing this?!
Don't call me... Elen.
I'm Ein.
I'm just Ein... as I always was.
Hurry up and run.
Inferno is coming after you soon.
This time for sure, you'll be completely...
Inferno is?
Elen... Wait!
Elen!
I'm Ein... as I always was.
Him...
That man.
Scythe Master...
This is wonderful.
The Godo Family, Claudia McCunnen...
and Isaac Wisemel of Inferno.
By stirring up those three's doubts and fears,
you're leading your sworn enemies who trapped you in the past
to self-destruction one after another.
No... that's not all.
I sent someone to tell the truth to Inferno.
They'll probably start taking action immediately.
To eliminate the traitor, Claudia McCunnen...
and her vanguard, Phantom.
The organization will come after me... Which means...
Cal...
I see. You passed the entrance exam, huh?
I'm happy for you, Mio.
I wanted to let you know right away.
Did my abrupt visit disturb your work?
You don't have to worry about stuff like that.
But the trading business... is a lot of work, right?
Yeah, I guess.
I'll be out of Japan starting the day after tomorrow for a while to buy products.
What do you want me to get for you?
You don't have to get me things all the time.
Besides, if I often get things from you, Mom will find out.
I see...
I guess you're right.
I'm supposed to meet up with my friends, so...
Relax and have a lot of fun. See you later then.
Okay.
Even though her mother was divorced,
the same evil Godo blood as mine and our boss's is running in Mio's veins.
If there's someone who takes advantage of that fact...
since she doesn't know anything, she can't even protect herself.
Even though her situation and her last name changed,
she's still my little sister. My precious little sister.
Shiga, the scheme this time is big.
If I can't come back to Japan alive...
Then...
I know, bro.
I'll take responsibility to watch over Mio's future all the way.
Thanks, Shiga.
The belly and shoulder, huh? It's nothing.
There was a time that I survived more than twice as many bullets as this.
The path of bloodshed is my... glorious path...
Hey...
Who survived?
They're all dead.
I see... After all, it's just you and me again.
It was always like this.
No matter what devastating experiences we went through,
you were always with me.
We always got by with my guts and your wisdom.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
So what happened to Claudia?
Inferno will probably take care of that woman.
More importantly, we need to think about ourselves, the Godo Family.
We were under that woman. Inferno won't leave us alone.
It'll be a war.
Ha! To hell with Inferno!
They tricked us. I'll make them pay dearly for that.
It'll be a battle to avenge these guys.
Say, Shiga, let's kill them all.
We don't have to go... that far.
Huh?
Things will be settled if just one more person dies...
Everything will...
Shiga...
Now that things come to this, you may not believe me when I say this,
but bro... I admired you... from the bottom of my heart.
Shiga...
Shiga!
By taking care of the rebel,
the Godo Family's good faith has been proven.
I'll mediate and smooth things over with Inferno for you.
Mr. Shiga, the Godo Family will be secure now.
Giuseppe... I'd love nothing more than to shoot you right now.
Will you shoot me?
You and I seem to have a lot in common.
Looks like we'll become good friends, Mr. Shiga.
Clo... Where are you Clo?!
Where... Where are you?
At least give me your excuses... Claudia McCunnen.
Run, Reiji...
Live!
Pursuers...
Cal...
Cal.
I'm surprised that you aren't tired of it.
No, I'm not.
You like that music that much?
Yeah, I do...
because someone I like so much bought this for me.
I thought I had nothing.
I didn't even have the normal things that ordinary people had.
So I thought I'd never get something like this.
Thank you, Reiji.
I want to be... by your side... forever...
C... Cal...
Cal...
Cal!
Next episode
Confrontation
The only reason this world isn't an endless hell
is because you're alive.