Tooru.
Run-chan, geez.
What's the matter?
Thank you, Tooru.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Birthday
Good morning.
Ah, good morning.
It's cold today, too.
Can't spring come faster?
By the way, isn't Tooru's birthday coming up?
Yes, that's right.
So, will you be having a party?
Not really.
You're being modest again.
Look forward to my present this year, too!
Yes.
Look forward?
Don't tell me it's another one of those?
What kind of animal was that, anyway?
That uniform...
It's a middle schooler, right?
They're having a school briefing today again.
Oh, I see.
They'll be taking entrance exams at the start of the new year.
And we'll advance to the next year.
Entrance exams...
Entrance exams?
That brings back memories. Doesn't it, Tooru?
Huh?
Yeah...
I need to make my second choice soon.
You've already decided on your first?
Yes.
With my grades, I think this one is closest to my level.
Where will you be going to high school, Tooru?
I guess you haven't decided yet.
You're in second year, after all.
I plan on going to the same place.
To Nikou?
I think you could do better than that.
Your grades are good.
No.
Anywhere where Run-chan goes is fine.
Here.
Thank you.
So, have you decided what high school to go to?
Yes... for the time being.
What about Nikou?
Sure, why not?
It has a good reputation.
It's should be your academic level, too.
Yes.
By the way, Tooru said that she wants to go to the same high school as me.
Go for a better high school.
B-But...
Your future will be assured if you go to a good place.
But, you just said Nikou was fine...
I changed my mind.
But even if I take the exam,
I already know what the result will be.
I just don't perform well enough...
That's right.
We can fix that.
W-Wait!
Who are you calling?!
Cram school.
No!
Okay, I understand.
Forcing you won't work.
So,
how does all-you-can-eat Kobe beef sound?
Okay, I'll try!
Run-chan, you changed your choice to a higher-level school?
Yes, more or less.
I made up my mind after talking with my mum.
So, you're getting a home tutor and going to cram school?
You're really into it.
You already know my tutor, Hira-chan.
Huh?
Look.
Let me introduce you.
This is Tooru-sensei!
Hi.
But... Isn't Tooru-chan...
Yes, that's right.
The glasses are important.
She is a teacher, after all.
I'm not talking about the glasses!
Well, then.
Let's start studying.
We will begin with something simple.
Huh?
For now, memorise all of this.
The basics are just about memorising.
It-It's a big pile...
Jenga!
The answer to that question is A!
Number 4 is a trick question.
Be careful!
What?
What is this voice talking in my head?!
My right hand is writing the answers all on its own!
What's going on?!
Huh?
A dream?
Oh, the letters!
Wait!
I won't be able to solve the problem like this!
Huh?
Run-chan, wake up.
A dream?
Yes.
Japanese
Language
Oh, you've bumped up your grade.
I've been looking at textbooks every waking hour.
Is that so?
All of the books are so beaten up.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I dropped those in the bathtub.
You dropped all of them?!
I'll buy new ones later.
Well, I'm off!
Run-chan, do your best.
Accepted
Okay, when the bell rings, flip your sheet over and start.
I can do this.
Start!
Oops, I'll use another pencil.
Is she sabotaging me?
Tokyo is scary.
Okay, I'll collect your answer sheets.
Um...
I'm sorry, did I hit you with the tip of my pencil?
Oh, it's fine.
I'm glad!
She wasn't trying to sabotage me.
So, you came from Kansai just to take the exam today?
Yes, I'll be moving here in spring.
That's why...
Ah!
Speaking of Kansai...
This is my good luck charm for today.
TL Note: Kobe is in Kansai
Huh?
Is it a cow god or something?
Yay!
It's there!
Look, it's my number!
I got accepted thanks to you, Tooru.
No, Run-chan.
It's because you did your best.
Congratulations.
And that's the story.
I somehow passed the exam.
You tried hard, Run.
I wrote words on my hand so I wouldn't forget them.
Oh, I wrote on my hand so I wouldn't forget things, too.
But if you did that during the test, it would be cheating.
I washed it off before the test, of course.
It became a habit, though.
Eventually, I was writing all over my body.
It was hard to stop.
Good morning.
They announce the results today, didn't they?
Haven't they already posted them?
I'll go later.
You're pretty calm.
I wouldn't be able to see it anyway.
Yes?
Tooru, I have a present for you!
Huh?
Here!
Since your birthday is coming up...
Cake?!
Cake!
Well, the 3 second rule always applies, right?
No...
...It was completely upside-down.
Just kidding!
Tada!
This is the real one!
Huh?
Did I surprise you?
I heard that when spirits are raised after they've been dropped,
You feel twice as happy!
I wanted to make you happy!
Where did you hear that?
I'll take the cake.
I won't drop it again! I'll be fine.
Just let me.
Your hands are already full, though.
Just let me!
Tooru, are you mad at me?
You're already 16 now, eh...
You've grown, too.
You were so small back then...
Huh?
You always used to crawl after me.
And any time you weren't holding candy, you'd start crying.
That was so cute...
Run-chan...
Huh?
What are you talking about?
It was a dream I had.
They met in elementary school
Dream?
Look.
You've grown so much.
You're still small, though.
I'm still small
Ugh...
Don't treat me like a little child!
Ah, I found a white hair!
You're pretty brave, bringing cake to school.
There's enough for everyone, so let's eat it at lunch!
Where should we leave it in the meantime?
Ah, that's right!
It needs to be refrigerated...
Well, we don't have any fridges here...
Where would the coldest place in school be?
The toilet, huh...?
You have to eat it, too, you know...
By the way, it's almost Tooru's birthday, right?
Congratulations.
Thank you very much
By the way, what are we going to do?
Don't worry!
I've prepared a present.
Really?
I'll give you that book you wanted the other day.
Thank you.
Um... I'll...
A cup.
A cup?
What's that ruler for?
What kind?
An E-cup...
E-Eh?!
Let's just eat the cake now, before it goes bad.
You're right.
Ooh!!
Looks good.
Looks delicious!
Time for a thrill game!
Huh?
One of these cakes actually contains wasabi!
Are you unable to celebrate normally?!
But... One of them pretty obviously has some green.
It's so obvious!
I'll let Yuuko have the most delicious-looking one.
Eh?!
Well, she's from Kansai.
TL Note: Apparently wasabi cake is normal there!
I envy you.
Well, let's eat.
But be careful!
There is actually another one with wasabi in i-
Run-chan!
This cakes is so cute...
Oh, you're taking a commemorative photo?
Since everyone is here, let's take one with all of us in it.
Okay.
Yuuko, you're blurry.
Huh?
I didn't move an inch!
Didn't you wiggle a bit?
Let's take another one!
Then let's all match up with Yuuko.
Hey, take it normally!
Oh!
I moved!
Take another!
We'll match up with you again, Yuuko.
One, two...
Ah, I moved again!
Geez...
Well, let's continue from yesterday.
Yesterday, we used Cavalieri's principle.
We finished the formula for calculating the surface area and volume of a sphere...
Huh?
Toorun?
Oh!
Cake!
This is...
U-Um...
Ah!
Now we add up to the diameter...
Toorun!
Hmm?
Happy birthday!
Hmm...
Eh!?
Well, then...
Could you come up and solve this problem, Yutaka-san?
Eh?!
Here!
Look, look!
Huh?
What is it?
This is a picture from when I was studying for exams!
Two years ago, huh?
You're eating cake.
Yes.
This was on Tooru's birthday.
Why are you being fed?
That was during my test period.
Now's not the time for that, Tooru!
Just kidding!
Here. Happy birthday, Tooru!
Eh?
Well, you didn't forget the present.
Yeah.
Not that, at least.
Also...
Look.
Hmm?
What?
This was Tooru's birthday last year.
Tooru is the one studying here, right?
Yeah.
Since Tooru was studying, I fed her this time.
I brought cake and presents with me.
Here, open up.
By the way, weren't you bothering her?
That's not true at all.
Right, Tooru?
Hmm...
Tooru did her best, too. Right?
And...
...here!
This is the annual commemorative photo!
Hold on! Why do you have that one?
Tooru gave it to me a while ago.
You should delete that one!
Eh? But, I don't want to!
Hey!
Give me your phone!
Really... Let's go, Tooru.
I'll delete it myself!
No!
Yeah.
Hey!
kyoushitsu kara koboreru kaiwa no aida o surinuke te
Weaving through the conversations overflowing from the classrooms,
hitorigiri de aru kurookawa sukoshi samishii
Walking alone down the corridor is a little bit lonely.
tanoshii jikan wa itsudemo
Fun times always
hayaku sugideyukukara
Pass by quickly,
omoi de no arubamu no peeji wa mugen nan dame e
So there are infinite pages in my album of memories.
kitto kitto kitto
Surely, surely, surely
zutto zutto zutto
Always, always, always
kianai egao no kioku
The never-fading smiles in memories.
Hey, Tooru.
Let's all eat cake together next year, too.
motto motto motto
More, more, more
Cut down on the wasabi cakes, though...
kon himo ashita mo mei go bimo
Today, tomorrow, and the day after
Hey, hey.
ibbai uyashiteikou ne
Let's make more and more of them.
Next year we'll be the ones taking exams.
Nagi, don't say scary things like that.
What are you talking about?
It's reality.
I see...
Next year, we'll be taking the exams.
Exams...
Well, we're going this way.
Bye bye!
It seems so sudden.
It seems like you only enrolled the other day.
You're becoming a second year already...
You're right...
And then, Run-chan will be in her third year.
Tooru.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Really?
Yeah.
Speaking of which, Run-chan.
Hmm?
Why did you decide to go to this school?
Hmm... Why do you think?
Tell me.
It's a secret!
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
Aliens?
Aliens.
Someone who came to correct the
mistakes humans make in this time period?
That's a time traveller.
Pithecanthropus Erectus.
Now it's known as Homo Erectus.
Wait, that's a primitive man?
All the way to the end, Miporin is the only one that gets to respond to my jokes!
That doesn't make me happy at all.
Next Time!
Aliens
Next time on A Channel: Aliens.
TL Note: Reference to Ghidorah from the Godzilla franchise.
It's said they were destroyed by a three-headed dragon!
TL Note: Specifically, the movie "Ghidorah, the Three-Headed Monster".
TL Note: Though in the English version of the movie he had destroyed Mars.
That were the Venusians.