99th   Seisho Festival
Day of the Performance
Let's go, to pluck that star together!
Regardless of how many I loose,
my arrows will not reach that star.
You who reach for the star without a care
could never understand my fury!
I should be able to seize that star!
That's what I believed.
But that was nothing short of arrogance.
If you cannot confront it, you may as well flee.
Yes, escape was the only way out.
I had no other option.
But I am cursed with this lamentation and regret.
This is nothing but unsightly jealousy.
So please tell me!
What must I sacrifice to obtain that person for myself?
O, and so it repeats.
The cycle of despair.
Beneath the light of the stars.
Our dream was not meant to be.
Seisho Festival
It's so dazzling.
99th   Seisho Festival
Two Days After the Performance
Classes 1-A, 1-B
Joint Celebration
Seisho Festival
99th
That's it for the 99th generation's first
Starlight performance at the 99th Seisho Festival.
Let's cheer to our splendid performance!
Cheers!
Well done, Junna-chan.
Nana...
This is just the end of our first performance.
We have to start preparing for next year straight away.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Wouldn't you say that was quite the success, Karen-chan?
You were quite bon yourself, Nana.
Mahiru-chan, weren't you nervous?
Yeah, but Karen-chan helped me calm down.
And here are the two leads.
You put on a great performance.
Thank you.
I haven't lost.
Then let's face the auditions again next year together, shall we?
Daiba Nana-san.
That means you as well.
Maya-chan?
I didn't think I'd be able to handle a goddess role,
but it worked out somehow.
You call that "working out"?
Nana!
Futaba-chan?
Thanks for helping me out with everything.
I'm rather indebted to you too, Nana-han.
I really enjoyed your shoulder massages.
She helped me with practice too.
She helped us with the costumes.
And the background scenery!
When everyone was getting hungry,
she made a bunch of snacks for us to eat.
I feel like the banana muffins that Nana made
are what got me through the final stretch.
I know! Banana!
Huh?
You're like a banana to everyone.
Sweet and kind and extremely nutritious.
You even help us with our stiff necks.
Nana is... a banana?
That's cute.
I guess she is pretty banana-like,
with her height and all.
She smells good too.
Banana, huh...
Nana?
Did I say something wrong?
Nana-han?
No, not at all.
That's not it.
I'm just happy.
I'm just...
so glad I came to this academy.
The play we all made together was so fun and happy and shining.
I won't forget about this play—
about the 99th Seisho Festival Starlight.
I found my eternal comrades and my stage of destiny.
This is the day I was born.
As the stage girl, Daiba Nana.
Girls' Musical
Revue Starlight
Who will be the one to claim that star?
At the top of that tower
A silent flame lit up inside of me
And now a burning longing fills my chest
We're not puppets on a stage
Being made to dance by fate
Go, take flight!
I know I saw it on that day
The glimmer of an exploding star
Until we have our promise from so long ago in hand
It begins before the curtain rises
The story plays out before my very eyes
In this new life of mine
I got to meet you
Once again
Seisho Music Academy
Spring Break             Day 1
Yes?
I'll arrive tomorrow at 3 pm.
See you, Banana!
Look forward to souvenirs.
Futaba-han, make haste!
You're perfectly welcome to carry some of the luggage.
All right!
Bye!
Starlight Dorm
It's really quiet without the others around.
The only ones staying behind are me and Junna-chan.
Hey, do you really need to record this too?
The next Seisho Festival is the 100th anniversary!
I can't let any precious moments get away.
Are you actually okay not going home?
I simply decided not to go home until I graduate. That's all.
If you're only doing this because you feel sorry for me, then...
Junna-chan, how about some udon?
I just want to be here.
Sure, I'll have some.
Seisho Music Academy
New Semester
And here we have a freshly minted second-year.
Junna-chan, tell us what's on your mind.
Wait, I have my dignity to uphold as an
upperclassman and the class representative.
They're the same, but apparently they're spanking new.
New students!
They're all nervous and stiff.
These are spanking new too.
Actor Training Program
And this is the second-year classroom.
We'll be in its care for the coming year.
Spring break is over, and everyone is here.
Wait...
Naruse-san and Osaka-san aren't here yet.
They dropped out.
NARUSE AYAHI
This isn't what I wanted my first job as
class rep to be after becoming a second-year.
NARUSE AYAHI
Well then.
We have to move on for the sake of improving our play.
Yeah...
100th   Seisho Festival
Start of Auditions
Acting Studio
The 100th Seisho Festival.
We'll be performing our second Starlight.
We're finally starting auditions for the lead roles today.
I'll be taking it home this time around.
Down with Tendo Maya!
Flora will be none other than me!
Then I'll be Claire!
I'll get a lead role without a doubt!
You're heavy.
Daiba-san.
Do you have a moment after this?
Sure.
Auditions again, huh...
It still doesn't feel real.
I mean, I still remember it like it was yesterday.
Our Starlight.
Our very own brilliant play that we all made together.
I'd love nothing more than if we could put on the same performance again.
Even with the same members and the same cast,
putting on the same performance twice is impossible.
That may be true.
They've made up their minds.
I'm sure they've experienced anguish,
despair, and anger that we can't imagine.
Remember what I said?
To face the auditions with the lead roles on the line...
There are those who leave the stage,
faced with an opponent their hardest efforts cannot overcome...
Or a dream they can never fulfill.
A physique that anyone would envy,
a clear, beautiful voice,
and an eye that can follow the entire stage.
Despite that, why are you...
Decide already.
Hold on just a bit longer.
If you're holding back just so you can remain the Banana-san that everyone loves...
I...
Daiba Nana, I won't forgive you.
Maya-chan...
Nana?
Junna-chan...
Oh, are those from the closing party?
Yeah, wanna see?
Hey, class rep.
Nice shot!
Did you have to take this one too?!
Seisho Festival
It was only two months ago, but it feels oddly nostalgic.
The play we put on for the Seisho Festival, our very own Starlight—I loved it.
I loved it too.
Yeah, me too.
Class B helped out backstage,
while we in class A sang and performed.
All of us in the 99th generation made it.
It was our very own play.
Is it really impossible to recreate it?
I don't think I'd be able to perform in that play.
Huh?
The stage is a living thing.
We may be performing the same Starlight,
but we could never put on the exact same performance.
And some people aren't even around anymore.
Yeah!
That's exactly why we have to practice even more
and put on a much, much, much better performance!
Karen-chan?
Hey, don't stand on the bench, Aijo-san!
This is a stage, my very own stage.
I took my shoes off, ma'am.
That's not the problem here!
Do you like tall places or something, Aijo-san?
Yup, I do.
Like Tokyo Tower!
An even better performance. Pursuing your potential.
But, to me,
Seisho Festival
that Starlight
is the best and dearest.
A giraffe.
How cute.
Girls' Musical Revue Starlight
Good evening, Daiba Nana-san.
Is it dazzling?
Huh?
I understand.
A real giraffe?
A revue...
It consists of song and dance woven into a mesmerizing play.
The more they can feel the glimmer that the stage girls emit,
the more the lighting,
the audio system, and the stage mechanisms
will begin to dance on their own.
Acting, song, and dance...
This stage will respond to the glimmer of the stage girls.
Glimmer?
To whoever puts on the brightest shining revue,
the path to becoming the top star will open up.
The top star...
The one who will stand on the stage of destiny.
Emitting an infinite glimmer,
unleashing their full potential,
they will transcend time to shine on: the eternal lead.
I don't care about that.
I understand.
However,
what if you could stand on any stage you desire?
Any stage?
Don't you know of one as well?
A dazzling stage.
One you can never revisit.
A dazzling stage that shines ever so strongly.
Is it dazzling?
I understand.
Can it really be any stage at all?
No matter which stage or when?
Will you participate in the auditions?
I understand.
So this is your true ability.
What made you change?
Is it dazzling?
What?
It's dazzling to me.
What made you...
I can't reach.
...go this far?
Position zero.
I can't reach the dazzling light.
Congratulations.
Is it dazzling?
It's dazzling.
The one to pass the auditions
is you, Daiba Nana-san.
Having become the top star, what is the stage of destiny that you desire?
The 99th Seisho Festival.
A repeat performance of Starlight.
A glimmer like that of blazing jewels.
Happy days that shine like the rainbow.
I want to go back.
It's dazzling.
Even now, that stage still is.
Very well.
You in the 99th generation will be performing
Starlight.
I love Starlight!
Me too!
Ah, Lumière d'Étoile.
Why not?
Starlight?
Why's everyone getting so excited?
What's with everyone, Junna-chan?
Huh?!
Junna-chan?
I-I mean, you just used my first name out of the blue,
Daiba-san.
Actor Training Program
99th   Seisho Festival
The Year Leading Up To It
Daiba Nana
The Stage of Destiny
And so the reenactment started.
The reenactment of the 99th Seisho Festival.
Precious friends, that precious stage.
Seisho Festival
The reenactment of those precious days.
Inside my reenactment, there is nothing to fear.
We will neither grow nor become adults.
The suffering that corners you...
The pain of attempting something new...
The sadness of being hurt and giving up...
I'll protect you from it all.
Seisho Festival
I know! Banana!
Huh?
You're like a banana to everyone.
Because I'm sweet and kind and extremely nutritious,
and even help you with your stiff necks?
Y-Yeah. Exactly.
As I think about how to recreate the exact same performance...
I thought I'd reached it...
but it's still dazzling.
Congratulations.
The one to pass the auditions
is you, Daiba Nana-san.
Now, Nana-san, having become the
top star, what stage do you wish for?
It's dazzling, even still.
I don't know how many times this makes it,
but very well.
Hey, why?
Why do you do all this for me?
The moment a stage girl becomes the top star...
The chemical reaction caused by the fusion of miracles and glimmer...
An eternal shine, a moment's combustion...
A stage of destiny that no one can predict...
I want to witness that.
You in the 99th generation will be performing
Who was that?
Starlight.
Huh?
Are you okay, Karen-chan?
A sandwich is circling around in my brain.
K-Karen-chan?
Are you okay, Karen-chan?
Don't worry, Karen-chan is sturdy.
Be more considerate, Banana-chan!
Hey, are you okay, Karen?
Today a transfer student will be joining the class.
I know it's sudden, but make sure to get along.
What?
This hasn't happened before.
Who is that girl?
Kagura Hikari
I danced a lot today, so let me ride on the motorbike.
We're walking home to train the lower body.
It's 5 million for the taxi.
I've folded the T-shirts and towels and put them away.
But...
...don't understand!
Never mind.
What went wrong?
Maybe he's saying that it's boring to have the same performance every time.
A stage of destiny no one can predict...
But no matter who shows up,
my reenactment remains the same.
Kagura Hikari-chan...
I think I want her for my play now.
Next Time
To Where the Light Leads
Girls' Musical Revue Starlight.
I understand.