This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
The recording day for her debut song, "Myself", had come...
And then that Takuto...
He fell asleep while he was a stuffed animal, and some strange girl picked him up.
That's because he's such an oaf.
Mitsuki managed to get him back, though.
Her recording went off without a hitch.
Takuto.
I'll keep this a secret from the chief, 'kay?
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Well then.
We still have another song for you!
In just a moment... we'll have the song that all eyes are on this week.
Isn't it amazing? Here it is...
...on sale this week... the song, "Myself".
This song is actually...
...from the artist who made Seed Records' New Artist audition...
...in just one try... the debut song for Full Moon...
...is produced by Takasu Kohei.
However, Takasu-san was unable to join us for an interview during this break.
Um... excuse me.
Can you please turn off the radio?
Which brings us to the song that's caught everyone's attention!
I detest music.
Listen to this.
Ah. Yes.
Full Moon's...
Welcome back, madam.
Where's Mitsuki-san?
Ah. She's resting in her room.
Is that so?
Has she done anything peculiar?
Oh man!
This manga is a riot!
Ribon
What is that vulgar behavior, Mitsuki-san?
Geh!
Ribon
Please excuse me, Grandmother.
I'll be more careful next time!
Geez...
She's only twelve, for crying out loud.
Ah...
Those guys... they're so lucky...
They're probably in Shibuya right now, huh?
Full Moon, Debut!
Wow...
What are you staring at?
This is your first live concert, isn't it?
Where are you performing?
Where, indeed...
Ah?
You're so helpless.
I'll go look for it.
Where did your manager say it was...?
That...she didn't tell me.
"I'll know when I reach the center."
Hey, where exactly is this "center"?
Hmm...
Over there.
Wow!
Man, you're such a hick?
That's because this is my first time in Shibuya!
Wow...
Anyways, where exactly are we?
Oh?
Why are they all looking up?
Eh?
Wow!
Who is that?
It's that girl.
You know, the one who was
chosen at that audition.
I know her.
I heard her song on the radio.
Ah... that girl, huh?
She's really cute.
They said you're cute.
How does the object of worship  feel about it?
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Why...?
For some reason... that doesn't look like me...
You could say...
...that there's a gap between what's real and what's just an image.
Really...
Please line up over here!
Wow!
Today is Full Moon's special live concert.
Those who wish to enjoy it...
...please line up over here.
There's this many people gathered for a new artist who hasn't even debuted, huh?
In-Incredible.
I'm going to sing in front of this many people...
What's wrong?
C-Can I sing well, I wonder?
What if I get the words wrong..?
When that happens...
"When that happens..."
Smile and make it up!
I don't want to do that!
I worked so hard to come up with those lyrics.
So you won't get them wrong, right?
Like I said...
I'm worried I can do it.
Hey, hey.
Now is not the time to
start thinking like that.
Anyways...
We have to find somewhere to transform you.
Over there.
Let's see... The exit is...
You're Full Moon, aren't you?
Don't you remember me?
Eh?
Have we met somewhere before?
At the beginning of the audition.
Um...
You don't remember?
Ah... sorry.
I... was the one after you.
Eh?
I was Number 22 at the audition.
Thanks to you...
I had to go home without auditioning.
Today's audition is over.
So...
The previously expected third judging will not take place.
I see...
Back then...
I'm very sorry.
Oh.
It's not something you need to apologize for.
Eh...
That's right.
If someone gets chosen...
...everyone else is disappointed.
That's right.
Because I...
...don't think that I would have lost to you.
Eh?
If I had gone instead of you...
I would have been the one chosen instead.
That...
I suppose that could have happened...
Because...
I'm an incredible singer.
A-Ah...
Good to see she doesn't lack self-confidence.
It's so beneficial...
...that cuteness of yours.
Eh?
What do you mean?
Oh?
You didn't know?
You weren't chosen for you singing...
The decision was based solely on your looks.
Eh?
If it wasn't for that, there's no way you would have been selected...
...with such a mediocre song.
Today's concert...
I'm looking forward to it.
You can do all sorts of tricks with the mic for your CD, but...
...you can't do something
like that for a live concert.
With only your looks...
Having to sing in front of flocks of people...
It'd be best if you realized your position as soon as possible.
That's such a spiteful girl.
Hmm?
I was chosen for my looks...?
Not for my voice...
Full Moon-sama
Waiting Room
Isn't she late?
That's right...
Maybe she got the place wrong...
Yes?
She's arrived.
Ah. She's here! She's here!
Sorry for being late.
Look! Look!
Isn't that a great poster?
I saw it.
It's the first time you've seen yourself like that, isn't it?
It was Takasu-san's idea
to go all-out and be flashy.
Well?
Were you surprised?
Ah.
I was.
Hmm?
Are you nervous?
N-No...
I've been through this before, too...
When you were an idol, right?
That's right.
The first stage I debuted on...
...was at a poolside in an amusement park, though.
Right in font of the stage, I was frozen stiff with nervousness.
After the other idols saw that, they taught me...
..at times like this...
...in the palm of your hand...
(Hitto: A Hit)
Write hitto.
Then, you take a deep breath.
If you do that, you won't get nervous.
Eh?
That's wrong, Ooshige-chan.
(Hito: Person)
Not hitto, it's hito.
Hito as in humans.
Eh?! Really?!
Then... then... I didn't make it because of that?!
Ah! I was tricked! Damn it!
Give me back my youth!
Give it back!
Give it back!!
Give it back!!!
I don't think that was why you didn't make it.
Mitsuki, be sure to write hito  properly.
O-Okay.
Ah...
Um... Ooshige-san.
Ah?
Hmm?
Was I chosen at the audition...
...because I look cute?
Who told you that?
Um...
Who...? Well...
My ears seem to be failing me.
Can you say that again?
It doesn't matter how well I sing...?
Of course it matters.
I don't know who told you this, but...
...you made the audition, and today's...
Um... you should get ready soon...
It's almost time.
That's right.
It's all in your hands now, then.
Okay!
Anyways...
Just focus on the live concert right now.
Ah... s-sure.
Come over here, then.
Oh... me too.
Wow! It's crazy outside!
There are lines all the way down the street.
I'll have to do a perfect job here.
I... wonder if I'll be able to sing.
Can I come in?
Yes!
Huh?
Where is she?
The bathroom.
I see.
Takasu-san.
Do you want to eat this?
It's a new potato product.
Hmm. It looks good.
With only your looks...
Having to sing in front of flocks of people...
It'd be best if you realized your position as soon as possible.
So you were up here, huh?
Takuto...
Takuto... I...
Ah?
No!
W-What are you doing?!
Ah!
My hair's all messed up!
You're so mean!
And they just made me look pretty...!
Hmph!
A singer who only depends on looks...
Of course you're concerned about your appearance, right?
Ah...
Have I said too much?
Should I beg for forgiveness, too?
The birth of the industry's first idol in disguise...
...you've become the topic of
discussion everywhere.
Hmph!
Where are you going?
Are you running away?
Sing like you're supposed to.
I'm going to sing.
Because that's my job.
Ah?
What?!
Eh?
W-What?
Who do you think you are,
saying it's just a job!
No matter how hard it gets...
...you're going to smile and do your best, because it's your job?!
I didn't say anything like that!
"Because it's my job..."
If you're going to have such
a cold attitude about it...
...you won't be able to
touch anyone's heart.
Eh?
You need to enjoy singing
from the heart first.
Ah.
I see...
That's right...
But...
Right now, I...
I haven't mentioned it before, but...
When you auditioned...
Back then, I...
...was surprised and moved.
Eh?
You sang with such a beautiful voice.
Somehow, it didn't seem like a voice...
...more like an aura of sound.
Even the lower tones came through clearly.
It was like a dream.
That such a singer existed...
...I was overjoyed.
Back then...
...I was happy, too!
It's been so long since
I'd sung in such a loud voice...
Breathing didn't hurt either.
It may seem normal to most people, but...
...to be able to use that kind of voice...
...makes me very happy!
Singing... is all about expressing
your feelings, isn't it?
If I sing without confidence...
...that's what the people
who are listening will hear.
Ah...
But, still... I...
It's fine. It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
Yep!
Okay! I'm going!
Ah!
Ah. Ooshige-san.
Mitsuki.
Over there. Look at that!
Eh?
What is this?
A huge mountain of postcards...
These are all advance orders sent to this store for your CD.
Eh?
It seems like a lot, but...
...these are just the orders from this store.
I
Full Moon's Debut Single...
I am placing an advanced
order for "Myself".
Please fulfill my request.
I heard it on the radio...
and loved it after
just one listen.
Full Moon's Debut Single...
I am placing an advanced order for "Myself".
Please fulfill my request.
I heard it on the radio...
and loved it after just one listen.
It's a really great song, isn't it?
It's the best!
I wonder what the girl who sang it is like.
I'm very interested.
She's a young girl, but...
...she has a pleasing voice.
It cleanses the soul.
This was the response to your publicity single that's airing on the radio.
Ah?
You weren't just "chosen for your looks."
You believe me, right?
Eichi-kun...
Becoming strong...
...is hard, huh?
But for now...
I'll keep walking forward.
Surely...
I'm...
...not alone.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then.
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all.
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
On that day I could see...
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Doushite kimi wo suki ni nattandarou
Why is it that I've fallen in love with you?
Kantan sugite kotaeru naranai
I can't find an answer easily...
Takasu-san!
What a trick you've set up!
That was an amazing display.
Ooshige-chan sure knows what she's doing...
It was wonderful, Takasu-san!
It was really wonderful, Ooshige-chan!
I just felt that I should do something for her.
Ah.
You're...
I've lost.
Eh?
I'm no match for you.
Your singing was too good.
It only makes sense that you were chosen.
Eh...?
Which is why...
...for saying all that...
...I'm ashamed of myself.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I have faith in my singing, but...
...I'm going to work even harder!
Me, too...
In order to share my
feelings with everyone...
...I have to work hard!
We have to both work hard, right?
You're right.
You really were here.
Thanks for earlier.
It wasn't much... just some
feathers floating around.
Not that...
Eh?
What you told me earlier...
You were trying to cheer me up, right?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just can't stand people who
hesitate and constantly worry.
Hey!
Are you listening to me?!
In the end... you got them across...
...your feelings, right?
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I couldn't sing at all
Nani mo utaenakatta
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Until we became so far apart...
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Preview
That girl's song...
It's a huge hit!
The kids at school are probably...
...all talking about Full Moon.
Of course!
Even the manager said it was a great hit.
Huh?
Nobody's talking about Full Moon, huh?
All right!
If nobody's heard of her...
...I'll let them all know!
Leave it to me!
Wait, Meroko!
If you go out, you'll let something slip again!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Is It Really a Hit?
Look forward to it!