Owari
Princess Hitei.
You're late.
How long were you planning on making me wait?
I'm terribly sorry, but...
Mask: "Unconcealed"
I don't want to hear excuses.
Getting here without being seen took some time.
Excuses like that won't make me any less angry.
Yes.
So, what's been happening with that unpleasant woman?
The strategian is headed towards Kyushu.
Apparently they were delayed, as they had just defeated Sabi Hakuhei.
After taking down Japan's strongest swordsman, they've been receiving endless challenges from swordsmen who want the title.
They are likely getting a lot of real battle experience as a result.
Sabi Hakuhei...
The man upon whom I bestowed the title of Japan's Strongest.
How foolish of them to get cocky merely from beating him.
I believe they will arrive at Satsuma shortly.
Which means their next target is Zokutou Yoroi...
It's quite arrogant of her to move ahead without even stopping back at Owari.
Considering that they've collected 4 of Shikizaki Kiki's 12 Perfected Deviant Blades,
of whom General Kyuu couldn't even find one, it's understandable.
I didn't ask what you think.
Yes.
But that's definitely like her.
Though we mustn't underestimate them.
Besides the strategian herself, that swordsman she has with her is...
Ah, the swordless swordsman?
What's his name?
The 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
Throughout their journey, this man has not once taken physical damage from his foes.
He's gotten by without even a scratch?
Right, without even a scratch.
Neither Uneri Ginkaku's Zerosen nor Tsuruga Meisai's Sentou could cut his body.
In Kyotouryuu, they forge their bodies as a sword.
Though, I should note that the Kyotouryuu school's strength lies not in offense but in defense.
Quite the lucky ticket she drew...
She has the devil's luck, as usual.
I look forward to future developments.
Zokutou Yoroi is a sword that boasts immeasurable defensive power.
Defensive strength vs. defensive strength...
I wonder how this will turn out...
Satsuma
Let the fight begin!
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
己をはらはら花に例えて　散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsumami aguneta guren no tama wo
摘みあぐねた紅蓮の霊を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarau kare no hi areshi mune yori
さらう彼の日　荒れし胸より
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
恐るるまま命は羽搏いて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
やがて　やがて　天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
朱く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai kira no yume wo ataeta mou
すれ違い綺羅の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabite meiyo ni samayoi
待ち侘びて冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
想いがはらはら舞う故に
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sora he egaite
絆を更なる空へ描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Zokutou
Yoroi
What's wrong?
Weren't you going to slash my armor in two with that sword you're so proud of?
Hey now, was your record five consecutive wins just a fluke?
Or do you feel like running away now that you're actually face to face with me?
Shut up!
That decoration of yours is like a sheet of paper before the strength of my sword!
Inakuzure.
Note: Crumple to denial
Inakuzure
You fool!
It's my win!
Winner!
Hey, Togame...
The sword broke...
What do we do now?
It looks like you haven't been paying attention to what I was saying again.
That swordsman was just a side character.
The person we're interested in is that warrior in armor.
The warrior in armor?
Yep.
The captain of the Yoroi Pirates, Azekura Kanara.
He is your opponent this time.
It looks like he's quite popular.
So wait, he wasn't using his sword for this battle?
Wrong.
That armor is Zokutou.
The armor?
One of 12 Perfected Deviant Swords, Zokutou Yoroi.
A Japanese sword modeled after western armor.
But it would appear that this sword has fallen into the hands of a rather troublesome person too.
Though, we were pretty lucky to catch a battle with Zokutou's owner right after arriving at the port.
Shichika, let's figure out where to stay.
I'll explain the details there.
Kyushu is well known for its hot springs.
It's a popular health resort with famous active volcanoes nearby.
and it's said that if you dig a hole anywhere, hot water will gush out.
After the mental and physical stress of their five month journey so far,
a hot spring inn was just what they needed.
Incidentally, it's mixed bathing.
They say this hot spring is supposed to help heal bruises and sprains.
How is it?
I can't really answer that,
since I haven't been injured anywhere.
Oh, right.
Though, a large bath like this feels great because I can stretch my legs out.
Shichika...
When we left the island, I said to you,
"Protect the swords, protect me, and protect yourself."
To tell you the truth, I'd thought that the last order would be the most difficult one,
but even after fighting all those formidable opponents, there isn't a single scratch on you.
Honestly, I'm really impressed.
What? That's not like you.
Really?
Don't tell me you feel accomplished just because we've succeeded in collecting four swords?
Of course not.
It's just...
Drink up.
Sake is kind of...
Just a little is fine, isn't it?
Or are you saying you don't want the sake I'm offering you?
Drink it!
Ugh...
So?
"It's just..." what?
It's just, you know...
We took back Hakutou Hari from Sabi Hakuhei just a few days ago, right?
Due to that, we have a little breathing room now in our sword collection journey.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
I'd already failed twice before...
To make up for those, I was kind of rushing ahead on things.
I see.
We started off by taking Zettou Kanna from Maniwa Koumori,
and now we've retrieved Hakutou Hari from Sabi Hakuhei.
So now, there's no need to rush.
We can slowly concentrate on collecting the rest without any worries.
Slowly?
Slowly and dirtily.
To tell you the truth, I had doubts about you in the beginning.
Well no, "doubt" is the wrong word.
But I've always been betrayed,
so I was afraid that you might leave me right after we obtained the swords.
That's cruel!
But I've recently decided that there's no need to worry about that.
This isn't a journey you can make while shouldering those kinds of worries.
Anyway, at this point I'm absolutely sure you won't suddenly betray me.
So you can rest assured.
What, after all this time?
I thought you loved me to pieces from the start.
No one decided that...
And anyway, didn't you seek out Kyotouryuu precisely because you wanted to avoid being betrayed like with Maniwani and Sabi?
Those who don't fight for money or for swords, the swordless swordsmen — Kyotouryuu.
I suppose...
And most importantly—
Love?
Exactly!
A man who will move for love.
I fell for you, so there's no way I'd betray you.
I've found new love for you every day of our journey these last five months.
It doesn't really show...
You don't seem like you'd do anything even though we're in a hot spring bath together.
What do you mean? You're the one who invited me.
I suppose...
Ah, that's right.
Stand up, Shichika.
I said stand up right there.
Okay...
You really do have a big body, now that I actually look.
You're on the slim side for your height, but nothing about you looks weak.
Haven't you gotten more muscular during our journey?
I have?
I don't really pay attention to that kind of stuff myself...
But if you say so, I guess so.
Why?
No reason.
Sorry for staring at you like that.
Now, let's talk about our plans.
You're not going to wear all those layers like usual?
Someone with no sense like you wouldn't understand,
but being able to lounge around at a hot spring inn is relaxing.
What do you think?
It's the first time you've seen me in a yukata!
What?
Never mind.
That armored warrior holds one of the Deviant Blades,
and that armor is itself is Zokutou Yoroi...
Is that possible?
Yes.
It might have been hard to tell from a distance, but the joints of the various parts of the armor are made of sharp blades.
It's the Deviant Blade that was made not with offense but defense as its primary focus — Zokutou Yoroi.
Remember how he completely shattered his opponent's sword.
It'll take a considerable amount of effort to put even a scratch on Zokutou.
I get that, but wait...
I'm not allowed to harm the swords at all, right?
Of course not.
However, there are a number of other ways we can win.
It's rare for you to come up with a plan that fast.
Even against an iron bulwark of armor, anyone can come up with a few ways to defeat it if they use their head.
For example?
Push him into the sea.
Even armor without any chinks would flood and suffocate its user if sunk.
And if we attach a strong chain to his foot or something, we can quickly pull it up after he drowns.
And if we clean it up properly afterwards, it won't rust.
Y-You sure come up with some evil plans...
We could also use heat.
We'll heat up the armor, making sure not to damage it.
Any kind of metal is easy to heat up, after all.
And then naturally, the insides would also heat up, killing the user.
What's the matter, Shichika?
N-Nothing...
But, okay...
If we're free to use backhanded methods, then we could just attack him when he's not wearing the armor.
I'd say that's more "obvious" rather than "backhanded"...
But that man...
Azekura Kanara would never take off that armor in front of anyone.
Our foe this time is definitely troublesome.
Let's be fully prepared before going into this...
That feels so good!
I see, it feels good there?
Though I've got to say, I feel a bit weird doing this...
Your feet have stopped!
Step on me more!
"Step on me more"?
It would feel great if you stepped lightly on my head.
I really can't...
I'd heard that the armor was big, but I didn't think it would be so huge.
Shichika, a difference in height leads directly to a difference in strength.
That sounds just like something little Togame would say.
Cheerio!
It's been a while since you hit me with a "cheerio".
Shut up.
Of course, small people have their own methods of fighting.
You can outmaneuver the opponent, and you're light.
But you aren't familiar with fighting like that, are you?
This time will be different.
You'll be fighting a giant man called Azekura Kanara.
Don't you have some sort of plan?
Not in regards to this, no.
The strategies of martial arts is a field I know nothing about.
Think for yourself.
An opponent larger than myself...
It's true, I've never thought about it...
Ma'am?
Stop! Hurry up and stop!
What is it?
Please excuse the late night interruption.
There's a person out front saying he'd like to meet you.
Who?
The Yoroi Pirates Captain, Azekura Kanara-sama.
I never expected you to actually come find us first.
Well no...
Shichika's reputation as a swordsman is common knowledge by now.
I should have anticipated this.
So?
What business does the effective ruler of this port city,
the Yoroi Pirates Captain Azekura Kanara-dono, have with simple travelers such as us?
Well, it isn't anything as grand as "business"...
I'd thought so when I saw you at the Obon Arena, but looking at you closer, you really are quite cute!
And I love the color of your hair!
Why thank you.
That armor also suits you quite well.
So, what business did you come here for?
I said it isn't anything as grand as business!
Azekura-dono, us simple travel—
You're no simple travelers.
The army general director in support of critical tasks under direct control of the Yanari Shogunate, Togame-dono,
and the 7th Kyotouryuu head.
You defeated Sabi Hakuhei in a duel on Ganryuu Island,
and even being swordless, you obtained the title of Japan's strongest swordsman, Yasuri Shichika-dono.
Calling the two of you simple travelers is rather absurd.
He even knows about Shichika's heritage...
You're currently collecting swords, correct?
I didn't come here to interrogate you or anything.
I'm a man of Kyushu.
As you're aware, and as you can see, I bear one of the 12 Perfected Deviant Blades that Shikizaki Kiki forged, Zokutou Yoroi.
You came here to tear this armor off me, right?
Maybe.
Assuming that's true, what of it?
As a pirate yourself, surely you're not shocked at the idea of having your own belongings taken from you?
I guess that's true.
To hurt others, you must be prepared to be hurt yourself.
I steal from others, so I have the resolve to be stolen from.
The same goes for the resolve to kill.
Resolve, huh...
No, nothing.
I see.
I didn't come here to make the first move or anything.
Well, you say that...
But here's what comes to mind first.
You've already had your men surround this inn, trapping us like mice.
I haven't brought anyone else with me.
I wonder.
Shichika.
Cheerio!
Huh?
What are you zoning out for?
Uh, sorry...
Kyotouryuu, huh...
I know it.
The hero of the rebellion.
The fact that you're the 7th generation head must mean that Yasuri Mutsue has retired?
Father's dead.
He, uh...
Well, he died.
What the heck's that?
Everyone has their own past.
But I would have preferred that you gained the title of Japan's strongest after you defeated me!
You're quite aggressive...
It's natural for anyone born a man to wonder who's stronger.
The title of Japan's strongest isn't something you carry around lightly.
I will agree with you there.
Now, Azekura-dono...
I'll ask you straight up.
You're aware of who we really are, as well as our true purpose.
So why did you, the owner of Zokutou Yoroi, come to this inn?
I doubt you came to hand over Yoroi as a present to the Shogunate.
Not a chance!
It would be the end of us as pirates if we were to show obedience to the Shogunate!
Pirates are fundamentally anti-government, anti-establishment.
Now, this is the important part, Togame.
Let's say that you manage to tear this armor off me.
What would you do after that?
Head for Shikoku?
No, if we manage to take Zokutou Yoroi from you, we'd probably head back to Owari for a bit.
By land? Sea?
Well we are at a port city, so I'd prefer sea if possible.
I'm sure there are boats that leave from Dakuon Port to Owari.
Indeed!
Satsuma
Ryuku
Tosa
Tanba
Owari
Musashi
(Edo)
Mutsu
(Shireizan)
Ezo
Boats here leave for Owari, Tosa in Shikoku, the capital of Kyoto, Edo, Shireizan...
Even Ryukyu or Ezo if you want. Endless possibilities!
After all, this is my port!
However!
If you really were to steal Zokutou Yoroi from me...
Do you really think you could leave my port safely?
He's already prepared?
He came to call us out on our plans before we even got down to work...
This man has read ahead quite a bit.
That being the case, you may like what I came here to say.
Let's hear it.
No matter who falls, the Shogunate will come out on top in the end.
Kyotouryuu.
Let's duel.
D-Duel?
Yeah.
If you can defeat me, I'll hand over Zokutou.
My pirate crew and everyone else in the city will stay out of it.
That sounds too perfect.
Of course, I have a few terms to go along with it.
Which are?
Just so you know, the Shogunate can't decriminalize active pirates.
We're not so bad off that we have to seek their exoneration.
I just want you to help me look good.
Look good?
The name "Yoroi Pirates Captain Azekura Kanara" is pretty well known in this area.
I want the duel to be held in Obon.
Why?
I forbid private fights here.
However, if you fight there, it's just business.
And win or lose, having Japan's strongest swordless swordsman fight will rile up the audience.
As a member of the Shogunate, I'm sure you'd be happy to see a revitalization of the local economy.
Are you trying to turn Shichika into an attraction?
That would be a cheap price to pay to get Zokutou, no?
Is he really going to wager his sword on something like that?
I suppose it's possible that he truly does just want to fight Shichika, the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head.
Is this the blade's poison at work too?
I still haven't heard the most important part yet, Azekura-dono.
If we beat you, we get Zokutou Yoroi,
along with safe passage back to Owari.
But what happens if you beat us?
You're considering the possibility that you'll lose?
That's pretty timid of you.
If you defeat us, what are you looking for as a reward?
There's no way he'd let us go for nothing.
He's most likely after the four swords we've already obtained.
Good call.
If I win...
I'll take you, Togame.
I see, I see...
What?
Y-You don't want our swords?
Swords?
I don't care about those.
The one I have is more than enough.
I'd rather have you, Togame.
I've fallen in love at first sight.
Please be my woman!
Even if he loses, you'll still come out on top.
Because, if you become my woman, I'll take over that guy's position.
I'd always thought that if someone from the Shogunate dared step foot here, I'd send them back without their head,
but I've changed my mind after seeing you.
I want to help you out, from the bottom of my heart.
As a tactician, you should see how good this deal is.
Having the pirates as allies would definitely be beneficial...
Kyotouryuu's fourth secret technique:
Note: Red blossom and green willows
Ryuuryoku Kakou!
Ryuuryoku Kakou
Alright...
I see.
So this is your armor-piercing technique.
Quite splendid.
This mirror was pretty expensive, though...
Well, whatever.
So you're able to deal damage anywhere you want with this technique?
Well, basically yes.
I can strike skin, muscle, organs, bones, or anything else.
My father told me that the trick to this technique is the conduction of the shock from the impact,
but I just go with my instincts.
Instincts?!
You used something as unreliable as that and aimed at my stomach?!
What if I died?!
I didn't really think that far.
If I had known that, I wouldn't have participated!
Change my sash, Shichika.
Okay.
What are you doing?!
I just felt like teasing you a bit.
Why?!
If you play tricks with your superhuman strength, my body will break!
Geez, what were you thinking?
Togame.
What did you think about that guy's proposal?
I'd already decided a while ago.
In fact, I had already decided when Azekura was still standing in front of us.
I slept so well last night that I didn't even dream—
What are you doing?!
I wonder myself...
I somehow got the urge to tease you...
This is bullying already!
You just kicked me!
Come on, aren't you always hitting me?
Now we're even!
You're being rather rebellious today...
So, what's your decision?
I shouldn't have to say.
His proposal is just what we need.
If we simply accepted his proposition on the spot then we would seem too willing.
I just wanted to make him wait a little.
No, I don't mean that...
Would Azekura Kanara be suitable as your bodyguard?
Well, it's true that the pirate's information network would be more useful than any clout the Shogunate carries from this point on—
What are you doing?!
I don't know.
My hand just moved...
Don't play around with a woman's hair!
It seems a little late to be saying that...
But anyway, how about this?
We get the Yoroi Pirates to cooperate with us in the shadows, and you and I continue to collect the swords.
Azekura probably wouldn't accept that.
It's probably true that he wants to fight Japan's strongest swordsman,
but beyond that, assuming what he said was true, Azekura probably just sees you as an obstacle.
An obstacle?
That's how he sounded.
As a man, he'd want to monopolize his woman.
So I guess that's not a bad proposal then...
No.
It could have any number of catches.
It's not something I can trust.
In the end he's a pirate, after all.
But didn't you say you can trust in someone who moves for love?
I suppose I did say that.
You may look grown up, but you sure say some childish things...
What do you mean by that?
Well...
Tell me what you think about this then.
What if that man become my bodyguard in place of you?
What would happen to me in that case?
That depends on the result of the duel.
If you die, you die.
If you barely manage to survive...
I guess you'd go back to Nanami on Fushou Island.
That's...
....not what I want.
You don't want that?
But... I guess...
If you're saying that you could collect swords more easily that way—
Cheerio!
Even for me, the tip of a toe hurts!
Is that as far as your attachment to me goes?
Listen, Shichika!
As far as I'm concerned—
Excuse me...
What is it?
A letter has arrived for you.
A messenger from Azekura?
From whom?
I don't know his name, but...
he was quite charming.
I've accepted many jobs from you, but this is the first time we've met face to face, Togame-dono.
No... Strategian-dono.
This is indeed the first time we've met, but I've heard a lot about you.
Commander of the Bird Squad and one of the 12 heads.
You're essentially the Maniwa Corps leader.
Maniwa Houou-dono.
Note: Houou = Phoenix
I'm certainly not the leader.
You're overstating my position.
I merely took on a provisional directorial role, since I have comparatively more common sense than the others.
Don't let your guard down.
This man is in a different league from the other 11 heads.
You have no need to put up your guard.
As I wrote in my letter, I just want to have a talk with the strategian.
Do you think I can believe that?
How many people do you think I've had to bow down my head to in shame because of you?
And yet you accepted my request and came out to meet me.
Doesn't that mean you intend to talk with me?
I want to avoid any further business with the Maniwa Corps if possible,
but if I know you're around, I can have you removed.
I should eliminate that which I can.
One arm.
If you listen to what I have to say, I will cut off my left arm for you.
You can have the arm of one of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads,
and in your words, the effective leader, just for listening to what I have to say.
I offer you one arm just to listen, that's all.
How about it?
I don't really...
There you go.
I am also fully prepared to cut off my right arm too, if you'd like.
N-No, that's fine...
I'll hear you out.
But you won't mind if Shichika stays, right?
No, I have no problem with him hearing this.
The 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika, right?
I believe you were acquainted with Koumori, Shirasagi, and Kuizame.
You're well informed.
Well technically—
We haven't been able to contact Chouchou, Mitsubachi, or Kamakiri from the Insect Squad.
Might that also be your doing?
No, I don't know anything about that.
I see.
Either way, this means that in just half a year, the Maniwa Corps heads has lost half its members.
We may have been wrong in betraying you, Strategian-dono.
Well, there was no real choice for our troubled Maniwa village to begin with, but I won't go there.
We'll have to make do with the remaining 6 of us.
Do you think you can do it?
No, rather,
do you think we'd let you?
I don't suppose you would.
There is currently a three-way face-off between the sword owners, yourselves, and us.
For us to continue fighting for the swords would be reckless.
And that is why, Strategian-dono, I wish to propose a temporary alliance between us.
Alliance??
Did you come all the way to Kyushu just to make fun of me?
You could call it a mere temporary truce.
We wouldn't have had so much trouble if it were that easy.
We're after the same thing.
It's true that we are both seeking the same thing, but not quite in the same way.
We would be happy to obtain just two or three swords.
Meaning?
We could just aim for them in the opposite order to that which you are following.
So we'd avoid fighting each other for each sword?
Exactly.
Given that I'm lacking intel, it's a worthwhile move to leave the Maniwani at large for a while.
Even if they succeed, all we'd need to do is steal the swords back from them.
Of course, if these negotiations break down, I'll have to fight with you right here,
but personally I'd rather not.
Is that a threat?
No, it's not a threat...
...yet.
Instant battle if we refuse...
And against Maniwa Houou, what a creepy guy...
I still don't have enough information.
Soutou Kanazuchi.
Note: Hammer, the Pair
That's the last sword I know the whereabouts of.
Of course, that will be the next sword we aim for.
If you go after other swords, we won't clash.
Alliance formed, then.
It's not an alliance.
It's a temporary truce.
This helps. Thank you.
Mutsu's Mountain of Spirits.
Tendou in Dewa.
And Edo.
There appear to be Perfected Deviant Blades in these three locations.
Why are you telling me this?
Consider it a gesture of gratitude for accepting my one-sided demands.
What is he scheming...
And it would appear that Princess Hitei in Owari has begun to move.
Princess Hitei?
Wait Houou, what exactly is that woman up to?!
Who knows? But I suggest you deal with it quickly.
You have my thanks.
For the time being, I'll trust you on today's talk.
But if you break the promise and we run into each other collecting a sword...
My sword will cut you down without hesitation.
Understood.
Well then, I'll be off.
Ah yes, there was one more thing.
I heard that you've been hitting your subordinate, followed by saying "cheerio".
I'd been thinking something seemed wrong with it, but after coming to Satsuma I've finally figured out what it is.
You should be saying "chest".
"Cheerio" actually means "goodbye" in the language of a foreign land.
N-N...
Nooooo!!
No, no, no!
This is a misunderstanding! A misunderstanding!!
Wait, wait, wait a minute!
I don't think I'm stupid!
I'm not stupid!
I'm not embarrassed! I don't get embarrassed!
I'm not mistaken!
H-H-He's the mistaken one!
Gyafun!
Is it that bad?
You have it wrong, all wrong!
Sh-Shichika!!
Yes?
Shichika, Shichika, Shichika, Shichika!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
You should understand!
It's not that I was mistaken!
I'm not wrong!
Um...
It was just a once off... once off...
No, I mean...
It was deliberate!
D-Deliberate?
Right, deliberate!
Who do you think I am?
I'm the army general director in support of critical tasks under direct control of the Yanari Shogunate, Togame the Strategian!
Logistics, schemes, war strategies, army plans, I can handle anything!
There's no way I didn't know that "cheerio" was a foreign word!
I... see...
So why were you saying it deliberately?
Because...
Ahh, whatever!
Lose your memory!
Forget, forget, forget!
Even if you tell me to...
Besides, don't you think it's embarrassing?
Just think, how many times, how many dozens of times have I yelled "cheerio" while punching you up until now?!
W-Well... that's true...
And each time, watching bystanders were thinking,
"Why on earth is that white-haired girl saying farewell while punching someone?"
No, I can deal with those!
That's still okay!
The problem is after arriving here at Satsuma!
For example, what do you think that Azekura guy thought when he saw me punch you with a "cheerio!" last night?
Yeah, you've been using "cheerio" quite often since we got to Satsuma.
He definitely thought I was an idiot!
The only impression people have been left with is "what an idiot"!
Is there any worse disgrace?
Well, I understand where you're coming from...
But why does that mean I have to think it's embarrassing?
I might have been the one to say it, but you didn't know it was wrong either!
Well...
Actually, I did.
Cheerio!!
Local pirates?
How about you tell us what you were talking about with them?
Luring them out was fine and all, but they turned out to be small fries...
What?!
What the hell did you say?!
Count yourselves as fortunate.
There aren't many people who can die to my ninpou.
Ninpou: Danzaien
Note: Decapitation ring
Captain!
They've accepted your proposal, Captain!
Right.
Ryuukyuu
Chest! Chest!
Oh yeah, didn't we want a chore boy?
Polish that armor up nicely.
5 \years
later
Kanara.
Why don't you try that armor on?
I had never forgotten.
That woman...
Making me remember such unpleasant things...
How effective will Shichika's armor piercing be?
He really is popular.
I'll tell you this now, Kyotouryuu.
I'm the kind of guy who can't hold back once I've gotten going.
You will either die here,
or if not, definitely sustain some pretty serious injuries.
And if that makes the lady I've fallen for sad, there's no helping that.
If you surrender right after the match starts,
you'll be able to leave this arena unharmed.
Shichika, for this battle...
If you can, I'd like you to win without killing Azekura or permanently incapacitating him.
What a demand.
Could Togame possibly be thinking it's okay for me to lose this?
Hey, don't ignore me.
No, stop looking at my woman!
It doesn't look like you'll do me the favor of surrendering, but that's fine.
Just put up a fight, okay?
Show the townspeople the skills of the man who defeated Sabi Hakuhei.
You don't need to tell me that.
However, by that point you'll be torn into pieces.
That's the stance he used when he fought Uneri Ginkaku...
What is he planning to do?
Let the fight...
I'll finish this in one hit.
...begin!
He vanished?!
I'll show you my skills, but I don't intend to put on a show!
Kyotouryuu: Ryuuryoku Kakou!
He landed it!
What the hell is that?
Gothic!
What's wrong?
Why can you still move?
My attack should have landed.
Did you use an armor-piercing attack, perhaps?
So Kyotouryuu has those too...
You're underestimating Zokutou Yoroi.
I'm afraid Yoroi won't even let armor-piercing attacks through.
Already out of ideas?
Round Gothic!
Kaishotai!
Mincho!
I see you're good at running around and dodging.
Ryuuryoku Kakou!
What a bad loser, Kyotouryuu.
It's disappointing to think you're my predecessor.
You have some nerve to call yourself Japan's Strongest.
Have the resolve to accept your defeat as Yoroi's prey.
Resolve...
What is resolve?
If Azekura is more skilled as a sword, should I concede victory?
Accept it and have the resolve...
Idiot!!
Togame?
What are you doing, giving up?!
I don't remember giving you permission to do that!
I told you to win!
Weren't you listening, you fool?
Listen, Shichika.
As far as I'm concerned,
a man who can't even show his face to the woman he's fallen for is worthless!
What fun would there be in traveling with a guy I couldn't get into a hot spring with?
There's no way I'd trust a man like that!
Togame...
So what if one of the Kyotouryuu techniques didn't work?
So what if you can't use Kyotouryuu here?
Even if you don't have armor, you've got that body you forged like steel for 20 years, right?
If you really have fallen for me,
then protect me with brute force!
Understood, loud and clear.
Kyotouryuu, first stance: Lily of the Valley.
How careless of me to lose sight of my simple nature.
I've been thinking too much lately.
It's bad not to think things through, but overthinking isn't good either.
Bring it, Mr. Rejected.
I hadn't intended it, but the crowd has seen quite a show already.
Don't get cocky...
I'm a pirate.
If there's something I want, I just get rid of anything in my way and steal it.
If you want to steal, then go ahead.
But isn't that Zokutou made for defense?
People with something to protect are strong.
This is a technique exclusive to Zokutou Yoroi that was passed down through the Yoroi Pirates.
Touzoku Kamome!
Note: Blade gulls
Touzoku Kamome
Shichika!
Those with large bodies are strong...
But that doesn't mean the bigger you are, the stronger you are!
That's the way!
You were relying a little too much on Kyotouryuu.
It's all you've known for 20 years, so it's not surprising,
but it's definitely not the only thing you've got on your side.
Even without using clever moves, you're more than strong enough with that tempered body of yours.
Damn you, Kyotouryuu!
This isn't swordsmanship or anything!
You have my thanks, Azekura Kanara.
Thanks to you, I finally understand.
My existence may boil down to that of a single sword,
but at the same time, I'm also a single human being.
Also Azekura, there's one more thing I want to say.
Don't touch my woman!
Winner!
Apparently you resemble the Captain's long dead younger sister, Togame-san.
He was saying that if she were still alive, she'd be about the same age as you.
How is he?
Oh, he didn't sustain any serious injuries.
He was back on his feet in no time.
So he's not going to come to see us off...
Well, what will be, will be.
Just as you're more than strong enough even without using Kyotouryuu,
Azekura Kanara is more than strong enough without Zokutou Yoroi.
Though, I'm sure it'll take some courage for Azekura to show himself in front of others after having been hidden all this time.
You should have gone to see him.
I'm not so cruel as to give a rejected man false hopes.
Rather, I think it'd be more polite if I were to leave quickly.
Really?
Anyway, something's been bugging me these past few days...
What?
How did you know that "cheerio" was wrong?
I'd just heard it from my father.
Though, you were saying it so boldly that I thought maybe I'd remembered wrong.
I see.
Cheerio!
So she's decided to stick with "cheerio"...
After some time, the two of them will be shocked when they realize the boat's course.
It was Azekura's revenge for being rejected by Togame.
Their boat wasn't actually headed for Owari,
but was set to sail slowly round the Sea of Japan and eventually arrive at the cold lands of Ezo.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
tasogare zo
黄昏ぞ
Say twilight
watashi wo terasu nara
私を照らすなら
If you cast a light on me
kokoro mo sunao ni somete okure
心も素直に　染めておくれ
color my heart to become open on this occasion
itsu no hi ka na mo naki kobune no you ni
いつの日か　名もなき小舟のように
Someday like a small nameless boat
tayutau nasake wo uchiake te mitai
たゆたう情けを　打ち明けてみたい
I'd like to confess my wavering affection
me no mae ni arawaru kakugo no shima he
目の前に現る　覚悟の島へ
Toward the approaching island where we risk our life
tomo miuketa ima
とも見受けた今
At the moment when we took in the scene
ushiro no namishibuki ga tooku natta
後ろの波しぶきが遠くなった
the sea spray in the back faded in the distance
yasashiku nareru yo to
優しくなれるよと
You can be tender
tomo ga noru fune
伴が乗る舟
the boat where my companion is aboard said
konoyo de hitori dake
この世で一人だけ
In the world he is the only one
makoto wo azukeyou ka
誠を預けようか
whom I wonder if I entrust my cordiality to
yasashii asu ga kuru
優しい明日が来る
Gentle tomorrow will come
haruka kanata no
遥か彼方の
in a faraway place
maboroshi oikake te tadoritsuita kaze no mukou ni
幻追いかけて　辿り着いた風の向こうに
where we chased an illusion and reached beyond a wind
atsui kaze no mukou ni
熱い風の向こうに
Beyond the hot wind
N-No, you've got it wrong!
I knew that "cheerio" was a foreign word!
I really knew!
So forget about this incident!
Got that? Forget it!
"Cross your heart and hope to die"
There, you promised Togame the strategian!
Now, our next destination...
What? Ezo?!
It's cold!
Cold! Cold! Cold!
I'm dying! I'm gonna die!
Next time on Katanagatari: Soutou Kanazuchi.
Soutou
Kanazuchi
Ch-Cheerio!