Oh!
It's the script!
The script for our brand-new Starlight is here!
Amemiya-san was up all night finishing it, all by herself.
When we saw how much effort Group A was putting in,
we decided that we couldn't let Group B be outdone.
This is still just the first draft.
We're gonna make it even better from here on out.
For today, I'd like to hear what you think of it.
I shouldn't need to mention how important the 100th Seisho Festival is.
Let's make it the best stage possible!
Yeah!
Can we make this part here longer?
Not shorter?
I feel like it would look more impressive during the fight scene if it were longer.
I see.
The design sketches for this year's goddess costumes?
Yeah, I got a lot of ideas from Hanayagi-san.
Really?
Like this headdress on last year's costumes.
Its silhouette made it look a touch heavy,
so I thought to remove it and emphasize the jewels on the forehead.
C'est bien! Very nice!
You are fortunate,
for you know not the tragedy your transgression will bring down upon you.
This line for the Goddess of Despair
is different from before!
It looks like there's been other changes as well.
But I think I like it better this way!
It's like the Goddess of Despair's sorrow
and her, um... hoddiness?
You mean her haughtiness?
Yeah, that's it! It's really well conveyed!
It's the same play,
but the lines and pacing have all improved.
"Life is as tedious as a twice-told tale."
Huh?
It's a quote from William Shakespeare.
You don't know it?
My life isn't boring!
That's not what it means.
A life is only lived once.
To merely repeat the same story is meaningless.
That's why we must always be
seeking out new challenges for ourselves.
Even if it's a repeat performance, we must change and grow to create an even greater stage.
That's what I think it means.
I get it! That's totally right!
Even though it's the same—
no, because it's the same play.
We must create an even better stage.
Is that not the very reason these auditions are held?
Even the casting for the main roles is subject to change.
Not just something different.
This repeat performance will display the results
of the 99th cohort's diligent effort and improvement.
It's starting again, huh?
We've got a new script this time around.
I like it.
I see.
Nana?
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Who shall be the one to grasp hold of that Star?
To stand at the peak of that tower?
A quietly kindled flame now blazes and consumes my heart
Whatever fate might bring
We dance on this stage of our own will
to
bi
ta
te
And we take flight!
I AM REBORN
I'm certain of what I saw on that day
The sparkle of those scattering stars
Shine on me until my fingers touch yours
From across a promise faded by time
The true story begins before the curtain rises
And it unfolds before our very eyes
It's here, in the place where I was reborn
That I found you once more
I wonder what's wrong with Banana.
Did something happen?
I've never seen her act like that.
I really like this Starlight, though.
You really adore Starlight, don't you?
Well of course I do!
It was the first performance I ever saw,
and it's why I became a Girl of the Stage!
You adore it too, right Hikari-chan?
Yes.
Huh? Is that...
a script book for Starlight?
I found it in London.
Whoa, it's all in English.
I'll translate for you.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to help you.
It's alright.
I asked you to do double-duty as our club advisor to try and keep this club going,
7th Middle School
Cultural Festival
When Passion Awakens
7th Middle School
Cultural Festival
When Passion Awakens
but everyone else's clubs are important too.
Daiba-san, why don't you try applying to Seisho Music Academy?
The Starlight Gatherers' Tower, right?
They say they're going to rebuild it for this year's festival.
Really? It's gonna get really busy again.
Working late into the night was rough,
but those were really fulfilling, memorable times.
It feels like such a long time ago,
even though it's only been two months.
It's going to start again soon.
The 99th Seisho Festival's Starlight.
Huh?
You know, I was always alone.
But once I came to this school I was able to make friends with whom I could truly perform.
I was able to stand on the stage.
My first production and my greatest friends.
Nana?
I have to protect it. My Starlight.
Starlight.
It's the story of goddesses drawn by the glow of the heavens.
The tale of a distant planet,
of a time long past,
and a time far, far into the future.
In a small village, in a small country,
the Festival of the Star is celebrated each year.
Beneath the rain of stars that falls once a year,
I, Flora and...
...I, Claire...
...were drawn by fate to meet.
It seems to me that we have always been together, since long ago.
Let us meet here again next year...
...on the eve of the Festival of the Star.
Pluck only a tiny Star and you will obtain
chiisana hoshi wo tsunda nara
The two were bound by their promise.
But the year that they both turned sixteen, on the eve of the Festival of the Star...
A long year has passed and
at last we meet again, dear Claire.
But a tiny measure of happiness
anata wa chiisana shiawase wo te ni ireru
Who are you?!
Claire!
I don't understand! Your voice, your warmth,
Pluck a great Star, and you will reap
ooki na hoshi wo tsunda nara
the promise I made with you...
I remember how precious that memory was to me.
But I have no memory of that night at all!
A reward equally great
anata wa ooki na tomi wo te ni ireru
On the eve of the Festival of the Star the year before,
Claire was badly injured on her way home and lost her memories.
Pluck both Stars, and unto you
sono ryouhou wo tsunda nara
There may be a way to restore them.
Tonight is the Festival of the Star, which comes only once a year.
If we can ascend the Starlight Gatherers' Tower
and pluck that Star at its peak,
An eternal wish will be granted
anata wa eien no negai wo te ni ireru
then Claire, your memories may...
Let us go,
to pluck that Star together!
Pluck only a tiny Star and you will obtain but a tiny measure of happiness.
Pluck a great Star, and you will reap a reward equally great.
To gather the Starlight grants forgiveness' light
hoshitsumi wa tsumi wo yurushi
Pluck both Stars, and unto you an eternal wish shall be granted.
Gather the Starlight, miracle of the night
hoshitsumi wa yoru no kiseki
The light of the Stars is the light of the people
hoshi no hikari wa hito no hikari
"To gather the Starlight grants forgiveness' light.
Gather the Starlight, miracle of the night."
Following the song's words, the pair made their way to the Starlight Gatherers' Tower.
Your light is the light of the Star
anata no hikari ga hoshi no hikari
However...
Who goes there?!
For 500 years, they had been confined to the Tower.
And it shall be bestowed upon you,
omochinasai
Goddesses of sin—sleeping, awaiting their deaths.
The Star which you have longed for
anata no nozonda sono hoshi wo
Rage.
Avoidance.
Arrogance.
Torpor.
Jealousy.
Despair.
Please, allow us to pluck a Star for Claire!
We have no Star for you!
Why were they imprisoned there?
What crimes had they committed?
Over the great span of time,
those Goddesses had forgotten even that.
Pluck only a tiny Star and you will obtain
chiisana hoshi wo tsunda nara
Alas, the wheel turns once again.
The cycle of despair shall repeat beneath the light of those Stars.
But a tiny measure of happiness
anata wa chiisana shiawase wo te ni ireru
While the Goddesses' black emotions cut at the pair,
they climbed to the summit of the tower.
Beyond here lies Claire's star.
Pluck a great Star, and you will reap
ooki na hoshi wo tsunda nara
And it shall be bestowed upon you, the star which you have longed for.
My eyes! I can't see!
A reward equally great
anata wa ooki na tomi wo te ni ireru
Claire! Where are you, Claire?!
Claire!
I remember your name.
Pluck both Stars, and unto you
sono ryouhou wo tsunda nara
I'm sorry, Flora.
Our dream could never have come true.
An eternal wish will be granted
anata wa eien no negai wo te ni ireru
Her eyes burned by the Stars' radiance,
Flora fell down from the tower.
She was separated from Claire for the rest of eternity.
And above them
the stars continued to shine forever.
Starlight.
This is a tale of a distant planet, of a time long, long past,
and a time far, far away in the future.
It's good.
Yes, it's good.
For the sake of her friend,
she thinks nothing of the danger.
Flora bravely tries to bring about a miracle.
Even though she lost her memory,
she at least remembered her promise to her friend.
Claire has such strength.
It's good!
Yeah, it's good.
This is a treasure! A treasured book!
It's old, and it's thick, and it's heavy!
It's just an ordinary old book. Nothing all that special about it.
Huh? But...
The really special thing is
the kind of stage we can create from it, and the kind of Stars we can become.
Don't you think?
Yeah!
We need to turn our next Starlight into the greatest stage!
The greatest stage, the most precious friends,
I want to protect it all.
For the fated stage,
I chose to repeat that year's performance.
The fated stage?
You mean that giraffe's...?
I haven't gone up against you this time around, have I?
You said it yourself, Junna-chan.
"Those were really fulfilling, memorable times."
That it was the greatest year!
I wanted that time to continue forever.
That's why I'm repeating it.
My eternal stage, that fabulous year.
What are you saying, Nana?
But since that day,
since Hikari-chan transferred in,
things have been weird.
My Junna-chan definitely isn't called Jun-Jun.
She can't get away with this.
Huh?
A script like that means nothing to me.
Everything is changing.
The next Starlight?
That's not my Starlight at all!
Nana...
If I want this cycle to continue
I can't afford to lose to anyone.
How did it end up like this?
What happened to this repeat performance?
Hikari-chan's participation in the audition made eight.
Karen-chan, who always came in last,
was cut from the cast.
But,
when Karen-chan leapt in...
It wasn't Hikari-chan?
The person responsible for all these changes
is Karen-chan?
I AM REBORN
This stage is a great tree,
its limbs laden with ripening fruit.
Those fruits, so fragile and tender—
they must be protected!
Student of the 99th cohort, Daiba Nana!
I will protect them.
No matter how many times it takes! Forever!
Banana...
We will now begin the seventh day of auditions with this Revue of Bonds.
kesshite dare ni mo jama wa sasenai
I will not allow a single soul to interfere
watashi dake no eien no butai
With the the everlasting stage that I create here
Bond of the Stars
A Revue of Bonds
All these changes in my repeat performance—
It was you, Karen-chan!
Starlight is an eternal tale told by eight!
There is no room for a ninth!
What then is your role?
Just who are you?
You're not the Karen-chan I know!
This isn't the repeat performance I know!
What did Hikari-chan do to change things so?!
What made you change?
What happened between you and Hikari-chan to make things so different?
I'm going to do Starlight with Hikari-chan!
I hate it!
I hate Starlight!
henka wa higeki wo
Change will only invite tragedy
To be separated from your dear friend—
tomare, tomare
Stop, stop now
a tragedy like that is far too cruel!
So I'll protect them.
I need to protect everyone!
Here in my repeat performance,
I must defeat you!
Or my repeat performance will come to an end!
That's a big non, non, Banana!
A Girl of the Stage evolves day by day!
We cannot stay the same, and neither can the stage!
sora mo kagayaku
The sky's radiance shines on
Each stage exists only for a moment,
kinou mo, kyou mo, ima mo
Yesterday and tomorrow, and even now
that one instant where it burns bright!
That's what makes it so precious,
so irreplaceable, what gives it its meaning!
umaretate no hoshi ga watashi ga todoku
The newborn star created here
In that instant, every Girl of the Stage
is consumed in flames,
anata ni
I'll show it to you
to be reborn every time she takes the stage!
You can't do this, Karen-chan!
The repeat performance must go on!
Or else!
Karen-chan!
taisetsu ni mamotte itai dake
My only wish is to protect what's most precious to me
No! You can't!
I'm sorry, Nana.
taisetsu ni mamotta watashitachi wa tsuyoku naru no
I met my precious one, and we both grow stronger
I will go.
I'm going to pluck that Star, together with Hikari-chan!
Karen-chan, what made you so radiant?
What made you so dazzling?
tsunagatta no, hoshi no kizuna
The bond of the Stars that connects us
itsumademo mamoru yo
I will protect it, for all time
The seventh day of auditions is over.
You forgot this.
You were always watching over us, weren't you?
So many times, all alone.
I wanted to protect everyone.
Was I so wrong to do that?
"But men are men, the best sometimes forget."
That's William Shakespeare.
"Time travels in diverse paces with diverse persons."
That's also from Shakespeare.
More.
More?
L-Let's see...
"He who moves not forward goes backward!"
"The future influences the present just as much as the past."
Nietzsche.
"It is never too late to be what you might have been."
George Eliot.
"The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make one."
Elbert Hubbard.
What else?
What else?!
Um...
"Upon every person shines a Star of fate.
A Star shining at night, or twinkling in the dawn.
A Star that shoots across the sky.
Even if the Star meant for me is hidden from view,
I will raise my eyes to the heavens, and on this day...
Student of the 99th cohort, Hoshimi Junna!
...I will grasp it, here and now. My own Star!"
That's...
My own words.
Wh-What's so funny?!
This is the first time I've seen you have so much fun.
No fair!
Making fun of me when I hardly know a thing about you, Nana!
Maybe I was too greedy.
Huh?
I did my best to make that year even more fun,
to bring everyone even closer.
Each time around, I played with the lines a bit
and added to the performance.
But Hikari-chan showed up, and Karen-chan changed,
and everyone else started changing too.
It felt like everyone was turning their back on my repeat performance, and I got scared.
But these new days are so exciting
and the new people you've become are so fascinating.
I didn't know what to do.
Is that all?
You're really a Girl of the Stage now.
We'll make it an even greater stage than before.
That stage and the girls who stand on it will continue to change.
You're a Girl of the Stage. You'll be fine.
So let's make it together, Nana.
Let's make the next Starlight together.
I'm sorry.
I... I...
Who would have thought that a big girl like you could be such a crybaby?
You're like a kid.
This...
You should keep it.
The time that you treasured so dearly and the things you gave your all to protect.
Take them all with you
to the next stage!
Yeah!
From time to time I feel such great unease, for, you see,
I can't help but feel that you will go, leaving me
Don't let your shining eyes reflect another's light
Nobody else but me
star
star
oh, fly me to the star
Little bird, whose song heralds the coming of dawn,
Won't you stop the hands of the clock for me?
A shooting star softly slips through the morning sky
And scatters to the earth
star
Oh, fly me to the Star
The last day of auditions has arrived.
I understand.
Shoujo Kageki Revue Starlight.