Welcome to the Velvet Room.
You've obtained the Fortune Arcana with your newest bond.
You are truly magnificent to have acquired so many new powers, one after another.
Only another heart can penetrate into the depths of one's heart.
The answer is Narukami Yu if you multiply it by Margaret.
Our hearts will—
Oh my, I forgot to multiply myself by something.
I was merely testing your level of understanding.
Congratulations. You passed.
Hide and seek it wants to play again
Like a detective, I won't let it get away
It's constantly costuming with loads of fake
I will strip search if I have to
Though I'm not afraid to know it, don't know how
I am so determined
To chase after what's hidden and seize this day, this moment
WANNA KNOW
Enter key to accelerate
WANNA GO
Ignition turned on
It's about that time to drive to truth
WANNA SEIZE
Stranger than in movies
Ignorance is not bliss
They say that truth will out
Can't keep on hiding
There's no turning back now
I'm gonna go on
I'm gonna go get what I want
I'm back! I'm the unlucky ninja, Mr. Experiment!
Here, Nanako.
Oh, thanks, Daddy.
You drink coffee, don't you?
Thanks.
No problem.
When I got married, I promised her mother that the least I could do was make the coffee.
It's become a bit of a habit.
It's good.
Drink up while it's still hot.
All right then.
Daddy, can you read to me?
Sure, what book?
Jack and the Beanstalk
A picture book of famous folktales
from around the world
This one.
Just a sec.
It's Dojima.
What?!
Okay, I'm on my way.
Sorry, but I've got work.
I might not make it back today.
Okay.
Take care...
A hit-and-run near Samegawa, huh?
Come to think of it, didn't your wife pass away in a car accident?
What's wrong, Big Bro?
I need a bandage.
Oh, it's a picture of Mom!
It's from when we went to Samegawa!
So this is where it went.
What do you mean?
Well,
Daddy put away all of our pictures of Mom.
What?
He did that right after she died in a car accident.
I don't know much about it since Daddy won't tell me anything.
Do you think he'd get angry if I kept this picture?
I'll ask him for you.
Okay, thanks!
I feel sorry for Daddy since he lost Mom.
Yeah...
I love Daddy!
I'm sure he feels the same.
Yeah! I think so too!
Uh, um...
What is it?
I love you too, Big Bro.
Why did God have to create tests?
Who cares? Let's just get to work.
Hanamura, I want a melon soda.
Then go buy one!
Oh, come on!
If you get me one, I'll let you borrow the notes I copied from Yukiko.
Whoa, seriously?!
Hey, couldn't I just borrow them from her in the first place?
She has better handwriting.
So close!
Guys!
Hey!
Huh? Nanako's with you today?
She made plans with Teddie.
I've been waiting, Nana!
A bear-y good day to you!
A bear-y good day to you too!
Nana, let's go on a date!
Okay!
Big Bro, good luck!
I'll give you a present if you get the highest test score.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go, Nana!
Man, I'm so jealous of Teddie right now!
That's enough complaining.
Let's start off with trigonometric identities.
The real you?
That's right.
You see, I still don't know who I really am.
My memories start with me living in that other world, not here.
I think I might've been someone special.
But then things started getting weird,
and that's when I ran into everyone and asked for their help.
Then I came to this world.
Uh, do you get what I'm saying?
Oh, I bet you're a king!
I read in a book that a bad guy cursed the king,
so he had to wander through the forest alone.
Now that you mention it, that could be it.
I hope you break the spell soon, Teddie!
Thank you, Nana!
What are those two talking about?
Beats me.
It looks like they're having fun.
I'm back.
Um...
What is it?
I stumbled upon this.
Nanako seems to really like it,
so could we leave it out?
I think you know her better than I do.
You decide.
Daddy, you're back!
What is it, Nanako?
Well, Daddy, um...
Today at school, I got a...
Nanako?
My tummy really hurts.
Are you okay?
Was it something you ate?
The bottom of my tummy feels all prickly.
What? We should call a doctor!
No, wait. Hasn't this happened before?
Does it feel like that one time?
I'm not sure.
Crap... I think I put that medicine...
Dammit! Who's calling now?!
Yes, this is Dojima.
Adachi? I'm hanging up.
Huh?
A sealed letter? For me?
Is it from Mr. Ichihara? When did it arrive?
You forgot about it?!
For the love of God— I'm on my way.
Daddy...
I'm heading out.
Yu,
there should be some medicine in the first aid kit.
Take care of her.
Huh? But...
Pen-Pen the baby penguin overcame many obstacles to return home.
Are you okay, Nanako?
Yeah...
He was greeted by a touching reunion with his father.
Hey, Big Bro...
Is Daddy...
my real father?
Huh?
I was thinking that maybe I'm not Daddy's real daughter.
Why's that?
Because bad people are more important to Daddy than I am.
Just today he rushed out and left me behind.
What's this?
They passed it out at school today.
My teacher told us to give it to our parents.
Dear Parents/Guardians,
About Classroom Observation Time; choose what day works best for you.
We hope that all of our parents/guardians enjoy good health and happy times throughout fall.
We appreciate your understanding and support in our upcoming educational events.
Now then, from 10/2 (Mon.) to 10/6 (Wed.), we plan on holding Classroom Observation Days.
As such, we would appreciate it if everyone could come and watch their child learn and grow.
Duration: Three Days, from 10/24 (Mon.) - 10/26 (Wed.)
He said to put down when they could come.
But Daddy has work,
so he can't go, huh?
Let's ask him when he gets back.
Okay, let's!
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Good night then.
Every Week is Safe Driving
Awareness Week
Moron! "I don't know" doesn't cut it!
It's a detective's duty to do whatever it takes to solve a case.
I-I'm sorry.
Please share any information you may
have about the hit and run murder.
Hey, Adachi.
Huh? Yu?
Where'd he go?
Oh, Dojima should be back soon.
You can wait here.
Thank you.
Man, Dojima never lets up, does he?
Is he like that at home too?
What do you mean?
He isn't convinced the kid's the serial killer, so he's doing his own research.
Not to mention, he's going nuts over the recent hit-and-run.
Uh-oh! Gotta get back to work.
Oh, Yu?
Here's the change of clothes you asked for.
Oh, thanks.
And there's this.
It's from Nanako.
What is it?
It's for a parent-teacher conference.
They need to know when you could make it.
Oh, whenever.
I'll fill it out later.
Will you be coming home tonight?
Probably not.
How's Nanako doing?
She's feeling better now.
But...
But what?
Oh, it's nothing.
Do you have a minute?
Aiya
Thanks for waiting.
I haven't eaten since lunch.
Here are the two orders for takeout.
Thanks.
I've been meaning to tell you
about Chisato's accident.
What's this?
Last night, I got a call from my old mentor, Mr. Ichihara.
I asked for his help on a hit-and-run case, and his results just came in.
Take a look.
It was a white sedan, probably American.
There aren't any cars like that around here.
Records indicate that it wasn't taken in to get scrapped or repaired.
But you see, there was a similar accident last week.
The initial investigation we're currently conducting is critical.
Why haven't you told Nanako anything about the accident?
Chisato was...
Chisato was hit on her way to pick up Nanako.
It was a cold day, and there weren't any witnesses,
so no one found her until it was too late.
By the time word reached me,
Nanako had been stuck waiting at the preschool all by herself.
She was all alone,
waiting for someone who would never come.
I couldn't tell Nanako that her mother had been killed.
I'm supposed to catch the criminals,
and I didn't have a single clue.
But I will catch the culprit!
What about Nanako?
What do you mean?
I think you should stay with Nanako when she's sick—
What do you know?
Mind your own business!
Very well.
Big Bro, where's that paper?
Did Daddy fill it out?
Yeah, he said whenever would be fine.
Really?! Daddy's going to come?
Yay, I'm so happy!
Isn't that great, Nanako?
Yep! This is my first parent-teacher conference!
Everyone says their parents are coming!
Oh yeah!
I framed that picture we found yesterday.
Thank you!
Hey, Big Bro...
What happens after you die?
You go to a place called Heaven.
I knew it! So Mom went to Heaven, right?
I'm sure she'll be watching over you during your conference.
Yeah!
Do you think I'll go to Heaven when I die?
Could I see Mom if I went there?
That's a long way off.
Yeah... I wanna see Mom, though.
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Touching
Knowledge
Professor
There was an accident around Samegawa about a year ago.
Could you look into it?
Finding old newspaper articles on it should be a snap.
This must be it.
The hit-and-run incident in Inaba.
Woman killed in Hit-and-Run near Samegawa
A woman walking home was struck and killed by a car while crossing the street near the Samegawa Flood Plain.
The driver appears to have fled the scene, and the police are treating the incident as a hit-and-run. She was later
identified as local resident Chisato Dojima.
According to a statement from Inaba Station, the accident took place in the evening hours. As few people were
in the area at the time, her body went undiscovered for some time.
No useful eyewitness accounts have yet been received. As the victim was a family member of an officer, the
police are committed to conducting a thorough investigation and tracking down the culprit.
The victim was a woman who lived in town named Dojima Chisato.
That's Nanako's mother.
I vaguely remember that.
People in town talked about it a bit at the time.
Did they catch the culprit?
I don't think so.
According to this article, the police are still investigating the case,
but they're severely lacking information.
They'll have a hard time solving this.
I see.
That's really awful.
I could never forgive the creep!
Nothing good ever comes from running! That bastard!
Your uncle's a detective,
so this must be eating at him, huh?
Yeah...
I think so.
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Lookie, Daddy!
I put Mom's picture here.
Uh-huh...
Daddy, do you remember this picture?
It's from when we went to Samegawa.
Nanako, save it for later.
Daddy, about coming to school...
What about that?
Uh, where's the form?
She means the form I gave you yesterday.
Oh, this?
Are you sure "whenever" is okay?
Yeah, since I'll never make it there anyway.
Sorry, but I can't afford to go when I'm so busy.
What are you saying?!
Forget it...
You don't have to come.
You have a case, right?
You have work, right?
Those bad guys are more important to you than I am, aren't they?!
Forget it! Just forget it!
Hey, Nanako!
Geez, what's gotten into her?
Nanako was looking forward to you going.
That was cruel of you!
What can I do? I've got work.
Why don't you try paying more attention to Nanako?
Excuse me?!
If you actually told her about the hit-and-run...
I said to mind your own business!
Nanako?
What hit-and-run?
You don't need to know.
Why not?
Forget it!
Why are you mad?
How come you never listen to me?
You never do!
Daddy, you're stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
How dare you call your father stupid?!
It's not like you care about me, anyway!
You hate me, don't you?!
You aren't "real."
You aren't my real dad!
Nanako!
Nanako, wait!
I'll search for her in the shopping district.
Okay, I'll try Junes. I'm counting on you!
Right!
Yu!
Find her?
No, I can't find her anywhere.
Has she mentioned anything to you lately?
Like somewhere she'd like to visit?
Not really...
Oh, wait...
Come to think of it...
Do you think I'll go to Heaven when I die?
Could I see Mom if I went there?
No, she wouldn't...
It's headed for Samegawa.
Incident
Woman killed in Hit-and-Run near Samegawa
A woman walking home was struck and killed by a car while crossing the street near the Samegawa Flood Plain.
The driver appears to have fled the scene, and the police are treating the incident as a hit-and-run. She was later
identified as local resident Chisato Dojima.
According to a statement from Inaba Station, the accident took place in the evening hours. As few people were
in the area at the time, her body went undiscovered for some time..
No useful eyewitness accounts have yet been received. As the victim was a family member of an officer, the
the police are committed to conducting a thorough investigation and tracking down the culprit.
Incident
Woman killed in Hit-and-Run near Samegawa
A woman walking home was struck and killed by a car while crossing the street near the Samegawa Flood Plain.
The driver appears to have fled the scene, and the police are treating the incident as a hit-and-run. She was later
identified as local resident Chisato Dojima.
According to a statement from Inaba Station, the accident took place in the evening hours. As few people were
in the area at the time, her body went undiscovered for some time..
No useful eyewitness accounts have yet been received. As the victim was a family member of an officer, the
police are committed to conducting a thorough investigation and tracking down the culprit.
Incident
Woman killed in Hit-and-Run near Samegawa
A woman walking home was struck and killed by a car while crossing the street near the Samegawa Flood Plain.
The driver appears to have fled the scene, and the police are treating the incident as a hit-and-run. She was later
identified as local resident Chisato Dojima.
According to a statement from Inaba Station, the accident took place in the evening hours. As few people were
in the area at the time, her body went undiscovered for some time..
No useful eyewitness accounts have yet been received. As the victim was a family member of an officer, the
police are committed to conducting a thorough investigation and tracking down the culprit.
Incident
Woman killed in Hit-and-Run near Samegawa
A woman walking home was struck and killed by a car while crossing the street near the Samegawa Flood Plain.
The driver appears to have fled the scene, and the police are treating the incident as a hit-and-run. She was later
identified as local resident Chisato Dojima.
According to a statement from Inaba Station, the accident took place in the evening hours. As few people were
in the area at the time, her body went undiscovered for some time.
No useful eyewitness accounts have yet been received. As the victim was a family member of an officer, the
police are committed to conducting a thorough investigation and tracking down the culprit.
Uncle!
Nanako!
Chisato, please...
protect Nanako!
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
Dojima
Family
Grave
I'm begging you!
Nanako...
Thank God you found her.
You go to her.
Right now, you're the family member she trusts the most.
She's more likely to listen to you.
You're still running from her?
Nanako needs a father.
I can handle things on my own
Even holding down the fort
So Dad, it's okay if you're out late
Daddy?
So this is where you've been.
When Mom was still with us,
you, me, and Mom came here to pick flowers,
When I get lonesome on my own
just the three of us.
Yeah...
Mom... Why did she leave me?
I open the window
I... I want to see Mom!
I want you to watch me
Nanako...
D-Daddy, did you forget about Mom?
from above the heavens, Mom
You hid all of her pictures, and you never talk about her!
I still remember your warm smiles
Do you hate her now?
You've got it wrong.
Do you hate me too?
Every single one from the day I lost you
Don't be silly!
I'm sorry, Nanako.
I'm always making you feel so lonely.
The two of us have fun
Daddy!
Cooking and eating together
I'm sorry, Nanako.
Big Bro's here
You know what, Big Bro?
Hm?
So I'm not lonely
I've been lonely since Mom died,
but I bet Daddy has been lonely too.
But really, I want
From now on, I won't cry anymore.
I have to work hard to cover for Mom so Daddy won't get lonely!
The whole family to be together
You're a good girl, Nanako.
Big Bro, let's work hard together!
I'm just holding these feelings back
Yeah, you can count on me.
I'm home!
It's Daddy!
Uh, so...
This is a special day for us as a family.
It's a special day?
That's right.
It's the day when you, me, and Yu become a family.
What about before?
Well...
At any rate, this is the day we become a real family.
I wanna see you, I wanna see you
Okay... I don't really get it, but isn't that great, Big Bro?
I wanna see you right now
Yeah.
Uncle, this cup...
From today on, that's yours.
And when I do
Please use it. I'm sure it would make Chisato happy.
I'll treasure it.
Smile like you used to
And before I forget...
Don't be angry as you hug me tenderly
"Any day is" something...
It means "Anytime's okay." I promise I'll go.
Okay!
Well, let's dig in!
Let's eat!
Cover the hole in my heart
Families are meant to laugh, cry, and bicker...
Overflowing with tears
They spend most of their long lives together.
They're supposed to be warm.
With your warm hand
Yep!
I can't believe I was avoiding that by chasing someone who had run away.
You're the one who made me realize that, Yu.
Thank you.
When you do, I can see
I did it because we're family.
I'm going to continue pursuing the culprit who hit Chisato,
There's pain aside from my own
but I won't use that as an excuse to run away.
We can overcome our loneliness
I'm doing it because I'm a detective.
You see, this is my town.
It's special to me since it's where you and Nanako live.
Just as long as we're together
That's why I am going to continue protecting this place.
I'll say it whenever and wherever
I'm doing it as both a detective and as a father.
Daddy, you're so cool!
Yeah, you know it!
As many times as you like
Dad, please don't forget
I love you
Did you say "beauty pageant"?
Check out our group date café...
I look stupid, don't I?
Not you too, Narukami!
Stop it!
Give me your hearts!
I suppose I'll take one.