Nagase...
It's you, right?
And you're Taichi... right?
Yeah, people aren't going to switch bodies every—
Wh-What's wrong?
Don't tell me...
It wasn't a three-way switch this time...
was it?
It was!
I'm Kiriyama Yui!
I'm Aoki Yoshifumi!
I'm Inaba Himeko!
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
What if you laugh more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
The comic I read just now was cool.
I want to eat curry now.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry, you gotta
drink more milk
Inabaaaan
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Cooks curry
Inaba Himeko
me yui
AAAAA
We should get married
I love you
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to eat a
pot of curry.
Wonder if I should.
The whole world
Let's go
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry
I can't go out with you
It'd be bad
I don't have the homework
for tomorrow
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
like a bird of many colors
Did you hear that?
Every month
on the 25th
Deadline
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
Student Cultural Society
Want some more tea?
No thanks.
I can't take any more of this!
Why do I keep getting stuffed in this yucky body?!
Why don't I get to switch bodies with Iori?!
What?
With me?
Uh, I think you're missing something here.
I won't be stuck in this body forever, will I?!
Hard to say.
Yesterday, they switched back after 30 minutes.
Taichi, Iori, shouldn't you go to class?
I don't want to keep you here because of us.
Pizza Chips
Double Cheese
Mushroom Village
Nah, skipping class every now and then is cool.
It's sort of exciting, almost like we're a secret society.
That's easy for you to—
Did you switch back?
Seems like it.
Some Fascinating Humans
Yeah. Well, you know,
I don't think this is necessary,
but I have a reputation to keep,
so pretend like I'm grilling you.
Oh, I'm gonna keep on eating.
It's noodle day.
Can't let 'em get soggy.
Well, you guys are usually good students.
Although you've managed to pique my interest...
Man, I always choke on the first bite
when I eat something hot, you know?
Wait, that doesn't happen to you?
Just get it over with, Goto.
Now look here, Inaba.
I want to be considered an open and friendly teacher,
so I let the students call me Mr. Go,
but that doesn't mean it's okay to drop the "Mr."
You don't get to lecture me
until you start doing your job.
Who did the bookkeeping for our class after the cultural festival?
Right, thank you very much.
Try not to mention that while other teachers are around.
So why are we here again?
Oh, right.
What were you all doing?
You three, Aoki, and Kiriyama didn't show up until third period.
We all had some mini chocolate buns yesterday that turned out to be spoiled,
so we were all late due to upset stomachs.
That's what happened.
Is that the same answer Aoki and Kiriyama will give Ms. Hirata?
Of course.
If that's your story, I can buy it.
You're excused.
Inaban's a real pro.
Yeah, she can lie through her teeth
and still come across all haughty like that.
She'll grow up to be a scammer or con artist.
Seriously...
If you don't have anything nice to say, shut up.
Did Aoki and Kiriyama get out of it okay?
Yeah.
And?
What's wrong, Yui?
Earth to Yui...
What's wrong?
Did you see a ghost or something?
Oh, I need to go to the restroom.
Good luck.
What to do?
I need to find a place where I can be alone!
Whoa!
What are you doing in here?!
That's right.
Then I have no choice!
Please
Wash
Your Hands
Hm?
Again?! What is going on?!
Hello? Is this Taichi?
Yeah, that's right.
Is Kiriyama with you?
Yeah, Iori's trying to calm her down.
Where are you right now?
Me?
I'm in the...
...restroom.
Huh? Oh.
You switched back?
Y-Yeah...
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Hello?
Hello, Inaba? Can you hear me?
Why am I in the restroom?!
What was Taichi doing?!
Put Taichi on the phone!
Yaegashi...
It's our turn to clean the restrooms today.
Don't run out on me.
Back to the restroom...
Huh?
You look tired.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Sorry, but it took a while to finish up cleaning—
Student Cultural Society
Taichi!
What...
What the hell happened?
Student Cultural Society
Wh-What do you mean?
What's wrong, Nagase?
Student Cultural Society
What happened between you and Fujishima while we were switched?!
Uh, nothing important...
I'll tell you if it was important or not!
How often do we get to see Iori this flustered?
Uh, well...
I probably should've said something sooner.
Student Cultural Society
He played with my boobs!
How am I supposed to get married now?!
I had to do that to figure out what was going on!
When you were in my body,
you went to the girls' restroom.
You couldn't have...
I was just trying to find a place to hide!
Hey, that's not what matters right now!
What matters is that...
Fu-Fu—
Fujishima is...
A-Are you okay, Nagase?
Why are you so upset?
And what's so special about Fujishima?
I've never seen Iori so stressed.
Fujishima's the Class 1-3 rep, right? What's she like?
She has perfect manners, stellar grades, and the teachers love her.
She's a model student.
Forget that! Taichi!
How big were Iori's boobs?!
Ow, hot!
We don't have time to waste on that!
If you really want to know, I can just tell you.
Iori is a C cup.
While we're at it, I'm a B,
and Yui's an A.
Wh-What do you think you're saying?!
It's okay, Yui!
You might be lacking in the boobs department,
but you've got it going on in plenty of other areas!
Wipe that look off your face!
And I'm not lacking!
Smaller can be better sometimes!
Oh...
So Inaba is a B while Kiriyama is an A.
Potato Sticks
Don't just stand there and stare!
Let's not forget Fujishima!
What am I supposed to do?!
We should focus on the body swapping.
Hey.
Hello there.
Goto?
How long have you been standing there?
Student Cultural Society
I just got here.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling under the weather?
I feel perfectly fine.
After all, this man is much healthier than he needs to be.
Student Cultural Society
The problem would be that I lack
motivation, tenacity, courage, spirit,
and all that other stuff, I guess.
Um... What's wrong, Mr. Go?
I came to see if you people were panicking about the personality swap.
Mr. Go, how do you know about th—
Oh, could you stop calling me "Mr. Go" or "Goto"?
That's not who I am.
Who...
...are you?
Who are you?
Yes, how do I respond?
I suppose you could say "Heartseed" is my name.
Heartseed?
Student Cultural Society
What does a little-known plant have to do with anything?
Dunno?
Well, I basically play the role of an observer.
I just happen to
be borrowing this Goto person's body at the moment.
So you're something else in Mr. Go's body?
That sounds about right, yes.
That means you have something to do with our personalities swapping.
Yes.
Well, then...
The five of you will randomly swap personalities for the time being.
So who switches with who and when they switch is completely random?
Yes.
Bravo, Nagase.
You're absolutely right.
And I'll be observing you.
But you don't have to worry about me intruding on your privacy.
That would require effort.
Do you more or less understand the current situation?
That was supposed to be an explanation?
Fine.
Then I'll start asking questions.
First, why us?
Are you able to control this phenomenon?
How do we make it stop?
And what is your objective?
Student Cultural Society
All excellent questions.
To answer your first question,
you seemed like a fascinating bunch...
I guess.
What's that supposed to mean?
Student Cultural Society
Well, after you've switched around a bit
and I'm like, "Okay, that was fun,"
it'll all stop.
That means you control when this stops.
Yeah...
Don't worry too much about this and go on with your lives.
And don't bother trying to figure out how it all works.
That's not the task you've been assigned.
Also, I recommend that you don't tell anyone else
about the personality swap.
That would only bring more trouble.
Student Cultural Society
Good luck then.
I'll be cheering for you a little...
from the smallest corner of my heart.
Wait!
Um...
I have more questions for you!
That's not the task you've been assigned.
Student Cultural Society
Don't expect us to shut up and just take it from you!
Hey!
The hell?!
Let me handle this!
Sorry, Mr. Go!
Student Cultural Society
No way!
Kiriyama!
See you around, then.
What's up with this whole "shocking turn of events"?
Yui was a karate champion in middle school.
Mr. Go wouldn't be able to do that normally.
When I dropped by the faculty office...
Me?
I've been sitting here going through paperwork.
Huh?
How come I haven't made any progress?
Did I nod off?
It sounded like he didn't notice a thing.
Dammit, this makes no sense!
No, if we think too hard about it,
we may end up doing exactly what he wants.
Maybe we should ask someone for help?
I think that's a bad idea.
He did say it would only bring trouble.
I know we can't really trust what he says,
but we don't want this to get out of control.
I don't want to make my mom worry.
Whenever our personalities switch,
we'll need to stay in contact and
get a hold on the current situation.
Try not to let anyone see you.
If you're forced to interact with other people, do your best impression.
Got it?
Got it.
It's been a week since we established the ground rules.
You people are too careless!
Who's made the most basic of mistakes by going into the wrong restroom
while in the body of the opposite sex?!
Me.
Idiots!
How can you screw that up?!
That's the first thing to watch out for!
Old habits die hard.
I just forget.
Don't forget!
You're making it harder for us to go to the restroom!
Um, I have a proposal.
Can everyone use the restroom regularly when they aren't switched?
I just told you it's harder for us to go to the restroom now!
But if one of us girls gets the urge to go while in Taichi or Aoki's body,
that means...
Ew! Yuck!
You don't have to be so mean about it.
Okay, Aoki and I will try our best.
Okay, thanks.
Why are you so nice to Taichi?!
You shouldn't worry about it.
I've learned how to pee while standing up.
What?!
You need to start worrying.
And were you serious about that?
Moving on.
What about our virtue?
Our bodies?
Nothing to worry about.
Right, Aoki?
Yeah...
I'll admit that I get the urge to try stuff when I'm in a girl's body,
but you don't need to worry.
I haven't had the opportunity to go to the restroom.
Honestly?
I'm being honest here.
This is the kind of situation where mutual trust is important.
I'm not gonna do anything stupid.
True enough...
Hey, Iori, when I switched bodies with you the other night,
there wasn't anyone else in your home.
Why was that?
It's not safe to leave a girl alone at night.
Oh, right.
I never mentioned this,
but my parents are divorced, and I live with my mom.
My mom's really busy, too.
Well, if you run into a thug,
just unleash the pepper spray and beat the crap out of him,
and it'll be okay.
It's not okay!
Huh?
Thinking it's not a big deal is the most dangerous thing you can do!
We can't wait until something goes wrong!
Uh...
Sorry.
Y-Yeah...
I'm sorry, too.
How long is this going to last?
Who is that Heartseed guy?
Oh. So this is what Aoki sees.
He's so tall.
Are you Nagase?
Correct.
Oh, Yui looks so tiny.
I-It's not what you think.
I don't have a problem with Iori touching me,
but I moved away because you're Aoki right now.
Yeah, I understand.
That wasn't very sensitive of me.
It's taking longer to go back to normal this time.
What's wrong, Nagase?
I screwed up.
Are you talking about what happened with Kiriyama?
Or is there something else on your mind?
Anything I can help with?
Time for Nagase Iori to ask Taichi questions!
Uh, what?
Each one of us implicitly has a soul, mind, and personality,
which contribute to our identity.
Now that Nagase Iori's soul is inside Aoki's body,
the result is identified as Nagase Iori.
However, souls and personalities cannot be seen or touched.
That's why we typically use physical appearance to identify a person.
That means that the body is the foundation for the identity.
But if our bodies lose their significance because of the personality switching,
will we still be ourselves?
Nagase?
Just kidding.
Whoa!
Hey, Taichi!
Oh, welcome back.
Phew, I'm back.
I finally returned to my own body.
Nagase seemed different somehow.
Well, maybe I'm overthinking it.
Hm... So that's how it goes.
What's that supposed to mean?
Huh? What's going on?
Oh. It's nothing, really.
Listen up, everyone.
We need three people from our class to volunteer
for the off-campus clean up.
Any takers?
What? There wasn't any warning?
Mr. Go probably caved again.
I'm too busy with practice.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
I'll volunteer, so we only need two more.
What?
I'll volunteer.
Huh?
Oh, Inaba.
You'll help?
I... I'll also volunteer.
Really?
Best of luck, Taichi!
Cut it out.
Let me go.
My day's been ruined, and it's all your fault.
I'll make up for this later, so cut me some slack, Inaba.
Yaegashi, do you have a moment?
I have something I want to ask you.
What's your relationship with Nagase?
What?
Friends in the same club?
Or something more?
That's right.
Wait!
This is a good opportunity to make this clear.
H-Hey, what are you going to tell her?!
Iori is mine!
Stay away from her!
Jobber and Low Blow
Next Time
I'm in love with Nagase?
Whenever there's a guy around, I start to shake.
Y-Your eyes are kinda scaring me.
Just let me handle this.
Sure. If that's what you want, Mom.
Selfless freak.
My daily life, gone with the flow of time
seemed like a dream beyond what my senses could appreciate
I don't understand, I don't understand
So I mumble, still little more than a child, and dream
Maybe I'm a coward
It shouldn't matter
I wish I could be stronger
Onto that sort of facade,
my weak cries,
scattered feelings,
and changing intentions
the sun shone
You were the only one that mattered to me
I knew that
Maybe
.              .
hi       to
ra        n
do      m
.               .
.              .
If we do our best
me yui
I love my sister
Tune in next time!
Inaba
Let's go!
I wanna eat curry