[thunder cracking]
[rain falling]
[intense music playing]
[growling]
[Thor] Geirröd Thor's Hammer!
Hah!
[heavy metal music playing]
JOY
[exploding]
[Göll whimpering]
[gods straining]
No, is he...?
[stammering] He... He... He's still standing!
[humans cheering wildly]
Lü Bu, what a man!
He took Thor's attack
and blocked it with ease.
That's my liege!
[yelling]
Huh.
What is this nonsense?
Wasn't that the move
that defeated Jörmungandr!?
What insolence!
That human, who does he think he is?
[gasping]
[shouting] Lü Bu!
I beg of you,
please, don't push my sister Griz
too hard out there!
I want you to be careful with her, okay?
Huh?
[gasping]
[straining]
Huh?
Hm?
What's this?
Hm.
[gasping]
[cracking]
[all gasping]
[groaning]
[both exclaiming in shock]
Oh my gods!
Thor's attack has shattered Lü Bu's leg!
This might just be the end of the line
for Lü Bu in this bout.
- [cracking]
- [grunting painfully]
[all exclaiming in shock]
[Guan Yu] Oh.
Be strong!
[whimpering]
[chuckling]
- Hermes?
- Yes?
I've decided high stakes fights like these
are most agreeable.
Quite.
My what a show.
Lü Bu trying to block
Thor's attack straight on.
That certainly was enjoyable.
However, his body won't be able
to withstand much more.
Hm.
This is over.
[tense music playing]
Ah! No, my liege.
Defeated again, before my very eyes.
Such cruel fate.
Look at all that blood!
Brünnhilde, what the heck are we gonna do?
Run away! Hey, Lü Bu!
Get out of there now!
- [hooves beating]
- [gasping]
Look, Göll. It seems we may have
an ace in the hole after all, you see?
- Huh?
- [horse whinnying]
That sound is...
[hooves beating]
[whinnying loudly]
- Huh?
- Lü Bu steed, the Red Hare!
There's a horse?
Where'd that thing come from?
This is madness.
Oh, how exciting.
And what a manly steed it is too.
The Red Hare? How's it here?
It must be... a miracle.
[snorting]
My old friend.
Right. I see now.
He hasn't given up.
And neither can we!
Until the end!
Oh!
We must believe in our leader
not matter what!
[soldiers yelling]
We pledge our lives to the Flying General,
our lord and liege, Lü Bu!
[all] Hail!
Hail!
Hail, Lü Bu!
Come on! Is sitting down there
on your knees your idea of a joke?
Well, it's not funny.
You're the strongest man in the world.
Get up!
Yes, he's right. We know you can do it.
[humans screaming encouragement]
Fight on?
That's what they want?
Wow, humans really can be so cruel.
What a reckless man.
I think that I like it.
I really hope he doesn't quit.
[Heimdall] There's no way he can get up.
I mean, do I want to see him try?
It'd be funny for sure.
But that's impossible. This fight is over.
They can't really
expect anything different.
- I might as well call it--
- [crowd exclaiming]
Huh? What's going on?
Lü Bu!
Go!
[humans chanting] Lü Bu!
Lü Bu! Lü Bu!
What? No way.
[chanting continues]
[soldiers cheering]
[straining]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[breathing deeply]
[Heimdall] He got up!
[humans cheering]
Yay!
Go!
[whinnying]
It would seem that Lü Bu refuses to quit!
Hmm.
[laughing]
Hell, yeah! Now there's a sight.
Lü Bu on the Red Hare again.
You used to ride the Red Hare
once upon a time too. What do you think?
Ha. They belong together.
The Red Hare is truly Lü Bu's steed.
[crowd cheering]
[fire crackling]
[Lü Bu] When I was but a child,
I watched a giant tree
be reduced to ash by a bolt of lightning.
I didn't fear the dancing flames.
I could only think of one thing...
Of heaven...
and the gods who lived there.
Up there are the strongest beings.
[thunder crashing]
[crowd cheering]
[humans cheering]
[gods cheering]
Fight on!
Lord Zeus, you're going
to allow this to happen?
It's against the rules, is it not?
Don't spoil the fun, Hermes.
Besides, look.
It may be a one-on-one fight,
but that horse is a part of him now.
[both giggling]
[Hermes] Hm.
[laughing]
My old friend.
This could be it.
I want to ask
if you'll entrust your life to me.
[snorting]
[whinnying]
- Yes, my liege.
- [soldiers cheering]
All right! That's the spirit!
[Heimdall] Lü Bu is
finally back in the fight.
The Red Hare has become his legs,
and now he's running circles around Thor.
But Thor is not moving.
What's Lü Bu's plan?
Ah, that move! He changed his grip.
Holding his halberd in that manner
can only mean one thing!
His secret technique!
[Lü Bu counting] 36,863...
[Brünnhilde] That fateful spring,
when Lü Bu finally discovered
he was the strongest man in the world.
He also realized that he was now alone.
- [Lü Bu counting] 77,500.
-[Brünnhilde] However...
- 77,600.
- ...despite this revelation...
- 77,700.
- ...he persisted.
Nine hundred and nine.
Lü Bu kept swinging his halberd,
seeking to improve his skills
with single-minded devotion.
He believed he'd meet
an opponent one day who could
finally
dwarf even his astronomical strength.
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
My liege...
He spent years doing nothing
but training in solitude.
And then...
[straining]
Lü Bu held his halberd in a way that...
[roaring]
...split the sky in two.
The superhuman strength
of Lü Bu's grip and swing
gave a tremendous amount
of momentum to his halberd.
And that is how
his secret technique was born.
Despite his achievement,
he was haunted by the fact that the attack
would never be used on another.
Still, he gave
that lonely technique a name,
Sky Eater.
I've waited thousands of years
to see this.
Finally, my liege
can unleash his strongest attack,
using his strongest weapon,
mounted atop his mighty steed,
facing off against his strongest opponent.
A worthy foe.
One he'd gladly call his comrade!
[roaring]
How amusing.
- You mortals are an intriguing bunch.
- [Mjölnir thumping]
Don't you agree? Are you getting excited?
[thumping accelerates]
Well then.
Let's go.
[narrator] Lü Bu could feel it.
He knew that the technique
he was about to unleash,
would be the most powerful attack
he ever performed in his life.
[yelling]
[bones crunching]
[horse screaming]
[narrator] Across from him,
the god Thor could feel the same.
[straining]
SKY EATER
GEIRRÖD THOR'S HAMMER
[straining]
[exhaling]
[laughing]
[roaring]
[growling]
[straining]
- [Göll squealing]
- [Brünnhilde grunting]
- My... My liege!
- [crashing]
[soldiers yelling]
Ah!
[bones crunching]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[sorrowful music playing]
No, don't tell me that she's dead.
Griz, please get up!
[whimpering]
What happened?
[sighing]
[Lü Bu] I gave it everything I have.
Ha!
[whinnying]
- [roaring]
-[Lü Bu] So this...
is it.
This is what happiness feels like
without restrictions!
[crunching]
No...
[wailing] My liege!
[straining]
So concludes the end
of round one of Ragnarok.
The winner of this round,
first champion of the final battle
between god and man...
is Thor!
[gods cheering]
- [ominous music playing]
- [snorting]
THOR VS. LÜ BU
TIME: 16 MINUTES, 28 SECONDS
WINNING ATTACK: GEIRRÖD THOR'S HAMMER
WINNER: THOR
[laughing]
How 'bout that?
I was worried about
how it was going to turn out.
Well, I never doubted the outcome
for a second!
What a thrill.
Marvelous.
For the first time in a thousand years,
my blood boils.
I know.
I haven't felt arousal like this
in quite a long time.
How grand.
[gods cheering wildly]
[Heimdall] Ragnarok round one has ended
with Thor as its victor.
The human race is one step closer
to its inevitable end!
[Japanese pop ballad playing]