The game for the sports competition will be...
A 50-meter freestyle one-game swimming match, as proposed by Kawashima-san!
Lucky me!
What did you write?
Vale   Tudo
If I win, I'm going to display the movie of your imitations for everyone to see.
If I win, Takasu-kun's spending his entire summer with me at my vacation home.
You'll be all alone for the entire summer.
For whose sake?
If you know the answer, come up and write it on the blackboard.
I will.
As expected of the class representative.
Oh sh-
Hey.
Idiot.
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami-tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami- tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami- tan, Taiga
Takasu and Judge Kushieda when sending this around
Everyone in 2-C must read this!
Exclude Ami- tan, Taiga
First round of the Takasu Cup commencing?
Ami-tan vs the Palmtop Tiger. 500 Tirols per bet.
The hell is this?
Will this even be a fight?
Of course Ami-tan will win at swimming! Taiga just sank, remember?
I want to be struggled over too, what should I do?
Damn... These guys...
Ami's mine, sorry arl.
Were you trying to write "all"?
Aren't you kinda screwed to be unable to write 'all'?
>Haruta
You cheated your way into this school, didn't you? >Haruta
Aren't you kinda screwed up to be unable to write 'all'?
Haruta... you're like...
I mean... everyone's writing all kinds of crap!
What?!
3000 Tirols!
Takasu Ryuuji
W-what's wrong, Aisaka?
If you've solved it, I'd like to see you go up and answer it...
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be afraid, Taiga!
Dip your face under as if you're washing it! Now, once more!
Even if you say that...
She's unable to dip her face in the water?
Isn't she a little out of her league?
I can already see how this fight is going to go...
I told you to ignore the crowd.
I know!
Well, she's gotta keep it up for Takasu's sake too.
Who has to...!?
Did someone do something?
Kitamura-ku-!
Keep working together with Takasu and try your best!
Huh? What? Together...?
Hey! Taiga!
I absolutely will not practice during class anymore.
Just doing imaginary training is enough!
Say that after you're able to dip your face into the water.
What're today's side-dishes?
Peas bound in eggs, tofu steak and miso soup.
Also, there's spinach and deep-fried-
Always something with beans, I want meat!
Don't be so picky.
Beans are the meat of the field.
Cheapskate.
That aside, make sure you properly practice during swimming class. Loosen up.
I can't loosen up.
Kitamura-kun's watching, after all...
Because he's watching, you have to try your best, right?
Now, look here...
Whose fault is it to begin with that I'm working so hard,
despite the fact that everyone is misunderstanding?
Huh? "Whose?"
Well, in order to keep Kitamura from going to Kawashima's vacation home-
OW!
Whatever. You only need to make my food.
Jeez, what now?
Hey, come on and make it already.
I'm going to take in tons of nutrition and practice like crazy.
The rain's not stopping...
No pool classes today, either, I guess...
Just when I've finally become able to dip my face into water...
Why can't we use the pool?!
Don't take it out on me.
Tickets for the public pool?
Use them.
I'm betting on Aisaka too.
Takasu went really overboard with how he was rooting for Aisaka on the piece of paper that was being sent around,
so I figured, "All right, I'm going to root for her too!"
F-For me?
Yeah!
Wh-Wh-Why? I can't even swim...
Aisaka is the type that shows her true strength in moments of desperation.
We don't know how this fight will go just yet!
I... can't make it like this, can I?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Shu-shu-shu-shu-shut u-u-up!
Good luck with the practicing.
Aww, man...
Idiot.
Hey, want to stop by somewhere on the way home?
How about Sudoba?
Good idea.
What the..? Why are you sitting cramped in between those?
Gloomy weirdo.
This cramped feeling calms me down.
Heave-ho...
My goodness! Takasu-kun's worn out as well?
Yeah; I've been like this for a while now because of a certain someone.
Huh? Because of who? Ami-chan doesn't know!
Why, you...
The jealous Taiga is cute...
What? How is she jealous?
She simply doesn't like you.
Is Takasu-kun an idiot?
You're the idiot.
Either way, don't provoke Taiga so much.
I mean, what's with the vacation house?
You don't intend to invite me either way.
I was serious, you know.
I'm seriously intending to win and spend the summer with Takasu-kun.
I'm really thinking about what to do after I win.
I think it'll be fun!
See, we're rather compatible, aren't we?
N-No, we're not.
He got mad, he got mad!
Why, you...!
Jeez.
Keep your mocking of others mild, okay?
All righty~
Farewell, then.
I am aware.
H-Huh? Aware of what? What do you know?
That the one who super-sized Taiga's swimsuit was...
You!
Huh? Umm... That was...
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You don't need to hide it. It was elementary, my dear Akechi-kun.
You see, Taiga was telling me before,
"Ryuuji is always there to help."
Huh?
Cleaning, fixing buttons, ironing clothes...
Oh, that? Doing stuff that small...
Doing those small things is what makes it great.
Huh?
Hey, Kushie-
I believe in you, and thus I'm leaving Taiga in your care.
Y-Yeah...
I'm the referee, so I can't really help you out, but...
I'm rooting for the same person!
Leave it to me!
All right.
Please, take care of tomorrow's rain.
Thank you, Teru Teru Bozu-san.
The weather seems to be holding out, but...
Look, Ryuuji. It's like I'm swimming, right?
It's about time we did some proper practice.
Man, what is this?
The match is tomorrow, you know!
What good will it do to practice the crawl stroke now?
We've got to make do with what we can!
This looks so dumb.
Yes, keep that up! Oh, try kicking your feet now.
Fine!
Huh? Hey!
T-Taiga!
That was awesome, Taiga! Your kicking power is out of this world!
You might be able to win with this!
Win? Me?
I was doing it as I usually do...
Well, you can't let your guard down,
But-
I see.
I can win. I see.
Taiga?
Yes. I'm going to win.
Yeah! Keep that spirit up!
It doesn't seem like this will stop for a while...
And just when you finally wanted to try...
What do you want to do? Go home?
You want to keep it up?
I see.
I guess we should.
We can't let the tickets we got from Kitamura's kindness go to waste.
It's not about that!
It's not that...
The reason I'm trying so hard is-
I know, I know. While we're at it, we'll leave that Kawashima utterly speechless.
Enough already. No matter what I say, it's pointless.
Huh? What now?
Wait, could it be about me?
Right, there won't be any food if I go away, after all.
I told you it's not about th-
But, you don't have to push yourself.
Even if you lose, it'll be settled if I go alone to Kawashima's vacation home.
I'll ask her to leave Kitamura out of it.
I can make heaps of food and put it in the fridge,
So... don't worry about unnecessary things and-
So you've finally revealed yourself, haven't you?
Huh?
You've wanted to go since from the beginning, haven't you?
To Ami-chan's vacation home!
Huh? What's up with that?
Well, it's none of my business where, when, or who you pant over or whatever.
What's your problem?! I'm trying to look out for you!
Who asked you to do that?!
You've been really weird lately!
First with that thing with Kawashima-
Are you still thinking about that?!
What is it that you're so disgruntled over?!
"What", you ask?
I can't stand it when someone's going off on their own,
Thinking they know what's going on inside of me, and acting like they understand me!
I just can't stand that!
It pisses me off!
Why won't you understand that?!
Which is it, do you want to be understood or not?
I don't know!
What?
Nobody should be able to understand how I feel.
I mean... I mean...
Even I don't know...
Huh? What?
What'd you just say? Hey!
I said that I'll do what you wanted and not attend the competition.
It itches.
I'm not at fault... am I?
Huh?
Ryuu-chan?
Why is Ryuu-chan awake?
I'm home!
Didn't Taiga-chan come over?
Why? Did you two have a fight?
Taiga said she doesn't give a damn about me anymore... and pissed me off... I think.
I see...
But... Ryuu-chan knows, right?
That Taiga-chan's always like that, contradicting what she actually means...
No, it's not like she doesn't give a damn anymore...
If she really hated Ryuu-chan, no matter how hungry she was,
she wouldn't eat from the same plate as you...
At least, that's what Yacchan thinks...
Jeez, without even removing her makeup.
Come on, pull yourself together.
You haven't eaten anything, have you?
I really wanted it to be sunny. And then,
I hoped you would seriously put up a fight today.
You see... I mean...
No matter what you think, I...
want you to win-
Win? I...
The lunchbox is innocent, so I'll be taking it with me.
But...
It was raining so much that my usual swimsuit didn't dry.
But I hope this doesn't break any school rules.
I'm getting worried.
That beautiful Ami-tan's about to swim in this pool, right?
In order to be able to bring Takasu to her vacation home, right?
Why is it always Takasu? Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why is it always Takasu?
Ow, ow, ow!
Quit it, you two!
It's not even been decided that I'm going to the vacation home yet!
As if that Taiga can win-
You don't know that until she tries!
Until she tries...
you don't know...
That idiot... This time it's only meat...
Hey, hey!
How long do you intend to make us wait?
It's hot, you know!
Why isn't she coming out, the Palmtop Tiger?
Who cares? Just pretend like you only came here to look at that bikini.
You're right.
Hey, we shouldn't make everyone wait through this heat any longer...
You're right...
What's this nonsense you're blabbering on about?
Come, let's fight this out fair and square.
Stupid chihuahua, now re-dubbed stupid bikini!
Taiga!
You're going to swim with that on?!
I thought she had armor on for a moment.
That's kinda cool.
Well then, the 50-meter freestyle one-game swimming match!
On your marks...!
Get set...!
Whoa.
Hair's showing.
WHAT?!
Cra-
I can't believe it! I can't believe it! I can't believe it!
Whoa, now!
The Palmtop Tiger used a delayed entrance strategy coupled with dangerous mind game tactics!
Damn you, mini-tiger!
Taiga!
Oh? An accident has occurred for the Tiger?
This is a golden opportunity for Ami-tan!
Damn it!
Are you okay? Did your leg cramp?
Idiot, let me go!
I can still go o- OW!
You can't go on like this!
I'm going!
But you-!
Aren't you happy?!
Wha-?
Don't "wha" me!
Your master's working hard for your sake! Be more happy about, you dumbass dog!
Keep it up, Ami-chan!
The situation has finally reversed itself!
All right, then! Go now!
I'll wag my tail or something for you!
And with that...
Ami-tan!
Don't push!
You idiot, that's dangerous!
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Taiga?
Takasu! Hey, Takasu! Are you all right?!
Okay, he's breathing! Aisaka, take him to the infirmary quickly!
DON'T TOUCH HIM!
Taiga...?
But, Aisaka-
Shut up!
You're all idiots!
Why didn't you notice? Why didn't you help him?
You all had your attention focused on the stupid bikini...
Nobody was... helping Ryuuji...
RYUUJI IS MINE!
NOBODY ELSE TOUCH HIM!
Um, you see,
I decided to come along to your vacation home too.
What?!
I lost the competition, didn't I? Ryuuji's going, isn't he?
I won't have anyone to tend to my daily needs, see?
That's why I've decided to co-
Wait a minute. Ami-chan's getting confused by your exceedingly selfish bantering.
Why not bring her? The more the merrier.
Ah, I see.
Could it be that Aisaka-san's worried about being separated from Takasu-kun?
After all, you proclaimed "Ryuuji is mine!", didn't you?
You're right, I'll admit it.
Because, I mean...
That is...in other words...
This guy's my dog, you see.
As his owner, I have to take responsibility for him.
I have to watch him so that he doesn't get all excited in other people's places.
What? Were you expecting something else?
No, we weren't. Not anything.
All right. Let's decide on a schedule, then.
Let me see!
You see, around this time, I am packed with my part-time jobs,
and around there I'm very busy with club activities.
Too bad we couldn't be all alone...
But there will be more opportunities.
What?
And that was how the first semester of Takasu Ryuuji's second year of high school ended,
And now a "stimulating" summer break was about to begin.
Next Episode Preview
You, who are going to the sea?
Go-Going together with Kushieda to a vacation home...
I might get punished for achieving this happiness, Taiga!
Kitamura-kun's thin, hazy, black seaweed...
What?