Thank you.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
Family name: Fukahori. Given name: Yurika.
Second year, class six, seat number 22.
So she's our senpai.
She moved here from Tokyo during her first year of middle school.
Her hobbies are oil painting and practicing the naginata.
Her birthday is February 10th.
That's all. Just for your information...
Wh-What are you talkin' about?!
Don't play dumb.
This has gotten as hard as a rock.
When you think about her,
you get a lump in your throat,
so you can't get the food down, right?
Poor thing...
You're completely lovesick.
L-Love?! So this is what love is...
Don't tell me you've never fallen in love before!
Nope.
You've got to be kidding me...
Wait.
If he really falls for that girl,
then he won't get between Ricchan and me.
Alright, we'll skip jazz after school
and formulate a plan instead.
MIKANOMACHI
END OF
SUMMER
SALE
Huh? At my house?
We ain't goin' to Rikko's basement?
You'll be more relaxed at home, right?
I don't mind, but...
If we went to that basement,
it's possible Ricchan would overhear us.
Here it is.
This is Ricchan's shop.
We live in a row house, so Rikko's place is connected to ours.
Hey, Ma!
Nii-chan!
Welcome home, Nii-chan!
You're back early today.
Play with us!
Hold on, hold on.
Where's Ma?
Mom, Nii-chan's home!
Bon!
What are you doin'?
Come on in!
Ma, this is Bon.
Well there, hello.
I appreciate you always looking out for Sentaro.
Oh... You're too kind.
Don't be shy. Dig in, Bon.
I thought you didn't have an appetite today.
I can always eat watermelon.
Sentaro loves his watermelon...
I was surprised when he told me he wasn't feeling hungry,
but I had a hunch he'd be able to eat some watermelon, so I iced one up.
Nii-chan! Nii-chan!
What is it, Taichi?
We found a weird bug!
A bug?
Where, where?
It's over here!
Nii-chan, if you plant a
watermelon seed, will it grow?
Let's plant one an' see.
Look, there!
Oh, there it is!
Amazing!
It flew!
Sheesh, don't cry about it!
A group date?
Yeah.
Ricchan and I will go with you to make it the four of us.
If it was just the two of you, she'd be on guard.
Oh... I get it.
Of course, you'll be the one to invite Yurika-jou.
If you don't do it, there's no point, right?
No... I can't!
I really can't do it!
Look...
What's that sound?
Sarah.
Sarah?
My girlfriend.
Huh?
What's wrong, Sarah?
You're in a bad mood.
Cute, ain't she?
Her full name is Sarah Vaughan.
A pigeon, huh?
What is it, Sarah?
You're really agitated today.
She's probably jealous.
Since you keep talking about another girl.
Huh? What's wrong with me?
I'm suddenly enjoying myself.
That was so funny!
I know!
Oh...
U-Um...
I-Idiot!
Who approaches a girl and runs away?!
I can't do it, man!
The note, the note!
Y-Yeah...
He's coming back.
I'm sorry...
...for suddenly interrupting you.
Are you free this weekend?
I would like to take this opportunity to cult... cult...
"Cultivate"?
...cultivate...
our friendship!
That idiot...
Bon! Bon!
She agreed! She says she'll go!
We're going to Rendezvous Rock, right?
Shall I pack us a lunch?
Um, that'd be great.
Just something light, like onigiri, would be good.
Okay, leave it to me.
By the way, just so I know...
Which of the two of you is inviting me?
Oh, that would be...
This guy!
He insisted on inviting you!
Huh?
Oh.
I see.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
You said okay to a date?!
Really?!
You really are a fool!
It was going as smooth possible,
and then you blew it!
Yeah, I dunno why I said that.
Wind back time for me, Bon!
As if I can!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
There's Kaoru-san!
Hey, what happened to your face?
Oh, just another one of Sentaro's fights.
Let's go, Kaoru-san.
Wait a minute, Ricchan.
Actually, one more person's joining us today.
I'm sorry!
I'm late!
Making lunch took longer than I thought.
You're the girl those hooligans were harassing at the beach.
Th-That's right!
You remember her, huh?
Actually, today...
Hey! Get a hold of yourself!
The one with the glasses invited me...
Are you alright?! Hey!
Kaoru-san invited you?
Yes.
What the heck are you doing?! Hey!
Is it okay for a newcomer like me to intrude?
Get up already!
Oh, of course.
What's wrong with you today?
The more the merrier!
Really? Good.
Oh, so it was Kaoru-san.
She's beautiful...
Kaoru-san must have a weakness for pretty faces.
What is it?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that your hat is really stylish.
Oh, this?
Even if I wore it, I would still look like a country girl.
Oh, that's not true.
Pardon me.
Ricchan, when did you change your hairstyle?
Yurika-san did it for me.
How is it?
It looks great. Really cute!
Oh, that's right.
I heard your family owns a record shop, Ritsuko-chan.
Yes... Do you like jazz, Yurika-san?
These two practice playing jazz together just about every day.
They play jazz?
Yeah.
Kaoru-san plays piano, and Sentaro is on drums.
That's really something!
I know some people who listen to jazz,
but I've never met anyone who plays it!
My two big brothers like jazz, so I listen every once in a while as well.
My brothers frown and get a wrinkle between their eyebrows while they listen,
but I prefer music that really hits you with a bang, you know?
Y-Yeah! That's it!
I'd like to hear you play the drums.
Y-Y-You can't!
I still, uh... stink at it!
Oh, but you know you can't get better at music unless you have an audience.
Come on, let me hear you play.
This... is an unexpected development.
Ow!
Oh, no! I think I got scratched by a branch.
Well, what do you know?
Looks like he's got the moves.
Say, I heard a rumor that couples who climb together
to the top of that rock will get married.
No girl's gonna get up that!
Bon, you up for it?
Why me?
Oh, I'm not letting you get away with saying that.
I can climb that far!
Would anyone like to go with me?
Go on, already!
Y-You can't!
I mean, the sign says it's off limits...
and it's dangerous.
Oh, that's too bad.
I really wanted to see the view from up there.
You shouldn't have wolfed it down!
Those two seem to be getting on well.
Kaoru-san... you can have this.
Where are you going?
I'm just going to pick some flowers!
Probably the bathroom...
Boy, this onigiri is huge.
It's my fault.
I hurt Ricchan.
In the cruelest possible way...
...I made the girl who's most important to me cry.
Those shoulders look so sad, but I have no right...
...to try to comfort her.
Good morning, Kaoru-san.
Good morning.
Bon!
C-Come with me a sec!
This! This handkerchief!
Yurika-san gave it to me as an apology for my towel yesterday!
It smells kinda nice.
Or is it my imagination?
What the hell was that for?
Kaoru-san?!
I couldn't let you pick up this handkerchief!
I couldn't bear seeing that!
You can have the handkerchief back.
I behaved badly.
It's all my fault.
What are you talkin' about?!
Spill it!
Shut up!
You're satisfied as long as you have this handkerchief, right?!
Go home and sniff on it all you want!
That's enough.
You lookin' to start a fight?
Stop it!
Sentaro, let go of Kaoru-san!
This is stupid.
Don't get rough with him!
You owe Kaoru-san an apology!
I don't owe that guy nothin'.
Wait, Sentaro!
You can't forget this.
This handkerchief is important to you, isn't it?
Kaoru-san...
I bet Sentaro is drumming away like a madman right about now.
Bon, you stupid idiot!
Like that...
It's easier to make up if you do it early on.
Come with me to practice.
No...
Kaoru-san, before you moved here,
Sentaro always practiced alone.
Shutting himself up in the basement, not letting anyone near him...
Even I didn't feel welcome in the basement.
But ever since you came, Kaoru-san, that feeling's gone.
I'm positive he was happy to find a friend he could play jazz with.
Kaoru-san, shall I guess what you two were fighting about today?
You like Yurika-san, don't you?
So you got mad at Sentaro
for showing off that handkerchief.
She is really pretty.
I wish I'd been born with looks like that.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Ricchan, you're plenty...
...a-attractive.
Thanks for trying to cheer me up, Kaoru-san.
I'm not... I wasn't...
I wasn't trying to cheer you up.
I...
Here we are!
Well, good luck!
Hey! Ricchan!
Open up!
Let me out, Ricchan!
What's the ruckus, Ritsuko?
Drastic measures.
I-I didn't come here to see you.
What?
N-Nothing.
He has the same feelings for the girl he likes.
Hey, don't just jump in!
Huh?
I wasn't jumpin' into anything.
He's jumping in again.
What the heck is this?!
It's jazz with a festive beat!
Cut it out! I can't play if I'm laughing!
Next time,
maybe I'll play something just for Ricchan.
And then...
maybe I'll try letting her know how I feel.
Sentaro-kun...
I'm coming in.
Oh, don't be so stiff.
What the...
...hell is he doing?!
I'm sure Ricchan is thinking about him.
But, meanwhile...
he's...
Um, Ricchan...
There's a song that I'd like to play for you.
Actually, I wanted to practice a little more first...
...but I feel like I have to play this piece I've secretly been practicing for her right now.
Play through me, Bill Evans.
"Someday My Prince Will Come".
It means my prince will arrive someday.
So are you the prince, Kaoru-san?
I'm right, aren't I?
You've been practicing for Yurika-san, right?
And this is your "dress rehearsal"!
No.
This is the real performance.
The one I like... is you.
You don't have to give me a reply right away.
I just wanted to let you know...
...that there's somebody here who's in love with you.
Ricchan's eyes are on him.
She's always thinking of him.
Still, that doesn't bother me right now.
You taught me that it was possible to fall in love like this.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.