When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Milady, good morning.
Come now.
Wake up.
Hey, it's still 32:00.
Note: In Japan, the clock for TV late-night programming runs past 24:00 into the next day
Let me sleep a little more.
Please don't say that.
Today's a great day outside.
How about going out once in a while?
I'll pack a bento for you.
Riceball-san. Riceball-san.
Newspaper Headlines: High School Girls Ultra Quiz!!
Must compete as a pair of best friends.
Look.
There are many spring-like events.
How does this look?
The High School Girl Ultra Quiz.
You must compete as a pair with your best friend.
Not interested.
I'd rather see the faces of those
who choose to compete in these.
What a waste. It says it accepts walk-in challengers.
The prize is-
Milady?
This is the prize when I win this competition?
This... This will...
This will become mine?!
All right, let's compete!
Why?
That's the story. So do you want to pair up with me?
So? Okay? Good? Yay?
What? You're in Osaka now?
What? Go alone?
Damn, she hung up.
Looks like Sakuya-san wasn't available.
Then I'll try Isumi next.
No, she's a bad choice.
Who can I pair up with?
Why don't you go, Hayate-kun?
If we need a high school girl appearance, I have several patterns ready.
Oh yeah. That's a trick we can use!
I... I'll go look for someone who's willing to be your partner.
Damn, he got away.
Hmm, a quiz tournament, eh.
Would competing in this create
an extra page in the diary of youth?
What I'm most interested in is that...
...they have an all-you-can-eat coupon at
blah blah shabu shabu restaurant!
This sounds good.
Image, on.
Oh my god. Oh my god!
What a big dream I just had.
But... if I do win... maybe I can ask him.
Can I ask him?
B-But...
Who... Who...
Who can I go compete with?!
Owwie.
Hayate-kun?!
Nishizawa-san. I-I'm sorry.
I was caught up in my thoughts.
This is...
Oh, this is it! What good, good timing.
Nishizawa-san.
Y-Yes.
Could you be a partner for this quiz tournament?
I-I will.
That's great! Lady Nagi will be happy.
This week, I will lead the story as the host.
Tima~
Shine! Jump! Shake your booty.
The 4256th High School Girl Ultra Quiz!
It has finally started with hundreds of thousands of
audience members who're a pain in the neck to draw.
Your host and MC will be me, Mikiri Teruo, and...
Abe Maou ~tima.
By the way,
anyone out there remember me ~tima?
Hey, don't try to stand out, boob monster.
I'm sorry ~tima.
Let's have the competitors come in.
We have a total of ten thousand pairs from around the nation.
Who will be the one to answer
all the quizzes and claim victory?!
Can't wait to find out ~tima.
Aika-san, why are we here?
Because I thought you like shabu shabu, Chiharu-san.
Why do I have to pair up with the Hamster?
That's what I want to ask you.
I'm practically taking a handicap like this.
Resist. Resist, me.
Anyway, I can win this myself,
so I don't care if my partner is Ham or Sausage.
I must resist this. What will I do if my future boss at wherever I work turns out to be a big sexual harasser?
Plus, this is the very first request made of me by Hayate-kun.
Let's win this and take the trophy.
When I win this, I'm going to go eat shabu shabu with Hayate-kun.
What are you talking about? I'll never allow that!
What?
If you want to eat, go alone with your lonely heart.
Never. Even if you say I can't, it's too late now.
I can't back out anymore.
Both Hayate and the trophy belong to me!
Hayate-kun will go have shabu shabu with me!
I swore to myself that this year, I will chase Hayate-kun even to the ends of the Earth.
Looks like both of them are ready for the fight.
Let's get the first stage going!
First trial is the famous, Yes or No Quiz ~tima!
Please move to the side you think is the answer to the question ~tima.
Picking the answer from two choices is easy.
We can't go anywhere unless we get it right.
Problem one!
You find Ishikawa Station in the Ishikawa Prefecture.
They're trying to pull off a trick question,
yet they're actually testing the honesty of the competitors.
The answer is obviously "Yes"!
This way! It's "No"!
I think it's "Yes"!
Do as I say!
Argumentative pair, please choose an answer already ~tima.
Don't be a drag from the beginning!
Time up!
The answer is...
"No".
You find this station in Aomori Prefecture.
To the incorrect pairs, "Good-bye Baby!"
See? What'd I tell you?
This is a common sense problem if you play ******** *S.
If you know the answer, say so sooner!
Problem two.
Chimpanzees and giant pandas.
Newborn giant pandas weigh less than newborn chimpanzees.
They're called "giant", so I'm sure a panda has to weigh more.
The answer must be "No".
The answer is "Yes"! I'm sure of it!
It's "No"! Stay out of my way!
It's "Yes"! Just come with me!
It's that pair again.
I'm telling you, it's "Yes"!
Okay, the answer is...
"Yes"!
Bye-bye to pairs who chose "No".
See? Baby giant pandas are 15cm tall and weigh only 90 - 130g.
I saw it on Animal ***net.
Tell me that first!
Problem three is about Japanese sake.
The temperature of "warm" sake is 40°C.
This problem isn't targeting the right audience ~tima.
What's the problem? You can
go back to your agency if you want.
Please don't, I beg you ~tima.
No one's moving.
Legally, sake is something high school girls
don't have anything to do with.
Ah, right. I forgot to tell you.
In this quiz, all pairs have life-lines that they can use.
It's totally a copy of Who Wants to be a Mil****aire.
There. Take it. It's yours.
It feels like a rule made just for this problem.
However, you can only use one of the choices ~tima.
Think well.
Telephone!
The Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair is using the telephone.
They're such wimps.
What? What should I do?
You're putting me on the hot seat already?
But, I do know the answer.
The answer is-
Yes.
The answer is "No".
The temperature of "warm" sake is approximately 45°C.
Great, Maria! I knew I could count on you.
And for your reference, there are: boiling, hot, warm, lukewarm, body temperature, and sunshine.
What about me...
The answer is "No".
There were no incorrect pairs.
Drop the bomb.
You saved us, Maria.
Thank you.
Keep it up.
Let's now move to the second stage.
The next one is also famous, the Scatter Away Quiz.
Pick up a quiz that gets scattered from the sky.
The time limit is five minutes.
You'll move on to the next stage if you can answer even one question ~tima.
Let's go!
All right, I'll go!
It's fine, I'll go.
Hush. You play with this.
Ahh, this popping. You can't stop once you start.
Hey, she's gone already!
I'm telling you to stay out of my way.
What's wrong?
Muscle cramp...
Geez, you...
I'm actually not good at running.
Too bad, you picked a losing card ~tima.
Actually, most of the envelopes contain false cards, so good luck ~tima.
Oh boy.
Get moving. You don't have any stamina, do you?
Are you in a position to say that?
Get a move on!
'Kay, 'kay, 'kay.
You lose. You lose. You lose.
We might not have any more chances.
I will not give up.
Eh?
I will keep moving for Hayate and the trophy's sake!
Even if my leg's cramping!
You're right. Shabu shabu with
Hayate-kun waits beyond this ordeal.
You're still wishing for such a nonchalant event?
I'm sure Hayate-kun likes shabu shabu, too!
The trophy!
The shabu shabu!
One minute left ~tima.
Oh no!
Open it please.
Okay.
You lose.
Just kidding. Here's your question.
Don't confuse us!
How much does it cost to ride
the Yamanote line for one station?
Um... Two thousand-
As of 2008, it's ¥130.
You got it right ~tima.
Easy peasy.
Have you witnessed the power that normality represents?
Moving on to the third stage.
Break Out of a Sealed Room Quiz ~tima!
If you can get out of that room within three minutes, you are eligible to answer the question.
I guess I'll leave this to a commoner.
What? It won't open!
The window won't either!
Nor the floor...
None of them look like they'll open.
If it means getting out, it doesn't matter how.
That's the way commoners do it.
Don't mind if I go out first.
A skyscraper?!
Twenty seconds left.
Where is it? I don't see anything.
God. You're so useless.
In games where you get out of a sealed room, you usually...
First you do this,
and find this here,
then when you do this,
you can open this to find this,
which you put in the slot, and...
No way.
It opened!
You made it out ~tima!
Congratulations. Here's your problem.
No way!
The very first game console sold in the world, back in 1972, was...
Um...
**telli-
Od**sey.
You got it right ~tima!
Next is finally the final stage!
I guess you paid the debt back you owed me in the second stage.
After all, all we need is my brain.
When the final stage ends,
will the Goddess of Victory bless these two?
Mikiri-san, I just noticed that your voice sounds identical to the narration voice we usually hear in this show ~tima.
Your "tima" is annoying!
Tima ~tima.
Also, there may or may not be some changes in this love triangle over the butler.
Continues in the second half.
Tima~
Keidoumyaku
Keidoumyaku = Carotid artery
Kuttemo sugu neruna!
Kuttemo sugu neruna = Don't eat right after you go to bed!
Everyone, do you want to go to New York?
Yes, I do!
Then pay for yourself.
I don't have the money!
Let's have our finalists come out ~tima.
Here's the first pair.
"We're so close we get in baths together."
Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair ~tima!
Don't introduce us like that!
Who leaked the information?!
The second pair is,
"We were supposed to have more screentime after the third season."
Kasumi Aika and Harukaze Chiharu pair!
What? The student council vice president and secretary?
Aika-san. We made it to the finals somehow.
Yes, we did, Chiharu-san.
Here's the third and final pair.
"We always eat the strawberry first when we have shortcakes and menma first when we have ramen."
You do?
I guess.
The expected winner of the tournament.
Katsura Hinagiku-Hanabishi Miki pair.
What? Even Hinagiku was in it?
Hey, I followed you because you wanted me to help you pick a gift for your relative who's being admitted to his top choice school.
Why did I end up here?
Basically, I want to make the prize money the gift.
With Hina-chan there, they have to be the winners.
I think I can get some good footage.
Go! Go! Milady!
You can do it! You can do it!
Hey, sit down! We can't see!
I'm sorry. I'll control myself.
Let's forget about the cheer groups
that stand out more than the actual competitors.
The final stage.
Don't Slip! Press the Button Quiz ~tima.
When you get an answer right,
the other groups' slides will rise a bit at a time ~tima.
The pair that remains up there to the end wins ~tima!
With Hina next to me, there's nothing to worry about.
Oh. So this height is already cracking her limit.
I-I'm fine.
I-I'm fine as long as we're at this height.
We'll answer all the questions.
I won't allow you to make any mistakes.
Okay? Okay?
This is the battle I can't lose.
I made it this far. I can't afford to lose.
Problem one!
I think, therefore I exist.
Say it in Latin.
Cogito ergo sum.
Correct ~tima.
Here's the next problem.
Those who understands coffee's true-
Barista.
Correct!
The quantum mechanical paradoxical thought experiment-
Schrödinger's cat!
Treaty of Meerssen!
Diary of Sarashino!
Nimouson!
Permin!
Ucchari!
Amazing! Katsura-Hanabishi pair is making this a landslide.
Keep it up.
You should answer some, too.
Aika-san...
To tell the truth, I'm coming to my limit.
Y-You, too, Chiharu-san?
You're right. Then let's take our leave, shall we?
What? She's gone already.
I'll follow you!
Kasumi-Harukaze pair, disqualified.
Meanwhile, Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair
seems to be in a tight spot, too ~tima.
Must answer...
...the next one...
Problem!
What fathers don't like is...
It's mine!
Papaya!
Pun Note: Papaya = Papaiya = Papa iya = Papa hates.
...papaya, but instead...
...name four other tropical fruits.
Kiwi, mango, pineapple, durian.
She gets it right again ~tima!
It's like sitting on a banana peel!
What will Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair do?
The angle is starting to get really nice ~tima.
You're disqualified when either one of you falls ~tima.
Don't copy me.
I think I'm at my limit. I think... I think...
This is nothing.
For Hayate's sake!
I will win and get the trophy!
Why is Nagi-chan all "trophy, trophy"?
Oh yeah, the trophy I saw on the flier...
It looked like Hayate-kun.
Nagi-chan...
I can't anymore!
Hayate...
You've got to fight for it.
You want to win the trophy, right?
Let's keep trying just a little more.
Ham...
I bet when we combine forces, there's nothing to fear.
Yeah! Let's do this!
Here's the problem.
What dango becomes quiet the moment you look at it?
That's it!
Go ahead, Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair.
Pun Note: Mitara = If you look at it; Shi~ = Onomatopoeia for asking for silence.
Mitara... shi~
Mitarashi dango.
Correct!
You did it!
How many letters were in the longest episode title ever for an anime made in Japan?
Leave this to me!
Episode 26 of School Ru**le with 187 letters!
Correct ~tima!
Well done, Nagi-chan!
Statue!
Matanpo!
Sam!
Iropaka!
No way! I'm getting pushed up?!
Rather, how is she pressing the button in that state?
That is a curious question... but we're...
You can do it!
Keep it up!
Will this one be the last problem?
At the cake house known for Koyuki's Special Seafood Cake,
how much do the cream puffs cost?
We know!
It's impossible for them to press it, but let's hear the answer.
Um...
It was...
¥200 a puff!
Correct ~tima!!!
Looks like this is the end.
Adieu!
That was a great fall.
The Katsura-Hanabishi pair takes an unexpected fall ~tima!
Therefore, the winner is the Sanzenin-Nishizawa pair.
I'm surprised you remembered the price.
Same to you.
For a hamster, you did pretty well.
For a pampered lady, you had some guts.
Oh yeah, the trophy!
Give it to me!
What should I do with this...
Maybe I'll go with my family, after all.
Nishizawa-san!
Ha... Hayate-kun.
Congratulations on your victory.
It was an amazing battle.
It embarrasses me a little to hear that.
Th-Thank you.
No, I should be the one thanking you.
Thank you very much.
I hope we stay on good terms like this, Nishizawa-san.
Yes, of course.
Hayate-kun. The day you accept my feelings might still be a long way away.
But, even so, I can continue to keep thinking about you, right?
Right?
What are you doing, Hayate?
We're going home!
We'll have a party tonight!
Yes, Milady.
Ah, wait!
Yes?
If you need something, say it already, Hamster.
Um, if you two want to...
Can we go eat shabu shabu together?
Can we?
Milady.
Sure.
Honestly, what thin meat!
Obviously, since it's shabu shabu.
What? You dare say that when I came with you?
You have a problem?
Calm down. I'll scoop all the lye out, okay?
By the way, shabu shabu is very healthy, and it's recommended for middle-aged people living alone, too.
Next week, we'll fight against the ¥150,000,000 we've all forgotten about.
Man, I had a lot of lines this episode.
Nagi and,
Hayate's
Butler Network!
Say my name! I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
Hayate no Gotoku has reached
episode 50 before anyone knew it.
The story's coming to the climax.
Will Hayate be able to defeat
General I-Will-Wrap-Everything-Up?
I'm not sure...
By the way, this is your character song, isn't it?
Yes. So you know, next week will be the last of the Butler Networks.
I must be the one to wrap everything up.
Therefore the service shot is me, too.
Milady, that's naughty of you.
No worries. Next week will be you cross-dressed bathing.
EHHH?!
See you again.
What? Milady's important online shopping merchandise?
Yes. Can you go pick it up from this shop?
Yes, ma'am. Right away.
Don't rush so much!
Why?
I don't want to see your face all of a sudden!
Mister Ayasaki.
I will give you these ¥150,000,000 as a gift to you.
I'm here to headhunt you for our company.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Spring.
Don't be such a stranger, Hayate!
I will protect Milady!