Hear ye, all Gamindustri residents far and wide.
We take one giant leap toward a new era today.
It brings me great pleasure to be together with you all
as we welcome this joyous day.
As you all know,
this world has been torn by strife over the past few years.
Lastation, governed by its CPU, the goddess Black Heart.
Lowee, governed by its CPU, the goddess White Heart.
Leanbox, governed by its CPU, the goddess Green Heart.
And Planeptune, governed by myself, the goddess Purple Heart.
Share Energy forms the basis of national power in this world.
The four nations competed over it, and sometimes we goddesses ourselves came to blows.
But now that will become
a thing of the past.
The treaty of friendship that shall be signed today
will prohibit taking Share Energy by force.
From this point onward, the only way to acquire it will be by making one's country a better place,
which will lead to worldwide development and progress.
We hereby swear to overcome the past and create a world filled with hope.
Yahoo!
Done and dusted!
The difference between your two forms never fails to amaze me, Neptune.
That aside, what'd you think of my speech, Noire?
Well, it wasn't bad...
Though I'm pretty sure Histoire wrote it for you.
It sure pisses me off that you got to hog the spotlight.
C'mon, Blanc. Don't say that!
I regret using rock-paper-scissors to decide the speaker.
Why don't you just let it go?
Saying that now just makes you sound immature.
She's right!
After all, we're no longer enemies!
We're best buds now, right?
A month has already passed since that amazing ceremony.
You aren't fulfilling any of your
responsibilities as CPU, Neptune!
Sonic jump!
Fiddlesticks!
Are you listening to me?
Well, I guess these peaceful days just turned my brain to mush!
Neptune, CPUs have all kinds of work—
Sis!
Tea's ready!
Thanks, Nepgear!
Wanna go head-to-head?
Sure!
Not you too, Nepgear!
Knock it off!
Zoinks!
Hey, the manual said not to do that!
Don't try this at home, kids!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#01 Planeptune's Goddess (Neptune)
Iffy!
Compa!
Done with work?
Yes.
I'm on my way to Nep-Nep's place.
Oh, then I'll go with you.
Under the right rules and regulations—
Take a look at this!
At the Share Crystal, not me!
What about it?
The amount of Share Energy gathered in our country's Share Crystal
is currently showing a downward trend.
There's still a whole bunch.
No need to worry, right?
Of course there is!
You know where we get Shares from, don't you?
Oh...
The feelings of trust that the citizens place in the CPU who rules them, right?
Indeed.
This downward trend shows that our citizens are slowly falling out of love with Neptune!
Say what?
I don't remember doing anything that'd make them hate me.
I don't think you've done anything recently that'd make them love you, either.
W-Well...
Nepgear's right.
We're sorry, Lady Histoire.
We just happened to overhear the conversation.
I don't mind if it's you two.
Not you too, Iffy!
Are you gonna take Histy's side as well?
But you're different, right, Compa?
Look at this, Nep-Nep.
Huh?
"We don't need goddesses."
Ack!
In order to make these people understand you,
you need to work much harder at your job.
She hit my weak point for massive damage!
I'm in big trouble!
It's this nation that's in big trouble!
For one thing, CPUs are supposed to devote all their blood, sweat, and tears to their citizens!
That is why you possess the great powers that you do.
Man, lectures are the worst.
With great power comes great responsibility!
How can I get away from here?
Oh, right!
I'll go learn what it means to be a CPU!
Huh?
Learn? From whom?
Uh... Noire!
What?!
Lastation's Noire!
I don't really get what's happening here, you see.
Mind explaining to me why a neighboring country's CPU is sleeping at our Basilicom?!
Oh, just pretend I'm not here and carry on with your job.
I don't mind.
Well, I do!
We're so sorry, Noire.
Sis!
What's the big deal?
Aren't you here to learn what it means to be a CPU?
Sorry, but I'll have to refuse.
I don't intend to extend an olive branch to my enemies.
Hey, I'm not your enemy!
We signed a treaty of friendship!
We're budd—
Doesn't change the fact that we're still competing over Share Energy.
You're still my enemy.
See, you keep saying all these totally uncute things!
That's why people say you have no friends!
I-I do have a friend!
Really?
Who?
Where are they from? What do they do?
Huh?
Uh... Well...
I'm done with those documents, Sis.
Hey there, Uni.
Just put them over there.
U-Um...
I was quite fast this time, wasn't I?
I gave it my all—
Guess so.
You've reached normal levels now, I suppose.
Hey!
Is Uni that so-called friend of yours?
I don't think you can call your sister a friend.
You've got the wrong idea.
I have other—
Really?
That's what you say, but aren't you just a loner?
No way!
Nepgear...
Sorry my sister had to butt in.
Nah, it's fine.
That's how Sis always is with me.
Looks like she won't ever praise me unless I do a better job than she would.
We all know that's just not gonna happen, though.
Uni...
I can't even transform yet.
That goes for me, Rom, and Ram too.
I-I guess...
I'm sure I'll be the first out of the four of us to get the ability to transform.
That's the spirit! I'm not gonna lose to you!
A text from Rom...
Why does she know I'm here in Lastation?
I told her.
She got really jealous.
Nepgear and Uni must be having such a nice time hanging out together.
Why can't I go visit another country?!
Don't be so selfish.
I wanna go hang out with Nepgear and Uni too!
I'm trying to work.
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Hey!
Shut yer mouth!
I said I was working! You friggin' deaf?!
You're such a meanie.
Let's go, Rom.
Wait, Ram!
Sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
We'd been fighting each other for a long time.
But unlike us, your sisters are so innocent.
I wonder if we can be friendlier to each other too.
Just because we stopped using force
doesn't mean we can become the best of friends overnight.
More importantly...
Yes, please allow me to continue with my proposal.
Whoa!
Stop!
Get your hands off those documents!
What?
But being a CPU starts with sorting out documents—
Do that at your own workplace!
Tch.
You're such a wet blanket.
Where do you get off being so condescending?!
Um...
You've got monster hunting requests from your citizens, right?
How about teaching Neptune what it means to be a CPU while we're at it?
Oh, she wouldn't need to lay a finger on any of the documents that way.
I suppose you're right.
This looks good.
It's nice and close to the border, too.
Does that mean you're telling us to go back to Planeptune after we're done?
Well duh.
I can't work with you around.
All right, everyone!
Time to go monster hunting!
Yeah!
Wait, why are you acting like the leader?!
We need to go monster hunting in two places.
The Nursune Plains and the Trune Caves nearby.
Both of them should be pretty easy to hand—
Sis.
What?
Nobody's listening.
Gosh, I'm pooped!
You okay, Compa?
Is this the famous "you can't read what it says from the back" sign?!
Sis...
That's how most signs work.
Hey!
We're behind schedule.
You take this way too seriously, Noire!
Problem?
Don't you ever get tired of it?
It's no big deal.
I want to create a much, much better nation.
Well, so do I,
but I'd much rather have fun doing it.
You have too much fun doing this!
She came!
Ah, my goddess!
It's Black Heart!
Oh no!
Access!
What?!
You're gonna transform now?!
Rule number two of being a CPU:
let your people bear full witness to your majesty.
Could you all give me some information about the monsters, please?
You just transformed in front of them.
What's so majestic about that?
So this is the Nursune Plains, huh?
Yes. A mass outbreak of Dogoos here is causing a lot of problems.
Understood.
It seems Neptune and Nepgear, our neighbors from Planeptune,
will eliminate them for us.
Zoinks!
That came out of nowhere!
We're supposed to do this?
Rule number 3:
show off at every opportunity.
I'll take some pictures so you can use them as PR.
This is such a pain.
Though, well, these Dogoos are easy as pie to deal with.
Let's do this!
Nepgear!
Okay, Sis!
I was not born
To be a puppet on a string
I embrace these irreplaceable feelings and keep them safe
Way to go, Nepgear!
In these radiant lands heading toward an age of reform
That's my sis!
Thanks!
I picture the world of my dreams
And let it ride the first rays of sunshine
Chest!
I'm gonna give it all I've got!
I hear from far away
A faint voice that calls my name
And burns itself into my memories
There are way too many of them.
Everyone wanders forever
We should help, Iffy!
In search of an answer
Right.
Letting their faint yet violent
Iffy! Compa!
Flame of life burn away
Here I come!
Their eyes speak of their desires
And shine a ray of light in the darkness
Too good for them!
So I reach out to the future
We've basically won alread—
It may be a thorny road, but I have nothing to fear
Because you're there with me
Sis,
we should help out—
Nope.
The point is for them to deal with this themselves.
Where do you think you're touching?!
Everyone wanders forever
Eww, majorly gross!
In search of an answer
Hey, stay out of there!
Letting their faint yet violent
Flame of life burn away
This tickles!
I'm gonna die!
Their eyes speak of their desires
And shine a ray of light in the darkness
I...can't...
So I reach out to the future
It may be a thorny road but I have nothing to fear
Because you're there with me
I'm gonna send your souls all the way back to Hell!
Spectral Edge!
Neptune...
Quit slacking.
I don't even wanna look at jelly or meat buns for a while.
Why didn't you activate your HDD form?
Those Dogoos would have been easy pickings if you'd transformed!
Well,
all's well that ends well, right?
You just had other people do your job for you!
That's why your Share—
Fine, be as lazy as you want.
I'll handle the rest myself.
Show me the way to the Trune Caves.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
I'll go with you.
No, that won't be necessary.
Stay here and help these guys recover.
'Kay.
This way.
Thanks.
Noire's so short-tempered.
Oh, Uni!
Did you take any cool pics?
Wow!
Super cute!
They're going straight to my email address!
Begone!
A dead end, huh?
Guess I'm done here.
An Ancient Dragon?!
Quite the strong one, aren't we?
Take this!
Hey there!
You...
Why'd you go back to normal?
I'm not sure. It happened really suddenly—
Neptune!
Noire.
You're supposed to transform at times like these.
Pay close attention!
Behold the power of a goddess!
Stop trying to act cool!
Thanks.
Leave this one to me.
Cross Combo!
I-I didn't need your help!
I would've been fine by myself.
I'm sure.
But helping each other is what friends do.
It's not like I consider you a friend—
Why'd you choose this area?
Because I wanted you to leave—
Because you figured rumors would spread across the border
and Planeptune would hear about my valiant efforts?
That way, I could replenish some of my Share Energy.
Thank you, Noire.
But we also gotta let everyone know about the goddess who almost got her butt kicked!
What?!
Keep that a secret!
Listen to this, guys!
Hey!
Noire lost!
Neptune!
We're friends, right?!
Hey!
Black Heart and Purple Heart
killed the monsters with a hyper magic combo!
Hooray!
That story gets crazier every time...
Why did my transformation revert?
Oh, so they purged all the monsters in the caves for us?
Now we can look for you-know-what without having eyes on the back of our heads.
Amazing!
I'd expect nothing less from Noire.
Zoinks!
You mean "Neptune," right?
I'm still not convinced you're behind all this.
I've come to this universe of countless stars
That's harsh, Histy!
To start our search for the ultimate game
What's wrong, Nepgear?
Someone put up some really weird pictures of me online.
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
Huh? Those are all the pictures I sent to my email address!
What are you getting so serious for?
You're so cute, Nepgear!
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
This is so embarrassing!
I get you. I really do
Are you sure you sent it to the right address?
It's not love
But there's desire
Of course I did—
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Oops.
I sent it to the address of a public mailing list...
Let's start a New Game+
I knew it.
But the response seems pretty positive!
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
"Visual shock"?
This rectangle pulse
"It hit just the right spot"!
is a love song
"Planeptune's still got a lot left in the tank."
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Wow, people love it!
Huh?
Friendship, love, bifrost
Don't tell me the reason our Share Energy went up so suddenly...
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
...was because of these pictures?!
You're amazing, Nepgear!
R-Really?
Good job, my sweet heart
Then if we spread these things around even more...
Huh?
Do it for our Shares, Nepgear. For the Shares!
See you next week!
Hey, hold on, Sis!
I'm worried about where this country is headed in more ways than one.
I'll post it all over the place!
Stop!
Under the right rules and regulations—
Wh-What is this?
Lowee's terror (lickorrist)
It's an explosion of art!