Takasu-kun, what would you do
if I showed you the real me?
Would you fall for me?
Well?
H-Hold on!
I-I'm...
Taiga?
Are they there?
Oh, my.
Does this look bad?
Was my timing off?
- Th-This isn't how it looks!
- Ta-i-ga!
Minorin!
Nobody's here!
Then where'd they go?
Oh-ho.
Why did you lie?
Maybe you don't want to admit...
that he invited another girl to his place?
Shut up, stupid! Don't make it sound weird!
Aww, but...!
But nothing!
Tell her the truth, now!
The truth?
- Omigod, Takasu-kun...
- H-Hey!
Ta-Taiga?
Taiga!
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
warete baribari
Cracking and crumbling.
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Pool's Open
Good morning!
Taiga-chan? Is something wrong?
Nope, nothing wrong with me.
What's for dinner tonight?
A takikomi rice dish.
One of your favorites.
Oh?
Should've added red beans to celebrate.
- Right, fugly bird?
- F-Fugly?
H-Hey, Taiga...
About earlier...
- Fug... Fug, fug...
- Kawashima was just messing with you.
- Fug, fug, fug...
- Just saying, since it put you in a bad mood.
Sorry about that.
Oh? And why are you apologizing?
You're so weird, Ryuji.
I-Inko-chan!?
G-Get up, Inko-chan!
Hold on!
Taiga!
Wake up!
Man, we've got no time...
O-Ow...
Huh?
M-My bad...
What?
Anyway, we overslept!
Quick, get dressed!
What's for breakfast?
Why would you wake me up this way?
No time for breakfast, or lunch!
We've gotta leave in five
minutes or we'll be late!
Oh man...
We need to drop by a convenience store
or we won't have anything for lunch!
Hey, did you hear me?
Tai-gah!?
Loud and clear, you sick mutt!
Convenience store!
Why're you so pissed about
missing one meal—
Ow!
We made it...
There you are! Finally!
Thanks for all your help yesterday.
Huh? Oh, y-yeah...
What's with the look?
Oh, are you mesmerized
by my summer uniform?
Just kidding!
You're holding up traffic,
dumb Chihuahua.
O-Oh, there you are, Aisaka-san.
Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san.
I see you're already in heat.
Hey, girls...
Ah, I get it.
Like, omigod...
Don't get too jealous
over one little incident.
You're totally reading into it.
You dimwit.
I only did that because—
Booya!
Top o' the mornin' to ya!
Ooh, this might help tone my upper arms!
Mi-Minorin, don't use me as a weight...
On the topic of opening the pool:
Okay, since the pool's finally
opening tomorrow,
I'm going to cover some key pointers now.
Summer provides opportunities
for romantic adventures!
My final chance as a twenty-something!
Gross, my tummy will stick out...
Yikes, my thighs...
I'm more worried about my upper arms...
Why are you girls complaining?
You're still young, dammit!
What? This school has co-ed
swimming classes?
Omigod, that's so embarrassing!
Why?
You're a total doll.
Hell, you're a model.
What is there to be embarrassed about?
What is there, huh? Tell
me. I'd love to know.
Swimsuits must be black or navy blue.
Shoulder straps mandatory.
- Teach, homeroom's almost over!
- What the hell is there, damn it!?
Fine! End this!
Stand!
Taiga, hurry up!
No way! I don't need to buy a swimsuit!
But the one you wore last year
got all moldy and gross.
You have to wash and dry
swimsuits right away.
Knock it off!
And why is that thing tagging along?
Because this is the only place
that sells swimsuits.
I-I didn't invite her!
Guys, check it out!
This would look perfect on Aisaka-san!
A little too perfect, even!
Stay calm, Taiga!
People are watching!
Takasu-kun, what do you think of this one?
Huh?
Uh...
It's uh, nice...
Hey.
How about this one?
Anything weird about it?
It won't make me stand out, will it?
Why are your legs so long!?
You'll stand out like a sore thumb!
What?
You think?
But I chose such a plain style...
Ka-Kawashima-san!
What brand is that?
Where did you find it?
Over there.
Oh, you want to get matching swimsuits?
A-Anything but that!
I beg of you!
Kushieda?
Hey, hey.
I'm, like, super-duper cute.
Scary, isn't it?
Even in this plain swimsuit!
How far can I take this?
The charm, the beauty, the bod!
It's a crime to keep this hidden, huh!?
You think so too, right, Takasu-kun?
Um...
Huh?
Hey.
You okay, Tai—
What are you doing!?
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
What do you mean? What's wrong?
I can't decide.
What's the problem?
You can only choose between
navy blue and black...
That's not it!
None of them fit!
Uh...
What if we tried something child-sized?
I'd rather die!
Don't you start sounding like
that dumb Chihuahua!
Th-This one's pretty small.
And it's not that expensive.
The material's solid and durable too.
You could even throw it in a dryer.
Did you try it on?
Well...
I tried it on...
And well...
It more or less fit...
But it was kinda...
Then this should do, yeah?
Yeah... I guess...
Taiga, what would you like for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want.
Oh, right. Are you ready for the pool?
Don't forget a towel. Well, it needs
to be a bath towel.
Shut up.
Now look here...
What are you so upset about?
The swimsuit?
Don't tell me you're still
mad about last night.
No!
Then what is it!?
I can't swim!
That's the problem!
That can't be the real reason.
Not if you're so ready to spill it.
Aw, I'm gonna be late!
Hang on.
Drink this first.
Thanks, Ryu-chan.
Hot!
What is that?
Ryu-chan's special soy milk.
The isoboing-boing thingies in soybeans are
supposed to help make your boobs bigger.
Isoflavones.
I can't let them shrivel,
so I'm taking precautions.
I'm so smart!
Taiga-chan's a pervy-pervy-perv!
Stop sexually harassing my mother!
I'm off!
Man, she makes such a racket...
What's wrong?
You're acting strange.
Soybeans...
H-Hey!
Gross! Give me more!
What are you doing!?
I need those isoboing-boings!
Why would you need...?
Swimsuit size...
And isoflavones...
Taiga.
Don't tell me you...
No! Don't say it!
Not another word!
You have...
a flat chest?
Honestly...
Is having small breasts
really such a big deal?
Sorry for taking so long.
N-No sweat.
Well?
Flat, right?
Like a board, right?
Uh, w-well...
Wh-What about the pads?
They're in...
But...
Th-They're sinking...
This is exactly why I hate the pool...
A-Anyway, put some real clothes on.
You'll catch a cold.
What's this?
Look, and understand my misery.
Pathetic boobs
This is...pretty bad.
Pathetic boobs?
Pathetic?
I'm so flat, it warrants pity!
Uh...
Well, that's just the opinion
of whoever wrote this.
Naturally, I left the photography
club awash in blood.
That explains why the photography
club suddenly shut down...
And I have to reveal this pathetic
body to Kitamura-kun...
I could never...
There's no way!
Hey, Taiga.
Got it.
I'll do something about it.
I'll make it so you can stand
in front of Kitamura...
with your chest puffed out.
It's okay.
You can go home and sleep.
Nah, I'll wait here while you work.
I'm staying up until you're finished.
Hey.
Um...
I just wanna say...
I'm being kinda weird and stubborn, so...
I'm sorry.
How are they?
I'll definitely be using these
when I get married...!
Maruo!
You look so much better without glasses!
You should wear contacts.
You think?
Totally! Right?
- I took off my glasses too...
- Totally.
Bye, Aisaka-san.
Girls' Changing Room
See you real soon.
Taiga!
Hurry up.
I'll do your hair.
Maya-chan, sorry about that!
I was having trouble getting my hair right!
Did I keep you waiting long?
Ami-chan!
Wow, it's so obvious you're a model.
I love your figure.
- What? That's not true.
- I'm kinda moved...
- No, you're way more developed than us.
- A goddess!
There you go again...
Like, duh.
I'm absolutely adorable today!
I'll allow the ignorant masses to prostrate
themselves before this heavenly angel!
Now, lick away at my shadow!
It must taste like gourmet food to you!
Jeez, don't tease me, Maya-chan.
Hey, Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run so fast!
My hair's gonna come undone!
Okay!
Time to warm up!
How about a quick run?
Nah, psych!
Minorin?
Kushieda?
Eureka, I've got it!
Nobody will see my belly
flab if I'm in the water.
I'm off for a dip!
Ciao!
Minorin...
Oh, Aisaka-san?
Finally.
I thought maybe your swimsuit was so loose
you were ashamed to show yourself in public.
What? Are you talking in your sleep?
Dream on.
I mean, c'mon.
Man...
Hope I don't get sunburned...
Perfection...
To grow so much in one year...
I'm still a fan of the tiger...
Oh, how average.
Though, you're still out of scale.
It worked!
Awesome!
The Bogus-Boobie Force.
She knows.
Minorin's really something.
Aisaka?
Huh? You're Aisaka, right?
I can't see a thing without my glasses...
But only Aisaka would be that size!
Why are you hiding?
I mean, that mouse hairdo
looks good on you.
G-Go away!
What!?
Did I say something wrong?
B-Beats me...
Hey, show us your biceps.
Like this?
Wow! Incredible!
Hogging the girls...
All to himself...!
We are against a class society!
Suffer the Summer Arriveth drop!
Maruo!
Hey.
Up for it?
Our class is typically unruly,
but isn't this getting a bit dangerous?
Right, Tai—
Kitamura-kun called my hair cute...
Uh, that wasn't how he put it...
Target acquired!
Here we go, comrade-in-softball!
Yeah!
Splash!
Right on! Next!
Gotcha, chief!
Ha-ha, you got thrown in.
Indeed, it looked like so much fun.
Y-You're...
Let's have some fun.
Don't get mad about this.
Yikes...
Hey, dial it down a bit.
Please, we're only playing.
Hey!
Taiga, you okay?
Taiga?
She's...
I can't swim!
No way...
She was serious!?
Shoot!
Hey!
- Hold on!
- C'mon, c'mon!
Taiga!
Teach!
- Whoa!
- N-No!
Calm down, Tai—
What should I do!?
A pad fell out!
But only one!
What!?
This looks bad...
Aisaka?
Taiga!
Aisaka!
- Stay away!
- I'm coming!
Taiga!
Damn...
In that case...
Taiga!
How humiliating...!
Oh, come on, I already apologized.
I didn't know you couldn't swim.
Everyone's gone home. Cheer up.
A simple sorry isn't going to cut it.
Your stupid prank was the reason
why my boo-boo-boobi—
Anyway!
Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize!
Apologize! Apologize! Apologize!
I guess Aisaka-san won't be able to join us
at the beach or pool if she can't swim!
So, Takasu-kun.
My family has a vacation home by the beach.
Would you like to spend vacation together?
What? Hold on.
Aren't you supposed to be
apologizing to Taiga?
Oh, fine...
Would you be willing if Yusaku joined us?
Oh? Something wrong, Aisaka-san?
Pull any more crap and I'll leak the
footage of you doing 100
impressions in a row.
Wait, wasn't it 150?
If you do that, I might sue you
for violating my privacy.
Even Little Miss Palm-top Tiger is
helpless against the law, right?
Hey, girls...
Cease this foolishness!
You'll only hurt...
your own fists.
B-But, but...!
Minori-chan, Aisaka-san keeps being so—
It's the dumb Chihuahua's fault!
What did you say!?
You were the one who—
Silence!
If you wish to forge a friendship with
your fists, fighting is not the way!
Settle this through sports!
S...Sports?
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
The battle for Takasu!
Ami-tan vs. Taiga!?
Why does Takasu get all the...!?
Ooh, yeah! Take me! Ravish me!