I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
A ship!
Hi! I just picked up your signal and,
well, I have a slight problem.
I'm kind of out of
fuel at the moment.
So if you could just
take me to Ganymede,
I'd really appreciate... it.
Dammit! Why is everyone
in such a hurry all the time?
Don't they know it's unhealthy?
Huh?
The house specialty is sea rat.
Used to be a staple food.
Harvested in the Ganymede sea.
After the gates stabilized,
food wasn't scarce anymore,
and people stopped eating it.
So they ran some fancy ad campaigns
and claimed it was a delicacy.
And? Is it tasty?
It's totally disgusting.
People eat it anyway for status.
It's "in" now.
Well, in that case, I guess I'm "out."
Lobster miso stew, please.
Order accepted. Arigato.
Well, I wanted to order the most
expensive thing on the menu.
Because you think when we bag
this guy, we're gonna be rich?
So Gatt was a spy, huh?
But Mom, there's nothing
to worry about now.
We blew his ship to pieces.
It doesn't matter.
One lost ampule doesn't mean much.
We'll continue as we initially planned,
but when things go wrong,
someone must take responsibility, right?
M-Momma...
You, Harrison?
I didn't! Mother...
Hey, waiter! Where's my sea rat sauté?
Come on, come on,
do that morphin' for my endorphin.
Yeah, it's Morgan.
It's a clean match.
Should we just grab him
and forget about breakfast?
Oh?
Young man, are you aware
that the Ganymede sea rat
is a very intelligent
and kind animal, hmm?
- What's that?
- That woman... who is she?
Well, I didn't know
the circus was in town.
Wha--
- Yeesh.
- I know I've seen that woman before.
Attention. We, the Space Warriors,
are eco-soldiers who work night and
day to preserve the environment
and protect endangered species
all over the universe.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I remember!
That woman has a 25 million bounty!
Mom, hurry!
Stop right there. Game over.
- Mom!
- Take it easy.
You don't want to see your
dear mother hurt now.
- You'd better let her go!
- How's our boy Morgan?
He's all full of holes.
Thanks to you, we lost our reward.
Fortunately, you're worth a lot more.
25 million'll buy a lotta lobster stew.
- Why--
- If you hurt her, we're gonna--
Hold your fire. These men are
professional bounty hunters.
- There's nothing we can do for now.
- Mom!
Take care of the base while I'm away.
- I'll be back in no time.
- Better hit the road, rat boys.
I don't think you wanna be here
when the police show up.
Hang in there, Mom!
Oh, Harrison, you'll get your
punishment later when I return.
- Mother! Mom!
- Let's go!
It's Harrison's lucky day.
Momma won't be back for a while.
Hey, you! Are you alive?
Take this...
to the ISSP...
But don't... don't open the case...
Oh no!
Hey, wait a minute!
What am I supposed
to do with this thing?
Universal Environmental Protection Society?
More like environmental terrorists.
They're called the Space Warriors.
Used to be a good group
of dedicated people
working to preserve the environment
and protect endangered species.
They did great work
all around the asteroids.
But a few years ago,
a new leader took over the group.
Everything changed.
Most of the members dropped out.
Those who are left are more violent
than the local crime syndicates.
They have a special thing
for the Ganymede sea rats.
And guess who's in charge
of these psycho terrorists?
Twinkle Maria Murdock.
Please do not associate us
with common terrorists.
We are warriors of peace, fighting
a noble battle for the law of nature.
Yeah, yeah...
We saw how peaceful you are.
Now how do we
pick up that reward?
The Ganymede police.
But the government just blocked it.
- What?
- I'm trying to track it.
Looks like the government
canceled their offer as of yesterday.
Why'd they do that?
When you're told not to open
something, well, who can resist?
Now, I didn't really open
this thing, you know.
It just opened up by itself.
Ah-ha...
We followed your instructions.
The bounty's been canceled.
We also have a bill that will protect
the sea rats from harvesting.
The sea rats on Ganymede will be safe.
Where. Is. Mom?
Well, whoever's got her
hasn't contacted us yet,
but we're trying to track them down.
If we catch them,
I promise you, we'll, uh...
If Mom isn't back here soon,
and I mean soon,
we'll set the plan
in motion immediately.
Wait! We're trying to do
everything you ask for!
We're carrying out your wish--
Whatever it is, you can't eat it,
and I'm starving.
Look at this, there's no record of
that terrorist attack we saw. Man...
What is going on?
I told you, you were wasting your time.
You must feel very foolish.
Might as well let me go. You've lost.
Not quite.
There's something behind all this.
Hi! I just picked up your signal and,
well, I have a slight problem.
I'm kind of out of
fuel at the moment.
I don't believe it.
If you could just take me to Ganymede,
I'd be very appreciative.
Please? Or if you could just
loan me a spare fuel rod,
I'd pay you back, of course.
Are you listening?!
I know you're there! Say something!
Ow...
That's what you did?
You took all the money you stole from us,
and you lost it gambling in a casino?
You know what they say, cowboy.
"Easy come, easy go."
They also say
"there's no honor among thieves."
- Got anything, Jet?
- Nah.
I have an old friend on Ganymede.
I'm trying to reach him.
Ah, man, there's nothing
even worth salvaging.
Huh? What's this?
No, we still don't know
where the virus is.
Yes, M-Mr. President.
We'll do our best.
- Hey, Chief.
- What.
It's about the men who
kidnapped Twinkle Murdock.
Did you find them yet?!
And you're sure this guy told you
to take this to the ISSP?
Yes, and I'm sure
that thing's worth a lot.
So what say we call it even,
and you cut me loose?
Right, Faye. Like I'm gonna
take your word for this.
What?
What's this whole thing about, Bob?
It's no big thing, Jet.
They decided to cancel
the bounty offer.
You better let her go,
or they'll book you for kidnapping.
No, Bob...
You know, when we worked
in the same department,
a lot of those illegal eye drops
we picked up seemed to disappear.
Wait a minute.
What are you saying, Jet?
If you wanna work
until retirement age,
kind of a bad idea to turn
against me now, buddy.
All right.
I get your message, Jet.
So what do you wanna know?
Hey, don't break the thing!
They call it negotiations, but they're
threatening to unleash a new virus.
In effect, all 8 million people
on Ganymede are their hostages.
How'd they pull it off?
They shanghaied a bio-engineer.
Retrovirus specialist.
Forced him to design a virus to
their specs called "Monkey Business."
Seems humans and monkeys have only
a 2% difference in their DNA structure.
This virus is tweaked
to act just on the 2%.
So it won't have an effect
on any other animals or plants.
It'll leave the rest
of the ecosystem intact.
- Huh?
- That's right, it's uniquely selective.
You see, it only
seeks out human beings.
You don't give up, do you.
ISSP had a mole inside their group,
but we lost contact with him.
May be dead.
So we had no other option.
So you're gonna cave in even though we
got the leader of the whole group here?
We're holding the trump card
right here in our hands!
Orders from the top!
There's nothing that we can do!
We're letting her go.
Us or them. Which one?
Which one of us truly deserves
punishment from heaven?
Soon, the hour of judgment will arrive.
Yes... very soon.
The release procedure is complete.
We'll continue to track her
using our covert agents.
- And the satellite?
- It'll be operational in about an hour.
Get the tech team ready,
but don't take action
till we know the location of the virus.
Sir, a communication
from Twinkle Murdock.
Long time no see, eh, Minister?
Now about all those
promises you made...
Well, yes, we've passed a bill to
limit the harvesting of the sea rats,
so their population will be
maintained securely.
But I didn't say "limit,"
I said "prohibit."
Well, then I'll bring it
back up in the parliament,
to look at it in a positive light.
Mm-hmm. I think you need a
demonstration of what's in store for you.
Wait! We can discuss this!
Momma, please, not this!
Momma, please, no!
Alpha 1-0-5 to team leader.
Target has entered the wasteland sector.
Acknowledged. Continue pursuit.
Huh?
Is that all they were planning?
Ah, damn.
All that work and no reward.
Jet, can you hear me?
Tune in to frequency 7-2, now!
They're doing a live broadcast
from their own satellite.
This is no longer about
sea rats on Ganymede.
Humans, with their consumer culture,
have escaped from the vast
system that we call nature,
and are committing crimes
that cannot be amended.
Those who are unaware of this
are what you might call
glitches in the natural system,
or to put it simply, bugs.
They weren't there!
That ship was a decoy!
Where are they broadcasting from?
They're not very far...
There, I got it!
They're in hyperspace!
Our retrovirus, Monkey Business,
takes these retrohumans
and returns them to their
proper place in nature.
Now do you understand? Huh?
Au revoir.
Good news, Jet,
the Ganymede government
just renewed the ransom
on Twinkle and her group.
- Oh yeah?
- This is it!
We're close enough to get to them,
and there's no one to interfere.
I'm afraid that just catching them
won't be good enough.
If those missiles hit Ganymede,
there'll be no one left to pay
your bounty except monkeys.
So no one's gonna bitch if we get rid
of that monkey missile now, right?
Yeah, but there's not much time.
They're at one of the gate exits.
I know all about it.
What about the defense system?
4 minutes, 30 seconds to impact!
The system won't be ready!
Hurry, this is an emergency!
Get the president on the line!
They're right up ahead.
Ah, shit! It split!
Jet, I got two!
Lock on the other one!
What? There are no weapons online!
That missile will hit Ganymede
before I have a chance to recharge!
Hey there, having a little trouble?
I can bail you out for 80%.
- You're insane!
- Okay. Bye-bye now.
All right, 40%!
That's my last offer!
- Okay, I get the 60.
- Deal! Just do it!
Shit, there's no time left!
Come on.
What is this?!
It's multiple warheads,
and this is not the military!
I'll make monkeys of you all!
Jet, listen, the top brass are
gonna close up the stargate!
What?!
They're going to enclose the whole
thing in hyperspace, missiles and all!
- This is no joke!
- Spike!
I hear you!
Go, Spike!
What's that?!
Didn't you pay attention in
your high school physics class?
Matter that gets enclosed in hyperspace
can be viewed normally by the naked eye.
But of course, it can never interact
with the matter on this plane of reality.
Mom, the gate's closed!
What are we gonna do, Momma?
Stop! Stop!
Yeah, yeah, all that work
and no reward.
For tough guys,
you sure complain a lot.
Now, don't take it so hard, boys.
We'll make some big bucks
on the next one.
Well, think I'll go take a shower now.
Next time? We'll make money?
Jet, is she saying what I think
she's saying, 'cause if she is...
I don't know, and I have no opinion.
Man... she's taking
a shower in our shower.
That's not okay, right?
Don't know, and have no opinion.
Fine, I'll go tell her myself.
Wait, Spike!
Bad move, Spike-O.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
The music box is broken. Or is it?
It starts to play,
and a haunting tune fills the air.
I awake suddenly from my dream.
There is no music box,
and yet there it is.
A tiny one nestled in my hand.
And I awake from my dream again,
as if I were peeling an onion.
It's a dream no matter how far I go.
I can never reach reality.
Trapped in an endless nightmare.
Next episode:
"Ballad for Fallen Angels."