Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' Darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! Sensation
hai!
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆