I have no wishes anymore
Chaika - The Coffin Princess
My hope was hard as rock, and now it is brittle
My body is battered and broken,
and I will not last long
But I will look back on my proud life
with a mask of false courage
The reason flowers blossom
is to say goodbye and wither
This is the law of the world
All of mankind is cruel
We betray and we are betrayed
Goodnight, let us sleep now
You will hear a song
A sad, sad song
A song about you
Fill the blackness
The Throne That Invites War
Can you move?
Yeah. We have to get back to the van.
Both of you, come here.
Let me bite your wounds.
I can't get to you myself.
So, what do we do now?
Sneak into the castle and nab the remains, or...
Over.
Huh?
Lost contest. Collecting remains, over.
Are you serious?
David, until now, grateful.
Is that really okay with you?
What about the remains we have?
Give, to white girl.
Chaika...
Selma! Okay?!
Soldiers came in and... the remains...
I couldn't protect them. I'm sorry.
Chaika!
Toru...
White girl, where?
She was taken hostage.
We have to hand over all the remains to get her back.
You'd better be careful, too.
Hey! What are you carrying?
Sir! It's a body that turned up during the tournament.
We were ordered to dispose of it outside the castle.
Go.
Sir Gillette...
This will lessen the pain.
Please drink.
Can't we do something?
We agreed to rendezvous with Leo and Zita here.
Until then, all we can do is first aid.
We're back.
You're safe...
It can't be...
No... It's impossible...
I know he...
Sorry I worried you.
Sir Gillette!
How?!
Wait. Explanations later.
Zita, use magic to stop the bleeding and infection.
Right!
It was here, right?
Can you get it?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Once the poison wears off, I'll be fine.
I'll be along later. Go on ahead.
Even molting didn't work?
You know Shin.
He must've used some strong stuff.
Damn it!
What am I doing?
Let's go.
Captain Gillette? Is it true?
Yes. I'm sorry to have worried you.
I'll explain everything later.
Yes. From my observations,
King Hartgen organized this
martial arts tournament in a plot
to gather all the remains for
the purpose of starting another war.
So it's true...
Did you find out anything about the emperor's fortune, the Gundo?
During the tournament,
we came in contact with the white Chaika.
In her words, the Gundo was taken by an individual called Guy.
Guy? Who is that?
He seems to be deeply involved with the Chaikas,
but further details are unknown.
I met him inside the castle.
He handed a girl that he called
"the emperor's fortune" over to Hartgen.
I did not see her function as a weapon myself, however.
It seems this has progressed further than I realized.
Remains and a fortune...
Why does Hartgen desire war?
I've brought the white Chaika.
Niva...
I have seen many Chaikas, but this is a surprise.
You look so much like the girl I saw back then.
Daughter of the devil, do not ask for forgiveness.
Curse and scream all you like as you die!
Memory... Whose?
The remains are on their way here, yes?
Yes, sir. They should arrive soon.
Everything will come together at last...
Captain Gillette, I am General Fyodor of the Wiemac Empire.
It's an honor to speak with you, sir.
I'm told you're currently in the Principality of Hartgen?
Yes.
Now that Hartgen's ambitions are clear, we cannot ignore him.
We must stop his plans at any cost.
I agree.
The situation is urgent.
Some nations within the alliance have formed a conspiracy.
We've learned that they've already deployed
a floating fortress to the Principality of Hartgen.
Captain Gillette, I believe we must not let go
of this peace that our people have finally found after many years of war.
I feel the same, sir.
Many powerful fighters have amassed at Goeranson Castle,
itching for a fight.
If the fortune and all the remains come together,
their power will pose a threat to all in the vicinity.
Once the floating fortress launches its attack, the beast can't be stopped.
Nations within the alliance will join the war one by one,
and the entire continent will be razed to the ground.
The only way to prevent it is to stop Hartgen's scheme before it manifests.
We will begin preparations to march immediately,
but we won't make it in time to stop the fortress.
The only ones capable of taking action now are the Gillette Squad.
I am gravely aware of the situation.
P-Pardon me!
Take out all your weapons.
Okay. Go in.
Stop.
Are you okay, Chaika?
Yes.
Coffin...
Let Chaika go! I'll give you the remains!
You promised an exchange, right?
No! No! Don't give remains! Refuse!
Sorry.
No! Refuse! Toru!
Quiet. Show me the inside.
You did well to gather all these.
I knew you would do this.
Step away.
They are all real, correct?
They're real. There's no mistake.
Guy...
So you've been on their side from the start?
My objective is to gather all the remains in one place.
To achieve that, I believe I was
quite generous in assisting you.
Especially with regards to this superior Chaika.
Let me see them, too.
That's...
Chaika.
The black Chaika.
Beautiful...
White Chaika, you have done good work.
You are the strongest and most formidable of them all.
Please, give back...
Thank you for your effort. Your mission ends here.
Hey! Let Chaika go right now!
I will have you watch until the very end...
The true form of Chaika that you attempted to become, but failed.
Cut the—
You...
You want to die in vain? Wait for your chance.
Now, let's begin.
Ilan miril indaril, juri, beluvil, delzart...
Come, to rise and hang adrift.
What do you mean, "begin"?
The remains gathered by the white one,
and the one brought by the red one...
A new history is about to begin.
I see! A new history!
Gaz's remains hold immense power,
and they're all here now, along with Gaz's fortune.
Today, I will make the name of the taboo emperor mine!
By my own hands, I will call forth the era of war once more!
Molle, bagul, elu, eisa, zaldo...
What is this?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to eat them.
Eat them?
Yes. I've already eaten the head and torso that were here.
Delicious...
How does it feel? My father's remains are mine.
I am Chaika Gaz.
My mission is to bring my father back to life.
What are you doing?! Stop!
Chaika!
Are you jealous?
Look closely...
At the real Chaika that you wished to be, but could not.
Real...?
Then grind your teeth in vexation.
Lament your worthlessness for failing to become Chaika...
For failing to complete your most important mission!
Man is imperfect.
However he may seek magic,
he cannot use it as he wishes.
He does not possess organs of magic in his body.
There is a limit to the magic fuel at his disposal.
Then how can man become perfect?
If he has within him organs of magic, like the Fayla,
and continuously takes in magic fuel from all things living in this world,
he can master all forms of magic without limit
and develop new magical arts.
Father... Father...
Rebirth confirmed. Ceasing observation function.
Are you... Guy?
I am Arthur Gaz...
The Emperor.
I have returned to take control of the world.
Did he say... Gaz?
Arthur Gaz...
Are you saying you're the reincarnation of Emperor Gaz?
To acquire a new body,
I died and have been reborn.
I will now reign over this world once again.
Emperor... Gaz?
The emperor...
Emperor! I was wrong!
I realized that the world of war
you created is where true worth lies!
War is the life I am meant to live!
Please, let me walk alongside you!
Pierce.
Hmm... Not bad.
Our fake father is dead!
Our real father killed him!
Father...?
Magic?
Without a Gundo?
Father...
Chaika.
You have done well.
This body satisfies me.
I'm so glad...
All of you have completed your missions.
My objective has been fulfilled.
Mission...?
Complete?
I am not daughter?
Chaika, only tool?
I have no daughter.
"Chaika" is the generic name
for the magic devised to bring me back.
You may call them tools if you wish.
To reconstruct my body,
I chose to die once.
And then I devised magic to bring my scattered remains back together.
A magic technique called "Chaika".
I did it...
I brought Father back to life...
Only I was able to place Fayla organs in myself and bring Father back.
The rest of you only gathered the remains, like worker bees.
All for me, the queen bee!
You are derivation #357, the wizard type.
You look a great deal like her...
Like the girl who contributed the memories for Chaika.
I kept her by my side on a whim,
but I no longer remember her name.
There is no longer any way to find out who you once were.
You were a magic technique that did its job well.
Magic... Me?
Chaika...
Hey!
I wish to ask one question.
You could have died and been reborn within your own castle.
Why go to the effort of having the eight heroes slay you?
I chose to be killed in order to plant a powerful feeling in me:
the fear of death.
I had myself cut apart and gathered by the Chaikas
so that they would fight among themselves and foster hostility.
Cut the shit!
Anger... Very good.
Rich, intense emotions and memories are ideal for magic.
You all must awaken to the murderous intent within you.
This is a good opportunity, so I will tell you
what you should do in order to effectively obtain rich emotions.
What?
When struck, you feel anger.
When stabbed, you feel pain.
When wounded, you cry that you don't want to die.
When you lose your family, you swear revenge.
When you fall ill, you moan.
When hungry, you loathe and envy those with plenty.
What is the most effective way to create many people of that nature at once?
That's...
War.
Precisely.
I once created a device to absorb feelings from people.
To increase coverage over the entire continent,
I launched dozens of them high into the skies.
Devices to absorb feelings?
He can't mean...
The "overnight castles"!
I wish for nothing but to absorb the thoughts
and feelings of all living things on the continent.
From this day on, I will forever live to fulfill all of your wishes.
I will bring endless war to all of you who desire battle.
Rend.
Niva Lada, my wand.
Appear, my sacred treasure.
Child's play.
Without even setting foot from here,
I will leave no trace of the attackers coming my way.
Disappear.
A fitting firearm salute, indeed.
It will soon become clear that you are the enemy.
Do you still believe you can start
another war with the allied army?
The allied army is not a monolith.
All humans desire war deep within their hearts.
I have only fired the opening shot.
Those who wish for war will embrace this chance and take up their weapons.
My wand, bring me my new castle.
Target floating fortress located.
Commencing operation.
The sky grows dark
The bell of the beginning rings out
I live on in you
I live inside you,
twisted and tainted
The ark of our genes
rocks on the water,
sailing for the end times
All that I can offer you
is the day our curse was broken,
but one day, one day,
we will meet again,
as long as you wait for me on this Earth
What is there to be lamented?
I think on the proof we lived together
and bite into my beautiful lips
I will devote my life, my love,
and whatever time I have left
to you
Father revived!
Definitely shocking truth!
What is Father's intention?!
What fate of Toru, Akari, Fredrica, me?
Must do what?
The Girl Who Carries the Gundo
Next time, the final episode:
"The Girl Who Carries the Gundo".
The Girl Who Carries the Gundo