Why did I do something that embarrassing?
I wanna die!
I don't wanna live anymore!
I don't wanna go to school tomorrow!
Am I stupid?!
Stupid, stupid!
I wanna die.
What's wrong, Bro?
Leave me be.
Bro's going through a minor
identity crisis right now.
Now, look here, Bro.
"Identity"? You what?
People who keep talking about identities tend to be the ones without an identity of their own.
Besides, how can you call something that's so easy to change an identity?
Komachi, dear, whatever are you talking like that for? My, how boorish.
Also, you look mighty strange.
I was imitating you.
Not even close.
I don't know what happened,
but I do know that it's too late to fix your twisted personality.
I mean, this is you we're talking about.
But I like you just the way you are.
Oh, I'm sure that line scored me a ton of points.
Gee, thanks.
I quite like myself the way I am, too.
I'm sure that line scored me a ton of points.
What the heck?
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Hello.
H-Hey.
U-Uh...
A-About our activities today...
Could you tell me when and where we're going?
Oh, right.
Mind if I do it after Yuigahama gets here?
Fair enough.
No need to do it twice.
Yo, 'sup!
Hey.
Hello.
You're too close.
Uh, Yuigahama, could you
give me some breathing room?
S-Sure.
Um, I didn't mean anything by it.
Yo, 'sup!
Let's do this thing, Iroha.
I hear things aren't going too well.
You can say that again!
What?
Nothing.
Yeah, nothing.
Seminar Hall 1
For now, just brace yourselves.
Hey.
Oh, looks like we have some new faces.
Hello. I'm Tamanawa from Kaihin High.
That was worse than I expected.
I got annoyed simply watching it.
Right?
So, what do we do?
No clue.
Well, let's think about what we can do, yeah?
You finished your assignment, I see.
I don't recall there being
any Japanese assignments.
Anyway, let's hear it.
What do you need help with?
So you decided to start with the budget?
You seem to be missing the point of Christmas.
Huh?
Let me show you what it's all about.
Ta-da!
Here it is!
Where'd you get those?
Four of them, no less.
I won these at a wedding after-party.
Twice.
I got told "You can go twice by yourself" twice.
Hey! What are you saying to her?!
Don't you know that once she goes four times,
she'll pay out of pocket to go a fifth time
because it was kind of fun?
Hell, I might end up having to
tag along the sixth time!
Seriously, someone take her
hand in marriage already!
You can have these, so go do some research.
It'll also serve as a nice change of pa—
Can we?
Thank you so much!
Why now? It'd be crowded as hell.
Yeah. I can't say I'm up for it either.
Why not? Let's go!
Oh, there's Pan the Panda!
Pan the Panda's Bamboo Fight!
We could go see that any time.
Why go when it's guaranteed to be packed?
Hey, come on.
I'm sure they made it all Christmassy!
No.
Bamboo Fight stays the same all year round.
After all, it's an attraction highly regarded for its setting.
You're awfully well informed.
This is common knowledge.
Let's go!
Not a chance.
I wanna go with you.
I mean, things had been kinda strained lately, and it's not often we get a chance like this.
Merch.
I'm sure there'll be Xmas-edition merch of Pan the Panda, at least.
I want to get something like that
for Komachi's present.
Good idea! Let's pick something out for her together!
In that case, I guess we'll have to go.
Yup!
Wait, are the four of us going?
I have a season pass, so there's an extra ticket.
That means we can invite one more person, right?
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
And who might that be?
That's a secret!
Oi.
Huh? Hikio's coming too?
Hikio? You're hilarious!
His name's Hikitani.
You're both hilariously wrong.
What're they doing here?
W-Well, I couldn't just take Iroha's side!
I was stuck between a rock
and a hard place, you know!
Right...
Hikki!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Is her soul getting sucked out or something?
Got it, Yui.
Thankies!
Yuigahama.
Tell us when you want a picture.
But if I tell you, you won't let me take one.
That doesn't justify taking a
photograph without permission.
Sorry.
I'll ask next time.
There won't be a next time.
I said I'm sorry!
Wait up, Yukinon!
This isn't very Christmassy.
I'm not sure it'll be of much help.
What do I do?
Shit, what do I do?
Hayato!
Let's ride together!
Tobe.
Dude...
Hey, Tobe.
Can you not?
Look, I can't handle this stuff.
And?
Tobecchi sure has it rough.
Yeah. Why don't you help him out?
Or, you can help him out!
Tobe x Hachi!
Please, no.
Sure.
Let's ride together, Tobe.
Hayato!
Sorry about that one time.
Is that why things were awkward
between you guys?
Doesn't matter now.
You guys all good?
Yeah.
You're such a bro!
Thanks to you.
Thank you so—
Girl, you okay?
Oh, Miura.
You look white as a ghost.
Water?
Thank you.
Miura's such a nice girl.
Yukinon, you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just finding this crowd
a little hard to handle.
Shall we?
Yeah!
You know, this isn't the least bit Christmassy either.
Hurry up, Hikki!
Enjoy your trip to the world of Bamboo Fight!
Wow.
Quiet.
Whoa, no talking allowed?
Just how much do you need to focus?
Hey guys, ain't Pan's eyes kinda fugly?
I'd rather check out Marie the Aristocat or somethin'.
Really?
I think he's a total cutie patootie!
Right, Hayama?
Uh, can't you see she's trying to make herself look cute by fawning over the panda?
Irritating! Cute! Bothersome! Embarrassing!
Hikki, my boy, what is it you desire?
I don't really—
Nothing, really.
Uh-huh.
It really is packed, huh?
I'm amazed they felt like
coming at this time of year.
I never want to do this
again if I can help it.
I want to, though...
Who's stopping you?
It's close by.
That's not what I mean.
But I won't wait for people
there's no point in waiting for.
I'll approach them myself.
Destinyland is awful at this time of the year,
but I wonder what the newer park next door is like.
It might be quieter there, I think.
That so?
Yup.
Well, someday.
Yeah, someday.
Let's get choosing, then.
How about this, Hikki?
Which one do you think Komachi will like?
You don't have to get so serious, okay?
Hey, Yukinon.
What?
Take a pic, Hikki!
O-Okay.
What? For real?
You all right?
Yes.
Sh-Shoot!
Go ahead.
We'll catch up later.
Got it!
Shall we?
Yeah.
Yui
Calling
Call Ended
Yui
And she's not answering.
Call Ended
Yui
We might as well ride it
if we got this far in.
They might be waiting at the exit.
R-Right.
Are you scared of these rides?
Not exactly scared...
You should've said so earlier.
Let's head back.
I'll be fine.
You're not great with these, right?
I'm telling you I'll be fine.
Are you stupid?
This isn't something worth
getting stubborn about.
That's not it.
I'll be fine, really.
I wasn't too sure at first,
but I was fine when I rode with Yuigahama,
so I can probably handle this too.
The drop's not for a while yet, so you can let go.
O-Oh, right.
Looks like you really aren't great with these.
I'm not.
You can thank my sister for that.
Back when we were kids,
she'd always mess with me at places like these.
Somehow, I can picture that.
And she seemed to be having so much fun.
That's how she's always been.
Hey, Hikigaya.
Help me someday.
Here.
Thank you.
How much?
Don't worry about it.
I don't wanna take money
from someone who's sick.
That won't do.
You don't see ambulances asking for money.
Paramedics are just as entitled to payment as...
Didn't we get into a similar argument before?
Did we?
After we made the attendant
get that plushie for us.
Oh, that.
We ran into my sister later.
I was really surprised when
you saw right through her.
That was just the impression I got.
Besides, she doesn't try to cover things up when someone sees through her.
Yeah.
I'm sure that's part of what
makes her so charming.
She's always been the apple of everyone's eye.
I was the obedient and unproblematic girl,
but I also know that they called me stuck-up, unlikable, and the like behind my back.
I got that a lot too.
In your case,
it must have been more like
crass, brash, or trash.
Hello?
Wasn't the last one kinda uncalled for?
Anyway, I had no idea how to conduct myself.
Do you still want to be like your sister?
I couldn't say.
I don't really feel that way now,
but she has something that I don't.
And you want it?
No.
I simply wonder why I don't,
and disappoint myself.
You're the same.
You have something that I don't, too.
We weren't the least bit similar, I see.
Well, duh.
So I think I wanted something different.
Once I realized I couldn't do anything,
I started wanting something
neither you nor my sister had.
I thought I could help if I had that.
Help what?
I wonder.
Sorry we went ahead without you!
It's not a big deal.
Anyway, I hope you took pictures of the parade.
Yeah. I got some of Pan too.
Mind if I check them out for a moment?
Uh, we could've gone there
if you'd just said so.
Huh? Where's Hayato?
Yumiko, come this way.
What's the big deal, Tobe?
Just come with me.
It's starting.
Brings back memories, huh?
I-Irohas?
Irohas!
And so, Yukinoshita Yukino.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
What the Lights in Each of Their Hands Illuminate.
"Of all who give gifts these two were the wisest.
Of all who give and receive gifts, such as they are wisest.
Everywhere they are wisest."
- The Gift of the Magi.
Seriously?
They should've just talked it out.
I feel like these two might break up due to a lack of communication.
RumiRumi, you're merciless.
Calling me RumiRumi's so gross.
G-Gross?
I dare you to say that one more time... please.
Gross.
O-One more—no, three more times!
Idiots everywhere.