The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Celty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
Dollars?
I don't know much about the details either,
but apparently there's a lot of them.
But skipping school on the first day?
I told you, I don't know what you mean!
Anyway, stay away from a guy named Shizuo Heiwajima.
Izaya Orihara?
This guy's really dangerous, so don't go near him.
Yeah. His name's Simon.
He works as a tout for that sushi shop run by a Russian.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
They're fabulous! Fabulous!
We serve Russian sushi!
They're tasty and cheap!
Please don't run away, sir!
We have Russian sushi!
Excuse me...
Do you understand Russian?
Yes I do.
Ah, great.
Could you tell us how to get there from here?
Oh, just go straight on this road.
Are you two tourists?
Yup.
This is a fascinating city.
Your trip will be enjoyable, I'm sure.
Thank you very much.
Please stop by the restaurant if you have time.
Ikebukuro... a bustling city that stretches from the east to the west.
There's a massive entertainment district to the north,
and at least a million people gather together in this city everyday.
Ikebukuro is a massive city.
This city is filled with foreigners.
He,
and also, her...
...both came to this city to look for something they seek.
They came here in order to change something.
RAMPANT
Clean-up
Officers
Yamazaki,
Nishizaki
Health
Officers
Tsuchida,
Asakura
Disciplinary
Officers
Kuzuhara,
Kanemura
Oh, we don't have any classroom representatives yet.
Does anyone want to run for the position?
A new city...
No one knows about your past.
It's your one and only chance to become someone new.
However...
Sonohara...
You're Anri Sonohara?
Does anyone else want to run for the position?
Okay, then you're our female classroom representative.
I'm leaving the rest to you, Sonohara.
U-Umm...
Do any males want to run for their
classroom representative position?
I kinda want to, but it seems like it'll be a drag...
But I don't want others taking the position either...
You do it.
What, me? Seriously?
Won't it be a pain?
But you get to work with her!
I'll do it.
U-Umm...
I'm Mikado... Ryugamine.
Classroom
Representatives
Sonohara
Ryugamine
Clean-up
Officers
Yamazaki,
Nishizaki
Health
Officers
Tsuchida,
Asakura
Sonohara!
Hey... about the meeting tomorrow with the other classes,
I've never done anything like this before, so...
Sorry!
I've got something I need to take care of, so if you'll excuse me.
You're quite the playboy now, aren't you?
Back in elementary school,
you used to cry when people started
rumors about you and an old friend of yours.
But this time, you're taking the initiative to schedule things with other girls!
Yeah, yeah.
But you needed to push a little harder.
At this rate,
you won't be able to experience a high school love comedy even though you're finally in Tokyo.
That wasn't my intention...
So...
...let's go pick up some chicks!
Now's my time to shine?
My turn?
It's finally time for me to be popular with girls!
No one's going to take a high school student seriously, are they...
People come to the city to seek change.
But things don't change that easily.
Even if you're in a different location, you're still...
...the same old you.
No thanks.
I have a boyfriend.
Doesn't matter!
Even if a guy hits on you and you end up going out for a drink,
it's not considered "cheating"!
Oh yeah, have you heard?
Apparently, Yumi's new boyfriend is a Dollars member.
Are you serious?!
Shouldn't she be scared?
Interesting!
You should tell me more about this over tea!
Are the Dollars sort of like a motorcycle gang?
In this city, there are people who band together and commit violent acts from time to time.
Each group has their own color that they represent,
and people refer to them as color gangs.
But the group that's been spreading their
influence lately doesn't have a certain color.
If you had to say, they're transparent and colorless.
That's the color of the Dollars.
People say they're a special team that
gathers members through their website.
I heard they've got the Awakusu group backing them up
Isn't the headless rider a member of the Dollars?
The three strongest forces in Ikebukuro!
> The Headless Rider
> Dollars
Shizuo Heiwajima
What about Mr. Simon?
Oh, people also say that the Dollars are behind the slashing incidents that've been happening lately.
Seriously?
Come on! Tell me more about this while enjoying a cup of tea!
Dollars?
Yes, I have.
Really?
Really.
By the way...
Have you ever heard
of the Dollars?
Really.
By the way...
Have you ever heard
of the Dollars?
What are they like?
The Dollars are amazing!
I heard they settled something with the Chinese mafia the other day.
And apparently, an underling from the Dollars was
responsible for the incident where a Yakuza was stabbed!
Geez, dude...
They ran away because of your gloomy face!
Kida!
Yo!
Let's see... your name reminded me of a manga character...
That's right! Mikado!
Wanna come along with us to Toranoana?
Susie Yasuda is holding a book signing!
Be quiet about that stuff!
Whyyy?
What's wrong with talking about Susie, the writer?!
Dollars?
Yes, I've heard of them, at least.
I heard a rumor about them from a friend today.
Hey, Mr. Setton, have you ever
Hmm.
I've never actually seen them
before. I wonder if they really exist.
You think it's something that was made up on the internet?
Well, I can't say that for sure...
Even if they really exist, it's best to steer away from them.
Dollars?
They battle the Flame Haze sealed beneath the Sunshine 60 day and night, right?
No, Yumacchi.
They're pipiru piru piru angels who fly in the sky while showing their underwear to everyone below them!
Why are you asking about the Dollars?
Well, you see...
Did you get scared after hearing about them earlier?
I've heard a lot of rumors about them too.
I hear they're pretty dangerous.
Really...?
You shouldn't go near them out of mere curiosity.
Don't go around trying to investigate them.
You're so cool, Mr. Kadota!
You're like the main character's mature older brother figure!
Do you get a lot of girls who are into older men?
No, no...
Shut up!
In this city, there are places you just shouldn't go near.
Whoa, so you're a tsundere!
You won't get a stomachache!
Come on, just try it once!
Just once! You won't die!
I'm kinda hungry.
Same here.
Want to grab something to eat before we-
The headless rider!
No way!
The occult being witnessed in broad daylight?
What a workaholic.
And from time to time, there are also
people who disappear, swallowed by the city.
And there are ones who desperately search for said people.
I'll be able to see her. I'll find her for sure.
My love will summon her to me.
Harima?
Harima!
I-I'm sorry! Wrong person!
And the city is also filled with danger.
Hey.
Even here...
Come on, let's go out for a drink!
And even here...
He was supposed to be seeking change...
Seriously?
He felt as though something would change...
...and something would happen in this new city.
But what was waiting for him...
...was a deep darkness that lurks in the shadows of the city that appears gaudy upon first sight.
He feels weak at the knees.
He wonders whether he'll really be able to live on in this city.
I understand how you feel.
If you ride the train, people treat you like a molester.
If you walk in the streets, you get weird invitations.
And when you go home, you
encounter troubles with your neighbor!
And there's the Dollars and the headless rider to worry about...
This is what Tokyo, the jungle made of concrete, is about!
BUT!
You must get over it!
If you swore to yourself to become an upstanding Ikebukuronese,
you must undergo the ordeal, Mikado!
Mikado Ryugamine!
Well, don't worry too much! You got me on your side.
Kida...
And when you're trying to pick up chicks, always have a smile on your face.
A bright smile.
But I don't think we'll be able to pick up an adult...
What are you talking about?
Our main goal is to talk to them, so it's all good.
I heard you're acting all conceited even though Mika Harima went missing.
You're a class rep now?
She's being bullied!
And the bullies look so cliche.
With that much makeup on, not even I would be scared.
Yoko's boyfriend is part of the Dollars.
Hiroshi!
Hey, you!
I've called over some of my fellow Dollars brothers, so let's get this party started!
There are people like this everywhere in the world.
It's actually kinda refreshing to see someone act so cliche.
I should help her, right?
But what do I do?
Cut it out!
No, I'll get beat up.
Then...
What a coincidence, Sonohara!
Later!
Wow... he's so cool...
This is it! This is the only way!
Bullies?
You're going to go stop them?
And in this city, events that exceed our imaginations tend to occur very often.
U-Umm...
Huh? What?
W-What?
Huh? W-
Wait a sec!
What do you want?
W-Well...
Bullying is lame.
It's not good.
What's this got to do with you, old man?
Whether you guys get punched right here or end up dying by the roadside doesn't have anything to do with me.
Even if I punch you, and even if you call me an old man even though I'm still twenty three...
...we have nothing to do with each other.
What?
Humans are really weak, aren't they?
Well, hurting girls isn't one of my hobbies.
That's why I'll make it my hobby...
...to stomp on their cell phones.
What the hell is with this guy?
I'm so bored of it now.
It's no longer my hobby to stomp on cell phones.
H-Hiroshi!
Yo!
Yo!!
Hey, man!!
You're gonna get violent?
Wow, I'm so scared!
You... bastard!
Whoa!
I surrender!
Wait!
Wait for me!
You'd better remember this!
Here come the kamaitachi.
But you're really admirable!
You tried to save a girl from being bullied.
It's been a while, Masaomi Kida.
Oh... hi.
That uniform is Raira Academy's, right?
Congrats on your admittance.
Yeah, thanks.
It's rare for you to be in Ikebukuro, Mr. Izaya.
So this is that Izaya Orihara I shouldn't make an enemy out of?
Oh, he's just a friend of mine.
I'm Izaya Orihara.
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Mikado Ryugamine.
Your name reminds me of an air conditioner.
O-Oh...
So... what brings you to Ikebukuro?
I came to see someone.
But I already got in touch with them.
No way... was that a trash can from a convenience store?
That just came flying?
How?!
This is bad...
Well, if it isn't Izaya.
A bartender?
Didn't I tell you never to show your face in Ikebukuro again?
Huh? Izaya?
Shizzy...
I thought you worked by the west gate?
I got fired from there long ago.
And didn't I tell you to stop calling me that?
I've got a name, and it's Shizuo Heiwajima!
Shizuo Heiwajima?
Another guy I shouldn't make an enemy out of?!
Come on, Shizzy.
You're still mad that I blamed you for that crime?
I ain't mad.
I just wanna kick your ass.
You can't even see logic or reason
when you get violent. I don't like it.
What a pain...
Come on, let me off the hook.
There he is! That's him!
How dare you make a fool out of me!
Let me show you what you get for looking down on us Dollars-
Bartender clothing?
No way!
Well, he wasn't there earlier.
S-Shizuo Heiwajima?!
Who the hell are you guys?!
In the midst of fear, humans tend
to lose their ability to think calmly.
You just went for my head, didn't you?
You know that you could kill someone by hitting a vital spot on their head, right?
If you know this, then you were trying to kill me, right?
So you shouldn't have any complaints no matter what I do to you, right?!
Ones with overwhelming power
brings about instinctive fear in others.
He's almost like violence dressed up as a human.
Someone who lives with only violence in their mind.
No... he's simply violence itself.
Well, nice seeing you!
I won't let you get away...
How?
Why did he come from the sky?
That's not the part you should be
questioning, but if I had to answer...
It's because I was making a delivery to an old
customer who lives on the top floor of that building.
Simon, you bastard...
Shizuo, it's not good to fight.
Shut up! Don't get in my way!
Hey, Mikado! Now is where you...
You're kidding!
Mikado!!
Wait! Slow down!
I'm... losing my breath!
S-Sorry.
There are also times when the city presents you with a gift.
A huge miracle, that may appear small...
An adventure he was seeking for,
and the possibility of the start of a new legend.
And...
U-Umm...
Thank you so much.
Please excuse me.
...there are times when nothing begins.
Found you...
...my love.
I heard the Dollars did it again.
I heard!
They had a huge brawl with some guy named Shizuo Heiwajima this afternoon, right?
I heard the Dollars picked a fight.
A sudden dispute between Shizuo and the Dollars.
Is what everyone's saying.
They're the cancer that's killing society!
No, that's not true.
Apparently they had a sudden dispute with Shizuo Heiwajima too.
I happened to be there to witness it. They were just pretending to be members of the Dollars.
They're the cancer that's killing society!
Not just that.
Just recently, people calling themselves the
Dollars attacked a passer-by and stole their money.
Huh?
The Dollars are so scary and ruthless.
You should watch out for them too.
Thanks.
They're really scary, aren't they?
Those Dollars.
Izaya was in Ikebukuro.
I was going to kill him once and
for all, but Simon got in the way.
But... I wonder why he was even here.
This city is filled with foreigners.
They all come here to look for
something and to seek out something.
They also come here to change something.
Welcome! Welcome!
I, too...
Eat sushi!
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Alone With Only Your Shadow For Comfort
Listen to my story.
I want you to hear this unique story about her and I until the very end.
Next time: Alone With Only Your Shadow For Comfort.
I'm sure you'll be trembling with fear and non compos.