Over here.
What's this?
All of you, return to your posts.
It looks like a ball of mercury.
It's like it's alive.
I have to move this out of here...
Is something wrong?
Load it on the truck!
Quickly!
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
The Holy Grail War is in grave peril.
It is confirmed that Caster's Master is behind
the kidnappings tormenting Fuyuki City as of late.
Therefore, I will make use of my emergency powers as judge and temporarily alter the rules of the Grail War.
All Masters are to immediately cease any ongoing
combat and focus on exterminating Caster instead.
The one who defeats Caster and his Master will
receive an additional Command Spell as a reward.
These are unused Command Spells the fallen Masters of past Grail Wars have left behind.
They should be of immeasurable value to you all.
Once it is proven that Caster has been
exterminated, the Grail War will resume as usual.
If anyone has questions, now is the time to ask them.
Though, that would be limited to speakers of the human tongue.
Well done, priest.
Now all the Masters will hunt him down.
Five familiars were gathered at the church.
Which means...
Which means that Lord El-Melloi survived.
Indeed.
And with a Command Spell as the reward,
Lord El-Melloi, having already used one, won't let this
opportunity pass by. Neither will the other Masters.
They'll want to keep it from the rest...
...by claiming it for themselves.
But that also means the Master who obtains the
Command Spell will gain a formidable advantage.
Of course, that wouldn't be good.
Once Caster is weakened from being hunted by the others...
...Archer'll be the one to finish him off.
U-Um...
Is this the Mackenzie residence?
Yes, that is the name of this house's owner.
Well then...
Is Mr. Iskandar, King of Conquerors, at home?
That would be me.
Oh, I see.
Um, could you please sign on the receipt here?
My signature? Very well!
You have my thanks.
Th-Thank you for your patronage...
It feels good to have the entire
world mapped across my chest!
Why are you dressed like that?
My package just arrived.
You went outside?!
Tada!
I tried this "ordering by post" thing.
I told you not to leave the second floor!
If the occupants aren't home and you're busy
with your familiar, who else can answer the door?
I had no choice.
It's rare to be summoned by the Church.
Don't be so grouchy.
I came to a realization after seeing Saber last night.
If I wear modern attire, there should be no
problems with going outside in corporeal form.
Hey, wait!
At least put some pants on before you go out!
Oh, leggings.
That's right, everyone in this country wears them.
Do I have to?
Of course you do!
And before you ask, I'm definitely not going
all the way to town just to buy you XL pants.
What?!
Boy, are you opposing my authority?!
Authority and your pants have zilch, zero, and absolutely nothing to do with one another!
Go defeat an enemy Servant before you start thinking about screwing around outside!
Then I'll buy you pants or whatever you want.
I understand.
Very well.
So you swear that you'll buy me pants once I've defeated an enemy Servant?
You...
Do you really want to walk around
outside in modern clothes that much?
The King of Knights was doing it.
As a fellow king, I cannot allow myself to be left behind.
I like the design on this shirt.
It's a fitting shirt for a ruler!
Even though it's important that we find where Caster is...
What are we doing?
There is a powerful field over Mt. Enzou, with Ryuudou Temple as its origin.
Because of that, anything that isn't a natural spirit,
such as a Servant, can only enter via the temple path.
Bear that in mind when using Saber.
There are three other spots where the ley lines converge.
Tohsaka Manor, Fuyuki Church, and...
New Town, East
...this new residential area east of the city center.
Consequently, this means there
are four locations in Fuyuki City...
...that have all the spiritual characteristics needed for the Grail to appear.
When the war enters its second phase and the Servants are narrowed down,
we'll have to secure one of these
as our base of operations, won't we?
That's right.
That covers the lay of the land.
Any questions?
Is there anything you aren't clear on?
Not particularly.
It was a perfectly adequate explanation.
Kiritsugu, can we assume all the other Masters will go for Caster?
No doubt about that.
But we have the advantage with regards to Caster.
Out of whatever madness, he believes Saber to be Jeanne d'Arc, which is to our benefit.
We just need to wait for him to come.
Master, that won't be enough.
His evil deeds cannot be tolerated.
We should go after him before the damage spreads further.
Iri, have you grasped control of
the spells of the fields in this forest?
Yes, I have.
But our real problem is the curse on Saber's left arm.
Eighteen hours have passed since you
defeated Kayneth, but Saber's arm won't heal.
Lancer must still be alive.
Shouldn't we defeat Lancer first,
so we can face Caster at full strength?
That's unnecessary.
Just use your knowledge of the area to confuse the enemy and keep Saber away from him.
You won't have her fight Caster?
Someone else will deal with him anyway.
In fact, the ones going after Caster
frenziedly would make much better targets.
I'll attack from the side and defeat them.
Master, just...
Just how despicable can you get?!
You mock us Heroic Spirits.
Why won't you let me fight?
Are you saying that you can't trust me, your own Servant?!
The new rule says we can't fight anyone but Caster, right?
It doesn't matter.
I just can't trust the judge of this war.
He feigns ignorance while sheltering Assassin's Master.
He might also be working with Tohsaka.
We'd do well to be wary of him.
That will be all.
Kiritsugu...
If...
If I...
If I decided to just abandon
everything and run away right now...
Iri, would you come with me?
What about Illya?
The girl's still in the castle!
I'll go back and pick her up, killing anyone in the way.
And then...
I'll devote everything I have to just you and Illya!
Can we really run away?
We can!
If we run now, we can still...
Lies.
That's a lie.
You could never run away.
You would never forgive yourself for abandoning the Grail and failing to save the world.
As your own first and final accuser, you would end your own life.
I'm scared.
He...
Kotomine Kirei is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Kayneth as bait to draw me out.
He anticipated my actions.
I'm already sacrificing you to fight, and I had to leave Illya behind...
But the most dangerous of them
has already decided to pursue me.
The one enemy I didn't want to face!
I won't let you fight alone.
I'll protect you.
Saber will protect you.
And... you also have Maiya-san.
Kiritsugu?
An enemy attack?
I'm glad Maiya didn't leave yet.
We can mount an attack together.
Iri, prepare a remote-viewing crystal ball.
There they are.
Irisviel, the enemy is provoking us.
They must be hostages.
I'll have to go down and save them.
He knows we're watching him!
As promised last night, I, Gilles de Rais, have come.
I would like an audience with Jeanne, my beautiful Holy Virgin.
Irisviel!
Feel free to take your time.
I have come prepared for a lengthy wait.
Now, children, it's time to play tag.
The rules are simple: you just need to run away from me.
If you can't...
Stop!
Now, run!
I'll come after you once I've counted up to a hundred.
Well, Jeanne?
How long do you think it'll take me to catch them all?
Saber, defeat Caster!
I shall!
Welcome, Jeanne.
How do you like this terrible spectacle?
It pains you, doesn't it?
Do you hate me?
I'm sure you do.
I'm sure you'd never forgive me for turning away from God's love.
Let the child go, fiend!
Jeanne, since you wish to rescue him that badly...
Okay, boy.
Rejoice.
It appears a devout messenger of God has come to save you.
It's dangerous here.
Now, run away from here.
Follow the path, and you'll reach a large castle.
I told you!
That I would come well-prepared the next time we meet.
Very well.
I won't think to fight you for the Grail any longer!
Oh, Jeanne...
How noble! How valiant!
O Holy Virgin, your presence dulls even that of God!
Caster!
I take up my sword only to destroy you!
If only I could use my left hand...
There should be a limit to Caster's mana.
If Saber can last until it runs out, she can win, right?
Kiritsugu?
More importantly, is there still no sign that other Masters have entered the forest?
Maiya.
Take Iri and run from the castle.
Head in the opposite direction from Saber and Caster.
I can't stay here?
This isn't a safe place with Saber fighting elsewhere.
I'm sure someone else also
arrived at the same conclusion.
All right.
What's wrong, Iri?
Looks like another has arrived.
How come?
Is there no end to his mana?
No...
Could the source of his mana be...
So that book is your Noble Phantasm?
Yes.
I learned how to command a demonic legion from the grimoire my sworn friend Prelati left behind.
What do you think, Jeanne?
Doesn't it bring back memories, Jeanne?
Everything is just as it was back then.
Your noble vigor and dignified air all prove you to be Jeanne d'Arc without a doubt!
So why?!
Why won't you awaken?
Do you still believe in God's grace?
You still think a miracle will save you from this predicament?
How tragic!
Have you forgotten the Battle of Compiègne?
Despite all the humiliation you suffered,
you're still content with being a puppet of God?!
How disappointing, Saber.
That swordsmanship was far from captivating enough to do the King of Knights justice.
Who are you?!
Who gave you permission to interfere?!
That's my question, fiend.
It will be my spear that takes Saber's life!
My prayers, my Holy Grail
brought that woman back to life!
She belongs to me.
Every ounce of flesh, every drop of blood...
Even her soul itself is mine!
Hey, Caster.
I won't be meddling in your love affair.
If you're set on subjugating Saber and making
her yours no matter what, then go ahead and try.
However...
I won't allow you to defeat Saber,
who has lost an arm, in my presence!
Lancer, you...
Don't get me wrong, Saber.
The only order I was given today was to defeat Caster.
Thus, I believe cooperation to be our best option here.
Well?
Just to be clear, Lancer.
I could kill a hundred of those things with just one arm.
That number is nothing to speak of.
U-Unforgivable...
Don't get carried away, you bastard!
Fervor, mei sanguis.
I, the ninth head of the Archibald
family, Kayneth El-Melloi, have come.
Einzbern Mage, let us duel for the
Grail with our lives and our honor!
You rely on traps?
Have you really fallen so low, Einzbern?
Very well.
This is no longer a duel, but an extermination!
I see.
Automatic Searching.
Found you, rat.
Scalp!
Time Alter: Double Accel!
You created a Reality Marble in your
own body to control time and accelerate.
Looks like you do know a little magic.
But only a coward would rely on such petty tricks after having been trained as a Mage.
Die and realize your place.
Ire Sanctio!
Controlling time within himself must place great stress on his body.
Found him.
Now, how far can you run in that physical condition?
Time Alter: Triple Stagnate.
This thing doesn't have eyes to see with.
If I slow my internal time to a third of its original,
and my heart rate and breathing rate as much as possible...
It won't be able to detect me.
Kayneth!
Fool! It's useless!
Episode 7
Forest of Demons
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
Maiya-san, no!
He's a disgrace to Magi everywhere.
Tremble and fall into despair.
Pierce it, Gae Dearg!
On whose will did the both of you fight?
Prepare to die, fiend.
Next Episode
Mage Killer