Cal, what're you doing?
What am I doing? Cooking.
What the heck did you use?
Those.
Just try it.
I made Judy's meals every day.
This is good!
Right?!
Surveillance
So I took one of the more expensive pots from the shelf,
and thrust a 50-dollar bill at him.
The pops at the store dropped his jaw! His face was so funny!
And then...
In other words, you're saying that you want to train that girl as an assassin?
Cal...
Yeah?
Do you know how to fire a gun?
Yeah...
"Do you feel lucky, punk?"
That was Clint Eastwood.
Hm, and...
I'm serious.
Huh?
To be more precise, I'm talking about something to do with avenging Judy.
Ah...
I'll tell you straight. Five million isn't enough.
I see...
But the shortfall is small enough... that you can earn it.
What do I have to do?
Be my assistant for a while.
What?
I understand how you feel, but...
This is amazing! This is amazing!
So I'll be an assistant to Phantom?!
Hey...
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Becoming your assistant means...
that I can be by your side when you avenge Judy, right?
Before that, there's something we have to pick up.
What is it?
A new gun?
New clothes.
Huh?
Let's go buy some tomorrow.
Ah... okay.
Hm? Are you going out?
Yeah. I've got a job.
Then...
Stand by at our hideout today.
What?! That's boring.
Work is boring. It's not fun.
Just stay put and wait here.
Okay.
Five million dollars was stolen and four of our men were killed.
On top of that, it was on your turf.
Despite that, you're saying that there's no apology or compensation from you?
I'm sorry for those who died,
but we can't be responsible for what happened before the deal.
How dare you!
Muroto...
Yes sir...
However, it is true that our business was interfered.
We're currently doing everything we can to find out what happened.
Then... I sure hope you'll be able to get the money back.
Until the matter, that included, is resolved, I'd like you to stay in LA.
Of course, I'll promise you a comfortable stay.
But normally...
Our money was stolen. Our men were killed.
On top of that,
we can't shamelessly go back to Japan empty handed anyway.
Say, Shiga. Why don't we extend our vacation?
How are we going to tell the old man?
Tell him the water disagreed with me or something.
The ringleader is Isaac Wisemel.
Wisemel is?
There's no trace that the information on the deal was leaked to the outside.
It's an inside job.
But this case hurt Wisemel, too.
It's true that no one would think
that he'd cause trouble in his own backyard for only five million dollars.
That's a perfect guise.
Wisemel's goal is to interfere with the Godo Family's joining Inferno.
He probably doesn't like me getting a big backing.
The way it was carried out was too aggressive.
You think he got to being a senior member with just his tough talk?
He's a man who uses force to get his way when necessary.
I'm sure he'll go after Godo again.
Then why don't you let him go back to Japan and...
It won't work without a bait, right?
We'll go shark fishing.
Godo is the bait and you're the hook.
Yeah, it's been decided that we're going to stay here longer.
I want you to stay here a little longer, too.
Understood.
As for the contingency plan...
Boring talk can wait. It spoils the alcohol.
I'll call you again later.
I hope you have a wonderful vacation.
He's a coordinator we were finally able to track down
who has no connections to Inferno.
Giuseppe, was it?
His sales pitch was that he's well versed in the underworld. If that's really true...
you don't have to plan everything.
It's true, but...
Forget it and just have a drink. It's on Inferno.
This is 30 year old liquor, Mr. Shiga.
Okay. I'll join you.
Bait... huh?
Reiji!
Hideout is secure!
Don't say it so loud.
Ah! Sorry!
Is this also part of that "comfortable stay" you mentioned?
What do you think?
Don't worry. I was serious when I said I wouldn't go back empty-handed.
It seems that you've got a subordinate who isn't happy about this whole thing.
You mean Shiga?
Don't worry about him. He's an advisor. So remonstrating is his job.
I see.
You just watch your step.
You're in a quite fragile position right now, right?
You can tell?
The stake that sticks out gets hammered down.
It's the same everywhere.
But...
the three thousand men of the Godo Family will soon carry you on their shoulders.
That's reassuring.
Have you decided?
H-Hold on a sec.
It's already been two hours.
I know...
But I don't know what to get.
There aren't any clothes you want?
There are lots of them!
Then...
There are lots...
but if I have to pick an outfit, I don't know what to do.
Why don't you pick the one you want the most?
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I pick one, that means I have to give up everything else, right?
Don't worry. This isn't the only opportunity for you to shop in your life.
If there's something you want, I'll bring you here again.
Really?
Yeah. So today, you can pick the one you want to wear now.
Okay!
Let's see... Then...
I'll tell you one thing, though... We won't come here every day, alright?
I know!
Do you, really?
Hey, hey, do I look cute? Do I look good in this?
Yeah. You look really good in it.
I've never worn such light, smooth clothes before.
Reiji!
Hurry up!
Go on ahead and go home.
SIG-Sauer, huh?
Just like your Beretta, it's a 9mm, 15-shot.
But this is smaller, isn't it? You said she's never used a gun before, so...
It doesn't look too bad. I'll try with this one.
Thanks.
So?
You didn't come all the way here
to deliver a gun that I didn't even request, right?
That girl, Cal, was mentioned in today's meeting among the senior members.
Was it Wisemel?
It's worse. It was McGwire.
He said he wants to see what progress she's making.
Wouldn't it be better if you at least teach her how to use a gun?
Welcome home, Reiji.
Oh? You've already changed?
That's my Sunday clothes.
These are good enough to wear at home.
Yeah, I guess. Those clothes will do fine.
Huh?
You're going to practice using a gun now.
Really?!
Is this... the practice grounds?
I haven't been here for a while.
This is a lonely place.
Shall we start?
Hold the gun firmly. Focus your strength on your hands.
Stretch your right arm and pull with your left arm.
Right. That's good.
Make sure your target can be seen through the gap.
Can you see it?
My hands are shaking.
Focus your strength on the fingers holding the gun instead of your arms.
Yes, keep holding it like that, and slowly pull the trigger.
You were too hasty. Do it more slowly. Pull it as if you're squeezing it.
Okay.
Ah! I hit the target! I hit the target!
Did you see that, Reiji?!
All right!
Try changing the magazine.
Okay.
She's very careful and good at handling the gun.
Okay. Try practicing by yourself for a while.
Okay.
"Lonely place"...huh?
"You talkin' to me? You talkin' to me? You talkin' to me?"
"Then who the hell else are you talking... you talkin' to me? Okay."
"You're dead."
Hm? Oh duh... Missed big time.
Cal!
Ah... uhm... that was... well, uhm...
I was doing De Niro...
Do it again.
What?
That De Niro or whatever. Do it again.
"You talkin to me? You talkin' to..."
Forget the dialogue.
Listen. Don't shoot right away.
When you have it at the ready, count to one before you shoot.
Okay.
I hit the target?!
I did it! I hit the target!
Hello.
Are you ready to go shark fishing?
Godo's sick and tired of staying put.
He's planning to splurge and have fun tonight.
Your mission is to keep an eye on them
and wait for Wisemel to slip up.
All right!
My picks weren't even remotely close.
How carefree.
All right!
Ugh! This isn't my day.
Don't be so down.
Only those who believe in the Goddess of Victory can win her heart.
You've already got her to spread her legs. I can't win her heart now.
Hm? You're quitting?
The only thing that doesn't betray me is this.
Don't drink too much, all right?
Okay.
He should be sticking with his group like other Japanese people, and yet...
Shiga, join me!
Ah... Okay, bro.
Hey, do you think a place like this is under the mafia's control?
No way. This isn't a De Niro movie, you know.
That girl is probably a genius.
But is it alright to make her take the same path as mine?
No, I shouldn't. I'll set her free... as soon as possible.
Let's go play poker.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I think my friend was here.
Oh, a Japanese man, right?
I think he went back to his room.
He was with a young woman.
He took the bait?
Ah... Whoops.
C... Can't be...
Elen?
Next episode
Reunion
No... It's not her.
Elen's dead.
I killed her... So...