Radio broadcast:
Strategy session
Talk tough
Emphasize 'everyone'
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
On Air
Plug Hyouka!
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Kudryavka Sequence
Classic Lit Club vs. Jumoji
The Classic Lit Club has already lost
its proofed manuscripts.
The ten letters have been fulfilled... Jumoji
Classic Lit Club Beaten
13:30~ Drama Club
14:00~ Marching Band Club
14:30~ Closing Ceremonies
15:00~ Dismissal
"lost"
Getting Around at Kanyasai
Kamiyama High School
Culture Festival Guide: 'Getting Around at Kanyasai'
Edited by the Executive Committee Chairman:
Tanabe Jiro
"I just helped out with the backgrounds"
"author"
"artist"
"The next story's title will be
The Kudryavka Sequence."
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
Hyouka
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
The Cooking Club has
already lost its ladle. Jumonji
"Executive" "09.25" "Committee"
Mail order
54th Kamiyama High
School Culture Festival
Closing Ceremony
Sold out
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having
antennas is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Is the Mountain Range Clear?