Chitanda-san,
can you decisively say that you will
foil the phantom thief Jumoji?
Of course, that is our intention.
With everyone...
Radio broadcast: Strategy session
Talk tough
Emphasize 'everyone'
With everyone helping us out,
I think that we are sure to be
able to catch Jumoji-san!
Oh, that's pretty bold.
Then what I'd like to ask you
next is what Jumoji is after.
Well then, we already
have something ready.
The Classic Lit Club's item
will be proofed manuscripts.
Proofed manuscripts?
Yes. Proofed manuscripts of the
Classic Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka.
Huh?
Are there fewer...?
Goal: Sell out all 200 copies!
These anthologies contain a story
no less compelling than the Jumoji caper,
On Air
so if you would like,
please come give it a read.
I think that everyone out
there will enjoy it.
Plug Hyouka!
Oh, that does sound interesting.
Yes.
Everyone, please check out the
Classic Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka.
I'm sure that you will
find it to your liking!
By the way, as we are rolling out
the red carpet for Jumoji-san,
the Classic Lit Club has
a favor to ask of everyone.
Oh, a favor you say?
Yes. Since there are only
four of us in the club,
we do not have enough eyes
to keep watch over everything.
So by all means, I would ask everyone
to come to the Classic Lit Club!
Thank you very much.
We are counting on all of you!
I get it! Force of numbers, right?
Yes. We are looking forward
to everyone helping us out.
Mm, I'm a sucker for requests like that.
Ah, also...
if possible, please purchase...
an anthology as well, okay?
And so, the Classic Lit Club,
the final target,
is more than ready to engage!
Chitanda-san, good hunting!
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please stand with us.
That was Chitanda Eru-san!
Okay, we're clear.
Wow, that was pretty good.
Thank you very much...
What's the matter?
Nothing... I'm just not sure
if I should be doing this.
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Kudryavka Sequence
Classic Lit Club vs. Jumoji
One, please.
¥200.
Oh, they're selling. They're selling!
We're almost there.
We've almost sold out.
Is he really coming?
As surrounded by others as he'd
be here, he couldn't make his move.
Yeah, you're right.
It's impossible now, isn't it?
How long is he going to keep
us waiting, for Pete's sake?
Is there really a Jumoji
in the first place?
Could they be doing this themselves?
Oh, that's possible.
Show yourself already.
Serves me right for expecting anything.
Oh, sorry. That's my cell phone.
Geez...
You're not answering?
Nah, not until our watch is over...
Hey, it's on fire!
It's on fire!
Put it out! Put it out!
Water?
We've been gotten.
Look at this.
The Classic Lit Club has already lost its proofed
manuscripts. The ten letters have been fulfilled... Jumoji
It's Jumoji's confession note.
Didn't I tell you so?
Did you really know this would happen?
He got them good.
I'm wondering if Jumoji
isn't actually a girl.
Huh? Why's that?
Well, I mean, think about it.
Classic Lit Club Beaten
We sold out.
Huh?
I wish I could have sold them
at the list price for you.
No, not at all! This is plenty!
Really... Really... Thank you so much!
Stop that. Oh, and another thing...
Yes?
Should I really be telling you this?
What is it?
I heard your school radio broadcast.
Yes, Irisu-san, I followed
your advice and...
About that...
My thinking was too shallow.
Let me be clear.
You aren't really suited for that.
When you try to manipulate
other's expectations like you do,
you just come across as sounding needy.
Needy?
Is that the way I sounded?
As much as the tip of my little finger.
However, oftentimes,
if you keep up the act,
you wind up someday swapping
out your true nature for it.
Right.
You're better off not taking
what I said at face value
and then botching its execution.
Being only able to talk straight to the
point may be a shortcoming for you,
but elsewhere, it can also
be a valuable weapon.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes. I was thinking that, as well.
This kind of thing is really not
something I'm cut out for.
So, um, what I mean is...
I've had my fill of it.
Wow. Not even you could catch Jumoji, huh?
13:30~ Drama Club
14:00~ Marching Band Club
14:30~ Closing Ceremonies
15:00~ Dismissal
I had high expectations of you.
Yeah, well... Sorry I couldn't
live up to your expectations.
Nah, it was still a pretty
entertaining culture festival.
I'll get you back for that cooking
thing sometime, though. See you.
Who is that?
Tani-kun.
Someone with a poor grasp
of the language, I suppose.
How's that?
He's someone who uses the word
"expectations" far too casually.
It doesn't really matter,
does it? "Expectations" isn't...
You shouldn't use the word "expectations"
when you believe in yourself!
"Expectations" is a word you reserve
for after you've given up.
Unless there's no other choice
and no hope left, it rings hollow.
Fuku-chan...
Expectations are something
that, for example...
I'm sure I saw Hotaro come this way.
There he is.
Let's get right to the point.
You are Jumoji, aren't you,
Tanabe-senpai?
Hmm? Is that a shot in the dark?
No, I have proof.
Tanabe-senpai?
First, there's this card.
Why does it not say "stolen" but "lost"?
lost
Who knows?
The next question is about "Ku."
"Ku" got skipped over.
That alone makes the Jumoji rule crumble.
But what if there was something regarding
"Ku" that we didn't know about?
Such as?
The Jumoji caper itself
was a code, wasn't it?
To deliver a message to some
party that began with "Ku"
that something beginning with
"Ku" has "already been lost"?
That would be quite a convoluted code.
Normally, you'd never crack the code.
But suppose the other party
knew how to decipher it...
To come right out and say it,
I think that that was the plotline
of The Kudryavka Sequence.
You're thinking, "How does he
know that title?" aren't you?
The Kudryavka Sequence is a twist
on Christie's ultra-famous work,
The A.B.C. Murders.
As was the Jumoji caper.
The culprit's source material
was The Kudryavka Sequence.
As for the recipient of the code,
the party whose name starts with "Ku"
is Kugayama Muneyoshi,
the student council president.
The artist behind A Corpse By Evening.
Am I wrong?
I don't buy that all the others were clubs,
but "Ku" alone referred
to a person's name.
Jumoji never wrote anything
about only going after clubs.
It's pretty thin.
It's not thin at all.
You presented a list
saying that all of your targets
would be chosen from among them.
Copying the "ABC" timetable
bit was a breeze.
Getting Around at Kanyasai
The list
with all the victims is right here.
The victims were all chosen
from off of this page...
The A Capella Club, the Go Club,
the Fortunetelling Club,
the Gardening Club, the Cooking Club,
the Wall Newspaper Club,
the Magic Club, as well as...
Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Once I understood that, it wasn't
that hard to trace it back to you.
It's awfully convenient that
all the victimized clubs
happened to be on this page.
Kamiyama High School Culture Festival Guide:
Edited by Executive
Committee Chairman: Tanabe Jiro
Only someone on the Executive Committee
could manipulate the page.
However, there are 20 people
on the executive committee.
Yes. But then we have this manga,
A Corpse By Evening.
Its author, President Kugayama,
who had teamed with Anjo Haruna,
must have known about
The Kudryavka Sequence.
Which is to say, President Kugayama
would be able to decipher
the "Jumoji Caper" code.
One possible theory is
that President Kugayama
lost the original Kudryavka
Sequence story, isn't it?
Jumoji could have caused this whole
incident to knock him for that, right?
Meaning that the message
from the culprit is this:
"Kugayama has already lost
his Kudryavka Sequence."
Then there's this afterword.
I just helped out with the backgrounds
It was written by whoever
helped with the backgrounds.
author
Anjo Haruna...
artist
President Kugayama...
Other than them,
only one other person knows the original story
The next story's title will be The Kudryavka Sequence.
for The Kudryavka Sequence.
Only this person could possibly
be Jumoji. Then there's this...
"Ajimu Takuha." That's an odd pen name.
This is a mashup of the first
characters of the names
of the three people who wrote this, right?
How so?
"Anjo Haruna" would be "A" and "Ha."
"Kugayama Muneyoshi"
would be "Ku" and "Mu."
When you remove those
letters from "Ajimu Takuha,"
the two remaining characters
are "Ji" and "Ta."
A second-year or higher who would
have been at last year's festival
on the executive committee and also
has the initials "Ta" and "Ji"...
Add to that someone who knows
President Kugayama quite well
and who knows that he draws manga.
There's only one person who fits that bill.
It's you...
Tanabe Jiro-senpai.
Well done.
I never imagined anyone besides
Mune and Anjo-san could crack it.
Holy smoke...
You've exceeded my expectations, Hotaro.
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
The Cooking Club has already lost its ladle.... Jumonji
Why did you use such a roundabout code for this?
You probably have an inkling why, don't you?
Is it because of your feelings for
Anjo Haruna, who has transferred out?
There is that. Also, it is
the culture festival,
so I felt like pulling some
kind of prank. But then...
not being able to say it out loud...
might be the biggest reason.
Ahem... Now then, there's
something else I'd like to discuss.
Tanabe-senpai, there's something
I'd like you to do for me.
That being...?
I'd like you to buy these.
The anthology, Hyouka, 30 copies.
You want me to buy those
in exchange for keeping this secret?
Yes.
However, I'm asking for the
Executive Committee to buy them.
Executive
09.25
Committee
That's absurd.
There is nothing absurd about it.
This is Kamiyama High School's website.
Mail order
You do mail order for items produced
at the culture festival, don't you?
You could have the
Executive Committee buy them,
then have them resell them
through the website.
I can't buy them without giving a reason.
There has to at least be some
kind of buzz about them.
Absolutely. But there is some
buzz about Hyouka here.
What do you mean?
Why, the Jumoji caper, of course.
You're going to make the
Classic Lit Club your final target.
I... and Fukube Satoshi, once I ask him...
Will be accomplices to your crime.
You will have inside men at your target.
Nothing could be easier.
Onlookers will throng to the
Classic Lit Club, Jumoji's last target.
The anthologies will also sell in droves.
It will create a reason to
list them for sale online.
And it will give you the means
to wrap things up nice and neatly.
What do you say?
True enough...
It's not a bad idea, is it?
Bringing a close to the Jumoji incident
and providing items for mail order.
It is in our mutual interest.
Glad to hear it.
So, how are you planning
to aid and abet Jumoji?
We'll prepare a proofed
manuscript as your objective.
Then we'll post guards, so that
no one can get near it.
Oh... Then what?
According to the guidebook,
the Chemistry Club is
giving a demonstration
on the reaction that occurs when
water is poured over sodium.
I saw what happened once
in a video somewhere.
It burns fairly spectacularly.
You don't mean to take that sodium...
Yes. Please get a hold of it somehow.
Beyond that, there's a group
from the Confection Club
that is carrying around water pistols.
Please negotiate to get
one of these as well.
You have a dangerous game in mind.
It's festival time.
Let's go out with a bang.
Good grief.
I'll come up with a way to somehow slip
the sodium in the manuscript pages.
Once we sell enough copies,
I'll give a signal like this
and then you'll shoot the
manuscript with the water pistol.
But everyone's eyes will be
on the manuscript, right?
Yes, they will.
All right, I'll place Satoshi's
smartphone near the room's door.
Please call it before you shoot the water.
All the onlookers' attention
will be drawn toward that.
All right. What about
the confession note?
The scene will be thrown into disarray,
so tuck it inside a copy of Hyouka
and drop it on the floor.
Very well.
All right, you'll have to buy a
copy to do that. ¥200, please.
Heh, pretty sneaky there.
We sincerely are up a creek here.
What was your name again?
Ahem... Oreki Hotaro, Class 1-B.
Are "expectations" what you have
when you think about Oreki, Fuku-chan?
Well spotted. How did you know?
I can tell just by watching.
When it comes to you, that is.
Fuku-chan, were you trying to best Oreki?
It's not that I wanted to best him,
but I'm always looking up to him.
But then, that's probably something
you wouldn't get, Mayaka.
I wouldn't say that.
Ah, I really messed this up.
I shouldn't have forgotten one thing...
Databases can't come up with conclusions.
54th Kamiyama High School Culture Festival
And so,
this year's Kanyasai comes to a close without incident.
Closing Ceremony
And so, this year's Kanyasai
comes to a close without incident.
Although, there were a
number of odd happenings.
Nice work.
So anyway, nice going, everyone.
I hereby declare the 54th Kamiyama
High School Culture Festival over.
I know it's a bit late now,
but I brought it...
The manga of someone who I believe
someday will write a masterpiece.
Ugh, you really did bring it, huh?
Yes. This is a borrowed copy, though.
Senpai, you knew about
this manga, didn't you?
Did Yuasa tell you? That little...
She said that you and the manga's
author were friends, Kochi-senpai.
Friends? Yeah, sure. I wonder
how Haruna is doing these days.
I haven't heard from her in a long while.
Have you read this manga?
I can kind of understand what you said.
Whether a manga is interesting or not
is ultimately a subjective matter.
But I still don't think that it's correct.
I mean, that would make it
so hopeless, wouldn't it?!
Which is where you get
A Corpse By Evening.
But it's a serious work, right?
If I were a gag manga fan,
I'd never read it.
That's how things are, aren't they?
You'd see if you read it!
I'm sure of it!
There are some works that
have that kind of power!
For someone who knows
the difference, right?
Kochi-senpai!
I'm kidding.
Huh?
I'm kidding. I don't really mean
what I'm saying, you know.
You just don't get the joke, Ibara.
Ayako doesn't really mean it.
I can't get away from it, you know?
I haven't read it. I gave up
partway through. Do you know why?
No.
You said, "You'd see if
you read it," didn't you?
Yeah, I get it. I get it fine.
But, see, it's not something
you want to admit, you know?
What if it was you?
Suppose you had a friend that
didn't read much manga
team up with a first-time writer
and decide to draw one of them.
Right?
You wouldn't think it's
a laughing matter, right?
That's why it's deep in my closet,
tucked in the box furthest back.
I decided not to read it,
and while I was at it,
I decided that nothing
about it was a masterpiece.
But fate always brings it back around.
Even though you went and got it,
I'm sorry; I'm not going to read it.
Uh...
I mean, if I were to read it,
then I'd call her up, wouldn't I?
But when I call her, I couldn't be like,
"I read it! You're amazing, you know!
I'm looking forward to the next one!"
Right?
That's from Body Talk...
Masterpieces are the ones that are
created masterpieces from the start.
Body Talk.
It's pretty good, too.
My stuff is a hundred steps below.
Is this all that's left?
Yeah.
O-Oh, to think... to think
we made it this far...!
It's incredible! That huge
pile of anthologies...
This outcome is beyond my expectations!
Expectations... Expectations, huh?
Huh?
Oh... nothing.
I can't tell Chitanda that I resorted
to blackmail to hustle them.
Oreki-kun,
you said that the reason
why I instigated all this
was because Kugayama lost
The Kudryavka Sequence, right?
It was just an assumption.
I had no way of knowing what
your true motivations were.
Well, I can't blame you.
Anjo-san is probably the only
one who knows how I feel.
You're saying that President
Kugayama doesn't know?
Yeah.
This code was directed at
President Kugayama, right?
That's right.
Then why?
Ever since Mune... Ever since Kugayama
finished A Corpse By Evening,
he hasn't picked up his pen once.
Anjo-san may be brilliant as well,
but I had no idea that Mune
could draw that well.
A nobody like me can't
hold a candle to him.
I know the story is
still there! It isn't lost!
If he would only get his mind right,
he could create a story that surpasses
even A Corpse By Evening!
But, as far as Mune cares,
drawing manga was something
he did on a lark that one time.
That was on a lark?
It's such a waste, right?
You think it's a shame, don't you?
And yet Mune doesn't want to draw.
I was willing to do anything,
if he would've just said he'd do it.
I was too afraid to ask Mune.
I didn't want to believe that he
wouldn't recognize the message.
It is out of that desperate gulf
that "expectation" is born.
I've been carrying my
expectation this whole time.
Then, isn't this what you
really wanted to say...
"Kugayama,
have you read
The Kudryavka Sequence?"
You really are good.
And so the answer was...
Oh, right. Mune...
never even opened the story that
Anjo-san poured her soul into.
He couldn't have cracked the code.
My message never got through.
Oreki...
Thanks for this. Give your
sister my thanks, too.
Yeah.
What?
Nothing. I'll tell her.
Well, what shall we do about
these four leftover copies?
There's nothing we can do
about them being left
except have all of us buy
one more copy each.
And now...
we're sold out!
Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
All that's left now is the truth
behind the Jumoji caper.
Now, there's nothing holding us back...
from putting all of our
curiosity into it!
Er, no...
Oh, in that case, I think that
Hotaro has found something out.
Oh, is that true, Oreki-san?!
Well, I mean...
What do you say we hear all about it
as we celebrate with
a selling-out party?
Oh!
Satoshi!
You're going to have to
let me have this, at least.
Huh?
Count me in for celebrating!
I didn't get to spend much time
with the Classic Lit Club,
so I want to hear all about it.
All right, why don't you
come over to my place?
All right, it's settled!
What's settled?!
Yes! Time to get away from this!
We're drinking tonight!
Now we're drinking?!
Oolong tea, mostly!
What kind of follow-up line is that?
Sold out
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "Is the Mountain Range Clear?"
Is the Mountain Range Clear?