I want to help you all!
I can't fight, though...
Don't worry, we're glad to have you!
You're officially part of the team now, Yui.
Welcome aboard, Yuiyui!
Welcome!
Thanks!
Kirara.
Manager!
What is it?
You've got a job. Here.
A TV reporter?
TV?
Yeah. It's a show called "Gourmet Report"
that features restaurants from around the city.
Interested?
You know I can't do this!
What?! But it's on TV, Kirara!
I already cancelled on Bauanne's fashion show, so I'm in no position to do TV work.
Aww...
Okay, I'll turn them down.
But I thought you'd enjoy
reporting on Marble Doughnuts...
I heard you might even get to
eat their new doughnut on air.
Such a shame...
Their new... doughnut?
I'll do it!
I'll do it, manager!
Oh, good.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Kirara vs. Idol!
The Blazing Doughnut Battle!
Close, that fool.
Imbecile that he was, it's still
disconcerting to have lost him.
Maybe if you went and got lost too, I'd have some peace and quiet.
Lock!
Do not make light of me, for there is naught but I who can defeat the Precures!
Just my imagination...
Amanogawa Kirara...
Today, you shall meet your match!
So this is the renovated Marble Doughnuts shop?
It smells great!
Those are real TV cameras!
We might show up on TV too!
I sure hope not!
What do I do?
Calm down, Haruka. Kirara's the one who'll be on TV.
Oh yeah!
Hey there, Kirara!
Glad you could make it!
No problem!
I expect great things!
Good morning!
It's a pleasure to work with you!
Kirara, let me introduce you.
This is our regular reporter, Ichijou Ranko.
You've heard of Kirara, right?
Nope, never.
Listen up, newbie reporter.
One day, I'm gonna be the brightest star on TV.
So don't drag me down.
Huh?
Well, good luck to you, too.
Are you listening? If you foil my plot to be a s—
Hey now, we're gonna start filming soon!
Where have I seen her...
I'm getting nervous!
Haruka, where'd that ribbon come from?
Time to start filming!
And, action!
Hi there, I'm Amanogawa Kirara—
Hi there, everyone!
It's your Sunday Angel, your little Ranran, Ichijou Ranko!
We may have a bumbling newbie in tow,
but we've still got a great show for you all!
Too close!
Now then, let's go inside!
Oh, they look delicious!
Are these doughnuts all handmade?
Of course they're all handmade, right?
Y-Yeah.
By the by, how many kinds of doughnuts do you offer?
We have—
20 flavors!
Y-Yeah, that.
Silly me, I answered that for you!
I'm actually a big fan of these doughnuts!
Thank you very much!
Pardon me!
I'm totally in L-O-V-E with these doughnuts!
Nobody loves them more than me!
Well, I bet I do—
Pardon me!
I love them a hundred times more!
Uh, thanks...
What's up with this girl?
And cut!
Good stuff!
Now it's time for the Marble Doughnuts Challenge!
Challenge?
If you win, you can eat their new doughnut before it goes on sale!
Finally! I'm getting that doughnut!
The first challenge will be to
create a character for the store!
In other words, a mascot design competition!
Hooray!
M-Mascot?
A mascot, huh?
The ribbon grew!
Kirara's a fashion designer, so she should be fine.
Well, we'll see about that.
Got it!
This is the Doughnut Princess!
The doughnut on her head ties the ensemble together!
Oh, that's pretty cute!
How typical of a newbie.
This is a real mascot.
Forget cookies, he's a Tough Doughnut!
Ruling, please!
Yours is more doughnutty, so I'll pick yours.
Aww...
My new doughnut...
And cut!
Well, this is a piece of doughnut for a future star like me.
I think it's pretty clear who's gonna win.
You may as well call it quits.
In your dreams!
That was good!
Next up, you'll convey the deliciousness of Marble Doughnuts in the Doughnut Reporting challenge!
What a far out burst of flavor!
The bittersweet chocolate matches the sweet whipped cream filling for a taste that's out of this world!
Combined with the nigh overflowing frosting, it's the best doughnut in the galaxy!
Ooh, that's a great report!
Pfft, that doesn't tell them anything.
This is how it's done.
C-Could it be?!
What heavenly flavor!
I feel like I'm floating in a chocolate sky among clouds of sweet whipped cream!
It lures me to dive into that sweet sky!
This harmony is like a dream... in fact, it must be!
But it's no dream!
Yes, such deliciousness is no dream!
I'll give the point to Kirara's report.
Yes! Gimme the doughnut!
This match is heating up!
It's time for the final challenge!
You're going down!
No, you are!
What could the final challenge be?
They multiplied!
Is that the Doughnut Princess?
And Tough Doughnut?
We made them.
When?!
You two will run a race wearing these!
This is the Mascot Marathon!
Huh?!
Kirara will be...
the Doughnut Princess?
Party Curls!
I accept this challenge!
What's wrong, Amanogawa Kirara?
Don your garments at once!
D-Do I have to?
Kirara, you don't have to force yourself.
I know you want that doughnut, but...
No, I'll do it.
Sure, I want the doughnut, but...
Tough Doughnut!
I just don't want to let that win.
I guess if you don't stand out
that much, you can't get on TV.
She's certainly behind...
I think you mixed the goals up...
Can you even run in that?
Like you can?
All right, time to start!
On your marks!
Get set!
Those must be difficult to run in.
Well, they're mascot costumes...
True...
But Kirara looks excited!
She'll win this.
I'm sure of it.
You can watch the rest.
Shopping Plaza
Go to Marble Doughnuts!
You're really missing out!
Smell ya later!
That sure looks heavy.
The show would be boring if I weren't running slow to give you a chance!
I haven't kicked it into high gear, either!
Time to show you just how fit a pro model has to be!
Marble Doughnuts are delicious!
One day, I'll be the brightest star on TV!
So you're doughnuts if you think I'd quit here!
Not bad.
Look!
Tough Doughnut is in the lead!
Kirara might lose!
This match...
is as good...
as mine!
She fell!
I've gotta...
win!
Doughnuts! Doughnuts! Doughnuts!
Kirara, you did it!
Hey, look!
Tough Doughnut stood up!
She's out, but not down! Amazing!
I'll keep running...
because I'll be the brightest star on TV!
You can do it, Gutsy Doughnut!
Tough... Doughnut!
Don't give up, Pumped Doughnut!
You're an inspiration, Bravo Doughnut!
Tou... gh...
Fight on, Doughnut Dude!
Tough... tough... tough!
I'm the Tough Doughnut!
You're the best!
Obnoxious...
So obnoxious...
You're all so obnoxious!
Shut!
Now, show me your dream.
I'll be brightest top idol on TV!
Huh?
Wha?
Uh...
Top!
...Comedian?
I said "Idol"!
Very well, then.
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
It's a doughnut Dyspairvil?
Maybe her dream wasn't to become an idol...
This way, everyone!
What're you doing with Ranko's dream?
Hmph. Why fret over such a meager dream?
Don't take me for a fool!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
Dyspairvil!
Dys dys dys... pair!
Look out!
Dyspair Dyspair Dyspair!
It didn't work?
Well, doughnuts are soft.
Dyspair! Dyspair! Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
What should we do?
We've got to get it to sit still!
Girls, I have a plan.
Huh?
Dyspairvil!
Okay!
Then...
let's do it!
Rose!
Dance, O roses!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
How pretty!
Here!
Dyspair!
Next up is this!
Luna!
Shine, O Moon!
Precure!
Full Moon Humming!
Dyspair!
It's so shiny...
Dyspairvil...
Ice!
Rage, O frost!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Viiiil!
We did it!
It seems that worked.
Quit dallying, for you have naught but to free yourself!
Dyspairvil!
Oh, this Dyspairvil seems to have quite the fiery dream.
That's right...
You'd never quit!
Dyspairviiiiiiil!
Ranko's red hot dream shall be released at once!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Just you wait, Precures!
I shan't end the way Close did!
Open!
The door to your dream!
The brightest star on TV, huh?
Well, I'll be waiting.
Sunday
Bon appétit!
Ranko...
She's an exhausting girl.
Who is, now?
R-Ranko?
Why are you here?
This is Ichijou. She's a third-year here.
Huh?!
She's older?
Amanogawa Kirara, I'll win next time!
I'm not doing TV jobs any—
If you want another shot, then come at me any time!
Goodness...
I didn't show up...
I didn't get on TV at all!
Haruka...
Sunday
Today was a lot of fun!
Goodbye!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Teach me to play the violin!
All right. Would you accompany me to the violin atelier?
But what brought this on?
There was this really pretty girl who I want to play like!
She certainly was pretty, but who was she?
Could those black clothes mean...
Go! Princess Precure:
On a Blue Note
The Black Princess Appears!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Toyama Prefecture - Koharu (Age 5)
Aichi Prefecture - Urara (Age 7)