Dear viewers, feast your eyes upon
this ultimate super-lightweight machine.
This state-of-the-art aerofoil able to
convert even a crosswind to forward thrust...
This saddle of pure molded
carbon-fiber with no synthetic leather...
This pursuit of function and form that
has merged into a single work of art.
It goes without saying that to obtain
such a machine required much sacrifice.
Ignoring my studies, laboring at part-time jobs,
Excellent
Fair
Fail
sparing not a second for anything
other than my time on the bike...
I risked it all to obtain this machine.
But this weekend is the Shimanami Cup.
My win there is almost guaranteed.
And at the end of my winning run I'll finally
be greeted by that rose-colored campus life!
Sorry, can you bring it up? It's open...
I am prepared for any contingency.
This lock is unbreakable,
save for using a hydraulic cutter...
W-Wait!
That's my bicycle!
Don't steal away my two years!
Give it back!
And just like that, the crystallization of
my past two years goes down the drain.
They are called the Cheery Cycle Cleanup Corps.
A mysterious autonomous circle
that regulates illegal bicycle parking.
At first they were a group
staffed by volunteers
diligently giving their
time to maintain the campus,
but in recent years they've
taken on a strange look,
and forcibly remove any bicycle just
a tad outside the designated area...
And those bicycles are ne'er to be seen again.
The rumors are that they end up
at bicycle rental shops around Kyoto,
or are transported across the Sea of
Japan and sold to that country in the north.
Lately they've expanded their influence
beyond the campus to the entire city of Kyoto,
so one cannot let down one's
guard even when venturing off-campus.
They are the hated enemy
of all Kyoto college students,
and a threat to our peaceful daily lives.
Why has such a thing happened to me?
It is necessary for me to
question the one responsible.
Who is responsible for this?
The Tatami Galaxy
Then I was a brand-spanking
new freshman university student
and before my eyes were innumerable
open doors to that rose-colored campus life.
However, ever since I learned
I'd passed the entrance exam
my heart had already been set
on the allure of a single circle.
And that circle's name is...
Cycling Club Soleil
There lay my future of pure, sparkling gold.
Together with the raven-haired
maidens in love rendezvous' fierce contest.
If the situation called for it, I'd even be
willing to let them ride sitting behind me!
...is what I, an idiot beyond
all redemption, had thought.
Icarus' wings made of hardened wax melted...
after he single-mindedly flew
straight toward the sun.
And I in pursuit of that rose-colored
campus life was indeed no different,
for the Cycling Club was a club in name only;
it was more like a hard-core cycling team.
I was cast quickly into despair,
and before my feet was a creature with a
face like a fish-man just risen from the sea.
You fiend! Slink back into the ocean!
You say some pretty mean things.
I am your compatriot!
That was my first contact with Ozu,
as well as worst contact.
I wonder what they find fun about rotating
their legs so fast they wear away the cartilage?
Let's do something more fun!
Hey.
Let's go on a run.
Right!
Even if you resist it,
there's no escaping your fate!
Training was as harsh as you could imagine.
But it was with the belief that
I could overcome the suffering
and reach my rose-colored
future that I turned the pedals.
In the world of "roadies," only
the fast are recognized and praised.
Speed is king! Speed is cool!
In high school I didn't
belong to any sports clubs.
In fact, I did as few activities as possible
and just stayed cooped up with
a bunch of other layabout guys.
So a full-blown athletic team was
far too heavy a burden for me to bear.
Even attempting to train,
with my feeble constitution there was
no certainty of improvement to begin with,
and of course there was no way
I'd place well in any competition.
And so I shuffled along,
wasting my freshman year.
As usual all you're eating
is chicken like a damn fool.
Shut up, this is the best source of protein!
My, my... Must be a struggle
for a poor fellow like you.
Instead of chicken, how about letting me
eat some salted tongue with green onions?
How 'bout you eat some of this!
Ozu never showed his face in the circle,
Don't be such a picky eater!
Eat it!
but he'd frequently show up in my room.
Why? Because someone called
Ozu's "Master" lives on the second floor
of this boarding house, and it
seems Ozu comes to visit him.
I surmised he was probably a
master at telling lewd jokes or something.
Your eyebrows are raised.
Why so tense?
Shut up! I have no interest
in wasting my time like you!
How cruel. I put a lot of effort into
enjoying wasting my college years.
And you have no right to
criticize me on that front.
Go home!
Don't hold me back!
God damn him...
Bicycle Club
What's this?
In there was a
cornucopia of information about
all possible kinds of
aerodynamic bicycle parts.
I have no physical strength.
Therefore, how about I do
battle with the specs of my bicycle?
Was it not a path of escape, even
for a weak person such as myself?
Having seen the light, in my second year
I embarked on a complete change of course.
Thinking back on it now, it was only
the beginning of yet greater unhappiness.
To get your hands on a good bicycle takes money.
A reduction of a mere 1 or 2 grams
requires an immense amount of funds.
Replacing the wheels, tires,
and shoes with lighter versions...
The handlebar, the stem, a compact crank...
For me to obtain a somewhat decent bicycle,
I left my studies to the side and
dove into every part-time job there was,
even dabbling in some illegal work.
I became nothing more than a saving fiend.
And finally in the winter of my second year,
taking loans from my friends
and acquaintances,
I got my hands on the full-spec
machine I had been dreaming of.
What lightness!
This bike is, indeed, my wings!
Had I only a girlfriend,
I felt I could fly anywhere!
Of course I had already heard the
rumors of the Cheerful Cleanup Corps,
so I took extreme caution.
I was so enamored with my new bicycle
I'd take her out with me wherever I went.
Sorry about this, Manami.
I had only let my guard down for a second.
I hadn't expected the Cleanup
Corps to go to such lengths.
I would never see my beloved wheels again.
Is this who I am now?
In the two years I have left,
will I stay such a weakling?
I could not shut my eyes from that reality.
But nor could I stand to look on it.
Manami!
Have you gone nuts?
No. On the contrary,
I have seen the error of my ways.
I had lost sight of something important.
Bought two years ago at the university co-op,
my Manami had been with me
through all my joys and sorrows.
I, once mad with visions of road
bikes, would no longer be led astray.
Manami is for me, my true life-partner!
But fate soon tore Manami and I apart.
Shimanami Cup
Manami... Have you seen my Manami?
Nope.
I didn't even consider it,
but it seems Manami was not
considered a participating bike
and was transported to
the finish area by mistake.
By the time I figured that out,
a great deal of time had passed,
so I started the race four hours
late and it was already after lunch.
The Shimanami Cup goes from
Onomichi to Shikoku,
crossing the bridges from island to island.
After crossing one bridge,
you run along the coastline of the island,
then climb up onto another bridge.
In other words, it's a strenuous up-down course.
Manami, why must you be so heavy?
I wonder where all the other racers are?
Or wait, is the race even still going on?
Excuse me!
What? There's still people out there?
We don't need any entertainment.
Even though my only goal
now was to stay on the course,
as night fell I began to lose
sight of the course indicators.
For what reason was I racing?
For what reason did I even go to college?
Manami? What the hell!
It's just a cheap-ass basket-bike!
Continuing with the news.
Today in Hiroshima prefecture, the 10th
annual Shimanami Cup was held in Onomichi city.
The 240 participants put on a fierce race,
and the winner with a splendid
victory was Kyoto's Higuchi-san.
That's the crystallization of my past two years!
I worked hard for this day.
It has to be
I'm very happy I could be victorious for my
disciple who always cheered me on," he said.
Enough, enough! I'm going home!
Where had all this energy I'd
expended the whole time vanished to?
This violates the conservation of energy!
Does not compute!
Is this not a blasphemy of modern physics?
While I was thinking of such things,
morning dawned, then night fell,
then morning again, then night, and
when I came to, I had reached Kiyamachi.
Your face is a face of extreme
impatience... You are unsatisfied.
I can sense your fiercely earnest talent.
Quickly I did tip my hat to
the old woman's keen insight.
Anyway, I sense there is an
opportunity you can't let pass by.
Opportunity?
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
Please grab it.
That'll be 3000 yen.
You raised prices again?
And damn that was quick!
It seemed that I had somehow
fallen into the sea of worthlessness.
Or perhaps I had never
even taken off to begin with.
In the end I was fated to waste
away my college life just as Ozu had said.
I apologize for abducting you like this.
I'm taking you to my circle's shack.
We have a serious favor to ask you, Senpai.
Akashi-san?
Akashi-san was a student in the
engineering department one year below me.
The previous year she was the sole
female member registered to Soleil,
and amazingly won the overall
victory at a road race held in Keage.
What are you going to use the prize money for?
There's no reason for me to answer that.
She had sturdy legs and an air
that didn't let others get near her,
but she had no real
interest in races and quit Soleil.
She invested all the prize money
in her current circle, it seems.
Here.
I apologize for the shady look of the place.
I've brought him.
You? You're the dropout from Soleil?
R-Right...
This is our club president.
I see, you really do have a feeble body.
You're exactly the kind of
man perfect to become a bird.
Become a bird?
Welcome to our Birdman Team!
Weight, 59 kilograms.
Chest, 80 centimeters.
Waist, 70 centimeters.
Indeed, you have the ideal body.
What in the world is this?
Akashi-kun is our star engineer, see.
And she seems to be interested in you.
We have the airframe almost
completed, as you can see.
But no one in the team is suitable to pilot it.
You don't have to do anything in particular.
So will you pilot it, with that
perfect body you have right now?
You're going to get in that plane.
But I'm a complete weakling.
I even dropped out from Soleil...
Exactly!
We need our pilot to be as frail as possible!
Well, that's not all, but you
are definitely our ideal pilot.
There is no special training you will need.
Simply come to the competition as you are now.
Just take care of your body
so you don't get the flu, okay?
What a sudden development.
It did feel a bit like I was forced into it,
and isn't this just a nice way of saying
"you're a stone falling into a lake"?
The Birdman contest is a cruel
game where you pedal and pedal
until you inevitably drop into the sea.
In other words, it didn't have to
be me; it could have been anyone.
And isn't it really scary to head
straight into the sea from such a height?
It's unbearable! I can't take losing any more!
It was spring of last year,
during the road race on Keage.
I had taken off with good speed at first,
but I immediately got winded, and
was staring up at the canal incline.
The power plant over there is quite wonderful.
It's full of dubious machines,
and stirs up my heart.
And it's especially lovely during sakura season.
Akashi-san, shouldn't you be in a hurry?
Aren't you the favorite to win the women's race?
Yes, I am.
Then, I'll be off.
The sakura are very nice.
And so Akashi-san won not only the
women's race, but the overall victory.
Back then I saw dangling
from Akashi-san the Mochiguman.
They come in sets of five, so
it seemed like she had lost one.
Afterwards I came across it, and had
continuously forgotten to return it till today.
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
This body has already crashed once.
Falling is something
I have firsthand knowledge of.
All I need to do is grit my
teeth and launch with a shout.
And then Akashi-san will surely come to
me after I've fallen, with a smile on her face.
Then afterwards, I'll sit behind Akashi-san
as she rides up the sakura-lined incline!
Wait! Can I allow myself to
be addled by such feelings?
Your dreams shouldn't be so
flimsy, weak, and limp noodled!
Is it really okay to lower my
future to such a shameless fate?
To no longer shoot for the sun, but to
live lazily on the ground? How is that Icarus?
I'd just be some kid with ugly-ass wings!
Wavering in the gap between reality and fantasy,
exhausted by the tumultuous
developments of the past few days
and my no-rest, no-sleep return from Shikoku,
I fell to sleep like a sack of potatoes.
Can you keep up with me?
This man is named Jougasaki, and is
the president of the Movie Circle "Misogi."
He's a man that lives for
working out and women's boobs.
And I asked him to teach me.
That's right, I'd made my decision!
I'd fly farther than anyone, higher than anyone!
And on the dawn of my victory,
Akashi-san will be sitting on the back of
Minami as we ride up the sakura-lined incline!
Listen up. Victory is everything.
I will not allow you to run from a battle
and live a life aloof like that Higuchi guy!
If you're a man, then grab victory!
Grab victory, and grab women's tits!
Jougasaki-senpai's teachings
were actually pretty clear-cut,
and my motivation rose
to higher and higher levels.
The Birdman contest was even televised,
and was the place for the circle to shine.
If I won, then I would no
doubt gain the attention
of raven-haired maidens from all around Kyoto.
I bet I'd need to broaden my field of
vision to other women than just Akashi-san.
But that is a trial all winners must face!
Being the hero sure is tough!
What have you done?!
I said you were fine the way you were!
But now you've got muscles!
Everything's ruined!
But...
Akashi-kun's plane is designed with
extremely sensitive aviation tolerances!
Even a 10-gram difference in the pilot
would mean redoing the entire blueprint!
Ruined! It's all ruined!
Enough! Akashi-kun, you be the pilot after all!
You and your muscles can get out of here!
And I already had my hands full thinking
up countermeasures to the Cleanup Corps!
Get out of here, now!
Akashi-kun, you hurry back to work, too!
I apologize for getting you
involved in this weird stuff.
I apologize too, for not
living up to your expectations.
No, actually the problem
was that you far surpassed them.
Birdman is, after all, an absurd goal
that goes against the reason of man.
That's why I was thinking
that the pilot should be a person
with a soul charred by
idleness and wasted passion.
I heard that after you finished
the Shimanami Cup on a basket-bike,
you came back all the way from Shikoku.
That's an incredible waste of energy!
Uh, that wasn't exactly my intention...
That's why I asked you,
but the idea that you'd go so far as to
train didn't figure into my calculations.
I suppose I still have a long way to go.
I apologize, but I have to redo the design now.
See you later.
Before I knew it I had
come to the Keage Incline.
I had prayed to come here with Akashi-san,
but now I felt like the rose-colored campus
life was slipping yet even farther away,
and my heart wept within me.
Maybe I'd be better off flowing
down and trying and make my name
as an Eggplant-Pumpkin
youkai that lives in lake Biwa...
The Cleanup Corps!
The man in the trench coat!
Hey, Ozu!
What the hell are you doing?
Oops, you caught me.
It's you!
Keep it a secret, 'kay?
It's an important source of
funds for the Secret Society.
This is Akashi-san's...
We're in a recession,
so bicycles alone aren't cutting it.
What the hell are you doing?!
A certain person up north is looking
for a plane much like this to play with.
It was just going to crash into Lake Biwa
anyway, so this is a far better use, right?
And what about my bike?!
You're the one who stole it!
I don't really concern myself
with each one individually.
Why not, eh?
It's how I show my love,
so grab it while you can.
After all, it doesn't
matter which path you take,
you'll keep ending up
right where you are now.
Maybe you're right...
Would it be so bad to give
yourself up and go with the flow?
We're connected by the
black thread of fate, after all.
Will you help me?
You've got debts, right?
Let's go around Kyoto collecting bicycles.
Only if I can aim mainly at
couples riding two to a bike.
Sure thing! You do that.
What is it?
I guess the jig's up.
Looks like Akashi-san is coming.
Don't tell anyone about the Cleanup Corps, okay?
Might be bad for your health...
Hey!
What the hell?
It's the trench coat man
from the Cycle Cleanup Corps!
N-No! That's not it!
Akashi-san, this is a misunderstanding!
I didn't do it! The Cheery
Cycle Cleanup Corps are actually...
What is the meaning of this?
Explain it to me now!
You've got it all wrong!
Senpai!
Senpai, where are the brakes?
I don't know!
Senpai...
Jump off!
At this rate I'll crash into the pond.
I have no choice put to try pedaling and fly!
Now's the time for all my training to pay off!
It's flying!
Where are the pedals?
Akashi-san, where are the pedals?
There aren't any!
We're in the free-flying category!
It finally dawned on me
that all this was truly wasted effort.
Perhaps this all started from the
moment I considered the cycling club.
If I had joined some other circle, I would
have surely spent quite a different two years.
Meeting Ozu was clearly
the greatest catastrophe.
Could Icarus have ridden the wind had
he not tried so hard to flap his wings?