The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
No way. That's a convenience
store trashcan.
Just stay away from a guy
named Shizuo Heiwajima.
You know, your violence can't be stopped
by words or reason, Shizu.
Didn't I tell you never to set
foot in Ikebukuro again?
Shizuo. Fighting is bad.
Shut up!
What? The toughest in Ikebukuro?
Or maybe him!
Shizuo Heiwajima!
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
They just up and fired me!
Kicked me out of the
company dorms, too!
And no severance pay, either.
I don't have the money for food or nothin'.
And the government won't help me.
Yeah, it's the government's fault.
Shut the hell up, already.
You took out loans to
bang a soapland girl?
It's love!
Mint and I share true love!
What?
Shut up.
We can only meet at her job,
and I don't know her cell number.
But our love is true!
You piss me off!
You only meet her at the soapland,
and you still don't know her cell?
Hey! Shizuo!
Let me clarify this right now.
What kind
of "true love"
is that?!
I don't like violence.
Badass Dude
Did you hear?
Kanra
Lately, that Heiwajima Shizuo
guy is pretty pissed.
Setton
Tarou Tanaka
The guy who dresses like a bartender
right? Heiwajima Shizuo...
Yeah.
He's always been a scary guy, but
he's been especially bad recently.
They say Ikebukuro's
practically a war zone!
I saw him once.
He's a scary guy, isn't he?
Heiwajima Shizuo...
I dunno...
You shouldn't base judgments
about people on rumors.
My, Setton, you know him?
You one of those guys?
Scary!
Save me!
I am not.
Geez... We're not "recovering" anything
if you keep smashing people into walls.
I'm sorry.
It stinks.
Not home for two or three
days, they said.
Lots of those these days...
Maybe it's those Manhunters
everyone's talking about.
It stinks.
Hey, someone's hurt!
It's that Slasher.
Just now?
I saw them!
They ran that way!
Geez... 'bukuro's getting
crazier by the day.
It stinks.
The whole goddamn town stinks.
What is this stench?
Pisses me off.
Hi, Shizuo. Tom.
Yo, Simon.
Shizuo?
Sorry. He's been in a bad mood lately.
Oh, Shizuo. Adolescence?
Yeah. He's in a rebellious phase.
Rebellious?
Hey, how've you been?
Another leading role in a movie.
He sure is popular, Hanejima Yuuhei...
No, Heiwajima Kasuka.
As his brother, you must be proud.
Heiwajima Shizuo.
Excuse me, here's my card.
Writer
Shuuji
Niekawa
He's got good looks,
but he can also act.
What was the name of his
debut movie again?
Oh, yes.
Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou.
Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou
I always knew he'd be big.
I've heard he does his own stunts, too.
Some people say you taught him.
I'd like to find out more about that.
Shizuo!
I hate violence.
It's true.
I wasn't always like this...
The first time, I got in a fight with
my little brother, Kasuka.
It was over something stupid, but I snapped
and tried to hit him with a refrigerator.
Mine.
Don't eat.
~Shizuo
I hadn't thought about picking it up.
Just... I couldn't control myself.
After that...
Shizuo is a dumb-dumb!
Dumb! Dumb!
I couldn't control myself.
When I get mad, my body
just moves on its own.
And each time...
They say some people,
when desperate, get extra strong.
But I bet that you can always do it.
A person's brain restrains
their strength because
if they always went full-out,
they'd destroy their bones and muscles.
But your brain lets it go wild!
The mysteries of life!
A shocking, fascinating discovery!
Hey, why don't you let me...
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
That hurts!
It hurts, Shizuo!
It's going to break!
I don't know the details.
Just that I can't control my anger.
My arm-bone... My arm-bone... My right arm-bone...
And that I destroy everything around me, even my own body.
That was all I learned from that.
And so,
I stopped holding back.
If I couldn't do it anyway,
why bother trying?
What do I care what happens to my body?!
I've wrecked my body many times.
And each time, I've become stronger.
Shrina says...
Ah, who gives a crap?
Anyway, I just kept getting stronger!
But...
Hey.
You're always injured.
Are you OK?
Wait a second!
Here you go.
You need to drink milk and get stronger.
Same for you!
Thanks.
I'd screwed up.
The next thing I knew...
Morning!
Why did this happen?
My family was normal.
It's not like I had any serious
trauma in my life.
But...
Kasuka.
What?
Aren't you scared of me?
Nope.
It was just when I had entered Raira.
Opening sale!
We'll give you a discount!
The shop is fresh!
We're going to the same school again.
The fish are fresh!
It feels like fate.
Russian Sushi!
Shut up.
How has your body been?
Hey! Why not let me give you a
celebratory reunion exam?
No?
Then, let me just take a blood sample...
Celty!
What happened yesterday?
When you didn't come
home, I was worried.
Were you looking for your head again?
Yeah right! I bet you met a guy somewhere-
Celty...
Would you stop punching me in the gut?
It felt strange.
Celty, I'll introduce you.
He's Shizuo Heiwajima, a good friend of mine.
I don't know how to put it.
Shizuo, Celty here is my roommate.
Or should I say future...
But it was like...
Raira Academy Entrance Ceremony
I'd remembered something bad.
That's right. That's right...
That was when that stupid
flea showed up.
That guy.
Izaya Orihara!
He...
That's Izaya Orihara. He
went to our middle school.
He's not a good guy... Actually, he's kind of an asshole.
From the moment I saw him, I disliked him.
That's awful, Shinra.
No, no. I didn't mean it in a negative way.
You piss me off.
Oh?
Too bad.
I thought you and I could have some fun.
Shut up.
Don't be like that, Shizuo.
See?
It's fun, isn't it?
The day we met, we tried
to kill each other.
There was no real reason.
I just didn't like him.
But...
Are you OK?
It's OK. It's OK.
He's built tough.
Is he really all right?
He's fine. He's fine.
Good work, man.
I screwed up.
Oh, what a coincidence!
Izaya's here, too!
Hey, why aren't you hurt?
Kill! Kill! Kill!
After that, some annoying days began.
Gang after gang of weirdos
tried to jump me.
I haven't done a thing.
I just want to live my life quietly!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Pissed off!
Annoyed! Annoyed! Annoyed!
Annoyed!
I know.
It was Izaya.
Izaya was pulling the strings!
Raira Academy Graduation
And when I found that out...
Izaya!
If only I could have killed him there!
Ever since we graduated Raira...
What do you think? Does it look good?
The idiot's been like this,
and the flea's been doing something
with the yakuza.
For a while, it was quiet.
And so, I...
So, yeah. I ended up...
Welcome.
Hey, did you see that?
No way!
It's that actor...
Yuuhei Hanejima.
Hey, Kasuka. What's up?
A bartender outfit.
You shouldn't change jobs all the time.
I bought a lot, so you can
stay here a long time.
Thanks. I'll do my best, I guess.
And then...
Damn it!
Izaya!
That stupid flea set me up.
He vanished from 'bukuro.
They quickly found out I was
innocent and released me.
But...
Sorry. I couldn't keep my promise.
Hey, Shizuo!
Tom was my senior in middle school.
He wanted me to help him with
his debt collection agency.
Basically, I'm his bodyguard.
At first, I wasn't into it.
Tom was like,
"You don't need to beat
them all up, man."
"Once they hear your name,
most people pay up right away."
So he said. But that was when
Kasuka started getting busy.
And I hadn't seen him at all.
I wonder if he's mad.
What?
Yuuhei!
Yuuhei, over here!
I don't know why, but I felt better.
So, yeah. I'm still working with Tom.
Repayment schedule?
We're from a public school, man.
I don't know any of that crap.
That's right. School, society...
It's all their fault.
It's like the darkness in our hearts.
Um, guys...
I said we don't get it.
Get lost, old man.
This is my job, guys.
Huh? What's that look?
H-Hey!
What's with that outfit?!
He's a butler, idiot. A butler.
You guys have never heard of Shizuo?
Who's that?
Someone famous?
Oh yeah? Butler...
Yoo-hoo!
Would you kindly bring me
another drink, butler?
So they're in 'bukuro and
they don't know Shizuo?
Yup, they went to public school.
My clothes... The clothes
I got from my brother...
But yeah, I don't like violence.
I want to be stronger.
Strong enough to contain my anger...
I feel better after talking with you.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
I've been so pissed off lately,
and I don't know why.
Yeah. I'd heard rumors about
that, so I was worried.
I see.
Sorry to worry you.
You really love your brother
Shut up.
See ya.
I want to stay away from other people,
but I can't be alone.
So I try to be connected to someone.
Like Tom or Kasuka.
They're like me.
I'm sure they too...
Yo.
Shizuo!
Your adolescence over?
Then eat sushi!
Sushi is good!
Sushi is yummy!
Some other time.
Izaya...
I see.
I thought it stank!
It was you!
What is he doing?
What will he do in town this time?
Damn it!
Izaya!
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Ephemeral Dream
I have this dream.
I have it over and over again.
Maybe when I'm awake in the dream, I'm asleep here,
and when I'm awake here, I'm asleep in the dream?
Next time:
Ephemeral Dream.