Lemme tell you.
This huge amount of snow is troublesome.
Especially on the day Headquarters says that we have to patrol carefully.
You haven't given up on Jakotto-san, have you?
Well, it's not really like that...
It's all right, ain't it?
We've been searching and searching.
If we can't even find her after this much effort, we should just believe in "maybe".
What?
I have a feeling that Kureha-chan is a little bit like Rio-senpai.
What's happened?
Beneath the mountain, at 11 o'clock!
About 400 meters.
Please, please wake up.
Even her clothes are frozen!
Kanata, take off your coat.
We are changing.
This girl...
A Roman soldier.
A Visitor
A Burning Field of Snow
You really can restore this machine!
No wonder you are one of the most talented girls in the academy!
This way, we can win.
It's all because of you.
Kannagi Noël-kun.
Noël-chan!
They found her while they were patrolling.
It's a Roman soldier.
I think she broke her left leg.
Look, her fingers are turning dark-red!
It's frostbitten.
If we're not careful, she might even lose her fingers.
The Witch of Helvetia...
Leave it to me!
It seems like it's going to be okay somehow.
Her fingers are alright.
That's good!
How about Noël-chan?
She said that she would be with her for some time.
But, why?
She's trying really hard.
She looked as if she was repairing the Takemicaduchi.
Really?
Trumpet.
Will she be successful, in the end?
But, I was surprised.
Of course, right?
Nobody ever expected to find a Roman soldier in such a place...
It's not about that.
This is my first time meeting a Roman.
We're enemies, aren't we?
That's why, when thinking about those people that look like demons...
Maybe we are seen the same way in Rome.
But, I thought about it.
After seeing that girl,  I thought that Roman people are the same as us.
Hey, Kanata! What are you...
Well, Kana-chan.
It's about the end of your shift.
There's still a lot of trouble going on at the peace conference, right?
I heard that it's like that.
Are you going to submit a report about her?
If I do that, the girl's likely to be taken to Central for interrogation.
We have to do this! Under such an unstable situation,
She's invading the enemy's territory!
As a soldier, she's ready for torture...
It's an "interrogation."
I will be the one to decide how she's gonna be treated.
Please, give me some time, Kureha-chan.
Please don't forget that we are soldiers, Platoon Leader.
Just listen to my words for now.
When you carried that girl here, did you meet anyone?
I don't know. I was focused on carrying her.
I got it.
Thank you.
Rio, how would you deal with this problem?
A Helvetian soldier...
What are you going to do with this?
Where am I?
Am I a Helvetian prisoner?
I don't speak Roman.
Fine.
So you took me prisoner—
What was that scream just now!
What's happening!
She... woke up.
Great.
Imperial Roman Army, First Armored Division, 13th Battalion B-Company.
Sergeant Major Aisha Ardora, serial number 1031021.
Why did you come here?
Imperial Roman Army, Sergeant Major Aisha Ardora.
What's your mission?
Serial number 1031021.
Alright, how dare you!
How's it going? Have you got a clue?
It's totally impossible!
It seems that she doesn't understand Helvetian.
All we know is her Serial Number and her name, "Aisha".
I'm Second Lieutenant Felicia Heideman who's in charge of this fortress.
You have such great breasts. I'm interested in them.
Can I suck or rub them?
Can I play with your body?
W-W-What are you saying, Platoon leader!
It seems that she really doesn't understand Helvetian.
But, that's bad.
We can't interrogate her.
We must find someone who can speak Roman as soon as possible.
Then...
Until we can interrogate her and make a preliminary report, our platoon is to protect this girl.
But...
I want to place a bet.
I didn't hear anything, so the result is not on me.
Aisha-chan, welcome to the Time telling fortress!
Ti-me-tell-ing-for-tress?
Right.
Time telling fortress.
Ah, I see... Then I made it.
Grandmother...
Hmm, is it too hot?
She ate it!
Tastes okay?
To escape, I need strength, so I'll eat your food.
She must be saying that it tastes great!
What on Earth is going on?
Kanata might be doing what she usually does but,
why is Noël also being so nice?
It's atonement for her sins, I guess.
Have you ever seen the fossil of an angel?
Angel?
They don't understand me, I know...
Roman. I wish I'd studied it.
Right.
If we could communicate with her using the language, we could...
Thanks for you work.
Oh, it's Yumina-chan.
Do you have enough people to shovel the snow at the church?
Yes.
The kids are working really seriously.
That's great.
So, they won't be kids forever, right?
Right.
Human beings grow every day, like the sound of Kanata-san's trumpet.
If it were Rio, I guess she would say "that's not good enough."
Wow, nee-san, aren't you stocking things in Treize?
A lot of things happened, and it turned out to be useless.
That's so bad.
By the way, about the fortress...
I heard about something bad.
Thank you for listening.
It's a wonderful melody.
Ah, I didn't know there were trumpets like that left.
May I?
Yes.
Because I think Rio-senpai would allow it too.
It's a good trumpet.
Really, I haven't seen one this nice...
Wow, the music you just played was so great!
That's just awesome.
Because I heard that from Iliya-san.
Rio-senpai heard the same music too.
The same music is heard, not only in Helvetia, but in Rome too!
Music really is heard...
in both Rome and Helvetia, in the same way.
Temporary measure.
Danke.
Dan...ke?
Yeah, danke.
What's "danke"?
It means "Thank you."
Finally, things are getting out of hand.
Well, this town hasn't become a target of the war.
If we include parents, sisters, brothers and all other relatives,
then almost all of the people living here have lost someone in the war.
It's always like that. Even those nice people would, when it happens...
Migel, the one who runs the pub. Remember?
I even went to his place yesterday.
It seems that the Helvetian military is doing a lot of things.
They are moving toward this place.
If that's related to the appearance of this Roman soldier in such a remote place, it's serious.
Anyway, we have to ask this girl.
Naomi-san.
Do you know anyone who understands Roman?
I sure do!
I am Yumina.
I am a servant of the Helvetian Orthodox Church.
May the blessings of the all be upon you.
Ah...
One of these kittens!
There's only one God, that greeting is blasphemy.
What is she saying?
She's just saying hello.
Don't waste time on that! Please ask her now!
Why are you here?
If you don't tell us, you put everyone here in a very bad position.
If you feel any sort of obligation to them, then tell us the truth.
I can't tell you about my mission.
But I wanted to see the Angel Fossil located in this town.
She says that she's doing this to see the Angel fossil.
Angel fossil?
What is that?
My grandmother was a Maiden here.
My grandma was a soldier of the time telling fortress.
She was captured at the Eastern Front and met my grandfather.
She was captured on the eastern battle line, and met my grandpa.
As I grew up, I listened to her stories.
I listened to her stories while growing up.
So I wanted to see the Angel of the apocalypse that brought judgment
to the world in the distant past, the one my grandmother spoke of.
She's not telling the truth!
The one who destroyed the world was the devil!
Alright. Please translate correctly.
I want to see the Angel of the apocalypse who destroyed the world.
That's why I'm here.
That melody... The marching trumpet!
The Ninth Independent Task Force of the First Imperial Guards!
The Ninth? Isn't it Colonel Hopkins'?
Isn't that the one you dreamt about?
He's the one's who's called "the God of Vingt."
He revived the weapons from the past, and is said to have destroyed three towns in one night.
It's alright.
He doesn't know that you're here.
Whatever you do.
I don't think you have time to worry.
If you don't make a decision as soon as possible, you will get into trouble, right?
To hand over that girl, or...
We don't have to worry!
We are soldiers of Helvetia.
I lost this gamble.
I didn't make it in time, Rio.
Please wait.
Rio-senpai said that she didn't want anyone to suffer misfortune anymore.
She said that's why she's doing what she can.
That's why she left, isn't it?
But, I don't like it.
We are the same, we are together!
As the leader of Platoon 1121, I command.
This order is based on my own judgement. I announce my responsibility for everything.
Are we all in agreement?
I am Second Lieutenant Felicia Heideman, the Leader of Platoon 1121.
A scout of the Roman military was captured in Treize.
Unfortunately, during the interrogation, there was an accident, so we don't know the details.
How surprising! There's also information saying that there's a Roman soldier in Seize.
You got a clue?
No, Colonel.
I got it.
At this time, Fortress 1121 will be taken over by us, The Ninth Independent Task Force.
Don't make such a big noise so suddenly!
Sorry.
Aisha-san is asking me about the tale of the Maidens of Flame.
It's strange. What she says is...
Search everywhere thoroughly!
This way too!
How about there?
Negative here.
We must find her!
Open that door!
She has to be somewhere. Watch the entrance!
She said "by the way, I still don't know your name."
Noël.
Her name is Noël.
Noël... Noël Kannagi?
Yes.
The Witch of Helvetia...
The Invisible God of death...
You said the invisible God of death!?
Ooh, is that a mouse?
Noël-san!
H-Hello. This is Fortress 1121.
In Nomansland, at Seize's border, there's a big Roman troop!?
Music in the Sky
Next Time :