Wow!
These are amazing! Your dad really is great, Erika!
Huh?
I'm glad you like them, Tsubomi!
Hey, don't just photograph us out of the blue like that!
Your father really is a superb
photographer though, isn't he?
That's not the point...
This is a really sweet photograph.
It's a photo of a family I owe an awful lot to.
Brings back some old memories...
Erika...
May I see your family photos too?
I know they're going to be really amazing!
We don't have any!
Dad takes all our photos, so he's not in any of them.
Right, Dad?
I never noticed, but you're right!
Is this to be my fate as a photographer?!
Dad?
All right! We're going on a family vacation!
Would you like to come along
as our photographer, Tsubomi?
I'd love to! Leave it to me!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
We're off to visit a family I know who helped me out when I was younger.
Their daughter's about to get married, apparently.
Ohhh!
Hey, Tsubomi?
Tsubomi, you don't have to take pictures until we get there, you know?
No! I am a photographer!
I'll be on the lookout no matter when or where I may be!
Good afternoon!
Wait, what?
I guess Tadashi and Aki must be out in the fields.
We've made a new friend!
His name's Maru!
We're just gonna go look over here for a sec, okay?!
Jeez, don't just show yourselves like that!
Come on, Dad!
Just listen to me!
We've talked about this several times before!
I'll be fine on my own. I like tending the fields.
Dad!
It's Tadashi!
Oh, Ryuunosuke!
Sorry we weren't around to greet you.
It's quite all right. We're intruding at a busy time for you, after all.
So you're getting married this month, Aki?
I am, yes.
Well, welcome to you all!
I'm glad you could all make it.
So what're you growing in the fields?!
Potatoes at this time of year.
Oh, I can't wait to try them!
Glad to see you're enthusiastic, Erika.
Well then, why don't you two go get
changed and come help me in the field?
Okaaaaay!
A Wedding in Tears!
A Commemorative Photo for Father's Day!
All right then! I'm gonna get some big ones!
What's with these things? They won't budge at all!
You have to do this...
Oh, I see.
Now try pulling them.
Okay!
Hey, I did it! Look at these, Tsubomi!
Nice job!
Oh, this is a good chance for a photo!
Yay!
Here, try one of these.
Take a look at this!
What?
A tomato's most delicious
when these white lines have spread out, and you can just see the insides through them.
Here, try it.
Ugh! I don't like tomatoes. They're too sour...
You'll like it, really! Just take a bite out of it!
Huh... It really is nice.
It's not sour at all!
Tsubomi, this is really, really good!
Oh, that's another good chance for a photo!
They really are tasty, and sweet too.
Hey, mister...
Seconds please!
You really do raise your tomatoes with a lot of love, don't you?
You seem to know a lot about them, don'tcha?
Yup! I love flowers, so I grow a lot of them myself.
Well, that's good!
Any plant or vegetable can be considered beautiful if you treat them with love and affection.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's a frog!
Get it away, Tsubomi! Get it away from me!
What's the problem? It's so cute.
Oh, this is a good chance for a photo!
Cat's paws! Meoooow!
Give it to me for a second.
Just make a cat's paw with your left hand.
It's a simple trick when cooking.
Let's dig in!
It's delicious!
Whoa! It's really delicious!
It really is.
Vegetables really do taste better when they're fresh.
Yeah. I'm really glad we came!
I want to stay here forever!
It really is nice to have so many people around!
Oh, Aki. How're preparations for your wedding going?
Oh, right. All that's left to do is close on our new house.
I see.
So once you get married, Tadashi will be living here on his own, huh?
I imagine it'll be quite lonely for you.
Not at all, not at all! I'll finally be able to relax a little.
Well then, I guess if Erika stayed, she'd just be a nuisance.
It's amazing how much noise one girl can make.
That's not fair, Momo!
I'm totally stuffed and lovin' it...
I also ate way too much.
What're those? The photos from today?
Yup!
You just printed them?
Yeah. Everyone's really enjoying themselves.
Mind if I take a look?
Of course!
Thank you.
This is...
Oh, that's the best photo I took today.
When he was talking about tomatoes, he seemed so happy that I just pressed the shutter without thinking.
Yeah, that tomato was delicious...
Your father really does love
tending to his crops, doesn't he?
But if I get married...
Dad will be left all on his own.
I can't...
I can't be his wife if it means abandoning Dad...
Aki...
Non, non, non!
Is there nowhere that would
better complement my beauty?
"This place is dull, so we should go
somewhere with a bit of nature," is it?
I suppose you're right...
All right then! Allons-y!
It's nice to take a morning stroll every now and then, huh?
Tsubomi, Maru says he's worried about Aki.
Huh?
Wait, you can speak dog?!
We've become good friends already!
I'd love to be able to help her, but...
Tsubomi...
Why won't you just listen to me?!
Huh?
Please, just give up farming and come live in the city with us!
Aki?
I've been a farmer my whole life.
I can't just give it up that easily.
You know that as well as anyone, Aki.
If you're going to stay here,
Dad, then I can't get married!
Why're you saying such stupid things?
I'll keep on farming this land even after you've left.
These fields are precious to me.
Fine then!
What should we do, Tsubomi?!
Why are you asking me?!
Oh! Dad! Let's ask him for advice!
Sounds good to meeee...
And that's what happened.
It seems Aki's been constantly worrying about him.
Aki's such a kind girl, after all...
Dad, can't you sort this out?
Please help her!
All right then! Leave it to me!
Good luck, Dad!
Aki, getting married is supposed
to be the happiest day of your life.
Tadashi sounded ecstatic when
he told me about it on the phone.
Ever since you were young, you've always been the most important thing to him...
That's not...
That's not true anymore.
Those fields have become more
important to my father than I am!
A-Aki?!
Dad, you idiot! All you've done is make Aki storm off...
What do we do now?
Dad's so fixated on his photos that he never bothers to understand how people might be feeling.
Your dad's a man with a lot of love in his heart,
for both people and photos. He's been that way ever since we first met.
Okay, let's take a quick break. We can't shoot if the model's crying.
Um...
If you don't mind, would you take a look at these photos of mine?
These are...
Look.
They all seem really happy, don't they?
So please, try to cheer up.
Because I'm sure if I can capture your smile, then, well...
it'll be even more beautiful than any of those.
Well, you're obviously prettier than a horse...
Your dad tried his hardest to cheer me up.
Erika, it isn't just that he loves photography.
It's that he loves the people and
objects he captures within his photos.
Dad's photos always manage to make me feel warm inside.
I'm sure if you just let him deal with Aki, he'll sort it all out.
It'd be nice if he did, but...
Hey, Erika!
Dad?
What're you doing?
Can you call Aki over for me?
I want to take a family photo of them.
That's not going to help...
The emotions captured by a photograph will never truly fade away.
That's how I know that Tadashi still cares for Aki just as much as he did back then.
That's what I want her to see.
Dad!
Erika, let's go find her!
Right!
Where are we, might I ask?
The air here is far too fresh. I feel nauseous.
Huh?
Hey, you over there!
You should respond when I talk to you.
And yet you don't, even though I grace you with my voice?!
What the heck's with you?!
Wait, it's a scarecrow.
Excuse me! Could you not walk through the fields, please?
Huh?
That girl...
The Flower of her Heart is wilting from her sorrows.
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Scaaaaarecroooow!
Tsubomi!
Huh?
We've got trouble!
Aki!
Erika!
Let's do it!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
She's fast!
Use a Red Seed!
Huh?
Match speed with speed!
The Blessed Perfume of Red Light!
A spray makes my mood speed up!
Ready!
Go!
What the?! They're unbelievably fast!
Marine! It's time for Operation Eyespinny!
Yep, got it!
Tch... Impertinent whelps!
Oh?
I think Operation Eyespinny might be a failure...
My eyes have gone spinny instead...
Blossom and Marine are all dizzy!
What're these?!
I can't move!
This way, Ryuunosuke!
Dad!
Mister!
What the heck is that?!
Dad...
Dad, you never gave thought to how I felt.
I can't run off and get married if it means leaving you all alone.
Aki?! Is that you, Aki?!
Aki! Aki!
Aki!
I'm sorry, Aki! I'm such a fool...
Aki, please, look at this!
What?
It's a photograph I took of you both, as father and daughter!
This photo is filled with Tadashi's... no, your father's love for you!
And it's still just as strong as ever!
Your father was just being blunt with you so that you'd realize he was all right alone...
so you could get married without regrets!
Crow...
Aki!
Scare... crow...
The emotions captured by a photograph...
will never fade away!
It was from seeing you and how
much Tadashi cared for his family...
that I decided I wanted to become a father like him!
That I wanted to build a family like his!
He made me see that!
Dad!
Emotions captured by photographs?
How utterly ludicrous!
Photographs are but a tool to convey my beauty!
You're wrong!
Huh?!
Marine!
Blossom!
Precure Grand Explosion!
Focusing your thoughts on what's before the camera and pressing the shutter!
Photography is about love!
What nonsense.
Get them, Desertrian!
Scarecrow!
You're just toying with Aki's kind concern for her father.
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Tch. How pitiful you are, to not appreciate my beauty!
All right then. Let's make this the best family photograph you'll ever have.
The best... family photograph?
Dad, I...
Hm?
I think I might be the one who'll be lonely without you.
Aki, you should know that no matter how old you are...
you'll always be my daughter.
That won't change just because you've gotten married.
I know.
Make sure you build yourself a wonderful family.
I will.
In the language of flowers, a sweet potato means "a bride's joy."
I'm sure Aki will be a very happy bride.
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born...
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
You know, photos really are amazing.
I have a new admiration for them.
That's right! A photo is all about the relationship between the photographer and...
Stop!
What I'm trying to say is...
that you're amazing, Dad!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
We've gathered more and more Heart Seeds...
...and we've finally got something to show for it!
The Great Heart Tree gives birth to a yellow wonder, whose body holds hidden strength like dynamite!
My name's Potpourri!
Yay! Wahoo! We did it!
Our super pretty...
...and super cute new friend, Potpourri!
Nice to meet ya! We'll all be working with you!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Third Fairy!
Potpurri's an Adorable Little Baby!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!