Why is Nishiyama-san here?
Why is Hayama here?
Hayama is moved to tears?
...near-death experience?!
She is still alone.
Did she...
Here!
Cat Café
Tricky Cat
Now, now, no fighting.
Let's all be fwiends.
Nishiyama-san, your drink's ready.
Oh, okay!
Kono's gotten so big.
She's quite the trouble maker now.
Welcome!
Is a counter seat okay?
Yes.
Huh?
Huuuh?!
You Have Got Them Hooked
Teru-chan!
Are you awake?
Let's go out.
Central Shopping Arcade
I found a shop that you might like.
Oh...
Like a boutique?
Oh, right here.
Cat Café
I heard it's new.
Let's go in.
N-No!
I'd be two-timing!
I can't!
You have already been
going to other places!
Tricky Cat
Coupon
min
yen
Here's a coupon.
You were planning on coming here.
I've heard about this place.
I wish you'd told me
we were coming here.
I wanted to surprise you.
My phone camera's not that great.
Welcome.
Is a counter seat okay?
Sorry.
Why is Nishiyama-san here?
Why is Hayama here?
She'll ruin my cat café experience.
Just my luck.
Oh, isn't this your friend?
H-Hello.
Nice to see you again.
She's just a classmate, Nishiyama-san.
Oh, you were the one who took in
the last of the cats Teru-chan picked up.
Oh, yes.
Hey, hey, what did you name her?
Oh yeah, I never asked.
Her name is... um...
Ours is Bel-chan after "Beelzebub," because he
was swarming with flies when we took him in.
Bel-chan
I gave her a name that will give her
a long life, "Eternal" or El-chan for short.
Eternal
El
What?!
Oh, it's nothing.
Eternal?
It's just obvious that you
used the dictionary.
By the way...
...the names of the kitties here are...
Princess
Konohana Sakuya
...like "Princess Konohana Sakuya"...
Princess
Konohana Sakuya
...or like "Lakshmi," or like "Viracocha,"
or like "Teutates."
That's a little much.
All of their names are so refined.
Nishiyama-san, think about it.
You'd be using those names
at the vet or out in public.
Oh.
Anyway, I didn't come here to talk to you.
Right, Mi-chan?
I've missed you!
Oh, Nishiyama-san,
thanks for always coming.
Hello!
Mi-chan is here today.
I was worried since she
wasn't here last time.
Sorry to make you worry.
What a pro.
She wasn't feeling well.
You can tell she's a regular.
It's not like I'm frustrated by this!
Ohhh?
I didn't know Nishiyama-san
goes to cat cafés.
It sounds like something she would like.
I wonder if she'll send
those pictures to me.
If you just went to the cat café,
maybe you don't need this.
What?
A ticket for the petting zoo, Animal Town.
Huh?!
Of course I need that!
I-I get it...
Animal Town
Free Entrance
I got them from Sakura's mom,
and I thought you'd want it more than me.
Wow, thanks!
It's good for two people.
When should we go?
What?
Ah, it's good until Sunday.
We have three people,
so we can split the last ticket.
I'm not going.
Huh?
I don't really like animals...
Huh?!
And I have work.
Eh?
Ehhh?!
Oh, you can go with your sister.
With my sister?
All right!
Let's have some fun!
H-Hey!
Wow, so cute!
Be gentler with the small ones.
That one is cute!
But, this one is cute, too.
Calm down.
That one, too!
Adore them one at a time!
Big Sis!
I feel like it'd be tiring, and I
wouldn't have the time to have fun.
Oh, yeah!
Animal Town?
Animal Town
Free Entrance
Yup.
Youko-sama and I can't go,
so if you'd like, how about it?
What, really?!
Hey!
Why are you inviting Nishiyama?!
Don't you think she'd like it?
You went to the cat café together.
We didn't go together!
What is it?
I have a bad feeling about this...
Animal Town
Morning.
Morning!
I didn't think Nishiyama-san was
going to come because of Hayama.
Her love of animals was stronger, then.
Kondou-san!
You were worried, too?
Yeah, you know how they are.
They went in!
Let's go in, too!
Animal Town
Welcome
Welcome!
Even trough they're
still at the entrance...
Yes, over here.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Oh, you're in charge of sales.
Are you always working here?
When will they go in?
It's been ten minutes already.
Nishiyama-san, you'll run out
of memory at this rate!
Honestly, I don't want
to stay with Hayama.
We can split up or something from here.
First, I'll go see the small animals that
are closest, then go to the dog show.
Small Animal House
Dog Show
Dog Run
Then, to the cat room, small dog petting corner,
watch the animal show, then the horse park.
Doggie
Petting House
Okay, Hayama-san.
We can split up from here.
Oh, really?
No way.
Did she have the same plan in mind?
Jump and catch!
Animal Town
Doggie Show
Jack succeeded!
Amazing!
That was amazing!
Hayama is moved to tears?
Despite the increasing number of unruly
human children, dogs are amazing!
Actually, dogs are better!
Don't think about it like that!
I guess they're going around together.
Will they be okay?
They might fight or something...
Well, I don't think Hayama-chan
will get angry today.
Really?
She vowed to exercise self-discipline.
Self-discipline?
To broaden her experiences
by getting to know all kinds of people.
Freedom from worldly
attachments or something.
Is that... so?
I don't really get it, though.
But...
...if Nishiyama-san keeps
picking a fight with her...
There!
Over here!
Wow, Nishiyama-san.
You have got them hooked.
Oh?
Well, it's natural if you own a cat.
Maybe you're just not good at it?
Yeah, I'm not that good at it.
Oh, are you drinking juice?
I'm being healthy and got tea.
Cold juices have too much sugar.
That's Nishiyama-san for you.
I should follow your example.
Doggie Petting House
That's a Weimaraner.
In America, it's known as the "Grey Ghost."
You don't even know that?
You sure know a lot.
You're amazing, Nishiyama-san.
Of course!
Hm?
I don't know why, but she's
in a good mood today, huh.
It's like she's another person entirely.
N-Nishiyama's going at full throttle!
The dam might break soon...
Nishiyama!
Today was more fun than expected.
I guess I could thank you, Hayama-san.
Nishiyama-san...
Huh?
Wh-What?
That Hayama!
I was nice enough to go with her...
...and she...
...she—!
Will you cheer me up?
Thanks, El-chan.
How was Animal Town?
It was fun!
I want to go again.
And Nishiyama-san?
How was she?
Same as usual.
She got angry half way and left, though.
What?
The petting houses and shows were fun, too.
Maybe she left because I said that her getting
carried away with herself was the funniest.
Those two just don't get along.
Quite right.
Stuffed Hut
But you know, I really thought
it was a good chance!
For what?
You know how Hayama-chan and Nishiyama-san
went to Animal Town together?
What...
I thought it was a good chance for them
to understand each other better.
Futaba-san...
And maybe they'd reach a point where it
wouldn't be as awkward in class anymore.
Ah...
You even like the same things...
I think you should be able to get along...
Didn't I say the same exact thing to you?
Finished the Mega Ogre Omelet Rice!
Oh, good.
And time's up.
Aw, I lost.
I couldn't finish.
Don't think you have won
just yet, Odagiri Futaba!
Stuffed Hut
I'll remember this!
Thanks for coming!
Can you get along with him even
though you have similar interests?
Sorry, not happening.
Hayama-chan!
Let's start a band!
You took way too long to say that.
It's the autumn of the arts.
What is going on?
Oh!
Youko-sama, you should join our band!
Nishiyama-san, Kondou-san!
You look like you want to be in a band!
What?!
Big Sis.
River of Three Crossings
I cannot cross, but still...
The tears trail down
My, what a wonderful voice.
I disappear with the foam, om
Om, om, om
Oh, I feel dizzy.
She's slightly out of tune.
River of Three Crossings in the beautiful spring
I want to pick that flower.
Yamaji, be my ladder!
There!
Get it, Yuu-san!
River of Three Crossings that Kou sings
Om, om, om
Youko-sama!
Get a hold of yourself, Youko-sama!
Thank God!
You're come to, Youko-sama!
You scared me, because
you suddenly fainted.
Is this was... near-death experience?!
The end!
That was "River of Three
Crossings" by Hayama Kou!
So bad!
The River of Three Crossings
is like the rivers Styx, right?
People tend to start singing
without thinking about it.
Like when you're alone or
trying to calm a baby down.
Nishiyama-san, you always sing songs
dedicated to Eternal-chan in your room, right?
I do not!
Oh, I want to hear it.
I told you there's no such thing!
Nishiyama! Nishiyama!
Hey, cut it out!
Nishiyama, yeah! Nishiyama, whoo!
Nishiyama, yeah! Nishiyama, go!
Nishiyama-san got super mad yesterday, huh?
Come on, I feel sorry for her.
You can't say that after
what happened at Animal Town.
Oh?
That's...
It's Kondou-san.
She is usually with Nishiyama-san.
It's strange to see her alone.
She is still alone.
Did she...
...get into a quarrel because of yesterday?
She is all alone, even though she
is always usually with her friend.
Come on, bread is better.
No, rice is the best!
Rice indeed!
You're...!
Is it okay if Kondou-san
joins us for lunch today?
When I saw her alone,
I couldn't help but invite her.
I do not mind.
Do not worry over that nobody
who gets mad over such trivial matters.
Huh?
Somehow Youko-sama is
being excessively welcoming.
She understands what
it's like to be a loner.
What?
Nishiyama's not a nobody!
She's actually really
hard-working and a nice girl.
She just intolerant of others!
Anyway, let's eat lunch.
Lunch.
So you have known Nishiyama-san
since elementary school.
Yup.
We were in the same group
during a field trip in third grade.
She was our group leader, and she helped me
out when I was a little slow on things.
And she's liked roles that
end with "leader" ever since?
Exactly.
And she wasn't always like this.
You know how things don't always
go the way you want in high school.
There's someone who's
always in her way here.
Oh no, is it my fault?
Nishiyama-san could get along so nicely
with Hayama-chan if she weren't so crotchety.
They like the same things, too.
If she were reasonably nice
on the outside like Hayama-san,
she could be the next class representative.
Huh?
Same goes for you, Nishikawa-san.
Hey—
What?
Stop being so prickly and snobby
and talk to people around you.
You're pretty, so I'm sure
here are people who admire you.
Y-You think so?
Yeah!
When pretty girls aren't friendly,
Is Kondou-san...
people won't want to approach them.
...complimenting, or belittling...
...or just plain insensitive?
So why not trying harder
to talk to people?
R-Right...
Thanks for today.
Oh, it was nothing.
Odagiri Futaba!
You beat my brother in
a challenge again, didn't you?!
I didn't mean for it to be a competition.
And you're always eating lunch with
Nishikawa-san, always just the three of you!
Huh?
Oh, I'm just special.
Spe-cial?!
She's so interesting.
You're up there with her, too.
At ramen, you have just got to get veggies
piled high, dumplings, and pork rice bowl, right?
Um, will you come with me somewhere?
Oh?
Let's see.
You're...
Hello, auntie.
Nishiyama-san's friend who has no tact.
Kondou-san is here to buy a cake
Nishiyama-san likes so they can make up.
Make up?
Oh, I know!
Here!
What is that?
Something that Nishiyama-san likes.
Oh, that's Nishiyama's uniform
from when she worked here!
I said cake, did I not?!
That's funny.
I'm glad you're amused.
Oh, auntie, you used to be one of
Nishikawa-san's servants, right?
Yes.
So Nishikawa-san really was a rich girl.
She can be intimidating and overbearing.
Kondou-san is pretty amazing.
She's as scary as a final boss.
Nevertheless, I really do admire you.
Huh? About what?
She should be apologizing after
getting mad about something so small,
but you bought an apology gift.
Uh, Youko-sama,
I think you misunderstand.
Huh?
Kondou-san wasn't alone today
because she got into a quarrel.
Nishiyama-san was absent,
because she was sick.
Wha—?!
I-I just... thought...
See?
Nishiyama Serina
No subject
How are you feeling?
Are you lonely  sleeping
at home all day?
But it's better to get rest.
Get better~!
I sent a ton of emails to her
to see how she's doing.
A-All this time... I thought...
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
It was kind of your fault, too.
Kondou Asako
What's up with this?
She suddenly stopped
emailing me after lunch.
Even through she sent so many
in the morning, I couldn't sleep.
Thanks.
You're so nice, El-chan.
"E" in "Eternal" is for your
cuteness that can't be drawn.
"T" is for your tremendous overflowing love.
She's actually singing a song
dedicated to Eternal-chan.
Wow, so there really is such a song.
"R" is for reaching beyond hyperspace.
When should we enter?
Let's listen until the end.
"N" is for the nameless blooming flower.
It's such a nice song.
What?!
"L" is for...
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's Asako...
It's
Asako...
...and Selina's preview for the next episode—
...and
Selina's
pre-
view for
the next
episode—
—hey, I've had enough!
—hey,
I've
had
enough!
Just
do
what-
ever!
Just do whatever!
Oh?
Then,
why don't
you sing a
character
song or
some-
thing?
Then, why don't you sing
a character song or something?
What?!
Char-
acter
song!
Char-
acter
song!
Character song! Character song!
clap
I-I guess I have no choice.
I-I guess
I have no
choice.
Next time: Curry Tastes Better on the Second Day