Einzbern Castle, Germany
— Eight Years Ago —
Master Kiritsugu!
Your child's been born!
She's so beautiful.
So small... So delicate.
Look, Kiritsugu. She has your eyes.
I'm so happy to have given birth to such a beautiful baby...
Iri.
I...
You're going to die because of me.
I know.
The Einzberns desire nothing further.
That is my purpose.
I am who I am today because
I took your ideals to heart,
and I pray for the same things as you.
You showed me a better path.
You granted me a life beyond
that of a mindless puppet.
You don't need to feel sorry.
I'm a part of you now.
So...
I...
I have no right to hold...
...our child.
Kiritsugu, do not forget.
You desire a world where no one
has to cry the way you are now.
That is your dream and ideal,
as well as that of Emiya Kiritsugu.
In a mere eight years, your battle will end.
And our ideal will become reality.
The Holy Grail will save you.
So hold her... Hold Illyasviel in your arms.
And take pride in your only daughter...
...as any father would.
Torino, Italy
— Three Years Ago —
Command Spells?
The mystical stigmata marking your right hand.
It's proof that the Holy Grail has chosen you,
endowing you with the power to
command a Servant.
Kotomine Kirei-kun.
The Holy Grail War...
The battle for that legendary holy artifact
has chosen me?
Normally, the Grail selects seven people,
as Masters to the Servants,
each of whom would be a mage.
For one such as yourself,
with no connection to magic, to be chosen
this early is exceedingly rare.
Servants...
Heroes, summoned from the past,
who fight alongside you... it all seems so...
I realize it may be hard to believe,
but legendary heroes, of past eras
and countries across the world,
will be summoned here, to fight to the death.
That is the essence of the Holy Grail War.
Of course, there is an unspoken pact among all the participants that the war must remain secret.
In order to guarantee everyone's compliance,
we of the Holy Church designate
an impartial observer.
Can a member of our Church act as an arbitrator
in a war amongst mages?
The impartiality of someone
selected by the Magus Association
could never be trusted.
So once again, we will ask your father
to oversee our battle,
as he did sixty years ago.
My father will be in Fuyuki City?
But if the impartial observer's son
is a participant, would that not constitute
a conflict of interest?
Tokiomi-kun.
Let us come to the point.
Kirei, everything we've discussed
so far is common knowledge
to those involved with the Holy Grail War.
The reason I called you here and introduced you to Tohsaka Tokiomi lies elsewhere.
And that would be?
Many years ago, we found evidence
that the Holy Grail
that will appear in Fuyuki City is not the same
as that which once belonged
to the Son of God.
I thought as much.
If it were, we of the Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament
would have been issued retrieval orders.
Regardless, this Holy Grail of Fuyuki City
is too powerful for us to ignore.
The Grail can, quite literally,
grant any wish imaginable.
Who knows what catastrophe might befall us
should it fall into the wrong hands?
Thus,
if we could, at least,
ensure that Fuyuki's Holy Grail will
select worthy individuals,
it would be irresponsible not to act.
The Tohsaka family may be a clan of mages,
but they have long been allies of our Church.
We know Tokiomi-kun very well,
and he has made his intention
for the Grail perfectly clear...
To reach the source.
That has always been the Tohsakas' sole ambition.
Once, the Einzberns and the Matous
shared that ambition,
but they have since strayed.
As for the Masters outside the families,
the less said, the better.
There's no telling what vile dreams
fuel their lust for the Grail.
Then my reason to participate
in the next Holy Grail War
is to facilitate Tohsaka Tokiomi's victory?
Obviously, in public we must act as enemies, each determined to win the Grail for himself.
Privately, however, we will be working together
in order to destroy the five other Masters
and ensure our victory.
That is our plan, Kirei-kun.
We will transfer you from the Church
to the Magus Association,
where you will study under me.
The order has already been issued.
You will study magic, at my home in Japan.
By the start of the Holy Grail War, three years from now,
you must become a mage powerful enough
to summon and command a Servant.
So...
Do you have any questions, Kirei?
Just one.
How does the Holy Grail choose the Masters?
The Grail tries to select those
who most need its power.
You're saying all Masters have a reason to desire the Grail?
Not necessarily.
In the past, there have been cases
of Command Spells appearing
on people who would not normally be chosen.
Ah, I understand now, Kirei-kun.
You still don't know why it chose you.
I'm surprised he accepted so readily.
My son would leap into an inferno
if the Church asked him to.
I'd go so far as to say it was anticlimactic.
From his point of view,
he's been dragged into fighting
a war in which he has no stake.
No, I think this may be exactly what he needs.
It's been mere days since he lost his wife.
Having a new mission to devote himself to
may help Kirei through his grief
that much more quickly.
Fuyuki City, Japan
— One Year Ago —
Aoi-san.
Kariya-kun, welcome home.
Are you home from your trip?
This one was quite long, wasn't it?
Yeah, I know...
Uncle Kariya!
Uncle Kariya, you're home!
Rin-chan.
Did you bring me a present?
Rin, where are your manners?
Here you go.
Thank you!
I'm glad you like it.
Where's Sakura-chan?
Sakura's gone.
Aoi-san...
Sakura is no longer my daughter or Rin's sister.
She...
She is at the Matou manor.
Why?
Why do the Matous want a
child with magical blood?
You know why.
The Tohsaka and
the Matou have been allies for generations.
The Tohsaka elders decided to
grant the Matous' petition.
There was nothing I could say.
And that's it?
I accepted that this could happen
when I married into the Tohsaka family,
when I became a mage's wife.
You're okay with this?
Those from families bearing magical blood
can never hope for a happy, normal life.
That's not true!
You married him because you
wanted that happiness...
This is between the Tohsaka and the Matou.
You turned your back on the world of magic.
It is no longer your concern.
If you do see Sakura again, be kind to her.
You two were always so close, Kariya-kun.
You've got some nerve, showing your face here,
you disgrace.
I'm quite certain I told you
I never wanted to see you again,
Kariya.
I hear you adopted a young Tohsaka girl.
You heard right.
You're really that desperate to ensure
the Matou family magic?
Are you, of all people,
telling me that I'm wrong to do so?
Whose fault is it that we have sunk to this state?
Kariya...
I wouldn't be in this situation
had you simply done your duty to
inherit the Matou family secrets.
Yet you have the gall to lecture me...
Enough, you vampire.
You only want the Holy Grail
so you can wish for immortality.
Next year will mark sixty years.
The house of Matou has no soldiers
to fight in the Fourth Holy Grail War.
And while once, you might have had
what it takes to control a Servant,
your older brother Byakuya does not.
Even if we cannot win this war,
I still have a plan for the one sixty years after.
The Tohsaka girl is sure to bear powerful mages.
To say nothing of her own potential.
In other words, as long as you
get your hands on the Grail,
you have no particular use for Tohsaka Sakura.
What are you getting at?
I'll make you a deal, Zouken.
During the next Grail War, I'll win the
Holy Grail for the Matous.
In exchange, you will free Tohsaka Sakura.
Ridiculous.
You, a quitter with no training,
will become powerful enough
in a single year to be a Servant's Master?
I know you have a method
that could accomplish that...
Your creepy little creatures.
Hmm?
Implant the Crest Worms in me!
Kariya, do you have a death wish?
The Matous should do their own dirty work.
I won't let an innocent outsider
be dragged into this.
Don't tell me you're worried about me, Dad.
If you hoped to handle this
before she became involved, Kariya...
you've come to me too late.
Monster...  You didn't...
Oh, she cried and screamed
for the first three days.
But since the fourth day,
she hasn't made a peep.
First thing in the morning,
I threw her down there
to see how long she'd last.
And there she is, still breathing a half day later.
The Tohsakas are something else.
Sakura!
So, what will it be?
Here's a broken shell of a girl,
who's been violated
by those worms, head to toe.
Now, if you still wish to save her,
I will accept your terms.
Done.
Just remember, until you fulfill
your end of the bargain,
I'll have Sakura continue her education.
After all, my primary objective is still
achieving victory in the next Holy Grail War.
On the off-chance you do deliver
the Grail to me,
then I would, of course, have no
further use for the girl.
She'll only have had to endure
one year of training.
I'll hold you to your word, Matou Zouken.
Lie there for a week, and allow them
to use you as their breeding ground.
If you don't go insane and die,
I will acknowledge that
you're serious about this.
It's here.
What is?
A report from my spies in London.
Apparently, the Grail has chosen a Master
from the Magus Association's highest tier,
the Clock Tower.
Who is it?
A very dangerous man.
The eldest son of the infamous
Archibald family of mages that has produced
nine consecutive generations of mages.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
Clock Tower, London
— Present Day —
In the world of magic,
pedigree determines rank.
This is because the secrets of magic
simply cannot be learned
within a single generation.
The parents must spend their lives training,
and pass down the fruits
of their labor to their children.
This is why the oldest magical families
are the most powerful.
Some of you may be wondering
why I am presenting such basic knowledge.
Yesterday, a student turned in an essay.
The title is, "How Wizardry
Should Be in the New Century."
This paper objects to the accepted theory that I have just presented.
It argues that a deeper understanding of spells
and skillful mana control
could enable someone to bridge the gap.
In other words, even someone with a very limited
magical pedigree could become a first-class mage.
I will admit that this essay taught me something.
Quiet!
I'll be clear.
Every word of this paper is drivel.
Bloodlines determine magical skill.
That is an irrefutable truth.
Mr. Waver Velvet...
I find it lamentable that
one of my students would harbor
such delusional beliefs.
Sir, I only wanted to raise the issue to the Magus Association because they haven't addressed it—
Mr. Waver!
Your family has
only produced three generations
of mages, correct?
It seems to me that, compared to
the Association's long history,
your family is still a crying infant.
And a baby must learn to speak
before he can talk back to his parents.
That egotistical blowhard, making a fool of me!
And he calls himself a professor?
My thesis just made him jealous!
He's afraid of my talent!
That's why he wanted to humiliate me in public.
Whoops, sorry...
You all right?
Y-Yes...
You one of the Necromancy students?
Shouldn't you be at your lecture?
I, uh...
Professor Archibald wanted me
to run an errand for him,
so I'm in a bit of a hurry...
Oh, how fortunate.
Could you take this package
to Professor Archibald?
This package?
It looks important, so I'm counting on you.
Important...
It's from Macedonia.
There it is.
So the rumors that Kayneth is fighting
in some Far East magical war were true.
The Holy Grail War...
Two hundred years ago, the families
known as "the three,"
the Einzberns, Makiris, and Tohsakas,
worked together to summon the Holy Grail,
a holy artifact with the power
to grant its bearer any wish.
However, the Grail can only
answer one prayer.
Their alliance disintegrated
into a brutal, bloody war.
That is the origin of the Holy Grail Wars.
Ever since,
the Holy Grail has appeared in Fuyuki City
once every sixty years.
The Grail selects seven mages
it deems worthy to possess it.
And it enables them to summon powerful
heroes' spirits, known as Servants.
Archer.
Saber.
Lancer.
Rider.
Assassin.
Caster.
Berserker.
There can only be seven Servants,
divided into the seven classes.
Once summoned, they fight to
the death, trying to establish
who is truly worthy of possessing the Holy Grail.
You don't need pedigree or influence
in the Holy Grail War.
You just need to be the most talented.
I'm a perfect candidate for this!
Additionally, one needs a relic
that once belonged
to the Servant, to act as a catalyst
during their summoning.
A relic...
No matter how many times I see it,
that device always bothers me.
It's a report from Clock Tower.
Lord El-Melloi has procured
a new summoning relic.
His participation is now assured.
The fact that two open spots remain unnerves me.
Don't worry.  The Grail will choose its seven, heedless of skill.
That quota means most of the participants will be weak.
No need to worry about them.
In fact, Kirei, I'm more concerned that
someone may have seen you enter this place.
Don't be.
No familiars or magical devices
were guarding the mansion,
not even invisible ones.
Of that...
Of that, I assure you.
I am Hassan, master strategist,
and no petty tricks will escape my eye.
I sense no presences in this vicinity, Master.
Please put your mind at ease.
My father will know immediately,
once another Servant is summoned.
I believe the other mages will
wait before acting.
Assassin, we are done here.
Continue guarding the outside.
As you wish.
It's only a matter of time.
Soon, the other Masters' familiars
will be lurking about this place.
What's that?
A separate matter.
I've been gathering intelligence
on the Einzbern Master.
It's been about nine years now...
The Einzberns are famously proud
of the purity of their blood,
but then, they unexpectedly adopted
a mage from outside the family.
Combat never suited the Einzberns,
who had focused their efforts on alchemy.
That is the reason they lost the
previous Holy Grail Wars.
Finally, I suppose they'd had enough.
The mage they adopted is a man who will be a great asset to them.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
The man known as the Mage-Slayer.
After years of searching,
we've finally found the relic
we sought in Cornwall.
Use it as your catalyst,
and the swordsman you summon will surely be
the strongest of all the Servants.
Kiritsugu.
The Einzberns can offer you
no greater gift than this.
I am deeply in your debt, Elder.
Leave no survivors.
Slay the other six Servants,
and complete the Third Magic, Heaven's Feel.
I will.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I've heard that name before.
So his reputation has even reached within the Church walls.
The Mage-Slayer was quite infamous in his day.
He appears to be a mere rogue mage,
with no connection to the Association,
but the higher-ups were not above
using his services to their benefit.
Like our Church's Executors?
Even worse.
This man is best described as a freelance assassin
who specializes in murdering mages.
He knows how mages think,
and he uses tactics utterly unsuited to a mage
to eliminate his targets.
Read the report.
Sniping...  Poison...
Bombs in broad daylight...
Bringing down an entire airplane,
just because his target was a passenger on it!
He uses these underhanded tactics shamelessly.
Because we, as mages,
live separate from the world's general laws,
it is paramount that we follow the
laws we've made for ourselves.
But this man lacks even a shred of pride as a mage.
His methods are inexcusable.
So, this Emiya Kiritsugu...
Why did he become an assassin?
I assume it was for the money.
As you can see in the report,
he's been responsible for more
than just killing mages.
He's popped up in conflicts all over the world,
bankrolling money by acting as a mercenary.
May I borrow this report for a little while?
Let's review everything we have so far, Iri.
So far, we know four out of the seven
Masters the Grail has chosen.
Tohsaka Tokiomi, head of the Tohsaka family.
A powerful, fire-natured mage,
specializing in Gem Magic.
Matou Kariya.
This kid severed all ties with his family,
but they still took him in
and made him a Master?
That old fart must be desperate.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
Dual natures of wind and water.
Expert in Necromancy, Summoning, and Alchemy.
And...
Emiya Kiritsugu.
Newest member of the Einzbern family,
their secret weapon...
And the man I love, with all my heart.
The fourth... Or rather, the fifth
Master comes from the Church.
Kotomine Kirei.
The Church?
He's the son of the judge, Father Kotomine Risei.
It says he studied under
Tohsaka Tokiomi for three years,
but severed all ties with him
once his Command Spells appeared.
What's wrong?
They have his whole life's story...
Have a look.
Since childhood, Kotomine Kirei
has accompanied his father, Risei,
on holy pilgrimages.
He attended Saint Ignatius of Manresa...
Skipped two grades... And graduated
at the top of his class?
Talk about a prodigy.
Then he abandons the fast-track,
and enters the Church.
Why lower himself
to join one of the Church's secret organizations?
Perhaps his father pushed him into it?
See?  It says they both belong to
the Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament.
If it were for his father, he would have
followed that path from the start.
But he changed vocations three times,
before joining his father in the Assembly.
He even served as an Executor for a time.
An Executor?
A heretic hunter.
Not unlike what I once was...
A mage-slayer.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
The assassinations that can be tied to him
all occurred within a very short period.
Simultaneously, he was hopping
from one war zone to the next.
Every time, it was when the battles
were at their fiercest.
It's as if he traveled the world
seeking his own destruction.
These are the actions of one with a death wish.
What does it all mean?
Alchemy, Necromancy, Summoning,
Divination, Healing.
Notice the variety of magic he's studied.
Why would he do that?
He'd train until he was one
step short of full mastery,
and then he'd switch to a new category
without a second thought.
It's as if he threw all that effort away,
like it was meaningless.
Iri...
The way Kotomine Kirei lives terrifies me.
It's like he is incapable of acting for his own benefit.
No one would do these things
had they taken the time to weigh
the risk against the reward.
There's no way he's just a freelancer
in it for the money.
His whole life, he's never had
a passion for anything.
He doesn't believe
in anyone or anything.
He has no desire of his own.
I have to wonder...
What is he after?
Why would he risk his life to obtain the Grail?
However, the Grail chose
Kotomine Kirei to be a Master.
Indeed.
So he must have a reason
to covet the Grail, after all.
I just have no idea what it could be.
That's what scares me.
Kotomine Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
After an age of nonstop combat,
he finally closed that chapter
of his life nine years ago,
upon meeting the mages of
the north, the Einzberns.
That is when he found his answer.
So the question is,
what was he seeking in those wars?
And what did he find?
You made it, by the skin of your teeth.
If the Grail chose you,
it means you've substantially progressed as a mage.
I'll give you credit, Kariya.
You look like hell, though.
Can you still feel your left leg?
Easy, there.
If the worms get too agitated,
they'll devour you from the inside out.
Either way, I give you a month to live, at best.
That'll be enough.
What?
I said that'll be enough.
Well, Kariya, as a reward for
surviving the entire year,
I brought you the perfect summoning relic.
Don't let your old father's
kindness go to waste.
I've got a Command Spell!
The Grail chose me!
The Grail recognizes my talent!
I don't have time to celebrate.
I need to prepare for summoning my Servant!
Serial Killings in Fuyuki
Good morning, Waver.
Morning, Waver!
Morning, Grandpa... Grandma...
Fuyuki is in real trouble.
It's so sad.
By the way, Martha...
I thought I heard a bunch of roosters,
crowing or something this morning.
What's going on?
There are three, out in the backyard.
Our backyard?
Yes. I wonder where they came from.
Waver, would you like some coffee?
Oh, Waver... Your hand!
Uh-oh!
That bruise!
A bruise?
That bruise wasn't there yesterday.
Oh, damn...
You just had to notice.
What is it, Waver?
Waver?
Everything's fine.
Here, have some coffee.
I put extra milk in it,
just the way you like.
Here, coffee.
Now I've gotta recast the whole spell
to make these two think I'm their grandson,
back from study abroad...
What a pain.
While I'm at it, best to add something
about the roosters I stole.
They actually found the legendary
sword's scabbard...
There isn't a scratch on it,
yet it's supposed to be 1,500 years old?
The weapon itself is a type
of Conceptual Armament.
It won't weather or dull
as an ordinary blade would.
Simply equipping this scabbard
will heal its wielder's wounds and
keep them forever young.
Just like in the legend.
Of course, that only works given a steady
supply of the original owner's mana.
In other words, paired with the hero,
this sword could be a Master's ultimate weapon.
I knew you'd say something like that.
A tool is nothing but a tool, right?
That applies to the Servant, too.
Once summoned, they're just another
tool in their Master's arsenal,
no matter how famous or powerful
they were in their own era.
There's no surviving this war
by deluding yourself into thinking otherwise.
That attitude is exactly why
my great-grandfather decided
the scabbard would be the perfect relic for you.
I wonder about that.
You don't care for his gift, then?
Don't be silly.
Acht really came through for us.
I'm positive that no other Master
has such a powerful relic.
Then what's the matter?
The bond between relic and owner is so strong,
we're sure to summon
the exact spirit we're after.
Arthur Pendragon, the legendary King of Knights.
It won't even matter how well our personalities mesh.
But, with Excalibur in our arsenal,
the Saber class will yield
the strongest possible Servant.
Exactly.
My Servant will boast power
leagues beyond the other six.
The problem is I must find a way
to fully harness that power.
Someone like myself would have
a much easier time
commanding a Servant of the
Assassin or Caster class.
There's no point in worrying over that
before the summoning.
It's not as if we can know what the
King of Knights was like in life.
Besides, regardless of your tactics,
once he learns of your ideals,
he'll understand. I know he will.
Just like I did.
What?
I've got it.
A way to use the strongest Servant...
in the most effective way.
Hello, Rin.
Hello, Kirei.
Going somewhere?
That suitcase looks pretty heavy.
Yeah, I'm going to live
with the Zenjou family.
And you're staying to fight
alongside my dad, right?
Yes, that's why I came here to study with him.
Kirei... Can I trust you?
Will you promise to protect my dad
and keep him safe,
until everything's all over?
If only I could.
If this war were simple enough that
I could make that promise,
we wouldn't need to send
you and your mother away.
You know what, I don't think
I'm ever gonna like you!
Rin, it's not polite to say such things,
even if you think them.
It reflects poorly on your father
and on your upbringing.
This doesn't concern my dad!
Listen up, Kirei!
If my dad gets hurt because
you were goofing off,
I'll kick your butt myself!
Rin, why are you yelling in the house?
Um...
I...
She was just giving me a little
pep talk before you left.
Here, let me help.
That suitcase is too heavy for you.
No, I can do it.
Kotomine-san, please watch over my husband.
Help him fulfill his wish.
Don't worry. I'll do everything I can.
Hello?
Your timing is impeccable.
The relic I requisitioned
just arrived this morning.
See for yourself.
What is it?
The fossilized, molted skin of the first snake,
shed at the dawning of our world.
If we use this as the catalyst to summon
the spirit we're after,
our victory is assured.
Hi, Sakura-chan.
Did I scare you?
Your face...
Oh, yeah...
Looks like I let the worms get
the better of me for a while.
Your poor uncle isn't as tough
as you are, you know.
I feel like you're becoming a
different person, Uncle Kariya.
Maybe I am.
Grandfather said I don't have to go
down to the worm room tonight,
since he needs the room
for a more important ceremony.
Yup, I know.
In fact, I'll be going to the basement tonight.
Are you going somewhere far away?
Yes, I have a very important job to do.
From now on, I might not have as
much time to talk with you.
Oh...
Sakura-chan,
when I finish my job,
why don't we go somewhere fun?
We'll bring your mother and sister, too.
I don't have anyone to call a mother or sister.
Grandfather told me to act as if
they'd never existed at all.
I see.
Uncle?
Then, we'll invite Aoi-san and Rin-chan
from the Tohsaka manor,
and the four of us will go somewhere
far, far away, like we used to.
We can all have fun together.
I'll get to see them again?
You bet.
I promise.
I have to go now.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Uncle Kariya.
Bye-bye...
You did learn the summoning spell, right?
Yes.
Good, but I'm going to have you insert two lines
from a different incantation.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
You, Kariya, are quite a bit little less capable
as a mage, compared to the other Masters.
And because of that, your Servant's
basic stats will be degraded.
Thus, we need to do something
during the summoning itself
to raise your Servant's innate abilities.
Kariya, you will add an incantation
that gives your Servant an affinity for madness.
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill!
Repeat it five times.
As each is fulfilled, so must it be destroyed.
A foundation of iron and silver...
Upon it rests the cornerstone and
the Archduke of Contracts.
Above them, my ancestor,
the great Master Schweinorg.
Become the wall that repels the gale.
The four gates close tightly.
Now burst forth from the crown,
and follow the winding road
that leads to the kingdom.
Is this simple ceremony really sufficient
to summon such a mighty hero?
I know it's disappointing, but yes.
The ceremony doesn't really
require an incantation,
because it's actually the Grail itself
that's doing the summoning.
As a Master, my job is to anchor the
Servant's spirit to this world,
and to provide the mana it needs
to manifest a physical body.
All set.
Iri, lay the scabbard on the altar.
That is the final step.
I call to thee.
Thy body, borne of my will.
My fate, resting on thy sword!
If thou wilt bend to my will, my justice,
heed the Grail's call, and give your answer!
I swear before you,
I will become all that is good in the world,
and I shall eradicate all that is evil.
But thine eyes shalt be clouded by chaos.
Thou shalt be trapped in a cage of madness,
and I shalt hold thy chains!
Seven Heavens, clad in the three holy souls,
cast aside your shackles and come forth...
Guardian of the Scales!
We've won, Kirei.
Victory...
...is ours!
You are...
I ask of you...
Are you my Master?
Episode 1
The Summoning of Heroes
I believe that you and Kiritsugu are
fighting for a noble cause.
There is no place for two kings.
I promise.
You're not even fit to look at me.
You are so cool!
Your first mission is to slay Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Next Time
The Fake First Shot