Where the winds are green and the tea leaves dry,
from a foggy country,
The ambassador of love and courage.
I am the Black Rose Baron.
Give me two plates of noodles. That's all. Thank you.
Hey, should we stop already?
This should be enough, for today…
Nekane is Jesus! 8D
Now, when even the plants are asleep, and in a secret, unseen place...
I couldn’t sleep right now...
Sorry for pullin' you into this.
You really like Zombie Rider, huh, Konoka?
I only like the son-in-law episode.
Huh?
Is someone there?
At this hour?
Oh, my!
You are...
Erm... What should I do?
Nooo~! ♥
Yeah?
Oh! That's wrong! Not for this.
Please wait for a moment...
Erm...
Aaah! I'm sinking!
Save me!
Ah! Thank you!
You are my... savior!
I was being chased by Inflation and suddenly fell into the river.
When I came to, I realized that I was carried into this place.
Into the bath?
It's strange, isn't it?
This is troublesome.
Um, in that case...
Would my presence here be unnatural?
Well...
Let's think about it!
She is Nekane Springfield!
Negi's Oneechan!
Ah, thanks!
I will leave Negi in your care!
Don't mention it.
"Natsumi, A family is the king of home runs in terms of relationships, after all."
by Chizuru.
"I really don't understand, Chizu-nee!"
by Natsumi.
Oneechan...
Ah. Oneechan...
Geez, Negi.
You're always so blur.
O-- O--
Oneechan!!
Yep! It's me!
Why are you here!?
She was transported here!
Transported?
She just realized that she got sent here!
Just realized...?
It's a long story.
Well, let's just say that's what happened.
That's the story?
Well, that's my story.
Thus, this is my oneechan.
I am Nekane Springfield.
I'm from Wales.
Let's be friends!
Pleased to meet you, Nekane-san!
Pleased to meet you too!
This is one unexpected development...
Way too unexpected.
The five inch nails of autumn prayers...
Your blooming light speaks of topics, the very surprising lone organizer!
I am the Black Lily Baron Potato!
Do you want to know my identity?
Don’t you want to know..?
Not really, myaaa...
I am the Black Lily Baron Potato!
Yes... yes...
Ah! Father!
Father?
I don't remember having a daughter that looks like you.
Listen well!
I am the Black Li...
You're horrible.
What?
Even my father...
Even my father......
I hate you!!
T-This has become an awkward situation...
W-W-W-W-W-What should I do?
I don't know, mya.
Black Rose Baron?
He's always appearing at random times.
He doesn't seem to be a bad person.
But, we don't know his identity or his intentions.
So someone like that does exist...
Negi, what if he is actually... the Thousand Master!?
Just kidding!
What? You were joking!
Stop fooling around, Oneechan!
Sorry, Sorry!
Zazie!!
Ahh... beautiful brotherly love.
What just happened?
Nothing...
Today, Chiu did some really interesting observations on things!
And then, I had some tea.
And ate some thing really yummy!
Nekane-san's destroyed some of the darkness, huh..?
She's a mage, that's why.
Back then, it wouldn't be considered a strange thing.
But, I'm worried that she didn’t tell Negi-sensei anything about it.
Yeah, it’s strange! There must be some secret behind it!
There are secrets, aru?
Hey!
What do you think, Asuna?
Asuna-dono?
Arrgh. This is vexing.
This time we will catch that Bonge-Bonge.
Bonge-
Bonge?
What is that?
It's that huge creature we saw just now, right?
I'll get my revenge for Zazie!
Come on...
Oh! That's absolutely right, aru!
As expected of Ojou-sama!
But, speaking of revenge...
Zazie came out unharmed after all.
Unharmed... Unharmed...
It's probably better if you don't think of a joke for this.
But, I think we should talk about how we want to deal with Nekane-san.
Yeah. That's right.
Then, let's go check up on her, de gozaru.
Now, what kind of mission...
Eh? Hey where's everyone going?
What about the Bonge-Bonge!
Hey! The Bonge-Bonge!
What happened?
I'm not telling.
Nekane-san was first seen here, right?
Yeah. She was in the bath.
All the way from Wales?
That's the story. But...
About her getting transported here,
and then being put into the bath isn't natural at all.
Not natural.
But, that's her character.
Character.
Zazie, slump?
Well, slumping is like this.
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
Okay.
Ahh, it's warm...
I found an eraser!
She used magic!?
What in the world...
Again...
What is it this time?
Nekane Springfield: 10 Points! Or so.
Please, buy Chupa-Tees.
How carefree...
Eh? Oneechan is acting strange?
What do you mean by "strange"?
Strange means what strange means, aru!
Not that "strange", de gozaru.
Oh, am I mistaken, aru?
What you said was strange!
Japanese is hard, aru!
What, did Oneechan do something strange?
Well, come to think of it...
She hasn't done anything out of the ordinary, de gozaru.
She just quietly erased a piece of the darkness when Negi-bouzu wasn't aware, aru.
Kuu-chan! Shhhhhhhh!
Ah! I acted rudely again, aru!
Darkness?
Well, we can't do anything now that the cat's out of the bag, de gozaru.
Actually...
Negi-sensei shouldn't worry about it.
About the fact that we planned to keep the thing about the darkness a secret.
Ah, that was careless, aru!
That was too careless!!
So, that's the case.
Thanks for letting me know.
But, it's all right.
She kept quiet about the darkness to keep me from being worried, right?
Oh. I see.
It's true that her sudden actions may seem strange,
from my point of view, she's always been like that.
Her speech, her smile, her smell...
So it's like that, huh, de gozaru?
Then we wouldn't have to worry, aru!
Yes!
Thank you!
I apologize for what happened before.
This is not much, but
What's inside?
A tasty piece of pastry.
I don't want it.
Since I'm on a diet!
Diet!?
Yep!
Diet!?!
My daughter!
I hate you!!
Uh, was that bad?
Yes. It was bad, nya.
Huh!? Don't tell me I failed!
No, it's not that serious, nyan nya.
Thank goodness... Then that's okay.
Ah! It's Makie!
Ah! Going back to Library Island?
Makie-san!
So, you're the missing person!
Eh!? I was just doing some gymnastics practice...
What gymnastics!?
Everyone is busy doing work...
You are a failure!
Huh, failure!?
YES. A FAILURE!
You, Sasaki Makie, fail at life!
I feel sincerely sorry for you!
Wha... she is peeking.
That's the smell of shampoo!
What's she looking at?
Oh? Ah! Yeah, that's right!
Kono-chan's smell...
What's up, Secchan?
Uh? Err, nothing, Ojou-sama!
Then, that's fine.
It's nothing!
You only have to say it once, I'll understand...
Nothing...
Don't tell me...!
Satsuki-chan is....!!
You have finally revealed yourself, haven't you!?
Satsuki-chan! Behind you!
Gotcha!~
Setsuna-san! What happened?
Are you okay?
Ah, yes... I'm alright.
She was after the food, huh?
Running in here is dangerous.
Yes. I'm sorry.
This is wonderful!
Thank you!
What dish is this?
Oden for packed lunches.
It's so delicious!
Even though she jumped out when she appeared,
it might just be a good thing for Negi-kun.
Being found when she's in the bath.
Sounds like nonsense to me.
That's true...
Have you seen Chachamaru-kun today?
Nope. I haven't.
Here you go.
Thank you for your tea.
What the hell is this!?
It's salty!!
Good. Something heart-breaking has happened.
Then, this salty taste is...
Your tears?
Yes! In a good way!
Do not cry!
Please... Press harder...
How is it, Chizuru?
Does it feel good?
Yeah... It feels so good I could fall asleep.
Thats so nice, can you do that for me later too?
Oh! Ako! I'll do it for you!
Really?
I'm really stiff!
No problemo!
Chao's massages can rival Heaven!
Ow!
I'm sorry, Chizuru.
It's the darkness!
This is bad! I'm calling Negi-bouzu!
Me too!
What did you say!?
Alright! I understand!
I'm coming right away!
Ah! It's a message!
It's a long story. I will give you details when we meet. Chizuru
What the....?
Ah! Negi-kun.
Something's happening.
Let's go, Secchan!
Yes!
Nekane-san?
Ojou-sama. Quickly!
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Help me!!
Ako!
Try your best!
Ako-san!
Okay... With my magic...
Someone, please lend me your power!
Leave it to me, aru!
Partner: Kuu Fei!
Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
I think it got you, aru!
It's a Suka Card!
Dammit!
Ayya!! But I will not be crushed! Torara!
Don't do it! It's impossible!
Let go! I can't move, aru!
This is getting troublesome!!
Ako-san!!
The lands with green wind and...
Screw the introduction!
I am the Black Rose Baron!
That Oden!
That means the Baron is......
Wind!
Now! Negi-kun!
Y-Yes!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Yeah! We did it!!
Negi-kun...
Yes?
I have something to tell you.
Actually...
The Baron is really...
Nekane-san.
T-The Baron is... Oneechan?
Y-You're kidding...
You're kidding right?
Suddenly and precipitately!?
Negi is suddenly faced with a surprising new fact!
Nekane is the Baron!
Why did she need such a disguise?
Why did she need to hide herself?
Pay close attention and wait for the next episode!!
Meanwhile...
Stop it already! I can't stand it!
We need to supply more Chupa-Tees!!
Wait for a while.
Next time, "I'm really irritated by stupid people who love to expose peoples' secrets!"
By Chisame.
"Chiu Chiu is also angry! Puun pu~n!!"
By Chiu!
God, I have a wish.
Oh! Really, really?
By the way, who are you?
Oh... That's enough already....