THE POWER OF ANIMATION
What? A massive Roman Army
contingent has appeared
at the Seize-No Man's Land border?
Aisha!
What was that gunshot?
We've secured a Roman soldier!
Are they dead?
No, still breathing.
Well done!
We will now rendezvous with the
1st and 3rd divisions on the border-
What are you doing-
Don't move!
Move and I'll shoot.
Captain!
Colonel, please escort your
men outside the fortress.
Fill the Blue Sky
What's going on?
Betrayal!
The girls took our commander hostage
and barricaded themselves in the fort!
What?
Fortunately, it missed her internal organs.
Then, for the moment, she should be OK.
Thank you, Yumina.
Well done.
She'll be a sacrifice to start the war.
She'd be worth less to us dead.
What is going on here?
For the last month, we've followed the
approaching Roman army from the rear.
It's probably nothing more than a display of power
to give them an advantage in the peace talks.
They must think we're fools.
But the Archduke insisted we do nothing.
So we needed something to
push them to attack us.
Like a sobbing POW executed
right in front of them.
You can't intend to-
The peace talks are a farce!
Rome must be destroyed!
Isn't that right, Noël Kannagi?
No, my dear ally, the witch of Helvetia.
You thought I wouldn't notice?
Stop!
You just used her!
Noël, you have something to do
with the Invisible Reaper?
Invisible Reaper?
That girl there was one of the greatest
geniuses in academic history,
the one who revived the Invisible Reaper,
an old-era bioweapons plant.
Your talent is still valuable.
Come back to me.
Kureha, toss him in the
underground distillery.
My comrades are already deploying
to fight the Romans.
One small spark is all that's needed.
Back to the battlefield, huh?
I thought it was finally over...
We've both got crap for luck.
I've locked the Colonel inside the distillery.
Thank you, Kureha.
Have something to eat...
Some cookies I got at Treize!
They're good.
Naomi, you're still here?
I'll leave if it gets dangerous.
This is really messed up!
The Flame Maidens are supposed
to protect the city.
We're getting them involved in battle!
Um, about that...
When I was hiding, I asked Aisha about
the legend of the Flame Maidens.
And she said that the Romans tell
a totally different legend...
What kind?
The Flame Maidens protect others' lives.
Wh-What?
It's time to switch.
I'm OK!
I don't trust you out here.
For starters, can you even
fire a gun at anyone?
If I think it's the right thing
to do, I might be able to.
Really?
I'm a fortress maiden, too!
Like our forerunners, the Flame Maidens...
What?
You believe that arbitrary
Roman fairy tale?
Yes.
It feels right to me.
The Flame Maidens protect others' lives.
I think that just might be the case.
What's wrong?
I can hear it...
Hear what?
Kanata!
I don't care how good her ears are,
she can't hear you from here.
A signal to stop fighting?
Yes! I heard it!
Really?
I'm sure!
It's too early to be happy about it.
She might have imagined it,
and even if not,
we don't know it means the
peace talks are over.
Anyway, we need to tell Colonel Hopkins-
Big trouble!
I went to take food to the
Colonel, and he was gone!
I'm glad you're safe!
We strike in ten minutes.
Colonel!
Do you really think they'll listen?
It's worth a try.
Roger.
It's useless.
The Colonel was laughing...
When he saw my Reaper
kill all those people,
he was laughing so hard...
He'll kill... He'll fight until no one is left.
But I helped him.
It's my fault.
If you think that, then save more
lives than you've taken, Noël.
Aisha...
Cease-fire?
Impossible!
But her ears are that good!
That's right!
We'll vouch for her!
She's a tiny kid, and she forgets stuff,
and isn't sexy at all!
She wouldn't lie!
Arrest everyone here!
Do you want war that much?
War advances civilization and science.
I want to bring back the glory
humanity once had.
What?
The Romans are going to attack
tomorrow morning!
Then, there's no way to stop the war.
Naomi was arrested.
Let's go.
It's impossible!
It's the Demon of Vingt!
But I want to deliver the
sound I've been given!
That's just selfish!
It's selfish!
How can you make that decision yourself?
We're soldiers!
Someone was saying the world is ending.
But I like this world.
I like this town.
I love the people here.
I can't give up.
Kanata...
Please.
Stop the war.
Aisha was saying the same thing.
But I...
As a soldier, I have killed people, too.
I'm just like you.
I'm...just like...you.
You have suffered enough.
So even if no one else forgives you, I will.
So even if...
You forgive me?
Thank you, Aisha.
If we do this, there'll be no turning back.
You're OK with that, right?
Yeah.
Then I've got nothing else to say.
Do what you want.
Thank you, Kureha.
For our sakes, you've always said
what you thought was best, right?
But I...
I don't want a girl my age
to be tortured, either!
But Rio's gone...
And Noël and Kanata are such slackers...
So I thought I had to work harder...
I'm sorry I'm such a bad captain.
Kureha.
Let's go, everyone.
May all of the Gods grant their
blessings to the Flame Maidens.
Primary converter reactor output rising.
FAP, FAC, DMR, ECP all normal.
Superconductor circuit functioning
within stable parameters.
Fire control system's looking good.
Primary and secondary cannons are online!
Release all joint locks!
W-Weight reduction system online.
Coefficient is around five.
Ready to go.
If we just do it like in training, we'll be fine.
Let's go, my girls!
Right!
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Load AP round!
AP round loaded!
Target locked!
Kana, the signal!
Right!
"Begin the attack"?
Fire!
It's Kanata!
The Takemikazuchi...
They've restored so much of that
ancient high technology.
Contact all tanks!
Do everything you can to stop them!
Begin the attack!
We won't let you through!
We don't want any more war!
Don't stop them!
You'll have to take us out first!
That's right!
Now, what will you do?
Demon of Vingt.
Circle around!
We'll meet up with the forces to our rear!
The Flame Maidens protect others' lives.
The rest is in your hands, Kanata.
Many years ago,
before the world became as it is now,
God sent an angel to punish the world.
The angel was wounded, and set his wings
down to rest, at a western-end town.
It was the maidens, who lived in the
city's fortress, that saved him.
He was sent to destroy them,
but they took pity on his wounds
Gaining the help of a giant spider,
they gave the angel refuge at the bottom of the valley.
Each, in turn, embraced the angel's neck,
to keep the blood from pouring out.
In return, he gave them a golden horn.
But eventually, the townspeople found
him there. They set fire to the valley.
Burning the maidens, and
taking the angel's head.
The legend says that then armies
of angels appeared, covering the sky.
But then a miracle occurred.
A glorious sound filled the air,
and the angels left.
The last maiden had used her last breath
to sound the golden horn.
Hey, you remember that girl?
The one you gave the caramel to?
She'll be caught up in this, too, won't she?
All troops, prepare to charge!
Nothing to do about it.
We're soldiers.
Charge!
What?
What's that?
It's an allied tank!
It's with...
The 1121 Platoon!
It's the cease-fire signal!
No...
It's a Roman military signal!
Commander!
We can't stop here!
Ready the main cannon!
No... They won't stop.
Captain!
Kana!
That girl...
What are you doing?
Attack!
Fire! Fire!
Both sides, lay down your weapons!
I am second heir to the royal line of Helvetia
and fiancée to the Holy Roman Emperor.
Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
I command you by the names of my father,
the Archduke of Helvetia, and of the Roman Emperor!
The peace talks have ended.
There is to be no more fighting!
Both sides are to disband immediately!
This is a royal order!
Those who disobey will be punished by
the first Helvetia Royal Guard,
in both leaders' names!
Impossible...
Then...
We don't have to fight!
Miss!
Sergeant!
Spring sure has sprung.
Hey, Noël,
that letter Aisha sent you...
What did it say?
My wounds are healed, and I'm practicing
the trumpet every day.
Translate it!
She's doing well and practicing her trumpet.
Yeah? Great!
Man, we get letters from Rome
but not from the capitol.
I'm sure she's busy.
She's a princess now.
But even on the battlefield,
she was surrounded by guards,
and we couldn't talk to her.
I hear Claus' bike!
She's here! She's here!
I can't tell you how much I've been
looking forward to the new girl!
I'm going to be really hard-
I am Lt. Rio Kazumiya Arkadia. I have been transferred
to the 1121 Platoon as of today.
Captain Filicia Heidemann, please
give me permission to arrive.
Very well.
We don't use ranks here, Rio.
Um, well...
The Roman Emperor is actually a decent guy.
He said he'd grant any wish I had,
as a reward for stopping the war.
And so...
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Rio.