While I appreciate the rare occasion that you actually make lunch for me, Sis...
why ethnic?
Oreki-san!
Thanks for watching the desk!
Sure.
We won!
That was a close call, though.
Congratulations.
Thank you!
We only managed it with your help.
Uh...
Sure...
That gave me a shock.
I didn't think you'd ever do something like that even if you were the last man on earth.
I was just carried away by the festival mood.
It won't happen again.
On a different note, Oreki-san,
there's something I'd like you to look at.
This.
Juumonji
The Cooking Society's ladle has been lost.
Mazui Presents
Every day is set in stone, and we
fukuzatsu ni kamaeta kyou ga
iki wo nonde sumashiteru
Just hold our breath and live it through
mi ni oboe arun darou
I'm sure you know what I mean
kimi wa dou shitai
What do you really want to do?
nani mo nakatta soburi de
Pretending like nothing happened to you
kabau itami wa mou
The pain inside just builds up
kokorodzuyoi kurai ni
It makes me feel all the more sure
sekasunda
And urges me to go on
tsukande koboshite
Catching on, falling through
fukanzen na bokutachi ga
We've yet to learn who we are
hikatte mienai
It's so bright, we can't see
mirai no jibun wo tsukureru nara
If we can decide the kind of person that we want to be
mezameru no ma hashire
When you wake up, just start running
shinkirou wo oikoshite
Breaking through all the illusions there
kawaritai no ma hashire
When you want to change, just start running
jiyuu na wan kamu dei
Your freedom will come one day
todokisou na kagayaki to ima wo erandeikou
I hope you choose this moment and the light that lies before you
toutatsuten wo shiranai fukai sai
We don't know where we might go, so after the sigh,
kokyuu wo kasanete
Just take another breath
The Juumonji Incident
Your ladle got stolen?
Yeah, just our station's.
I guess someone's really bored.
And it's not just the Cooking Society.
The Go Club and the A Capella Club also had something similar happen.
The Fortune Telling Society, too!
The thief left a note...
and its contents were the s—
I guess that means someone is really bored.
I must say, the fragrance of this spice is—
Oreki-san.
Crap.
This is bad.
It's happening again.
Chitanda Eru's curiosity is getting fired up...
Who would interfere with the festival like this?
Why are they signing it with Juumonji-san's name?
Why are they stealing one thing after another?
I'm curiou—
We don't have time for that.
These anthologies—
About those anthologies...
I don't think it'll be enough to simply advertise in events.
That's true...
We really need to do something more flashy.
Exactly what I was thinking.
How about we use this mystery to promote our anthology?
We could announce it during tomorrow's school-wide radio broadcast.
If we could do that, we'd be able to sell all these!
I see...
That's a good idea!
What do you mean by "promote"?
We have nothing to do with this problem.
Like this:
The Classics Club's famed detective Oreki Houtarou catches the culprit,
the mind behind the mysteries hounding the cultural festival, Juumonji!
Read about the rest of his exploits in the Classic Club's anthology, "Hyouka"!
That's a wonderful idea!
Not bad at all.
Right?
If we can find out who Juumonji is and reveal the mystery to the whole—
Not a chance!
What's do you mean "famed detective"?
I am not going to be some crowd-drawing panda!
Let's give it a try, Oreki-san!
Let's say I did play the clown.
There are 1000 students and countless visitors here.
We'd never be able to find the thief.
Is it too hard?
It's impossible.
If only that thief would target the Classics Club...
I guess...
Then how about we make it up—
No!
I'm kidding! I'm kidding!
Target, huh...
Which clubs have been targeted so far?
The Go Club, A Capella Club, Cooking Society, and...
What was it again?
The Fortune Telling Society!
Right, that!
A Capella Club, Go Club, Fortune Telling Society...
Cooking Society...
A.B.C.!
Hello? Suzuki-kun?
The clubs starting with "E" in Japanese are...
The Movie Society, Gardening Club, Drama Club, SF Society.
What is this all about?
It's a pattern,
and a really simple one, at that.
o
u
i
a
A Capella Club.
Go Club.
Fortune Telling Society.
Skip one character, then Cooking Society.
e
There's no doubt that "E" will also appear.
The gojuuon!
Note: Japanese hiragana alphabet
Exactly.
They hit the Gardening Club.
While they were gone for a short time, someone stole their water gun.
Water gun?
They were going to use it for their sweet potato roast.
One of their members came here yesterday holding it.
Wait a second.
In Christie's "The A.B.C. Murders",
someone with a name starting with "A" was killed in town also starting with "A", right?
So, the Cooking Society had a ladle stolen...
Wait a second.
Chitanda-san, did you hear what got stolen from the Fortune Telling Society?
Yes, it was the Wheel of Fortune.
A tarot card.
Okay.
Which gives us...
A Capella Club
Cooking Society
Gardening Club
Fortune Telling
Society
Go Club
(Drink)
(Go stone)
(Water gun)
(Ladle)
(Wheel
of Fortune)
The Gardening Club's water gun was an AK, wasn't it?
AK? What's that?
A Russian assault rifle.
A Capella Club
Cooking Society
Gardening Club
Fortune Telling
Society
Go Club
(Drink)
(Go stone)
(Water gun)
(Ladle)
(Wheel
of Fortune)
If we go by that pattern,
then the go stones could just be called stones, right?
Probably.
Then the A Capella Club...
It doesn't matter.
We'll know as soon as we check.
Why?
What's the signature on the letter?
Juumonji?
Why do you read it like a name?
If you read it normally, it just says "ten letters".
"Ten letters"!
I see!
The ten letters a, i, u, e, o, ka, ki, ku, ke, ko...
So the last in that sequence would point to...
The Classics Club!
With this, I think we're involved enough to promote ourselves, right?
I'll go talk to the Wall Newspaper Club right now!
She seems excited.
What's wrong?
I just thought of something.
This incident...
No, never mind.
I'll go investigate some more.
What's up with him?
Who knows.
Aren't you going back to the Manga Society?
I will.
What?
You don't like me being here?
Why are you angry?
I'm not angry!
How to negotiate...
First, make them feel like you have expectations of them.
Second, give them the impression that it's not that important to you.
Third, ask someone of the opposite sex in private.
Alright!
Okay! I'll go interview the Gardening Club!
Hey!
What about A Capella?
I'm on the phone with them!
Hurry with the Cooking Society!
Yeah, I said that! Now get to work!
Excuse me...
Shut up and get me that story!
Sorry Chitanda-san, we're kind of busy right now.
Could you come back later?
Of course! Later th—
Wait, no!
This is about the Classics Club!
Unless you have some special scoop, I can't—
I do!
What do you mean?
I don't have a lot of time here.
Could you make it quick—
Wait...
Where are we going?
The Wall Newspaper Club is the only place I can turn for this.
Basically, I mean...
I...
I have expectations of you!
I... I see.
Thanks...
But there isn't much for me to gain from it.
Really...
Well?
Don't you feel like giving this your all now?
I don't really get what you mean...
I thought so.
I told you, we're really busy.
We can talk later if you don't have a scoop.
Please wait!
It is a scoop!
Someone is going around stealing things from clubs!
The culprit is...
Juumonji!
You're talking about Juumonji, right?!
Do you know something?
Um... well...
I see.
The gojuuon...
I hadn't heard about the Fortune Telling Society's one.
So that's why.
What do you mean?
We're the Wall Newspaper Club, right?
So you're saying...
We had a utility knife stolen.
So you're busy right now because of this incident?
Yeah.
It sucks that we were hit, but we wanted a story like this.
Good job figuring that out, though.
Yes, it was Oreki-san.
Oh. I see.
Thanks for the info.
It'll help.
Wait, Tougaito-san!
I've given you this info,
so you'll write about the Classics Club in return.
Right?
Please!
Insisting like that would mean I didn't trust Tougaito-san to write about us.
Sorry!
Chitanda-san!
How was it?
Did they agree?
Well...
I wonder...
Never mind, I'm just talking to myself.
Oh?
Anyway, I talked to the A Capella Club.
They had an apple juice stolen.
I asked the Wall Newspaper Club, and they said they had a utility knife taken.
Which begins with "ka".
So it all fits.
The only club beginning with "ki" is the Magic Club.
Their next performance is coming up soon.
If I go to watch it...
You might catch the culprit in the act?
Right.
That's their weakness.
They're tied down by their own rule.
It shouldn't be hard to find out who the one behind this is.
But if we uncover it at "ki"...
Then they'll never be able to reach the Classics Club at "ko", right?
There are plenty of ways to deal with that.
I suppose...
Either way, I'll try catching them at the Magic Club.
I hope I'm not too late.
See you!
Shuubun
When the light and dark are in balance
Hyouka
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Showing 2           Showing 6
Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Program
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Showing 1           Showing 5
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Curtains Rise
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Close-up Card Magic - First-years Takamura Youichi
and Nagai Kou
Curtains Fall
Curtains Rise
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Bowl and Ball - Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Curtains Fall
Apparition
- Second-year Tayama Kazuya
Program
Showing 1           Showing 5
Living Dead
- First-year Takamura Youichi
Rainbow Link
- First-year Nagai Kou
Only 2 pm?
Well, if it isn't Fukube!
Hey, Tani-kun.
If you're here, then you must know.
Know what?
Don't play dumb!
The thief, Juumoji!
Well, yeah.
I guess this'll be our next contest!
Hear about the Wall Newspaper Club?
A utility knife, right?
I know.
Yeah.
The Wall Newspaper guys are in the game now.
Next issue's headline is about Juumoji.
And whoever catches the thief gets a whole extra to themselves!
Well, sorry, but this one's mine.
I might not look the type,
but I'm a big mystery fan!
Go easy on me.
Geography Prep Room
Hey, Ibara.
You've read Christie's The A.B.C. Murders, right?
Of course.
Could you tell me what the reasoning was behind killing people in that order?
Are you okay with spoilers?
Sure.
Do you think it would be a good story if it was just "Because I wanted to kill by A.B.C.'s"?
You think this case is the same?
Yeah.
Stealing in gojuuon order was something anyone could figure out.
Juumoji should have expected that.
That makes sense.
I was thinking about other connections or meanings behind the thefts.
Assuming that the culprit isn't just a nutcase.
Oreki, do you want to catch Juumoji?
Me?
Why?
You're getting into it.
I don't care.
But now that Chitanda's gotten curious, I can't avoid it.
You could just ignore her.
The problem is that she's not someone I can ignore.
What an idiot.
Okay then.
You're going?
Oh, and thanks for the flour.
You saved us.
Oh.
Right, right.
You want me to pay for it?
You make me sound evil.
I traded that flour, "Straw Millionaire" style!
What?
So give me something in return.
If you don't want to, that'll be the end of the line, but whatever.
I see.
Then...
You can have this.
You sure?
Yes.
But without that, you can't cosplay as—
Don't call it "cosplay", you idiot!
The Magic Club's fifth showing will begin shortly!
Irisu-senpai!
Good afternoon!
Oh, it's you.
Do you like magic tricks?
I don't know enough to say I like them.
Is that weird?
No.
Just unexpected.
Maybe...
No way.
You didn't need to say it like that.
Mayaka's senpai?
I saw them at the Manga Society yesterday.
It looks like fun!
Hey, look!
Wow, it's Tanabe-senpai and His Highness the Student Council President Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Hi there, Miss Empress.
Hello.
Hi.
Oh, Fukube!
Hello!
Welcome, everyone!
The Magic Club's Magic Show will now begin!
Thank you all very much for coming!
We hope you enjoy the performance the Magic Club has prepared just for you!
Now then.
How will you steal something...
with all these people watching?
Mystery thief, Juumoji.
We shall begin with Takamura Youichi's act, Living Dead.
What's wrong?
Well...
The candle!
Sorry!
Damn!
When?
Wait, before that, no one came close to the stage other than the performers.
Which means it was already gone?
Why did I even come here?
Come to think of it, there wasn't any reason to think Juumoji would strike during the show!
Thank you very much!
They're selling better than yesterday.
Yeah! Those posters might be working.
That's good.
She should have just done what Senpai told her.
Yeah.
We would have sold more yesterday if someone didn't object to everything.
Now, now.
Don't make me feel sorry for her.
Don't pay attention to them.
Yeah...
And seriously? She couldn't find it?
She's totally lying.
She probably got too scared to show us some crappy manga.
She just named some obscure doujin to get us off her case.
Yeah, yeah!
No way there's a manga like that!
Hey—
Stop it, that's enough.
If you've never heard of it, keep quiet.
We're back.
But Senpai...
Didn't you hear me?
If you've never heard of it, shut up.
So President, how was the magic show?
It was fun.
Maybe I should go check it out tomorrow.
I think you should.
When's the showing?
They put it on a few times every day, so you can choose the one you want.
Really?
Then—
Sorry, I'm going out for a bit.
Okay!
Fuku—
This is just sad.
I'm running away to Fuku-chan.
Ibara?
Yes?
Yuasa-senpai?
Sorry things got all weird like this.
Why are you apologizing?
I've just been staying quiet all this time, but I do want to help you out.
But then things will get bad between you and Kouchi-senpai...
I don't want that.
It's better like this.
Ayako isn't being serious.
Ayako?
Kouchi. Kouchi Ayako.
How do you know she isn't being serious?
Because Ayako and I are friends.
Just from that?
Ayako and Haruna were friends too.
Haruna? Who's that?
Anjou Haruna.
One of the authors of A Corpse by Evening.
It was a collaboration?
Someone else did the art.
Ayako might know who.
What class is that person in?
Haruna isn't here anymore.
She transferred.
I see...
But can you say Kouchi-senpai isn't being serious just from them being friends?
That's true. Sorry...
But I can't tell you any more.
After all, Ayako is also my friend.
Do you mean there's something regarding Kouchi-senpai that you'd rather not say?
I'll go back after I get some air.
Ibara...
I'll be back soon.
Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!
Mystery Thief Juumoji's Nefarious Deeds
But, ah, the gall of this scoundrel! We at the Wall Newspaper Club
have had a utility knife stolen from right under our noses!
This is a blatant challenge on the honor of a media outlet!
We have thus deduced, loyal readers, that this "Juumoji" will commit his final act on the third day,
between the hours of noon and 2pm, striking either the Classics Club or the Crafts Club.
Classics Club
Tougaito-san!
They beat me, Houtarou.
They stole a candle from the Magic Club.
We found a note, too.
That's good.
We don't want to catch them until they come to the Classics Club.
Well, yeah, but...
I thought that I could catch them in the act.
You thought the crime would happen during the show?
Yeah.
Juumoji never said anything about when it would be done.
It was the same with the Cooking Society.
Why didn't you tell me if you realized that?
I didn't know you going to try and catch them.
Well, I guess...
I'm back!
It looks like the 20 copies I left with Irisu-san are selling very well.
Well, this is Irisu we're talking about, after all.
And one other thing.
The Wall Newspaper's afternoon extra was on the Juumoji Incident.
The information about going in gojuuon order is on there as well.
The Classics Club's name was on there too.
The last crime will either be the Classics Club or the Crafts Club.
Crafts Club?
We had one of those?
Yeah, we did.
If they strike there, our plans are all shot.
I was thinking of going to the Broadcasting Club tomorrow.
If they could advertise for the Classics Club as well...
What is it?
Well...
You just look kind of tire—
I'm back.
Hey, Mayaka.
How many did we sell today?
Excluding the 20 we gave to Irisu, 16 copies.
Great accomplishment!
Great accomplishment?
Maybe.
Going around and asking favors is my job...
But it's so tiring...
Body Talk.
It's a level below A Corpse by Evening, but...
It's a good manga too.
Mine's a hundred levels below it!
Houtarou's changed.
Or rather, he's changing.
Thanks to Chitanda-san.
He's becoming someone who can show us the kind of endless possibilities that I yearn for.
Do I really only think that it's a good thing?
The suspects number over a thousand.
To deduce the culprit from amongst them all isn't humanly possible.
Thus, the only way to catch them is to catch them in the act.
This case isn't up Houtarou's alley,
so I'll solve it myself.
Houtarou...
I'm going to catch Juumoji.
Buy Online
Oh? They're selling stuff online, too?
Next time: The Last Target.
The Last Target