When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Mister Ayasaki, I would like to give
you this gift of 150 million yen.
What?
Who is this mysterious man?!
To be continued in the tense
final episode next week!
Hey, we just got started here!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Spring
We now go back several hours from
when the opening scene happened.
And now, all of you, rise!
Listen well!
Once again next year,
you will turn S Ward of Tokyo an ever
more shockingly brilliant white!
Okay, now let's all sing
the school anthem together!
Yeah!
The white school reigning
over the land of Suginami
This year has felt both
long and short somehow.
But I'm really glad I passed the year.
Our mother school
That's right. Studying
for the exams paid off
and Hayate had more or
less passed the finals.
Fire up that engine in your heart
World History Answer Sheet
Hayate Ayasaki
More or Less Pass
Butlers shall pass or
they are bound for Hell!!
Darn! Too bad.
Tama, you may go.
Um, Head Butler, enough with the bad jokes...
I will remind you again, Ayasaki.
The monetary amount you have managed
to repay the Miss in this past year
is still a paltry sum.
If you were to fail out of school,
you would once again find yourself out in
the cold with your debt of 150 million.
Be sure to keep that squarely in mind.
Yes, Head Butler, sir!
Hakuou! Hakuou!
All right! I'll keep this up
and do my best again next year!
We're leaving, Hayate.
Update blogs daily
What?
Hey, please wait, Miss!
Hakuou Academy!
Yes, we nailed it.
Well, frankly, it's a pain. But my
friends, we will meet again in April.
The closing ceremony is now over!
Come on, Hayate! Hurry, hurry!
Keep dawdling and I'll leave you behind!
Um, what are you in such a hurry for?
We could bask in the aftermath
a little longer...
Not really interested.
I want to hurry back to the residence
and play the continuation of
"Monster Hunter Portable 2nd G"!
Huh?
That's really all there is to it!
Oh, please wait for me, Miss!
I've got Hayate all confused!
But I'm just getting
started! My turn yet again!
What? Something important
the Miss had ordered?
Yes. Might I ask you to
go get it from the store?
Under no circumstances are
you to look at what it is!
As you wish! Then I shall go right away!
Don't be in such a hurry!
T-Take some side trips
and kill plenty of time.
Specifically, wait until about early evening.
Huh? Why?
Wh-Why? Because...
I-I just suddenly don't want
to see your face anymore!
Don't make me say any more than that!
I understand.
Then I shall take my time and return
to the residence around early evening.
N-Nagi!
L-Looks like we managed to
gloss over that somehow.
Hayate will surely never even dream
that he's being sent to pick
up something like that!
Nagi, don't you think that was a bit cruel?
That's right!
That butler-in-debt was awfully depressed!
D-Don't look at me like that!
Come on, everyone! Let's hurry
up and start getting ready!
And so, Nagi's trap was quietly laid.
Meanwhile, at Hakuou Academy...
Yukiji's loud snoring
could be heard, as usual.
What? No way! For real?!
You want to pay 50 billion yen transfer
fee for me instead of Matsui?
And Mr. Kaoru, whom we hadn't
seen at all since Episode 18,
was making Gundam models, the same as ever.
Is this a Guntank?
And furthermore, 10,000
meters up in the air...
Mistress Kuzuha, it seems we will
be arriving at our destination
by lunch tomorrow, as planned.
Good. I must obtain the
rumored object at all costs.
But what in the world is this legendary item?
A mask made by an ancient conjurer.
They say that if you wear it, a
mysterious power makes you grow taller.
What?
Your smaller form is fine in its own way.
But I would love to see your
gallant form once again as well.
Mistress Kuzuha!
Sion.
Africa, huh?
But I hope she makes it back
safely by the new term.
Do you really mean that, Chiharu?
You shouldn't say things like that.
Even with the kind of person she is,
the school still needs her talents.
How specifically?
In what way?
Huh?
Come on, let's go have tea somewhere.
If you'd like, I'll treat you to some cake.
With pleasure.
Then, shall we three go for a quiet
gathering to reward our hard work?
Come to think of it, I
didn't get to see Hayate.
It seemed like he made it
safely to the next year,
so I would've liked to
properly congratulate him.
I wonder what this is.
Considering the Miss's demeanor...
I wonder if I messed up again somewhere.
W-Wait, what are you doing?!
Let me go!
Welcome, Mister Ayasaki.
Forgive the rough treatment.
Who are these people?!
Could they be after the ordered item?!
Huh? "Victoria Elizabeth
Steward Dispatch Company"?
Indeed.
We are the biggest butler dispatch
company in the industry,
making great strides on a global scale.
I have never heard of such a thing!
We have kept an eye on you for some
time through a certain source.
When did you get these?
The videographers were...
A one, two... us!
Did you enjoy it?
Hakuou Academy's Society for the
Research of Video is for all eternity!
So that's it...
Mister Ayasaki, I would like to give
you this gift of 150 million yen.
What?
The story now finally goes
back to the original scene.
I would very much like to
poach you for our company.
This is an advance payment.
Please take it to repay your
debt to the Sanzenin family.
So you've even investigated about that?
No, thank you!
Since I have also promised the
Miss that I will work and repay
that money myself, without fail.
Oh-ho. Are you certain? You may
never get a chance like this again.
If you truly have the
Miss's interests at heart,
should you not take this money to
clear your debt with her immediately?
As for that...
Please contact us whenever you like.
I look forward to a favorable response.
All right! All right!
All right! All right! All right!
What is it, Tama? A little more to the right?
Sheesh. Why do we have to help out, too?
A-Are you all right, Isumi?!
Whoops! I accidentally slipped, too!
Whoa! Hey, Sakuya!
Man, coincidences sure are frightenin'.
Safety First
A warm, youthful spring. To be
continued in the second half.
I'm Nagi!
(Nagi da zoooo!)
Miss, how much is really left of my debt?
(Ojousama, hontou wa ato ikura desuka, boku no shakkin?)
I may never get a chance
like this again, huh?
It's true. To remain forever at the
Sanzenin residence like this is...
It just may be my own selfish desire...
Wait, this is no time to
be thinking about this!
Right now, I need to deliver this
ordered item to the Miss first!
What?!
All right! It's perfect for sure this time!
Oh, my.
This is...
Delicious, right?!
Questionable.
I would have to agree.
It is not delicious, but it is
also not entirely inedible...
What the heck?! Darn it!
And here I am, trying so hard!
But Nagi, why have you undertaken
such an elaborate celebration?
Because this might be the
only time we can do it.
Hey, Maria, get me those Maximum Tomatoes!
They've got the power to get rid
of all exhaustion, after all!
I want to make sure Hayate gets to eat them.
Yes, yes.
Man, I worked hard on my finals, too.
Quit complainin' already.
Ya studied for the exams with
him, so congratulate him.
Say, Sakuya.
Thanks for letting me
have your spot at Hakuou.
I'd been meaning to say this someday.
I-I'll make it up to you, I swear!
Once I become a big shot!
What're ya sayin'?! That's
not like ya at all, ya wuss!
Never ya mind that! Just
accept it and be grateful!
Sheesh, that butler-in-debt sure is late.
Where is he and what's he doin'?
Thanks for the food!
Taiyaki Pastries
There's no filling inside!
Does this count as a kind of win?
If it is, maybe I'll get
to see Hayate or something.
H-Hayate!
Miss Nishizawa!
Oh, could I borrow your bicycle?
What?
I will be sure to return it later.
S-Sure!
All right, I've caught up!
Here goes, Eight!
There!
My dream was a message! I'm
going to become a Major Leaguer!
Young Master, this is it!
This is how you do it!
Yeah, I got it, Nonohara!
Chashu ramen!
The Young Sir won't be home today,
so I'll have a simple dinner...
I appreciate you putting
up with me that one time.
N-Not at all...
Oh, um, this is the 100th unit
in the Master Grade Series.
I was totally expecting it to
be a Guntank or the V or V2,
so I just couldn't get excited
about it until now...
I see.
Saki!
Oh, Hayate.
Pardon me. Did you see a small
box around here somewhere?
Pardon?
Saki?!
What's this?
Oh, Hayata.
Oh, you three! Please
give that box back to me!
So it's his.
Then I guess it won't
contain anything too good.
All right, here goes!
I got it!
Oh, sorry!
What?!
Boohoo.
I finally get to see Hayate, but
I didn't get to talk to him much.
Perfect timing, Miss Nishizawa.
I am returning this to you.
Thank you very much. It helped a lot.
Excuse me now!
Hayate...
We'll meet again, right?
Well, then, I look forward to
working with you again next year.
Yes, a job well done.
If you are that happy about it, you should
let it show on your face, Chiharu.
H-Hayate?! What in the world happened?!
Why did you come falling out of the sky?
H-Hinagiku...
The cake...
Well, I was trying to leap to that
building, but I missed my footing.
My cake... My cake...
It's smooshed flat now...
Well, whatever.
Um, Hayate, congratulations for
making it to the next grade...
Pardon me.
I'm in a bit of a hurry, so
I'll see you in the new term!
My cake...
He should be penalized for that.
We must have him pay us back
next time, plus reparations.
What in the world was that about?!
Wh-What is this?
I haven't faced such an onslaught
of unfortunate events in a while.
It's almost as if I'm being tested somehow...
This is bad. If I remember right,
that's a flock of wild geese.
As I recall, wild geese is the general term
for large waterfowl in the Anatidae family
of the Anseriformes order, but
most of them come in the fall
from Siberia to winter here and in the
spring, they once again return north.
At this rate, the Miss's precious
ordered item is headed for Siberia!
All right! It's all or nothing!
H-Himuro, I can't wait!
I'm going to learn the samba
during spring vacation!
Even now, you are already quite
good at it, Little Master Taiga.
Himuro, that box...
Please return that box to me...
Depending on the situation, I would
have no problem with that, but...
Are you all right with this?
Huh?
This ship is headed for Brazil.
What?!
Nooo!
I just barely escaped being transported
to the other side of the globe.
But I can finally get this to the Miss...
Hold it, Tama!
Come on, follow me!
Hold it!
Now! Do it, Tama!
What?
Congratulations on advancing to the next grade!!
Hayate Ayasaki!!
Th-This is...
Why don't you get yourself
over there, Ayasaki?
Everyone is waiting for you.
Um, what is this...
Yer more dense than I thought.
Well, seeing you this surprised make
the preparation worth it, though.
But why the Arc de Triomphe?
Where did you get the Arc de Triomphe?
Nagi.
Looks like it went well.
Miss!
Maria, bring it out.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh! Th-That's...
Hayate, good work on the finals!
This is just a token of my appreciation.
What?!
In other words, it was all a
surprise event planned by Nagi.
Hurry up and open the damn thing!
Nagi came to us for advice, and
we all picked it out together.
I worked hard on the exams,
too, but I got nothing!
You better be grateful!
Everyone...
I cannot accept such a fine gift!
What?!
I mean, I owe you a debt of 150 million...
On top of which, I have selfishly asked
you to keep me on at the residence.
Don't be such a stranger, Hayate!
M-Miss...
It's true, it'll take approximately 40
more years for you to repay the debt.
I know all that!
That's why I chose that for your present.
Because it's reputed to never
break, even after 100 years.
Miss...
Hayate, I want to be with you forever.
Not just for the 40 years,
but for 100, even 200 years.
Because what binds us together
isn't just money anymore, is it?
Miss!
H-H-Hey, everyone's watching!
But what ya said was way more embarrassin'.
Ugh, for crying out loud!
Is that so? That is really too bad.
Then I shall wish you all the best.
As you heard, he refused our company's offer.
What shall we do?
I suppose he passed, more or less.
If he had responded to the headhunting,
I was planning on driving him
out of that mansion, but...
For now, he's still worthy
of holding onto that thing.
Though, who knows how long that'll last.
What do you think of that stew, Hayate?
Uh, um, I suppose it is tasty in its own way.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
It's also ordinary in its own way.
Ooh, but it kind of gets
rid of that tired feeling!
Replenished!
I didn't work hard so you
could feel replenished!
What the hell?!
Miss, please get up. It's morning.
Last night was fun, wasn't it, Hayate?
Yes, thank you very much, Miss.
But so, it's spring vacation starting today.
All right, Hayate, let's go
view cherry blossoms today now.
Pardon?
F-For example, how about somewhere like this?
Boating Dating Spots in Tokyo
It's been a while, so I'd like
to try a boat ride or something.
Spring is the season of wavering emotions!
Today, for sure, Hayate and I will move
our relationship into new territory!
Oh, I'm great with boats, you know.
I actually once had a part-time
job working at a boathouse.
Good grief.
Even with a full turn of the seasons,
nothing has changed with these two.
All right, let's go, Hayate!
Now that's decided, time
to get the bicycle ready!
Yes, Miss!
Can't show you!
See you later.
Then here we go, Miss.
Yes, I am counting on you, Hayate.
And so, there is still
much more to their story.
Next time, they will battle the Aegean Sea.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
Final Episode
Lettering by
Ryoko Shiraishi
Rie Kugimiya
...Butler Report, Final Episode!
Good day, I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
And so, this is the final
episode of the Butler Report.
A lot has happened along the way.
But you've certainly grown to
become a fine butler, Hayate.
Thank you very much, Miss.
I think you have grown as well.
D-Don't say stupid things like
that! You have a dirty mind!
What is the matter?
This is what you get for
saying things like that!
Hayate as a maid to close things out!
For the bonus segment of
the next anime series,
we've got to go with Hayate's Maid Report!
So, see you again someday!
Preview
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
final episode, "Radical Dreamers".
Hayate, I'll be counting
on you in the future, too.
Yes, I look forward to it!