I must kill or be killed!
Are you awake yet?
There's no need to be scared.
I won't attack you anymore.
You're...
I have no name.
But if you must, call me Ein.
That's what they always call me.
Ein...
Why did you attack me?
To have you prove your skills.
My skills?
You were born with certain instincts.
An instinct for killing,
and an instinct for surviving.
Both are instincts that define an assassin.
No way!
I don't understand!
Besides, what proof do you have?
You tried to kill me, didn't you?
In that situation,
a normal person would have panicked and gotten killed as a result.
But you were different.
You chose to act before assessing the situation, and managed to survive.
Zwei.
"Zwei"?
That's your name.
No, it's not. Quit calling me by weird names!
I have a real name, and it's-
My...
...name is...
You don't have one anymore.
It's useless to even try to remember it.
What do you mean?
Your memories have been erased.
By Inferno.
Marvelous.
The victim was a well-known crime lord.
Your Phantom is superb, Scythe Master.
It is presumed that he was dragged into a gang fight.
I'm honored, Mr McGuire.
I can't believe a kid was able to pull this off.
Exactly.
Precisely the reason why I've given her the title of "Phantom".
You've made quite an accomplishment.
You've created a ghost that is truly out of this world.
Well, it's all thanks to Ms McCunnen's support.
Looks like you've got some capable people working for you, Claudia.
But I heard you took your time in eliminating that journalist.
I beg to differ.
Also, you allowed tourists to witness the murder.
I have no idea where you heard that from,
but all witnesses have been taken care of.
Their bodies have been disposed of, as well.
Oh?
Excellent.
Did Phantom take care of that, too?
Yes.
You were supposed to be killed.
So that all evidence relating to the incident would be erased.
But Master noticed your talents,
and decided it'd be a waste to let you die.
Master?
Scythe Master.
My master.
Master then erased your memories,
and prepared a new life for you.
A life as a member of Inferno.
A life as an assassin.
An assassin?
Me?
You will become Zwei, my alter ego.
Don't be ridiculous!
Why in the world would I-
I couldn't possibly kill a-
Sure, you can refuse.
But when you do...
...you will die as originally planned.
Right now, right here.
You will change if you want to live.
Only by killing, will you be allowed to exist.
I...
...don't want to die.
This is a dream.
All of this is just a nightmare.
If that'll make you feel better, then that's fine.
Just pretend that it's all a dream.
But I'll tell you this now. It'll be a long one.
Change into that.
Starting today, you'll be with me day and night.
You will follow every one of my orders.
Understood?
Let's get started.
Zwei's progress is coming along nicely.
He's faithfully participating in the training without complaint.
He's quite obedient.
Even thinking is a chore in the midst of that rigorous training.
Yes.
That's how you break them.
Let me show you something that won't betray your expectations, Ms McCunnen.
You think I was expecting something?
What is mine is yours.
Everything is for the sake of Inferno, after all.
This is how you hold it.
Don't put your finger over the trigger.
Focus all of your power to your fingers instead of your shoulders.
This is the rear sight, and this is the front sight.
Focus your aim through the rear sight into the front sight.
When aiming, stretch out your right arm.
Stabilize the gun by pulling back with your left.
Even then, most of your power should be within your hands and not your arms.
Don't panic when pulling the trigger.
Pull it as if you're squeezing gently.
Shoot.
Fire the remaining five shots in succession.
From this distance, you should be able to hit the mark all six times.
Once you have that down, we'll work on your speed.
Your target is to fire six shots in four seconds.
First, concentrate on hitting the target.
That's still too slow.
Looks like you're able to shoot accurately now,
but at this rate, you'll die before you can shoot your target.
Repeat.
I will continue to fulfill all tasks given to me.
This way, I don't have to think.
This way, I can be at peace.
I'll even forget all the questions I have...
And my daily life will disappear.
I'm heading out.
Carry out the usual training menu.
You're going out?
I've got a job to do.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
He's Scythe Master?
We haven't had a sniping mission in a while, but it shouldn't be a problem for you.
You will be 700 yards away from the target.
We've prepared a Remington .308 for you to use.
The current weather at the location is cloudy with slight winds.
It'll most likely stay that way until tomorrow morning.
The details are inside that envelope.
Any questions?
No.
Very well.
So, how's Zwei coming along?
He's finished the basic regimen.
Tomorrow he'll start with a different training menu.
I guess I should start getting his practical test ready then, hm?
Don't mind me.
As you were.
I guess we've never met before.
I'm Claudia McCunnen.
Don't you have anything else you want to know about me other than my name?
No.
But I'm sure you're interested in learning about Inferno, since they picked you up.
I'll take your silence as a "yes".
Inferno...
...is a group trying to create a new sovereign order in a world without legal order, I guess.
If gangs and mafias could be compared to nations,
then Inferno would be the United Nations.
Inferno's goal is to unite the underworld.
A fantasy like that wouldn't have even been told as a joke a little while ago.
But now it's being turned into reality by...
...Phantom.
That's right, your coach.
Phantom's power is absolute.
Her existence, as someone who can effectively eliminate targets,
provides the highest level of confidence to Inferno,
while instilling the greatest fear in its enemies.
Without a doubt, she is the best assassin alive.
But...
In the end, she's only a puppet of the organization.
Both Phantom and I have no choice but to live as slaves.
Like you say, we may be forcing this lifestyle upon you.
But you're not a slave.
Even you possess a freedom.
Speed.
Speed?
Even in a set course, as long as you desire and work for it,
you can accelerate towards any goal.
You may even be able to stand at the top of this organization.
How you run through it is up to you.
Don't ever think of yourself as a slave again.
As long as you have that thought in mind,
you're granting victory to those who belittle you.
I wanted to chat for a little longer,
but there's work I need to tend to.
Goodbye, Zwei.
You know, cars are driven by people.
Not by puppets.
Even in a set course, as long as you desire and work for it,
you can accelerate towards any goal.
Desire...
Work...
I'd forgotten about those words for a while now.
Ein.
What is it?
Did you... kill someone in today's mission?
Yes.
Why did you... become an assassin?
I don't know.
I've never been told about my past.
That means...
Yes.
I'm just like you.
They erased my memories and made me an assassin.
But so what?
Surviving the moment...
That's all that matters to us assassins.
There's nothing for us in the past or future.
But this woman called Claudia said...
Claudia?
She came here this afternoon.
She said we weren't slaves, and that we have freedom.
If that's what you want to believe, then so be it.
But soon, like me, you won't be able to feel anything.
Because it's the only way of coping with this way of life.
You'll be like that someday.
You'll understand when you actually kill someone.
When you're just aiming at bricks, it's easy to pull the trigger.
But...
Fire.
Fire, Zwei.
Zwei...
This is just the continuation of a dream.
A dream that will not end until you die.