I thought your half-assed beatings were better than Ishihara's dirty tricks.
That's why I put up with them.
But now you've gone too far.
Three weeks before Sakuragi was due for release, his rage exploded like a thousand suns.
You got some nerve.
If you want to die, then we'll grant your wish and kill you.
It looks like it'll be over tonight.
I'll need you to stop by tomorrow and sign a death certificate.
That's one thing taken care of.
Yes.
By the way, Ishihara,
are things going smoothly with that kid?
Yokosuka Jou?
Yes.
Please make it quick.
I'm dying to see him.
Bro...
I... I...
All right, time for the morning-
Wh-What in the world...
Yokoyama!
What happened?
Explain!
Nothing... happened.
What?
What are you saying?
Did Sakuragi do this?
Did he?
No.
The four of us just got in a little fight.
Sakuragi... has nothing to do with this.
Don't give me that crap!
Didn't Sakuragi do this to you?!
H-He didn't...
You...
You're going to disobey me?!
You fuckers were silenced?!
Mr. Ishihara...
Please, forgive us.
Please.
Damn it!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Sakuragi...
You're fucking dead!
Mario, forgive me.
It must've hurt.
"Grasshoppers can fly.
So can birds.
Yet... aren't we even allowed to dream?
Will we be allowed to leave this facility alive?"
That's what Sakuragi thought...
as he faced the darkness in his heart.
Minakami.
Um...
I also...
think there's a problem with how Mr. Ishihara treats Sakuragi.
I think something needs to be done.
Well...
I'm going back now.
Get plenty of rest.
Man, what the hell happened to Mario?
He's in the hospital?
I heard Kumagai took him there.
Anyway, all we can do is wait.
Let's go back.
We'll catch a cold.
Excuse me.
You there.
You mean me?
Yes, you.
You look a little pale.
Are you okay?
Do you have a cold?
A fever?
No, not particularly.
You're Yokosuka Jou, right?
Yes.
Joe, let's go!
Y-Yeah!
Don't hesitate to come play in my office.
S-Sure.
Excuse me.
What did he want?
Did you see his eyes?
Yeah.
He's definitely after you, Joe.
I'm not worried.
What are you doing in this shit cold weather?
Bro!
Yo.
It's been a while.
Bro!
What are we going to do?
Sakuragi's going to be released in just three weeks!
Calm down, Mr. Ishihara.
He survived the lynch mob, and I can't provoke him to do anything.
He follows the rules strictly.
What are we supposed to do?
It's simple.
Make him break the rules.
Make him?
Sakuragi won't break the rules for himself.
Strictly for himself, that is.
I see.
Mario's hand was smashed?
So that's why he's in the hospital.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have told him it was his fault.
You're not the only one to blame.
Yeah.
Guys.
Don't...
get involved with me anymore.
Don't worry about me.
I just need to hold out for three weeks.
Then I'll be waiting for you on the streets.
Got it?
All right, Bro.
What are you boys hiding?
Guys.
Go back to your cell.
Hey, now.
You're not gonna say hi to me?
Or what is it?
Won't greet a guy who's not in charge of you anymore?
Well?
Stop!
Line up!
Attention!
Bow!
All right, good.
Nice little boys.
Now, excuse us!
Who said you were done?
Keep your head down till I say you're done!
And don't move a muscle!
I see.
So that's his plan.
He's trying to make us suffer...
...to provoke Bro into breaking a rule.
He's still the dirty fucker he always was.
Bring it on.
We'll endure it till the end!
Mr. Ishihara!
What are you doing in the rain?
Please, this isn't-
Shut the fuck up, Kumagai!
Sakuragi, something wrong?
Hate me, don't you?
I don't mind if you hit me.
Bro.
Guys...
What the fuck is wrong with them?
Normal people wouldn't last five minutes.
Is something wrong, Mr. Ishihara?
Feel like giving us a rest now?
Or did you get diarrhea from standing out in the cold rain?
You fucker!
Who said you could talk?!
What's that hand doing there, Sakuragi?
That's enough.
Whoa, there!
You know what happens to people who raise their hands against the guards!
Like I care.
Bro!
You reckless bastards.
Thanks.
The youngsters' tears stained the ground along with the rain.
However, their sorrow and hatred remained in their hearts...
never to disappear.
Yo, Sakuragi.
It's dinner.
Can't hear me?
I got food.
What's that?
You're not hungry?
All right, that's cool.
I can't let you out on the streets, you see.
You know a secret, don't you?
A year ago, two kids were being held in 2-6:
Sakuragi Rokurouta, who'd been sent there for injuring someone,
and Hagino Ei'ichi, who'd been sent there for attempted burglary.
They were the same age and quickly became close.
Why... did you try to steal?
I didn't have a choice.
I couldn't think of another way.
How else was I supposed to pay my mother's hospital bill?
Hospital bill?
My mother's... really ill.
But I don't have the money to send her to the hospital.
I can't just wait quietly for her to die!
Then... you shouldn't have gotten caught so easily.
What's your mother gonna do without you?
You're right.
Now...
you just need to think about how to get out of here quickly.
Hagino.
Dr. Sasaki wants to do another test for tuberculosis.
Mr. Ishihara...
Hagino was checked just last week.
Sakuragi.
It's fine.
Thank you.
Now, enjoy yourself.
Yes, I will.
Last week...
you said it was the last time!
Don't you want to see your mother?
Mr. Ishihara...
With that...
I can get out early, right?
What?
I thought you promised!
You really thought it was that easy?
Like hell it is.
I suggest you stay as Dr. Sasaki's obedient little pet.
Hey.
You know...
I think I'll be able to see my mother sooner than I thought.
Mom...
"Inspector Ishihara was selling me to Sasaki...
as a sex slave.
Ishihara broke his promise to release me early.
So I'll wait for my mother in heaven."
Hagino...
In the end, Hagino Ei'ichi's death was dismissed as an accident.
You killed him!
What the hell are you saying out of the blue, Sakuragi?
You and Sasaki drove him to commit suicide.
No, that wasn't suicide.
You guys killed him.
Well, either way, it doesn't matter.
You're not getting out of here for beans.
To Bro?!
Yeah.
He hasn't received any food since he's gone in there either.
Wait, it's been a week since then.
You'd better be shitting me!
Are you going to just let that go?
You're going to just let him die?!
N-No!
I wanted to do something, so-
You're just the same.
You're just like Ishihara.
You see us as nothing more than little bugs.
Please, listen.
I'm...
Please, just leave us alone.
We'll save Bro, whatever it takes.
Yes, I haven't given him a single serving.
Just as you instructed, Dr. Sasaki.
Human beings can't survive two weeks without food and water.
Yes.
Then...
You can list the cause of death as acute heart failure due to weakness.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
These guys...
are trying to kill Sakuragi.
Cabbage.
You really think we can't tell what you're thinking?
Hagino...
This is getting bad.
I might have to apologize to you face to face.
Sorry.
Damn it, where's he hiding?
Find that kid!
Bro!
Turtle?
Good, you're still alive.
Hey, what are you doing here?
You haven't been eating, right?
You came here... for that?
Piece of cake.
All of the guards are super dumb.
There were some pickles with rice today, so those are in the rice ball.
Well, Bro?
Isn't it good?
Yeah.
It's great.
I've never eaten...
a rice ball this good.
Really?
That's good to hear.
Hagino.
It seems like...
I won't be seeing you yet.
I've got some great friends down here.
They're all crazy as fuck.
But they're my dear boys.
I want to spend more time with them, you see.
The care Bro showed for every one of his friends gave him the strength to live and the will to fight.
For the second time, Sakuragi swore,
"Hagino, I'll enable you to rest in peace."
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
The hell of water torture.
The six make a firm decision.
"We won't let Bro die, no matter what."
Hello, everyone, I'm Satake Uki!
Today, we're interviewing Ms. Kanjiya Shihori, who voices Setsuko, the heroine of the show.
Enjoy!
She's the nurse for 2-6.
She's a strong girl, but also ladylike,
since she shows some soft spots as well.
You're the first person who's ever wanted to go back so quickly.
It really makes you think,
and all the characters are
attractive in their own ways.
They all grow and change
as the story progresses,
so I hope you'll enjoy
that aspect too.