Hey, everyone, we're going
to start Kaleido Star.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Do you have siblings?
Nice older brothers or sisters.
Or darling younger brothers or sisters?
Very soon, I'm going to be an older sister.
Is it a boy? Or is it a girl?
I should be very happy, but...
I'm a little anxious. I am. I am.
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
I know. But, you don't need to worry.
I'm going to find a room where
I can live with my friends,
and we've decided to create
our own company together.
I know, I'm sure it'll be hard,
but I want to give it a try.
So, I don't think I'll go
back there for a while.
Oh... Really?
Er... Well... What should I say?
Congratulations...
Oh, that's why they say "Congratulations"
on occasions like these.
I'm happy for you, Mother.
What? Really?
I sound kind of weird?
Well, I'm acting the same as usual.
"Amazing Family Ties."
All right.
As of today, a new life will start.
A new...
I should be happy.
But why do I feel this way?
You don't need to look so sad.
I will come with you, Sora.
So, you're coming with me?
Of course. So rest easy.
If you ever peep into Mia or Anna's bath,
you're going to immediately
be food for Jonathan!
Oh... Yes!
Thank you for waiting.
You're late. You're late.
Do you have everything with you?
Yes.
Then let's go.
Until we find our own place,
we'll take you up on your offer
and stay with your family.
Everyone in my family is also
looking forward to seeing you guys.
Miss Sarah...
So, all you guys are finally heading out too.
Where are you going, Miss Sarah?
I'm leaving for training, of course.
Bye...
Training?
She left to train for singing. Didn't she?
Somehow, she looked like she
left for martial arts training.
Since it's Miss Sarah,
that could be the case.
But, thanks to Ken's family,
I was really saved.
My grandma felt relieved.
After all, a newspaper
already printed an article
saying that after Kaleido Stage's
owner changed, the cast quit.
There is no way that I can turn
young girls out into the streets.
Wow, you sound very manly.
Don't tease me.
Sorry.
Sora...
Are you worried about something?
What? Oh... No. It's nothing like that.
Sora!
What?
Your suitcase!
Oh, I remember...
Before you come to my house,
there is something I want
you to be prepared for...
Be prepared for?
I've already spoken strictly
to her about it...
But, my younger sister is especially...
This is it.
Wow...
It's like a park.
I know. My father built it.
Your father? Amazing!
Oh, I know. And, about my younger sister...
Wow!
It's Anna! It's really Anna!
Here!
Hold it, hold it!
Pose, pose!
My younger sister, Lucy, is a big Anna fan.
She doesn't think it's funny.
Ken!
It's not nice to keep
them outside for so long.
Here, hurry. Come inside quick.
Go inside.
My mom is...
Hey...
Ben! Everyone is here!
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, come in.
Really, all you do is rest.
You're wrong.
I'm trying to get the idea
for a new design of...
Here, move, move.
Here, please, please.
My father designs furniture.
Don't be so modest, have a seat.
I'll make coffee.
Oh, thank you.
Here, Anna.
Hurry, hurry.
Have a seat, quick.
Wow! Anna is sitting on our couch!
Ook Ook!
Somehow...
Anna is different from what I had in my mind.
I'm very sorry.
So, this was no good either?
Definitely.
I wonder if posing as a
monkey is too ordinary...
Good!
Oh, it's good!
This is the last one.
I'll leave your luggage here.
Oh, thank you...
Wow...
This room is so adorable.
Sorry.
This used to be a kid's room.
So it's kind of messy, but...
Not at all. It's wonderful.
Did you design this, too?
Yes, if you find anything you like,
you can take it with you when
you find your own place.
Really?
Here. This time hold this.
Ah! I still want to take
more pictures of Anna!
Well, take it easy until dinner.
Anna!
I think we should find our apartment quickly.
Yes, we should.
A kid's room...
Once my father and mother's
real child is born, I...
Sora, what's wrong?
You've been depressed for a while.
What? I don't think I am.
When did he sneak in?!
Sora?
He's gone.
You!
What's wrong, Sora?
Is it a bug or something?
Sora!
What's the matter with you?
I got you!!
I'm sorry for making all that noise.
How shall I say this?
But to show you how sorry I feel,
let me help you prepare dinner.
Us too...
Oh, thank you.
But you don't need to worry.
Our place is always noisy, and...
Ken used to jump off the bunk bed
often when he was a child too.
He did?
Yes. He'd say that he was
going to be a Kaleido Star.
But, that boy, since he was a child,
his heart's been weak, and...
Even so, it wasn't so bad that he had
any problems living a normal life.
So, he had a hard time giving up.
I understand how he feels.
But, as his mother, I couldn't
let him do what he really wanted.
Even now, I'm nervous,
worrying that he may say he wants to
appear on stage one of these days.
Ken! Give me my camera back!
No!
As long as you have this, you'll
keep chasing after Anna.
What's wrong with it? I'll
brag about it to my friends.
Then you should invite your friends here.
She is the real Anna.
Oh, that's a good idea!
Dad, please don't say anything unnecessary.
I have a younger brother.
I did the same. We used
to fight all the time.
Me too.
When I had a quarrel with
my mom, it was rough.
At our house... I don't think we ever fought.
What?
Now, let's have dinner.
Sora...
Ken...
Can't sleep?
I was just enjoying the cool weather.
Sorry my place is so noisy.
No. I think it's very nice.
Everyone says whatever is on their
minds. It's like a real family.
Even though they're your adopted parents,
aren't they your real family?
Yes, sure. What am I saying?
I thought so.
I think you're worried about
something, aren't you?
Oh... Not at all.
On the contrary, there's
something to celebrate.
My mother is going to have a baby.
Really?
You're going to have a sibling.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
They couldn't have a baby for so long.
I thought they weren't having kids
because they were concerned about me.
And if they were, I thought
I'd feel so bad...
But I feel better now.
When my younger sister was born,
I remember I felt a little sad.
This is something natural,
but both my parents devoted all
their energies to my newborn sister.
So I used to say unreasonable
things on purpose,
and gave my mother and father a hard time.
But I'm afraid I can never
do anything like that:
having a serious fight, or
speaking my mind to them.
I'm afraid of destroying our family bonds.
I don't think it's like that.
Okay...
Please tell me anything.
I... think I can be part of
a family if it's with you.
You're right.
We're like family, you and me.
Sora...
Mia and Anna too.
What?
We're going to make our own Kaleido Stage.
It's no time to be depressed!
First thing tomorrow,
I will try hard to find an apartment!
Well, good night, Ken.
No... I didn't mean it like that.
I know...
Since I'm with everyone, I
should be able to keep going.
Also, I want to show my performances
to my mother and father.
Please be my friends forever too.
That Sora...
She gets rougher and rougher with me.
The Empress...
We're leaving!
Aren't you tired?
No.
A penthouse with a yard...
Amazing!
Too expensive.
A standalone house in the suburbs
might not be a bad idea!
Too far.
How about here?
It's less expensive and it looks
like it's in a convenient location.
Hm...
No.
Mr. Policeman.
Why is it not good?
This place was robbed before.
What...
It's not easy to find a nice place.
Not necessarily.
This is it.
It's old.
It's not as bad as it looks.
The rent is cheap, it's in a
convenient location, and...
I live here too.
Miss Kate!
This is it.
Wow...
What do you think?
I think it's pretty good.
I told you.
The inside is cleaner than I thought.
It's pretty big.
Oh...
The view is good, and...
Yeah, it motivates me.
Yes, it does.
I think this place is good.
Me too.
Then it's settled.
From here, we're going to start
up our own Kaleido Stage.
By all means!
Since I live just below,
just let me know if there's
anything you need.
Isn't it perfect?
Everyone, why don't we have
coffee or something in my room?
In your room?
It's a little messy, but
don't let it bother you.
I'm the one who usually cleans up this place.
A perfect place...
There's the distinct possibility we'll
have to clean Miss Kate's room too.
Well... I guess there is no
such thing as the perfect deal.
Jerry, where's the coffee?
Jerry?
So, Mr. Policeman's name is Jerry.
It's so cute.
It's too good for him.
Who cares what kind of name I have?!
Jerry!
Who knew we would find a place so fast?
Yeah, we're lucky.
Lucy will be disappointed to lose you.
Shall we leave Anna alone there?
Don't!
Someone's waiting in front of the house.
Oh, Sora...
Sora...
Father... Mother...
What?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Since she came here all the way from
Japan in that kind of condition,
I wonder if they came here
to take Sora back with them.
After we finally found our own apartment...
You surprised me...
'Cause all of a sudden
you were waiting for me.
When we went to your dormitory, they
said they had no idea where you went.
So it took a while to find this place.
Oh, sorry. I meant to call you later.
Anyway, are you okay coming all the way here?
I'm fine.
Your mother insisted on coming here.
Because...
I was concerned after we talked on the phone.
Did I sound that bad? Weird...
If you're worried about me, I'm fine.
Over the phone,
I can't tell whether you're
doing all right or not.
Oh, really?
Oh, by the way, we found an apartment today.
That policeman Father met referred it to us.
So don't you feel relieved?
And there's even a doctor
living on the floor below us.
Her name is Miss Kate.
I think Mr. Policeman is
secretly in love with her.
Sora...
Why don't you come back to Japan for a while?
Because if you've quit Kaleido Stage,
I know you'll have a hard
time making a living.
If you're worried about that,
my friends and I will...
Even though you're going to
create your own Kaleido Stage,
if you rest for a little while
in Japan, you will get new ideas.
And if you do that, we don't need
to worry about you every day either.
So, can you...
Before long, you won't have
time to worry about me.
Once you have your own child...
Oh...
Sora...
Don't be silly!
Why wouldn't we worry about you?!
We'd never be like that!
Sorry...
No...
I didn't come here to say this.
I should also apologize. Sorry...
Midori?
Mother...
Oh, dear! Ken, call an ambulance.
Yes!
Ben, get a car ready!
Midori, be strong!
Please lie down.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Midori! Midori!
Mother!
A Caesarean section?
But she's only seven months pregnant...
It's an emergency situation.
There are no other alternatives.
Hey, Ben.
Why don't you calm down a bit?
Oh... Yeah...
What shall I do?
Sora, be strong.
I'm sure that she'll be all right.
It's because I said something
terrible to her...
That's why my mother...
It's not your fault.
No, it is my fault.
I just thought that once
my mother had a baby...
There would be no room for me...
I know my mother is so
happy about having a baby.
But I can't feel happy for her
from the bottom of my heart,
and I don't like being like this.
And I thought if I went back to Japan now,
my mother would sense that
part of me that I don't like.
That's why... I said something like that.
Mother was trying so hard to be a family...
But I... I broke it.
Sora.
Aren't you worried about your mother
from the bottom of your heart right now?
You're wishing that she'll have
the baby without any problems.
Don't you think that's
what family is all about?
All of you are a real family.
No matter what happens, your
family will never fall apart.
Both your mother and her
baby are trying hard...
Let's cheer them on.
Yes. Thank you, Ken.
Mother, please hold on.
And, you too, baby...
Please... Please be born safely...
I'm waiting for you.
It's a girl.
Your mother is calm. She's resting now.
Thank you very much.
She's so tiny.
Your mother was only seven months pregnant.
But she's fine.
You were the same.
What?
You were in an incubator like she is now.
Back then, your mother and father
were so worried about you,
and they blamed themselves too.
Unable to hold you for a while,
every time they saw you in the incubator,
they used to tell you to be
strong and grow up healthy.
I remember very well that they
were cheering for you like that.
When you told me you wanted
to join Kaleido Stage,
the first thing that came to my mind was:
"If he were here, what
would your father say?"
No matter how much I thought about it,
I didn't get the answer in the end.
But, perhaps, I thought he would have
been bewildered and sent you off
while worrying about you like I did.
Little Sora became so big,
and she found what she
wanted to do by herself.
But your mother and I will
never stop worrying about you.
Father...
Sora, go see your mother.
Yes.
Sora...
I scared you, didn't I?
Mother, I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing? It's not your fault.
Yes it is.
I said something terrible.
I'm sorry.
But that was not what I really think.
That was...
I thought I knew how anxious you were,
but I said something that
drove you into a corner,
and put you in a situation that you had
to say something you didn't want to.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
To tell you the truth,
I wanted you near me when the baby was born.
After all, you are the
only big sister she has.
But then you said something like
"I'm not coming home" on the phone.
So, I lost my composure.
I told your father something selfish,
saying that I'd go right over
to see you as soon as I hung up.
But thanks to that, my wish came true
even though it was different
from what I was expecting.
Mother...
Hey, come closer, Sora.
Yes.
Thank you for growing up a healthy girl.
When we decided to adopt you,
I was anxious, wondering whether
I could be your mother.
I think it's the same
kind of anxiety you had.
When you called me "Mother"
for the first time,
I was so happy, I secretly cried.
Now, when you're away from
me, I worry about you.
But, when I think that you're
doing fine and working hard,
it makes me happy.
I adore you so much, Sora.
Mother...
If you have any problems, you have
to tell me, at any time. Okay?
Yes.
Hey, Sora.
What?
Can you name the baby?
Me? Are you sure?
I always wanted you to name my baby.
Okay.
They said she had a healthy baby!
I'm glad!
Let's celebrate! Celebrate! Call everyone!
Everyone?
Who she is talking about?
The Empress card also represents childbirth.
Wow... She is adorable.
A little sister... Congratulations, Sora.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything this time.
You're welcome.
But we didn't do anything extraordinary.
You have such a nice son.
What!
A nice son? Oh, well...
You did a good job, little sister.
I will too.
I will do my best here for my dream.
Oh...
I decided!
What?
The baby's name!
Yume! I want to name her Yume. "Dream."
Yume...
Isn't it a nice name, Father?
Father?
Oh... No... Well...
Yume... I hope she grows up fast.
"Next Kaleido Star"
I need to repay Sora's kindness a lot.
And so, it's our show, a new challenge.
Even though Miss Layla rejected it.
To our surprise, Rosetta
came here to help us.
And a mysterious shadow dashingly
appeared like the wind...
Who is she really? Who? Who?
Next time on Kaleido Star, "An
Amazing Change From Zero to Hero."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru