I knew it.
It's coming!
It is that Eotenes bitch!
The Eoten Fatale has arisen once again,
this time slaughtering the elite
Squad Levi members one after the other.
I'll kill you!
Eren believes his faith in his companions caused their deaths.
He transforms and engages the Eoten Fatale,
but he suffers an agonizing defeat and is captured within her maw.
Give Eren back!
No matter where this bitch goes, I'll kill her,
slice her apart,
and pull you out of her filth.
I'm sorry, Eren.
Wait...
just a little longer!
Wait for me!
Wh-What?
Fall back for the present.
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel
We will kill
The enemy is huge
We will jump
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
The Defeated
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 6 )
Maintain this distance.
She may be tiring.
The bitch seems to be slowing down.
So she bit him right out of the Eotenes' neck?
Is Eren dead?
He's alive.
The target possesses intelligence.
Her objective seems to be Eren's capture.
If she wanted him dead, she would've crushed him.
But she went to the trouble of putting him in her mouth, and now she's trying to flee.
Her goal may have been to eat Eren.
In that case, he'd be in her stomach.
The reasonable assumption would be that he's dead.
He's alive!
That would be nice.
If you'd done your job and protected Eren, this wouldn't've happened!
Now I get it.
You're that one brat.
Eren's childhood friend, right?
We'll restrict ourselves to a single objective.
We need to give up on killing this Eotenes bitch.
But she's murdered so many!
As long as she can ossify her skin, she's unbeatable.
Just follow my damn orders.
We'll gamble that Eren is still alive,
and take him back before he leaves the forest.
I'll start working on her body.
You keep her mind occupied!
He's so fast.
Fast enough that she has no time to harden her skin!
We can strike her neck.
She's tired.
I'll bet she can't even move!
I can kill her!
Stop!
Eren!
Hey!
Let's get out of here!
Eren?
I think he's okay.
He's alive!
Also slimy.
Forget that bitch.
We must retreat.
Don't lose sight of the core objective.
Or is sating your bloodlust more important?
More important than your friend?
No, I...
They're coming back already?
What happened?
No idea.
But I'm sure they'll be cartin' in lots of dead bodies as usual.
Elad is coming home.
I see.
Think Orlo will have time to come home?
I'll have dinner ready for him, just in case.
Gunther's coming back.
I see.
This is the part I just can't get used to.
No one can.
How will my friends die?
How will I die?
That thought consumes my mind.
I try not to dwell on it.
If I were imagining my own death,
I probably wouldn't be able to fight.
Yeah.
You're right.
How long can I survive?
Well, aren't you alive right now?
For now.
Isn't that pretty great?
You're alive!
You say that when we're surrounded by the dead?
I feel like I can't go home again.
We're almost done.
There were around five casualties we couldn't recover.
Not even pieces of of them?
Sir, we couldn't reach them due to Eotena activity...
It's probably best for the families if we don't bring them back.
Say they're MIA.
Yes, sir.
We saw several Eotenas near the forest,
but none are moving in this direction as of yet.
We're heading out.
Inform all squads.
Yes, sir.
This is wrong, Commander Erwin!
Hey, you—
We should get them back!
Ivan's body was right there!
And an Eoten was standing over it!
Don't go and create another casualty!
If They attack, we need only defeat Them!
Ivan was a childhood friend of ours.
I know his parents.
At least let them bury their own son!
Don't be foolish!
Bickering brats?
Corporal Levi.
If you've confirmed his death, your job is done.
No matter where the body, dead is dead.
Recovering it won't change a thing.
No...
We'll say Ivan and the others went missing.
That's my final decision.
No more quibbling.
How can you two
even call yourselves human beings?!
Hey, Dieter, that's going too far!
Reconnaissance Legion Wagons ( 1 )
These wagons incorporate a sophisticated suspension system
of ultra-hardened steel, which can be manufactured only in factory cities.
Reconnaissance Legion Wagons ( 1 )
These wagons incorporate a sophisticated suspension system
of ultra-hardened steel, which can be manufactured only in factory cities.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Reconnaissance Legion Wagons ( 2 )
Wagons hitched to Survey Corps horses travel at
around 20 km/h. They can maintain that speed
on varied terrain, be it paved or unpaved road.
Reconnaissance Legion Wagons ( 2 )
Wagons hitched to Survey Corps horses travel at
around 20 km/h. They can maintain that speed
on varied terrain, be it paved or unpaved road.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Eotenas!
That's...
Dieter!
That utter imbecile.
The rearguard reports contact!
Onward at top speed!
Not a tall tree or a building in sight.
Fighting out here will be difficult.
We're better off outracing them to the Walls.
They've almost got us!
You think we need to fight?
MMG has limited utility in open areas.
And look.
They just keep coming!
Then what do we do?
We...
No good! They're right on top of us!
I'll get behind them!
I'll draw their attention, then you—
No.
Just abandon the bodies.
They'll overtake us.
B-But that's...
We've never been able to bring back every single corpse.
Those guys are no different from the others.
Are we doing this?
Are we actually doing this?!
Fuck it.
We have to!
That did it!
Stay on course!
We'll continue on once we've determined our position.
Stay alert!
We'll have to bear slightly further east.
Corporal Levi.
I...
This proves that they were alive.
At least to me.
This was Ivan's.
Corporal!
Let's move out!
Eren.
It's best if you give up on the Reconnaissance Legion.
What?!
Now you're gonna start making fun of them too?
That's not the issue here—
The Legion has returned!
They're opening the gates!
Let's go, Mikasa.
It's the return of the conquering heroes!
Who'd've thought so few'd come back...
I'm sure the rest got themselves eaten.
Serves 'em right for going outside the Walls.
It's like we're just sending Them free snacks.
Eren?
What's wrong?
Eren.
Eren!
You shouldn't get up yet.
Just rest.
That Eoten...?
It got away.
How?
What about everyone else?
What about the plan?
It failed.
Rest for now.
What's this?
Did you save me again?
We've almost reached the Walls.
Weren't there more of them this morning?
Far more.
Another disaster.
All that fanfare when they left this morning,
and they're limping back already?
What the hell was the point?
Who knows?
But judging by those glum faces,
I'm guessing our tax money wasn't exactly used wisely.
Eren, keep your cool.
Awesome!
The Legion's stone cold awesome!
They keep on fightin' no matter how many times they get walloped!
Corporal Levi, sir!
My daughter is in your squad.
I'm Petra's father.
I wanted to talk with you before she sees me.
She sent me this letter.
She says that you respected her abilities enough to allow her into your squad.
She says she's going to "devote herself" to you.
Well, I guess she's too starry-eyed to consider her father's feelings!
And as her father,
I think it's too early for her to marry.
She's still so young, and she has so much to experience...
Commander Erwin! Answer us!
Did this expedition learn enough to justify the number of casualties?
You think the dead have no regrets?
The financial and human costs of the 57th Sortie were ruinous.
The political factions that had supported the Legion were utterly discredited.
All those responsible, including Erwin,
were summoned to the capital,
where he was to give up custody of Eren.
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
On that day, Annie was
part of Eren's escort as he and his companions answer the summons to the capital.
Suddenly, Armin accosts her
and asks for her help with a highly sensitive mission.
Smile
Raid on Stohess District ( 1 )