"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
It's been a while since we last
wore these uniforms.
Oh, it's Kona-chan.
Kona-chan! Morning!
Oh, Kagami-san, Tsukasa-san...
Good day to you, kyaran...
Oh dear, Tsukasa-san...
Your ribbon is tied crooked.
Thanks.
Gross.
What's wrong with you, Kona-chan?
This is so sudden...
Yes... As of late, I am completely
hooked on Mari-Mite...
Mari-Mite?
Are you a child?!
"Image"
Hey, don't start mimicking the
costumes from stuff like that, okay?
Let's see...
That's called cosplay, right?
I wouldn't go that far, you know.
Are you sure about that?
I already do a lot of that at work.
Oh, yeah... Come to think of it,
she works at that kind of place...
But, Kona-chan as a girl
in a well-to-do family...
She's so incompatible with
that image that I can't imagine it.
Too many baseball broadcasts
have run over lately.
Why are midnight anime viewers
the ones forced to make the sacrifice?
If you want to watch
anime that much,
why don't you subscribe
to cable or something?
They have channels just
for that and stuff, right?
If I could, I'd like to get it, you know.
The guys from the cable TV
service said all sorts of stuff,
ending with "We can't
provide service here."
Yuki-chan, morning!
Good morning, Tsukasa-san.
You seem down.
Did something happen?
Actually, I went to treat
my cavity the other day.
Oh, you went to the dentist!
Way to go!
Why is it that when you go
to a dentist once,
you have to go back so many times?
Wow, I really know how you feel.
I've never been able to finish
in one or two visits!
Miyuki-san, good day to you.
Oh, Konata-san. Good day to you.
I hope nothing has occurred?
Yes, thankfully.
--Nothing less from Yuki-chan!
--I am glad that you seem
fine as well, Konata-san.
--She's speaking in the same way,
yet it doesn't seem awkward at all!
Or more like, she didn't even notice
how Kona-chan is speaking.
This is the first time that
I've actually seen anyone
really greet someone else
with a "Good day to you."
Is that so?
At the all-girls high school
that my friends attend,
I hear that they greet each other
with "Good day to you" regularly.
I see...
A real well-to-do girls'
high school sure is different.
How elegant!
Kuroi told me to collect everyone's
summer vacation homework.
Thank you for your efforts, Sebastian.
Se-Seba--
When you speak of butlers,
of course you would
assume Sebastian, correct?
Yeah, there is that image.
--Say something amusing, Sebastian.
--That's impossible!
Okay, we're fresh out of vacation,
but it's no time to space out!
It's about time you started
thinking about your future
as you delve into your studies!
About the future, that means
after graduation, right?
After all, we've passed the halfway
point of our high school career.
But you aren't thinking much
about your future, right, Kagami?
Why's that? That's kind of rude!
I mean, you wanted to be in
the same class as all of us,
so you chose literary studies, right?
--Tsukasa, you blabbermouth!
--My bad.
And of everyone you could
choose to tell, you chose her!
Oh, you should just
be honest and say it.
You're such a lonely little girl...
There, there.
Shut up!
Yoo-hoo! I'm here again!
Oh! Sis!
About my summer
vacation homework...
Just like you told me the other day,
I wrote answers that seemed right
even when I didn't really understand.
But now they're making me
do it over! Help me!
That's fine with me, but...
If I help, maybe you'll have
to do it over yet again,
in all sorts of ways.
She's dodging it!
You don't get an extension
on summer vacation,
but the homework gets an extension?
Maybe I should borrow
Kagami's notes after all.
The last cry of a cicada
is like a lullaby...
I see... The extra innings forced
the on-air time to shift...
I guess there are good things
about it every so often.
Wait, the timer recording
is shifted wrong too...
Huh? Yuki-chan, where
are your glasses?
Actually, they broke this morning.
I had forgotten I placed them
on top of my chair,
and I accidentally, you know...
I'm terribly sorry,
but can you two lend me
today's class notes later?
Sure, that's fine.
You sure are a clumsy girl,
as always...
"Konata's notes" "So messy that an ordinary
person can't read what's written on it"
Konata-san, your handwriting
is so mysterious...
"Tsukasa's notes" "So tidy that she couldn't
finish copying everything down"
Tsukasa-san, hang in there!
They sure are useless. Here.
Thank you so much.
Good thing we have the same teacher.
Um, but... Can you keep this a secret?
I would hate to pour cold water
on their generosity.
I'm so hungry!
Yuki-chan, let's eat lunch!
Oh, Tsukasa-san, Konata-san,
thank you for your notes.
Oh no, no need for thanks.
I never thought that I would
lend you my notes, Yuki-chan.
Well, I'm sure there
won't be a next time.
"Stare"
Stare...
Um... Is there something on my face?
In games,
when characters in glasses
come to school without glasses,
they suddenly become
really popular with guys,
but I guess you don't
see that in real life.
You don't see something
of that sort, unfortunately.
You know, choco-cornets
look like drills.
Drills?
Oh, come to think of it,
we talked the other day
about which side is the head
of a choco-cornet...
Like how the thin end
looks more like a butt...
When you take another look,
the thicker end looks
more like the butt.
Butt?
Wow, that's a fat butt.
And jelly rolls to boot!
When the bottom half
of your body gets fat,
it's troublesome when you're
trying to buy a new skirt...
Right, right. When you fit
your waist, your hips don't fit,
and when your hips are just right,
your waist is all loose.
Since you can't help it,
you buy the one with
the slightly loose waist,
and your skirt starts spinning
around as you walk.
Right, right.
A cornet body with love handles...
When you put it to the side,
you get a napping body.
And too much napping gets you...
A cornet body.
I don't know where
I'm supposed to laugh.
Sis, didn't you get rid of the summer
pudginess by going on a diet?
Yeah, but though I lost weight,
I didn't lose anything
on my waist or my hips.
No, Kagami, I can see
the fruits of your diet.
Really?
Yeah, I can see the difference clearly.
They say that when you go on a diet,
the things you lose first are
the things you don't need to lose...
That's enough! You don't
have to spell it out!
The point when reading a passage
is to think about the theme
of the sentence at all times,
and read into what the author
wants to portray as a message...
"I see..."
I heard that people with bad eyesight
look like they're glaring
and people are scared of them,
but after all...
That depends on the person as well.
Hey!
You looked my way when
you said that, didn't you?!
I heard somewhere that when
you make your eyes narrow,
you look very pretty.
It's like you get a look of sorrow
behind the eyes or something.
Come on, we can't all do it!
She's late... What the
heck is Konata doing?!
Oh, she's here.
Sorry I'm late!
So late!
You always complain about baseball
games going into extra innings,
so how can you be
loose about time too?!
Well, you know, lately there
have been so many of them...
So, you know, maybe
I got infected too?
You can't catch that!
So, why are you late?
Did you oversleep?
No, no, I'm not a child, you know.
Then tell me the adult reason
why you're so late.
Well, when I got all ready to go out,
I had plenty of time to spare,
but when I started playing
a game to pass the time,
I couldn't find a good place to leave it off.
Worst excuse ever.
You're worse than a kid.
You know, the second
trimester has lots of events,
like the school arts festival
and the school sports festival.
And there are exams right afterwards.
Lucky for you, Kona-chan,
you can do so well in the sports fest
because you're so athletic.
I hate the sports festival
because it tires me out.
It's rare to see a homebody like you
in such good physical shape.
I wonder what our class will be
doing in the arts festival.
It's not like we have anything
that we really want to do.
We never really decide on what to do
if we don't have someone
that says, "I want to do this."
And usually, the first one
to speak ends up doing it all,
so nobody really says anything, either.
And we have to get ready
for all of it after school.
And you go home so late,
you miss the afternoon anime.
So you did go there after all.
Lucky Star!
"chicken meat - 500 grams" "celery - 2,
onion - 1, bell peppers - 2" "red peppers,
curry powder, tomato (stewed)"
Since I'm in charge of
cooking dinner tonight,
I have to go grocery shopping.
Really? What are you going to make?
Chicken curry, everyone's favorite.
Everyone in our family loves chicken.
Curry, huh... That sounds good.
I hear that when you let curry
sit overnight, it gets tastier.
I hear that too.
I guess I'll make a bit extra,
and use it for lunch tomorrow.
I mean, we'll have leftovers anyway.
Hello, Hiiragi residence.
Oh, is that you, Tsukasa?
Oh, Kona-chan? What's wrong,
so early in the morning?
The curry...
Curry?
The curry I made last night...
I let it sit overnight, and it rotted!
You're kidding!
It's true.
How come? Usually curry
doesn't rot in a day.
Right.
Did you add something strange?
I didn't... But there was mold
growing on it this morning!
So you have your cornet again today.
It's all right because it's tasty.
If you're okay with it...
Come to think of it... I just
realized this a few minutes ago.
Tsukasa and Kagami, your lunches...
Sometimes your lunches
have proper side dishes,
and sometimes you have
very simple side dishes.
There's a clear difference, isn't there?
Well, Tsukasa and I
take turns making lunches.
Since I'm not too good
with household chores,
in the end, I go with the easy stuff...
Excuse me for being so simple!
What? Kagami, are you the type
"Excited!"
that makes pots explode when you try to cook?
Nobody like that really exists.
Wow, Yuki-chan, your lunch
looks tasty again today!
Oh, no...
Today I just packed
leftovers from last night.
Dinner at Miyuki-san's house...
...is this luxurious?
On top of that, these are leftovers?
Um, what is this inside the fried eggs?
Oh, that's the eel
left over from last night,
that I decided to put into the eggs.
Usually, you don't have
any eel left over, right?
All we have left over is
moldy chicken curry.
I'm telling you, I don't think
your house is normal.
Morning!
Yo!
Look, look!
They bought me a cell phone!
Oh, good for you!
Because my proficiency test
scores were unusually high...
Give me your number.
I'll give you mine too.
Yeah... What was the number?
Let's see...
Hold on for just a sec.
--Let's see... Let's see...
--Konata, you have a cell phone?
Yeah, though I tend to forget it
at home most of the time.
It's okay, nobody but Dad
ever calls me on it.
Then what's the point of
even having a cell phone?
You think so?
Keroro!
Isn't it cute? They bought me one
together with the cell phone!
That reminds me,
someone in my class
has tons of straps hanging
from her cell phone,
and when she weighed them all,
apparently they weighed
a total of 800 grams!
Wow, that many?
Sounds heavy!
When she took all of the straps off,
her stiff shoulders were cured.
In that case, a mere phone call
would be a workout.
You never know when your
cell phone is going to ring,
so it's kind of exciting.
You think so?
I hope someone calls me soon!
In this day and age, don't get
so excited over a cell phone!
By the way, did you
find your number?
Oh, not yet!
In England, the war for
the royal throne began
between the House of Lancaster
and the House of York.
The two houses wore red roses and
white roses when they fought,
so this war is called
the War of the Roses.
It began in 1455, and
ended in 1485. At this time...
Oh, is it me?
It's my cell phone!
I finally got a call!
Who is this?
Okay, confiscated.
Come pick it up at the
teachers' office after school.
I'm so glad! She gave it back to me!
But to think that you start off
with a spam text message...
Oh, Dad? Yeah, I'm still at school.
I've been talking with
Konata and Miyuki and stuff,
and it got late...
Yeah, I'm fine. I'll be home soon.
See ya.
This is what happens when
I run even a little late.
Hello.
Oh, Dad?
Yeah, I'm still at school.
I'm with Kona-chan and
everyone right now.
You'd think he'd get the idea
after he calls one of us.
Fathers are always worried
about their daughters.
There's been more and more
spam lately. It's a pain.
Oh, you should change
your text address
to something that isn't too obvious.
I changed mine too.
Something that isn't obvious?
Like what?
My address is iluvgirlsinglasses
in English characters.
I would have preferred
something like "maid,"
but addresses like
maid san and miko san
are so popular that...
Wait, wait, hold it,
I get what you're saying,
so don't speak so loudly
in front of the general public!
Talking with you is more
of a pain than the spam!
Morning!
Heya!
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
My cell... my cell phone...
She forgot to take it out of her pocket.
It went to its reward?
Maybe they won't
buy me a new one...
He made it through!
Persistent little guy!
Then, the text message
you sent last night...
The one where you said Kagami
wanted her notes back,
that was your last text message?
Yeah. By any chance, did you reply?
--Let's see...
--You never return text
messages in a timely manner!
I make it a point not
to return messages
from someone I can
talk to at any time.
Return text messages
with text messages!
I see you every day,
so I didn't think I needed
to return the message.
You're going to lose friends!
Well now, it's not something
that needs to be rushed...
Don't decide that on your own!
In the end, I didn't
get my notes back.
Tsukasa, I'm coming in!
Oh, Sis...
What? What's wrong?
I was reading the manga
that Kona-chan lent me,
and I was so touched
that I was crying.
Morning!
Kona-chan, thank you for the manga!
It was really interesting!
It was so silly that it
cracked you up, right?
I was so touched that I cried!
With those reactions, you two can't
be talking about the same series.
Here. If you cry, you're in
the same boat as Tsukasa.
If you laugh, you're in
the same boat as me.
I'm not reading it!
I don't want to be classified
in either category!
I'd like to see your reaction, Sis...
Wanting to know more about
your friends... Is that so wrong?
Then, what about Attack Number
(One)? Do you cry, or laugh?
--Laugh.
--Cry.
Then, what is your favorite manga?
Sgt. Frog.
These two... Are they similar,
or are they different?
Kona-chan, why don't you join the
manga research club or something?
You like manga...
Well, I wouldn't mind joining.
I'm sure they have
very flexible hours too.
Draw, draw, draw, draw...
Did you seriously draw all of these?
Now, Konata-san,
who did you draw here?
This is Tsukasa.
That was me?
This is Miyuki-san.
Well, I could kind of tell
from the general feel...
This is Kagami.
Oh, so I breathe fire.
Oh, my... Kagami-san,
you're so like your image!
What a frightening girl!
I'm telling you, stop that!
The new Full Metal book is out.
That's right, the new Comp issue
is coming out today too.
I'm going to swing by Gamers.
Wanna come with me?
Oh, sorry... I'll settle for
the local bookstore today.
I have errands to run too.
This is where you come with me to
nurture the friendship between us!
What? You're sure
coming on strong today.
In the first place, the word
"friendship" doesn't fit you at all.
Well, you know, as a sign
of that friendship,
I want the points from
your purchases...
--So that's what friendship
is to you... That's so cheap.
--I can almost reach out and get
that item that I've got my eyes on!
Lucky Star!
It's so quiet...
Is she mad that I mistakenly
used sunflowers
for the twin-tail ribbons?
Me?
What? You want me?
Towards Akira-sama? Is it all right?
I understand.
Um...
Um, it's already started...
This isn't good... Before
they change the channel!
Morning Luckies!
Just kidding! Or so I tried to say.
Now, Lucky Channel has
started again this week!
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Since Akira-sama is
in a very bad mood...
Giving out your own name
before the name Akira Kogami...
Do you not understand
the concept of rank at all?
Um, that's not what...
Lately, you've been
getting needlessly popular
all over the place with
those twin-tails of yours.
Popular? Not at all...
Aren't you getting
a little full of yourself?!
I'm terribly sorry!
In the first place,
everyone was expecting
the Akira Fashion Project
to have me in twin-tails, right?
But what are those?
You are absolutely right!
I'm going to wear twin-drills!
Twin-drills?
Don't underestimate
the Getter's speed!
♪ 2, huh...
The days of the twin-tails are over!
The next fad will be twin-drills!
Didn't Konata say it in episode two?
"A drill is like an ideal for a guy!"
An ideal, is it?
Then, everyone, we'll continue this
on the radio, and on our homepage!
Please look forward
to the next episode!
Bye-nee!
You know...
Yes?
Those twin-tails.
Oh, the ones I had?
Yeah. The ones you did in live-action.
Yes.
You had sunflowers, right?
I did.
I've seen those before somewhere...
Can it be that...
--How many years ago... My...
--Oh, hold on a minute...
--Ribbit, ribbit!
Boy, was I nervous!
It was very cute, and very nice.
On the first song that you sing,
don't you always get kind of nervous?
Like, will my voice
come out well enough?
You're up next, Miyuki.
I'd like her to sing
"Lots of Memories"...
Why is that?
Oh, can you hand me the mic?
Here. Go for it!
Um, I am not used to
doing something like this,
so please forgive me if it ends up
being painful to your ears.
It's all right! Just do your best!
Oh, how cool and sober.
I see, so that Miyuki
is the connection...
♪ Pleiades in the wind ♪
Even her singing style is cool...
This is a new form of moe, I tell you!
Yuki-chan, you're so cool!
♪ Where did everyone go? ♪
♪ Without even a send-off ♪
♪ Pegasus in the meadow ♪
♪ Venus in the street corner ♪
♪ Where did everyone go? ♪
♪ Without someone looking over you ♪
♪ The stars on the ground ♪
♪ Nobody remembers them ♪
♪ People are always staring at the sky ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Tsukasa here.
Wait, time's up already?
Next episode: Energetic
Despite Not Being Myself.
"Energetic Despite Not Being Myself"
Look forward to it!