By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
By Tsukuyomi Sasami
Myth
「The Hare of Inaba」
Once upon a time, there was a very cute and intelligent bunny.
One day, the bunny was having a hard time getting across the river.
Suddenly, a shark appeared.
A bunny! Sasami is a bunny!
The shark looked very suspicious, but the bunny, being a genius and all, proposed an idea.
Hey, Mr. Shark, can I step on you?
I didn't think the hare of Inaba would be so straightforward!
But hey, if you're going to step on me,
you can be as straightforward as you'd like!
Yay!
Using the shark as a foothold, the bunny managed to get across the river.
Thank you, Mr. Shark.
According to the actual story,
the hare gets her fur ripped off.
In other words...
Since we're humans, I get to take
your clothes off and embarrass you!
Don't lust after your little sister!
Huh? What are you doing, Paparin?
Looks like you get abused even in parallel worlds.
Greetings mighty goddesses!
Do you care to listen to my story?
You see, I...
Hmph. Big mistake there, bud.
As a fish, you should know to not to talk to gods.
Lemme try!
That was refreshing.
The three gods left while feeling no
remorse for following the original tale.
The shark was dying, all alone,
but when he looked up, he discovered he was being enveloped in a warm light.
Mr. Shark, I shall give you this
medicine to show my gratitude.
A benevolent god appeared at last and healed the shark's wounds.
Oh, no one's ever been this nice to me before.
In order to thank you for your kindness, I will...
I will offer my life to you, the
beautiful and benevolent Sasami,
and swear to serve you for etern—
Sasami?
Why don't you come to school today?
You pervert!
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
It all starts at the tips of gods' fingers
watashi no kisetsu tachi
They are where my seasons begin
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
This is a song much longer than the stars
nemuri wo yusaburu uta
A song that will wake you from your sleep
Sasami@Unmotivated
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
When I covered my ears walking in the crowd
watashi ga kieta mitai datta
It felt as if I had disappeared
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa
Yes, I want to express my true feelings,
zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm too immature to use pretty words
deatta kouya no hana
I see flowers blooming in the wild
kowakute yasashikute
They're fearful and gentle
fureta shunkan ni jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I brush through them,
it turns dioramas into realities
kamisama no itazura de egakareta
The map of my future is drawn by the gods
watashi no miraichizu
Drawn by mere whims of the gods
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
It rings with thousands of sounds
oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
And breaks through tomorrow, chasing after today
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
When we tightened our bonds under the watch of the stars
nukumori ga mieta yo
I found your warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our bond forms with the blood we shed
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
But it's the kind of bond I'm compelled to keep
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 3
You lose if you work
Sasami's report. Chapter 5, revision 2.
"The power of Amaterasu."
My brother, Tsukuyomi Kamiomi, holds the power of Amaterasu.
People with Her power can alter the world to their liking.
With just one wish, the Myriad Gods will begin to alter the environment.
Yes, how may I help you, Sasami?
Food
Food.
Yes, right away.
However, he doesn't realize that he has this power.
Yes, he still thinks I have Her power.
My family, the Tsukuyomi family,
are descendants of the first human being
who obtained Her power, Ninigi-no-Mikoto.
We're hidden away in the Tsukuyomi Shrine,
located deep in the mountains of Kyushu.
There, we train to inherit and protect the power of Amaterasu,
in addition to altering the world in favor of human beings.
We're what you call a mysterious family.
I was born in the isolated
environment of the Tsukuyomi Shrine
and I underwent training to become a vessel for Her power.
The strict discipline and training regiment I went
through each day was akin to being tortured in hell.
I had believed that I was living a normal life.
But one day, I snapped. I couldn't stand the training and ran away from home.
I descended upon civilization and saw a city for the first time.
When I went inside a manga cafe and discovered the Internet,
my world got turned upside down.
I was caught immediately and got escorted back home,
but I began to question my way of life.
Ever since, I began frequently running away from home to see the world through the Internet,
or to escape into virtual reality.
Yearning for my own normal life, I took my brother—
What's the matter, Sasami?
Red Blue's out.
Right. I'll go buy some immediately.
I took my brother—
Thank you for waiting.
That was quick.
I'll leave the other one in the fridge.
I took my bro—
What are you writing?
Don't look, you pervert!
Oh, were you writing about something embarrassing?
You shouldn't keep secrets from your brother.
Now, tell your brother about your embarrassing adult problems. Spare me no details!
Get out!
Let's see... Where was I?
Oh, right.
I took my brother and ran away from the Tsukuyomi Shrine.
But my family wouldn't let me off just like that.
There's probably some alteration that's currently hiding our whereabouts.
But with the Valentine's and Yamatano Orochi SNS incidents,
they may be on to us.
How much longer will my peaceful, unmotivated life last—
What the hell? What's going on?
What's wrong, Sasami?
Brother, what do I do? I...
Oh! Alas, the day when my love gets rewarded has arrived!
Very well.
Leave everything to me.
Now, let's move to the bed.
Shut up, idiot!
Listen to me!
Stop being so horny!
Oh? I thought you wanted me to sleep
with you because you had a nightmare?
Oh, of course.
Jeez, I was thinking about something else.
That's not it!
Look at this.
I wonder what happened to me...
Yes, this is truly mysterious.
You're already in high school, but these don't appear to be growing.
Brother!
I have nerves running to it.
Will it hurt if I cut it off?
Goodness, what is the matter, Sasami?
Brother, do you know what this is?
An arm? What about it?
It's an alteration...
He doesn't realize something's wrong.
I've decided to call this a sarcoma for the time being.
Sasami's report. Chapter 13.
Postscript.
My family, the Tsukuyomi family, is short-lived.
In order to maintain the most optimal bodies to harbor Amaterasu's power,
we resort to incest, which slowly deteriorates our bodies.
The women of the family become priestesses, training their spirituality to maintain Amaterasu's power.
When the time came, I inherited
Amaterasu's power into my body.
In order to not use it for my personal gains, I was
drugged to strip away any form of desire from me.
The men of the family become slaves to assist the
priestesses, risking their lives to protect them, look after them,
and ultimately become tools for impregnation.
My brother hid his face and lived in the shadows like a ninja.
He had no qualms about his way of life, much like a robot.
If I were to order him to kill himself, he would happily oblige.
And I take advantage of my brother.
My brother will never betray me.
My brother will never harm me.
My brother will always love me.
No matter how ugly I may be,
or how horrible of a woman I am,
my brother will accept me, support me, and protect me.
That is why when I ran away from the shrine, I took him with me.
I'm never going back.
I don't care about the world.
I was already at my limit.
When I ran away, I was trembling in fear, regret, and sin.
My brother hugged me.
He never said a single word at the shrine, but that night he didn't stop talking until I fell asleep.
"It'll be okay, Sasami. Please don't be afraid. Please don't cry.
You're free now.
Hold your head high knowing that, and live as happily as you can."
"Pain..."
Pain
"Pain, regret, guilt...
Give me anything you don't want.
I'll endure it for you.
That is my duty.
That is the meaning of my lfie."
That is why he fulfilled his duty
What?
Why are you moving on your own?
H
E
L
O
OLLEH
Yes. You and I are two
different "personalities"
Different
"personalities"
What... are you?
"I was set up by the people at the shrine."
"I am the personality that split away from you when you were drugged. I can take over in cases of emergencies."
They did that to me?
"Don't worry, my duty is to protect you.
I am only saying hello because your job is over.
You are safe now."
Safe?
"Your greatest threat is the hunters from the Tsukuyomi Shrine.
Once you're caught, you'll never escape again.
They will drug you and hypnotize you and forever isolate you from the real world."
"But what the shrine wants is the power of Amaterasu, not Tsukuyomi Sasami.
And at the moment, Her power resides in..."
You didn't!
"While you were asleep, I simply showed this report to him.
He came to a conclusion. In order to protect you, he is going back to the shrine in your place."
Someone please...
Just for today...
Someone please help me...
Stupid Brother...
Dammit.
'Sup.
You okay?
You're a girl.
What are you gonna do if your face gets scratched?
Lemme see.
Don't cry. You did your best.
I didn't... even try.
I thought I could live without trying.
I thought I'd be happy if I could live my own life, away from home.
But I just made my brother live for me.
I just placed all my weight on his shoulders.
Don't push yourself.
I won't have it.
He's my brother.
He can't just take everything and go far away.
All I've done is cause him problems,
and I've yet to give him anything in return.
Trying your best and pushing
yourself are two different things.
You're still a kid, so you're allowed to have someone hold your hand as you walk.
That's not being overdependent.
That's called trust.
If you've got family problems, come talk to me.
I'm your family.
Where am I?
The Tsukuyomi Shrine.
It's been a while since I've come here.
You've been here before?
Let's talk as we walk.
I could've destroyed this place when I wanted to,
but they said they would manage the
stupid gods for me, so I just let them be.
Does that mean...
Long ago, the creator gods, Izanagi and Izanami, gave
me the absolute authority to maintain this country.
You're...
Amaterasu, the god almighty?
But the Myriad Gods would just do as they please, not listening to a single word I said.
So I said screw it. Went to live in a cave, but I got dragged out.
Got real fed up after that, so I gave my power to Ninigi-no-Mikoto and went into hiding.
Ame-nigishi-kuni-nigishi-amatsuhiko-
hiko-ho-no-ninigi-no-Mikoto.
My distant ancestor.
I was thinking about going back to work once he died,
but he passed the almighty power down to his descendant in an unthinkable manner.
Incest...
He had a kid with very similar
DNA and passed my power down.
But the world the humans made wasn't so bad, so I decided to watch over it.
Kind of like what you're doing:
Making sure the guy with your
power doesn't do anything stupid,
but still making him do all of the tedious stuff for you.
You're not going to get it back?
I'm tired of godhood.
If I'm going to get my power back, I want to
have someone much younger to succeed me.
Like her.
Tama?
Time to eat!
Thank you very much.
She's a new god I created using a part of myself.
She was originally a part of me, so I call her my sister.
All I've told her is that the almighty god gave birth to her.
So that's why she calls my brother "Paparin"...
Bow down to me.
This is a shrine, after all.
Kagami?
You shall be cleansed by the color red.
This is a shrine, after all.
Kagami's similar.
She was created after I cut off a part of myself that had been cursed.
But some evil person found her and raised her.
She was modified into a cold-hearted
robot with magical and modern weapons.
A robot created from a god...?
I didn't fancy the idea of being used for evil, so I took her in and now I'm raising her.
Pray for your life.
This is a shrine, after all.
Get it? You pray at a shrine.
So... what are you doing here?
We're destroying this shrine.
Why do you think we showed up?
Normally, we're one with the world and lack a perceivable existence.
So why do you think we're here?
Why?
Because you wished for us.
You wished for us Yagami sisters to protect your peaceful everyday life.
That's exactly what I'm gonna do.
Now, let's get your stupid brother and go back to living our ridiculous lives.
All right!
Sister, there's a problem.
I don't see Mr. Tsukuyomi anywhere.
I can smell him! I'm positive he was here,
but he's nowhere to be seen!
Hey, can I ask you something?
Miss Sasami!
I didn't know you returned!
Hey, do you know where my brother is?
Kamiomi came back a bit ago,
but he got kicked out soon after.
He was making this crazy claim that he had the power of Amaterasu,
and he said he would he would
become a priest in your place.
We checked just to make sure, but he had zero divinity and spirituality.
He was disowned for taking you away from here,
but he had the gall to come back spewing nonsense!
The master got angry and threw him out.
So... what's going on here?
I made a huge mistake.
It seems like Amaterasu's power had resided in me all along.
I just wished for my brother to live happily,
and the gods who responded to my wish had in turn granted my brother's wish.
Be right back
I thought I had lost my power, but in reality, I just wasn't able to use my power to its full potential.
I was in pain every time I went outside was because
apparently some evil god was doing something to me.
But...
I'm okay now.
I can live under the sun now.
Reflecting
Now, let's go, Sasami.
Sasami@Unmotivated
Anyway...
I guess I'll start trying today.
In times of troubles, the main act has been called!
I'm Tsurugi!
The duty of us three sisters is to
support Sasami in being a lazy cow.
So this time, we'll be singing the song!
We'll never give the mic back to you, Sasami!
Go ahead.
Tsurugi, I want to join too!
I love singing.
Okay! Then let's sing together.
The only place you can hear the almighty god of Japanese mythology, Amaterasu's voice is on Sasami@Unmotivated!
Yay!
Looking disappointed, you laugh.
Hey, let's go home!
I'm going home too!
I can hear you!
Teach, it's fine if I don't sing along, right?
If you could, I'd really like you to sing along.
After all, you're just like Sasami...
Please don't compare me to that failure of a person.
Then could you please tell her to
put a little more effort into living?
She might just listen to you.
Why is that?
I think we'll find out very soon.
Oh, the song is about to end.
Thanks for singing along, ladies.
So I can leave now?
Unmovitated Cooking Show
It's time for the unmotivated cooking show.
The dish we're making today is a classic beef stroganoff.
Classic Beef Stroganoff
The ingredients needed are beef, onions, mushrooms, tomato, red wine, butter, bouillon, and paprika.
Serves four
Beef
Onion
1 medium
sized
Mushroom
Tomato
1 medium
sized
Red wine
mL
Butter
1 teaspon
Bouillon
To taste
Get someone else to buy them.
Paprika
To taste
When you want to eat, stomp the floor with your heels,
and the cooked dish will magically appear in front of your door.
Try it. It's very easy.
Next time, on episode 4:
Next Time
Episode Two
Leeching off
your family
Leeching off your family.