You lied to us.
You did ask me to make you a Puella Magi.
You just didn't ask about the details.
Why didn't you tell us?
You didn't ask.
It's easier if you don't know.
Mami never even found out.
You humans aren't even aware of your souls.
They exist in your neurons, in your beating hearts.
If your body dies, your spirit is annihilated.
I took out your souls and gave them a form
so they'd be easier to keep safe.
That way, fighting Witches would be a bit safer.
How dare you, without telling us!
You're too naive to fight like that.
If you got a spear stuck right through your torso,
how much do you think it would hurt?
This is true pain.
If you were hit just once, you won't even be able to move.
You were able to fight Kyoko as long as you did
because you were shielded from that pain.
You can do that because your body and soul are separated.
That's the only reason you survived that battle.
If you go further, you won't feel pain at all.
But then your movements will be slower, so I don't recommend it.
Why? Why does it have to be this way?
Because you agreed to fight in exchange for your wish.
And I did make that wish come true, didn't I?
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 7     Can you face your real feelings?
Stand up!
Show respect!
Homura, you knew?
Why didn't you say something?
I've tried before. No one believed me.
Why would Kyubey do something so cruel?
He doesn't believe he's being cruel.
Human values don't mean anything to him.
It's simply payment for the miracle...
is how he'll reply.
That's ridiculous!
He turned Sayaka into that!
She just wanted to heal the man she loves!
A miracle is still a miracle.
She made the impossible come true.
Even if Sayaka Miki had spent her life caring for him,
he would never have been able to play.
Even a whole life doesn't normally buy a miracle.
But that's exactly what he's selling.
You mean she can never have a normal life back?
I told you to give up on Sayaka Miki.
But she saved my life!
If Sayaka hadn't become a Puella Magi,
Hitomi and I would have died!
Don't confuse gratitude with responsibility.
There is no way you can save her.
You don't owe her anything. You don't have to pay her back.
Don't get into matters that don't concern you.
Homura, how can you always be so cold?
Maybe...
It's because I'm no longer human.
How can I face Kyosuke like this?
Stop moping around, you dunderhead!
Come out for a bit. We need to talk.
So you regret it now, do you?
Being transformed into this...
I think I'm okay with it.
I needed this kind of power to do the things I've done.
There's nothing to regret.
You're just paying for what you get.
Yep, I'm paying fair and square.
If you're just living for yourself, it's all up to you.
No hard feelings. No regrets.
If you think like that, everything's fine.
Why did you bring me here?
This is going to take a while.
Wanna eat?
Don't waste food...
or I'll kill you.
This used to be my dad's church.
He was kind and honest, to a fault.
He was the type who cried when he read the morning newspaper.
He believed you needed a new creed to reach a new age.
He began preaching things different from the main church.
Obviously, everyone left his church.
The main body excommunicated him.
No one wanted to hear what he said.
No surprise there. He looked like some kind of cult.
He tried to preach the right things, common sense...
but no one would listen.
We didn't have enough to eat.
I didn't understand. He wasn't saying anything wrong.
Just something different.
If they'd listen for just five minutes,
they'd all realize he was right.
But no one would.
I couldn't stand it. I couldn't take it.
I couldn't watch people refuse to listen to him.
So I asked Kyubey to make people try to understand him.
The next morning, his church was full.
More people came to follow him by the day.
I went public as a Puella Magi.
No matter how many people followed him, they couldn't fight against the Witches.
So I took that as my job, like an idiot.
I thought my dad and I were saving the world, on the stage and behind the scenes.
Eventually, Dad found out my secret.
That all those people had come by magic, not because they believed.
He scolded me and called me a witch that manipulated peoples' minds.
Isn't that a joke? I was the one fighting real Witches.
Dad broke down.
It was the worst thing for him.
He got drunk, went mad, and killed the entire family.
Only I was left.
My wish destroyed my family.
I wished without understanding people, and it made everyone suffer.
That was when I made up my mind.
Never to use my magic for anyone else.
The power was only for me.
Miracles aren't free.
When you wish for hope, it creates an equivalent despair.
Happiness evens out and the world stays in balance.
Why are you telling me this?
You should just do what you want.
Live paying for what you bring on yourself.
That's weird.
Aren't you supposed to be thinking just about yourself?
Why are you worrying about me?
You're starting with the same mistake I did.
You shouldn't live with regrets.
You've already paid more than enough.
You should try and get back some change.
Like you?
Yeah. I've learned from my mistake, but you're still making it.
I can't just watch that.
I think I misunderstood you.
I apologize for that. Sorry.
But I don't regret making a wish to help someone.
If I regret that, those feelings will become fake.
Why do you...
I don't think I paid too much.
I can use this power to do good.
By the way, where did you get those apples?
You can't say.
Then I can't eat it.
I can't appreciate you giving it to me.
You idiot! We're Puella Magi!
No one else can understand us!
I'll fight the way I want to.
If I get in your way, you can try to kill me again.
I'm not going to lose.
No hard feelings.
Morning, Sayaka!
Good morning, Sayaka!
Uh, morning!
Where were you yesterday?
I just didn't feel well...
Sayaka...
It's okay. I'm all right.
Don't worry about me.
All right! Today, I'll...
Oh, Kamijo's out of the hospital?
You feeling better, Kamijo?
I'm not going to get better staying at home.
I'll be off my crutches next week.
That's great for Kamijo.
Yeah...
Get over there, Sayaka. You haven't talked to him yet.
No, I'm fine.
What's this about?
It's about love.
I've been keeping a secret from you and Madoka.
For a long time, I've been in love with Kyosuke Kamijo.
Really?
I didn't expect that from you. He's quite a catch, isn't he?
You've known Kyosuke for a long time.
Yeah, I guess... I mean, it's not really a...
Is that all?
I've decided to be honest with myself.
What about you?
Can you face your real feelings?
What do you mean?
You're a precious friend to me.
I have no intention of stealing anything from you.
You stare at Kamijo even more than me.
You deserve to try before me.
Hitomi?
Tomorrow after school, I'll confess to Kamijo.
I'm giving you one day.
Make sure you have absolutely no regrets.
If you want to tell him how you feel or not.
I...
Madoka...
Can I go with you?
I don't want to leave you alone.
Why... Why are you so nice?
I don't deserve this...
No...
I've just started having regrets today.
I thought maybe if I hadn't saved Hitomi...
Just for a second.
I'm a failure as a hero.
I can't face Mami now.
Hitomi is going to take Kyosuke away!
And there's nothing I can do about it!
Because I'm already dead! A zombie!
I can't hug him with this body!
I can't kiss him!
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Sayaka...
I'm okay now. I needed to get it out.
Come on. Let's go beat up a Witch!
It's not like you to just watch.
She's fighting a Witch tonight, not a Familiar.
A Grief Seed should drop. It's not a waste.
So you're giving her your prey?
Idiot! She's going to lose!
Sayaka!
Oh my god, I can't watch this.
Get back. I'll show you how it's done.
Hey!
Go away. I can handle this alone.
Sayaka!
Oh come on. Did you...?
You're right! If I do it this way...
It doesn't hurt at all!
Stop...
Please stop...
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Kamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate God Himself
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Takashi Tensugi
I'll be a different kind of Puella Magi from all of you.
I've decided.
I don't need any payment.
I won't use magic just for myself.
Episode 8     I'm such a fool
I'm such a fool.