It's morning, huh...
Yeah...
In the end, we couldn't sleep, huh...
All thanks to that...
What are we going to do about today's "Scare Minorin, Enter the White Knight" plan?
While we're already scared, will we be able to scare Kushieda?
Oh, shut up.
If we don't do it, the future won't change!
I know that, but...
What should we do?
Something Minorin will be scared of...
What do you mean by "something Minorin will be scared of"?
Ki—
You're up early! Kitamura.
What kind of foul plans are you plotting so early in the morning?
Foul plans, you say...
Huh? Maybe...
the culprits of what Kushieda was fretting over yesterday were you two?
So that's how it is, huh?
Sheesh, why is that?
Don't you feel sorry for Kushieda?
No, that's not—
I-It's a present.
Present?
Mi-Minorin is extremely fond of horror.
She said she loves being surprised and getting scared, so I wanted to make some summer memories—
Hey, Kitamura.
I see now.
So that's why instead of her being scared, her eyes were glowing with avarice.
All right! Make me your accomplice!
Huh?
Why don't we work together
and make Kushieda genuinely frightened!
No, look—
Oh, yeah. I'll invite Ami too.
Stupid chi' too?
She's bound to be familiar with the area.
All right! We'll strike while the iron is hot!
No, but Kawashima won't do it!
Leave it to me!
I'll definitely talk her into it!
Worry, do not!
Wh... What should we do, Ryuuji?
"What", you ask...
Nothing we can do.
Seaweed...
Fireworks
Oh, my. Even though I was planning to make breakfast, I got beaten to it.
Morning, Takasu-kun!
Y-Yeah.
Huh? What are you making?
Ah, lunchboxes.
Everyone said they're gonna be playing at the sea for the whole day today, see.
You got up early for that?!
This won't do!
Chef, this unworthy Kushieda will be of assistance too!
Now, order me as you please!
Y-Yeah.
Then can you slice up the onions?
Yes, wholeheartedly glad to do so!
What's on the menu?
Egg sandwiches and tuna sandwiches.
Also, soup from the leftovers of the curry... I guess.
Yeah! Good! Good!
You're good at that, Kushieda.
Oh? Did you just praise me?
Yay.
With the cleaning yesterday too, you're rather skilled.
Both my parents work, see.
When my little brother was at home, I had to make lunchboxes too.
You have a little brother...
He's an active high school baseball player, Akechi-kun.
Ah, it got in my eye!
Hey! You okay?
I screwed up.
Takasu-kun?
Huh? Ah! Gotta peel the apples!
Takasu-kun's really skilled at cooking.
Yesterday's curry was magnificent too.
It wasn't that big of a thing, though...
I think that diligent side of you is really wonderful.
The rest of the class doesn't know this side of you.
I feel kinda special.
Whoever becomes Takasu-kun's bride will be really happy.
Kyusheda!
What is it, Takyasu-kyun?
A-About yesterday...
Well, about that...
Don't...
tell anyone about that, okay?
Eh?
I haven't talked with anyone else about that.
How should I say this...
I dropped my guard.
I said more than I should have.
But I'm glad it was around Takasu-kun.
Thank you for listening.
Oh! Not good!
You clumsy-dumsy!
Aren't you the cute one?!
D-Don't call me cute!
Just kidding.
But, Chef, what shall we do next?
Oh, right...
Shall we mix it?
Shall we mix it with real force?!
The sunlight's burning today too!
Komachi Angel!
Minorin's so energetic...
Then we'll do it according to plan.
Huh? What about Kawashima?
She's helping out, right?
Yeah! With Ami's guidance, we set up traps in a nearby cave.
Then we'll get nowhere without her help.
What's she doing?
Dunno.
I'll go get her.
Taiga, take care of this.
He-Hey!
Here!
I'll carry it.
It's heavy for girls, right?
I-It's fine.
I'll be fine.
Kawashima? You there?
I am.
Everyone's gone on ahead.
Jeez, what are you do—
I was admiring myself.
Takasu-kun, want to look too?
You're really...
Hey, hey! Isn't this rather risqué?
Just look at this cleavage!
It's fine, isn't it?
That's all?
Ah. You already saw me in a bikini at school.
Not that.
But this part comes off, you know.
Look.
Put it back on! Put it back on!
Eh? Then put it back on.
I refuse!
How cold of you.
If you're going to be like that, I'm not going to help out.
Eh?!
D-Don't say that!
Hey. Why does Takasu-kun want to make Minori-chan enjoy herself?
Wh-Why, you ask...
If you're not going to tell me, I'm not helping out.
You got five seconds, 'kay?
Five...
four...
three...
You sure?
Two...
one...
zero.
Not helping out.
Taiga!
Come at me!
Come on! With impact, now!
With force, now!
Cold!
Just what are they doing?
Hey! Hey! Why?
Because it's, like, boring.
If you're not with us, we won't be able to get around in the caves, right?
I drew you a map, didn't I?
I'm sorry, Yuusaku, but you'll have to do it on your own.
Hey...
No problems with that, right?
Takasu-kun was the one who chose after all.
Sorry, Takasu. That Ami suddenly...
It's fine.
I'll come with you.
Going alone would be difficult, right?
Even so...
If the two of us leave by ourselves, it might look rather suspicious...
It's all right.
I'll somehow manage alone.
I've come up with three price-worthy ideas for traps.
Kushieda will most definitely go half-crazy from fear!
I-I see...
Hey! Kushieda! Aisaka!
What is it?
I'm going to the toilet!
Man! It's so good!
Takasu-kun sure is a cooking prodigy!
No, Kushieda helped me out after all...
Huh? Minorin did?
Yeah!
That egg sandwich was mixed with force by yours truly!
Oh! Lunch while I'm not around?
Jeez, Kitamura-kun!
Just what are you?!
Announcing to girls with a loud voice that you're going to the toilet!
Yeah, sorry.
And besides, you were gone for so long. Just what—
Everything's all set.
Y-Yeah.
Speaking of long—
What? What? What's this consultation?
Oh, Kushieda. You see, actually—
Hey, Minori-chan.
Towards the cove there's a really pretty cave, you see.
Cave, you say?!
It's my special place.
Special place?!
Wanna take a stroll over there later?
Wah! A stroll!
Sounds good! Let's go! Let's go!
I can't wait!
Heh, so it's here!
A-min's special stroll...
Danger
What an atmosphere, huh...
Right?
Okay, let's try going in then!
B-But, doesn't it feel like something will come out?
Oh! Like an encounter with an unidentified creature?!
No, if it was a living thing, it'd be fine...
Yeah, let's make sure to capture it alive!
Making him our accomplice was really the right thing to do.
That coaxing's cool too...
All right!
Here we go! Kitamura's Explorers' League!
We're going to find the two-headed golden cobra!
It's dark! It's narrow! I'm scared!
I feel like I've heard that before.
It's unexpectedly spacious.
Around here, yeah.
Hey.
Stop being unfocused.
We didn't come here for a simple test of courage.
You understand?
Y-Yeah.
From here on, it goes down a level, so be careful.
The first barrier.
What?
Fried tofu.
Oh yeah, that's right...
Kitamura's got the brains, but...
...he's an idiot.
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun!
Hey, isn't it getting cold?
Because we've come further in.
No, I didn't mean that...
What's up?
I smell ketchup.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
This...
Blood... writing...?
"Gyaaa," it says.
So this is the second...
Yeah, he's an idiot all right.
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun!
Don't sigh!
What's this?
This is...
Hey, what's wro—
Ta-Ta-Ta-Takasu-kun! That's...!
No, umm...
A woman's hair!
It's the curse of a brokenhearted woman who lost her way inside this cave and died an unnatural death on a trip of grief!
No! Let me out!
Let me leave!
Minorin, calm down!
Nice assist, Takasu.
Let me out!
Let me leave!
Eh?
You set up some traps too, huh?
It's a curse!
No, umm...
My final trap is fifty meters up ahead.
It's terrible!
Look forward to it!
Y-Yeah.
Come on, Kushieda! Get yourself together!
Kitamura-kun's skilled after all.
Minorin's really scared.
It wasn't Kitamura.
Huh?
Of course, not me either...
Th-Then...
It's not part of the setup.
The same as last night... for real...
One, two! Three, four!
Minorin!
It's dangerous alone, let's hold hands!
Really! Let's tie up! Let's tie up real good!
All right! I'm all warmed up now, so let's go on ahead!
Uh, umm...
So stupid.
I'm going to use a shortcut to go back before everyone else.
Hey, Kawashima! Where are you going?
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun!
Are we going even further in?
This is the exit.
Right, Ami?
Where're Ami and Takasu?
Ryuuji...?
I said wait, Kawashima!
Do you really know the way?!
Of course I do.
Are you that uneasy about being separated from the rest?
I'm not really good with...
dark places and such...
Then...
what would Takasu-kun do if I left you behind?
What?!
Would you be scared?
Would you be uneasy from being separated from me?
Would you be lonely?
Would you think that you don't want to be separated from me?
H-Hey.
You need me?
This isn't the time for that.
Do you want to return to Minori as fast as possible?
Like I said!
I don't think that girl suits Takasu-kun.
Wha— it's not like I...
The one who's suitable for Takasu-kun is...
Wh-What?
What?
Huh?
Where...
Where's this?
Huh?!
You're kidding! I'm lost!
Hey! Hey!
You're kidding, right?
I wouldn't kid about something like this!
Wh-What should we do...?
H-Hey...
I-It'll be okay!
I'm sure Kitamura and the others will come looking for us!
Don't be afraid! I'm here with you!
I'm sorry.
No! You don't need to apologize!
That I was lost...
was a lie.
Like I would ever get lost!
D-u-m-m-y.
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop it, Takasu-kun! I'm getting slippery!
This isn't the time to be laughing!
But! Takasu-kun was acting just like a kid!
I was really scared, you know!
Takasu-kun's...
a very dull guy.
You! Again!
But that part of you...
I don't dislike it.
Earlier I said Minori-chan wasn't suited for Takasu-kun, right?
I really meant that.
I mean, Takasu-kun's the moon.
The hell's that?
Minori-chan's the sun.
By being at her side,
I think you'd simply get burned away.
I mean, Takasu-kun wouldn't hit Minori-chan, right?
You can't be equal simply with admiration.
The one you can be equal with would be...
someone like me...
That was—
—Kushieda's voice!
Wai— Takasu-kun!
Sorry, I...
It's fine. Let's hurry!
Y-Yeah!
Kushieda!
Ryuuji!
Takasu! Ami!
You were all right?!
Kitamura, where's Kushieda?
What happened?
Well, that's...
Kushieda was taken by something...
What do you mean by "something"?
I don't know,
but there's something here.
Don't tell me by that, Kushieda was...!
Out of batteries?!
Takasu, lend me yours.
Yeah.
What is it? This sound.
A voice?
Kushieda!
I'm coming now!
Hey! Kitamu—
Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun!
Kitamura-kun! Kitamura-kun!
Wh-What is this?!
Everyone, don't get separated!
For now, stay calm!
I don't care anymore. When it's come to this...
I'm gonna beat it to pieces!
Huh— wha—
Taiga?!
Tai—
Stop! Stop!
Kitamura, an accident has occurred!
We must rescue Taiga!
Acknowledged!
Are you all right, Aisaka?
Kita...
Kitamura-kun...
Kitamura?!
You're late, Akechi-kun.
Ku-Kushieda?
Yes. I am indeed Kushieda Minori.
Also known as Minorin.
The culprit is me!
And...
my partner in crime...
is him!
The hair in Takasu's room...
and the scattered clothes in Taiga's room...
those and everything else was all our doing!
We're sorry.
Well, the way you were trying to scare me was so amateurish, you see.
I ended up wanting to teach you how.
Showing you that this is how you scare people.
That means... you had exposed us already...?
When you two are lurking around like that on your own, yeah.
And that's why I made Kitamura-kun my accomplice
and started trapping you instead.
But I had fun. Thanks.
You're not gonna get mad?
Nah, I won't!
I mean, I really love horror!
Eh?!
You could call it the "Manjuu Kowai" method.
If I say "I'm scared of ghosts," "I'm scared of the occult,"
someone's bound to try to scare me.
That's what I would gladly receive!
And now that we're done telling you the gig...
It's lit!
It's beautiful, right?
Today really was one hell of a day.
Really, that was so much trouble.
About the conversation earlier...
I didn't really give you an answer.
Huh?
I'd be lonely without you around.
Rather, it's not about whether I'd be lonely or not.
Isn't it about whether you'd be lonely or not?
I've never really considered whether I'm lonely or not.
Then consider it.
Properly.
Isn't that a bit painful?
If it gets painful, just straightforwardly express that emotion.
I mean, we're...
Equal?
Hey.
Takasu-kun's really...
kind sometimes.
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
It's the last night. Are you enjoying it?
Kushieda...
Umm...
Yeah?
Th-Thanks.
Huh?
I was completely fooled and utterly frightened,
but when I'm with you, it's fun.
No matter when.
That's my line.
I really had fun too.
And the curry was also really good.
And you listened to my strange little tale without laughing at it.
Takasu-kun properly understood me.
I'm really sorry for scaring you.
I really wanted to show Takasu-kun ghosts
and ended up kinda overdoing it.
Show me?
Yeah.
Because you said you wanted to see ghosts.
Eh? Ah.
Why did Takasu-kun want to scare me?
Eh?
W-Well, that's...
Taiga told me that you were scared of horror.
So you wanted to tease me?
That's not it.
Takasu-kun would never do something to someone that they dislike.
You're the type who's always considering how to make someone happy.
Why did that Takasu-kun do something like this, I wonder.
I really want to know that.
I really think it's strange.
I wanted to show you one.
A ghost.
I wanted to make you believe that ghosts exist.
I think it's too early to give up just because you can't see them.
That's what I figured.
I see.
Takasu-kun, next we'll go find a UFO!
One that isn't a man-made satellite — a real one!
Eh?
And after a UFO, yeah...
A Tsuchinoko!
And then, if we keep finding the things I want to see...
if my world has been changed...
then...
Kushieda!
Huh?
An exploded...
UFO is...
It's like a dream!
I really saw one!
I saw one!
A sudden outbreak of a galactic war, huh?!
The Earth will be protected by us!
The trip continues till you're home, you know!
Everyone, don't let your guard down!
Maybe I should go home to my parents' house after this.
See you later!
Shall we stop by the supermarket and buy some stuff?
I'm tired, so don't talk to me about damn housewife tasks.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, there's a special sale today.
Shut up about that.
Next Episode Preview
Oohashi High School Culture Festival (Part One)
Culture festival:
getting excited from band preformances, chests throbbing from a cosplay café,
heating up one's friendship around a campfire,
and an embarrassing leg-lock at a pro-wrestling show!
What are you plotting...?