I am Tomoe Mami.
Just like both of you, I attend Mitakihara Middle School as a third-year student.
And...
After forming a contract with Kyubey, I'm a magical girl!
Another weird dream...
Morning, Madoka!
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 2
I'd Say, "That's Really Delightful."
Madoka...
Last night, weren't you late getting home?
I was invited to a senpai's house.
Well, I won't say annoying stuff about a curfew or anything, but...
Give me some information before dinner time.
Yeah... I'm sorry.
People really can't see it.
Wow...
What a beautiful room!
I live alone, so don't restrain yourselves.
Although I don't have proper hospitalities prepared, either.
Mami-san, this is really delicious!
It's super good!
Thank you.
Since Kyubey has chosen you two, this is no longer someone else's affair.
I thought a certain degree of explanation was necessary.
Yeah, yeah! Feel free to ask me anything.
Sayaka-chan, that's backward.
Wow, pretty!
This is a Soul Gem.
It is a gem birthed by the contract between Kyubey and a girl who has been chosen.
It gives existence to magical powers, and it is proof that you are a magical girl.
"Contract"?
I can grant you girls a single wish, no matter what it is!
Eh? Really?
A "wish"?
Anything would be fine.
I can make any kind of miracle happen for you.
Things like gold and silver treasure, perpetual youth,
or like a Manchu Han Imperial Feast?
No, the last one is a bit...
However, a Soul Gem is created in exchange for that being done.
Possessing this jewel means the duty of battling witches will be imposed upon you.
Witches?
Hey, Mama.
Hmm?
What if... just what if?
If you were told that magic could grant you any kind of wish, no matter what it is...
What would you—I'd take firing two or so of those executives.
After that, right... the company president too...
I want him to think about retiring soon, since he's already at the age where it's impossible for him to work effectively, but...
there's nobody to replace him, you know.
Oh, really?
What if Mama became the company president?
So I could use that technique.
As long as I firmly secure the necessary arrangements with the sales department,
planning and general affairs will do exactly as they're told...
In that case, the problem would be the baldy from accounting...
Should I pluck it off?
Mama, there's a scary look in your eyes.
What is a witch?
Are they different from magical girls?
If magical girls are born from wishes, then you could say...
Witches are beings born from curses.
Magical girls sprinkle hope, and witches spread despair.
Furthermore, it's vicious since normal humans are unable to see their figures.
Anxiety and suspicion, excessive rage and hatred...
They bring seeds of calamity such as those to the world.
Murders and suicides without clear motives are very likely to be caused by a witch's curse, you know.
They become a formless malice that eats into the insides of a human.
If those guys are so dangerous, why doesn't anyone notice that they exist?
That's because witches are constantly hidden within a magical barrier, so their form is never revealed in public, you know.
The labyrinth-esque area that you two wandered into before was one of them.
That was a fairly dangerous place, you know.
Normally, humans who are swallowed up by those don't get out alive.
Mami-san, you're battling against something that scary?
That's right. My life is certainly at risk.
Therefore, both of you should also choose your path carefully.
Kyubey has chosen both of you, so you have the opportunity to be granted any sort of wish.
However, it is adjoined with death.
Troubling, huh...
I have a proposal regarding that, though.
For a short time, would you two like to accompany me while I exterminate witches?
What it means to battle a witch...
It'd be good for you to find out with your own eyes.
Moreover, you can take time to carefully consider whether you have a wish worth granting or not,
even if it means going so far as to trespass on danger.
Morning!
Good morning.
Morn—
Morning, Sayaka.
Is something troubling you, Sayaka-san?
As I thought, no one can see that one except for us.
Looks like it.
Umm...
Ah, no, it's nothing! Let's go, let's go.
(It seems that we can do things like converse just by thinking in our heads.)
(Eh!? It's so soon, and we already have that kind of magical power!?)
(No, no, right now I'm still just relaying thoughts between you.)
(But it's convenient for talking in secret, right?)
(Somehow this feels weird.)
What has been the matter with both of you since earlier?
You are frequently exchanging looks...
Eh!? No! This is... um... that is...
Could it be... you two have a relationship where you understand everything immediately just by looking eye to eye!?
My! To think that after just a single day, you've gotten that intimate with each other!
Yesterday after I left, just what could have...
No, as you'd expect, that didn't happen.
A lot certainly went on though, you know...
But that mustn't happen, you two! You are both girls!
That's a forbidden...
form of love!
You forgot your bag!
Hitomi-chan is kind of acting like Sayaka-chan today...
What is that supposed to mean!?
(Anyway, like... is it really okay for you to nonchalantly come all the way to school with us?)
(Why?)
(I told you, right?)
(I said, "That girl from yesterday is a transfer student in this class.")
(Wasn't she aiming to take your life?)
(Actually, I consider the school to be safer.)
(Mami is here too.)
(Mami-san is a third-year student, so isn't her class kind of far?)
(No need to worry.)
(I can hear the conversation perfectly.)
(At this amount of distance, we're still in range of telepathy.)
(Ah, um... g–good morning.)
(I'm watching over you properly, so be at ease.)
(Besides, I don't expect even that girl to do something like attack you in public.)
(That's fine, then...)
(Ugh. The shadow of our gossip.)
Is that transfer student also a... um, err...
magical girl?
Just like Mami-san?
That's right, there is no doubt about it.
It looks like she holds a considerable amount of potent power.
But in that case, she's an ally of justice who attacks witches, right?
So what gives? What's her reason for suddenly attacking Madoka?
I was the one she was aiming for.
It seems like she was trying to prevent the birth of new magical girls, you know.
Eh?
Why? If you're fighting the same enemy, aren't more allies a good thing?
That's not how it is.
Instead, it is far more common for it to be competitive, you know.
That's... why?
There is reimbursement in the act of defeating a witch.
Therefore, depending on the circumstances, when you are struggling to achieve victory...
There are times you will clash with each other, too.
In other words, she had established that Kyubey aimed to talk with Madoka from the beginning...
and that's her reason for going so far to get involved since this morning?
I believe that is probably the situation.
(Don't worry, Madoka.)
(After all, if she tries to reprimand you or something, then I'll beat her up for it!)
(We even have Mami-san here, too!)
(That's right.)
(Regardless of Miki-san, I'm here, so it's all right.)
(Be at ease.)
(Don't say "regardless"!)
So, just like we've studied so far,
phrases whose subjects are a person or object performing an action are referred to as actively voiced.
In regards to a phrase being passively voiced, it is when the subject, a person or object,
is on the receiving end of an action, such as "B was acted on by A."
That form of passive voice uses the verb "to be" plus the past participle.
For example, "He likes me." Kare wa watashi no koto ga suki...
Here!
Hey, Madoka...
Have you thought of some wish you want granted?
No...
How about you, Sayaka-chan?
I don't have anything either.
Somehow, well...
I really thought I'd come up with more ideas than I could count, too.
Even though there are tons of things I want to do or get...
When it gets to the point of risking your life for them, that'll really hold you up, won't it?
Like you don't want them to that extent, or something.
Yeah...
How unexpected.
Most girls happily reply immediately, after all.
Well, I'm sure... we're just idiots.
Eh? Is that so?
Yeah. Happy idiots.
It shouldn't be particularly unusual, right?
To have a desire you want fulfilled, even if it means exchanging your life.
There's a great number of people in the world who have problems worth such a thing, aren't there?
That's why... for those of us who can't find anything...
It means we don't know that level of sorrow.
We're too blessed... and have become idiots.
Why... was it us, I wonder...?
Don't you think it's unfair?
There must be other people who truly feel like they want this kind of chance, you know.
Sayaka-chan...
(It's all right.)
Continuing from yesterday?
No, that is not my intention.
I wanted to bring everything to a conclusion before this thing made contact with Kaname Madoka, but...
At this point, I am already too late.
So. What will you do?
Do you intend to become a magical girl too?
I...
You don't have any right to ask that question!
Remember yesterday's conversation?
Yeah...
If so, then fine. I pray that my warning will not be futile.
H–Homura-chan!
U–Umm...
What kind of wish did you have granted to become a magical girl?
Hitomi, sorry. Today we have some minor business...
My, it's a confidential matter?
Um...
How enviable!
Something that could thrust itself between you two...
Doesn't exist anymore, does it!?
No, like I said, that's wrong...
Akemi-san.
Would today work for coming to a café with us on the way home?
I have a bit of urgent business to attend to again today.
I am sorry.
Well... Now then, "Firsthand Magical Girl Experience" full course level one.
Shall we do it in high spirits?
Are your preparations okay?
I'm not sure how it'll do for preparations, but...
I brought this!
I thought it'd be better than nothing.
Well... if you have that kind of determination, it'll be helpful.
Madoka, did you bring something?
Eh!?
Um... for me...
Wow...
F–For now, I thought I would just consider clothing...
Yup.
If it's enthusiasm, you have enough, surely!
I give up! I lost to you!
This is a trace of the magical power left behind by yesterday's witch.
Basically, searching for a witch means relying on your legs.
That is, a Soul Gem grasps the witch's presence, and you proceed by following it.
That's surprisingly simple, isn't it?
The light isn't changing at all, is it?
That's because it has been a full night since we let her slip away, after all.
There are not many footprints that remain.
At that time, if you had immediately chased after her...
It's unknown whether I would have taken her out or not, but...
That was not enough of a priority for me to ignore you two.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Yup! As I thought, Mami-san is an ally of justice!
On the other hand... that transfer student really irritates me!
I wonder if... she's truly a bad girl?
Hey, Mami-san...
Don't you at least have an approximate target on the witch's current location?
Witch curses influence a relatively large number of traffic accidents and other incidents resulting in injury, you know.
Therefore, it's advantageous to check large roads and entertainment districts where quarrels often occur.
In addition, unpopular locations that may attract suicides.
And then, it's the worst when they possess something like a hospital.
Since even under normal circumstances only weak people are there, and their vitality is sucked out of them...
It becomes something too horrible to look at.
This is a considerably strong surge of magic.
It may be close...
There's no mistaking it. It's here.
Mami-san, that's...!
The mark of a witch's kiss...
Just as I thought.
Is this person...?
It's all right. She has only become unconscious.
Let's go.
Today, she definitely won't escape.
Amazing!
It's merely consolation, but...
For defending yourself, this helps more than nothing.
Absolutely never leave my side, okay?
Okay!
Stay away! Stay away!
How is it?
Are you two scared?
I–I'm not anything like that!
I'm scared, but...
Keep at it!
Soon we'll be at the deepest part of the barrier!
Look. That is a witch.
Grotesque.
You're going to fight... with something like that?
It's all right.
Do you think I would lose?
Stay back.
Mami-san!
It's all right.
I cannot show myself to my future kouhai...
in such an uncool state, can I!?
That was disappointing, you know.
★ Tiro・Finale!! ★
She won?
Amazing!
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch egg.
E–Egg?
If you have good fortune, witches will be carrying one of these every now and then.
It's okay.
In that condition, it's safe.
Actually, it's a helpful and precious object.
My Soul Gem's color has become a bit impure since last night, hasn't it?
Come to think of it...
However, if a Grief Seed is used...
Look.
It became pure.
See?
With this, my exhausted magical power has been restored.
The reimbursement for defeating witches that I spoke of before... is this.
There should be at least one more use remaining.
I give it to you...
Akemi Homura-san.
It's her...
Or, I wonder if you are dissatisfied with sharing among people?
It was your game.
It should belong only to you.
I see. That's your answer, then.
Kuu～!
That one really does give me a bad feeling!
It would be good to get along with each other...
If both people feel that way, yes.
This place is... huh?
I...
N–No... Why did I...
Such a thing... How come? That kind of thing...
It's all right. It's all right now.
You just... saw a bad dream for a little bit, that's all.
It feels like the case is closed, doesn't it...?
Yeah.
Finding something like a wish I want granted...
For me, it's too hard, and I can't decide on something right away, but...
Still, Mami-san's appearance as she perseveres for the sake of helping people is very wonderful.
If even someone like me... can really help somebody in that sort of way...
I'd say, "That's really delightful."
That's what I thought.
Waving my hand, I say
"Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
Forcing myself to laugh, I become lonely...
無理に笑って　寂しくなって・・・
Distant car horns at the traffic light of an intersection
交差点信号　遠くのクラクション
The laughing voice of an unknown stranger
知らない誰かの　笑いあう声
Today I walk alone while coming and going through familiar streets
今日は一人で歩く　通い慣れた街
But somehow, compared to usual...
でもいつもよりもなんだか・・・
It seems as if I'm a bit smaller
自分がちょっと　小さく思えるよ
Waving my hand, I say
"Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたねって　手を振って
Fabricating a smiling face, I become lonely
笑顔を作って　寂しくなって
In truth we haven't talked enough yet, but...
ほんとはまだ　話し足りないけど・・・
The words "Well then, see you again later!"
それじゃまたね　って言葉で
Tell the lie "We'll meet again."
「また会える」って　嘘をついて
I say it while smiling as usual
いつも通りの　笑顔で言うよ
See you again tomorrow...
また　あした・・・
Only forcing yourself to put on an appearance...
Even though you're scared and you can barely handle it, you can't go to anyone for consultation.
You can do nothing but cry alone.
It isn't a pleasant thing... to be something like a magical girl.
Episode 3
Nothing Is Scary Anymore
Nothing is scary anymore.
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net