WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the original character designer:
蒼樹うめ(Aoki Ume) - affectionately called ウメス(Umesu), うめ先生(Ume-sensei), or てんてー(Tentee).
Okay, well then, let's continue. It's Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika episode two audio commentary!
Yes!
Yes~!
With the role of Madoka Magi—... Madoka, I'm Yuuki Aoi!
Ahahaha~
Yup, and with the role of Akemi Homura, this is Saitou Chiwa.
I look forward to working with you!
In episode one, you know... we had Kitamura Eri-san as a guest.
Yup, yup.
Our episode two guest, is this person!:
Yes!
Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika character designer, Aoki Ume-sensei!
Yaaaaay! *clapclap*
Yaaaaaay~!
I'm sorry for intruding~
I look forward to working with you.
Ume-tentee is cute!
Sensei is so cute~!
Amazing, my position hasn't changed but it's like you completely outrank me...
Yeah that's right, it's like we're the mini mini squad today.
(lol)
That's right.
The two of us.
By a scale of 10,000.
Ne~ I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
Now then, now then, it's episode two...
That's right.
Mm!
When you first heard about this, did you have any impressions, Ume-sensei?
The very beginning?
Yes.
When it was like, "let's create this work", how was that planned?
When it was like, "let's create this work"... how was that planned
Um well, the producer Iwakami-san had contacted me,
Yes.
and then there was Shaft-san's director Shinbou, and Urobuchi-san.
How did you–To an extent without spoilers, how did this piece of work's concept feel?
If we're talking about my very first time hearing about it,
It was a mahou shoujo-feeling thing, but in Urobuchi-san's style,
and for me, it was kinda like... I heard various things, and then it was basically like "Would you like to do something fun?"
Ehh~ I see.
Um, did you read the script before creating the characters?
Um... before designing, the very first thing we had to do was the settei for this sort of sekaikan...
How many characters should there be?
What kind of items would fit?
That is what was done in the very beginning, yes.
Ohh.
So, from that point forward, what happened with the tentative draft's development?
In the very beginning, well, we roughly made a summary and went from there, you know...
Ah, I see.
Is that so...
Um well, each of the individual characters have their own image color, which personally left a big impression on me...
Mm, mm.
Mm!
Everyone has their own individual image color, don't they?
Mm, mm.
In the beginning, how were the colors for Ume-sensei to use decided?
Yes.
Um... Urobuchi-san certainly gave me all the of image colors for the characters, though...
Ahh!
Ahhh!
I certainly had to follow those directions (lol)
Ohh!
It was on my mind while sketching.
Eh, so how was that like?
Who was it really on your mind for?
Eh? Who...?
H–Homura is probably the one who was most, if I'm not mistaken.
Ohh!
Ehh?
How was the feeling in that?
Well, I was told to "make someone red" or such. And that's all I was told.
Um, when it came time to draw, I certainly completely forgot that (lol)
Ah... Is that so?
Ehh?
There are characters that I hadn't forgotten about it for, and others I did (lol)
Eh is that so?
Ehh?
When you first created the characters, which girl was the easiest, and which gave you the most hardship?
Right, let's see...
Really, Madoka ended up being pretty simple and quick.
Ohh.
Mm, mm, mm.
Madoka, and... Homura wasn't all that hard either.
Oh, is that so?
Ohh.
Mami wasn't really very troubling either (lol)
Ehh?
Sayaka had difficult parts.
Eh!?
Uwa, is that so? Why?
Um, her personality is considerably boyish...
Ahhh, I see.
Ahhh~
So overdoing the boyish look for her would be a bit...
It might be too strong of an impression, I thought.
I see.
Ah, right, then there's this guy, right?
Mou, QB-san.
Ahh, QB-san!
Mou, he can completely dampen our mood.
QB-san, you know...
QB-san!
QB-saaaan~
Anywhere and everywhere it's QB-san, you know.
Ah, you're using that pronunciation?
Mou, somehow, I've been saying "QB"-san lately too.
QB-san is Beh-san...
(lol) Mou, mou, mou.
(lol)
QB-san was considerably hard.
Ehh?
Right.
L–Like what parts, for example?
Um, making him cute. Really cute!
Ahh.
Ah~, cute~!
That's right!
Well in terms of looks, he is cute.
He has his quirks.
(lol)
Mou... QB-san, you know! Really now...
Was his main outline decided by something like a cat or a fox?
Ah, um...
I wasn't really going out of my way to make something like a cat, or any other animals...
Ehh?
Is that right...
It was "Make a mahou shoujo small animal."
Something really cute.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ah~
He's cute, really cute... well, his cute parts are cute enough.
That's right~
(lol)
Then, um, Ume-sensei you've done work with director Shinbou and SHAFT-san before, with the Hidamari Sketch series...
Mm, mm.
Yes!
For us it's a delicate situation, if it's our first time working with people.
Mm, mm.
From your position, Ume-sensei, I'd love to hear your impressions on the group of people you work with.
Yes.
Mm, mm.
...
They're fun people... or something.
(lol)
(lol) You say that with a smile that looks like it's hiding something (lol)
Saying it to other people is very tough, but...
Oh...
They're really fun people... really warm people...
Extremely original, and...
Then still, they have a very established and experienced-type feeling to them.
It's like an amazing ambivalence, it's kinda mysterious...
Ne~!
But it feels like they don't really reveal things to other people.
Yeah, I really get that.
Certainly for this–especially for this(lol), Madoka☆Magika, it really felt that way...
That's right~
Even for us, when we first saw Ume-sensei's characters during auditions,
Mm, mm.
we thought "What is this!? So cute!"
Cute!
Then after reading the script we were like "Arere~?"
(lol)
"There are quite a few depressing lines, aren't there?"
Ne!
Ah, you mean the lines in the auditions?
That's right, there were all sorts of them.
We had the sekaikan explained to us a little bit, so we knew "somehow or another," but...
Ah, I see.
Mm.
Ah, ne?
(lol)
Ne!
Who'd have thought it was to this extent?
Ne?
Right now we're on episode two, though.
(lol)
It's quite amazing.
That's right...
Actually, well, this is a bit of a different matter, but with this volume, there'll be a drama CD included...
Mm, mm.
Ah, that's right, ne.
It's relative to episode ten, which will air before this volume comes out, but...
But there has been a drama CD relating to that episode ten attached this time...
And so, for those of you who might've thought to listen to a drama CD when this volume is your first time watching...
Mm!
You should really hold out for a little while until you see episode ten!
It's a drama CD you'll want to listen to, though...
That's right.
Somehow, you know, a lot of things which are hidden happen in this piece of work, so it's very prone to spoilers.
Right.
That's right, isn't it?
But if they listen to it, they might not understand it, you know.
That's right.
They might just be like "What is this world?"
It may give off the feeling like parallel world.
That's right.
Well, in a certain meaning it might be a parallel world.
That's true~!
Or something.
Deep down, Ume-sensei, what impressions do you hold towards this piece of work called Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika?
This is a bit of a vague question, but... yeah.
Like when people are trying to find out what kind of piece of work this is, or they ask you "what kind of series is it?"
Right, right?
It's actually pretty hard to say anything, since there isn't a lot you can say...
So for you, Ume-sensei, who is aware of the ending...
Right.
What do you say?
That's right, ne...
Well, the title has "Mahou Shoujo" attached to it... and you could say it really is a mahou shoujo thing,
it is able to leave behind some of that feeling, but you know...
Isn't this actually more like a "human drama" between middle schoolers?
Ahh~
And courage.
that's right~    That's right...
It involves the pains of growing up, but...
It's true for both their heart and bodies, but...
Ne?
It's the age where you feel pain the hardest, you know.
Somehow, really... well, you get what I'm saying, right?
I really get it... but this, what is it...
This kind of... all of the characters are girls, and so their standpoints and viewpoints are of a girl...
So I kind of wonder how much all of the male viewers could sympathize with them, you know.
... Is what I'd think around episode 2.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I understand I understand.
(lol)
Somehow this far into it, this piece of work has already denied being a mahou shoujo-show, and not just because of pessimism...
That's right.
(lol) Right.
Right, like... will she become one or not?
That kind of feeling is another fun part... I feel as if that's another extremely new thing it does.
That is true.
It's sort of rare for the protagonist to be constantly thinking "What's a mahou shoujo?" isn't it?
Usually it starts when they become a mahou shoujo... then it's like "Okay, what to do from here."
Right, right, right.
Ne?
It's like who are they going to love, or what are they gonna save...
Somehow that sort of thing is like the primary, natural basis for a mahou shoujo, though...
But this has the theme of asking "What's a mahou shoujo?" "Why become a mahou shoujo?" too.
Ne?
Ah, that cute thing again.
Cute.
(lol)
QB-san is... QB-san is.
QB, cute.
This somehow, for example... The Soul Gems and such match each character's design...
Sensei, how did you decide on the drafts for things like those?
Right, when I came up with clothing, um... I started with their individual weapons.
I see I see, I see I see.
When I was thinking of the clothing, I wanted it to fit considerably well with the weapons...
I see~
Ahhh
So the designs were heavily based around weaponry, too.
Yes.
So for Mami-san, it's guns.
That's right, ne.
Clothing based on fighting styles must be hard... I see, I see.
Then, it's clothing that has to be easy to move in, too.
Right!
Ahh... well, if you consider the sekaikan...
Ah, the sekaikan!
Having the image of the weapon they carry match with their clothing would make for nice designs, I thought.
Ah, I see I see
Ahh, I see~
Right, that is true.
But, it's there. The weapon and their image color are held very well, they all feel very complete and perfect.
Ne!
Everyone is cosplaying, you know.
(lol)
I don't think that's true, though...
Everything really feels like their own though.
Ah, right, actually in episode two... Um— Ah..
To start from the beginning, the notebook that Madoka was drawing her mahou shoujo form in...
For that, Ume-sensei gave me something like a settei base draft,
and then she told me to please draw some sketches of Madoka.
Ume-sensei, your stare at that time was pretty intense.
(lol)
I was like "Ahhhh!"
Amazing...
So, I drew an extremely minor detail.
Ah, is that right?
Right, somehow... I thought "The clothing is cute!"
It's cute~
Thank you very much...
Ah, here it is.
This is it.
... right.
Ao-chan, you're skilled too, from the start.
No no, not at all, um, i–in front of a pro you can't say that kind of thing...
(lol)
There's really no way!
But from the start— Ah, QB's mouth opened.
Agh, cute!
(lol)
Immediate sorrow!
Well at least around this part, he could be a cat.
That's right.
When his face comes up like "BAAAM" you're suddenly like "Ouch!"
(lol)
About the sketches in that notebook, in the beginning the image was going to be different...
Right, if I recall, it was Madoka drawing on the front cover of the notebook...
Ah, that's right, ne.
When we first started, I really thought that Madoka's drawing skills would be poor,
so when I tried to draw it poorly, it was like "why is this so extremely poor."
(lol)
I wanted it to feel like Madoka was a girl who'd sketch in a notebook from time-to-time, and for this premise, Yuuki-san fit perfectly.
Skilled.
中の人(naka no hito) - person inside.
This is a term which, in this context, refers to seiyuu (the people 'inside' a character). Yuuki Aoi is referring to herself here.
I was told that the person inside's art quality was about as good as an outside person's!
(lol)
It is a mystery. (lol)
But, I was really happy.
It's like I was able to draw something that I usually wouldn't.
Ah, I see.
An awesome change of pace.
Really cute outfit, huh?
It's cute, you know~  It looks really cute from behind, too.
They are watching a different version of the video from us - they are seeing a commentary version in between TV -> BD transition. This "Kamijou-kun hair color mix-up" is cleared up in ep4's commentary.
Right, Kamijou-kun's hair color is white?
Eh? Light-brown?
Kamijou-kun is... gray.
So it's gray!?
Desu ne, certainly.
Since characters like that are almost fairytale-like, and he was in the sunset, I was wondering "What color is that~?"
The dark girl has come.
She's come!
(lol)
Ah, seriously, going back to the beginning... after seeing episode ten,
going back to episode 1-2 gives an impression like "Ah, this time was so pleasant..."
Ne~?
The first time watching this you think it's fun, though, you know...
Somehow though, um—
Cute.
(lol)
(lol) Cute, huh...
Somehow though, up until now, regarding this piece of work, there are quite a few scenes that leave an impression on you, right?
Yes.
Ahh, that's right, ne...
In this piece of work.
Right. Well, this might seem a bit spoiler-ish, but...
Well, for the first DVD, on the premise that you've only seen this much, it's a level of spoilers that can't be helped.
As for scenes leaving an impression, this much up until now really has changed since seeing it on TV.
You can tell enhancements were inserted afterwards, and things like the colors are really amazing now, too.
That's right, isn't it...
Like, compared to seeing that scene on TV... it has become one part like that...
J–Just before?
(lol)
Like "that" just before~  or the "that" from the one time~
There are a lot of "that"s which we cannot speak of~
In this piece of work, your impressions when watching it for the first time...
are truly different than when you come back and see this much again.
With this BD/DVD exposure, I'm really remembering.
I really remember. A good tactic to get people to watch it once more.
Right, right, right.
Right, it's like "Ah, this actually meant something like this..."
At this point, Homura's actions make her a bit of a stalker-mate or something, though...
But, what is it...
The slight, delicate "angle" that this puts on conversations, and then afterwards you notice it, and it's like "Eh!?..."
"She's into Madoka's circumstances, and is really direct."
And it keeps a really steady balance on their "mysterious relationship" feeling.
I think it's absolutely amazing. Truly.
Right, truly. Then, um, Inu Curry-san.
Yes.
How is it like to work with Gekidan Inu Curry-san's sekaikan?
Ne~!
Um, well, I know the full story now, but it's still extremely fun to see every week.
I understand~
"Uwah!? It's become something like this!?"
There's a lot of art that I truly couldn't have imagined at all.
It's really fun, you know.
That's cute!
Also, it's eerie.
Right, right, right, it's so mysterious~!
Yeah, really.
Enchanting!
Yeah, and then Kajiura-san's music is—
(ﾟ∀ﾟ) Ne!?
It's amazing...
It's perfect, when it starts my whole body is like "ahhhhh~!"
Ahhh~!
*Ahhhh~!*
(lol)
Editing scenes alone in a room seems like a hard fight.
Ahh, scary~
It really is amazing.
For us during after recording, when we see things on air, it's much different from the after recording schedule in comparison...
That's why it's like "wanna watch. wanna watch. wanna watch."
ﾐﾀ━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━ !!!!!
Then there's the shock of QB's impact...
Really though, after Emiri-chan saw that QB's mouth doesn't move, she was like...
"Are!?"
It was amazing.
"I was betrayed!"
betrayed!
That was an amazing impression she made, wasn't it?
Everyone, ahhh~
It has a feeling of "What'll happen tomorrow?", doesn't it?
Right, you only grasp as far as it goes.
Mm, mm.
Really... this cute-looking thing...
Ne~ Riding on your shoulder with a "Piron!"
What kind of living things did you mix and match to make him? QB, that is.
Ah... he does have a basis that looks like a cat, but...
The important keywords I was requested to follow are something I'd have to cover up right now.
Ehh?
Could you say it without spoilers?
Then...
Oh...!
Oh!!
A little bit?
A little bit, it piques my interest!
Um...
It's related to the origin of Kyubey's name, but that might be getting a bit foul here....
Ohh? We still don't know!!!
Don't know!!!
What is this!?
The origin never comes out in the anime, so you wouldn't know...
Right, right, right
Or I think it never comes out...
So, that's still under wraps?
Yeah, that's right.
The origin of QB's name isn't -fGpx3vvB*a#7!~?
Note: Yuuki Aoi was probably about to say "Incubator" and then stopped herself, so she just said gibberish.
What?
(lol)
What's that? Dunno what you're saying.
What's that?
Ah, welp, dunno.
Ooooooh?
(lol)
Ara ara, there are no spoilers.
It's regrettable.
No, no, but this is truly a fun piece of work to repeatedly watch.
I really think that is true.
It's quite like that.
And well, we're talking from a position of having just done after recording, but...
Really, it deceives you every time.
That's right, isn't it.
It's an original work,
so you don't hear the details of how things are going to develop, then...
When you first see the scripts, it deceives all of your expectations everytime.
And, it does it on a pretty drastic scale, too.
On a drastic scale~
It hits you with some amazing shocks,
it's a really amazing piece of work which leads you around by the nose, and it takes on some angles that haven't really been explored before...
It really is original.
That is really true.
That's right.
It's original and it inhabits your consciousness, don't you think?–Who really had parts in creating that?
Ah... well, I think Urobuchi-san was probably the biggest, but...
In the end, you'd say that you really are concerned with the development every week...
It draws you in.
Ohhhh
Even for me, too, I wasn't given the full script... well, by now I have, but what'll happen next really did stay on my mind and concern me,
like "How will the characters move this time?"
"Ah, what's going to happen next!?"
I see~
Each time.
It really calls to you, I think...
Ah, the fighting has come.
ｷﾀ━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━ !
This sekaikan... it's really scary, isn't it?
Ah~, amazing, isn't it?
Ah, then, I almost forgot to ask this.
Um, you had some jurisdiction over the auditions, right, Ume-sensei?
Ah!
That's right, yes.
I was trying to fulfill requirements.
Well, I just kind of want to ask, but um, what kind of image did you have when you heard our voices?
Scary!!!
Well, everyone is truly cute!
It was all smiles.
There were such people!
There were such people...
(lol)
No, but really, you know...
What is it... mou ne, I can't say anything, you know!
Mou, the feelings are overflowing.
Yeah, that's right~
Ah, this witch gives me a gross feeling!
But it's nice~ （； ´Д｀） lol
I think that Mami-san's fighting style is really cool.
Ohh!
Ne? It's cool, isn't it?
It's super cool!
Truly.
Actually, this...
This calmness! She's really just continues to be calm, even in her fighting style!
What a mysterious balance this world holds! I always think that.
It's like even though there's an unbalance, it's all held together in order.
Exquisite!
Mysterious.
But this sort of slight "gross feeling" or such,
your view and opinion feels unbalanced, but then it kind of has persuasive power, doesn't it?
ahh...
Like this sort of witch's world, for example.
That's right...
From the start, your anime bias is telling you it's some kind of a fantasy, it isn't real...
But then within that world, they have this other kind of fantasy world...
That's really quite...
What is it... it's mysteriously wonderful!
Ne?
This world.
Right.
No one could imagine this world's feeling.
I really think a lot of geniuses had to be gathered for this.
Cool, ne?
It's cool.
She'll shoot everyone with this fighting style.
shooting (lol)
How she can smile is so cool, though.
cool~
The mustache people are darting about here.
Hige Ojisan!
Hige Ojisan! So cute, Hige Ojisan!
Mustache people!
Everyone was saying they want this strap.
Yeah! This, and a talking QB plushie.
Ah, ne!
Right, right, right.
Don't leave that in a child's room... (lol)
Become a mahou shoujo! Become a mahou shoujo!
(lol)                                     Become a mahou shoujo!
(lol)                                         Become a mahou shoujo!
would be what that QB is saying.
Um, if you're hearing it now, you might think of that as cute, though.
But to us right now, it's more like "EEEEEEEEEEK~"
It is forbidden to put it in a child's room!
(lol)
It's wonderful that she's just drinking tea like this...
Ne~!
It's lovely, isn't it.
It's such a cool style of fighting, you know.
I was thinking, "What if everyone drank tea after a fight?"
Yeah, I was thinking about that! Like what each character would pick.
Ahh, I see.
Right, right.
Madoka would have Rokucha... or maybe she wouldn't have something like Rokucha.
Strawberry Milk~
(lol)
Sayaka would! Sayaka would!
Sayaka would!
Ohhh.
Everyone decided their respective things.
Yeah, yeah
They decided.
For Homura, it's coffee.
Right.
Homura is so coffee-like!
(lol)
Ya~
Ah, we're going to end soon.
Ah, that's right.
This time also has Ao-chan's special ending!
Yes!
Please excuse me for letting it happen again. (lol)
No, no, no.
We heard it first earlier, and it was really cute.
Ah!
Yes.
Ne!
It was supposed to be in a method that felt like Madoka singing karaoke or something.
It was surprisingly natural, but I sang while giving it my all!
If hereafter everyone had a song, my song for Homura would be a kinda...
a song of resentment and bitterness directed towards QB.
(lol)
That is true!
Yes.
♪Why, you, QB–!♪
or something (lol)
Homura would be especially singing that, you know.
It'd have that kind of atmosphere to it.
(lol)
She's saying a cool thing...
That's right, ne.
Every single line really has a lot of meaning to it.
كانت هذه الترجمة من قبل ولكن تم ال
Well then, Ume-sensei, it was a pleasure to have you as a guest... we've only done episodes one and two, so...
To an extent without spoilers, regarding this piece of work titled Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika...
Your feelings towards it... Well, this time's commentary was fun, so it's fine, though...
Say what you would like!
This is hard!
(lol)
Seeing as it's only episode two, well, um...
For those of you watching this for the first time on DVD, please watch until the end.
For those of you who watched to the end on TV, I would like to thank you for wanting to watch again on Bluray/DVD!
(lol)
Mou, really, you know...
That's about all you can say without spoilers.
That's right!
I never thought there would be this much that you just couldn't say, it's so hard to say things!
That's right...
A lot is going to build up from here on out, you know.
Let's have fun while watching, please!
Yes!
Um, to our episode 2 guest, Aoki Ume-sensei, thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
That concludes DVD/Bluray episode two commentary!
Please listen to volume two's!