Doujinshi Market.
A place where, mostly, self-published books are bought and sold.
Day in and day out, each participant works daily to achieve their goals.
Though some manage to achieve their dreams,
Some become depressed in the face of reality.
The people who live in the world of doujinshi - this is their story.
And then,
I was feeling guilty,
So I was doing my best to listen to my shop manager's lecture, but...
My hair was touching my nose,
And it itched like crazy!
Seeing my face like that, he was all like,
"What's with that face, not satisfied or something?"...
And without thinking, I ended up saying "Sorry! hair..."
I completely forgot, of course...
The manager's touchy about wigs...
So of course, I got fired!
Ahh... and I was planning on buying a bicycle!
Tsuyuri?
Sorry.
I was asleep.
Eh?  So you weren't listening to me at all?
I was listening...
After that, you got into a pool naked...
What're you talking about!
You weren't listening, were you?
...hang on - nodding off like that, Tsuyuri, are you sleepy?
Yes.  I didn't sleep last night...
You stayed up all night?
What were you doing?
The thing is...
Don't tell me, something perverted?
Excellent guess.
It's certainly perverted.
Eh...  Wait...
Really?
So you were up all night...
But when did you find someone...
Huh? I do it by myself.
By yourself?!
Until you run short of sleep?
A, all night...
If you're interested, would you like to help me?
Help you?!
The next stop is, Yurigaoka, Yurigaoka.
This isn't yuri!
Excuse me.
The next stop is, Ooizumi School.
See here, Tsuyuri...
As a friend...  I like you.
That said, I can't imagine having any more of a relationship than that...
Ooizumi School.
The next stop is, Ooya.
It's work, so I'd pay you.
Hey!  You can't do something like that!
How much should I pay you?
It's not that kind of problem!
How about 20000yen?
Departing!
You look horrible.
I couldn't sleep last night.
What did you do, all night?
Leave me alone...
...I'll ask you one more time - doujinshi?
That's right.
That's where you use manga characters and stuff to create your own manga, right?
Largely.  Incidentally, a lot of people draw perverted manga.
I mainly draw rape manga.
R, rape?!
Then, by "losing sleep while doing perverted things"...
I was drawing manga, of course.
And by "work", you meant...
I wanted you to help me sell books.
I mean, what did you think I meant?  Having come this far..
Father, Mother, Najimi's still okay!
You have insufficient funds.
Please pay the remainder at the window.
Are you okay?
This is our circle's space.
Circles?
Groups of people who conduct doujin activities.
There are many circles with only one member, though.  Like me.
So, does your circle have a name or something?
"Panty Revolution".
Sorry, I'm just not getting it.  Could I hear it again?
"Panty Revo-
Enough, I got it.
The Comic Festival will now commence!
Najimi, quickly, set up the books.
Yeah...
Well, I'll be back.
Eh? Where're you going?
The toilet.
Oh, me too!
No, you've got to watch the store.
That's why I asked for your help.
You can go when I've come back.
See you.
Eh? Wait!
Uhm...
The new book...
Could I have a look?
Yes?
Ah, sure, go ahead!
This...
Ah, n, no!  I, I didn't...
Um, how much is this?
How much is it worth?
Huh?
Ah, never mind! Um, well then,
Two...
That'll be 500yen, please.
Here.
Thank you!
You're happy when your books sell well.
Yes.
Very much so.
It's calmed down a bit, hasn't it?
You really helped me out.  Thank you.
Don't mention it!
Considering that I'll be able to buy a bicycle with this...
Uh, a quick question - are doujinshi profitable?
If you became really popular and sold tens of thousands of books,
You'd be able to make at least 10 million yen in revenue.
Ten million?!
I'd like to work hard so that my books could sell better...
T-Tsuruyi, how much do you make?
Hmm, assuming that I sold all 300 copies and backing it off a bit...
About 50000 yen.
It feels like I'll be able to sell that many today, I think.
Wait, paying me 20000yen, that's better than...
A wonderful book, isn't it?
I'll take one copy, please.
Thank you.
Also, I'll take you there with the beret, please.
Huh?
To take away?
Eh?
I'll dine in here.
Well, neither is possible, but...
It's great that you're being difficult.
What's wrong, Sora?
Aha, I'm sorry.  I was kidding.
Justice!
Sora.
Wait, you said "Justice"...!
Oh, if it isn't Najimi.
What a coincidence.
"Coincidence", you say...
Justice, who's this?
Najimi.  She's my childhood friend, Sora.
Najimi's name (her full name, even!) is a homonym for the word "osana najimi", which means "childhood friend".
But wait, what're you doing here?
Could it be that you're that popular circle's "Justice"?
You've heard of me?
I'm honoured.
Eh, popular?
Aren't you participating today?
I'm doing some personal shopping at the moment.
Hang on, Tsuyuri.  Didn't you say if you were really popular, you'd be able to sell tens of thousands of books...
Yes.
Justice, how much do you sell?
We had three new books this time, so...
30000 books in total.
If you sold each copy for a thousand yen, you'd be able to buy an apartment...
Our circle sells them for 100 yen.
That's still 3 million yen!
The printing cost was 2.9 million yen.
Adding minor expenses to that, there's almost nothing left.
Huh?
Why is that?
But,
So long as people are reading my manga, I'm satisfied.
Money is unnecessary.
Justice, you're so cool!
Thank you.
Don't get all full of yourself now...
But what a surprise.
So if I became like that, I'd be able to...
For big business to be in a place like this...!
Impressive, doujinshi!
Najimi?
If this business goes well...!
Yes!  If it goes well, I'll be able to eat delicious meals until I'm full!
Wait!  What's with "meals", the scale's too small!
That's right!  If it goes well, I'll also be able to eat desserts!
Hey, hey, can we buy this?
That's right!  To begin with, am I someone who can start drawing doujinshi right away?
I haven't drawn anything outside of classes at schools, haven't I?
This is something you drew, yeah?
Ah, yeah!
I can do this!
Thanks to you, the chances of achieving my dreams have risen!
Th, then, are you going to buy my book?
No!
What's wrong?
If you're going to celebrate, now's the time!
You're the one who's laughing, Najimi.
Osana Najimi will now proclaim!
I'll make my fortune through doujin!
I can see it, I can see it!
My future!
It's dangerous, so could you please get down from there?
It begins, it begins!
It's finally begun, hasn't it.
I'd better get someone to cook up some rice with red beans.
You were thinking about something strange just now, weren't you?