A warm May morning where the winds brush my cheeks.
The trees glisten in the sunlight,
and if you listen very closely,
you can hear birds chirping from within.
Water's boiled!
It's been one whole month since we moved here.
We've gotten used to our new life,
and every day has been fun!
Hina, help me with these!
Do not call me by that name!
G-Gotcha, Strarf...
but really, can ya lend a hand?
I do not partake in such mundane tasks.
C'mon, you helped out with our cooking!
You made some octopus balls, remember?
Silence, pest!
Strarf has also become part of the family to us.
Now, we all call each other buddies!
And we'll finish with a good luck charm!
Every day begins with Lene's homemade English tea.
I'm gonna be late!
I've got work, so I'll be out late!
What is this?
A little more good luck than usual.
Oh?
Thanks.
Well, I'm off.
Have a nice day, Master!
Ann's Diary.
Master is as handsome as ever!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Clash! Battle Trike!
And now, we present the final match of the previous Busou Shinki World Championship.
Wow...
So that's how strong the Strarf models are...
Do you want to fight like that Strarf?
Heeeey!
Oh look, Katsura Armor!
R-Really?
Whoah, that's some cool armor!
Now wait just a minute!
You ignored me.
I saw you glance at me, and then you totally snubbed me!
Hmm... it's coming to me...
Thug Girl?
No!
It's you!
What's wrong?
What a chilling coincidence!
The Strarf that I fought in last year's World Championship was...
the same model as you!
So, um...
this is your first meeting?
W-Well, yeah.
Let us have a mock battle.
I-I'm letting you off for today.
She's running away?
She chickened out.
So, what'd ya come for?
I've got something to discuss with you all.
Discuss?
And now, the latest on the Shinki Snatcher.
Good timing. The news is covering this.
The Snatcher struck again last night, sneaking into a Shinki shop in Enohama,
and stealing 30 Shinkis and over 200 Shinki Parts.
A Shinki thief?
Yeah. He could be after every Shinki shop in town.
So I'm gathering muscle to take the law into our own hands.
I'd be happy to let you all join.
We don't need your permission.
What are you saying?
Our fellow Shinkis are being plundered by pure evil!
While a lone Shinki may be weak,
if we combine our strength, we can fight for justice!
You wish to enter combat?
I've got just the thing for you, Strarf!
I spent all night on it!
Entering combath!
Fine, geez!
I was stupid to even think of letting you join my justice squad!
Halt.
I'm intrigued.
I will join you.
You required muscle for this?
Vigilantes are supposed to patrol the streets at night with wooden clappers.
That's how it's always been.
Would such noise not reveal our position to the enemy?
Oh, but it's supposed to! This is where we'll make our stand.
That's not how you use those.
The temperature's perfect...
I wonder if Strarf's okay...
Eh, who cares.
She wanted to go.
And she'd get more done with that nutjob than we could.
Oh, Ann! I'll wash your body for you.
Huh?
Um, I can handle... it...
Oh, hush now.
It feels good...
Oh, this is hard to clean...
Th-That's cold!
Come now, bear with it.
It's a lady's duty to be clean down to her last screw hole.
N-Not there!
S-Sto—wah!
Shinki Parts?
What's with this?
Can you remind me what we're doing with all these Parts?
I spotted 'em lying around in an abandoned apartment building!
With this as our bait,
we'll teach that greeting-less, housewarming soba-less rat who ignored us for a whole month
a little lesson in being neighborly!
Ooh, that Part looks pretty pricey!
I'd like to get my paws on that!
You're barking up the wrong tree!
Did you not hear a scream just now?
Dunno. Sure you're not hearing things?
He's pretty suspicious.
Let's tail him.
There's only one thing to do when getting out of the bath!
No, table tennis is for the hot springs.
We're at an indoor bath, so we need this!
All right! Grab your bottle in your right hand,
legs shoulder-width apart,
place your left hand on your hips, and drink!
When ya hit my age, ya gotta have liquor.
That's a luxury, sir.
He's so obviously suspicious. He's got to be the culprit!
I can't believe we still have such filthy vending machines!
What's up?
Another suspicious enemy.
Another one?
The Shinki shop...
Seems like we've got a bingo this time.
Anything there?
Nothing.
Hina's been out pretty late...
Master is late too...
His work should have ended a while ago...
Got it!
Hello? Ann speaking.
Master! How are you?
I got into a bit of trouble,
and it doesn't look like I'll make it back...
As I thought...
we aren't alone.
Master's at the police station?
They found him walking with a large bundle of Shinki Parts,
so they took him in for questioning.
They were apparently reported of a robbery in the area...
Master is the Shinki Snatcher?!
Absolutely not! Master would never do such a thing!
It must be a false charge!
W-Well, yeah, but what about Master?
He said that he'd be held there until the charges against him were cleared.
That means that there's only one way for us to save Master!
Yes...
We'll combine forces with Strarf and find the real criminal!
We're attacking. Are you ready?
Once we're done with this fight, I'll give you that match you asked for.
My, such words are grossly unfit for the battlefield, are they not?
Way to trigger your death flag.
My elegant weaponry will beat you into scrap!
We'll take out anyone who gets in our Master's way!
That's what we call love!
I'll finish you in five seconds flat!
This place'll make a nice graveyard for you!
Such words are also...
unfit for the battlefield!
Might you be my next target?
Wait, Yda!
I'll defeat her!
I'll do it even if I go down in flames!
Is there nothing you can do to reign in that pointlessly ardent nature of yours, Ach?
There's no such thing as a pointless love in this world!
Neither is there a pointless justice!
I suppose it was foolish of me to ask.
In that case, we'll fight together.
Here we go!
Over there!
Watch it!
The Shinki thief!
I'll head inside! You two follow that man!
Roger!
Ann!
Two on one is no fair!
Well then, shall we have a duel, fair and square?
I accept!
I'll be your opponent!
I'll punish you in Master's stead!
Punish?
W-Wait—
No excuses!
Can you keep up with my speed?
My, you're not half bad.
However, your fighting style lacks beauty!
You must be more magnificent! More gorgeous!
I don't have a grudge against you...
but...
if we don't catch the true criminal, then Master will—
This isn't over...
you evil Shinki!
E-Evil?
You heard me.
Protecting my Master from the forces of evil, down to my last breath...
is my duty!
Stop this. You two were tricked.
Your master left here long ago.
Your attacks focus solely on style.
You lack substance!
Wait, Strarf!
Yda! We're done here!
There's no point in fighting any longer!
Do you plan to double-cross me, Ach?!
These Shinkis are servants of the Shinki thief!
They're not.
The real servants of the Shinki thief... are us.
We were activated by the Shinki thief, and tricked into fighting for him.
Aines and Lene sent a tip.
Let's go, Yda.
We know the truth now, so there's no point in staying here.
Hold it! Are you trying to run away?
We're not running.
We're going on a journey.
A journey to find true love, true justice, and the master we were created to meet!
Huh? A journey?
Yda, let's hurry!
Understood.
One day, when we find a suitable master,
let us have another match!
We're leaving.
I'm with you!
So uh, how is this all ending?
I don't know, but I hope they find their perfect master someday!
What an awful day...
My everywhere hurts...
Let me see your wounds. I'll lick them for you.
This is all their fault! We'll get even, cat's honor!
Why?!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Master!
Talk about a long day...
I can't believe I got mistaken for a thief!
But it's a good thing the charges were dropped!
Yeah. Apparently, the real criminal was caught by some Shinki...
Wait, you mean...
You should thank Strarf.
Hina?
I-It was nothing. I did not fight for Master's sake.
Thank you, Hina.
But don't push yourself too hard.
I did not push myself...
I was simply negligent.
Lucky her.
I'd like a coat of paint, too!
But you didn't even fight!
I got a scratch when I fell over earlier!
Hey, I've got plenty of those!
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Hina's special treatment ticks me off! I want Master to fix my wounds, too!
I know, if we just tear off our paint jobs...
Whoah Ann, where are you shaving?
Well then, I can shave my paint off too!
Hey, so can I!
Lenient... far too lenient...
Next time, we'll have an action packed race battle, all for Strarf!
Next time, on Busou Shinki!
Next time
"It's a Race! One Lap Around the Park!"
One lap around the park?
Strarf's getting into this...