It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Decision
The date has changed.
It's the 23rd.
Ms. Nagumo, I found some new shampoo.
Oh, thanks.
Ms. Nagumo.
Shinpei and I saw a memory from 14 years ago when ya first met Haine.
Right.
I heard.
At that time, ya were...
really flat!
Can I touch and see what they're like?!
Fine by me.
Oh wow. Don't they give ya shoulder pain?
They do.
Why'd Haine end up like that?
She was a normal little girl when she was playing with ya.
That's right.
I was a fool to have let my curiosity get the best of me.
I think this body of mine was born from a part of Haine.
A piece of Haine that fell when
Ryuunosuke was killed was me.
I'm afraid that I might turn out like Haine someday.
Don't worry.
I'll kill you if you do.
Mio.
What? Oh, it's me.
What is it?
Yer so cold.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
I do hate myself.
Wh-What are ya saying?
A tiny nose.
Short fingers.
Hair everywhere.
Excessive sweating.
Stop.
Ya hate it all.
Everything's the complete opposite of Sis.
It's not just the way ya look,
but yer grades and personality too.
I said stop!
Yer Sis's shadow.
How long are ya gonna keep it in?
At least tell Shin how ya feel.
I'll tell him if ya won't.
No!
Ya can't do that.
These are your mother's ashes.
I would never feed Haine the woman I loved.
She died on January 3rd, 2013.
The cause of death was heart failure.
So ya lied about finding a donor.
She'd already been dead fer a
while on the day of her surgery.
Ya shoulda told me something that important.
The Hishigata family has been involved with shadows for 300 years.
This secret must be passed down,
but I only needed one successor.
My father told this only to me
and left my brothers in the dark.
I thought it would be too much for you.
You believe that human life is precious, don't you, Sou?
Of course I do!
That's why I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
If ya want to apologize to someone, apologize to Tokiko.
I dunno why exactly,
but I can't really blame Dr. Hishigata.
He just did everything he could to save someone he loved.
I'm not sure I wouldn't do the same if I were in his position.
But the fact remains that he helped the mass murder at the revival ceremony.
Human sacrifices were made into shadows,
and the memories of their murders was erased.
He thought no one would find out.
It seems like yer dad planned further ahead.
Yes.
Ushio is still Ushio despite being a shadow.
Yer mom is still Chitose too.
Not sure I could go through with it.
You're too kind.
Shinpei.
When was the last time you slept?
What?
You've been continuously awake through your many loops.
You have horrible bags under your eyes.
It's true that I've been awake the whole time.
Don't wear yourself out.
Thanks.
We're all with you, so get some rest tonight.
She's right.
It might be my only chance to sleep.
Hishigata Clinic
Thanks.
Where are ya going?
Ushio, huh?
Ya shouldn't be wandering around on yer own.
I told ya to tell me if ya need to go to the bathroom.
Let me go home.
Go home? Like to yer house?
Alone?!
No way! Are ya cra—
Yer so loud!
Did ya forget something?
Well, something like that.
Still not gonna let me go?
I dunno...
If ya really gotta go, why don't I just come with ya?
Fine.
Come along.
Nezu
I'll be right back. Wait outside.
Why'd ya just walk in like that?!
Well, I felt the presence of a shadow.
Don't worry.
It can't move.
I'm home.
I-Is she...
Yeah, it's a shadow of my wife.
Two months ago, she went to the farm and came back a shadow.
The moment I saw that light, I thought of that day.
I remembered the day Ryuunosuke was killed, 14 years ago.
It tried to copy me, but I had immunity.
Huh?!
What's wrong?
It's acting strange.
It never did that before.
She probably received the same telepathy from Haine that made Chitose go mad.
That so?
Wait, Nezu!
Sorry, but let us be.
Wait!
I can hack into her, and she'll be herself again!
Even if ya do, it's still a shadow,
and it's unlike ya or Mrs. Hishigata.
It killed my wife and took her form.
It's my wife's enemy.
But...
I couldn't kill it until now.
I wanted to exterminate shadows, yet I let my greatest enemy live.
I don't need any more time.
Just let me end this to have closure.
Please.
I'm so sorry, Kaoru.
I'll be with ya soon.
Impressive, Negoro. Your bandaging is perfect.
Summer Time Rendering
Hishigata Clinic
The long night ended.
It's morning.
Are you okay?
You really slept a lot.
Present
Limit
Good, the approaching edge of time is now a bit farther.
I now have a little leeway to the number of loops left.
But my eyes still hurt and my headache is getting worse.
Is everyone safe?
Right!
Good morning.
Good... morning.
We all made it to the morning of the 23rd alive.
Today, on the 23rd, we'll be hunting.
Before the final battle tomorrow,
we must weaken the shadows' forces.
Our first target are the shadows Ms. Nagumo saw at the funeral.
Her team will go to the Kogaito household,
while Ushio's team will check out the Hitobuchi household.
Bistro Kofune
Our team first went back to Bistro Kofune.
Alain was prepping for lunch hours.
We thought he would be angry,
but he kindly welcomed us home.
Rose and Gil watched Bistro Kofune all night,
so we sent them back to Toki.
Mio will help Alain.
Shadow Mio will stand guard.
Sou will stay at Bistro Kofune too.
So Sis and Shin will be all alone today.
What? Uh, I guess so.
Sounds nice, don't it, Mio?
What?!
It's fine. We have Sou with us.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
Stay safe, ya two.
Here, use this.
It's real hair from Sis.
What's this fer?
Oh, I get it!
I found hair on the floor of her room and the bathroom.
It's got her data, right?
I only found a few strands, but ya can use them to recover.
Mio, yer a genius!
My hair has been restored!
All right, let's do this.
Yeah.
Sou, take care of Mio.
Leave it to me.
Don't die out there.
Shin.
I have to tell ya something later,
so ya gotta come back in one piece.
Got it.
Call me if anything happens.
Yeah.
Hitobuchi
I don't sense any shadows nearby.
They ain't here anymore.
Just like Ms. Nagumo said,
the Hitobuchi family has been wiped out.
She saw the shadow of Hitobuchi Kanae, a school teacher we nicknamed "Bucchi."
She taught every kid on the island,
including Ushio, Ms. Nagumo, and me.
There she is.
Hey, look!
Her hair is blonde.
She's got blue eyes too.
Creepy!
She's a foreigner!
Ya foreigner!
Hey!
Die!
U-Ushio!
Yer not getting away!
Hey!
What are ya doing?!
Bucchi.
Nurse's Office
It ain't my fault.
I didn't do nothing wrong.
That's right. Ya didn't do anything wrong.
Ya were just upset.
I ain't upset.
Those two bully weak kids because they're weak.
But I ain't a weakling.
I just taught 'em that.
Ya certainly are strong,
but violence is unacceptable.
People who are truly strong don't hurt others.
What's that mean? I don't get it.
These hands of yers aren't made to hurt people.
I want ya to use 'em to hold hands,
to stroke someone's head, or to hug.
Ya want me to hold hands?!
Eww, no way!
Shinpei.
Y-Yes, ma'am?
Keep a good eye on Ushio.
I'm counting on ya.
Right.
Next time, think about what I said before ya make a fist.
I can't promise that.
I'll hit back if someone hits me.
Yes.
Yer so honest.
I love that about ya.
Bucchi...
She was so kind.
I know.
But she was scary when she got mad.
Yeah.
We're the only ones who can avenge her death.
We followed the presence of shadows into the forest surrounding Mt. Takanosu.
Well? Feel anything?
Yes, I feel them more.
Be cautious. They probably sense me too.
Yes, I know.
Shinpei, are ya nervous?
Of course.
It's just the two of us against them.
Don't worry. I got yer back.
Ya can just take a bird's-eye view and relax...
Shinpei, get on.
G-Go away!
Stay back!
You've got so much energy as always, Hamaji.
You'll be a tasty meal.
What? Ushio?
I missed one!
Shinpei! Behind the kids!
Ya got so big, Shinpei.
Are ya doing well?
Yes, Mrs. Hitobuchi.
So good shadows are fighting bad ones,
and yer a good shadow.
Correct answer, Toudai!
No worries.
We'll beat up all the bad shadows.
Right, Shinpei...
Exactly!
Why are ya still up there?
I can't get down!
Ya put me here!
Shinpei really gets led around by the nose.
Yeah! They're like a couple.
It ain't like that!
Listen, this is a top-secret mission, so ya can't tell any grown-ups.
Whoa!
Roger that!
This is so cool!
I couldn't tell the kids that the real Bucchi was killed.
That's fer the best.
There's no need to scare 'em.
Will they keep quiet about the shadows?
It's okay.
No one would believe them anyway.
Shinpei, there's blood.
It's still fresh.
Did Bucchi do this?
It's a 34-year-old woman who ain't from the island.
She's from Osaka.
A tourist.
I don't see a human-shaped stain.
The tourist was taken away.
Damn!
Haine is eating more to heal her wounds from yesterday.
What a fool.
Eating more strangers won't heal her.
Fer both Kobayakawa Shiori and Haine, the originals no longer exist.
Ushio?
Wait, did I just say something?
Hold on.
Ms. Nagumo Ryuunosuke
It's Ms. Nagumo.
Let's meet up with everyone like we planned.
I'll have the kids go to Bistro Kofune.
It's safest there.
Both teams met up and reported on the situation.
Basically, we only defeated the shadows of Mrs. Hitobuchi and two kids.
The Kogaito home had stains, but no shadows were present.
After that, Totsumura joined us and led an investigation into the shadows we fought in the gym.
All of their homes were empty,
but the families told neighbors that they were leaving for vacation or business.
Fer instance, the Kobayakawas said that Shiori
would be recovering at her uncle's house in Kainan.
I called 'em, but there was no truth to that.
In the first loop, yer shadow said
that they were running from debt.
Debt?
Are they trying to avoid suspicion in case we erased them?
They must want the summer festival to go on as planned tomorrow.
It doesn't seem like they're going to attack us.
Are they afraid of Ushio's hacking?
They might not show their backs to us anymore.
So they really want the festival to happen.
Can't we cancel it somehow?
To do that, we'll need to see that man.
Looking back, I was trying to meet him right from the start.
It's the first place where I was killed.
Hiruko Shrine.
It's where everything began.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
I wanted to talk to ya, Mr. Karikiri.
Do you have time?
Of course.
Why don't we talk inside?
Come with me.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Face-to-Face