I will kill.
In order to live...
Elen...
Are you ready?
It has begun, Mr. Shiga.
This is what I've been searching for.
The play you've written will definitely backfire on you one day.
And you'll go to hell, Scythe Master.
That sounds rather interesting.
Now, my fellow creations,
sing and dance...
...in this murderous and blood-thirsty world!
Who are these girls?
There's no one else in this world with such twisted tastes.
So they're the same as us.
There are at least two more of them.
Sounds bad.
Not true.
Apart from these girls, there shouldn't be any more assassins from Inferno.
Why do you think so?
That person won't allow unrefined stage props to appear on the stage.
He plans to draw the curtains himself?
This is the final battle.
Neun and Fünf left the stage?
They're putting up quite a fight.
This wasn't part of my scenario.
That's right.
There isn't a better ending scene than this.
Let's go.
I'll bait them.
Use this chance to find Scythe.
The rest will be easy after killing their commander.
You're the only one who can understand his intentions.
Be careful.
You too.
2 on 1.
Oh?
So you're here...
Ein.
Welcome to my stage!
I won't act on your stage.
Only two are here?
Don't tell me the others are...
Are you going to surrender?
No, I'm here to kill you...
Master.
Kill me?
That's interesting.
How are you going to kill me when you're on the verge of despair?
There's no way I'm scheduled to die in this scene of your play.
You do not wish to see such a boring ending.
I never thought you would've understood so well.
It's just as you said.
The reason why I returned to this island-country is to see the co-acting of my daughters.
Let me introduce you.
These two are Sechs and Sieben.
You can acknowledge them as your younger sisters, Ein.
That's Ein, your prototype.
Have a little fun with her.
And when she reaches her limit,
slowly skin her and scrape her flesh off.
What's wrong, Ein?
You can't step back anymore.
Even though I went easy on you, you can't even fight back.
How boring.
Their thoughts, actions and even breathing...
...are exactly the same as how you trained me.
That's right.
Ever since the moment you created me,
nothing has changed.
Relying on you even till the end...
I'm sorry, Cal.
My, my.
This is surprising.
I never thought you would have such fighting strength in you.
I told you already.
I'm here to kill you.
But that's impossible for you.
Why?
Because I surrender.
That means I'm not a threat to you anymore.
So? Can you still kill me, Ein?
This is the difference between you and Zwei.
Compared to Zwei who can kill under his own intentions,
you can only kill under orders.
If you go against that, your heart will sink to darkness.
The horror and guilt of killing will swallow you.
Your will-less mentality is even weaker than that of a normal person.
You won't be able to shoot me.
That's right, it's impossible for you.
Because... you need me.
Thank you for bringing me such an enjoyable night, Ein.
Elen...
You really are a foolish person.
Do you really think you can see through everyone?
Of course.
I will kill you.
Because...
I hate you.
I'll never forgive you for hurting him.
What will come of killing me?
Others will come and kill you.
You won't find your memories.
You're just walking in a spiral with no end.
Even if that's true...
I can kill you right now, Scythe Master.
Beautiful...
That's beautiful, Ein!
Don't call me Ein.
My name is Elen.
I will live the life that he wished for.
Elen...
This is a prank by the Muses.
Please go to hell first.
I still want to stay with him for a little longer.
Let's go, Elen.
Oh?
So Scythe Master and the Phantoms...
How should we deal with it?
Those who destroy old systems and create new ones are the young ones.
Flowers that fade away... Ghosts that don't exist.
Even if it's just a fleeting dream,
we have things we must do.
What's going on here?
Seems like something happened at the chapel and the old school building.
How scary...
Have a safe trip,
Reiji.
Helmut von Giuseppe. Born in Berlin.
Doctoral degree in psychology and brain physiology.
Active as an expert in the fields of interrogation and brainwashing.
After that, he entered the underworld and wandered from place to place.
He then became the middleman for freelance assassins.
His nickname in the underworld was Scythe Master.
In order to search for Elen's past, we must research that man's background.
She met Scythe and began her life as Ein,
five years ago.
Their encounter took place in Hong Kong.
Really?
This man came to this orphanage?
Yes, around five years ago.
He said he wanted to adopt a girl from Ulan Bator.
Adopt a girl...
She was a girl with milky white skin.
If she's still alive, she'd probably be the same age as you two.
This might be my imagination...
But the girl over there looks exactly like her.
Ulan Bator.
We came to Mongolia.
But we couldn't find any more clues.
Go to the grasslands and look up to the sky.
You'll definitely find out that way.
As long as you look up, you will understand.
We're here.
If you are a child of Mongolia, you will never forget the sky.
The sky and the clouds will be engraved into your flesh and bones.
As long as you look up, you will understand.
I don't think we need to go on anymore.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I remember this sky.
I've seen it countless times in my dreams.
Seeing this is enough.
In my wrongful life where I couldn't fulfill any promises,
there is still a promise I want to fulfill.
There's no need to search for my memories anymore.
Even if I can't find them, I already have the name you gave me.
That is to make you smile.
I have memories of being with you.
To find your true smile.
One day, I will...
These memories... These memories are enough for me to continue living.
These memories are enough for me.