Translators
midsummer
TheDeath
(German)
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
Rika-chama
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Honestly, this stupid snow is so annoying!
Especially today, after Headquarters ordered us to be more thorough on our patrols.
Yeah.
You haven't given up on Jaquette-san yet, have you?
It's not really that...
Doesn't matter if it is!
After searching and searching, if nothing turns up, then it's natural to believe that, just maybe... you know?
What?
Just that you sounded a bit like Rio-senpai is all, Kureha-chan.
What is it?
At the base of the mountain,
at 11 o'clock,
distance about 400 meters...
Hang on!  Stay with me now!
Even her clothes are frozen!
Kanata, take off your coat.
We're gonna trade them, c'mon!
Oh, right!
This girl is...
From the Roman army...
To think that you were actually able to restore this facility!
I can see why you're called the greatest genius in the academy's history.
With this, victory will be ours!
And it's all thanks to you, Kannagi Noel-kun.
Noel-chan!
They found her while on patrol.
She's a Roman soldier.
I think her left leg is broken.
Hey, her fingers are turning red!
What?
It's frostbite.  If we aren't careful, she may lose those fingers.
The Helvetian Witch...
Leave her to me!
Somehow, it looks like things are going to be okay.
Even her fingers will be all right, apparently.
Isn't that great?
And what about Noel-chan?
She said she'd stay with her for a while.
But... I wonder what was up...
She was so focused and working so hard,
like when she works on the Takemikazuchi.
I see.
A trumpet.
I wonder if she was a scout after all.
But I was surprised!
Well of course you were!
No one expected to run into a Roman soldier in that place—
That's not what I meant!
This is my first time ever seeing a Roman soldier...
and you know how they're always referred to as this fearsome enemy?
So I thought that maybe they'd looked more like monsters...
The Romans probably think the same of us.
But I thought, as I looked at that girl, "Romans aren't any different than we are."
Hey, Kanata, you—
Say, Kana-chan.
It's almost time for school lessons to end.
The peace talks are still full of disputes, aren't they?
It seems like it, yes.
Are we going to... report this?
If we did, that girl would be taken to the capital and interrogated.
Doesn't matter!
They're using the unstable state of affairs to invade enemy territory!
A soldier should be prepared for torture—
She would undergo interrogation.
I will decide how to deal with her.
Please give me some time, Kureha-chan.
Please don't forget, Captain.
We're soldiers.
Can I ask you something?
When you were carrying that girl back here, did you run into anyone?
I don't know.  I was so focused on the task at hand...
I understand.  Thank you.
Say, Rio.
If it were you, what would you do?
A Helvetian soldier...
What do you want with these?
Where am I?  Am I now a hostage of the Helvetier?
I don't understand Roman.
So you took me hostag—
What was that scream just now?!
What happened?!
She... woke up.
Thank goodness.
Ground Forces of the Roman Empire, 1st Armored Division, 13th Tank Battalion, Company B,
Sergeant Aisha Aredora.  ID Number 1031021.
Why did you come here?
Army of the Roman Empire, Sergeant Aisha Aredora.
What is your mission?
ID Number 1031021.
Well aren't you spunky?
How's it going?  Have you learned anything?
Nothing at all!
It doesn't seem like she understands Helvetian at all!
The only things I was able to get were her ID number and her name — Aisha.
I'm the one in command of this bastion, Second Lieutenant Phylicia Heideman.
You have really nice breasts, don't you?
I'm rather fond of them.
I wonder if it would be all right if I played with them for a bit?
Would be it all right if I played with your entire body?
W-W-What are you saying, Captain?!
It seems she's really unable to understand Helvetian.
But that's a problem.
She can't be questioned like this.
We need to hurry and find someone who can understand Roman.
Then...
Until questioning is possible so we can draw up a proper report, we'll take care of her here.
But!
I'm thinking to try a little gamble.
No matter what happens, I have nothing to do with this.
Aisha-chan!  Welcome to the Time-Heralding Bastion!
"Time-Heralding Bastion"?
Yeah!  The Time-Heralding Bastion.
Then I've really arrived...!
Grandmother.
Say "ah"!
Hm?  Is it too hot?
She ate it!
Good?
You need strength when escaping, so I'll eat for now.
I'm sure she said it was good!
What's going on?
Kanata's always like this, but for Noel to be the same...
She might be trying to atone.
Listen, have you ever seen a fossilized angel?
"Engel"?
Oh well, you don't understand me anyway.
I should've studied Roman.
Yeah, if we could only communicate...
You're working so hard!
Hey, Yumina-chan!
You got enough people to help shovel snow at the church?
Yes!  The kids are working very hard at it.
That's great.
I guess that means even they can't stay kids forever.
Yes.
People grow more every day.
Just like Kanata-san's trumpet-playing.
Though Rio would say that she still has a long way to go.
Oh?  Weren't you going to Treize to stock up?
Things happened, and it ended up being a wasted trip.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, that's right.  Speaking of the Bastion,
I've heard a terrible rumor...
Thank you!
It sounds great.
I had no idea that trumpets like those still existed.
May I?
I think Rio-senpai would've let you as well.
This is a great trumpet, and that I'm able to see it even once is—
That song you played just now!
Amazing!
This is just wonderful!
I mean, Ilya-san's sound resonates in me,
and also resonates in Rio-senpai!
Plus, that same song resonates not only in Helvetia, but in Rome, too!
Sounds really resonate, don't they?
The same way in both Helvetia and Rome.
First aid.
Thanks.
"Danke"?
Yes, exactly — thanks.
I wonder what "danke" is?
It means "thanks."
Someone saw us after all.
This city never bore the full brunt of the war,
but parents, siblings and even relatives if you include them in the count —
almost everyone here has lost someone they've known to the war.
They're always a nice bunch of people, but when it comes down to it...
Do you remember Mikael, that guy who dealt with the alcohol incident?
I was actually at his place until yesterday.
He said that it appears as though the Helvetian Army's on the move, in large scale, heading this way.
If that's why a Roman scout is in a place as remote as this, then we've got a serious matter on our hands.
Well, at any rate, we need to ask this girl.
Naomi-san, do you know of anyone who understands Roman?
I most certainly do!
I am Yumina.
I serve the Helvetian Orthodox Church.  I wish you happiness a thousandfold.
So it's one of those heretics.
There is only one God.  A god such as yours is blasphemous.
What are you saying to her?
Just a simple greeting.
Who cares about that?  Just hurry up and ask her!
Why are you here?
If you won't speak, that will bring all those here a lot of trouble.
If you feel even the least bit thankful, then you should speak with us honestly.
I can't talk about my orders.
I wanted to see the petrified angel that's supposed to be here in this city.
She says that she came here to see the fossil of an angel.
"Fossil of an angel"?
What is that?
My grandmother was posted at this bastion, the Time-Heralding Bastion.
"My grandmother was a soldier here at the Time-Heralding Bastion."
She was captured on the eastern front.  That's how she met my grandfather.  I used to hear the story often as a child.
"She was captured on the eastern front and became a POW.  This is where she met my grandfather."
"I grew up listening to her stories."
I'm very eager to see that angel my grandmother saw back then for myself.
The one who brought punishment down upon the earth long ago, an angel of the apocalypse.
Those teachings are wrong!
It was a demon who wreaked havoc on the world!
Cut that out!  Just tell us exactly what she said!
She wanted to see one of the angels of the apocalypse that destroyed the world.
She said that's why she came.
The call for advance?
That code is...
The Imperial Guards, 1st Division, the 9th Independent Mobile Corps...
The 9th... that's not possible!
Colonel Hopkins' Corps?
Is he someone famous?
He's called the Demon of Vingt.
The one who activated weapons from the former age, completely leveling three towns in a single night.
It's fine.  He doesn't know that you're here.
It's okay.
At any rate,
it doesn't look like we have time left for hesitation.
If you don't decide quickly, won't you all be in trouble?
Whether or not you're going to hand over that girl—
There's no need for hesitation!
We are Helvetian soldiers.
I lost the gamble.
You didn't make it in time, did you, Rio?
Please wait!
Rio-senpai said that she didn't want anyone else to have to live unhappily!
That's why she was going to do what she could!
Wasn't that why she left?!
I'm against it... even considering something like that...
Even though we're all the same?
Even though we're all alike?!
More importantly, as Captain of this 1121st Platoon, the following are my orders.
These orders are my own decision, and I so declare that I will carry all responsibility for them.
Understood, everyone?
Captain of the 1121st Platoon, Second Lieutenant Phylicia Heideman.
A few days ago, a Roman soldier was captured at Treize.
Unfortunately, due to an accident during interrogation, we weren't able to establish any details.
But coincidentally, we've had eyewitness accounts of a Roman soldier here at Seize.
Do you have any ideas?
I do not, Colonel, sir.
Understood.
As of this moment, our 9th Independent Mobile Corps will take command of the 1121st stronghold.
Don't cry out like that!
I apologize.
Aisha-san was telling me just now about the legend of the Fire Maidens.
But it's strange...
How she describes the story is—
Do a thorough search!
Anything?
What about over there?
She's not here!
Find her!
Try over here!
She's gotta be here somewhere!
Guard the exits!
Oh yes, she says that she hasn't asked for your name yet.
Noel.
Her name is Noel.
Noel... Noel Kannagi?
Yes.
You have the Invisible Devil here?!
"Invisible Death Reaper"?
Oh, was that a rat?
Noel-san!
H-Hello?
This is the 1121st stronghold.
What?!
A huge Roman force has appeared at Seize's border, in No-Man's Land?!
Next time, Resonate into the Blue Sky!