Sign: Minamizono Apartments
Just a sec.
Cabbage!
You moved?
Yeah.
Where to?
Next door.
Next door?
Next door, as in next door?
Yeah, room 203, right next to you.
Now we can spend New Year's together.
Seriously?
Hey, Mario!
I heard you moved!
Let's drink as a celebration!
Oh, you're here too, Cabbage?
Great timing!
Wow, Joe sang?
Yeah.
It wasn't anything official, so he only had time for two songs,
but the entire crowd was excited,
and all the women fell in love with him.
I see.
At this rate, I bet we'll be best friends with a superstar.
I know!
I'll be Joe's manager next year.
He needs someone to depend on.
No, wait, maybe I should form a production company.
Why are you smiling?!
You look so happy when you talk about Joe.
Wh-What are you saying?!
Why would I be?!
Hey, Joe.
Why go into music?
It's not simply because you love to sing, right?
I have a sister.
A sister?
My sister and I were abandoned by our parents at a young age,
and we were both raised in an orphanage.
But my sister found a foster parent, and...
I don't know where she is, or what she's doing.
So I want to become famous as soon as possible.
If I can become famous and let my sister know where I am,
maybe we can be reunited.
I like that story.
A young man who sings in order to be reunited with his long-lost sister.
It's a touching story.
So, what were you doing before you joined Five Lemons?
So that the more we move forward...
Joe sang recklessly.
Under Kawamata's instruction,
he trained frantically...
in order to be famous as soon as he could.
New Year's of 1958
I got the "super lucky" fortune again this year.
Oh, really?
I guess I can't make a profit on New Year's day.
It's a little early, but I'll go to Mario's place.
Hey, Joe!
What are you up to?
Paying a visit to the shrine?
You get a break on New Year's, right?
Is she your friend?
Well, whatever.
If you have time after this, let's go to Mario's place.
We'll get everyone together and
celebrate New Year's with a bang.
Joe?
Turtle, don't bother me anymore.
Can you leave me alone?
Joe...
That asshole!
Give me a fucking break!
"Can you leave me alone?"
Damn, right!
Who wants to be with him anyway?
Man, I can't believe I have to listen to Turtle ranting on the first day of the year.
Say that again?!
We don't all get together often,
so let's enjoy ourselves and drink.
Forget that idiot!
I'll never talk to him again.
Get me another cup!
Turtle, that's enough.
This is an important time for Joe.
You can't blame him.
He's a disciplinary school graduate trying to make his big debut.
The woman who was with him is probably his manager,
and she must've told him to cut his ties with us.
Still!
Turtle.
You already knew that, didn't you?
Basically, you're throwing a fit because Joe won't play with you.
Y-You idiot!
I am not!
Don't worry, I'll play with you, little boy.
Cabbage...
You asshole!
There, there.
Who are you calling a little boy?!
We'll also take turns babysitting you.
Don't touch me!
There, there.
Don't touch me, asshole!
Something unthinkable may happen along the way...
Stop! Stop!
Your pitch is off.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's okay.
Take a fifteen-minute break.
By the way, Joe,
you've cut your ties with your disciplinary school buddies, right?
Yeah.
Joe.
Mario.
It's been a while.
You got time to talk?
Sorry, I'm busy.
It won't take long.
What do you want?
Well, sit down.
You heard from Turtle, right?
Yeah.
He got drunk and was ranting about it.
It's just like you heard.
I don't intend to be involved with you guys anymore.
None of us will get in your way.
We all know that you're fighting on your own right now.
So don't worry about us, and do your best.
Mario...
This is my new address.
If you need something, give me a call.
If there's something we can do for you, we'll do it.
And...
When you're going to sing on a big stage,
get Turtle a front row seat.
Thanks.
Make sure you don't forget about him until that happens.
Whoa there!
Don't drift off into space while you work!
I'll let you see your sister.
I'll never forget.
I could never forget.
I couldn't live with it if I did.
Unthinkable things may happen on the way,
but simply put them off to the side as a bad dream,
so that the more we move forward...
I'm being selfish, so why is everyone so kind?
Let this reach Meg.
Hear my song, Bro!
I'll sing from the bottom of my heart!
I must say, your popularity is pretty astounding.
Oh, it's not that great.
Hey, Shigeo.
Daddy!
You looked so cool today too, Daddy!
Really?
Thanks, Shigeo.
Joe...
you looked cool too, though not as cool as my dad.
Thanks.
Big news, Joe.
The Western Festival!
This is cool.
What about it?
Look at the performers.
Sign: New Star, Yokosuka Joe
It's my...
It's here.
That's the day you'll take your first step towards stardom.
Really?
I can perform in the Western Festival?
Didn't I say you should leave everything to me?
Congratulations.
Good going, Joe!
Thank you.
Well, we don't have much time until the festival.
So let's start rehearsing.
I did it, Meg.
Hey, did you know?
I heard there's going to be someone really hot in this year's Western Festival.
I did!
Someone at King, right?
Want to go get tickets and see it?
Yeah!
Hey, what about you, Meg?
W-Well...
I'm not interested.
After she parted from Joe,
Meg had become a beautiful woman and was working as a hostess at a cabaret.
She had made strenuous efforts to get there.
Damn it!
Fucking Joe!
He's got some nerve!
What do we do, Mickey?
He promised never to sing again, but he broke that promise.
I'll make it so he can't sing ever again.
No, we can still use him.
What do you mean, Mr. Tsubouchi?
Five Lemons will be the ones who perform in the Western Festival.
You'd like to have your Five Lemons perform with us in the Western Festival?
Yes, Joe shouldn't have a lot of songs,
so we can also make our own arrangements.
You took Joe out of our band without our approval,
but if you consent, we'll put it all behind us.
What do you say?
I don't think it's a bad deal for you either.
You want Joe to perform with your third-rate band?
Say that again?!
It's certainly funny to see the people who used Joe as a slave fawning over him,
but unfortunately, we already have a band.
If that's all, please leave.
We're busy.
You don't mean that, Miss Yamauchi.
If we try, we can even destroy the stupid Western Festival.
In fact, I can just—
Put that toy back in your coat!
A third-rate manager for a third-rate band, I guess.
The Fukumoto gang has my back.
Do you have the guts to point a gun at me?
The Fukumoto gang?!
If you don't, then get lost, you half-breed!
"Half-breeds" were half yakuza and half legitimate.
They fed off businessmen like hyenas.
They were hard to handle because they behaved timidly with the yakuza,
but swindled normal folks as a way of life.
It's ridiculous to be afraid of that stupid hag!
Whatever!
If you're too scared, we'll get Joe ourselves.
Guys, be quiet.
Shut up, you moron of a manager!
It's your fault that—
Didn't I just tell you to shut up?!
M-Mr. Tsubouchi!
I'll settle this properly.
Why me?
I got it in the mail this morning.
He probably couldn't get more than one ticket.
Joe definitely wants you there more than anyone.
Why should I go?
You got the ticket, so you should go.
I can't just take a day off from work.
W-Well, neither can I.
Someone's gotta see Joe sing on stage, or who's gonna report to Bro?
Report?
The 28th... is the anniversary of Bro's death.
That's right.
So...
Can you take care of it, Turtle?
Can you report to Bro?
All right!
I'll go, okay?
Sign: New Star, Yokosuka Joe
Good going, Joe.
Hey, can't we, Meg?
I'll pay you well.
He's the one!
The one with blue eyes!
I heard he has a really good voice.
Really?
Yokosuka Joe, huh?
Sign: New Star, Yokosuka Joe
What's wrong, Meg?
Brother?
Day of the Festival
Joe, what are you doing?
Hurry up and get ready.
The band is already at the theater, you know?
What's wrong, Joe?
You're going to sing in front of 2,000 people, so you shouldn't be looking so blue.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Kawamata.
You've helped me so much,
but I'm the only one going on stage.
What are you saying, Joe?
You don't need to worry about that.
Yeah, Joe!
Besides, if my dad went on stage,
he'd be too cool and put you in the shadow!
You joker.
Joe, come tomorrow, you'll be a star.
You gotta stand with your head held high.
Go sing to your heart's content.
Thank you.
What do you guys want?
Why are you here?
What do you think?
We're here to settle things.
Settle things?
Joe, you have to run!
Run where?
This is the only door.
Hey, that's enough!
Shut up!
Joe, I know you're in there!
Come on out!
Daddy!
Don't worry, Shigeo.
I'm right here.
Okay.
You listening, Joe?
If you won't come out, I'll start by killing this hag!
Shigeo.
I need your help.
If you won't come out...
Hey, Charlie, hold her down.
Okay.
Minakami Mario.
He lives at this address, and I need you to tell him about this.
Please, Shigeo.
Mario...
Minakami Mario!
Say your prayers, Joe.
Brother...
Is this... really my brother?
Is this Yokosuka Joe... really my brother?
Meg knew that high expectation led to a great fall,
but she couldn't control her racing heart.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
The curtain rises on making Joe into a star.
His sister waits for him alone.
Joe, now captured, entrusts everything to Mario.