From the me of yesterday, to the me of tomorrow...
Please don't mind the missing pages in the diary.
There were mistakes, so it was ripped out and thrown away, that's all.
It's absolutely not because there was some kind of misfortune.
Rather because  it was something happy.
It was such happiness that was too good for me.
And so, this is wrongly written.
It is something that didn't happen in the first place.
So it was ripped out.
Please don't mind and continue like you have now everyday.
And...
Also, with the person named Asou Renji,
please do not get involved with him anymore.
It will bring misfortune to him, and yourself.
To the me of tomorrow, from the me of yesterday...
After parting with Chihiro, the time that had passed had been much more than thirteen hours.
Chihiro must have... forgotten all about what happened yesterday.
Not only about the things that happened yesterday...
but everything from after the day she met me.
About me... everything...
Chihiro is the same as always.
The same as always, just like Chihiro was before she met you.
Why did she wrote that kind of story? Do you know?
If you have something to say, I'll listen.
I see. It's painful, isn't it?
Please don't say comforting things.
Otherwise, it seems like it really ended.
It really did end.
To put Chihiro's symptoms specifically,
it's not that she's forgetting what happened.
The memory in the brain itself disappears.
It's like a memo that disappears in thirteen hours, which is repetitively lost.
With today's medical science, Chihiro's condition cannot be cured.
Even if it is cured from a miracle,
the memo that vanished once does not return ever again.
And...
In this kind of world, miracles do not exist.
What exists are coincidence and the inevitable.
Then from there is what oneself does, and that's it.
To not be able to reach your hand to your loved one is painful.
But if it's connected continuously,
the heart will be continuously weighed down by the burden.
But, it isn't something that can be forgotten just because of that!
I didn't say to forget it.
To live carrying that burden, is one of the ways of living.
I won't say that you should live like that.
Can I ask just one thing?
What is it?
The reason why Himura-san is always at the church...
is because of having to carry that burden?
Who knows... I've forgotten.
Come in.
What is it?
Nothing much, just wondering what's wrong.
There's nothing wrong.
Really? And also, isn't it about time to submit the future career survey?
Yeah.
Did you decide on what you want to do?
No, not yet...
Is that so? Well, take your time to think about it...
since it is Renji's dream.
It's not possible.
Huh?
I can only think about tomorrow.
With such talk of the future...
a thing like tomorrow can't exist.
Renji...
A thing like tomorrow, would be better if it never came.
You shouldn't say things like that, as tomorrow might be better than today.
What's wrong, Renji? Where are you going?!
Perhaps tomorrow will be even better than today?
There is no way... it'll be like that.
What are you so worked up about, young lad?
Kuze-san.
Here.
Sorry for the trouble.
Humans are... cruel.
Hmm?
Even while being in such suffering, hunger, even sleepiness, you can still feel.
And even when you eat or drink, you feel further suffering because of not being able to forgive oneself.
But, that's proof of living.
Kuze-san...
What is it?
To make a dream come true, what do you have to do?
Let's see, to make a dream come true, first the dream itself must exist.
The dream itself?
It might seem obvious, but it's something important.
The image of wanting things to be this way, or even things like memories are fine.
Memories...
For me, that is this...
Not forgetting that memory, and to go on with making more...
That is the first step of making a dream come true.
If... that thought is impossible...
then you can only wait for a miracle to happen.
"In this world, miracles do not exist."
"What exists are coincidence and the inevitable."
That's Himura's way of speaking.
But at times, an action's result becomes the inevitable,
and that combines with coincidence, to make a dream come true.
I don't know if that's a miracle or not,
but there's one thing that's certain.
If there is no desire for it, nothing will happen.
Desire, huh...?
Even though I have a desire for it,
there are some things I can't do anything about.
Chihiro's memory does not come back once it disappears.
The time that she has spent with me, has already...
I always felt like I wanted to cry.
Every time I looked up, tears would come out.
Chihiro...
Umm...
Yes?
Umm... Do you mind if I ask something a bit odd?
Are you... someone that I've met before?
I... still remember.
I still remember everything.
Those aren't things that can be forgotten.
How... How can it be like this?!
Chihiro...
"Soon I will part with Renji-kun."
"Even though it'll be painful and lonely, it was decided from the beginning that it would end like this."
"So it doesn't matter."
Because this would be the last time, I kissed a lot.
Because this would be the last time, I loved a lot.
Even though it's sad, this memory will also soon disappear.
Still, I think it will definitely be all right.
No matter how painful...
No matter how lonely...
I will forget soon.
But, it's very painful because I still remember.
It's very painful.
Renji-kun's warmth is still in my heart.
Truthfully, I want to stay with Renji-kun even now.
I always want to feel Renji-kun's touch.
Even now, I want to be with Renji-kun.
I don't want to forget; I don't want to disappear.
No longer do I want to go back to the days full of nothing.
Renji-kun... was a knight that rescued me from the suffering.
Renji-kun... was a prince that rescued me from the never-ending time.
Even though it's forgotten.
Even though it disappears.
Still, I love Renji-kun very much.
No matter how much the time passes...
Even though everything disappears from me,
I, as of this moment...
love Renji-kun from the bottom of my heart.
Renji-kun... Thank you very much for everything up to now.
And... Goodbye...
Still... There is something that can be done...
even if it may be futile.
But... But...!
Even though it's not enough, even though it's far from enough...
I will put it together, I will surely put it all back together.
So... So about me...!
Thirteen hours... is a very long time.
Why do you do such things?
Chihiro?
Despite the fact that I shouldn't...
Because with Renji-kun... I have to forget...
I've thought about it... over and over again.
It's not possible... not possible at all... to not think about Renji-kun for thirteen hours.
Chihiro!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
I won't let you forget...
I won't let you forget anymore, no matter what happens.
I... am always with Chihiro!
I...
So...
Renji-kun!
Chihiro!
No matter what, we'll always be together.
Everyone, I think, pleads at least once to God...
even if without believing in anything.
The day when one prays with a true heart will eventually come.
Something that everyone is looking for...
Something that everyone wants...
Something that is made from circulating memories and the bonds between people...
What is in front of that is...
I said to leave the lock on the hard disc off, otherwise I can't edit it.
President, are you still insisting on that?
Isn't it better just to give up and turn your attention to the new work?
It's fine. Just let me do what I want.
It won't end this way.
With the clips that he filmed, there's no way it'll end like this.
Even if it is vexing, it's shining, right?
Isn't it better to observe your condition more first?
You've just confirmed that you're fully healed just today.
No! I can't stand still anymore!
My body feels so light!
Hey, Kei-chan!
What's for breakfast?
If you look at the time, it's actually dinner.
For me, it's already after school.
It's fine if you make something simple.
Besides, you have tests coming up soon.
It's easy, easy for me... since my head is different from Hirono-kun's.
Besides that, can't you do something about that lifestyle of sleeping during the day and waking up at night?
It's not like it's a problem.
There's enough time to spend together.
It doesn't get in the way of each other's studying and work.
Isn't it all good?
The menu is troubling to cook.
Our breakfast and dinners get reversed.
I don't mind having cooked meat right after waking up.
My pride won't allow that.
It's decided that I will make a proper breakfast whenever Hirono-kun wakes up.
It's okay if you're flexible about it.
But I want to do it like that.
Because... you'll eat it while it's warm.
It's from Kei.
Kei-chan, how was the examination?
"Full recovery."
"Starting club activities now."
She says, anyways.
That's a relief.
Don't you think that's mean, Hiro-senpai?
Acting like a dumb student full of excuses...
But really, it's his identity of Shindou Nagi-sensei who I'm a big fan of.
I feel really betrayed.
It's so frustrating that my anger pierces the skies.
That's not something to be so angry about.
Are you taking Hiro-senpai's side?
Is it the rumored guy to guy relationship?
Did a guy fall in love with a guy?
Is it the happy, yet embarrassing boy love?
What the heck is that?
Well then...
This is it.
This is it?
From here on, this is my place to fight.
I see. Well then, good luck.
Hey, Senpai...
What is it?
Thank you.
Now, I am able to walk with my own legs.
I'll go wherever I can run.
Make sure you follow me properly.
Yeah.
That's right. I can't always wait for someone to take my hand and guide me.
Have a good time, Kei-senpai!
I've got it.
You know...
What is it, Renji-kun?
Chihiro, you previously said that you feared being forgotten by people rather than disappearing, right?
Let's see... I may have said that.
I see.
I've decided.
That place, was my favorite place.
The quiet and abandoned train stop that no one visited, was a perfect place to read alone.
However, there was a visitor today.
That was... a chance meeting of less than 45 seconds.
It's from Chihiro.
What did Chihiro-chan say?
She says that in order to make a dream come true, continuously thinking about it is the first step.
That's right.
For me, I was able to find my dream because of Chihiro.
For me, I was able to see the color that I was always searching for.
For me, I haven't found my dream yet, but have found my way to live.
Your way to live?
Being together with Hirono-kun!
For me, I understood what I wanted to film.
For me, I want to continuously kick off running from now on.
For me, I've achieved my last dream, so I'm satisfied with this.
It's not the last.
It's still just beginning...
I will... walk together with you.
Oh, good evening.
Hey.
You've made me wait for quite a long time.
I see. I'm sorry, Yuuko.
It's been a long time, Yu-kun.