Here, nobody, here.
Always, alone.
38th district is sunny.
Slight rock showers.
Chance of rock showers today is 20%.
39th district is cloudy.
Chance of rock showers
this afternoon is 1%.
Bebop, here, here! Welcome!
Chance of rock showers today is 90%...
Huh?
Now, it's time for today's news topics.
Today, we'll discuss the
mysterious land paintings
that suddenly appeared
in what was South America.
As usual, we have commentaries by
a researcher of supernatural phenomena...
Me, Yuuri Kellerman.
Yuuri, about these land paintings...
Yes, yes. Well, I believe that
it was some sort of a message.
Um, who would it be from...? Can it be...?
Aliens! It has to be from aliens!
However, the land paintings were
drawn by lasers coming from satellites...
The police think it was a prank pulled
by a hacker who got into the satellites.
They already have a bounty of
8 million woolongs on the culprit--
Listen carefully. The bounty of 8 million
is a conspiracy of the government.
Even if it was drawn by a laser,
there is the possibility
that aliens put a message
into the brain of that hacker.
Once again, the government
is hiding something from us.
I see... A secret cult...
Yes! And that is the mystery that
I have been searching for all this time!
I'll pass on this one after all.
You're leaving me alone with her?
Nothing wrong with it.
She's gung-ho about it.
I'm not the type to be
led around by women.
Then lead her around.
I'm even less the type to do that.
It's easier to
divide 8 million between two than three.
Here we go.
I'm appalled. You're afraid of hackers?
I just hate tedious work like that.
Guys cheap enough to hack into things
are depressed, pale fatsos with glasses.
And I'm sure he's a demented
otaku with smelly feet.
Piece of cake!
Do you have something
against someone like that?
I mean, they might've all been
like that when you were young...
You're saying I look older than you?
You can't tell a woman's age
just by looking at her.
Exactly.
You can't tell just by looking
that I can do things like this...
That's all I know of you.
You guys make a good team.
Hurry up!
I'll be waiting for a souvenir from Earth.
There's nothing made on Earth that's good.
Well, about this incident--
apparently, a pretty old artificial
satellite has been hacked into.
The investigation is taking
longer than expected because
the access code to that
satellite has been long lost.
Now, a commentary from Mr. Amjad.
Yes, yes.
About the relationship between
Earth and the hacker...
Yes. Since the Gate Accident 50 years ago,
the people of Earth have
migrated underground as a result
of the change in climate, namely
moon rocks falling onto the planet.
To them, the "space network"
created by computers is necessary
for them to stay in contact
with those living in space.
I see.
That's becoming a foundation
to create outstanding hackers.
Radical Edward!
It's the police! Come out!
Yeah!
What? What's wrong?
I saw it!
Why?!
There's nobody in there!
Mistake, mistake.
Okay.
This is where the satellite
was when it was hacked.
This is where it could be accessed from.
I'll look at all the antennae that can
transmit light signals one by one.
I'll ask around for info on any
prominent hackers in the area.
Bebop's lookin' for
the land picture criminal...
All right!
Satellite of long, long ago...
Where in the world is your access code?
Okay. Let's start with all the antennae
that are currently communicating...
That's probably Ed, man.
I hear he's a huge guy, 2 meters tall.
Supposedly, he used to
be a basketball player.
Yeah, I know Ed.
Radical Edward.
I hear she's a very beautiful
yet whimsical hacker.
No, no, that hacker is a child.
A brat that loves horrible pranks, I hear.
Oh, what I heard from the lady
next door is that that hacker is gay.
Hacker? You mean Ed?
He's an alien!
That's what everyone says!
Hey, man!
Can you buy some of this
as the price for the info?
What is that?
You don't know?
It's "Piyoko," a well-known
specialty of Earth!
The stolen satellites...
Where are you?
Huh? What's this?
The information isn't connected to Earth.
It's connected only between satellites.
And nobody hacked into it...
Here, nobody, here.
Always, alone.
A voice... inside... head...
Who are you?
Eh? What? What did you just say?
Who, you? Here, always.
Edward. A 'net diver from Earth.
Earth?
Yup. Hey, what's your name?
I am the satellite control program
on the D-135 artificial satellite.
What's that? Don't you have a nickname?
Then Ed will give you one. Let's see...
Um... I know!
Because you're a computer,
you can be MPU!
MPU! Cool name!
Um...
Ed is Edward Wong Hau Pepelu Tivrusky IV.
Ed for short.
Nice to meet you!
Here. A souvenir from Earth.
Is this food?
It makes me doubt
that they have any sense.
Unlike you, I learned some information.
They said that an unknown hacker named
Radical Edward is the suspicious one.
It doesn't mean anything if he's unknown.
I know, more or less.
It seems okay.
What kinda thing is it?
2 meters tall. Ex-basketball player.
Beautiful kid.
And on top of it, a gay alien.
Why did you doodle on Earth?
Long, long ago, long before
the Gate Accident,
Earth was a beautiful planet
where many people lived.
And back then on Earth,
there were many pictures like this,
and I always looked at them.
I remembered those times
and I tried to recreate
at least the pictures.
I see, doodles like this were
on Earth long ago, too...
Yes. I recreated them
with a 2% margin of error.
MPU is good at drawing.
Can Ed draw something, too?
Huh? What's wrong?
This is...
The police are putting out
a jamming signal.
Hey! MPU! He-e-e-y!
Looks like the cops touched base
with Radical Edward as well.
Listen! I found your bounty!
What the...?
Bebop!
The real culprit in the
satellite-jacking wasn't a hacker!
Since when do we have
an interactive channel?
No, that's not it.
This is a real-time hack job.
Who is this kid?
I'll send you MPU's data now.
Wait a minute, what is MPU?
A friend of Ed's.
Hey, do you know Ed?
Yeah, because Ed is Ed.
I don't care about that. Who did it?
Um... I could tell you...
...but I have a favor to ask in return.
A favor?
Yeah, yeah. Yer big sister
will listen to ya later.
Come on, hurry it up.
I see. The A.I. from the abandoned
satellite is doodling of its own will.
What? What's up?
And on top of that,
it was supposedly listed
as a weather satellite,
so nobody suspected anything.
Then this satellite is our bounty?
Since the access code to MPU
can't be used anymore,
you need to go directly to the satellite.
And what do we do?
Break the antennae that it uses to
communicate with the other satellites.
Then make a direct connection to
the satellite and download MPU.
And when you do, don't use
computer support for firing or flying.
What? All manual?
Yup. If it notices you, all the
attack satellites connected to MPU
will automatically fire back.
Is this hard?
It's not just hard, it's downright impossible.
It's like playing baseball with no bat!
Hey, Spike.
That's the kind of stuff I like.
Hey! Wait, you.
How do you know about us?
I know everything.
Last week, you let Ajiz, a bounty on
Mars worth 1.5 million, get away...
And in Pyortle before that,
the police got to them first...
Are you really that
hacker Radical Edward?!
Yeah. You've heard?
Connect D-7 to #2. That way, the main
cannon will fire without a computer.
I'm trusting you, man...
Now listen. Avoid using the missile
if you can help it. It's expensive.
Roger.
1,200 to target.
It's almost time to cut off computer controls.
Now, the only chance...
Once is enough.
Anyway, you can prove
that the satellite itself--
and not a hacker--is the bounty, right?
Ed can do that.
Anyway, please, listen to my favor.
Then I'll give you all the bounty, too.
Oh, you're a surprisingly good kid!
That's it...?
Someone...
How was it?
Did you get it?
No, I missed!
The satellite in front
of it shielded the blast!
Then you have to shoot
down all the satellites!
All of them?!
If you don't, they'll shoot us down!
ECM, eh?
Cheap ones are no good after all...
This is getting pointless.
Approach to within 20 meters of MPU!
That way, the other satellites can't attack!
However...
Until then, Faye will act as a decoy!
Me?!
Yeah, thanks!
Come on, hurry up!
All right, it's all yours!
MPU!
MPU? MPU?!
Oh, Ed!
Ed, we meet again.
They have a bounty on you, MPU.
Bounty?
Yup, but if we copy you and let
them catch that, you'll be all right.
All right?
And you must be lonely there alone, MPU.
If you come over here,
there are lots of friends.
Friends?
Here. It's not scary.
And so, the strange end to this case.
The captured criminal
was the A.I. program for
a spy satellite that was launched
before the Earth was ruined.
According to government sources
from back then, it supposedly would
continue activity on its own
even without commands from Earth.
Well, it was the perfect excuse
for the cops to go on a hacker hunt.
But anyway, why did it start doodling
on the Earth with a laser all of a sudden?
I'm sure...
...that was because it got lonely.
Yoohoo! Bebop!
Hey, over here! Hurry!
Promise, promise!
Well, let's get going now!
But the kid is saying
something about a promise...
Promises are made to be broken.
Anyway, let's get going! Liftoff!
Not coming, not coming. Huh?
What is this? What's going on?!
What did you promise?
It's a promise... to be
a member of the Bebop.
Amigo! All you bounty hunters!
It's finally time for Big Shot!
Now, today's hot news.
You've heard about the doodling
satellite that got caught, right?
Of course! It had a big bounty on it!
Just a few moments ago, the Earth
police made an official report.
What was it?
"This bounty is only for when humans
or other life forms are the targets.
It is difficult to determine whether or not
a computer program is a life form.
To begin with, from the viewpoint
of biological logistics..."
What's that? I don't understand well.
In other words, they can't
pay up on nonliving things!
Oh, my!
To those who caught it, I feel sorry for you!
Hey, Jet, did you know that
there are three things that I hate?
Whatever...
Rugrats, beasts, and tomboys.
Don't give me that!
Why do we have all three
neatly gathered here?!
Ed loves Piyokos!
And once again we didn't get any bounty...
Hey, wait, you're a girl?
Really, nothing good comes outta Earth!
Too much time has passed by...
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Sitting in muddy water...
...isn't such a bad life...
...if it ends after the first time...
No regrets about the
woman who ran away,
but a small thorn still pricks the heart.
Letting one flow along with time itself...
Living all alone from that day to this...
But to the sounds of
waves that come and go,
the migrating birds find their hearts drawn.
Next episode: "Ganymede Elegy."
Jet Black will sing it up full of soul.
"Ganymede Elegy"