Saturday, April 4th.
The height of spring.
Everyone knows it's the season to start anew.
I, Satomi Koutarou, began to live on my own when I entered high school.
This is my best friend, Makkenji.
His name's Matsudaira Kenji, so I call him "Makkenji."
I've been stuck with him since elementary school.
This is Kasagi Shizuka-san, my landlady.
She manages this apartment complex,
even though we're supposedly the same age.
Looks like she was cleaning up the yard for us.
So this is the apartment that will be my castle for the next three years.
Room 106 of the Corona Apartments.
No security deposit or money put down.
No fees to use the common area either!
Plus, the rent's only 5,000 yen a month!
Invaders of the Rokujouma!?
I see. You're all moved in, then?
If you had anyone help, make sure you thank them.
Okay.
How are things on your end, Dad?
They suddenly relocated me for my job,
but stuck me in a dorm for singles.
I can get meals here and take baths.
No problems for the foreseeable future.
I see.
Well, this is a good opportunity.
Find someone nice.
Well, I forgot I have some stuff to clean up.
I'd better get going.
First day of
Kindergarten
Sure thing.
Talk to you later.
Good night, Koutarou.
Night.
You just moved in, right? You should take a day off.
I need to save some money up by spring.
#01 The Invasion Begins!?
Didn't your dad leave you some?
If possible, I'd rather not spend that.
That's why I looked everywhere to find an apartment like that.
It is pretty impressive that you
found a place like that for 5,000 yen.
But aren't you worried?
You know, there's rumors the apartment is haunted.
I didn't notice anything last night.
And even if there are some ghosts, I'm not giving up on that place.
Whoa!
Satomi-kun.
We don't have enough people at Site B.
Could you head over there?
Sure, I'm on it.
Site B... Site B...
Koutarou.
Am I hearing things?
Ouch...
Where am I?
Koutarou.
I have long since awaited your arrival.
Endless days and nights.
I wonder just how many
times I dreamt of this moment
within those repeating states of slumber and wakefulness.
Koutarou, we finally meet.
Ow...
Um, so how did that happen?
So get this, Landlady.
This guy hit his head at work and passed out.
What!? Are you okay?
Yeah, the doctors said that apart from this bump, there's nothing wrong.
That's all well and good, but don't go and worry us like that, Satomi-kun.
I mean, Satomi-san.
Why did you change that?
Well, you're my tenant.
That's true, but starting today, I'll also be your classmate.
Exactly. There's no reason to be considerate with this guy.
But you definitely need to be more considerate!
Satomi-kun, want to go home together?
Sorry, Landlady.
I have something to do, so I'm kinda...
Oh, that?
Enjoying your time alone with the beautiful president, eh?
If you think all men only want to get into girls' pants like you, you're way off-base, Makkenji.
Sorry. See you later.
Sure. Later, Satomi-kun!
He's part of the Knitting Society.
Huh?
He already chose a club to join?
He was invited during the school acceptance announcements and joined right away.
I thought he was going to
keep playing baseball, but...
Satomi-kun, I've been waiting for you.
Sakuraba-senpai, thanks for having me here.
Ow...
I see.
I knew I saw you at the hospital yesterday.
I never would have thought
you'd be at the same hospital.
I've been frail for as long as I can remember,
so I go in for periodic checkups.
You can never be too careful.
I see.
rou
Well, if you see me around
somewhere, feel free to say hi.
Especially now that I'm officially a
part of the Knitting Society with you!
Club Entry Form
Year 1 Class A
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Club
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Club
Knitting Society
Are you sure about this?
Joining this club, I mean.
Huh?
I know tons of people would love to have someone like you on their sports team.
There's something I want to do.
To do it, I need to learn how to knit.
Well, I'm not too good with my hands,
so I'm not sure how long that'll take, but...
Got it.
In that case...
Right.
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Club
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Club Entry Form
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Year: 1 Class: A
Full Name:
Satomi Koutarou
Knitting Society
Let's start tomorrow.
Yeah, Sakuraba-senpai!
I'm back.
So you're back!
All right, today's the day!
I'm going to make a ton of
noise while it's still light out!
He didn't notice last night or the night before that,
but now's my chance, while he's awake!
Now be surprised, my dense friend!
It's spooky time!
Huh? Wait...
What are you doing in my room?
What!? You can see me?
Of course I can!
How'd you get in here?
Why?
No way!
You're touching me?
You're touching me!
Go back to your own place!
That's weird.
Did I forget to lock the windows?
Hey!
What was that for!?
Y-You...
I was waiting for that reaction!
It's weird that you're able to talk with me,
but that also saves me a lot of trouble.
Wh-What are you?
I'm Sanae.
Higashihongan Sanae.
I'm the ghost that haunts this room.
I get it.
A ghost, huh?
So what does a ghost want with me?
This is my home,
so I want you to leave!
Don't be ridiculous!
This is my home!
It took me forever to find this place!
I won't hand it over that—
You're resorting to violence now?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Take this!
Poltergeist attack!
Hey! Careful! You could have killed me!
Duh.
That was the point!
Now, I'll finish you!
I knew it. Sacred items keep you at bay.
And my grandma sent me a ton of them!
This was my home first!
Get out of here!
I refuse!
I'm trying to make things easier on my dad,
so I'm not giving up this affordable apartment!
Ow, ow...
Ow...
Who... are you?
I'm...
Um...
Yurika... um...
I'm the princess of love and courage!
Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika!
I'll protect the peace in this town!
Co-Cosplay?
Oh, I see.
N-No! It's not cosplay.
The glass...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to!
I was just in a hurry!
But I can't pay you back.
I don't have any money.
Why were you in such a hurry?
Oh, th-that's right!
This room is in danger!
Danger?
Yes.
At this very moment, lots of magical energy
is gathering in this room!
Magical girls will come to use it for evil!
So please, run away from this place!
Right now!
Huh? What!?
Um... Open up!
Please listen to me!
Hold the grand opening for your cosplay party somewhere else!
That's right. We're busy!
I don't like this either!
This outfit doesn't cover my chest or butt all the way.
But the Magical Land says I have to wear it proudly!
Please! Believe me!
Believe me! Believe me, please!
Want to call a temporary truce?
Yeah.
I guess so.
Do you believe me?
That I'm a magical girl, I mean.
Sorry, but that's a little hard to swallow.
There's no such thing as magic.
Please!
I'm Karama!
And I'm Koroma!
N-Now what!?
My apologies for startling you.
Wh-Who are you?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kurano Kiriha.
A descendant of the Earth People,
and a member of the Kurano clan,
masters of oracles and incantations.
The Earth People?
Oh, wow! How cute!
Basically, people who live underground.
Um, so basically you're
a descendant of people who
moved underground centuries ago.
And recently you found the location of
a shrine that's important to your people,
and that's this room?
That's right.
So Koutarou, could I ask you to relinquish this room to us?
We wish to rebuild the shrine.
I see.
I understand, but...
Hey, that's not how you treated me!
Of course not.
She's not acting the way you did.
And quiet down, you guys!
I'm sorry!
By the way...
If you're willing to leave,
we'll gladly compensate you.
Gold bars?
No, no! You can't have this room!
That's right!
You can't!
Very well, Kiriha-san.
Excellent, Koutarou.
Thank you.
Why are you getting greedy all of a sudden!?
No! I couldn't take something this valuable.
But if she's being so generous,
I have to at least consider it.
Yes.
Now we can move on to our next goal.
Karama!
Koroma!
It's time to invade the surface world!
Invasion time!
If we can activate the shrine
and gather lots of etheric energy,
we can make many ether weapons.
Hold it!
What do you mean, invade the surface?
Don't worry.
We'll treat you as an honored guest, Koutarou.
That's not the problem!
The deal's off!
I'm not giving you the room!
Well said.
I refuse as well!
Me too!
Shut up, you cosplayer!
What about this, then?
Do you really think this will weaken my resolve?
We endured being underground for a millennium.
But how long can you endure?
Hey!
Why are you being all perverted in my room!?
It's not the time for that!
The magic power...
Again?
There'd better not be another one of you!
How... How... How rude!
Wh-What?
Don't fondle them, you jerk!
What?
Sorry!
"Sorry" isn't good enough!
You fondled my noble breasts out of sheer lust, didn't you?
I-It was an accident!
I would never fondle them on purpose!
They're barely there to begin with!
Barely... there?
Well, that's true.
If he was going to fondle somebody, it'd be her.
You want to?
Not a chance!
Even less of a chance!
How dare you, Neanderthals?
Blue Knight!
Activate anti-personnel pulse
laser and sonic impact cannon!
As you wish, my princess.
I'll kill you all right now!
Karama! Koroma!
We're on it!
Etheric Field! Maximum Power!
Eliminate them, Blue Knight!
As you wish, my princess.
What is this!?
You can regret your insults
after you've been vaporized.
Blue Knight!
As you wish, my princess.
What are you doing to my room!?
What!?
You can't lay a finger on me, you Neanderthals.
Oh yeah?
Special move, Sanae-chan Tulip!
Good job, Sanae!
A b-bear?
Don't look!
How rude!
Stop it!
A bear!
Stop!
It's a bear!
Stop it!
If you surrender, I'll forgive you.
Do you really think a princess of
the Holy Fortorthe Galactic Empire
would deign herself to some outland barbarians?
Blue Knight!
Transform into Final Attack Mode
and fire a limited blast from your Genesis Buster!
As you wish, my princess.
Emergency alert!
Ultra-high energy readings fifty meters above us!
Looks like an antimatter cannon!
Not good. We'll all be destroyed!
What!?
It's huge!
No! I don't want to die!
You're already dead!
Hey, Tulip!
Stop it!
Blue Knight.
Begin firing sequence.
As you wish, my princess.
Hey, I said stop!
Please stop, ma'am!
Don't try to stop me, Ruth!
Princess Theiamillis!
Destroying this entire planet is a
violation of the treaties on intergalactic war.
But they said I was flat-chested.
Your task is to make the life form at
these coordinates swear loyalty to you.
Doing otherwise will cause you to fail!
Do you want to be the
fastest failure in the history of Fortorthe,
and bring shame upon your mother?
Blue Knight,
shut down the Genesis Buster.
Satomi-san, what is going... on...
The room is a mess!
You guys!
Yes!
The next time you damage this building,
or cause trouble for the neighbors...
Yes?
I'll make you regret...
the fact that you were born.
I understand the situation.
A ghost.
An underground person.
An alien.
And a cosplayer.
And you're all fighting over this room.
It's hard to believe,
but I guess I don't have a choice.
As the landlord, I order you all to resolve this peacefully.
If you can't...
you're going to find eternal peace, right now.
Sign this, please.
Corona Convention
My signature below indicates my willingness to abide by the agreements above.
.
Sa
tomi
Ruth
The treaty is now officially in effect.
You understand what will
happen if you break it, right?
[APPROVED]
No matter what anyone says, this room is mine!
I won't let you have it!
Who is that landlord?
How did she hit me!? I'm a ghost!
That hurt...
But...
Yes?
My shoulders feel much better.
Next Episode
More Invasions!?
What?
Huh?