Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
And so...
Can anyone tell me what "AD" means?
It's here...
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
The time's finally come.
What has?
Is something about to happen?
Angel's assault begins.
Angel's assault?
What do you mean by "assault"?
It's exam season.
Uh... how does that...
Think about it.
Making us attend classes is important, but making us take tests and getting good scores...
That's also important for Angel.
But this exam period might actually be a good opportunity for us to take Angel down.
You sound like you've got an idea, Yurippe.
Let's hear it.
We'll interfere with Angel's tests and make her get bad marks.
That way we'll force her score down to the lowest in the school.
What will that accomplish?
The loss of her reputation.
Do you think she'll be able to retain her dignity as student council president like that?
So you're saying that'll weaken her?
At the very least, the opinions of the ordinary students and teachers will change.
It'll cause a change in their behavior that we've never seen before.
What kind?
Who knows? I can't predict that.
Then isn't this meaningless?
But if she isn't a creation of God, an angel...
If her emotions aren't made of steel...
If she has a human soul, same as us, then...
That loss of dignity will be an effective emotional attack.
First I'll announce the members participating in the operation.
I've already made arrangements for us to take the tests in Angel's class.
Wouldn't it be best to just attack with all our members?
It wouldn't "be best"!
We can't afford any mistakes this time!
If our plans are exposed, they'll immediately move us to a different classroom,
and we'll lose any hopes of ruining Angel's tests!
I see.
Count me out then.
That kind of work is for the girly members.
Which is why the participants will be...
Takamatsu-kun, Hinata-kun, Oyama-kun, Takeyama-kun,
and Otonashi-kun.
Me again?
Please call me Christ—
I just chose the normal looking members.
Now then...
Operation start!
Seating will be decided on the morning of the tests by lottery.
If we don't get a seat close to Angel, it'll be difficult to interfere.
Got it?
Get the seat in front of her.
Don't ask the impossible.
Let's see...
20...
I missed!
11.
Quite far from Angel.
33...
Totally no good!
Down to me, huh...
25...
I'm pretty far too.
Yay! I got number 1!
What the hell's with this damn thing!?
Isn't anyone close to her?
I don't care if it's beside or in front!
I'm got the seat in front of her.
Alright!!
So, what should I do?
When the answer sheets get passed out, take two of them.
And when they're collected at the end, switch one with Angel's.
Leave that sheet blank—
No, that would be too suspicious...
Write down lots of stupid answers.
Like what?
Just write about what you'd like to be in the future.
It's a physics test, you know...
It's fine, just write "pilot" and "dolphin trainer" and stuff.
That's pretty stupid...
What do we do when the tests are collected?
Hinata-kun, wait for the right moment, then do something stupid!
Make it so everyone focuses on you.
That's just...
Why do you think I included you in this operation?
I never thought it'd be for a clown act!
And then at that moment,
after gathering all the tests from behind him, Takeyama-kun will switch out Angel's test paper with the fake one.
If anything goes wrong, make sure you don't panic and just help each other out.
Okay?
Ah, wait a second...
What should I put down for her name?
"Angel".
Are you an idiot?
Isn't "Student Council President" fine?
Yeah! She's going to be an idiot who writes "I want to be a dolphin trainer" on her test anyway, right?
No way!
Being unable to write your own name is too unbelievably stupid!
And wait, how do you people not know her name yet anyway?
We've never had a chance to find out.
That's messed up!
Fine, go find out what it is then.
Go to the staffroom and check the register.
Geez, you could be a bit more—
Where are you going?
The test is about to start.
I just... got a bit nervous.
Dammit, what do I do?
It would be too cruel to hand in her test under the name "Student Council President"...
No, worse than that...
Answering the question "What is the resulting amperage when applying 3.0V to a conductor with 20Ω resistance?" with...
"I want to be a train company director!" is just...
Are you that worried?
No, that's not it...
Calm down.
It's okay.
Um...
I'm Otonashi.
Otonashi-kun.
I don't know your name either...
Me?
Tachibana.
And your given name?
Given?
Kanade.
Tachibana Kanade...
What a beautiful name...
Like her name, "playing music" seems to suit her.
Note: Kanade = playing music
Thank you, I feel better now thanks to you.
Do your best, then.
It's "Tachibana Kanade".
Oh yeah, that's what it was.
So you did know!
I just forgot.
The test is starting. Sit down.
That's weird...
How am I answering these so easily even though I lost my memories?
Don't take the test seriously.
It might be a factor in how people disappear.
Whoops.
I can't answer seriously.
Alright, pass your tests forward.
What the hell is that?!
Huge two-legged bamboo shoots are walking across the field!
Hinata, you moron...
Geez, no choice.
I put a propulsion engine under your seat just in case you messed up.
How did you like the feeling of being an astronaut?
I just got driven into the ceiling then dropped!
And how did you make a propulsion engine in the first place?!
You should be thankful I helped you out.
Operation successful, right Takeyama-kun?
There were no mistakes.
And call me Christ—
Next is Takamatsu-kun then.
What exactly am I...
You'll be drawing everyone's attention.
Isn't that Hinata-san's role?
Don't you know the story of the Boy Who Cried Wolf?
Repeated lies makes people lose trust in you?
Exactly.
Don't tell me that's why you included so many—
I wonder.
Please excuse—
You're doing it.
Just give it up and fly.
And then get driven into the ceiling.
I have to think of something that'll successfully draw everyone's attention!
What kind of answers should I write next?
Man, you have it easy.
You just need to be sneaky.
You're not flying like us.
What are you talking about?
I'm carrying out an extremely risky part of the mission!
Then swap with me.
No!
See, your part is better!
Aren't you the lucky one!
This is a job that requires the kind of cunning that only I have!
Aren't you lucky you don't need to use your brains to fly!
What? You calling me stupid?
Shut up!
Stop fighting!
Crap.
Sorry!
We were arguing about the answers!
We just figured it out!
Hinata got a zero!
Everything's okay!
No problems at all!
Sorry we were loud!
It's all okay now!
I see.
Idiot.
Who's the idiot!?
So, what kind of answers should I write next?
What's the subject again?
World history.
Then answer like aliens have taken over the Earth.
Alright, pass your tests forward.
I have to do it.
What's wrong?
Sensei, the truth is...
I actually look thinner wearing clothes!
What do you think?
I see that. Sit down.
Okay.
Seriously, the best you could come up with was something that weak?
I was confident it would pass...
I thought it would be surprising...
that no one would see it coming...
I train in secret...
Yes yes, put on some clothes.
It went perfectly this time too, right Takeyama-kun?
There were no mistakes.
Now will you please call—
You're up next, Oyama-kun.
So I really do have to do it!
I can't come up with anything!
Your seat is a bit behind and to the left of hers, right?
Oh, you're right...
Then I don't have to do anything crazy?
Yep, you just need to confess to Angel.
Wait, what?
Confess to Angel.
"I'm sorry I didn't pick a better place or time!"
"I've always liked you!"
"Please go out with me!"
If you do it exactly like that, you won't have to fly.
What, he just has to confess?
That's not fair.
No way! Try being in my shoes!
You just got away with physical damage,
but I'm going to take critical mental damage!
This will be my first time confessing to a girl!
And I know I'm going to get rejected too!
How innocent. It's perfect for practice.
Unlike you, I don't practice!
I only fall in love seriously!
What? Are you saying my love is a dirty lie?
Shut up!
Stop fighting!
Sorry!
Yuri's just a bit cranky right now.
Last night she dreamed about Hinata, and he was like,
"Don't think that the me tomorrow will be the same as the me today."
"You'd better be careful."
or something like that.
And then Yuri said that it turned out to be true!
So there are two Hinata-kuns?
I guess, yeah...
Then there might be more than three?
Well, maybe...
Discomforting.
She's calmed down now, so don't worry!
Everything's okay!
Thanks for worrying!
Who is there more than three of?
Who's cranky?
Come on, I just covered for you guys.
What's with the complaining?
You brought that on yourselves.
So, what kind of answers should I write next?
What's the subject?
English.
Answer everything in Katakana then.
Alright, pass your tests forward.
Tachibana-san!
I'm sorry I didn't pick a better place or time!
I've always liked you!
Please go out with me!
Pick a place and time then.
You there, sit down.
Okay.
Wow, he did it.
He's gonna fl—
Hey, what the hell was that?!
What? Don't come over here!
Why did I have to fly?
Oyama-kun already took enough damage to his heart.
But why me?
I don't get it!
More importantly everyone,
let's have lunch.
Classroom Block A — Roof
There were no mistakes, right Takeyama-kun?
It went perfectly.
And call me Chri—
How much more are you going to make me fly into the ceiling?
The whole exam period.
Let's change up the members for tomorrow!
Matsushita-kun and TK look too heavy.
Don't pick me just because I'm light!
And even if sending me flying once or twice has impact, people are going to get bored of it eventually!
"Man, he's flying again."
They won't even watch it!
That's why we'll keep doing it while adding more gimmicks each time.
What are you planning on making us do?
I'm scared! Aren't we in this together?
We are, so help me out!
I said I'm scared of this!
Will I have to confess again tomorrow?
Maybe I'll take the bottom off next.
The plan is pretty much perfect.
But will anything change because of this?
In the end, we'll just run around causing a ruckus as usual,
and then things will go back to normal, as usual.
That's all I thought would come of it.
Then the exam period ended.
Staff Building First Floor — Hall outside Staffroom
Tachibana?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Nothing.
The Next Day
They've started.
What has?
Rumors that Angel got all zeros on all the tests.
Seriously?
And that her answers made a mockery of the teachers.
It's gone that far?
What did you people do?
We flew, did tailspins, and sometimes jumped out windows.
What do you mean?
But wouldn't the teachers realize that it wasn't her doing, but rather someone's idea of a joke?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Teachers wouldn't know anything about that.
They only see what's in front of them.
The student council president turned in joke answers.
So, Angel's going to be punished for it.
Is that what that was about?
Did Tachibana defend herself?
No idea. And it was in every subject too.
How would she be able to explain her situation to every teacher in every subject?
From the teachers' perspective, she probably looks like a lone rebel.
A lone rebel...
Gymnasium
And then, a few days later,
a school-wide assembly was held.
And so, effective today,
Tachibana Kanade-san will be resigning from her position as student council president,
and the current vice-president Naoi-kun will be acting as president in her place.
No way!
She didn't resign, she was fired.
Yurippe...
She's been demoted to the same level as us common students.
Will she be able to stop us now that she's lost her moral backing?
We'll put Operation Tornado into action tonight.
That's the last song that Iwasawa left behind.
Is it really okay for me to sing this song?
I guess.
It depends on how well the fans react to this new song, "Thousand Enemies", and the second incarnation of GirlDeMo.
不機嫌そうな君と過ごして
fukigensou na kimi to sugoshite
Living with your attitude for so long,
分かったことが一つあるよ
wakatta koto ga hitotsu aru yo
There's one thing that I've learned
そんな振りして　戦うことに必死
sonna furi shite tatakau koto ni hisshi
You've been pretending, fighting so hard
Hey...
What are we fighting against?
Anyone who gets in our way, of course.
Who's going to get in our way?
If anyone comes, it'll be Angel.
Or maybe that acting student council president will come.
That guy's just a normal student.
We can't shoot him.
Yeah, I guess.
Will Angel come?
形ある　そんな心
katachi aru sonna kokoro
A clear-cut heart
誰だって気付けば持ってる
dare datte kitsukeba motteru
Anyone has one, once they realize
君も持ってる
kimi mo motteru
You have one too
She's here!
Let's do this before she activates her Guard Skill!
Wait, don't shoot!
Why not?
Something's strange about her.
Strange how?
I don't really get it!
It's not a change exactly, but she seems passive...
Like she's wandering towards some other objective...
What are you talking about?
いつまでも持ってたいよ　鋼のような
itsu made mo mottetai yo hagane no you na
A will like steel, letting nothing past
donna mono mo toosanai kakkona ishi wo
I want to hold on to mine forever
どんなものも通さない 確固な意思を
Angel??
What are the guys outside doing!?
What should we do?
Hold on a second.
What is this?
Something seems strange...
What is she...
That's the meal that no student ever eats, the famously super spicy Mapo tofu!
What's on going?
Why would she pick that?
Is she going to try to get revenge by making us eat it?
Yurippe-san, the audience looks like it's reached its highest level of excitement.
いつまでも一緒だから 恋人のように
itsu made mo issho dakara koibito no you ni
We're always together, like lovers
Your orders?
Turn them on!
Turn them on.
その気持ち　全部聞いてやる
sono kimochi zenbu kiiteyaru
Those feelings, I'll hear them all
君にも聞かす
kimi ni mo kikasu
I'll let you hear them, too
たっぷり聞かす
tappuri kikasu
I'll let you hear them all
What the...
Isn't that the super spicy Mapo tofu that no one dares ask for?
Even the tough guys order it with rice and eat it over rice.
This is what I picked up so I have no choice.
H-H-Hot!!
But it's good!
Try some, Hinata!
No way!
Maybe a little then...
Hot! Hot! It hurts!!
But the aftertaste is...
I see, this actually has a deep flavor!
Right?
You've never had Mapo tofu this good, right?
It may be an unexpected hit on the menu.
Angel bought that meal ticket.
This?
Yes.
She just wanted to eat this...
I'm sure this must be her favorite food.
I stole that simple pleasure from her...
Angel is human.
What kind of angel would go find her favorite meal for comfort food when feeling down?
She couldn't leave us be when she was the student council president because we were disruptive,
so she started developing Guard Skill to counter us making weapons at Guild.
Is that how things were?
What a joke.
And to think we still haven't found any clues about God...
Is it possible...
Maybe Angel could become one of us now?
What kind of stupid talk is that?!
After so many of our friends have fallen victim to her...
I mean... not victims, since they're all still here but...
Do you know how much pain she's put us through?!
That's right!
She might have been quiet today, but who knows when she'll bare her fangs again!
She'll slit our throats while we sleep!
Seems that was a silly question, Otonashi-kun.
Apparently.
I wonder why I made such a dumb proposition...
It's probably because the thought of her going to buy a meal ticket by herself,
then eating her Mapo tofu alone in a corner of the cafeteria...
The image of her like that is too sad.
Losing the trust placed in her and being stripped of her position...
Her lonely figure sitting there...
is just too sad.
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
Everyone becomes alone someday
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
What the hell do you want?!
They're ordinary students.
This is the end of the line.
You're under suspicion for various offenses,
but for now we're going to escort you all to the detention room for carrying out activities outside of curfew.
As the new student council president, I don't intend to give you any leeway.
Take them.
What's with these people?
That's the acting president of the student council.
That Naoi guy...
That's a stupid way to do it!
Angel is a necessary existence.
Are you admitting it?
What the hell do you want me to reflect on!?
Those kids are...
God!!
Wasn't your previous life also real to you?!