Haruka... Haruka.
Good morning.
Breakfast is ready.
What's for breakfast?
What could it be?
I know! Soft-boiled egg!
Huh?
You got it!
Yay!
Would you like some more coffee, dear?
Sure, that sounds good.
Mama, Papa said he'd rather have tea.
Is that true, dear?
Oh, well...
I don't know how you knew that, Haruka.
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
I win!
Okay, Yuu-chan, you're it!
It's always us! That's not fair, Haruka-chan!
Of course it's fair. It's rock-paper-scissors.
You're good at that game, Haruka-chan.
Why don't you try me, the Queen of rock-paper-scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
That was just sad, Sensei.
It's easy.
You're all saying what move you'll make.
Huh?
Papa! Mama! Look, look!
Grandpa bought it for me!
It's very cute, Haruka.
Yeah, you sure have grown.
Hey! Don't call me shorty!
Huh?
Hey, do any of you have a boy you like?
N-No way!
Boys are so immature.
Right, Haruka-chan?
Why are you all lying?
Huh?
Aya-chan, don't you like Kousuke-kun?
What?!
And Mai-chan likes Hajime-kun.
And Kaoru-chan...
Oh! Kaoru-chan likes Kousuke-kun, too!
Aya-chan, you like Kousuke-kun?!
N-No!
I don't like any boys!
Kaoru-chan has liked him ever since kindergarten, right?
I-I never said that!
I-I don't like Hajime-kun...
You've liked him since he helped you up when you fell, right?
What are you talking about?
Hey, that's great!
Hajime-kun likes you too, Mai-chan!
I do not!
I don't like Mai at all!
Stupid Haruka-chan! I hate you!
I never want to see you again, Haruka-chan!
We're not friends anymore!
Haruka is a compulsive liar?
Yes... You see, she often makes things up.
That can't be...
Some of her classmates have been hurt,
and we've received numerous complaints from their parents.
I'll let you deal with that.
But dear...
Isn't raising the child the mother's job?
I've got an early start tomorrow. I'm going to bed.
Hm, what could this be...
Your daughter is perfectly normal.
There's nothing more I can do.
What's that?! How rude!
Wait a minute!
Please, just leave!
Mama, am I sick?
No one will play with me.
Everyone says I'm a creepy girl who says strange things.
Dear, when are you coming home?
We need to talk about Haruka!
I told you that taking care of Haruka is your job.
Also, I don't think I'll be able to make it home from work tonight.
Dear?! Dear!
Something evil has possessed my daughter!
Please, do something to exorcise it!
I can't help you...
I am merely a simple monk.
Why...
Why my only child?
Mama.
Papa will come home tomorrow.
Shut up! Whose fault do you think this is?!
Grandpa, lately, Mama's been drinking a lot and getting mad so easily.
And Papa won't even come home.
Mama, and Papa, and my friends...
Do they all hate me?
Silly girl.
You know that's not true.
Hey, now.
You'll spend the entire day with us today, right?
I'm sorry, Haruka.
I have to go out this evening.
I've got plans as well.
Papa, you're going to a hotel with Akiko-san?
Wha—
And Mama, you're going to dinner with Mister Yoshino! No fair!
I'm going, too!
What is she talking about, dear?!
I-I don't know any woman by that name!
And what about you? Who is this man?!
Y-You have to believe me, dear!
She's just spouting nonsense and...
Again? You're doing it again?!
That's cruel, Haruka!
How badly must you destroy our lives before you're satisfied?!
Papa... Mama...
Wait, Kumiko!
You're leaving her as well?
What will you do about Haruka?
Father...
I don't care about that girl anymore!
What on earth are you saying?!
Mama, wait!
I'll never do anything to upset you again!
I'll even do the cooking and cleaning!
So Mama, please don't go!
Don't go! Don't—
Haruka!
What have you done?!
I should never have given birth to you.
Wait, Kumiko!
K-Kumiko-san!
...rry...
I'm sorry...
Monsters aren't welcome here!
I-I'm not...
She looked at us!
She's gonna read your mind!
That's why your parents abandoned you!
Monster! Monster! Monster!
Stop... I'm not! I'm not!
Liar!
I always thought something was weird.
You pretended to be our friend, so you could secretly read our minds and laugh at us.
N-No...
You're horrible!
Never come near us again!
Let's go.
Wait! We're best friends, aren't we?
Sorry... I can't.
Are you alone as well?
I can't hear your voice.
Are you the one who's been feeding that cat?
What a bother.
I took it to a shelter, so don't ever come here again.
I see. You're transferring?
Good luck at your new school.
Finally, we're rid of this troublemaker.
I'm Kotoura Haruka.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Kotoura...
This one's going to be a pain.
Sorry for being a pain.
What was that? What a freak.
Poor Manabe, having to sit beside her.
No matter where I go, it's always the same.
If only everyone would ignore me,
like he is...
I'd be satisfied.
Huh? Who are you?
Huh?
TLC
Tobikage
Timer
Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo AFX : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Kaitou[Kid]
QC
Robo731   Floris257
Encoder
Floris257
Kotoura-san and Manabe-kun
So, Kotoura-san, where did you move here from?
Not that I really want to know.
I should never have become the class representative.
If you don't want to know, then don't ask.
U-Uh, which club are you going to join?
Please don't join the tennis club...
Don't worry. I'm not interested in tennis.
Huh?
What's with her? Creepy...
Hey...
Manabe!
What's up, Moritani?
You remember that invitation I gave you?
Oh, the invitation to come to your house?
Yeah, yeah!
I refuse!
Isn't your house a karate dojo?
Not interested.
Shot down again...
She looked so disappointed.
She must really want my martial arts skills.
She's not after whatever skills you might or might not have.
Huh?
I heard you, so I just blurted that out.
Sorry.
You heard me?
Wait, did I say that out loud?
Oh, God! I'm so embarrassed!
Week Later
Weeks Later
Let's eat together, Kotoura-san.
That looks so good.
I wonder if she'd give me a bite?
Do what you want.
What? Really?!
Wow, thanks!
Whoa, it's delicious!
Did Kotoura make this?
I did.
That's awesome!
You really know what I'm thinking?
Just like everyone in class said!
But keep the magic tricks to a minimum, okay?
If you do too much, people will be intimidated by you,
and you'll find it hard to make friends.
That's none of your business, and it's not magic...
I get the croquette!
Hey! Don't just snatch that without asking!
Morning, Kotoura!
Mornin'!
One, two, three, four, five...
Kotoura! Partner up with me!
Hey, Manabe!
Over here!
You're not getting away!
Kotoura! We should walk home together sometimes!
I'm going this way.
I'm going this way, too!
So it seems.
Are you used to the school yet?
Aren't you going to make any friends?
Come on, talk to me!
Why are you hanging around me?
What do you mean, why? Of course I...
Wait, why do I?
You're such an idiot.
Oh, yeah! Hey, so tell me...
What's the secret to that mind reading trick you do?
That's so cool!
If I could read people's minds, I could do anything!
Idiot.
There's nothing cool about it.
You idiot.
Hey!
What do you mean, "idiot"?!
I called you an idiot because you're an idiot!
You don't know anything!
Kotoura!
I've been looking for you.
I noticed you weren't in the classroom.
So this is where you were.
Hey, Kotoura!
Now, let's not rush things.
We begin with a kiss, right?
What the heck are you thinking about?!
You really can read people's minds.
Is it ESP?
Yes, it is. Do you get it now?
If you don't want me reading more of your thoughts,
you should stay away from me.
But...
That means...
I have to keep the dirty thoughts in check!
This is very bad!
ESP's gonna be the end of me!
Not being able to think dirty thoughts is torture for a guy!
You're... not scared?
Sure I'm scared!
You're gonna treat me like a total pervert!
I'm exhausted...
What was all that about?
That Manabe-kun.
I've never met such a weirdo.
No.
I can't.
Pedestrians and
Bicycles Only
Hey, if it isn't Kotoura!
Ya-ho!
That looks heavy.
I'll carry it.
And you want something perverted in return, right?
No way!
Really.
You have no confidence in your own heart.
Come on, just hand it over.
Are these ingredients for dinner?
It's great that you help out at home.
I live alone.
Huh?
Pedestrians and
Bicycles Only
It's green.
O-Oh, right.
Are you all right?
Th-That was too close!
I read the driver's mind.
He didn't care that the light was red.
Kotoura...
Surely you get it now, don't you?
I'm just a creepy, mind-reading monster—
Thanks.
Hey, you're hurt!
I-It's no big deal.
Yes, it is!
Do you live nearby?
There, that should do it.
Th-Thanks.
So you really do live alone.
Where do your parents live?
I can't control my power.
Throughout my entire life, I've been inadvertently reading people's minds without realizing it,
and hurting them.
Kotoura...
I ruined everything.
The only thing I can do is make sure no one gets close to me.
So that's why, even at school, you...
Why are you trying to get close to me?!
Stop it! Leave me alone!
You're the one who'll end up getting hurt!
Is that okay with you?
You don't want to hurt anyone?
Don't give me that! You're the one who's hurting!
But there's nothing else I can do!
I don't like being alone, either!
I don't want to hurt people, or get hurt!
But what I hate the most is...
...is when...
...the people I care about leave me!
That's why I'm better off just being alone.
Look, Kotoura.
Regardless of whether you can read minds or not, people who want to leave are going to leave.
But not everyone is like that.
So let's try this, okay?
I'll stay with you.
No matter what happens, I won't leave.
How about it?
You... mean it?
Sure I do.
Actually, as far as I'm concerned, we're already friends.
Hey! Don't cry!
I'm not crying.
No, you totally are.
Why are you thinking about something that dirty right now?
Uh... W-Well...
Seeing a girl crying is kind of a turn-on, you know?
Y-You pervert! You're the Prince of dirty thoughts!
Who are you calling "the Prince of dirty thoughts"?!
Damn it! I hate these manly instincts!
Nice to meet you, Kotoura.
Same, Manabe-kun.
What's wrong, Kotoura? Why the glum face?
There are tons of people on the other side of the TV thinking dirty thoughts.
What'd you say?!
I'm the only one who's allowed to have dirty thoughts about Kotoura!
Episode 2
The First......
Shut up, you pervert.