After Dr. Wakaoji asked her what
she wanted to convey with "Eternal Snow,"
Mitsuki found an old music box
inside the storage shed.
It was a present that Mitsuki's father
gave to her mother a long time ago.
Takuto's Death Spirit Powers
revive the music box
and the melody to
"Eternal Snow" comes out.
After hearing this, Mitsuki discovers
her message.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
In this week's guest corner,
we have in our studio
Full Moon and Madoka Wakamatsu,
who will be competing with
their renditions of "Eternal Snow."
How are you two doing?!
- Hello.
- Hello!
Wow, so cute!
What are you holding
on your chest, Madoka?
Yes, this is my friend,
Gu the piglet.
How cute that
a piglet is your friend.
Thank you very much!
By the way, are you two doing
the recording on the same day
at the same studio
in this competition?
Yes.
Since it is the same song,
will they actually be
completely the same?
No, I believe that both the
arrangement and the image
will be very different.
Then, specifically,
how will it turn out?
That is a secret.
Oh, that's too bad.
How is yours progressing,
Full Moon?
Is it secret with you too?
Oh, that's not the case at all.
Tell you the truth, there's nothing
to even keep a secret about.
Huh? Really?
Yes. Actually, I haven't
been told anything.
Umm... Isn't your producer
a former member of Route L,
Mr. Oji?
Yes, Mr. Oji has only
told me to think very hard
about what I want to convey
in this song.
And what do you want to convey?
More than anything else,
I've been thinking
that I want to warm people's
hearts with music.
I see, to warm hearts.
Maybe that is Mr. Oji's goal.
What? Do you think so?
Thank you very much
for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Miss Sasaki, what was
with today's interview?
Wasn't my part short compared
to Full Moon's?!
Sorry, with the appearance of Oji,
the director suddenly...
The appearance of Oji?
Does Oji draw that much
more attention than Mr. Takasu?
Miss Wakamatsu!
Do you have some time?
Excuse me! Please stop it.
Didn't I tell you that we're not going
to take your magazine's coverage?
Umm... What's happening?
Everything's fine, Madoka.
He's from a tabloid magazine that
writes about scandals of young talents
and he's our enemy, so to speak!
That's rude, do you need
to say it to that extent?!
There are even stars that have
had their careers killed off
because of things written up in
this magazine, which were all lies!
Careers killed off?
Miss Sasaki! Do you have some time?
Yes!
Now, let's go!
Oh, yes.
Huh?
If you have any interesting
material related to stars,
I welcome it anytime.
I'll make sure to show my gratitude.
Okay, see you later!
Madoka? Hurry up
and come over here!
Oh, yes!
Mr. Oji, isn't it about time
to allow Full Moon to sing?
No, it's not that time yet.
Why?
Do you need a reason?
But Madoka Wakamatsu's side seems
to be rapidly progressing with their plan.
It doesn't matter.
Mr. Oji, don't you think the
staff is feeling dissatisfied too?
Full Moon surely feels that way too.
Schedule time is being taken
up for the preparation,
but she hasn't been allowed
to sing at all.
If she doesn't at least
do some warming up,
she won't suddenly be able to sing
in the actual take.
Do you think so?
What?
Don't worry. Please leave it to me.
Oh...
Mr. Oji...
Don't you want to sing soon, Mitsuki?
Yes.
I wonder if the recording
is really going to be all right?
I love you, my tears won't stop.
If this is how it's going to be,
I wish I had never met you
It's no good, stop it.
Yes sir.
What's wrong, Madoka?
I'm sorry.
You're not being yourself.
I fell in love with the
Madoka Wakamatsu
who's filled with more
self-confidence and dignity.
Yes, thank you very much.
Get back your usual self
by the main take.
Do you understand?
Did you hear the story about
Full Moon's new song?
Huh? What, what?
After Mr. Oji signed
on as a producer,
many famous musicians
have asked to participate in it
and it's going to be
an awesome line-up!
Wow, is that true?
Then isn't Madoka Wakamatsu
in trouble?
It seems like Mr. Takasu is
going to completely lose face.
Oops! Hush!
What on earth am I doing wrong?
I don't understand what
Mr. Takasu is demanding from me.
Huh?
Didn't I tell you not
to nestle close to me
when people are not looking?!
I'm only keeping you for
my image as a gentle, animal loving girl!
If you don't stop it,
I'll change your name
to "Yummy-looking."
Oh, darn it!
I'm going to lose if it
stays like this.
What should I do?
Oh...
If you have any interesting material,
I welcome it anytime.
There are even stars that
have had their careers killed off.
Hello?
Is this Mr. Yomitani?
That doctor!
I wonder why he called you
out all of a sudden.
I don't know. Maybe it's time
for him to finally let me sing.
That's possible.
Mitsuki!
Dr. Wakaoji, I'm sorry I was late!
That's fine, but what did
you need to talk to me about?
I came here because I was told
that you needed to talk to me.
What? I came here because
I was called out by you.
I was also told to come here.
Who was that guy?
What was that just now?
That's gonna be a problem.
What? What do you
mean by "a problem"?
Anyhow, we should contact Ms. Oshige.
Who cares about the director?
I have my own circumstances over here!
Old man, one more drink!
Yes!
I'm not getting through to her.
Dr. Wakaoji? What has happened?
Listen to what I say carefully.
All right?
Yes...
Maybe I drank a bit
too much last night.
It's this morning's
"Fresh-Picked Entertainment News."
We'll turn this corner over
to Mr. Kinoshita.
Okay, now for
"Fresh Picked Entertainment News"
- Huh?
- and today's first story.
- Mr. Wakaoji called me yesterday.
- She's now the number one
pop idol, Full Moon.
The photo of her with the producer,
Mr. Oji, was published
in a weekly photo magazine
on sale today!
What the—?!
It happened at an Italian restaurant
famous for being
a date spot for celebrities.
W-What...
What is this?!
Speaking of Full Moon's
companion producer Mr. Oji,
he used to play the
keyboard for Route L,
but has returned to the music industry
this time to produce for Full Moon.
BIG SCOOP!
FULL MOON (16) ON SECRET DATE
WITH HER PRODUCER
Wow, what is this?!
Isn't this it?
The thing they were showing
on TV this morning.
Yeah, yeah. Full Moon is
going out with the producer.
What? That's so shocking!
Hey, we're going.
Okay.
And I liked her so much!
What was that?
Did you actually have a photo taken?
Yeah.
Wait a minute! Isn't that bad?
But...
What happened just now
is like an accident
that a young female singer
like you comes across now and then.
Even if you're being careful,
an accident just happens
when it happens.
You're not the one at fault.
Neither am I.
We just had a little bad luck.
People forget about
silly rumors quickly.
But you might need
some perseverance until then.
Mitsuki, do you think
you can handle it?
Yes.
Good, I'll be with you.
You don't need to worry.
Yes!
So that's what happened.
He's surprisingly dependable.
Yes. I felt really glad that I asked
Dr. Wakaoji to produce for me.
I think so too.
He is really an adult.
To tell the truth,
I didn't know what to
say at that time.
What is this?
Isn't this a lack of oversight?
I-I'm sorry.
First of all, I don't care
if it is Oji or whoever,
but is the recording actually
going to be done?
If I don't hear some material soon,
I won't know what to tell Mr. Miyata.
Yes. That's...
SCOOP!
WE DELVE INTO
FULL MOON'S PRIVATE LIFE
Will I be able to let go of
these thoughts of you?
Hold me tight,
if this is how it feels
to fall in love with someone,
I wish I never knew.
I love you,
my tears won't stop.
If this is how it's going to be
I wish I had never met you.
Umm... Mr. Takasu?
Huh? Oh yeah.
How was my singing?
There's something that weighs
on my mind, no matter what.
Huh?
Let's end it here for today.
Mr. Takasu?
I really want to sing this one song.
Grandma, please make sure
to listen to my song someday.
And please come to like,
even a little bit,
music that you've hated for so long.
TODAY'S RECORDING SCHEDULE:
A. FULL MOON 1:00 - 6:00
B. MADOKA WAKAMATSU 1:00 - 8:00
There's a huge group of reporters.
That's because it's right after
Full Moon had that kind of a scandal.
Mr. Oji seems to have
already entered.
Will Full Moon come?
Well, don't you think it's impossible?
There's even a rumor that
the release is going to be postponed.
What?! Is that true?
Good morning!
What? She's here?
Hello, I look for your guidance today.
Oh? Yes...me too.
Hey, how do you feel?
I have so much desire
to sing right now,
I feel like my chest is
going to burst open!
Good, then let's begin.
The emotion that piled up inside me
while I didn't sing all that time...
I hope this song will warm
the hearts of people who listen to it.
I hope they are wrapped up
by a warm happiness.
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep getting stronger.
I wonder if you can notice them?
Even though
- Can it be that...
- I've never mentioned it,
I've never mentioned it,
they're silent like this snow.
But they...
You planned it like this...
by not having her sing until now.
...keep building up.
You really feel Full Moon's desire
- to sing the song.
- Hold me tight,
- I became quite nervous, but...
- if loving someone
was going to feel like this,
I wish I never found out about love.
I love you, my tears won't stop.
Where is Mr. Takasu?
- He's late.
- If this is how it's going to be,
- Good morning, sir!
I wish I never
- Mr. Takasu...
- I wish I never
- I look forward to your guidance today!
- found out about love.
- Then let's begin at once.
Madoka, be on stand-by.
Yes...
Madoka!
Yes!
Please come over here.
Yes.
I thought about doing it
after the recording,
but I wanted to take it upon
myself to talk to you about it now.
Yes.
Do you not believe in me?
What?
I heard about the story
from the editorial staff.
Umm... There is a reason for this.
Reason?
Umm... Well, I mean...
What kind of reason is there?
In this world, no matter what
kind of dirty thing you do,
the one who's standing
in the end is the winner.
I won't make a pretty statement like
saying that what you did is dirty.
But you don't believe in me.
That's...
I believed in you.
Huh?
I told you before.
I can only work with somebody
who believes in my skill.
I intend to settle what happened
this time in my own way.
What do you—?
We will perform the recording
as planned.
But after today,
I will step down from producing you.
I believed in you.
What in the world happened?
I have no idea.
Madoka...
Oh, Mr. Takasu...
What happened with
Madoka Wakamatsu?
I'm sorry, Ms. Oshige.
Mr. Takasu...
Madoka...
You should think hard one more time
about the reason why you want to sing.
That's all I can say.
You should think hard one more time
about the reason why you want to sing.
The reason why I want to sing.
If I don't know that reason,
will I be unable to sing
like she was?
The time's finally come for Meroko
to put on a stellar performance!
Okay, okay.
So what's it this time?
A school friend of Mitsuki
is confused
and decided that she's
an expert in the matters of love
and is asking her for advice!
Huh? How could she
be an expert in love?
Right? And so it's now time
for me to help out!
That is a bit weird too!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Is Mitsuki an Expert on Love?"
- Look forward to it!