I hate being right.
No time to lose! Move it!
She's coming for us!
After making a sudden reappearance,
the Female Titan wiped out the Levi
Squad's most elite soldiers, one by one.
I'm gonna...
Kill you!
Blaming himself for their deaths,
Eren turned back to face the enemy,
unleashing a furious assault in his Titan form.
Yet for all his rage, Eren was defeated,
and taken by the Female Titan.
Do you hear me? Give him back!
I know you're in there.
And after I kill her, I'll carve out her insides,
and pull you out again. I swear I will.
Just hang on a little longer.
Don't give up, Eren.
Never give up!
Get back here!
What?
We'll stay back for now.
Maintain current distance.
She's slowed down a bit.
That fight wore her out, too.
It looked like she may have bitten the entire nape off.
It's unlikely Eren survived.
He's still alive in there.
This Titan is different; it acts with purpose.
If she wanted Eren dead, she could've simply crushed him.
No, she needs him for something.
But she also needs her hands to fight,
so she's been holding him on her tongue.
It is possible she just wanted to savor her quarry.
In which case it's likely he's already been swallowed.
If so, he's dead.
He's alive.
Someone's optimistic.
If you had just done your damn
job and protected him like you
were supposed to, we wouldn't be having this conversation!
Oh, I see now. The "childhood friend", right?
Suddenly it's all making sense.
Right. For the sake of argument, let's narrow our goals.
First, we forget about taking her down.
No way. She's killed too many of our people for that.
She's dead.
She's got defenses that neither
of us has been trained to deal with.
I'm telling you it's a lost cause.
Instead, we'll act on your assumption that Eren is alive,
and focus only on freeing him before she exits the forest.
I'll handle all the cutting.
You find a way to distract her.
Right.
He's fast!
She can't even react! Her skin can't harden in time!
Her nape. It's wide open!
It looks like her whole body's gone limp.
Now's my chance!
Don't do it!
Eren!
Got him!
Time to go.
Eren.
He's alright. Disgusting, but alright.
What'd I tell you about trying
to take her down? Now come on.
We've got Eren. That means our work here is done.
Don't screw this up by making it personal, you understand?
We all get that you love him, but try not to act crazy.
I... I was just...
They're already on the way back?
Is that bad?
Probably. Odds are they'll have
a stack of fresh corpses in tow.
It sounds like Eld will be home sooner than we thought.
Is that so?
Think they'll give Oruo enough
time to pop by and say hello?
I suppose in any event we can
set a place for him at the table.
They say Gunther's coming back.
Do they?
This is the part of our job I'll never get used to.
You're not alone in that.
Seems like death's just everywhere.
All I can think about is how it'll end.
Which one of us is next and whether it'll be me.
Try not to obsess over it.
Only thing that train of thought's good
for is breaking your nerve. Believe me.
Push it out of your mind.
I s'pose you're right.
Nah, I know you're right.
So how much longer 'til our number's up, you think?
I dunno, but we've made it this far.
Yeah, luck of the draw.
So what? We're alive. Be glad for it.
Sorry, it's kinda hard to celebrate around so many bodies.
They'll never see home again. Why should we?
Almost done, sir.
We estimate about five to be unrecoverable.
Not even an arm or a leg?
Sadly, the Titans didn't leave much behind.
And honestly sir, I think it would be best for the
families if we didn't bring back what little there is.
We'll put them down as "missing".
Sir.
Also, sir. Our spotters report several
Titans have emerged from the forest.
Fortunately, none yet seem to be headed in our direction.
We move out immediately. Inform the squads.
Sir.
No! I refuse! It's inhumane!
Damn you, shut up!
We can't just leave 'em out here! He was
there! I saw Ivan's body. He was right in front us!
And if you didn't notice, there were Titans nearby.
Go back and we could wind up dead ourselves.
So if they attack, we'll fight! It's what we do, right?
Ivan and me, we grew up in the same town together.
His parents are like family to me!
I can't face them again if we leave him!
Sentimental garbage!
Stop shrieking.
Captain Levi!
If you've already confirmed his
death, then there's nothing more to do.
Whether we have his body or not makes no difference now.
He's still just as dead either way.
That's cold.
Ivan and the others will be listed as missing in action.
That's my decision and it's final. Now let it go.
You heartless bastards!
That's the kind of respect you show
the men who give their lives for you?
Unless you want to be MIA, I suggest you shut your mouth!
Wait!
Heads up! We've got company!
Titans!
Is that...?
Dieter!
That damn fool.
Enemy spotted at the rear!
Full speed! All soldiers!
Our best chance might be to circle
back, make a beeline for the trees.
We can't put up much of a fight out here.
No, our best option now is to continue to the wall.
It's about to be right on top of us!
Looks like we've got no choice but to fight!
Ground's too flat to engage ODM gear. And not only that...
We'll soon be outnumbered.
Perfect. Then what do you suggest we do, genius?
The only thing we can.
We're done! It's gaining on us!
I'll jump behind the bastard and distract him!
Give you a chance to put some distance...
Don't bother.
You've got to jettison the extra weight.
Dump the bodies.
B-B-But, sir!
Do you know how many corpses we've already left behind?
These aren't special. Dump them!
Consider it their last service to the cause.
Are we doing this? We can't seriously be doing this!
Damn it.
I'm sorry, there's just no other way!
That's it! We're losing him!
Alright, soldiers, look sharp. We head
out the moment our positions are confirmed.
A minor course correction to the East should work.
Captain, I... I wanted to say.
We can't always carry our fallen comrades home,
but we carry their memory.
This was Ivan's.
Thank you, sir.
Let's move 'em out!
Eren. You should let the Scout Regiment thing go.
Seriously? Why does everybody think they're a joke?
What people think about 'em isn't really the issue.
Perfect timing! They're back!
We can make it if we hurry.
Get a move on! I want a good view!
Sure taken a hit, haven't they?
Yeah. Rest of 'em got eaten.
That's what happens when pride
takes you outside the walls.
Nothing like seeing our hard earned taxes go
toward keeping those bastards fat and happy, right?
Eren.
What is it?
Talk to me.
Eren!
Easy.
Don't try to move just yet.
You need rest.
Where's the Female Titan?
She got away from us.
What do you mean? She... She was... We were...
What about the mission?
It didn't go as planned.
But don't worry about that right now.
How'd I get here?
Did you have to step in and save me again? Is that it?
Look. We're almost home, okay?
Am I miscounting, or are there
fewer of 'em than when they left?
No, there's a lot fewer.
Must've been a bad one.
I don't get it. They were all piss and
vinegar this morning. They're already back?
Hell, why bother leavin' in the first place?
No idea. I'd say by the looks on
their faces they hoped to be gone longer.
Our taxes hard at work, ladies and gentlemen. Bravo.
Eren. Ignore it.
Awesome! Beat, but they're still ready to go!
You gotta be made of nails to ride with these guys!
They're unstoppable!
Excuse me, Captain Levi?
G-Good evening. I, uh... Yes.
I'm Petra's father, sir.
Might I bend your ear before she sees us?
I received this letter from her somewhat recently.
Apparently you handpicked her yourself?
She's very excited, I can assure you.
In fact, it sounds like she's
utterly devoted to you in every way.
So devoted that, well, to be honest her
mother and I are a bit concerned, you see.
Now, I... I know that fathers can have trouble letting go.
But still, I can't help but feel she's
far too young to be thinking about marriage.
She has so much yet to experience before settling down.
Give us some answers, damn you! We have a right!
How many lives were lost on this mission?
Was it worth it? Was is really worth it?
You think the last thing going through
their minds was "for the good of humanity?"
The causalities incurred during the Scout Regiment's
latest excursion beyond the wall were profound.
So much so, that what little public
favor they still held was all but crushed.
Within hours of their return,
Erwin and the battle-weary
survivors were called to the capital.
The Scouts' custody of Eren was summarily revoked.
Having been assigned to the elite security
escort team the day Eren is summoned to the capital,
Annie faces a dilemma when Armin emerges from the shadows,
imploring her help in a secret
mission of vital importance.