W-Well, that one wasn't a joke!
Minami-chan really does feel...
W-Well, that wasn't a joke!
We're seriously gonna kill you!
Minami-chan...
She really...
does feel that way.
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 9
Me, Romance, and Diplomacy!
A week after the training camp, the second year boys have returned from suspension.
Yuuji.
Hm?
What is—
Whoa, scary!
Don't dodge.
Of course I'm gonna dodge if you try to headbutt me!
It was a kiss, not a headbutt.
All right, don't move from there.
Put your hands behind your head and slowly explain.
Touching lips, smooching,
something that's only natural for two who have vowed to spend their future together.
Wait, I know all about kissing.
I'm asking why—
When, where, and with whom?
No, I'm saying I know the definition, not that I have experience.
I see. That's fine then.
I thought I was gonna die.
What brought this on?
Those two were kissing just now.
Seriously?!
Jeez, Akihisa's being an idiot, as always.
He should've known that's what a kiss would get him.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Actually, when you were asleep...
All right!
We've located another heretic!
All right, take him away.
Stop! I didn't do anything!
I'm sorry! Please, stop!
Though I could only kiss your cheek
because you rolled over in your sleep.
Brethren, where are we?
The courtroom where we deliver final judgment!
The heretics will face...
the Iron Hammer of Death!
Good. We will now commence the heretic's hearing.
Huh? Yuuji, what are you doing here?
I got dragged in because of you!
Read them their charges.
Defendant, Yoshii Akihisa,
Yoshii Akihisa
will henceforth be referred to as The First Party,
First Party
Yoshii Akihisa
Shimada Minami
and in a similar fashion, Shimada, as Flat Chest.
Flat Chest
First Party
The defendant has been charged with an act of treason for opposing our doctrine.
Early this morning, The First Party performed a coercive act of indecency on Flat Chest,
First Party
Flat Chest
and one of our brethren secured him.
We intend to perform a thorough investigation of the relationship between The First Party and Flat Chest,
First Party
Flat Chest
Investigation
First Party
after which we will outline the proper measures to be taken against The First Party and the watch to place on Flat Chest...
Flat Chest
State the conclusions only.
First Party
Flat Chest
Conclusion
First Party
Flat Chest
Conclusion
I'm jealous that they were kissing!
Verdict: death penalty.
Death Penalty
Wait, Akihisa, what's going on?
That's what I'd like to know.
Does anything ring a bell?
When was the last time you met Shimada?
The last night of the training camp, I guess.
Oh, back then.
Minami sneaked in when you were all fast asleep.
And you didn't think that was strange?
I thought for sure that she came to assassinate me.
Then what were you talking about before that?
Let's see...
Shimada Minami
I
I wa
I wan
I want
I want to
I want to ta
I want to talk
I want to talk to
I want to talk to yo
I want to talk to you
I want to talk to you abou
I want to talk to you about
I want to talk to you about so
I want to talk to you about some
I want to talk to you about something,
can
can you
I want to talk to you about something,
can you come
can you come over
I want to talk to you about something,
can you come over to
can you come over to my
I want to talk to you about something,
can you come over to my room
can you come over to my room?
Yoshii Akihisa
I
I don't
I don't rea
I don't really
I don't really mi
I don't really mind
I don't really mind.
W
Wh
I don't really mind.
Why
Why th
I don't really mind.
Why thi
Why this
I don't really mind.
Why this la
Why this late
I don't really mind.
Why this late at
Why this late at nigh
I don't really mind.
Why this late at night,
Why this late at night, th
I don't really mind.
Why this late at night, thou
Why this late at night, though?
Shimada Minami
O
Ob
Obv
Obvi
Obviou
Obvious
Obviously,
Obviously, it
Obviously, it's
Obviously, it's be
Obviously, it's beca
Obviously, it's becau
Obviously, it's because
Obviously, it's because o
Obviously, it's because of
Obviously, it's because of m
Obviously, it's because of my
Obviously, it's because of my l
Obviously, it's because of my lov
Obviously, it's because of my love
Obviously, it's because of my love!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
No, never mind.
So what were you talking about?
Something like a confession of love.
Shimada to you?
No... me to Minami.
That should've totally set bells ringing!
Heretic Yoshii Akihisa, will you accept the sentence and repent for your sins?
The sentence?
Special bungee jump penalty.
What is that, exactly?
I can only give you a hint to save you unnecessary anxiety.
It's like skydiving without a parachute.
It's totally obvious! No bungee?! Will I be doing a bungee jump without the bungee?!
Oh, it's Himeji-san! Save me, Himeji-san!
Minami-chan does love Akihisa-kun...
Minami-chan...
Eh, you're still on that?
Yoshii and Shimada made eye contact!
I thought I'd have a chance with Flat Chest!
If he took Shimada on top of Himeji and Kinoshita,
Aki-chan would be the only hope left!
Aki-chan
G-Good morning, Aki.
Y-Yeah, good morning.
Um, can I share your table?
Eh?
Mine broke.
Oh, no choice then.
Go ahead.
Thanks!
Why have you gone all quiet?
Well, aren't we a little close?
There isn't much room, though.
You're right.
Say, Aki, um... I'm not forcing you,
but do you want to have lunch together?
I packed a boxed lunch fo—
What are you doing, Darling?
Sh-Shimizu-san?!
I won't let this pig get close to you, Darling!
I-I've got no choice! My table broke, after all.
But you don't have to share with this pig!
Grumble grumble grumble
Minami-chan does love Akihisa-kun...
But Mizuki and the rest are hard at work studying.
I don't want to disturb them.
Aki's grades are going to be poor either way.
I feel like you just said something bad about me.
Unforgivable! Your handmade boxed lunch would be wasted on this disgusting pig!
The fries you seasoned with your handmade sauce at four in the morning!
The Salisbury steak made with the ground meat you bought especially for it!
The potato salad made with pesticide-free vegetables!
How do you know about all that?!
Not to mention the rice with the heart on it!
Miharu!
Um, Miharu, I've been putting off saying it, but you need to stop doing things like this.
I mean...
I'm going out with Aki.
Tatami Flip!
Tch!
So, Miharu, please understand.
I don't want to! We'll get married and call our daughter Mirai, taking the "Mi" from your name!
Wait, Shimizu-san!
What will you do if you get a son?
"Namihei" would do for a boy!
Never mind all that, we couldn't have a child!
Class is about to begin.
Why are you here, Shimizu? Go back to your own class.
I have important business!
Please overlook me being here!
Important business?
Yes, the very important business of
annihilating all the pigs from this classroom!
You are forbidden from entering this classroom from now on.
That pig!
You're in trouble all the time.
Always the talk of the town.
Don't say that. It isn't really my fault.
Actually, thanks to you, this is
gonna be a real pain in the ass.
Huh?
There's been a movement within Class D to begin an ESB.
It doesn't really matter to us whether Class D
begins an ESB with another class, does it?
Even if they're coming after us?
What?!
But we have the worst facilities in the school!
They won't gain anything.
Don't tell me...
Yes. Shimizu's taking it out on us.
In order to get Shimada off of your table,
she's trying to force us back to using the orange boxes again.
But the whole of Class D won't just blindly follow Shimizu-san...
We were the main culprits in the group peeping;
all girls consider us their enemies.
Flat Chest
Class D's rep is Hiraga Genji,
but I doubt he can keep Shimizu's jealousy and the girls' thirst for revenge in check.
No way!
Because of last week's suspension, us guys still haven't recovered our points.
We'll be overpowered, even with Himeji on our side.
There's only one other way: to avoid the battle.
Is that really possible?
It's up to you and Shimada.
I want to confirm one thing.
What is it?
Are you and Shimada really going out?
As best as I can remember, probably not.
It's probably because of the mix-up with the texts.
The mix-up?
I see now.
Akihisa aside, you couldn't have
chosen worse timing, Yuuji.
I see.
My bad, Akihisa.
Then, clear that up with Shimada and get your relationship back to normal.
That'll settle down Shimizu as well.
That's...
Muttsurini, is one of Shimizu's surveillance bugs here?
I did find one. I removed it, simulating device failure.
What did you want to talk about?
The thing is, that text I sent you
during the training camp...
That was actually... actually a misunderstanding.
Huh?
Well, misunderstanding as in
I sent it to the wrong person.
Who was it for?
Sugawa-kun, I guess.
What?! You were going to confess to Sugawa?!
No way! I thought you were only interested in girls!
No, no, that's not it.
Yoshii Akihisa
Back
Accept
Yoshii, why are you
trying so hard to p
trying so hard to peep
Yoshii, why are you
trying so hard to peep?
Obviously, it's because of my love!
Shimada Minami
Compose New SMS
That's awful on so many levels.
Sorry!
Anyway, like I said, I messed up.
I see! I thought something was
off, too. Now it makes sense!
Minami, you were a bit careless too.
Jeez, I don't want to hear that from someone who sends texts to the wrong people!
What are you going to do about my first kiss?!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Saying sorry isn't gonna cut it!
Th-Then...
What is it?
I-It was...
my first too, so we're even. Okay?
Of course it's not!
Eh? I-I see.
That's... Well... Thanks for the kiss...
She's okay with it?!
Um, Minami, I want you to answer
me without getting angry.
What is it?
You told Shimizu-san we were going out, remember?
Does that mean you...
Th-That was...
That was, you know, because Miharu was too clingy. I thought she'd give up if I said I've got a boyfriend!
It seemed like the perfect time.
That's a pretty lame excuse.
She's not being honest.
You should've told me earlier.
I thought you were in love with me there.
O-Of course not!
I thought something was wrong, too.
You're never that sweet—
You're dislocating my arm!
That clears up the misunderstanding.
Once we tell Shimizu this,
everything will be resolved.
Thus a battle with Class D has been avoided.
However...
Question 9
Transliterate the following
phrase into English.
haatofuru rabusutoorii
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
heartful love story
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Although this is used quite
often as a catchphrase for books and
movies, some people mistake the
"heart" part. It's an example of a
familiar word that some find
unexpectedly difficult. On an
unrelated note, it's "ai ni michita
koimonogatari" when translated into
Japanese, and I wish all of you can
spend the days of your youth like in
a "heartful love story".
Shimada Minami's Answer
hurt full rough story
Teacher's Comment
"hurt" means injuries.
"full" means containing much of something.
"rough" means coarse or rude.
"story" means a tale.
You are so wrong that it seems as if you
purposely came up with this answer. I
think you're the only one whose life could
be described as a "hurt full rough story".
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
hurt full rough story
Teacher's Comment
Oh, I did not expect another one.
Listen to this.
The situation has worsened.
Beep
Um, is it true that you have
photos of Akihisa in a sailor suit?
They're 100 yen each. No unauthorized reproduction.
I'll take everything you've g—
Beep
Oops, wrong one.
What was that?! That sounded pretty bad for me!
Shut up, Akihisa. Don't sweat the small stuff.
It's not small stuff!
Why is there a black market for
my photos just like Hideyoshi's?
Stop right there, Akihisa!
In that case, things are even worse for me!
This is the right one.
How's it going in Class F?
They haven't noticed our moves at all.
Good. Let's use this chance to rebuild our points.
We'll declare an ESB against them
immediately if they find out about it.
Wait, I thought Class D wouldn't attack us!
You've got it wrong.
This ain't Class D.
It was the guys from...
Class B.
Damn that sneaky bastard Nemoto!
Why would they start a fight with us?
Nemoto's been in a pretty bad
situation since he lost to us.
He also got other boys to
participate in Operation Peep,
which failed miserably.
He's probably starting to lose authority in Class B.
That's why, to quell the dissatisfaction of his classmates,
Dissatisfaction
Cross-dresser
Enemy
he's going to create a new enemy.
That way he can direct all that dissatisfaction on to us by making us the enemy.
So he's just using us to shore up his own position, huh?
Eh?! If they attacked with our scores as low as they are, our loss would be a absolute!
Guess we'll just have to create a situation where they can't start an ESB with us.
You can do that?
Yeah. We just need some other class to start one before they do.
Declaration of War
That means...
We're going to make Class D start an ESB with us.
You're kidding! Didn't we just clear things up with Shimizu-san to avoid a fight with them?
Declaration of War
We'll be given time to replenish
our scores once the battle starts.
Declaration of War
+Time
+Replenish
This way we can take it easy and use the time to build up our scores.
+Time
+Replenish
I see! Class B would hesitate to attack us when we're at full strength.
But Yuuji, as things are, we won't even win against Class D.
I have another plan to deal with that.
Anyway, for now, we'll provoke Class D
into starting a battle with us.
How do we do that?
Just do what you did this morning.
Cling onto Shimada and make Shimizu rage.
Eh?!
No way in hell!
Please!
You won't change my mind!
Asking me to act like this idiot's girlfriend isn't funny!
Shimada! You're the only person who can do this!
We'll go back to using orange boxes if Class B attacks us now!
Himeji's parents will start worrying again if that happens,
Mizuki
Parents
Worried
and this time she might really be transferred out.
Transfer
I need your help as well, Himeji.
Me too?
Yes. Shimada alone won't be convincing enough.
I want you to act green with envy at their relationship.
Is that... too much to ask for?
Um, Minami-chan, Akihisa-kun!
I know you're not thrilled about this, but please!
Mizuki...
I'm sorry for being so selfish,
but I still want to stay at this school.
So please...
I-I got it! I just have to act, right?
Thank you so much!
Now that it's decided, let's get started!
Is this the script?
Hmm, let's see...
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly, Aki.
You know, I love you.
I always felt that way too, Minami.
Wait, what's with these lines?!
I can't read this!
I know it's an act, but still, it's just too embarrassing!
Oh well, then let me show you how it's done.
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly, Aki.
You know, I...
I love you, Aki.
I fell for you the moment I laid eyes on you.
Being "just another friend" has
always been so painful for me.
I've always longed to be more than just friends.
Aki, sorry for being so forward,
but I want you to know that I love you.
Will you go out with me?
And that's how it's done.
I-Incredible.
That made my heart race.
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Will you leave me alone just a while longer?
Huh?
There are some dreams that you
just don't want to wake up from.
Jeez.
Muttsurini, put that surveillance bug back on the roof.
Got it.
You three will stage your performance there.
I'm sure Shimizu will listen to the act and think exactly what we want.
The setting will be Shimada and Akihisa having a lovers' rendezvous on the roof.
You two need to go there arm-in-arm.
Arm-in-arm?!
But—
Good luck, and clean up your act.
F-Fine...
I'll send you straight to hell
if you touch anywhere strange.
It's hard to walk when you're holding on to me so tightly.
It's only normal; we're going out together!
But my elbow's touching your... there.
Eh?
Y-You pervert...
Your rib, I mean—
Bear it! I need to keep up the act!
Hey, Minami!
What is it, Aki?
Minami, what do you like about me?
Isn't that obvious?
From the top of your head...
From there to where?
...to your eyebrows.
Oh, my forehead.
What are you two doing?
Mizuki...
You're arm-in-arm, and so close...
It makes it look just like you two...
are going out together!
Huh?
Was there a line like that in the script?
I see! She's ad-libbing!
You're right, Mizuki.
I'm going out with Aki.
Is that really true?
Yes.
Sorry for keeping it from you, Mizuki.
Minami-chan!
So you really do like him?
Sorry for keeping that from you, too.
I knew how you felt about him.
Sorry. You'll never forgive me, will you?
No, I sort of knew already how you felt.
Actually, I'm relieved now that it's out in the open.
So you'll forgive me?
It's not a matter of forgiveness.
I believe everyone's free to choose in love.
That's why I can't hold it against you.
Mizuki...
Thank you.
But...
I won't forgive that kiss you gave him this morning!
It was criminal!
And it was his first kiss!
Well, I got those texts from him,
and it just sort of happened...
Just happened?! Even if God forgives you, I won't!
Isn't that the surveillance bug?!
Minami-chan... you idiot!
Oh no! It's all over if Himeji-san drops out of character with that thing on!
Himeji-san!
Wai— Hold it right there, Aki!
What are you doing, Aki?!
Are you choosing her over me?
I'm sorry! I need to do this!
Aki! Stay with me!
I...
Aki, I...
love you.
So that's... how it is.
Calm down, Shimada.
Don't say anything careless—
It's all right.
I'm done with the act.
Aki prefers proper girls like Mizuki anyway.
Himeji-san.
Akihisa-kun!
Thank you.
I hadn't noticed it.
What's wrong, Himeji-san?
You don't look well.
You can tell?
Yeah, you look kinda lonely.
Lonely, huh?
That must be the sadness,
from having someone you love taken away from you.
Even if it was just an act.
Don't worry about it. It was just pretend.
You're right.
It was pretend.
I'd get a little jealous too.
Eh?
That is, if there were some other guy you two fell in love with, even if it was just an act.
Huh?
If that really were to happen,
what would you do, Akihisa-kun?
Eh?
Let's see...
I guess I'd just think as hard as I could.
I guess I'd think real hard about what to do.
You'd... think hard?
Yeah. I'd think hard, in my own way.
And then I'd lay it all bare.
What I meant was who you'd choose...
Eh?
It's nothing! Don't worry about it!
But boy was I surprised!
By what?
It really didn't seem like an act just now!
Don't tell me, you...
Eh?
Eh?!
...have some acting experience?
Oh.
Ah.
Himeji-san...?
Idiot.
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Question 10
Answer the following question.
Give examples of ingredients
that are added to miso soup
as a supplement for the
nutrients that miso lacks.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Green onions
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Other vegetables
that contain vitamin C such
as onions and crown daisies
would also be good answers.
Miso is very good for your
body as it is rich in Vitamin
B and contains soy protein.
On the other hand, it has
high salt content, so be
careful not to consume
too much sodium.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 10: Give examples of ingredients that are added to
miso soup as a supplement for the nutrients that miso lacks.
Vitamin C - Oranges,
Vitamin C - Oranges, hydrochloric acid.
hydrochloric acid
Would that still be food?
Next episode: Me, Romance, and the Art of Love!
Me, Romance, and the Art of Love!
This will be on your test.