I managed to start walking home with Kawai under the pretext of keeping her safe,
but it's kinda sad how we're just
"walking home together" and nothing else.
I guess I can deal.
Hey, we're here.
We're hom—
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Five
I Knew It
As I arrived home from school...
Stop it!
Come on. Just for a bit, okay?
I saw one of the residents being assaulted by another right at the entrance.
You're giving off the scent of a crazed man!
And yet, it didn't bother me. It's frightening how easily we grow accustomed to things.
Enough enlightenment! Help me, you fool!
Sayaka, knock it off.
The entrance is no place for this. Take it to your room.
You're not helping, Ricchan!
Oh, come off it.
She reeks of booze!
Don't you think it's a bit early for you two to be drinking?
Hey, I haven't had a drop!
When I got home from work...
I'm home.
I found Sayaka waiting in ambush right by the entrance.
That sounds scary as hell!
I just wanna give you a welcome-back hug and kiss.
Sorry, but I'm Japanese!
Have you been listening to me at all?
Just a little peck.
Why are you making me sound
like the unreasonable one here?!
Just a little.
Hey! Your tongue's raring to go!
Now, now. Don't be a spoilsport.
Why are you playing around by the entrance?
Would you like a squeeze? Well, would you?
Could I go next, please?
Mayumi's
Sumiko's
I'm sorry.
Mayumi's
Sumiko's
Have you been drinking alone ever
since you got back this afternoon?
Did something happen?
Well, I went drinking with my circle yesterday...
Didn't you just destroy your circle recently?
This is a new one.
100 Sayakas says it's gone within two months.
Thanks.
What a scary conversation.
I met up with another member for an afterparty, but one of their friends was an ex of mine.
Wow, awkward.
I kept smiling because I didn't
want to bring down the mood,
but he took it the wrong way and wouldn't leave me alone.
And then he plastered his mouth on my face.
I took my heels off and drove them into his
crotch with ball-breaking force, which helped,
but I needed Mayumi's lips to wash the horrible taste away.
Aww. That makes no sense.
Exes give me the creeps.
I nearly barfed back there.
Actually, I should have.
You don't have to be that harsh.
Well, men do tend to have a hard time moving on.
They don't get that we've
completely forgotten about them.
Look who's talking.
Your three-timing ex...
...had you eating out of his hand.
Man, I wanna be tied up.
If you've got something to say, say it out loud!
Also, I get the feeling one of you only has themselves in mind!
You haven't moved on either, have you?
That's not true!
I'm not that shameful a woman!
I had a lot of pent-up frustration, so I just wanted someone I could get off with.
I think you've lost sight of
what's shameful and what's not.
You know what they say.
Men
Ritsu
Mayumi
Sayaka
Sumiko
Men store their love stories in different folders,
Men
Ritsu
Mayumi
Sayaka
Sumiko
Women
Tatsuya
Tooru
whereas women overwrite theirs.
Tatsuya
Do you want to overwrite "Tooru"?
I'm your typical overwriter.
And how many overwrites is that, now?
That is exactly why you have issues.
What the hell?
100% of the guys you dated
turned out to be scum, right?
Not 100%!
Then...
130%?
It went up!
I took the future into account.
Jack the Cheater
pickup_lines.txt
You need to save these virus-like men in a separate folder,
suckup_presents.jpg
cheating_signs.mpg4
Scanning
take your time researching their tricks and characteristics,
and use that information to write a virus scanner.
A virus has been detected
It's because you keep overwriting and forgetting
about them that you keep falling for the same tricks.
I get it now.
Don't agree with her!
Once one of those scummy exes gets in touch
with her, she panics and tries to recover the data,
but because it's all corrupted, she ends up wrapped around his little finger.
Shut up already!
You say that like you're any better, Ricchan.
Normally, one would just take what they're
given and stick it in a temp folder somewhere,
Sayaka
Temp
Files
You're
so cute
Gee, thanks
Let's
hang out
Yeah, let's all go
but you keep checking the contents—
Sayaka
Temp
Files
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
even for the most trifling things—
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
What's the extension?
Is it a virus?
What data format?
and even though you're doing this by choice, you decide it's too much effort to keep up.
In a way, you're a bigger pain than Mayumi.
She still set me up despite knowing Kawai so well, huh?
You might be a pain, Mayumi, but at least you're a pain who's easy to deal with. I like that.
Thanks.
I hate you.
Hey, what about me?
Your hard drive's busted.
It's too late, huh?
Unlike Mayumi, I don't have any precedents,
so don't jump to conclusions.
Though it might be a little accurate if you apply that to how I interact with friends.
No precedents?
So you don't have any experience.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Dating, of course.
What are you getting flustered for?
N-Nothing.
I wasn't interested in dating, anyway.
Is that so?
I'm hearing stuff like "Does it hurt?" and "Don't be scared" from inside his mind.
His virgin fantasies must be in full swing.
Maybe I should take your first.
Hey!
There's the Usa Block!
I was just kidding, bro.
I just felt something soft on my arm...
I-I'm going back to my room!
Hey!
How sickeningly naïve.
If we go by the analogy earlier,
doesn't that make you the virus, Sayaka?
I'm sorry.
She ran away with alarming speed.
Why does this always happen to me?
Usa!
Did Ricchan go to her room?
Sumiko?
Yeah. She got really mad and stormed off.
She wasn't mad just now.
I get the feeling I keep messing up lately.
Oh? I don't really see it that way.
And I don't even know if I should be getting too close to her.
Let me give you some advice, then.
While Ricchan doesn't mind being alone, she doesn't always want to be alone.
Sh-She really is a pain.
That's why I told you she was a tough nut to crack.
She's a pain,
but I guess there's nothing we can do about that.
Slurp
You two should just suck face and get it over with!
What are you saying, Mayumi?
They keep giving off this irritating stench of naïve adolescence!
It's soul-crushing!
Be defiled! Get corrupted, I say!
She's turned red all the way to her ears.
I'm taking the day off from work tomorrow!
I'm back.
Man, it's hot.
I bet that cooled you off.
What are you up to?
You were supposed to get flustered,
blush after glimpsing my wet skin and underwear through my clothes, and tell me what you think!
Pew pew!
Let's see...
Well, I see the top and bottom aren't coordinated.
Wh-Why water pistols, anyway?
Sumiko found them while cleaning the shed.
And since it's so hot, we figured we could play with them.
For some reason, Ricchan was totally up for it.
She covered me in water from head to toe.
You seriously piss me off!
Oh, Ricchan.
Hopes and dreams crushed!
Serves you right!
No, please stop!
That "this is good in its own right" face is really annoying!
I surrender!
You just set a new record for annoying!
Water pistol
I shall show you no mercy.
Don't say that!
Ricchan seems really lively.
Isn't she, like, a different person today?
Won't you join us, Sayaka?
I'd rather not get wet.
Yeah, can't have your makeup getting washed away.
Water strike!
That was fun—
no, a disaster.
But Kawai was really gung-ho about it, strangely enough.
Isn't this the book she's been reading lately?
Eureka
Sorry for reading it without permission!
I just got curious.
You're not much of a bookworm, though, are you?
You've got me there, but I thought even I'd find this book interesting.
Why so?
Well, you get influenced by any good books you read, right?
And you've been kinda cheerful ever since you started reading this one.
That's also why you were so gung-ho today, right?
Regretting her actions now that she's back to normal
You always look like you're having so much fun reading,
so while the long and wordy
books might be out of my league,
I wanted to try reading something cheerful.
I just flipped through, but the first part got me laughing.
The toilet scene?
Yeah.
The one where they use a bidet for horrible things.
It's a nice change, having the assistant be
the crazy, wild partner in a detective story.
Yeah, the detective is a normal guy. Except for the crossdressing.
Seriously?!
I knew there was something off about the way she was being described.
Sorry. I'll give it back now.
I've finished it already.
You can borrow it.
Thanks.
She's not mad... right?
How unusual.
Ricchan's in a real good mood today, isn't she?
Where?
Where are you right now?
Oh, I'm a slow reader, so I'm only up to chapter four.
Sorry about that.
My knee slipped.
Play nice, my beautiful leg.
I'm glad to hear your knees are all right.
You sinner, you.
With legs that strong, you could stand back up no
matter how many times you got two- or three-timed.
I don't know what you're talking about, but I do know that it pisses me off.
Here I was, genuinely enjoying this
book, when you had to ruin my fun!
Genuinely, my ass.
You could've done that in your own room!
But no, you just had to lie around in the common area.
I can see right through your schemes. Usa? More like U suck!
Shut up!
You still had no reason to kick me!
I'm not letting you score big
until I find my own happiness!
Hurry up and find it, then!
I would if I could!
Ricchan?
You're still here?!
Why?!
Crap!
I let my guard down because she
usually gets tired of us and leaves!
No reason in particular.
"Why"? Dude, how could you?
You're one to talk!
But well, I do want to crush
your teen spirit, so keep going.
Keep screwing up all you want.
Seriously, don't say another word!
I'm so bored.
Anything interesting to talk about?
Any ideas, Ricchan?
How about discussing a book you like?
I'm not very good at outlining plots,
and while it may just be killing some
time, I don't really want to help Shiro.
That come out of nowhere. And it stings.
Well then, you could talk about writing too.
That's even worse.
Wouldn't you be more suited to talking about writing?
You used to write novels, right?
Stop, you're making me blush.
I'm recharging my batteries right now.
Ah, so he's one of those. You know, the self-proclaimed "hidden talent" types.
That look hurts.
Let's put our heads together and come up with a story to rid us of this boredom.
This should be fun
Landlady's orders!
One that's thrilling and exciting, please.
I've got one!
Recently, this girl in my circle who got three-timed took a box cutter and...
No real life thrills, please.
Let's keep it strictly fantasy.
That girl tried to go to Neverland just recently.
No stories about going to fantasy lands either!
What about you, Mayumi?
Let's see...
Our protagonist is chosen as the Hero and
sets off on a journey to defeat the Overlord,
only to wind up in mortal danger.
This sounds promising.
Now, upon being told that giving up is also a form of bravery, some men actually would give up.
Men like Shiro and Usa.
She set up a whole story just to insult us!
Clichéd stuff will also do.
Stuff like, "A long time ago, there lived an old man and woman."
Fine, then.
A long time ago in a place far, far away...
there lived an old man and woman.
One day, the old man went to the
river to shave with his electric razor.
So dangerous!
I-I know!
He's using a safe, rechargeable one, right?
His wife helped him out by carrying the extension cord.
This is bad! That lady's more like the stepmother in Cinderella!
I knew it. Having bad luck with men
does make you say some brutal things.
I can say things that'll put a smile on your face, too!
Uh...
The old lady kindly washed her husband's hair with shampoo.
You're not doing a very good job!
Sayaka, take over.
What? From there?
Hurry up and get them out of the river!
Hurry!
Here we go.
And so, from further upstream...
came a jumbo-size Shiro!
In the flesh?
Now even Shiro's life is in the old man's hands!
Creepy-crawly, creepy-crawly, he came floating down.
Those sound effects are dripping with malice!
Wait, if this is how a jumbo-sized Shiro floats down the river, just how deep is this thing?!
Is the old man treading water?
I can't think of any more, so tag, you're it.
From further upstream floated Shiro...
Creepy-crawly, creepy-crawly...
So you kept those sound effects.
He came floating down...
and floated onwards.
Stop him!
Fine. They took pity on him, trussed him up like a roast pig, and took him home.
I'm a pig, all right!
They took an axe that'd been collecting dust for years...
It doesn't look the least bit sharp!
...and used it to slice him into thin strips...
Ouch!
But I kinda wish I was there.
Ricchan, that book has something to do with cooking, doesn't it?
...only to find Usa inside!
The old lady was overjoyed.
No fair, Usa!
The old man was also overjoyed.
And the three of them lived happily ever after.
The narration and visuals have nothing in common!
Would you like this instead?
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
It's the "Don't fight over me"
version that everyone dreams of!
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
Our Battle Has Only
Just Begun (Fin)
Victor's spoils
The two options don't seem very different to me!
That was thrilling and exciting.
And they all lived happily ever after.
Don't end it like that!
Our story was full of ups and downs, eh?
That wore me out.
And I'm sleep-deprived as it is.
It's fun how each person has different views and ideas.
Yeah, discussing something with others is always fun.
For the first time in a while, I feel like writing something.
Let me read it once it's done.
Of course!
I don't really care.
Huh?
I'm so sleepy.
You were up late reading last night.
I thought you'd let your overwhelming pathos take over
and were actually in the middle of the usual ritual to
lead millions and millions of your comrades to heaven.
Don't call it "the usual"!
Yeah, I may not have read many books before,
but this one's really fun and easy to read.
Right, Kawai?
Like the elevator scene?
That made me laugh!
Squat jumping? You've gotta be kidding me!
The scuffle on the roof, too.
Yeah, I totally lost it there!
The author has a knack for writing good conversations, right?
The Teen Spirit Destruction
Brigade is Formed
The characters really stand out, too.
And Broken
Discussing things is fun, isn't it?
Especially when it's stuff you like.
Oh, but it got totally serious after the first death, in chapter three.
Yeah.
It got more interesting!
It got less interesting.
I thought it gave the story more depth.
But it'd been taking normally serious themes and playing them for laughs until then,
so this one felt like an easy out.
Oh, right. You are quite well-read.
B-But the scene with the key was...
quite good.
...kinda hard to understand.
I don't like that character.
I like that character.
So there are people who feel
that way about the book too.
H-Huh?
I was doing so well for a while there!
I bet she thinks we're totally incompatible.
I bet he's so busy thinking useless things right now
that he hasn't noticed her face at all. Quality Usa.
Ain't youth grand?
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
All the singles out there can't stand how beautiful I am
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little panic in the air
So we try to help each other out
One for all, and all for one
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
Hasn't a grade school girl been coming over to hang out with Shiro lately?
Oh, you mean China?
She's cute.
This reeks of crime. I'm about to suffocate here.
You know that my head may be full of perverted thoughts, but they're all about girls age eighteen and up!
There's no room for kids in there!
Stay away from kids if your
head's full of perverted thoughts!
But girls that age can be surprisingly mature, so the unthinkable might happen.
She should just hook up with Usa
instead—wait, that'd be a crime too.
I have the discretion to wait until she comes of age, you know!
Does that mean you're gonna stay a virgin for another ten years?
Episode Six
Could it Be
Uh, no, that's not what I meant.
Hang in there.
Hey, knock it off!