Really? You landed your dream job at the company, Obata?
It's all thanks to what I learned at your seminars, Professor.
Oy, oy! Give the "Professor" thing a rest!
Right now, I'm just a middle-aged florist.
Your dad used to lecture at a university?
They still occasionally ask him to come give lectures.
Really?!
I didn't know he was that distinguished...
So what do you do at your company?
I work in the planning and sales
department, promoting our flowers.
Though more often than not, I'm just given everyone's odd jobs!
Well, that's great!
So what brings you here today?
I've actually come to ask you for a favor.
Professor, I implore you to come join our company!
Huh?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
My Father's Been Scouted!
He'll Quit Being a Florist?!
You dad is a really impressive scholar, isn't he?
And your mom's glasses make her look brainy too, don't they?
What did she do?
My mother did clerical work at a company called Red Florian.
Red Florian?!
That really chic florist all the celebs and stars use?!
Which means their meeting had some connection to flowers?
That's right!
Dad was doing research at the botanical gardens...
And Mom was searching for a flower that Red Florian was looking for...
I'm so sorry! Are you all right?
Yeah. Sorry about...
The two of them met amongst the fields of spring.
What an amazing man...
You are more beautiful than any flower...
Let's get married!
Yes!
That pacing's way too fast!
No, I think that's pretty much how it went.
They fell in love at first sight and got married within a month, apparently.
Seriously?!
A fateful encounter amongst the flowers...
It's kinda cliché...
but awesome!
Isn't it?!
Even I'm kinda envious...
Your family gets all the luck, huh?
Your dad's gonna get a really great job...
Looks like you Hanasakis have a lot to celebrate!
Hooray! Hooray!
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
Tada! I've made your favorite, Tsubomi! Meat and potato stew!
What's the matter, Tsubomi?
Dad... are you going to join Obata's company?
I refused his offer.
Huh? Why?!
Being florists keeps our hearts burning far more than our research ever did.
Right?
Yup!
I enjoy being able to sit down and eat with you guys far too much to give it up that easily!
Now then, we should eat this lovely meal before it gets cold, shouldn't we?
Yeah! Let's dig in!
Okay, okay, try to answer this one.
A dog that likes pork cutlet and a cat that likes deep fried seafood played chess against each other.
Which one won...
No, I think I've got everything there covered.
Right.
Excuse me, then.
Huh? Isn't that the guy from before?
I've been waiting, Tsubomi.
The offer I made your father was a very good one.
But no matter how many times I ask him, he always says no.
Huh?! Your dad declined the offer?!
Why?! What gives?!
Your father is both talented and extremely knowledgeable.
Won't you please help me convince him?!
Tsubomi, please! I'm begging you!
Stoooooooop!
I have a suggestion!
Rather than standing around here talking, why don't we go somewhere else and discuss this?
Well? Let's go.
The weight and temperature of the sand induces perspiration.
Bathing in sand truly does wonders for the skin.
Now my skin shall become smoother,
and I shall be all the more beautiful for it.
Hey, Snacky. More sand on my soles, please.
A message from Professor Sabark? What is it?
Hurry and defeat the Precure?
I'm taking a nice hot desert bath at the
moment for my complexion. I'll do it later.
The Precure are no match for the likes of the most beautiful Lord Kobraja?
I am most beautiful...
The Precure are waiting to behold Lord Kobraja's beauty?
I suppose if I must...
Then I shall allow them to feast themselves upon my beauty!
Be grateful, Precures!
This is...
Isn't this a Drosera obovata?!
Whoa! There's even Hypericum kinashianums!
Do you know this one? It's an Acystopteris japonica.
Of course I do!
The spores that grow on the underside of an Acystopteris really are beautiful...
They're so pretty...
Ferns really are interesting, aren't they?
They sure are!
They're nerding out so hard I can't follow at all...
You're very well informed, Obata.
That's because I love them!
So, Tsubomi, to continue our discussion from before...
Excuse me a moment.
Hello, this is Obata.
Yes, everything's fine.
Not at all.
He's really not helping things.
I guess he's just really busy at work.
Yes, if you'd please.
Excuse me, then.
Sorry about that!
Sounds like you're bogged down with work.
Yeah, a bit.
But if I don't work hard, we'll lose out to the other companies.
That's why I really need your father's help.
So please, Tsubomi, won't you help me out?
I'm begging you!
Do you hate Obata, Tsubomi?
O-Of course I don't!
Right. After all, you were really
enjoying your conversation earlier.
So you must have some reason for being so hesitant, right?
If you don't tell us, neither Obata nor I will understand, you know?
I don't think there's a "winning" or "losing" approach to flowers.
Huh?
All of these flowers have their own unique merits.
So even if you don't have some new species, it doesn't really matter.
That might be fine for you, but I have a job to do!
If I don't create flowers that'll sell, I won't win!
You're just a child, so you might not understand, but...
Children have hearts too, you know?
Grandma!
Professor Hanasaki!
It's been a while.
Grandma, you know Obata?
Indeed.
Back when he was a student, he used to come here every now and again.
He's matured into quite the young man.
Oh, you're too kind.
You remind me of how Youichi and Mizuki were back in the day.
Huh?
The two of them were always so busy with their work.
They were traveling around Japan, and sometimes around the world.
They were constantly leaving on some business or another...
And while they were away, I always
watched over Tsubomi in their stead.
Tsubomi always saw them off with a smile on her face.
But one day, they finally realized...
that while they were working so hard to support their family...
that very family had come apart at the seams.
After that, the two of them quit their jobs and opened the flower shop here in Kibougahana.
Tsubomi was more important to them than their jobs, so they chose to live as a family once more.
So that's what happened...
If he accepted your job offer, then he might've had to watch his family come apart like that again.
Was that not why Youichi declined it in the first place?
That's...
I think creating new flowers is something truly amazing.
But...
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Yes!
I'm very sorry!
Yes, as soon as I can.
If you would.
That's a rather sullen face you're wearing.
I'll be taking that discolored Flower of your Heart!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Tsubomi, I'm sorry about before. I said some pretty selfish things without realizing the situation.
It's all right. Because you were there, I was able to tell Obata how I really felt.
I see!
What was that sound just now?!
A Desertrian!
Tsubomi, look at that!
Obata!
We have to save him!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now then, my dear Precure!
I have come, just as you wished!
Allow your eyes to feast upon my radiance to your heart's content!
Huh?
What on earth are you going on about?
Nobody's been waiting for you!
What did you say?!
And I even halted my makeover for you...
Go get them, Desertrian!
Cellphoooone!
Blossom!
Ceeeellphone!
Marine!
Are you all right?!
What's with that thing?! It's unpredictable and so fast...
I also wish to do research!
Huh?!
I also yearn to create new flowers!
That's my dream!
Obata's... dream?
But I can't tell them that.
If I told them I wanted to join the
research team, they might fire me!
I don't want that!
These are Obata's true feelings?
Watch out!
I want to do research...
but I'm too scared to say it!
Hmph! What a coward!
Someone like you is capable of nothing!
That's not true!
What made Obata so anxious was the fact that he loved working with flowers!
It's because his feelings were serious that he became so scared!
All of this is irrelevant.
If a Flower of the Heart is usable, I shall use it.
I won't forgive you for playing with Obata's hardworking heart!
I've had it up to here with this!
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
No matter how fast he is, there's only one of him!
And two of us!
Precure Double Shoot!
Non! There's dust on my beautiful face!
Now's your chance!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
Now I'll have to restart my makeover!
So what'd Obata say?
That he'd given up trying to recruit Dad.
And someday, he'd like to be able to do his own research, but lacks the confidence right now.
Eavesdropping again?
I-I'm sorry!
Excuse me!
Um, I'd like a sunflower, please!
I'm sorry, but sunflowers aren't in bloom right now.
Whaaat?!
Sunflowers love the summer,
when the sun is at its happiest!
In order to make a flower truly
beautiful, it needs time to grow!
So when summer comes, please come back, okay?
I'll keep the biggest and prettiest sunflower for you!
Really?!
Really! I promise!
Then pinky swear on it, 'kay?
Okay!
Cross my heart, hope to die, stick a needle in my eye.
You're a bit like a sunflower in the spring yourself.
It's a promise!
Huh?
In order to make the flower of your dream bloom, isn't this where you need to work hard and grow stronger?
Yes. That's what I'm going to do.
I don't know how many years it'll take, but I'll challenge myself!
That's the Obata I know!
Give that here!
The Flower of his Heart has been revived!
In the language of flowers, a white hyacinth means "serene love."
By returning his flower-loving heart, we've made him happy again!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born...
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Dark Precure, no matter how strong you are, you cannot separate our hearts!
Hard work and guts!
Love!
Courage!
True friendship shall shine bright!
Cleaving the dark and purging evil!
It grants us infinite power!
So the likes of the heartless Dark Precure...
...shall never defeat us!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Biggest Predicament Yet!
Dark Precure Makes Her Entrance!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!