How would you rank Rider's Noble Phantasm?
It's in the same league as Gilgamesh's Gate of Babylon.
In other words, too powerful to be given a rank.
Things ended exactly as we planned.
If we'd gone against Rider unprepared,
we would not have been able to defend against it.
This begins the second stage.
We will use the information Assassin gathered
to have Archer defeat our enemies.
In the process, a means to defeat Rider will reveal itself.
Yes.
You've done excellent work as a Master.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
I believe that last night's attack involved all the Assassins.
Understood.
By the way, Maiya,
where are we with the new base?
Tomorrow morning, I will take Saber and madam there.
I see. Thank you.
Of course.
Goodbye, then.
No sign of movement from the Tohsaka residence.
Since Assassin's attack on the first day,
Tokiomi hasn't left.
An unsettling silence.
The Matou Master appears undefended.
An easy target.
But...
Berserker's strange special ability
suggests he should be left alive,
to distract Archer and Tohsaka.
Lord El-Melloi should have been removed from battle already.
However Lancer still remains.
We must discover his new Master's identity as soon as possible.
Caster's location remains unknown.
But last night,
several children vanished from the city again.
They continue their atrocities,
with no apparent plan whatsoever.
Rider and his Master are constantly on the move in his flying Noble Phantasm.
Tracking them is difficult.
However large-hearted he may seem, he is an extremely dangerous foe.
Further, I'm concerned about the Ionian Hetairoi that Maiya reported.
But more importantly...
Can we assume that Assassin has been completely destroyed?
In that case, his Master...
If his plan was to work with Tohsaka by using Assassin as recon,
then he should have never been able to leave Fuyuki Church.
But that isn't what happened.
His ambush at the Fuyuki Hyatt...
His attack in the Einzbern forest...
Both of those are inexplicable.
But if we assume that I was his real target, then it all fits.
But why?
Why pursue me?
Two days ago, he should have had no way of knowing that I am Saber's Master.
Kotomine Kirei, who are you?
You seem in an excellent mood today, Archer.
I still see little value to this Grail.
But even if it is trash, I don't care.
I've found another form of entertainment.
Kirei, what of you?
For once, you seem strangely pleased.
I am simply relieved.
I've finally been freed from an unpleasant burden.
Once they disappear, what becomes of the Command Seals?
In theory, they return to the Grail.
The Holy Grail retakes the Command Seals
from a Master who has lost his Servant
and withdrawn from the war.
And if a Servant loses its Master,
the Grail will take those unused Seals,
and redistribute them to a newly chosen Master.
The Command Seals stay a part of this world until their use.
At the end, any remaining are given to the judge.
So depending on what happens now, a new Master may yet appear?
Possibly, yes.
But the Holy Grail does not deem many to be worthy of that role.
Thus, when a new Master is sought,
the Grail tends to select those it has previously found suitable.
What's wrong?
Continue, Kirei.
The reason the Holy Church protects those who have left the battle is the following:
In the event a place should open among the remaining Masters,
there is a high probability that any unpaired Masters
will receive the Command Seals left behind.
This is why Grail War participants try their best to kill,
and not simply disable, enemy Masters.
From that perspective, Kirei,
is there not a good chance that the Command Seals
will be bestowed upon you again?
Impossible.
If, as Tokiomi suggests,
the Holy Grail chose me to support the Tohsaka family,
I have performed that duty.
Tokiomi already possesses a winning strategy for the remaining Masters and their Servants.
There's nothing more for me to do.
How does it feel to drive a car, Saber?
This is a splendid vehicle.
I cannot help but think what would have happened
had these existed in my time.
Irisviel, are you certain it is all right that I drive this vehicle?
You seemed to enjoy the act of driving.
It's fine.
If you're happy, then I'm happy, too.
This is another strange building.
From now on, this will be your base of operations.
Ah, if you could take those, Saber.
Understood, Irisviel.
Maiya...
What is this key?
It appears quite different from the others.
It's the key to the storehouse in the yard.
It's old, but I've personally confirmed it is solidly built.
No preparations were made, so this may be somewhat lacking as a residence.
That's fine.
For now, so long as it keeps us out of the rain, that's sufficient.
No then, Saber, let's go and explore!
Yes, let us.
I think this is supposed to be like one of this country's haunted houses.
I'm sure all the hallways have wooden floors,
and the rooms' floors are woven grass with partitions made of paper!
I told him once I wanted to see a Japanese mansion.
Maybe Kiritsugu remembered.
Was it not what you expected?
No...
I enjoyed it.
But this isn't really an ideal base for a magus...
The magical barriers are well-laid, but for an atelier...
In an open room like this the prana will leak out.
I'd have preferred a room walled off with stone or clay.
This is perfect!
It's a bit small, but I can craft my spells here just as well as back at the castle.
Simply inscribing a magic circle here should be good enough to make it my own.
Let's get started.
Will you help me, Saber?
We'll draw a magic circle there, six feet in diameter.
Understood.
I'll require your help once we start to craft the mercury.
I'll tell you how to distribute it, so don't worry.
Will you bring me the ingredients we left in the trunk?
Irisviel, I must ask you something.
Today, it seemed that you have carefully avoided touching anything.
Am I imagining things?
Driving the car,
holding the keys...
Normally I wouldn't fret over it,
but you aren't even handling your own magic.
If you aren't feeling well,
it's important that you tell me.
It is my duty to protect you when it's necessary.
So I must know these things.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
This isn't something that I could keep hidden.
Put out your hand.
Saber...
I'm going to squeeze your hand with all my strength now.
All right?
Yes, go ahead...
Irisviel?
I'm not playing with you.
This is all I can do now...
Just tugging your fingers is the most I can do.
Grasping something or picking it up is beyond me.
Dressing this morning was so difficult.
Wh-What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
I'm just not feeling too well, so I cut off my sense of touch.
Shutting down just one of my senses allows me greater control over my power.
That means I can do everything else I must.
Being able to do things like this is the specialty of a homunculus...
It is not that simple!
What exactly is wrong with you, anyway?
Don't you require treatment?
You may have forgotten, but I'm not a normal human.
When I'm ill, a doctor cannot treat me.
I suppose you could say it's a problem stemming from my creation.
Don't worry about it.
Of course, it'll mean that you'll have to do some menial things for me.
From now on, I'll need you to drive, like you did today.
You'll also have to help me with my magical rituals.
I'm sorry.
I'll be relying on you, my knight.
Of course.
I apologize for prying.
Please forgive me.
It's really okay.
Now, let's get started on that circle.
If I rest in a magical circle, properly connected with local ley lines,
my condition should improve a little.
Understood.
Then I shall retrieve the ingredients.
Saber's Master...
has merely been hired to achieve the Einzbern's long-held dream,
attaining the Holy Grail.
I was a fool to expect more from him.
Just another mongrel...
Mongrels, all of them,
all with utterly uninteresting reasons for seeking my treasure.
You caused me to go to all that trouble, and that is all you have to say?
Think of those whose effort has gone to waste.
Wasted effort?
What do you speak of, Kirei?
The work put in by you and the Assassins has paid off splendidly.
Do you mock me, King of Heroes?
You do not understand?
I suppose that it's to be expected.
Your own worth is invisible to yourself.
Regardless of its own self-awareness of this fact, a soul seeks pleasure.
This expression of the soul appears in the form of interest or appreciation.
Thus, Kirei, having you tell me what you've seen and heard was already of great importance.
What you spoke of at greatest length was what interested you the most.
First, let us discount the man you've deliberately avoided speaking of.
An interest you are aware of is nothing but obsession.
Which means...
Of the remaining four, who did you speak of most passionately?
Berserker's Master.
Kariya, was it?
Kirei, you spoke of him in great detail.
His circumstances are complicated.
Thus, they required the most additional explanation.
Incorrect.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin to investigate thoroughly enough
that you could notice those complicated circumstances.
All this was due to your unconscious interest.
I accept that I made an error in judgment.
It's true that, in the long term, Matou Kariya poses no threat.
He was not worth the attention.
By overestimating his abilities, I have brought your prying gaze upon me.
So that is your response.
Then imagine for me a scenario in which chance and fortune
ensured that Berserker and his Master survived until the end.
Can you imagine what would happen then?
Hey, Kirei.
Isn't it time that you understood?
The true question I ask of you.
Tell me, Archer...
What could be the point in imagining Matou Kariya's victory?
No point.
None at all.
Come now, don't be so mad.
Think about it...
The fact that Kirei Kotomine never recognized the futility in such speculation.
Do you not agree there is a clear, unshakable meaning there?
Explain for me, Archer.
If you'd been given the same question regarding the other Masters,
you'd have perceived immediately that there was no point to it.
You would have immediately rejected it as a waste of time.
However...
That was not how it went with Kariya.
You abandoned your usual sharp wits, wasting your time in pointless thought.
You put the futility out of mind.
You did not count your wasted effort as a loss.
In other words, you found enjoyment in it.
Celebrate, Kirei.
You have understood what entertainment is at last.
Entertainment?
You mean joy?
Indeed.
There is nothing in Matou Kariya's fate that could bring joy to a man.
Life is nothing but suffering and tragedy in his eyes.
For him, a quick death would be a blessing.
Kirei, why must you insist on defining joy so narrowly?
Where is the paradox in finding suffering and tragedy but other forms of pleasure?
There is no one fixed type of joy.
Your confusion derives from your failure to understand that.
This is something that cannot be allowed.
King of Heroes, an inhuman monster such as yourself
may find pleasure in some small amount of pain.
But that is the soul of a sinner, an evil that must be punished!
Thus it is so, according to the path of faith that I follow.
And so, you have defined joy itself as a sin.
I'm astonished how far you've succeeded in warping it.
You never do cease to be of interest to me.
This pain...
Oh hoh...
So it indeed happened.
But faster than expected.
Impossible...
No Servant has been freed from their contract.
Why has a new Master been chosen?
It appears that the Holy Grail still expects much from Kotomine Kirei.
Kirei, you should attend the Grail's summons.
Without doubt, you have a reason to seek this wishing artifact.
I have a reason to seek the Holy Grail?
If this wish-granting device is truly omnipotent,
then it can give shape to the wish within the depths of your heart,
that of which even you remain unaware.
So you claim that since I do not know my desire,
I should use the wish-granting device as a means to learn it?
But that can only happen after I have destroyed six other wishes.
If I seek the Holy Grail for my own desire,
that will mean that I have betrayed my own teacher and mentor.
Then you'll need a strong Servant,
if you would seek to fight me.
Of course before any of that, you must steal another Servant,
one controlled by another Master.
In that case...
No, I won't say it.
Everything from here onward is up to you.
Do exactly as you like.
That is the true meaning of entertainment.
And entertainment leads to joy...
And joy will lead you to happiness.
Your path is now clear, Kirei.
So clear there is no longer any need to hesitate.
Episode 12
The Grail's Invitation
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
I shall be the first to strike!
Now is your best chance to finish them.
Let's end this!
I'm certain this world is filled with God's love.
Now, once again, we shall raise Salvation's banner!
Next time
The Forbidden Banquet