"Arashigaoka High School・(Place)"
"Kureha Tsubaki・(Yuri)"
They're beautiful in bloom, aren't they, Kureha?
"Sumika Izumino・(Yuri)"
I think we can be together
here without anyone seeing us.
Don't worry about that.
We're not doing anything wrong.
But...
I want to be with you, Sumika. So...
Sumika, I'll never back down on my love.
Kureha... Me neither!
Bear shock!
A bear! There's a bear on the loose!
"Bear"
"Bear Warning Issued・(Warning)"
A bear got over the Wall of Severance?
Kureha...
It's all right. I'll protect you, Sumika.
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become true
friends with you. To cross the wall...
Yurikumaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"NEVER BACK DOWN ON LOVE"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
Growl, growl!
One day, at the far reaches of space,
the minor planet Kumaria exploded!
The fragments of Kumaria became a
meteor swarm that rained down on Earth...
Which made the world's bears rise up as one!
They all started attacking humans!
Like, who could've seen that coming, right?
"Wall of Severance・(Place)"
The humans built the Wall of Severance
to try to drive us bears from their world,
but guess what, man-made rules
don't work on bears! Growl!
We are bears.
Bears eat people. It's what we do!
And so...
Everyone, starting today,
you'll have some new friends.
This is Ginko Yurishiro and Lulu Yurigasaki.
Show them a warm welcome!
Growl! We've just transferred to
this school, disguised as humans!
Muahaha! Looks like
nobody can tell we're bears.
Rawr!
So many girls for me to pick from.
Sniff, sniff...
Uh-oh! The whole room smells delicious, growl!
Okay!
I'll work hard and eat
lots of girls! Right, Ginko?
Oh, and Ginko Yurishiro
here is a bear too, of course!
She's my darling, and I just love her! Teehee!
Now, as I'm sure you all know,
bears unfortunately appeared on the
roads near our school this morning.
It ought to be unthinkable for bears
to cross the Wall of Severance
and enter the human world.
The warning has been lifted,
but you mustn't be careless.
As you move through the school,
be sure to keep someone--a friend--with you.
Right there!
I've finally found her. Yes, that girl smells.
A delicious smell.
Slurp.
Sumika?
Hey, Kureha, what do you
like in your lunch box?
My lunch box?
Yeah!
I like fried chikuwa in seaweed batter.
What about you?
Let's see... I guess spaghetti, and shiokara.
Shiokara? With lunch?
Is that weird?
What?
You sound like an old man.
Old man?!
Yep.
Hey, that's mean!
I mean, maybe it smells a little
when I open my lunch box, but...
But I love it.
What?
Even if you've got old-man taste sometimes,
I love you. I love you so much.
Sumika?!
Sumika!
Kureha?
What's wrong?
I, um...
Didn't you eat lunch?
N-No...
Here.
Let's eat together. We'll each take half.
Okay?
There's chikuwa in this roll.
Mm-hmm! Not fried in seaweed batter, though.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Say, let's eat here every day from now on.
Is that okay? I mean...
I want to eat with you.
Food does taste better eaten together, huh?
Yes.
Grrrrr...
Growl! I'm hungry too!
Delicious smell... I want to eat her, growl.
Oh, Ginko, you're such a glutton.
You know, you can sink your teeth
into me anywhere you'd like, right now!
Hee, I said it! I'm so daring!
The storm chased us down.
It's only the beginning. A warning that
it'll start with what's most precious.
The Invisible Storm will destroy everything,
until we're worn away into nothing.
Kureha, I'll never back down on my love either.
What?
Just like you didn't give up on me,
I won't give up on you--on love.
No matter what happens to me.
--Grrrrr.
--Growl. I'm starving!
--It smells, it smells, a delicious smell! Growl...
--Grrrrr.
I won't back down on my love.
I'll protect you, Sumika.
Kureha...
I thought so.
You've been caught up in the
Invisible Storm too, haven't you, Tsubaki?
Yurizono...
"Mitsuko Yurizono・(Yuri)"
It's just cruel to cut down flowers in full bloom.
The Invisible Storm destroys
beautiful, kind things first.
Yes. But this has made up my mind.
I can't keep letting these things happen!
Tsubaki, Izumino, let's stop the
storm together. We'll take a stand!
As class representative,
I'm ashamed of myself
for turning a blind eye until now.
I'm sorry, Izumino. Will you forgive me?
No, there's nothing to forgive...
Say, I think we could be good friends.
I'm sure the three of us can stop the
Invisible Storm if we work together!
But now we should go home for the day.
There was that warning...
I say we come early tomorrow
morning and fix the flowerbed.
I'll help, of course.
Yurizono, your hand...
It's okay. This means I'm
one of you. We're friends!
Who did that?!
♪ I am so happy, I got to eat a lily! ♪
♪ I want to eat that girl!
Who do you mean by "that girl"? ♪
♪ I want to eat this girl!
Who do you mean by "this girl"? ♪
♪ Let's go on trial! Yeah, let's go! ♪
Grrrrr.
"Kureha Tsubaki's House・(Place)"
Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
Yep! Guess what, Mom?
We ate snacks together today!
Great, were they yummy?
Mm-hmm! They're really yummy
when I eat them with her!
You really love her, don't you, Kureha?
Yeah! I do!
Yes. That's why this time, the one I love...
...I'll protect with my own hands!
I'll never forgive those bears.
I'll ruin those bears!
This is Unit 103.
We're at the flowerbed in the
Arashigaoka High School courtyard.
Lots of bear prints here, and bloodstains.
Looks like there was a vic.
We found her effects at the
scene--she may be a student.
We're searching the area now.
--Yes, we were supposed to meet.
--Request immediate backup. I repeat...
We were going to come early
and fix up the flowerbed.
This mobile customer is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
I heard they found a shoe on the ground!
Then she must really be...
Apparently she came early
to work on that flowerbed.
No way! You mean...
It's her fault for being alone.
To survive, we need friends!
Yeah... Yeah, you're right.
But now the next Invisible Storm...
It's her fault for not being invisible.
To the bears, we're just weak prey.
We have to always stay in the herd.
Right, the mood of the herd
is what's most important!
It's not true...
It's not true!
No way was Sumika eaten!
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Who is it?
Sumika?!
Is your love the real thing?
What?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true, go to the roof.
The bears are waiting for you.
What do you mean? Is Sumika safe?!
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
The time for judgment has come, growl.
Grrrrr.
Sumika!
Sumika... Give back Sumika!
Growl, growl, growl, growl...
I want to eat her! I want to eat her right now!
Court is in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
Come, the door has opened.
This is the land of enlightenment
for all living things... yes, even human and bear.
Let us now pass judgment--
for the sake of humans and bears!
LIFE Sexy!
For humans and bears.
LIFE Cool!
LIFE Beauty!
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Defendant-bears. Do you admit
that you are criminal-bears?
Growl... But, we're so hungry, you know?
We won't back down on our love, growl.
Your Honor!
Humans and bears have a wall called Severance
between them that is not to be crossed.
The defendants have crossed it
and infiltrated the human world.
This is blatant overeating. They are guilty!
Sparkle!
Your Honor, the prosecutor
is blatantly hostile to bears!
Counsel, was that intended to be an objection?
I mean, even bears have to eat to live, right?
Are you telling them to starve to death?
If we admit the defendants' appeal,
more lives will be lost!
Objection! He's showing
undue favor toward humans!
Sustained.
This court must be a scale that
weighs both worlds impartially.
That is the sexy way!
Shaba-da-doo.
Sparkle.
Okay, so we can eat her then, right?
That doesn't...
Your Honor, a Love Judgment, please!
Very well. Defendant-bears, I ask you:
Will you be invisible? Or will you eat humans?
We'll eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
Growl, growl!
Growl!
Yuri approved!
Ra-ra-rawr!
Kureha, I'm going to eat you.
Where is what I hope for?
I'm searching in the Invisible Storm.
Mmm. Searching for what?
Mmm. Searching for it where?
Give me the Promise Kiss!
Thank goodness, you're awake!
Yurizono... Where are we?
The nurse's office.
What? Why?
We found you passed out on the roof.
What about Sumika?! Where is she?!
She hasn't been found yet.
That can't be... He said the bears
on the roof would give her back!
Calm down. You were the
only one lying up there.
Just me? But...
I'll go get you something hot to drink.
Was that a dream? But I know that I...
Please be okay, Sumika.
Chomp, chomp, chomp.
What's that sound?
Could someone be vandalizing
the flowerbed again?
Munch, munch, munch...
Growl! Human girls really do taste good!
I'll eat them. I don't care if it's a crime, growl.
I won't let anyone wreck my love.
Bears are... eating someone!
Shock!
Bear shock!
Those are the transfer students...
I get it--they're bears pretending to be human!
Slurp.
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love