I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
If you don't work, you don't eat.
You're a hunting dog.
Hunt up some food.
We girls are different.
We have to be pampered
'cause we're delicate and refined.
3 million Woolong reward...
Well, I'll just have the boys
get it for me, then.
Damn, that blues harp sounds sweet.
I knew it would.
I thought you liked jazz.
Don't be dense.
I started wailing the blues
when the doctor whacked my
bottom on the day I was born.
A baby hipster. Very cool.
No doubt about it. It's Giraffe.
All right, I'm going in from the right.
You take the left side.
- Lard Boy's in the way.
- Hm?
Oh... That's Fatty.
Make a move, Jet.
The ball's in your court.
Yo! Hey, Fatty!
Fatty River!
Long time no see, buddy!
Oh! Who'd have guessed,
if it isn't Jet Black!
Well, well, when the hell
did you blow in?
How about you?
You're looking pretty cheery.
What happened, did you
catch a nice big one?
I had no idea you were
a fan of the blues, Fatty.
You kidding me? I listened to the blues
when I was still in my father's sack,
if you know what I mean.
- Sorry!
- Hey...
Give him back, now!
Zebra!
Hey, you! Wake up!
Hey!
Ah, great. You die,
and I lose the reward.
Don't... Don't be fooled by him.
By the way he looks.
Don't talk! Try to stay alive!
Not me... He needs help now.
Help him.
This stone...
Wait!
Hmm... I can't be sure
until I run all the tests,
but this may be
worth a hefty sum.
So what do you
wanna do with it?
I have no idea.
The guy gives it to me on his own,
then he dies on his own.
I don't see any reason
why we shouldn't keep it.
There is no reason.
You're not responsible
for that kid, after all.
Gimme that!
This thing is gonna
pay for our food.
Our food, not yours.
You know, I think your
heart's made outta lead.
Not like me, I'm a nice guy.
I have a gift for you.
Yay! All right, what is it?
An official invoice?
An invoice for what?
All the expenses you've racked up
since you've been on our ship.
And thanks for your business.
Yeah, great. Anytime.
Why do you wanna know
about this dead guy?
Well, uh...
Ha! So you were after Giraffe too.
Did you get a good deal?
Enjoying the sweets?
I always do.
There's no bounty in it, you know?
Yeah, that's right.
There's nothing to gain here at all.
No, I mean it!
There's nothing on the line here!
Yeah, right, Jet.
You're gonna owe me one for today.
All right, you know that kid on the
blues harp the other day? Name's Wen.
Giraffe was after the kid's
so-called father, an old friend.
He goes by the name Zebra.
- They were friends?
- Jeez, you didn't even know that?
The two of them were the leaders of
the Self-Defense Volunteer Squad.
They worked together
until about ten years ago.
I don't get it.
Why was he after an old comrade?
Ten years ago, they had a
confrontation with some space raiders.
A land dispute.
It all came down at some
R&D facility near Mars.
A few days later, the raiders
are wiped out, Zebra's missing,
and Giraffe is found
blindfolded in a silo.
They say Zebra double-crossed him
so he could run the squad solo.
Later, Zebra turns up
in a wheelchair with the kid.
Guess it didn't turn out
the way he planned.
So the bottom line is Giraffe was
killed off over some internal politics.
Betrayal may come easily to women,
but men live by iron codes of honor.
You believe that?
I'm trying to, real hard.
Tell me, who are you?
Just some suspicious guy.
What do you want here?
Before Giraffe bought the farm,
he asked me to come here to help you.
- But Zebra shot Giraffe...
- Uh-huh.
Then why would Giraffe ask him
to help the kid? It doesn't make sense.
Hm? Hey, the kid's in the headlines.
Guess he must be pretty famous, huh?
Yeah. Kid's a genius.
Plays like an old pro.
Hey, wait a minute,
this guy isn't Zebra!
What's that?
Look close. Can't you see the date?
What the hell?
This was published thirty years ago!
How can he have the same face?
Come on, there's nothing to be afraid of.
Come here, let's talk.
You'd better stay out of it.
Little twerp like you
sticks his neck out too far,
he'll get it cut off, understand?
Don't give me that crap, kid!
Sorry, but I'm not a kid.
Yeah, all kids say that.
I know what I look like.
But I was alive when
this place was an outpost.
Before the asteroids were even settled.
Get the picture?
The hyperspace gate had blown to bits.
From that day on,
my body completely stopped aging.
I can't die.
There was always someone
discovering me, doing experiments.
But they all died, and I kept on living.
The end for this guy started when
his Self-Defense Volunteer Squad
hit our R&D lab.
I needed a new cover.
Someone to play the part of my parent.
Don't... Don't be fooled by him.
By the way he looks.
Not me...
He needs help now.
Help him.
I think he's the third guy
I've used like this.
Now... where's the ring?
Ring? What ring?
That's okay. Even if you had it,
it'd just be a case of
casting pearls before swine.
Ah, quit complaining, you big klutz.
You're lucky you got away with
this little scratch on your arm.
But we don't have the money
to pay for a funeral.
I'm sorry.
Can it, Ein.
Don't be obnoxious.
Jet, the alpha-catch.
Shit... this piece of junk...
All right.
Now... what do you make outta this?
A hotel room.
That's it! He's remembering
the time Giraffe got blown away.
Give him back, now!
Zebra! Come over here, hurry!
Shit... And then what?
Come on, what did Giraffe say?
I have it now.
I can do you in with this.
This stone has the power
to return time to you.
Now hand Zebra over to me!
Zebra!
When the gate exploded,
a coordinate system was created
from the resulting
twists in hyperspace.
A kind of singularity that
drew in vast amounts of energy,
enclosing and crystallizing them
into a single faceted stone,
the gem that makes up this ring.
The same energy broke
Wen's circadian rhythm.
His pineal body continually produces a
substance like melatonin that inhibits aging.
That's the theory in a nutshell.
- Get the picture?
- Yeah, as if.
I don't either.
Which simply means there's
no way to know for sure
until we stick the gem
into the kid and find out.
Anything could happen.
It could blow sky-high
the moment it hits.
Kinda makes it interesting.
- Yes, my dear?
- I just thought I'd say goodbye, Spike,
since I'm sure it's the
last time I'll be seeing you.
Huh. You mean you're finally leaving us?
No! I mean you're not coming back.
I don't like this setup, Jet.
Don't like it at all.
Men are such total idiots.
I see...
Yes, I can finally die at last.
I-I feel so heavy...
But I feel... I finally feel at ease.
Do you understand?
Do you...
Yeah, I understand...
As if.
Bang.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
You know what heavy metal is, right?
- What'd you say?
- Heavy metal! I said heavy metal!
What? I can't hear you!
Hey! Can you do something
about all that noise?
It's going to be running
through the whole next episode.
I think I'll stay out of it, then.
I can't hear a word you're saying!
Next episode:
"Heavy Metal Queen."
Is this really getting
through to anyone?