I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
This peculiar story
began on a blazing hot day.
Out of the blue, I got an e-mail
from an old acquaintance of mine.
There was no explanation,
and the message was very terse.
All it said was,
"Seek the holy beast of Anzan."
"I am where the four gods meet."
The message came from a guy named Pao,
who I had lost touch with long ago.
I was leery, to say the least.
So I decided to look into
his current whereabouts.
Pao's background was unknown,
but he had a reputation
as one of the three greatest
feng shui masters on Mars.
But when I finally managed to
locate him, it was not in this world.
I suppose you couldn't have sent me
that message from here, could you.
The one who visits from
the inauspicious door...
receives word from the heavens
and will lead me to the sun stone.
Just like the pakua said!
Look out!
What are you aiming at?
Heck of a place for target practice.
I found a way out!
What?
Hey! Whoa!
- Idiot.
- Shit!
This way!
Earth chi!
Well, that was a
pretty close one, huh?
Huh?
I'm glad just you're safe.
Uh-huh...
What are you up to?
Take a look over there.
Jet's got a friend.
Ohh...
It's a fine romance.
She's too young for that.
Hot dog bun, not too young!
Maybe he's got a thing.
Nah, afraid she's too old.
Oldy and moldy, history, mystery!
Pao's little girl, huh?
I just didn't expect you
to be this old already, Meifa.
I'm sure you don't remember this...
When you were this little, I met you
when I was visiting your father.
Were you friends with my father?
How did you know him?
How? Well...
He was an acquaintance.
It's been ten years, you know.
But I sure am sorry he got killed
in that transport accident.
He was on his way to Jupiter.
They told me it was very sudden.
There was a hyperspace fluctuation.
Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
You Jet's girlfriend?
Does he have a thing for you?
All is fair in love and war!
Jet, why were you
at my father's grave?
No one outside the family
knows about his accident yet.
Message: "Seek the holy beast of Anzan."
"I am where the four gods meet."
What's this?
This is a message that was
sent here by your father.
- When?
- Three days ago.
Right before the accident...
It means he knew!
Can you help me, please?
Huh?
It has to be!
It's about the sun stone!
Sun stone? What's that?
The direction, the day,
and the time you arrived
were all the best
combination for feng shui!
Especially if you're on a quest!
What... kind of quest?
For the sun stone!
Please, Jet, help me!
Yes. Yeah, we'll have it soon.
R-Right, I understand.
- So how's the boss taking it?
- Uh... you know.
- That can't be real good.
- Not good at all.
Let's do it.
I didn't owe any favors
to Pao or the girl.
I could've just blown the whole thing off,
but something made me hang on.
Maybe it was all the
dangling questions.
Why'd Pao send a message
to me before he died?
Four gods and the
holy beast of Anzan.
What did all that mean?
And who were the guys who tried
to shoot us at the gravesite?
And then there was Meifa.
With that gypsy scarf
and all that spirit.
This universe is composed
of the three chis.
One is the chi of heaven,
the energy that comes from the sun.
And one is the chi of earth,
the power that comes from
the planet we all live on.
And the last one
is the magnetic chi
that comes from
living organisms like us.
You mean human chi?
Yes, from the human body.
Each body produces
a magnetic field,
which interacts with the
magnetic field of the earth.
And that's what creates
the energy we all use.
Universal feng shui is the science
that reads these natural energies
and applies them to everyday life.
- Ice cream.
- Huh?
Universal feng shui...
Is that any different than
plain old fortunetelling?
"Fortunetelling," indeed.
Fortunetellers only predict and foresee.
But feng shui is active.
It has the power to turn
bad luck into good luck.
For example, if you were a powerful
feng shui master like my father...
What's wrong?
I just realized that I never spent any
time like this talking with my father.
Wait a minute! First of all,
I'm not old enough to
be your father, all right?
Why, if anything,
I could be your boyfriend.
No, wait, that would
be bad, wouldn't it?
Open foot, insert mouth.
I mean, I'd be more like
your older brother.
- Ice cream.
- Ice cream?
Ice cream cone!
Let's go, big brother.
I believe "Anzan"
refers to this building.
The Mountain Hotel.
Over there!
Blue dragon!
White tiger...
Snake and tortoise...
- Red phoenix!
- What's that?
The zenith cross.
It's the four gods.
It's here. It's the sun stone.
You sure about that?
Here they come.
They're right over there.
Right.
Careful.
I finally found it.
This is it, Jet. The sun stone.
A black rock?
Jet, hey!
- Get outta here.
- Hey!
- Skeezers!
- Stupid suits!
A bottle of lao chu.
I don't need a glass.
Hey!
Now, what are you guys up to?
You think I'm gonna tell you that?
Not a chance, baldy.
We're from the Blue Snake!
We're on assignment!
So you're syndicate scumbags.
What are you following us around for?
I-I can't tell you that.
E-Even if you kill me,
I can't tell you any more.
It's Pao! We were after him,
but he got away.
We tracked the message he sent.
That's what led us to you.
I'm telling you the truth!
We're on the low end, so that's
all the information they gave us!
Yeah, I believe you.
Look at these cheesy glasses!
Jet...
My father... He's alive?
The words in Pao's message
had led us to the stone.
But did that mean
Pao was still alive?
It seemed he wanted us
to have this stone.
But why? What were we
supposed to do with it?
Every time we solved a mystery,
it just led to new ones.
Darker and more unsettling
than the ones before.
And our only clue
was the stone itself.
I decided to run some tests.
So this is a piece of the moon from
that gate accident fifty years ago.
Feng shui masters
call it the sun stone.
You see, all the time-space
fluctuations were absorbed by the stone,
condensing a tremendous amount of energy
which has been amplified by the sun.
Looks like a plain old
moon rock to me, you know?
Hey, how much is it worth
if we try to sell it?
All right...
You two smoke outside
if you need to smoke.
What? Excuse me, but you
always smoke in here, Jet.
This is now a non-smoking area.
Come on, you're joking around, right?
Do I look like I'm joking to you?
It's my ship.
So what are you gonna
do with this sun stone?
I don't know. I have no idea.
My father had something
in mind, but what?
Hey, come here!
Ein! What are you doing?
The luopan...
- What is it?
- It can't be...
It shouldn't spin like that,
I took the magnet off.
I see... I get it now.
So that's the point!
Huh?
We can do it!
You see, my father has
a sun stone as well.
The two stones resonate
to one another.
If we follow the energy,
it'll lead us to my father.
So that's why Pao wanted
you to find this stone.
It's like a beacon.
Yes, but... I don't know why
he sent that message to you...
And not to me.
What do you think, Spike?
They make a good couple.
I think it's a dangerous combination.
And why's that?
The more righteous a guy
was back in his youth,
the more likely he is to fall for some
young thing when he gets older.
Is that right...
Definitely. Men are
extremely predictable.
My father believed in universal
feng shui, and in nothing else.
He couldn't believe in people.
So my mother left him,
and she took me with her.
That was seven years ago.
The thing is, I'm sure that
he could have found me.
It wouldn't have been
all that hard, you know?
But he never tried once
in all those years.
I'm sure there's a good reason for it.
And what's the reason why
those men were after my father?
They're bad men!
How did they know him?
Please, tell me the truth, Jet.
I wanna know who
my father really is.
Pao... was a consultant
for a major syndicate.
That's the real story.
He leaked some inside information to me
back when I was a detective with ISSP.
See, he was looking for a way out,
and he thought I could help him find it.
I tried, but... it's impossible for someone
to leave when they know that much.
Once you join a syndicate,
they own you forever.
If you cross them, they take
revenge on you and your family.
I'm sure that's what
he was trying to avoid.
But you can ask him yourself
if the sun stone leads us to him.
Yeah... yeah... yeah...
Here! Over this way!
There's nothing here.
- And the radar?
- Mm-mm.
That can't be.
I'm sure this is the right spot.
Hm?
Wait, hold on...
- Got company!
- These guys never give up.
Spike, Faye, deploy.
This is your little party, Jet.
Battle stations, or die with the ship.
Those are your options.
What the hell am I doing this for?
It's called "giving," Faye.
Think of us as fairy godparents.
We're about to grant the
princess a very special wish.
We are, huh?
Robot ships?
So these must be
the evil stepsisters.
Shit! They're trying to scare us.
I got it! I got it! I got it!
- Spike, come back in!
- What's that?
New plan. Looks like if we apply
enough energy to the sun stone,
we can draw out the
forces trapped inside it.
Yeah? Great, then what?
Then we take our shot.
All or nothing.
Whatever you're gonna do,
do it fast!
I put it in.
All right.
Spike, hit it with
your plasma cannon.
Right, I'm shooting a rock now...
Looks like you made it in time, Jet.
Pao! You're alive!
Meifa... It's been a long time.
Pao, you're in an
unstable force field.
I can't get any closer.
Yes, I know.
There's no oxygen left here, anyway.
I sent you that message
because I hoped
you'd manage to bring
my daughter out here.
In other words, you're saying
you used feng shui
to reach us and bring us out here
according to your will.
That's right.
It's not right.
You weren't in control
of this operation.
Meifa is here now because...
because she wanted to find you.
You might be right.
Perhaps I gave myself
too much credit.
Meifa, it's so wonderful
to see you one last time.
I hated you...
for all those years.
It's true. It hurt so much.
But now I don't.
Daddy...
Now, I don't know
if it was a good thing
or a bad thing that we
brought her out there.
But that is how this
peculiar case ended.
Meifa went back home to Mars.
Our no smoking area became
a smoking zone again.
And life returned to the same
daily routine just like before.
One thing has changed, though.
When I read the news,
I never check the horoscopes anymore.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
He came with a whistle.
Andy appeared out of the blue,
on horseback.
Who is he, friend or foe?
Or just an old-fashioned cowpoke?
The next episode is a shocking
sci-fi spaghetti western epic saga:
"Cowboy Funk."
Hey, aren't we taking this
cowboy thing a little too far?