Hey, sleepyhead, wake up!
Hey, sleepyhead, wake-
I gotta get up.
Taromaru, time for breakfast.
Taromaru?!
Taromaru!
It's not...
No!
Why?
Why?!
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
A Meeting
Field trip!
A fun, fun field trip!
Megu-nee! Did you pack a banana for a snack?
They sure are having fun.
I sure did... not!
We should be there soon.
Noooo!
Oh, is that it?
We're heeeere!
Hey, calm down a little.
Guess you're the kinda girl who gets
all fired up on field trips, huh?
I-I-I-I am not! I'm not!
Look at yourself, you're blushing.
Now, now.
But I really am worried...
Wh-whaaa...? I'm worried about you!
This place was hit pretty hard, too.
You don't have much presence,
so I'm worried you'll get lost!
It happened on a weekday,
so there weren't many people around.
I-I will not! I'm a teacher! And I do have presence!
Yeah... they were all going to school or work.
Then let's hold hands and keep one up in the air!
It's almost as if they still have memories
from when they were alive.
Then let's hold hands and keep one up in the air!
It's almost as if they still have memories
from when they were alive.
What do you mean, "then"?! Jeez!
Well, let's not get distracted,
and try to enjoy the field trip, alright?
What do you mean, "then"?! Jeez!
Well, let's not get distracted,
and try to enjoy the field trip, alright?
You're so mean!
After all, it's been a while since we went shopping.
Hey, you two!
Hurry up!
That's right, we've gotta keep
our eyes on that one. She's dangerous.
They left the door open?
Are you on lunch break? Hello?
Hey, keep your voice down.
Why?
Why, uh...
Inugami Yasutaka Piano Concert
Looks like there's an event going on.
An event? Like a festival?
It's a concert event.
So keep quiet so you don't bother them, okay?
Okay!
Shhh!
Thank you. Now, let's go!
Wow, it's huge!
I knew there'd be some here...
We can handle these numbers.
Try not to make a single sound!
Right.
Got it!
Shh!
Sorry.
Okay.
Let's go!
There aren't any in here.
Thanks, Ri-san.
I wonder what they've got?
Ri-san, I'm going to check downstairs.
The supermarket?
All the stuff there is probably rotten.
We want more canned goods, right?
Don't push it, okay?
I know, I know!
Hey, Ri-san, look at this!
Hmm, what is it?
I'll be fine. I'll definitely bring help back for you.
Kei...
There it is!
Yes, this is a huge haul!
Oh, Yamatoni beef!
A-a dog?
What? What is it?
Hey, no fair, that's mine!
Crap!
I hope Kurumi's alright...
Hey, Ri-san?
When's Kurumi-chan going to be back?
I don't know, shall we wait for her?
Okay.
Enka Corner
Ri-san, you're so refined.
Huh?
Phew, I'm safe.
Kurumi!
Ah, it's that dog!
A doggie!
Woof, woof, woof!
They can communicate?
Woof!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Arrgh!
Woof, woof, woof!
Sorry, just hold on a sec.
Here you go.
Hey, Yamatoni beef!
Hurry up, Ri-san.
Hold on one second.
Ri-san, you're so mean!
It's okay, he's not bitten.
Here you go, Yuki-chan.
Nice to meet you, doggy!
Yay! Yay! It's a doggy!
Yuki-chan, calm down!
Where did he come from?
I found him downstairs.
I wonder what happened to his owner?
I guess we should bring him along
in case we run into them.
Hey, Kurumi-chan, what's his name?
Beats me, does he have a tag on his collar?
Oh, he does!
Umm, Ta-ro-maru.
Taromaru?
Okay! Nice to meet ya, Taromaru!
Is the escalator broken?
There aren't as many here on the upper floors.
They're not good with stairs.
Let's go through the hardware and electronics store.
Okay.
Portable stove, gas cylinders...
And then...
Yes!
This!
An alarm keychain?
That's right.
It's so cute!
If you pull here, it'll...
Don't play with it, okay?
Remember, they're doing an event.
C'mon, just a little?
I. Said. No.
I got it!
What're you gonna do with that?
Use it for scaring away bad guys, of course!
Alright, we've gotten most of the important things.
Yep.
Then let's go to the clothing store next.
Yay!
Shh!
Sorry.
Is it alright to be doing this?
I think it's alright, given the circumstances.
I mean, we are girls, after all.
I-I'm okay...
It's fine...
I can still fit...
Hey, we're moving on!
Hey, can we please wait for a sec?
Megu-nee's not really in a position
to go anywhere right now.
We can go apologize to the shop people together.
I wasn't okay...
Megu-nee?
Yeah. I wanna cheer her up.
Let's see...
How about we get her a present?
Yeah, let's do that!
Do you know what Megu-nee likes?
Hmmm, I dunno.
She likes this, right?
Oh!
Here!
Megu-nee, here, a present for you!
You're going to buy it for me?
Yup!
Are you sure?
Of course!
Thank you, Yuki-chan, but you can hold on to it.
Huh, why?
Do you already have one?
Well, yes, but...
I knew it!
But that's why I want you to have the same one I do.
Oh, so we match!
Okay, then I'll pretend it's you,
Megu-nee, and protect it!
And he kinda looks like you, Megu-nee.
How?
This part especially.
4th Floor Map
So you get to keep it for yourself after all?
Yup!
Figures...
I got here first! Yay!
We're finally at the top floor.
Taromaru?
What's wrong?
4th Floor Map
Taromaru?
Taromaru, shhh!
Keep quiet, okay, Taromaru?
Thank you.
Ri-san.
What is it?
I heard something.
It sounded like a chair falling over.
One of them, you think?
But there weren't many at all on the floor below us.
And Taromaru was just whining, so maybe...
...there's a survivor?
Taromaru's owner?
If that's the case, we've gotta save them.
It came from here?
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
A movie theater!
Hello? Excuse us!
Doesn't look like anyone's here...
Hold on a sec, I'll check it out.
We'll wait here.
Be careful.
Look, look, Ri-san!
Doesn't this doggy look like Taromaru?
I-it sure does.
Run!
They're coming! Tons of them!
Yuki, let's go!
Yuki!
Kurumi-chan, where's Ri-san, and Megu-nee?
They're okay, just run!
I knew it...
It was just my imagination.
Run!
Crap!
There are so many of them...
Ri-san, scatter some glowsticks down there!
Right.
We're gonna break through. Follow me!
Let's go, Yuki-chan!
Yuki-chan?
What?
Are you okay?
You're burning up.
I'm fine!
Are you hurt?
We're alright.
Guess you really are the kind of girl
to get all fired up on a field trip.
Sorry.
It's okay, just rest, alright?
Okay.
Taromaru!
We should let her sleep a little.
You should rest, too, Kurumi.
You're the most tired out of all of us.
Yeah...
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
We didn't find any survivors anywhere.
There were lots of kids in that movie theater.
I guess they'd been waiting for someone
to come save them for a while.
No... The door was barricaded.
It was blocked so nobody could get out.
I don't think something came in and got them.
Someone inside must've been bitten.
I hate that. I just can't stand it.
I mean, there must've been people who ran
into that theater to protect their loved ones.
To protect... the people they care about.
If I'm infected, don't hesitate to do what must be done.
What are you saying?
Promise me.
Pinky swear!
What is it, Yuki-chan?
I'm hungry.
Alright, let's go home and make dinner.
Yeah.
Let's go back to the school.
Someone really was here!
I'm scared!
Are you happy, living in here, shut away?
Of course not!
We're out!
Alright, let's go back.
C'mon, Yuki!
Yuki?
Hey, did you hear that?
Huh? I didn't hear anything.
I heard a voice calling us.
Yuki, you just imagined that.
Let's get out of here, okay?
No! I really heard it!
Yuki-chan, calm down.
You heard it too, right, Megu-nee?
Huh? Well...
Hey, Taromaru!
Let's follow him!
No, Yuki-chan!
Yuki!
No!
Get away...
Help...
Someone!
Someone, please help!
Please!
There! Over there!
Taromaru? And...
There really was someone...
No, Yuki-chan, it's dangerous!
But...
But look!
Yuki-chan!
Dammit!
They're coming to...
Crap, at this rate...
Girls!
Cover your ears!
Hey, come with us!
Yuki, hurry up!
Taromaru...
Thank God you're alright.
Um, excuse me.
Did you see another girl around here?
She's about my age.
No, we didn't.
Oh, I see...
It took me a little longer to go,
but I'm leaving, Kei.
Talking on our way home
Telling each other our secrets
Even when the 5-o'clock chime rings out
I wonder why I feel we still haven't talked enough
A tiny four-leaf clover
Sways in the gentle breeze
Hey, I'm sure that yes, I'm sure
I hope tomorrow will be sunny, too
We walked the road together
Always saying we'd meet at the usual place
Ah, the fluffy clouds above
Seem like they'll be burned, they're shining so bright
Even if, one day, these days
Are but a faded memory
I want to give you
A lot of smiles right now
Next Time!
Going shopping, going shopping!
Don't waste your money, alright?
Manga's not a waste of money!
You should get some books for homework...
I wonder if they have the new volume!
Welcome
Next time on School-Live, episode 6:
"Welcome"