Tsukuyomi Shrine Daily Duty Log.
Kept by
Mitchan.
Kept by Mitchan.
I notice that Master makes statements such as,
"You lose if you do your best" or
"No need to do your best because you're just a human".
Or some variation thereof.
I'm totally fine with that,
but every time he says that he looks at me
in triumph as if he just outsmarted me.
That ticks me off and I just lose myself.
Next thing I know I black out...
When I finally come to, a few hours have already passed.
Right in front of me is Master,
sitting on the floor completely naked
then I realize that he's been addressing me
as "Master" instead of "Mitchan"...
Master
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 9                                               Ganbaranai
"IT'S NOT THAT I CAN'T DO IT"
I'm an assassin sent by Arahabaki,
the evil occult society.
I'm the spirit that haunts this Killing Stone Golem,
the golden furred, white faced nine-tailed fox,
Kyuubi no Kitsune!
Kyuubi no Kitsune?
Also known as Tamamo-no-Mae!
She who toys with the balance of this country!
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey, have you ever wished that
you could change the past?
Change the past?
I don't remember any incident like this
in my past! So could this be...
Mom wouldn't get caught this easily!
I've been waiting for this moment.
I spent about 10 years,
possessing you as a young child,
waiting for the moment you'd wish
you could change the past.
What do you mean?
I programmed myself to wake up
as soon as you made that wish.
All so that I could Alter the past to my convenience,
leeching off your Power of God!
Alter the past?
That's right. Altering history! That is my ability.
But it requires an enormous amount of power.
So it would be impossible without
absorbing and using your Power of God.
Altering history? It is taboo to Alter the past!
That's forbidden!
But this is what you wished for.
What...
Sasami Tsukuyomi, you harbored regret!
Regret is the desire to repent for the mistakes of the past.
The regret of the Supreme God could even
distort time and space and tamper with the past.
No way!
I do regret some things...
I betrayed my mother.
I also broke my promise and couldn't even
let my deceased mother rest in peace.
This Killing Stone Golem wouldn't have emerged
in this time and place under normal circumstances.
Do you know what that means?
What?
The Alteration of history has already begun!
The moment you harbored regret, everything ended!
No way...
I'll kill Juju Tsukuyomi right here, right now.
If I do that, the Power of God
will be transferred to her daughter.
And her daughter, Sasami Tsukuyomi,
is right in the palm of my hand.
That is the purpose of Altering history!
Our archenemy, the Tsukuyomi Shrine,
has been weakened.
The Power of God belongs to us!
I'm certain that the Arahabaki will prosper even more!
And this should help Milady at least a little...
"Milady"?
I know that we, the Arahabaki,
are going to rule this world, this planet!
That's ridiculous.
They used my mom up until she died,
all to manage a single country.
Just dealing with my life in this little body
is already too much for me to handle!
And THAT is what you'll rule the world with?
Don't make me laugh!
You can never do that!
Someone like you, who can't even talk smart
without using such a trick as Altering the past...
You'll never do that!
You can never rule the world!
Is that all you've got to say?
Now, go ahead and die, Juju Tsukuyomi!
The end shall come to Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Glory to Arahabaki!
What...
I remember this!
The day my mom died!
Good work.
Tsurugi?! What's going on?
I'm in the past inside someone else's body,
and now history has been Altered!
This is no time to relax.
Whoa!
Mom?
Yes, it's your mother,
who returned from the Land of the Dead because
she couldn't bear to watch her daughter's foolishness.
So you finally caught up with us.
What do you mean by that?
Remember she stuck her arm into you
and put some drug in you the other day?
She made sure to put her divine spirit
inside your body at that time.
She used it as a lifeline to return
from the Land of the Dead.
She put stuff like that inside my body?
Is that why I became so big?
I meant that to be a little bump,
but I just couldn't adjust the size.
I was so worried! Because not even
the Power of God could make me lose weight!
We can argue later.
For now, we're going to work together
and stop Tamamo-no-Mae's plot!
Indeed. I'll never let her conquer the world.
Altering the past is hideous enough to begin with.
This is the perfect timing for that
parent-student-teacher conference.
Tamamo-no-Mae activated her time travel
ability using regret as a trigger.
To reverse that, we need to erase
those negative emotions.
But how do we do that?
We travel back in time and find a hint in the past.
Is that even possible?
We're in a different time period right now, aren't we?
Juju's divine spirit came back inside Sasami,
but it looks like it wasn't supposed to happen.
Her ability malfunctioned, so I took that
opportunity to use that against her.
We're gonna travel back in time a little.
Here, I'm done!
What? I lost again?
Alright, Tsukuyomi, take off your clothes!
But I've only got my underwear on.
How about that bag?
Oh, I can't let it go, but I can't lose
my last piece of clothing, either.
Oh yeah, Papa-lin!
Just forget about the bag.
You can solve the problem by covering
your face with your underwear!
Oh, I didn't think of that! You're smart, Tama.
Yay, he complimented me!
I don't think it solved any problem.
What is this?
My bad. Looks like we came to the wrong time period.
It sure looks like you have a happy life.
Yes, I'm having so much fun every day.
Sasami, I think she was trying to be sarcastic just now.
What? Really?
Let's go to the next one!
What is this?
This is right after my Big Brother and I ran away
from the Tsukuyomi Shrine.
I felt like I was being crushed by guilt for running away.
Why are you there?!
Your Big Brother is always by your side!
If you see me, think there are thirty of me around you.
Shut up, you roach!
Get out of here!
Hey, I'm hungry, so cook something!
But because of my perverted Big Brother,
I didn't have time to be depressed,
Hey, I'm hungry, so cook something!
But because of my perverted Big Brother,
I didn't have time to be depressed,
which helped me a lot.
Here, Mom.
Mo m
What is it?
A present for Mother's Day! I heard there's such an event!
You mustn't draw, Sasami. Creative activities are evil.
When people create objects,
they imbue their wishes into them.
A wish of the one with the Power of God
can distort the world.
If you've got time to play,
you'd better train, you good-for-nothing.
I was really sad at that time.
That couldn't be helped.
That was a part of the training
to be a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Wha-?!
Mo m
I see you were actually happy!
I've had training to control my emotions!
It is no untruth to say that creation is dangerous.
Scolding is a mother's duty.
Mom...
Mom... You look so happy.
As a human, having her own child means happiness.
That's to be expected.
So you wanted me to be born...
Of course.
Hey, check it out! Something fun is going on over here!
Wait!
You're the candidate to be the next Tsukuyomi priestess.
What do you want with a failure like me?!
Be serious about training? Don't go to the town?
I'm sick and tired of listening to
your preaching, Big Sister!
Ruza...
I...
I like you!
What?
Die!
I didn't know that my mom was so passionate!
Don't look!
Stop it!
Don't look at the mistakes I made in my youth!
Creation comes after destruction!
Only she who has glimpsed the brink of destruction
and been cornered against the edge of death...
Only in her will the Power reside!
I know that's me, but she sure sounds
like she knows what she's talking about.
That's some serious training.
It must be tough to be a human.
That is also a part of the duty of a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Mom...
Let me ask you once again, Sasami.
No matter how many times you ask me,
I'm not going back to be a Tsukuyomi priestess.
But you're a Tsukuyomi priestess right now.
Whether you accept or abandon
the duty that's been succeeded for generations,
you should still have conviction.
I can't just let those wild gods of Japan
manage this country,
especially in this tumultuous time,
where no borders exist in this world.
It must be protected and managed by humans.
It's true that the gods in this country are nonchalant.
They're weak, indecisive and always making mistakes,
but because of that, you must overcome them
so that you can grow!
Isn't that what becoming stronger is all about?
You won't find Paradise in your room
or under your blanket.
You may get hurt in the process of going to school
or living day-to-day in society,
but you will be strong one day. You will become an adult.
Let's have more faith in the gods in this country!
And let's send them to the outside world!
We're nothing but caretakers
temporarily borrowing the Power of God.
This power isn't ours. So to think
we must protect it is sheer arrogance.
There's no need for us to do our best
for others or the world.
The era that we protect has ended.
I want to believe in the gods,
so I won't do my best anymore.
We don't have to do our best anymore.
I'm still half-baked, so I tend to waver a lot.
So for now I'll let you hold the Power of God, Mom.
And in the meantime I'll grow.
I'll be strong and good enough so that
I won't be crushed by the Power of God!
Is that your thinking?
Because I died so soon,
you were forced to become a Tsukuyomi priestess
even before you were mentally ready.
I used to underestimate you,
thinking that you were being selfish,
refusing to do your best because you weren't ready yet...
But you...
You reached that conclusion
after thinking and contemplating about it.
And you even realized our true objective, which no one
had ever been able to reach since time immemorial.
Your mother is proud of you.
You opposed me with conviction.
I no longer call you a traitor.
The one who was foolish and wrong was me.
You two were never wrong.
You just pushed yourselves a bit too far, is all...
I commend you for carrying out such
a troublesome duty like this for so long...
I think you did a good job.
Is this the advent of the Grandson of the Sun Goddess?
Note: the event in which Amaterasu sent her grandson to Earth
to found the lands that would become Japan
Now what are you going to do?
Everything started when I got tired
and abandoned the Power of God.
But we could start it all over again right here, right now.
I've had enough rest.
I took advantage of you guys and rested way too long.
In return I wore you humans out.
That shouldn't have happened in the first place.
The sun stopped rising, saying, "I'm tired now!"
That is unforgivable.
I don't know whether your long-standing
history was right or wrong.
You all have suffered much and many of you have died.
This country became corrupted, too.
It's because I didn't do my best.
That's MY regret!
Note: the Kusanagi Sword (Tsurugi), the Yata no Kagami Mirror (Kagami)
and the Yasakani Magatama Bead (Tama). These are the Imperial Regalia
Give me your honest answer!
Was I wrong? Did I mess up?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I just couldn't figure it out.
Should I have worked harder?
You did your best for a long time.
And you returned after taking a little rest.
Just pass the baton if you're tired.
I think that's the most effective way.
You're not wrong.
Don't regret our history, God.
We'll do our best until sunrise,
although it's a weak moonlight...
Okay!
Now, you shall die, Juju Tsukuyomi!
The end shall come to Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Glory to Arahabaki!
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but I made a promise to do my best a bit longer.
I can't allow myself to get killed!
What the...!
You let your ability activate by using our desire
to change the past as a trigger.
However we no longer have regret!
No way! Why is there a divine spirit
inside Sasami Tsukuyomi?!
I'm supposed to be able to control
the half-baked Sasami any way I want,
so what is this enormous divine spirit doing inside her?
I'm sorry, but I used you as a reason
to get Mother and Daughter to make peace!
Tsurugi?!
She happened to have the rare ability of
Time Travel, so I used it!
Say your prayers!
You mean to tell me that you used me?!
Kyuubi no Kitsune, she who has overturned
so many countries in the past, has been used by you?!
Now I can truly carry out the duty which
the Supreme God entrusted me with long ago.
I'll kill you so cruelly!
I'll grind your flesh and make a
sumptuous feast out of you!
I'll protect them all the way until the sun rises!
We're the ones entrusted with the
three sacred regalia, and that's our pride!
Okay, take care of the rest for me, will ya?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Sasami!
Do you want me to help you, Big Brother?
No, it's all right. You go inside and get warmed up.
I'm fine. Let me do it.
Okay. I'll bring another shovel,
so we can shovel snow together.
Then, one of the lady neighbors would be like,
"Oh my, you two siblings get along so well!"
and I'd be like, "Siblings? No way,
we're a married couple!"
Stop talking nonsense!
Hello.
Sasami Tsukuyomi.
H-hello... Have we met somewhere before?
TSUKUYOMI       KAMIOMI
SASAMI
You're famous.
You were absent from school for so long,
but suddenly you start coming to school one day.
Note: her hair ornament is in the image of the ancient god, Arahabaki, sole deity
of an aboriginal religion predating Japan's Eight Million Gods
And not only that, you happen to be
the little sister of a teacher.
It's quite interesting, you know.
Everyone's very interested in you.
Oh...
I'm the student council president of
Konohana Sakuya Academy.
Note: Named for the goddess of Japanese Life, Konohana Sakuya
(wife of Ninigi, the grandson of Amaterasu and founder of Japan)
Let me know if you ever need help with anything.
Let's be friends.
O-okay.
Well, well, good for you, Sasami.
Now you've got a new friend.
I will ask you this personally.
Please be nice to her.
However...
If you ever plot anything shady by using Sasami
or hurt her in any way,
I don't care if you're her friend,
I would not forgive you!
Are you Emishi? Or Tsuchigumo?
No, maybe Kumaso?
Note: Emishi, Tsuchigumo and Kumaso tribes were clans of ancient Japan
who did not claim allegiance to the emperor
I'm unlike anything you're guessing.
I see. Now I'm even more interested.
You two are so interesting.
Excuse me! What is your name?
Jou. Jou Edogawa. Isn't that a weird name?
Nice to meet you, Sasami!
You've got me very nervous.
You took direct action, which is very unusual.
Didn't you hear me say it? I'm very interested in that girl.
I understand that you're curious, but do control yourself.
That girl has lost the Power of God.
No way! But I felt her tremendous
divinity from this far away!
As you can tell by looking at the skeleton of the sun god,
some divinity remains in the empty shell, too.
I was planning to suck all her power,
but I guess I've got the wrong target.
But I get the feeling that this is going to be quite fun.
I can't wait to start my second year,
no, I can't wait for the spring.
You're our Master.
Even if you wish for total destruction,
all we could do is to follow your wish.
I know. I have high expectations for you.
Everything is for my happiness.
In other words, everything is for my personal desires!
With the full force of the Arahabaki,
let's spit on the cocky ones who call themselves gods
in this country and in this world!
As you wish...
...Milady.
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
What is this? An ending song?
Who would've thought I'd find this
establishment at a place like this?
But this miniature landscape
doesn't even amount to a dedication for God.
Here, I'll mark my first step towards world domination
at the head of the Arahabaki by dominating this place!
Milady, if you're so hyper from the beginning,
everyone's going to feel awkward about you.
Why? The beginning is very important
when it comes to stuff like this!
Would it be unbecoming if I invaded this place
without declaration of war?
Fine. I'll be courteous enough to
follow the rules of their strange world.
But what am I supposed to do?
Anything will do! Jou Edogawa will do anything!
Let's see. I guess you just grab this mic and sing.
What do you mean? Oh well, no matter...
There's nothing I can't do, as one who's inherited
the enormous power of Arahabaki!
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomademo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
Hikari sasu koi iro
Light shines on the love color
Zutto te wo tsunagou
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kasanari au shintoatsu
You're the best!
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kanjitainda
For a long time
What do you think?
Great work, Milady!
It looks like this is the end of it,
so let's go home and get warmed up.
I think they just used me...
Next Episode
Preview
Ganbaranai
@Pro-Wrestling
It's time for Ganbaranai@Pro-Wrestling,
and it's brought to you by me,
Sasami Tsukuyomi the commentator.
Ganbaranai
@Pro-Wrestling
Great Ganbaranai is at the red corner,
and Ganbaranai the Kid is at the blue corner.
Animal Ganbaranai is at the black corner,
Ganbaranai Isamu is at the yellow corner,
and Rasher Ganbaranai at the pink corner.
These five are...
Next time, episode 10
Next Time
Episode 10
"Fight an Enemy
You Cannot See"
"Fight Against the Invisible Enemy"