Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Hey...
What are we in line for?
Do you know, Yuki-chan?
No idea...
Now, now...
Miss
The Jam of Haruhi Suzumiya
Early Ticket Sale Drawing
There you have it.
Too bad.
I also got a miss.
Um...
I drew a winner.
Me too!
My true friends!
What about me?
I'm gonna follow you through.
No matter the pain.
Through the darkeness of this world if I must.
Big guy blocking...
'Cause you'll be there to shine the way.
Past the end of the future.
Here.
Won't let weakness...
...break down my soul.
That was incredible.
I was quite moved.
The first person who came out was so cool.
That guy?
No?
People actually go for that, huh?
Konata, you haven't said a word.
The whole fatigue setting in after an event's over thing, huh?
I guess I was a bit moved myself.
I wonder what this feeling is...
Can't Change
So Quickly
What are you doing?
Come on. We're going now.
You're really proactive about some odd things.
Because today's our last chance to
see the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
When you put something off to tomorrow...
...or the day after...
...it ends up raining...
...or the petals start falling.
Oh, yeah.
What happened to the goldfish from the summer festival?
Actually...
...I ended up feeding it too much...
...and it ended up like this.
Huge!
Shogun?!
I took a little too good care of it.
Wait a minute.
Are you sure you didn't feed it something funny?
That's no longer a goldfish!
I can only pray that it's because he's living a good life.
Are you going to eat it?
How could I?!
There's an anime where animals a guy took
good care of return as humans to serve him.
You always bring up hardcore references.
I should probably put it on a diet...
Kagami.
Goldfish Scooping
Are you thinking about getting a replacement?
It's gotten pretty chilly.
We should probably head home.
When you wear daytime clothes to see
nighttime cherry blossoms, it gets cold.
And your butt gets cold when you sit down.
I've heard that the average temperature in March...
...is close to the average temperature in December...
...and April and November are quite similar.
If it were November or December, I'd definitely wear a lot more.
In March and April...
...you just tend to dress lighter.
Isn't it because you're sick of wearing winter clothes?
Maybe it's a way of expressing
how you want it to be spring already.
You look like you're fine, Kagami.
Maybe it's because you're wearing...
Long-wavelength infrared effect
Came prepared.
I'm not wearing any!
That's all you get today, Goldy.
It'd be a problem...
...if he showed up as a wife beater...
As if...
What's wrong with Sis?
Man, that really smarts...
I have really delicate skin.
This season is brutal for me.
Sounds like a pain.
And I stay in the house most of the time.
They have a lot of goods that help for allergies.
Why don't you buy some?
Transform!
I see!
This works!
Reduces the effect of allergies by 99%!
Now he's suspicious on the outside and the inside.
Don't get in trouble with the police.
I'm going to go do some shopping.
Have fun!
Want to come along?
Nope!
Wait, Dad.
You're going shopping like that?
Of course.
Or it'd defeat the purpose.
Here's our next story.
Woman robs convenience store
Last night around eleven...
...a woman broke into a convenience store...
...and attempted to steal the cash.
Hey, Yu-chan.
What is it?
Aren't there a lot more robbers
disguised with allergy gear this time of year?
It sounds possible.
Freeze.
How did this happen?
Tomorrow?
Sure.
Haven't done that in a while.
That's right.
Plus, I'm already done with my homework.
What did you just say?!
You finished your homework?!
For real?!
Unbelievable!
Sorry.
I lied.
Yeah, you know how you have to lie on April Fool's?
Good thing I remembered.
No, seriously...
And you have no intention of doing it, huh?
You must be bored.
You're the only person who would call at this hour just to lie.
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
Yes, this is Izumi.
This is Kuroi.
Is this the Izumi residence?
Teacher.
Izumi, it's me.
Sorry.
I accidentally overwrote a save file...
...on a game I borrowed from you.
Just lying! Hey!
Fooled you!
Today's April Fool's!
There was somebody else as bored as me...
Teacher.
What's up?
The other day, Miyuki-san said...
Even someone like Ms. Kuroi can be a teacher...
...so getting a certificate must be a cakewalk.
...something like that.
That brat...
So the sweet talk was just an act...
Um, Teacher.
I was joking...
Konata called me just so she could lie.
Honestly...
Did you lie to anyone today?
That's unusual.
What was it?
I-I just did.
I lied about lying.
Th-That's hard to get.
And there's no need to force yourself to lie.
Wh-What was Kona-chan's lie like?
Something about finishing her homework on her own.
In retrospect, I really shouldn't have fallen for it.
It's impossible.
If she lied, then she hasn't done her homework yet, right?
Well, knowing her...
...she definitely hasn't done it!
I see...
You were just thinking...
...that it's a good thing you aren't alone, right?
No...
Konata.
Do you have a minute?
Is that interesting?
Unique.
I see.
Konata.
I'm actually thinking about remarrying.
Wait, I know that you're against it.
In your mind, Kanata will always be your only moth—
What?
You're okay with it?
If I get remarried?
Why not?
B-But...
You know...
She'll be your new mother?
What will my new mother be like?
Uh...
Well...
Wh-When you put it that way...
Okay. Here's the next question.
What is the kenjogo form for iku (to go)?
It's gotta be ukagau (to inquire)!
Piece of cake!
That's right.
It's to inquire.
That should be the correct answer.
Sounds right.
The correct answer is mairu (to visit).
O-On second thought, that's right...
Yeah...
I went with the flow there.
What's with the weird atmosphere?
Me too...
This is what happens when
you're positive you're right.
Multiple choice quiz, question one.
Which prefecture does not border the ocean?
A. Ibaraki.
B. Tochigi.
C. Kyoto.
It's B!
B, right?
This is easy.
The correct answer is B!
Next question.
Of the hardest known problems in mathematics...
...the theorem proven by...
...Princeton's Sir Wiles in 1994 was...
A. The Pythagorean theorem.
B. Taylor's theorem.
C. Fermat's last theorem.
Why is everyone so eager when the answer is obvious...
...but then they keep quiet when they're not sure?
Since it's spring break, we should visit Miyuki-san's house.
That sounds good.
It's pretty far so I've never been there before.
Miyuki-san's family is rich, right?
I wonder what it's like.
A pool in her backyard?
Nah...
A security fence around the whole place.
No, it's probably a lot more normal.
She probably has a pet.
A ferret might fit her image.
A white one.
Nah, gotta be a dog.
A huge, white dog.
With a huge yard and a white parasol.
She might have a dog.
That's how the conversation went.
You're welcome to visit...
...but please don't expect too much.
I'm sorry to say that I have no pets.
However, while we don't have a white, big dog or a parasol...
...one of our neighbors does.
And the neighbor's kid is entering Ryouou this year.
She's also been invited. Do you want to come?
My friend's cousin...
...is entering Ryouou.
It's a small world after all.
S-So sleepy...
Honestly...
It's because you got used to sleeping all morning.
Konata.
Yo.
What?
You also got used to sleeping in?
I've been gaming for three days straight...
I'm about to die...
The only thing they have in common is their laziness!
Miyuki Takara
Minoru Shiraishi
Konata Izumi
Tsukasa Hiiragi
Miyuki Takara
Minoru Shiraishi
Konata Izumi
Tsukasa Hiiragi
We're in the same class again!
You're right!
That's great.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
You're in our class.
Indeed.
That's wonderful.
Let's have another great year!
Let's!
Minami Iwasaki
Yutaka Kobayakawa
We're in the same class!
I-I hope we have a wonderful year!
So do I.
Kagami's the only one in a different class again.
I see you guys all the time anyway.
If we weren't in different classes, you'd wear me out.
That's too bad...
Sis...
No big deal.
It's the same as usual.
Besides, someone like Konata...
...will come borrowing notes or textbooks.
You know me well.
So that's that...
Go on ahead.
See you later!
Yo, Hiiragi!
What class you in?
We're in the same class again!
If you count middle school...
...that makes five years straight?
Let's have another good year.
Huh?
Some heartless people only look for their top priorities.
There, there.
We're like part of the background!
I wonder how class assignments are decided.
They might try to avoid grouping all the good students together...
...or try to divide up relatives...
...or split up the troublemakers as much as possible.
At least that's what I've heard.
It probably depends on the school.
In TV shows, all the troublemakers end up in one class.
It's more exciting that way.
But high schools are supposed to gather people of the same level...
...so there shouldn't be any big troublemakers.
That's true.
Miyuki...
That's where you say, "You need to
realize that you're a troublemaker."
You don't want to be put on the same level as her, right?
No, that's not true...
The bell already rang.
Teacher sure is late.
That's right.
Everybody, sit down!
Still good.
Barely made it.
No good.
I'm your homeroom teacher, Kuroi.
Y'all advanced a year in school now...
...so stop acting like you're on vacation...
...and start working hard.
Th-That wasn't convincing at all!
Class Rep
First
Semester
Duties
Library
Staff
Well, I won't bug you about studying all the time...
...but this is your last year in high school...
...so I want you to have a meaningful experience.
Okay.
Let's get straight to class duties.
Class Rep
First
Semester
Duties
Library
Staff
Class Rep
First
Semester
Duties
Library
Staff
Takara.
Can you be class representative for the first semester?
Yes.
Once you've been class rep, it gets attached to your image.
That's true.
Though I don't have any problem with it.
The teacher usually decides roles for the first semester.
Because of all the unfamiliar faces...
...it's hard for the students to choose.
In Ms. Kuroi's case, isn't it less
work for her if she chooses Miyuki-san?
I can hear you.
Teacher's hair was all wild.
But it looks like we'll have another fun class with Ms. Kuroi.
Well, she's a fun person.
The class atmosphere usually depends on the teacher...
I see.
I get it.
So you two are blaming your laziness on your teacher.
I can hear you.
I'm Iwasaki.
Nice to meet you.
That girl's pretty cute.
I was in the same middle school as her.
She never talks.
And she's a downer.
And all she does is read. It's creepy.
But she's actually a really nice person.
So I'm the only one who knows.
I feel a little special.
Next.
Y-Yes!
The first impression is important.
I have to be cheerful.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
Though I may look this way...
...I didn't skip here from grade school.
Just kidding.
Skipped?
What was that?
H-Huh?
Huh? What?
Did Big Sister's influence turn me into a maniac?
In that case...
I'd like to decide on class duties...
Anybody interested in being class representative?
Guess not.
Iwasaki.
You were class rep in middle school.
Go for it.
Really?
Can you do it, Iwasaki?
I'm sorry.
I'm planning on a different duty.
I'd prefer someone with experience...
What are you planning on?
Working in the library?
The nurse's office.
Teacher!
I'll be class representative!
She's a really nice person!
Cherry blossoms bloom into future, love, and dreams.
Spring...
...tends to gives you the feeling that...
I can't stop my heart from racing.
...something's about to begin.
A new meeting.
Let the two of us spend...
Konata Izumi
A new life.
...this touching season together.
Konata Izumi
A new love.
This moment of a lifetime...
Konata Izumi
With your childhood friend...
The upperclassman you admired...
This meeting is the beginning of our story.
Or a strange transfer student...?
Cherry blossom petals dance in the air...
A little anxiety and a lot of expectation...
It's what they call 5 seconds to falling in love.
...carrying our wishes...
Also known as MK5.
That's the happy image you get...
But in reality, you have to start over with people you don't know...
...so it's depressing.
I'm already used to it.
You've got it easy.
Big Sister!
Yu-chan.
Haven't seen you since morning.
That's right.
Not since morning.
Oh.
This is the person I told you about...
The one who helped me.
So you found her.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you.
See?
Just like I said.
I knew she would pass.
Okay.
But Yu-chan...
You forgot that she could have passed but chosen not to come.
It worked out in the end so it's okay!
By the way, what are you doing?
We wanted to check where the nurse's office is.
Since I'll probably be visiting it.
I see.
Show us the way, Big Sister.
Okay.
Leave it to your big sister.
Where is the nurse's office?
NURSE'S OFFICE
AAAAAAAAA
I've never gone before so I don't know.
Hey now.
You've been here two years, and you
don't know where the nurse's office is?
Well, doesn't that just mean I had a healthy two years?
No, you went there for your physicals.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think I've ever been to the art room.
If you choose music for your fine
art, you won't have a chance to go.
I myself have never stepped foot in the judo hall.
I didn't even know we had a tea room until recently.
Even after going to the same school for three years, huh?
I guess everybody only goes to the places they need to.
I rarely go to the study room.
I go there!
Unexpected.
The silence...
It's perfect for sleeping.
Really...
Oh...
Yu-chan went to find the nurse's office
with the girl who helped her during exams.
They ended up in the same class.
It's a miracle.
When you stop and think about it...
...the fact that I met and became friends
with Kona-chan and Yuki-chan at this school...
...might be a miracle!
Pretty much.
We can only be here together for one more year.
But Kagami was the only one in a different class the whole time.
Don't mention that.
The correct answer is B. hemlock.
It'll be on the test so keep that in mind.
Hey.
Wake up, Izumi!
Potemkin!
What were you dreaming about?
Sorry.
I'm actually concentrating really hard on not falling asleep.
But Teacher...
They still come!
Those demons of sleep...
With no warning!
No way to defend!
A full-out attack!
Not sure why you're trying to explain yourself...
Maybe this will help you stay awake.
Miyuki-san, you don't fall asleep in class, right?
Is there some kind of trick?
I wouldn't call it a trick...
But I really need my sleep...
...so I go to bed at eleven.
By the way...
...I went to bed at ten during our second year.
No good.
No chance.
Can't copy that!
I remember that this stuff was important so I took notes...
...but I was asleep half the time so I have no idea what I wrote.
I can't tell.
But just looking at this makes me feel good about myself.
This is proof that I tried to study.
But what did I write down...
Aren't those formulas?
Ms. Kuroi.
Wow!
You can understand this abomination!
Pretty much.
But that means you weren't dreaming about world history.
Okay.
Big Sister, you're still up?
Guess it stinks.
Oops.
It's already this late?
Maybe somebody's on.
You never learn, huh?
Can't wait for tomorrow.
Good lucky!
This is Lucky Channel, broadcasting to the whole wide world!
I'm your navigator, Akira Pretty Kogami!
And I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
We've already reached the 15th episode of Lucky Channel.
Huh?
This is the 15th episode?
Yes...
Then isn't this your last one?
Uh...
See ya.
Didn't you hear?
The producers told me that...
...starting with episode 16, the show
would feature Akira Kogami alone...
...so good luck.
Uh, that's...
Hey!
Gotcha!
April Fool's!
Oh...
That's what it was...
See ya, sucker.
That's right...
Anyway, you were pretty pumped.
During the Jam of Haruhi...
...the MC was someone who looked like you.
Really?
Couldn't be...
So when am I going to get a concert?
No idea...
They better tell me early...
...since my schedule's filled up for the near future.
I'll go check right away!
Hurry.
Look!
The East is...
Hurry it up...
...is burning red!
Hurry... it... up...
Circle.
Circle?
Producer says okay.
Next time?
Understood!
Next week during this time...
...we'll have a live concert featuring Akira Kogami!
N-Next week?!
F-F-For real?!
They secured a stage?
Yes.
He pulled some strings to get it done.
And bend.
Awesome!
Alright!
Not bad, Itou!
Man...
I can't wait to hear you sing.
No way!
Seriously?
For real?!
Leave the MC duties to me.
So you do know what you're doing.
Believe it or not I'm well-known for my abilities as an MC.
I'm going all out!
There you have it, everyone!
Let's go crazy next week!
Then we'll see you next week!
Bye-bee!
Oh, yes.
Will Minoru Shiraishi really be back next week?
I'm a lieutenant.
Hey.
What are you going to sing first?
You're not starting with Sunny Sunshiny, right?
The first song isn't Sunny Sunshiny, right?
Oh, he already started.
What are you singing first?
Anyway, in that case...
Whenever you're ready.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Inori.
I'm Matsuri.
I'm Miki.
I'm Tadao.
Next time:
「Ring」
Ring.
Look forward to next time!