I will act as a married woman.
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who are you talking about?
You'd get somewhere with a single-lens
reflex camera and a telephoto lens.
It is you, Onee-chan!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Usuda Sakura.
Yamaji? Yamaji?
You called, Youko-sama?
I invited my classmates to visit tomorrow.
We will be playing in the garden.
That's wonderful!
Start preparations immediately.
Of course, Youko-sama.
Welcome to my home!
Shall we play house?
That sounds delightful.
Yes.
I will act as a married woman.
I will be the wife of a chairman.
And I, the wife of a real estate magnate.
Today, I will go to the beauty salon and nail salon.
Meanwhile, I will have my pet trimmed.
Perhaps we will have foie gras
sauté with caviar this evening.
A tradesman will be visiting today.
Actually, This Is What I Live For
And that's just one of the heartwarming
memories from when Youko-sama was younger.
Stop talking about things from the past.
You're a rich girl through and through.
Sounds just like you.
But... has Sonobe-san...
...always been like that?
Yes.
She said she was already
well into adulthood by then.
What were you like when
you were little, Futaba?
Hm, when l was little...
Futaba's
Memories
I'm home!
Welcome home, Futaba.
What's for snack?
Is bread okay?
Yep!
Yummy!
I was an energetic girl who ate a lot.
You have been like this since then...
What about you, Hayama-chan?
Well, I...
Teru-chan, what's wrong?
Santa... presents!
What about presents?
I told Santa-san I wanted a white tiger,
but he tried to pass it off with this.
And if that was impossible, I would have
conceded to my second choice of a puma,
third choice of a snow leopard,
or fourth choice of a saber-toothed cat.
That's terrible.
He's cutting corners.
He should quit, huh?
Teru-chan... cheer up.
Okay...
...but it's probably my fault.
Santa didn't get me what I wanted,
because I was a bad girl.
I'll be a good girl and study hard.
Yeah...
...even if it's just for show.
One Moment Please
And that's when you awakened!
What do you mean?
It seems your sister has always been kind.
Yeah, I'm jealous, since I'm an only child.
Teru-chan!
Onee-chan.
Can I have lunch with you all today?
Oh, we have already finished our—
I'm having bitter melon today.
Stir fried?
Nope, it's raw.
You still jealous?
Oh, yeah.
It comes out tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow?
Grand Prize
This Month's
Grand Prix
Tama-chan (1 year old)
You see, Teru-chan has...
No way.
My kitty is just as cute.
My kitty is a hundred times cuter!
Its coat is silky, and it has cute eyes!
Hayama Bel-chan (1 year old)
What?!
Morning!
Hm?
What are you looking at, Nishiyama?
Nishiyama?!
Al... ways... always...!
You're always, always—
Collection of Popular Cats!
That won't do.
None of these kittens
have done anything wrong.
Oh, is that...?
There's a picture of my kitty in here!
There's so many of them,
and they all look the same...
What?!
It's obvious! He shines
differently than the others!
Hayama Bel-chan (1 year old)
Get your eyes checked!
Ugh, what a doting parent.
Hayama-san.
So it really was your cat.
He's a cute one.
Mine is cuter, though.
Why, thank you.
The kitten you got from me is cute, too.
Not as cute my mine, though.
My cat is cute, but yours is also...
And yours is also...
Well, well...
Well, well, well...
Well, well, well, well...
I don't get it!
My, that's amazing, Hayama-san.
It's so lovely.
It would not be as lonely
living on my own if I had a pet.
But my apartment does not allow...
You need to find another place, huh.
I do not have the means for that.
Oh, but you do have a dog.
Huh?
A faithful dog who runs free.
Who are you talking about?
Oh, no.
To think of Yamaji as a dog
is quite unpleasant.
Youko-sama.
Throw this and say, "fetch."
Fetch...
Here.
That's creepy!
What?!
I won't lose.
No, I won't!
I can do it, too!
I'll take a cute picture that's magazine-worthy!
Hey, wait!
Let me take your picture!
Come back!
Nishiyama?
I respect animal photographers.
Nishiyama-san?
You'd get somewhere with a single-lens
reflex camera and a telephoto lens.
Wait, are you really thinking to buy them?!
You actually own that stuff?
Hayama-chan, so photography's a hobby of yours?
Oh, it's not my hobby.
It's my duty.
Duty?!
Do you have other hobbies?
Mm, not really.
Maybe reading.
Like international guides to torture?
I finished reading most
of those in middle school.
Is that so?
Is eating your hobby, Futaba-san?
It's not a hobby.
Humans need to eat, right?
That's why I eat.
Humans...
Why do you have a look of pity in your eyes?!
What's your hobby then?
Why are you asking so nicely now?
My hobby?
I like cooking.
You're kidding.
That'd be the lamest joke of your life.
Wha—
You mean you like to eat cooked meals?
Or that you like eating a ton of it?
No, I like actually making it!
I like eating, so I can actually cook!
Even though I eat bread for lunch.
You can tell us your real hobby now.
You don't believe me!
I really do like cooking!
I'll eat something at a restaurant
and try making it at home.
So it really is eating.
Well, I guess my hobby
would be eating out then.
E-Er...
I have...
...a request.
I have always wanted to try this...
On the way home, while talking with friends.
I can't believe you have never eaten here.
Since Futaba-san said her hobby
is eating out... if you are willing...
Actually, this is what I live for!
Th-This...
It has been my dream to eat this.
What a humble dream.
Let us talk endlessly about vague
and silly things while eating this!
Go ahead!
What should I say?
Anything is fine.
I do not mind if you talk about food
or animals as you normally do—
Those aren't silly!
How is it? Is it good?
I feel like there is something missing.
It would be much better with mayonnaise.
So you still need some, huh?
Youko-sama?
This might not be the right place to ask
you this, and it's not a silly question,
but I feel like it's okay to ask now.
Futaba?
What are your parents doing right now?
I do not know.
My mother passed away
when I was young, but my father...
Your dad?
When my father lost everything
and decided to start over, he said this:
"All right, daddy's going to do something big!"
From then on, he has been
sending money regularly,
but I do not know where he
is or what he is doing.
You have had it hard, Youko-sama.
A little late to say it now, though.
So that's why you're living on your own.
Yes.
If you ever need anything, just ask.
We want to help!
Thank you for making my dream come true.
You're over exaggerating.
Keep on inviting us!
For when it's related to food, right?
Onee-chan?
I knew it!
It is you, Onee-chan!
"Onee-chan"?
Youko-sama, you have a brother?
Oh, no.
Yuu-san is—
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takezono Yuu; Onee-chan
and I are promised to each other.
What?!
Promised to each other?
Sounds like something rich people do.
You have the wrong idea.
I have known Yuu-san since we
were young, it is nothing formal.
I'm serious about it, though!
Yes, yes.
Ah, okay.
I see now.
I have money, so you
will not have a difficult life.
Money?
Oh! I need to go to cram school.
Onee-chan, I'll see you again, right?
Yes.
Please continue to get along
with Youko onee-chan.
We will.
Yup.
If you will excuse me!
It has been a long time,
Young Takezono-sama.
You worked at Onee-chan's place.
You're Yamaji, right?
What are you doing?
I have something to deliver to Youko-sama.
Are you still pretending to be her servant?
You're getting in my way,
so can you stop already?
Stalker.
He's just a child.
A child...
Hey, hey, about that boy from yesterday...
You mean Yuu-san?
He seemed pretty attached to you.
Yeah.
It has been a while since I have
seen him, but I am glad he is well.
He seems like a reliable boy.
There's a difference with the rich ones.
Oh, yeah.
I can't walk home with you guys today.
Oh?
What are you doing?
My cousin's staying with us for a week.
I need to go pick her up.
Your cousin?
My, I would like to meet her.
Really? I could really use some help.
Help?
West Park
Sakura!
Oh, Futaba-chan.
Sorry, were you waiting?
Geez, you're late!
I'll introduce you.
These are my friends,
Youko-sama and Hayama.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
She's my cousin, Sakura.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Usuda Sakura.
My, you are adorable.
Yes, I know.
What?
Sorry, she's a little weird.
D-Do not worry.
She really is adorable.
By the way, why does she
have so much luggage?
I have clothes and other things.
This amount of luggage is normal for a girl.
So this is what you meant by needing help.
Thanks for helping!
You summoned me?
I told you, that's creepy!
I don't think I'm extraordinary,
but I'm pretty up there.
I see...
That's why I've planned out my life.
Sakura's
Life
Sakura
Student
Age
Occupation
In the summer when I'm fourteen, I'll be
scouted in Harajuku and debut as an idol.
Idol
After being in some movies and commercials,
I'll get married at twenty-three.
Bride
I'll give birth to a boy at age twenty-five.
Mommy
At twenty-eight, I'll debut as a model
in the young missus' magazine.
Model
At fifty, I'll move overseas
and live a carefree life.
Socialite
That's how I've been thinking of it.
You never know what life will bring.
Youko
Former Rich Girl
That's depressing.
This person is a kind of handsome.
I accept many types of people.
He's actually...
...more of a stalker who
pretends to be a part-timer?
Ugh, that's the worst.
I don't need you in my life.
I'm not even in your life, huh.
Onee-chan!
Oh?
Yuu-san!
I'm so glad I ran into you.
Here!
It's wagyu beef I received as a gift.
Wagyu beef?
We can't finish it all,
so I wanted to give some to you.
It's yummy!
Yuu-kun!
Usuda!
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
What are you doing here?
What?
You two know each other?
The meat's sweet juice floods your mouth!
Yeah, we're in the same class.
Right now, he's the top
candidate to be my darling.
Don't decide that on your own!
Aw, you're just embarrassed.
It will be so wonderful!
I am not.
Why not?
You two would make a good couple.
You think so, too?
Wagyu beef...
No!
Youko onee-chan is my betrothed!
What do you mean, "betrothed"?
That is...
Is it over for me?
Do I sill have a chance?
Well, it's a promise they made
as kids, nothing formal.
And Youko-sama isn't serious about it.
Right, Youko-sama?
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef.
Youko-sama...
See you, Onee-chan!
Wait, Yuu-kun!
Meat. Beef. Wagyu beef. Meat!
Er...
What should we do?
Youko-sama!
How was yesterday's meat?
No fair.
The marbled wagyu beef
was probably delicious.
I'm jealou—
Huh?
You bully!
Shame on you.
What?!
My first meat in a long while...
It is fine.
I can cook this!
You just need to fry the meat.
The outside was crunchy
while the inside was rare.
Ah...
You messed up cooking it, huh?
Hey, you still have meat left, right?
Yes, but...
All right, I'll cook it for you.
What?
I told you.
Cooking is my hobby.
It's good quality meat, so the
trick is to not cook it too long.
Here it is.
Oh, this is it!
Ouch.
You really didn't believe that I could cook?
If I only ate and couldn't cook,
it'd be pretty bad.
I'm sure most people think you only eat.
No way!
Well, anyway, let's eat while it's hot!
Let's eat!
Delicious!
It's tender and juicy!
Ah, this is what meat is supposed to taste like.
The Japanese style radish sauce was good, too.
I don't make things that I have to
splurge on and can't eat them normally.
In other words, Mom's cooking is my specialty!
Momma!
Be in awe and worship me.
A mom's cooking?
My mom also...
She often made a dish of veal
spareribs simmered with chickpeas.
Veal...
It was very delicious...
...but today's meal was just as good!
Thank you for the meal.
It has been a long time since
I have eaten at home with others.
Youko-sama...
How about seconds?
I'll fry up all the meat!
Futaba-san.
Eating delicious food
makes people happy, right?
It puts you in a pleasantly good mood.
So you should keep eating
yummy things, Hayama-chan.
What are you implying?
I will learn to cook delicious dishes as well.
And I will invite you both over!
I gladly accept!
What will you make?
I will poeler straight-from-the-bakery bread
crusts topped with fresh-squeezed mayonnaise.
Then on a whim, the chef will
flambé it with a special balsamic?
Make it on the crunchy
side with the works!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll do it!
I'll
do
it!
I'll sell
delicious
steak for
cheaper
than this
place!
I'll sell delicious steak
for cheaper than this place!
And
so, the
cooking
show-
down
began.
Futaba
went
about
to find
ingredi-
ents.
And so, the cooking showdown began.
Meat!
Futaba went about to find ingredients.
...I think something like
that will happen next.
...I think
something
like that will
happen
next.
My, that
would be
good!
This will not happen.
My, that would be good.
A cooking story needs a taste tester!
A
COOKING
STORY
NEEDS A
TASTE
TESTER!
Waiting
for an offer
to be the
taste tester.
Nishikawa
Next time: Your Birthmarks Have Faded