Last time, a rival finally appeared in front of me!
I'm Nidou Kaneru.
Kaneru and I will fight to prove whose doujinshi will sell better,
With our pride and willpower on the line!
Enough already...
I'm not done yet!
I'll bet you're looking forward to seeing whom the goddess of victory will smile upon!
You meanie...
And sure enough, the result?
Right after this!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
Aren't you going to ask me why I'm in a good mood?
Why are you in a good mood?
So you realised!
You made me realise.
I won, I won!
Did you win a Columbian Horned frog or something?
Not a pet, I'm saying I won a bet!
So you were saying you won by selling just one copy?
And to Hoshi-kun alone, at that.
To be able to become that happy over selling one copy...
Honestly, I'm a little jealous.
Well...  yeah.
My name is Nidou Kaneru.
24 years old.
Second year employee.
With a very ordinary office job.
I'm back!
And when I come home, all that's waiting for me is my manga's manuscript.
That's right, I'm basically a doujin author on the side.
I really liked it at first...
But it isn't easy.
I'm hungry...
Though my books don't sell,
I'll still press on.
So then Tsuyuri told me,
"It's too early for you to be bragging," see?
Wait, are you even listening?
Eh, ah, sorry.
I was busy looking at Sora so I wasn't really paying attention.
Geez, Justice...
Sting, sting!
Sora...
Jus-ti-ce!
Well, whatever.
You're back to your usual self after all.
Thanks to you.
I was able to give him the epic I'd crammed my heart into with all my might, after all.
Take this!
Take this.
It's a manga I drew for your benefit.
Read it and see the error of your ways!
Though that manga you were desperately trying to finish turned out to be pointless in the end.
Najimi, I'll ask you again...
You went into the hotel with him for research, right?
That's right.
But I still don't trust that guy.
I'll be watching him, with constant vigilance!
Huh? You're still going on about that?
Well, I'll see you later.
Yeah.
"Illustration Techniques to Put You Ahead of the Competition"...
This is it, this is it!
G-Good day!
T-thanks for the other day!
This is quite a coincidence, huh?
Were you looking for a book as well?
Yeah.
"Illustration Techniques to Put You Ahead of the Competition." I guess you could say... this.
This, you say?
Won't you let me have it?
No way, there's only one copy here!
Then isn't that all the more reason?
Huh?  But I found it first!
Please!  I've turned this store upside down looking for it!
Even if you say that...
Why not?  You won before, after all!
I... don't know whether I'd call that winning...
Then let's do rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors?
I'll go with rock, so...
Rock, paper...
Wait!
Oh god, that's mean...
But wait, it's silly to decide this with rock, paper, scissors in the first place!
What's going on, Najimi?
Geez, how embarassing...  raising your voices in a bookstore!
It wasn't my fault, it was all her fault!
And this is?
Wah!  It's the girl Najimi-chan was competing against!
Competing, you say...  It wasn't really...
I see.
By selling your books, you force yourselves to improve.
It's a wonderful relationship.
Hello... my name is Nidou Kaneru.
I'm a businesswoman by day.
A businesswoman?
Is it strange?
I, uh, no.  I'm Osana Najimi.
This is Justice.
And this is...
"Justice", from that famous circle?
You've heard of me?  I'm honored.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
I'm Sora!
I always buy your books!
I was in tears while reading the 500 page epic you recently released...
And, and...
I...
Thank you kindly.
No, no!
Kaneru-san...
I think I'll let you have this book.
Really?
Yeah.  After all, I can always get drawing lessons from Justice.
From me?
From Justice-san?
Why not? I have the side benefit of being this guy's childhood friend.
I'm envious...
Well, it doesn't bother me, but...
Me too, me too!
I'd like him to teach me, too.
He wouldn't do that.
If you're okay with learning from me, I'd be happy to.
Hey!  Hang on, why'd you go and agree to that?
Why not, Najimi?
If you compete on equal footing, the two of you'll be able to reach an even higher level.
That might be true, but...
Fine then.  I'll show her my true colors!
This should be it, but...
She's not here as promised, huh?
Then let's go home.
Chi.
Good morning.
Welcome, please come in.
Sorry to intrude!
Those are some cute pajamas.
And a cute plush toy!
My name is Aiorosu the bear.
A gallant warrior.
I don't like fighting-kuma.
Nice to meet you-kuma.
Well, same here.
Sorry, I was half-asleep!
Did I do anything weird?
Well, yes.
Saying such unladylike things...
Quiet, Tsuyuri!
This is my friend Tsuyuri.  She's also drawing doujinshi.
Nice to met you. I hear you're competing with Najimi over sales.
Eh, no, not really.
It'd be more fun for me if you won.
I'll be rooting for you!
Please do your best.
Thank you!
T-this girl...
This is...
If you stare at this too much, it'll shorten your lifespan.
What kind of picture is that?
So, how are my drawings? Do they leave an impression?
Though it's common to both of you, you're not very conscious of drawing three-dimensional scenes.
The drawing...
Three-dimensional, huh...
Well, this is new.
Okay, uh...
Well, I'll try and draw it for you.
Like this, while visualising the space inside the paper...
Amazing!
So that's how you do it!
Do you get it?
Well then, I'll give you more advice about your art.
Living by yourself's pretty nice...
N-not really.
Oh, that's right!
If there's time, there's something I'd like to give you.
I got this from a person at work, but...
A Colombian tree frog.
For you to have bought one...
I don't need it!  I don't, I don't, I don't!
But keeping pets here is prohibited, and I've got Aiorosu here...
Like I care about that!
Justice, why don't you take it?
At my home, my python Guilty-kun is allowed to run loose, so...
It'll get eaten!
Then, Tsuyuri!
Frogskin leather bag...
Thats no good either...
Then I'll buy it!
Thank you!
Would you like some tea?
Nah, I wouldn't want to bother you.
My tea is said to be delicious, and is famous around my office.
Amazing!
Oh, Sora-chan, you're so cute! I love you!
Kaneru-chan's childlike and cute too!
Eh?  But I'm not a kid anymore!
Wait, "-chan"?
Kaneru-chan!
Ah.  Bears.
Aiorosu is over here...
No!
Buck-chan has-!
Ah, I'm really sorry.
Right now, I'll continue on.
Ah, this feeling...
Well then, I'll make some tea.
No, we'd really prefer not to bother you.
Don't leap out of your seat just yet - something really ribbiting is coming up next!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
Already at the halfway point,
I can hear everyone's disappointed voices.
If you're not voicing your disappointment, do it now.