Rider, look.
You scared, boy?
Yeah, I am.
Or to put it another way, in your terms,
my heart is dancing.
Now you're getting it.
The enemy is inside?
Berserker!
They're going to drink now?
What has become of your beloved chariot?
Oh, yeah...
I hate to admit it,
but Saber won it from me.
Did you forget my decision?
I believe I said I would
defeat you at full strength.
It is true that I am not fully equipped.
However,
because the Iskandar you face
tonight is not perfect,
he is beyond perfection.
Oh, I see.
It is true that you radiate
a more impressive aura than usual.
Apparently, you do believe
you have some chance.
King of Babylonia,
I have one last question,
the final one of our banquet.
I shall allow it.
Speak.
Hypothetically,
if we armed my Ionioi Hetairoi
with your Gate of Babylon,
it would be the strongest army on Earth.
And?
Will you not become my ally?
If we joined forces,
we could surely conquer even the stars.
You never fail to entertain me.
It's been ages since I've laughed so
much at one who was not a jester.
But I must decline.
I have named but one man friend,
and he is the only one I ever shall.
And there is no need for two kings.
A king who stands alone...
Then it is with the utmost respect
for your conviction that I challenge you.
I accept.
Show me what you're capable of,
King of Conquerors.
I deem you an adversary
worthy of my judgment.
Are you guys really friends?
I certainly can't bring myself to be unfriendly.
He may well be the last opponent
I shall ever face.
Don't give me that...
You can't die here.
I won't let you!
Have you forgotten my Command Spell?!
Right...
You're absolutely right.
Gather, my comrades!
Tonight, we take our place as the
greatest legend in history!
Our opponent is the mighty
King of Heroes,
a truly worthy foe.
Now my companions,
let us show the first Heroic Spirit
where our path of conquest leads!
Come, lord of conquest...
And I shall show you the
figure of a true king.
Why are you suffering so?
Because Berserker has...
to fight...
Why?
Because the priest said so.
The priest?
Yeah, he promised me...
That he'd give me the Holy Grail.
If I have the Grail, I can rescue you.
You're going to save me?
Yeah...
Remember, I promised...
that we'd all play together,
like we used to...
Then, I can see Mommy again?
Your mom...
Now!
Too shallow?
He can see it?
He knows how long this blade is.
Could he be a knight I once knew?
I ask this,
presuming you to be a skilled
knight of some renown.
If you face me knowing that
I am Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
then identify yourself,
as a knight's pride demands!
If you do not, you are nothing more
than a nameless assassin!
You...
N-No...
Arondight?
You can't be...
Arthur...
Sir...
Lancelot...
Why, my friend?
You were once first among knights
of the Round Table. So, why?
What made you into Berserker—
Lancelot?
Lancelot...
You saved your people,
but you never led them.
Because I never led you...
You are trapped by an ideal of a king
who exists for others, not himself.
My ideals...
My kingship...
Just a naïve little girl.
Did those reduce you to this?!
Arthur!
Lancelot...
Your dream of conquest united them.
I applaud your zeal.
But, warriors,
have you not realized the truth?
All dreams, by definition,
end when the dreamer wakes.
And thus,
it was inevitable that I would be
the one to bar your path.
King of Conquerors,
I shall wake you from your endless dream.
I shall see to it personally!
Get ready!
Now awaken, Ea!
We have prepared a worthy stage
for your splendor!
Behold the glory...
Enuma Elish!
Hang on, boy!
What...
That sword is
an anti-world Noble Phantasm that
can obliterate anything.
Rider...
I just remembered.
There was something I meant to ask you.
Huh?
Waver Velvet,
would you serve as my retainer?
You...
You are my king.
I will serve you, swearing fealty to you.
I want to follow where you go.
I want to share your dream!
Very well.
As king, it is my duty to
inspire others to dream.
And as retainer, it is your duty
to see my dream through,
and to pass tales down to future generations.
Live on, Waver.
Watch to the end, and then tell the story.
Tell them of your king,
of Iskandar's charge!
Now...
We go, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon.
It can never be reached,
and that is why you strive for it.
Tell them of conquest,
then make it happen.
For the men who watch from behind you!
Really, you always
have something up your sleeve, don't you?
Have you woken from your dream,
King of Conquerors?
Yeah.
I suppose so...
On this campaign,
my heart danced...
quite a bit...
Challenge me any time you wish,
King of Conquerors.
This world will remain my garden
until the end of time.
And so, I promise you,
you will never tire of it.
That sounds wonderful...
Ah...
My heartbeat itself
was the sound of Oceanus's waves...
Child, are you Rider's Master?
No.
I am his retainer...
So I see.
Well, child, if you are truly a loyal subject,
have you not a duty to
avenge your king's death?
If I fight you, I will die.
Obviously.
Then I cannot.
I was ordered to live.
I commend your loyalty!
Never diminish it.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in paths of
righteousness for his name's sake.
Even though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me;
Your rod and your staff—
they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in
the presence of my enemies;
you anoint my head with oil.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
Episode 23:
The Ocean at the End of the World
You would steal the Holy Grail from me?!
What are you doing, Saber?!
Such a pain...
No way!
It longs for life, for its own birth!
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
I knew you'd come.
Next Time:
The Final Command Spell