akogareteiru no yo
Oh, how I wish I could be
anata to scandal
Caught in an affair with you
itometai no kokoro
To take your heart for myself
ano ko yori mo hayaku
Before she gets a chance to
hito wa
Oh, why
nande nande
Do we, do we
nando
No matter
kizutsuitemo
How much it hurts us
koi ni
Keep falling
koi ni ochiru ikimono na no
Keep falling in love again and again
It's like, it's like milk tea
maru de maru de milk tea
Together, the two of us
betsu betsu no tokoro de
Born in different worlds
umareta futari
Like a sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet milk tea
amai amai no milk tea
Drink, drink it up right now
atsu atsu yo ima sugu
While it's still piping hot
kyun to nomihoshite
It's like, it's like milk tea
maru de maru de milk tea
The perfect blend of one and the other
zetsumyou na kagen ga
But you can't see that
wakaranai no ne
The perfect, perfect milk tea
toro torokeru no milk tea
At the end, the very end
saigo dake chotto dake
Just a little bitter
horori to nigai