“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
I'll kill that bastard who ordered them, Kida Masaomi!
Your eyes are the same as a man ready to run to his death.
Which Horada is "that Horada?"
I wanted to tell you what that person is thinking.
I came prepared to kill, too.
Nobody can deny me that!
You're ready to accept what we're about to see, right? No matter how bad it is?
Kida-kun!
Why?
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Masaomi...
Mikado?
Ryugamine-kun... Why?
You're right. This is a terrible sight to behold.
She's here again. The black rider!
Come on, crush them all into pieces!
Now! Fight back!
Hey, what gives?
What the hell is going on?
Yo.
K-K-Kadota!
Why you...!
If this is all your disguise consists of, you shouldn't have carelessly gathered all these people here.
Kadota-san... What in the world...
You see, Togusa reminded me that when Izumii got arrested,
he wasn't the only one who escaped.
There was also a guy named Horada who didn't get charged.
And then we got about thirty of our friends together,
put on yellow rags and blended in here.
Yumasaki and Karisawa would've stood out though, so we left them out.
We're never going to get any action, are we?
Too bad we stand out so much.
I honestly didn't even want to remember you.
You heartless scumbag.
Were you the one who broke Saki's legs?
N-N... No... I...
Were you the one who made Saki cry?
S-Shit... Ch-Chaka... Where's Chaka?
So it was you!
Damn it!
I really meant to split your head open with that crowbar.
Mikado and Anri, you guys aren't from this side of life.
There's no reason for you to see dead bodies.
That's all I was thinking.
Masaomi!
Masaomi! Masaomi... Hang in there!
Kida-kun!
Sonohara-san and Masaomi,
Celty-san told me everything about you.
I'm sorry. I... I didn't know anything.
Ryugamine-kun, I...
You don't have to say it. I think I have a good idea of what's going on.
So don't say it unless you have to.
If I had told you what I was so troubled and worried about,
maybe none of this would have happened.
Me too. I thought you were starting to avoid me,
and I was scared...
Masaomi...
It's my fault.
I couldn't bring myself to tell either of you who I was...
Sonohara-san...
I'm sorry. You two are the most important people in the world to me,
and you were always there with me...
You two suit each other well.
Masaomi...
Hey... If you're going to take me to the hospital,
can you do me a favor?
What?
Take me to Raira Integrated Hospital.
I have a girl waiting for me. Please.
Masaomi? Masaomi! Masaomi!
You guys are pathetic.
Kadota-san!
Seriously. I told you not to run away, but this isn't what I meant.
You've gone way overboard.
Don't tell me all those people are...
Yeah. Those people are all Dollars.
They have no color, so anything is possible.
You can say that they're gone, but since you can't see them anyway, then there's no way that they've truly vanished.
Hey! Horada's getting away!
This way, Horada-san.
That bastard!
I'll go after him. You make sure Kida-kun gets to the hospital.
Okay, got it.
The van's waiting for us outside.
Togusa, you're in charge!
I have some cleaning up to do.
I'll leave Kida to you guys.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Kadota-san, Higa isn't here!
Who cares!
S-S-She's here!
It's the black rider!
Shut up!
Horada-san, what are we gonna do now?
We're running away now!
We'll find someplace to hide, wait for things to cool down,
and then if Izumii-san gets out of jail, we'll give 'em back what for!
Horada-san, ahead. Ahead!
Ahead?
I-It's Shizuo! It's Hewajima Shizuo!
You mean he's alive?!
Why is a flag there?
Why is he still alive? How?
Horada-san!
Don't try to run!
Horada-san, get a grip!
T-The black rider!
Horada-san, calm down!
You ran a motorcycle cop off the road. You've got balls.
Don't mess with traffic cops, kid.
Horada and his gang were arrested.
Apparently they accused Hewajima Shizuo of damaging their car,
but the police didn't listen.
Take care.
Thank you very much.
Sonohara-san is...
There's no mistaking it. They took it.
Now we can finally get that reward from the Awakusu Club.
Yeah. I couldn't get my hands on the bullets, though.
That's okay, that's okay.
Anyway, it would've been really lucky if I could've used this to kill Shizu-chan.
So then he used me to inform Horada about Shizuo.
He could at least have shot him in the head or chest, maybe then he might have died.
It really is a shame.
That sounds about right, Mother.
Thank you, very much.
Now go home and resume your normal life.
You're Orihara Izaya-san, right?
Sonohara Anri-chan? Or should I call you Saika?
What do you want at this hour?
I'm going to cut you.
Why... Why have you done this?
I haven't done anything.
Oh, right. If you want to know why I did that,
it's because I like humans.
So I guess I wanted to see all the different facets of humanity.
And now, here's my question. Is what I just said true?
Or is it false?
If I can control you, I'll know.
By the way, what about you?
If you really want a peaceful, happy life,
shouldn't you kill everyone you know with that sword?
That is... That is wrong.
Dear me. In that case, if you won't choose between Mikado-kun and Masaomi-kun,
even though you obviously like them both,
can we really say that you have the right attitude?
Aren't you happy with the way things are now only because you think you can't love other people?
Since Saika will love those people in your place? How ridiculous.
Be quiet!
Hey. I don't want you to think too little of me.
Even I am no match for Shizu-chan if I fight fair.
Well, they shouldn't have given me this.
I'll tell you now, I'm not going to shoot you.
Who should we go with?
That couple walking over there?
You wouldn't be hurt if I did that, because you can't love people.
I've known about Higa being one of the slasher incident victims for a long time.
Why do you think I had him get me this gun?
It was for you.
Because I wanted to declare war on you.
I also deeply love humans. I'd never hand over a human like I would a sword.
Because humans belong to me.
However, I don't want Shizu-chan, so you can have him.
I'll be praying that your fish-filleting goes swiftly,
so good luck. See ya!
You're late.
What's with your face? What happened?
I took a pretty good punch just now.
Hey!
Simon?
Hey, do you mind if I get some things off my chest?
You're so cowardly it's ridiculous.
Yeah... I think I'm cowardly too, honestly.
However, Simon,
I like my cowardice.
Masaomi has a girlfriend. That girl made a phone call to our shop.
She told us about you, and what's happening now,
and everything else.
Saki?
Why would Saki...
She truly is in love with Masaomi.
Looks like she's given up on you.
I see... so Saki...
Hey, Izaya...
Don't go destroying the city.
Simon, it's just that I love humans so much.
Don't try to fool me with that kind of logic.
You just don't want to lose to Shizuo, do you?
You have an obsession with him, don't you?
Your thoughts,
are easier to read by other people than you think.
Simon,
your Russian speech is much different from when you speak Japanese.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What?
Was it you who told Horada about Mikado-kun?
What do you think?
How scary. You're still holding that grudge.
Seriously... There are tons of people who I can predict perfectly,
and then there are people like Simon and Shizuo, who overturn those predictions.
That's why I will never stop love, love, loving humans!
That's right! That's why I can keep doing this crappy job.
It's so much fun that I could vomit.
How many times must I tell you?
The human race probably really hates you.
Really, now?
Saki...
I know.
You never came for me, Masaomi.
You were calling Izaya-san the whole time, over and over.
Laughing, Izaya-san showed me his call records.
But there's nothing to worry about.
Even if you had come, things wouldn't be much different for me.
Stop it...
So the fact that you didn't get hurt is the most important thing.
Let's break up!
Let's break up...
I must be a terrible person.
What made Saki think I was so cool?
The fact that you're so weird, yet so nice.
How long have you been there?
A while. Karisawa and the others told me about it... everything.
You're an idiot. You're a real idiot, Masaomi.
I've known that for a long time.
You know what? I want to apologize.
I let those people kidnap me on purpose.
Izaya-san told me it'd all be over if I did that.
So that night, I... I went to their hangout spot by myself.
Then, Izaya-san started giving out information...
I knew that.
Izaya also told you...
to pretend you couldn't walk, to keep me in check.
I bet he wanted to make me his pawn.
Masaomi...
I'm psychic, you know.
I've gone against Izaya's words for the first time.
I feel like I can finally tell you this now.
I couldn't save you. I'm sorry.
However, I still love you, Saki.
So please, don't break up with me.
Hey.
You are an idiot after all, Masaomi.
A real idiot.
I can't help it.
Can't you turn a blind eye to one of my faults?
If you know it's true, then fix it.
Let's fix it together.
A few days later, Masaomi disappeared, together with Mikajima Saki.
They sent letters to the school to drop out, and then they were gone.
Our lives, with the three of us together, had changed.
However, the town didn't change at all.
Russian sushi!
Him... or them...
or them... or him...
or him.
It's peaceful.
Yeah. It seems there was some internal division among the remaining Blue Squares,
so the Kokinzoku have calmed down as a whole.
Is that so?
Then there's no worry about Mikado and Anri-chan being targeted anymore.
Wai– What? What's with the sudden change of clothes?
It's so provocative...
I'm gonna go take a shower and get the bedsheets ready...
What's wrong?
It's just, you usually jab me in the ribs
or pinch my cheeks when I say something like that.
I'm really provoking you.
Or them, either.
Will the everyday lives we lost ever come back?
I wonder if I really loved Kida-kun.
I wonder if that's why I miss him so much.
However, I'll never know.
I never know that kind of thing.
There's one thing I've learned.
The Dollars are the city. All kinds of people come, and go.
They aren't dyed in one color. Something is always happening.
Someone is always forming hatred, love, or friendship toward someone else,
or just passing them by.
Just as the city will keep existing as long as there are people,
so will the Dollars, regardless of anybody's intentions.
Good evening.
Evening.
Oh, there's a new person here.
Hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Bacula.
Kanra-san invited me here.
I met him online, did you too, Bacula-san?
No, we know each other in real life.
We're basically friends from work! Outwardly, that is.
When will you die, Kanra-san?
That's a stronger comeback than I thought!
That's terrible.
I'm sorry,
Kanra-san is so irritating,
I just,
Excuse me, Bacula-san.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong here.
Masaomi?
Is this Masaomi?
I'd be happy if you could answer this.
You know me in real life, so tell everyone how charming I am.
Three points.
If I gave Kanra-san a score,
In other words, I'm so beautiful you can't explain it?
I mean elementary school kids shouldn't see you because they wouldn't be able to handle you.
Oh, excuse me,
I have to call it a day here.
Okay.
Thanks for coming!
Goodnight.
Wait, Bacula-san!
Come back sometime!
We'll give you a nice welcome!
I'll be back. See you!
G'night.
Good night!
A place to call home. The everyday lives we've lost.
Both of them still existed on the Internet.
He's coming back.
Masaomi is going to come back.
When he does, I should complain.
I should get really mad, even if I end up laughing.
We'll both do it.
Even now, when I think about it, it's weird,
but I experienced something that would change my life...
Something that was actually completely normal,
but still very, very strange... and yet could happen anywhere...
in this town called Ikebukuro.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.