The head of the Dollars is your beloved
best friend, Ryuugamine Mikado-kun.
Take me to that meeting.
You want a fight, you'll get one.
If there's a group, within the Dollars,
working with the Black Rider,
and they're attacking the Yellow Scarves...
It'll be a real gang war.
We'll eliminate you from reality!
We, the Yellow Scarves!
Young Men Arrested for Vandalism
I heard it was the Dollars.
They took my money!
Same here!
The Dollars made me buy an expensive ring!
I didn't stop then.
Dollars
Why didn't I...?
Everything
Covered in Fog
Masaomi... Did he say anything?
Kida?
He hasn't come by.
I don't suspect you.
You didn't tell anyone I was
part of the Dollars, right?
Right.
You shouldn't feel responsible.
I'm quitting the Dollars.
We ain't invisible anymore...
I see...
I was thinking. Are you part of the Dollars-
No!
OK.
That day, he said...
But once you're on the other side,
three days of that, and it's the new normal.
If you really want to escape the everyday,
you must constantly evolve.
I decided I'd evolve.
But...
The Sky Has Fallen
This is the result.
Now connecting you to a voice
answering service.
Ryuugamine Mikado
So, you didn't hear me?
I told you, no little fights.
But-
I did say that, didn't I?
G-General!
You're OK with this?
We're sure the Headless Rider
belongs to the Dollars!
We're just gonna do nothing and
let them mess with us?!
And if we keep this up,
the Dollars leader might show himself.
Ryuugamine Mikado
I'll look into the leader
of the Dollars myself.
Until we know for sure, you stay put.
Got it?
Either way, it's too late to stop things.
<Setton> I see.
I know you're worried,
but there's no reason to be concerned.
Even if you hadn't done anything,
this still might have happened.
Really?
Fights like that happen a lot in this town.
It isn't anyone's fault that someone
from your school was attacked.
So don't worry about it.
You're with the Dollars, right?
Aren't you?
<Setton> Got it?
Then I'll drop out of private message mode.
OK?
<Saika>
Hey! Are you gonna smack into me
without saying anything?
Huh?
Heiwajima...
Shizu-
Huh?
-o...
Huh?!
Man, the weather's sure nice today!
Hey, Shizuo.
Yo.
I hear he's part of the Dollars.
He was at the meeting six months ago.
Idiot!
You don't mess with Heiwajima Shizuo
or the black dude at Russia Sushi.
Not unless you want to die.
Yo.
Hi.
You alone?
Kida's not with you?
Did something happen with Masaomi?
No.
It's dangerous to be out alone.
A Raira student got attacked.
You knew him?
I see.
Thank you.
Since the Slasher attacks,
things have been crazy.
I heard the Yellow Scarves are
going after the Dollars.
The Dollars haven't reciprocated.
The boss hasn't given any orders.
A lot of people seem unhappy with that.
Those are just rumors, though.
Are you with the Dollars, Kadota-san?
Why do you ask?
I was wondering if it's really OK
for the Dollars to exist.
Are they really needed?
I dunno.
I can't go to Ikebukuro.
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of
the Dollars, right?
I'm quitting the Dollars!
The Slasher's part of
the Dollars, right?
We're just gonna let the
Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
We're just gonna let the
Yellow Scarves do this to us?
We should hit back!
What the hell is
our leader doing?
Isn't a leader for
times like these?
I don't think violence is the answer.
Shouldn't we wait for things to calm down?
Sending
I got an e-mail just now!
Who the heck?
Is it the leader?
He wants us to
do nothing?
Then go work things out
with the Yellow Scarves!
He wants us to
do nothing?
Then go work things out
with the Yellow Scarves!
Have fun!
And now Mikado...
And at a time like this...
I see.
You were having a private messaging
session with Saika, Sonohara Anri-chan.
But no matter how much you typed,
you got no response.
You thought that, all things considered,
she must be really depressed.
But...
<Saika> But yeah...
Are there lots of fights?
You think so?
This town's in big trouble.
What should I do?
You can't reach her cell?
<Kanra> Um,
you know...
You're using the PM
mode wrong, Saika-san.
She's got the power off.
<Kanra> You talking
about Ikebukuro?
It's really bad.
People are getting
hurt every day.
What's wrong with Kanra?
He's just scaring her!
<Saika> Really?
<Kanra> That's what
the Yellow Scarves
think, anyway.
They won't be happy
till they've hit
the Dollar's leader,
and hit him hard.
<Saika> Really?
<Kanra> That's what
the Yellow Scarves
think, anyway.
They won't be happy
till they've hit
the Dollar's leader,
and hit him hard.
<Saika> Sorry.
I've gotta go.
Anri-chan was the girl at Sonoharadou, right?
Yeah.
The antiques store where
my dad sold Saika...
So the leader of the Dollars is a classmate,
and she has friends in the
Yellow Scarves, too.
Anri-chan doesn't know that
Mikado leads the Dollars.
The three of them are friends,
and none of them knows about the others.
I think so.
I don't know the details, either.
I'm sorry.
Please don't ask anything.
A love triangle, indeed.
So what will you do?
I can't say anything if Anri-chan doesn't.
I just have to pray they'll be OK.
<Kanra> Kyaho!
It's Kanra-chan!
Hey, no one's here!
Ya'll aren't enjoying yourselves
without me, are you?
Hmph!
But it's OK!
I'm having a great time, too!
The game's getting good, so I'm out!
Bye-bye-be!
<Kanra-san has left the channel>
<There is no one in the channel>
It's been several days.
I haven't looked at the
Dollars site since then.
Things keep getting worse in the city.
But nothing's changed in my life here.
Takiguchi-kun left the hospital.
I can be at peace here.
This is my everyday life.
But...
Kida already went home.
Thanks for coming to see me.
Um...
I'll be splitting off here.
I see.
OK.
See you tomorrow.
You're part of the Dollars, right?
N-No!
Of course you are!
Run now.
What are you doing?
Are you betraying us?
Mother told us to.
Mother told us to stop you.
If the Yellow Scarves are about to attack
the Dollars, please stop them.
Yes. Understood,
Mother.
Thank you.
I'm counting on you.
It's my fault.
It's my fault Kida-kun...
Can anyone in the Yellow
Scarves hear my voice?
Anyone?
I have to do something.
I have to do something...
Hello?
Move the queen to C-Ke-6.
Black to G-6.
Good, good.
This is getting good.
Out with it!
I-I don't know what you're
talking about. Honestly...
I can't hear you.
You can't remember?
Screw you!
It's true! I swear!
That's enough.
But we need to make an example...
You really don't remember anything?
Next thing I knew, everyone was mad...
It's true!
It's true...
Hypnosis or something?
You're getting sleepy... Very sleepy!
Like that?
Actually, it may be that.
'Cause... Yeah.
The Dollars have a Headless Rider.
Why wouldn't they have a hypnotist?
Um...
What?
Yes, sir.
I saw them with a girl.
A girl?
Ah, come to think of it...
So did I.
I think they only started acting crazy
after they saw the girl.
What kind of girl?
She was wearing a Raira uniform, glasses,
and I think she had big breasts.
The girl with the Headless
Rider had glasses, too.
No, it's impossible.
She had big tits, too.
I'm amazed you noticed
that, during the fight.
OK!
We'll catch her and-
No!
I told you. No fights!
But if we grab her-
The rest of you got it, right?
No one does anything till I say so.
It can't be.
It can't be...
'Cause...
'Cause she...
Anri...
Really?
Then I'll show you my notes.
They'd be useless!
Huh? What is it?
Something's wrong?
I know.
Masaomi and Sonohara-san are gone.
When you're alone, you remember
how big this town really is.
The first time I was here,
I remember wanting to go home.
But when Masaomi took me around,
I met lots of people,
and I experienced lots of things.
And it felt like the town was mine.
But I'm sure some of them
belong to the Dollars.
Ryuugamine-kun?
Good timing!
Hey, we'd like to talk to you.
U-Um, Harima-san?
What did you want to talk to me about?
Oh, yeah.
About Anri-chan.
What's going on with her?
What do you mean...
You haven't noticed?
Noticed what?
She's been worried about something.
I was concerned about her, so I asked,
and she insisted she was fine.
She's always been like that.
I hadn't noticed at all...
I was worried.
So I was wondering if you'd heard anything.
No, I haven't heard anything.
OK, then.
I'll ask for you.
OK!
If you learn anything, let me know.
All right.
That's all.
Let's go, Seiji-san!
Ryuugamine.
You like Sonohara, don't you?
Wh-What now?
Don't try to fool me.
I can tell just by looking.
If you really do love her, don't look away,
no matter what happens.
No matter what you see,
no matter what you learn about her,
don't look away.
Once you've got her in your embrace,
don't let go.
Once you decide you love someone,
that's your responsibility.
Goodbye.
I'll fulfill my responsibility to love you, too!
Yagiri-kun's a weird guy.
But I thought he was kind of cool.
Damn, what's with that bastard?
Stupid little kid, acting all tough...
It's kind of weird, isn't it?
Horada-san!
Over there.
A Raira uniform...
Glasses...
No matter what I learn,
no matter what I see, don't look away.
Responsibility...
I didn't notice she was worried
about something.
Masaomi... Did Masaomi notice?
I was probably so worried about
my own problems, I didn't notice.
Not about Sonohara-san or the Dollars.
What do I know about the Dollars?
Why didn't I quit the Dollars then?
I'm quitting the Dollars.
People, stop writing that.
I'll kill the Yellow Scarves.
Do something, leader.
Who is the leader, anyway?
Do you think the Dollars should exist?
There's no need for them anymore.
I'm quitting, I said.
Stop writing that.
I don't want them to disappear.
I want the leader to do something.
He created the Dollars,
so he should take responsibility.
What does that mean?
There's no hierarchy. Everyone's free.
That's what the Dollars are, right?
Don't rely on the boss whenever
things get bad.
I remember seeing a post like this once,
"Why don't we make the
Dollars a good group?"
"There are some bad members,
but don't worry about them."
Why don't we make the Dollars a good group?
Like, maybe do enough good things to negate
the bad impressions those others leave?
Why don't we make the Dollars a good group?
Like, maybe do enough good things to negate
the bad impressions those others leave?
The leader's got nothing to do with it.
That's right. The Dollars don't
belong to one person.
It's all of ours!
Losers.
We should just do what we can.
Die.
Agreed! Let's all protect the city
from the Yellow Scarves!
We all make rounds or something?
We're invisible. They don't
know who we are...
That's right.
That's right!
Back then, too...
A girl's being attacked
by the Yellow Scarves.
Where?
In front of Veloce.
They're taking her
somewhere.
Where?
In front of Veloce.
They're taking her
somewhere.
What kind of girl?
I think it's a Raira uniform?
She has a
Raira uniform and glasses.
Huge knockers.
I think that's a Raira uniform...
Raira... Glasses... Knockers...
She has a Raira uniform and glasses.
And huge knockers.
It can't be!
Sonohara-san...
The queen's been surrounded by black.
No way...
It can't be. It just can't...
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Declaration of
Disbandment
Is this a dream?
It wasn't. His hands told me so.
When you realize something's important, why's it already gone?
Next time:
Declaration of Disbandment