Where do waves come from?
Hm?
How do dolphins jump so high?
Huh?
Why is the ocean blue?
Why is that, Brother?
You got me!
Those are tough questions.
Bit by the curiosity bug, eh?
Curiosity?
The sea gives birth to many things.
It can give the admiration to say "How pretty,"
or the fear to make us shout "Eek!"
And you've finally got the hunger to learn all about it.
If you truly want to know, thinking alone isn't enough.
You must jump into the sea...
to find the answer yourself.
Okay!
Oh my.
All right, wait for Dad!
Looking back, that was the beginning of my dream.
I see.
You dream of learning about
the sea through its creatures.
Guess that's been inside you since long before we met.
But it's thanks to you that I finally took notice of it.
Have you told your family?
No...
not yet.
I see...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Lady Dyspear, the key to beauty is naught...
but eye makeup!
Please allow me to make yo—
You failed.
Shut, you are a failure.
Beauty, you say?
We've no need for it.
How foolish...
How did you become such a disappointment?
I may as well end it—
O-One more chance!
I beg you, give me one more chance!
I swear that I shall defeat the Precures!
I will stake my life on it!
One chance.
There will not be another.
Right!
A Surging Confession!
Minami's Deep Blue Dream!
Minami!
You got a letter!
Thank you.
Who's it from?
It's from my mother!
Dear Minami, spend your Christmas with cheer.
It's a Christmas card!
Your mom's got some good taste!
It's splendid!
Minami?
You looked kinda sad for a second.
Are you worried about something again?
Not quite.
Dear Minami, spend your Christmas with cheer.
I just haven't told my parents about my new dream...
I see...
So, they still think you're going to work with them?
Well, it's kinda hard to admit.
I plan to tell them after the new year, but...
But?
I'm so ashamed...
I'm grateful to them for allowing me to enroll here and learn all that I have...
yet I must betray their hopes...
But I'll manage! I prepared myself for this the moment I settled on my new dream.
Okay!
Let's get pumped!
You gotta come out swingin', right?
If we wanna get Minami ready,
we need to hit up the Christmas party...
and have a ball!
Yeah!
Are you ready, everyone?
Are you hype?!
Yeah!
Then let's get this Christmas party started!
Okay!
A Christmas tree!
Merry Christmas!
Got it!
Keep 'em comin', girls!
Got it, got it, got....
Guwaaaagh!
Ranko's so talented!
A real triple threat.
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Nanase's good at ventriloquism!
We love you, Perf!
Redaromaroma bluaromaroma yellowromaroma!
The parrot can do tongue twisters!
N-Not bad, amateur...
Next up is the Christmas-exclusive musical group made of our academy's very own all-stars!
Give it up for...
La Princesse!
0Christmas0
0Hey!0
0Merry Merry Christmas0
0If you decorate the tree with ornaments of smiles0
0and light the candles with the flame of your dreams0
0Santa and his reindeer will come from afar0
0to dance into your chimney tonight0
0Ring a bell with courage and hope0
0to let happiness ring around the world0
0Hey!0
0Joyful, colorful, Christmas0
0Splendid, merry, and filled with cheer0
0Hey!0
0Joyful, colorful, Christmas0
0Connect your hearts on this holy night in love and peace0
They loved it!
This is the funnest party ever!
And the magnificence of Minami's performance simply cannot be overstated!
I agree!
You're getting some new fans!
Seeing everyone happy made it worth the effort.
Shirogane, dorm mother.
Miss Kaidou, you have a call from your mother.
Hello, Mother?
Ah, Minami?
Yes, thank you for the splendid card.
Sorry to bother you with a call as well,
but I wanted to tell you Merry Christmas myself.
Minami, is something wrong?
No, nothing!
Are you sure? You haven't caught a cold?
You always seem to catch one every winter...
When I was a little girl, maybe.
Oh, they sound merry.
We're having a Christmas party.
Oh, I'm sorry for pulling you away from it!
Not at all...
But I'm happy to hear you're having fun.
Well, take care, Minami. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas...
Minami?
What happened?
It's nothing.
You don't look like it's nothing.
My mother... is too kind...
You must love your parents.
That's why you don't want to let them down.
But your loved ones would want to know your true feelings, would they not?
Girls...
Especially if it's important!
At this point, we should go tell them right away!
If you still have to worry...
we'll be right there with you.
Haruka...
This is it...
Naught but action!
What'd your brother say?
He said he'd be right over!
Great!
I'll go get prepared.
What?
It must be...
Shut!
I see you're alone, Cure Mermaid.
Today's naught but your doom!
Of all the times...
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
Now...
do prepare yourself!
I've been prepared!
Get her!
Dystroyvil!
I'm in...
I'm in... Hope Kingdom?!
The sea...
Dystroyvil!
There's naught but to pick you off one by one!
Cure Mermaid, I'll begin with you!
Dystroyvil!
This is it!
Royal Majesty!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
What?!
Girls!
Sorry we're late!
We're glad you're okay!
How did you follow me here?!
Girls, stay on your guard!
Your doing?
No matter!
There's naught but to crush you all!
Attack!
Dystroyviiiiiiil!
Dystrooooy... viiiiil....
It's polluting the sea...
With despair! You'll all drown in this sea of despair!
Dystroy...
Ice!
Vil!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
I won't stop...
The sea gave birth to my passion, my curiosity, and my dream!
It matters not what the sea gave birth to!
The dream you bear is naught but to crumble!
No matter how you girls may struggle, you are naught but to end in despair!
The time may come when I'll be awash with despair and hardship...
But even still...
Dystroy!
What?!
The sea will always give me hope!
I know the currents will be rough, but I have a dream to pursue!
Neither the sea nor my heart will be polluted with despair!
Coral!
Rage, O coral!
Precure!
Coral Maelstrom!
D-Dystroyvil!
Gah, what are you doing?!
Dystroy... vil!
You're naught but to go forth and destroy!
I am the Princess of the Sea, Cure Mermaid!
Those who pollute the sea or our dreams...
Dystroy!
...shall be brought to justice!
Dystroyvil...
Now!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
That was my last chance!
Cure Mermaid, awaken the Castle of the Sea!
Right!
Flow with lucidity, O great seas!
So this must be...
the true seas of Hope Kingdom!
Yes!
You look like a weight's off your shoulders.
Huh?
So something did happen back then.
You noticed?
Come on, I am your brother.
I was planning to hear you out on whatever you were concerned over...
but it looked like there was no need.
No.
Good luck.
Thanks.
And I thought it was cold before...
Snow, eh?
I do hope Minami doesn't catch a cold...
Didn't you just talk to her on the phone?
I did, but you know...
Mother! Father!
Minami!
Wataru!
What's the matter?
You could have called us if you were coming!
It's a Christmas surprise!
Well now!
In that case, we're glad to have you.
Minami, thanks for coming.
I... came tonight because I have something I simply must tell you.
And that is?
I'm sorry!
I can't work with the Kaidou family!
I can't live up to the hopes you have for me!
I have another career... another dream I want to pursue!
Congratulations.
The time has come for you to dive into the big blue sea.
Bravo!
You came all this way to tell us?
Thank you.
You're... not mad?
Of course not.
But I'd been meaning to work with the Kaidou family this whole time,
yet now I'm turning it away so selfishly...
What's selfish about that?
Though to be honest, I'm a bit relieved to see you put yourself first for once.
You've always been such a kind child.
So kind that you'd always put our needs above yours.
And now, you've finally found something you want to do.
I'm so proud!
Mother...
Just like how things are born from the sea,
your dream was born from you.
Minami, follow the path you believe in.
Your happiness is our happiness.
Father...
Oh dear, let's not soil that beautiful face.
Everyone, why not continue this discussion over dinner?
I have a reservation at a nice restaurant nearby.
You think of everything!
Come, Minami. Let us hear all about your new dream.
Certainly!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
It's snowing!
Huh? Towa, what are you making?
A snow castle!
Well, lemme help!
Me too!
Oh no!
It's Shut?!
No, we can't let him destroy the castle!
You may take great pains for your beauty, Shut, but at this moment, you are unsightly!
Go! Princess Precure:
Beautiful?!
The Wandering Shut and the Castle of Ice!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Osaka Prefecture - Ai (Age 9)
Gifu Prefecture - Yuna (Age 6)