The treacherous sunset wipes away those annoying sweat drops.
As if it wanted to tear it apart,
the machine roars as if it's singing a song.
Selty
Sturluson
The quiet fairy is over here.
Yagiri
Seiji
Atonement is a piece of a broken love.
Yagiri
Namie
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Heiwajima Shizuo
Over the valley of buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't be meaningless.
Erika
Karisawa
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Yumasaki
Walker
Kyohei
Kadota
Coming out of the darkness!
As long as you feel it now,
Togusa
Saburo
you'll see that dream isn't meaningless.
There's surely something only we can see.
Mikado
Ryuugamine
Something that no one will snatch away from us.
Masaomi
Kida
The fact that this aim isn't meaningless!
Anri
Sonohara
It's more amazing than Kamisakuramachi-Ginza.
I don't really know too many details myself, so don't take everything I say on the matter seriously,
but there are lots of other dangerous people around.
Be careful.
By the way, I saw that black bike today.
This is our first big target in a while. A teenage girl!
Thank God for that informant.
At that time, my body began to shake.
The sun rises, yeah!
Brezhnev
Simon
Over the horizon, oh!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
that light won't be meaningless.
Is the "reality" you're seeing... truly "reality"?
The scenery you see every time always remains the same.
Congratulations, on your acceptance to your new school, everyone.
Japan currently faces many gloomy issues.
Such as the birthrate declining, on top of other things that are a cause for concern,
but when I look at all of you in attendance today,
it truly feels to me that all of you will lead Japan toward a bright future.
It really lifts my spirits.
Undoubtedly, today is a special day for you all.
But I also realize, as I stand here,
Don't you believe that today is just a day like any other?
that today is a special day for the teachers, as well.
I am Ry-Ryuugamine Mikado.
A reserved boy who has just arrived in Tokyo...
I am Sonohara Anri.
Pleased to meet you all.
Along with a girl who seems a little as if her mind is somewhere else.
I'm Kida Masaomi!
I may seem mature,
but inside I'm just a fragile little fifteen-year old, just like the rest of you!
A happy boy who's always off in his own world...
I am Kamichika Rio.
Pleased to meet you.
Here's a girl who has another side to her.
It's common to have people like these around you.
Umm... Harima?
Harima Mika? Is she absent?
Absent...
This is the typical scene you all have seen before.
Late on the first day?
We were just taking care of introductions.
Introduce yourself, right there.
I'm Yagiri Seiji.
Pleased to meet you.
Although, there are times where something causes reality to show you another side of it.
Then, Yagiri... please have a seat.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I don't think I'll be able to come to school for a while.
No, I don't think I'll ever be coming back.
Huh?
That's all I came here to say.
Pardon the intrusion.
Hey, Yagiri, what do you mean by...?
It's just as I said.
This is a very important matter to me.
I don't have any more time to mess around with you all.
I'll excuse myself.
Hey, Yagiri, hold on.
Hold on!
An event, that disrupts the peaceful scenery and eventually throws everything into disarray,
makes you question what you'll do next.
And here, there's also a girl who has been through one of these, "events".
Two days ago, she actually should have died.
Highly
Unpredictable
The girl was born in a normal household.
She lived a life free of worries or hardships.
But when she started middle school,
an envelope arrived at her home, suddenly and without warning.
: : : Nakura's Profile : : :
Nickname
Nakura
Everything sucks,
I just want to
vanish without a trace.
Nickname
Nakura
Everything sucks,
I just want to
vanish without a trace.
Nickname
Nakura
Everything sucks,
I just want to
vanish without a trace.
Region:
Nakura
Everything sucks,
I just want to
vanish without a trace.
Region:
Tokyo
What was in it?
A photo.
It shows that my father is having an affair.
He was with another woman.
There was also a letter that said something like,
"Do you actually think this should be forgiven?"
It was probably sent by someone who knew the woman.
What your father did was terrible,
but what the other person did was terrible, too.
I didn't know what to do,
so I just decided to hide the pictures for the time being.
Ever since then, that normal and peaceful scenery...
began to disgust me.
It sounds like you had it rough.
What's the matter, Rio?
I was only able to put up with it for about six months.
I figured that things would be better if I brought everything out into the open.
If you don't want to talk about it, you don't have to force yourself.
There are some things I can't tell others about either.
I'm fine.
I want you to know.
I couldn't believe that I mistook my cell phone for the remote control!
After all of that... nothing changed.
I don't know if my mother chose not to talk about it,
or if they worked things out in private.
My father's boring jokes, and the extremely sweet taste of my mother's stew...
Not one thing changed at all.
I figured, maybe I should just disappear...
Lately, that's all that's been on my mind.
In a way, I feel the same way.
Although, I'm not as far gone as you are, Magenta-san.
What happened?
This person I was dating...
ended up leaving me for my father.
That's so cruel.
The one who I can never bring myself to forgive is my mother.
What did she say?
She said it happens all the time,
and since we have to keep up appearances... not to make such a big deal about it.
There wasn't even one utterance of how she felt.
So the way I saw it... she was putting our family's reputation above me.
Then again... I don't know... Maybe she was just looking out for my well-being in the future.
I don't think so.
Is that so...?
She doesn't really care about you, Nakura-san!
She probably only cares about herself-
Dinner's ready.
OK.
Magenta-san, would you like to disappear with me?
If we died together, maybe they'll understand...
exactly what it was they should have treasured the most.
When I look back on it now... it was a foolish choice.
But in the end, she felt that this is what needed to be done.
She felt the strength of Nakura's words.
She wanted to see the face of the person who had the same views and feelings as she did.
Even if the man were lying to her, she had nothing left to lose...
or so she thought.
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes.
Oh, are you Nakura-san?
From the moment she saw his face, she thought that this man wasn't Nakura.
Yet, she went with him because she wouldn't be able to forgive herself if she ran away.
So when it happened...
Hey.
Hello.
Are we all set?
There's no one around.
Well then... Sorry for tricking you!
Shock, resilience, regret... All of these emotions passed through her mind at the time.
Yet, right before she lost consciousness, she convinced herself that this was her fate.
After all that's taken place... why should she care about what becomes of her now?
She was just going to vanish without a trace.
However...
There is someone here.
Even while she was unconscious the world still continued moving.
Even though the job doesn't seem like it'll be too difficult...
You should still be careful.
Her feelings, her will, her emotions... To her, none of these things held any meaning.
I just can't do it. I just can't seem to gather the money.
I'm not saying I won't give you the money eventually!
Although, if anything happens to me...
Shiki-san, of the Awakusa Group, wouldn't be too happy about it...
Old man!
I don't have time.
I'm not busy, or anything,
but I'm only gonna be able to waste around another two and a half minutes of my life on you!
Another guy you shouldn't make an enemy out of is...
Yo.
I'm sure a skilled transporter like yourself doesn't need someone like me to tell you how to do things, but...
you don't need to do anything more than what was requested.
Just rough 'em up a little bit.
Well then, I'm counting on you!
The world was still turning.
Things began to move in a different direction... away from the fate that the girl believed would take place.
Hey.
Wh-What the fuck  are you?!
Are you OK?
The text said, "I've been asked to bring you to a certain place."
The bike ran without a sound. Though every so often, it let out a neigh like a horse.
It was a surreal feeling.
But the body that she clutched onto confirmed that this was reality.
The girl thought about the warmth she was feeling at this moment.
What were they thinking, what did they know, and how did they live their life?
When this person looks at her, what did they see?
Someone is waiting
for you on the rooftop.
Understood.
Here's where my job
ends.
Magenta-san.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Nakura.
Are you really Nakura-san?
I'm the Nakura who wants to disappear.
Nice to meet you... Were you the person who saved me?
Yes, that was me.
Thank you very much.
Were you scared?
Yes.
Sounds like you had it pretty rough, huh?
Yes... But why do you know that?
I know because the man who arranged to have you kidnapped was me.
I also arranged to have you rescued. It was all me.
What do you mean?
You were seeking death, yet you got kidnapped instead.
You felt scared and a bit frustrated because you still clung on to the hope of surviving, despite the fact that you had decided to die.
Yet, in the end, you didn't resist even though you wanted to, because that would've contradicted your previous intentions of dying,
so you convinced yourself that this was fate and there was nothing more that you could do...
But, now that you know you've been rescued, you feel relieved.
In the end, I just wanted to see your face.
To put things simply...
I just wanted to see that utterly speechless look on your face when you realized that someone saw right through you.
Why?
Let's see...
To you this would sound a bit philosophical, but...
If I were to try to give you a reason for it...
It would have to be that I just love humans.
Humans are so appealing and interesting. I just can't help myself.
Oh, and just because I like humans, it doesn't mean that I like you personally.
That's important to note.
Was everything a lie?
Do you finally understand the position you're in?
Come.
Some people have jumped from here before.
Though, I wouldn't really say this place is a well known suicide spot...
it is high enough that jumping would mean certain death.
Here, look at that stain down there.
You... think of yourself as someone special, don't you?
There's no way that'll happen.
Everyone's the same.
There's simply no one out there who can just lead an honest life.
You've got one or two secrets, right?
Have you ever wondered why your parents are no good compared to you?
That's...
Allow me to summarize things for you.
I think everyone who cheats or knows someone who's cheating,
will just keep laughing at boring jokes and continue to eat the overly sweet food, don't you think?
Look.
No matter what worries they had, all that remains are the bloodstains on the concrete, now.
Stains. Indifferent, all of them, without exception,
returned to God as equals...
Want me to let go?
See?
Well, this was good.
I'm thankful that I got the chance to see your ugly feelings today.
I'm actually just interested in the things that are involved in your worrying.
I'm not interested in your worries themselves.
By the way, it was fairly boring since you did everything I expected you to do.
Ultimately, I knew that you never intended to die.
Well, see ya.
It's been fun, Magenta-san.
She hesitated for that brief moment.
Would she be able to hurt him by killing herself?
Then she thought... that maybe she may have just been waiting for an opportunity.
For those words, that just so happened to come from a man like that...
Without her knowing... something happened.
Um...
Why?
Because the world isn't
as terrible as you think.
Again, she does something uncalled for.
The girl thought of her mother and father.
Her father and his mistress, and about her parents' relationship...
She thought about how each of them had a part to their lives that she didn't know about.
About how she didn't know if they were truly as evil, selfish, and hating as she previously believed.
About how she didn't know if they were just hiding behind their compromises and weaknesses.
As she was making her way home, she thought about forgiving them.
Ever since that day... the world had a different look to it.
Every person has their own emotions,
and single person has their own secrets.
She realized that of course, this was nothing out of the ordinary.
Where do you wanna go?
I'll take you wherever you wanna go, so today it's your treat.
Let me see... Well, how about a bookstore?
There are a lot of bookstores. What are you gonna buy?
You could find people like them anywhere,
Um, some manga to read in my spare time.
and yet, she was sure that they had secrets of their own.
Feelings that they can never discuss with anyone.
Please wait.
Yagiri-kun, what really happened?
I don't know what you're talking about.
B-But you cut class on the first day...
I said, I don't know what you're talking about!
Wait!
Um...
Is something wrong?
I wonder what's going on with her?
I'm such a playboy...
That kid in the glasses is in love with me.
She's probably just nervous about the dangerous and risky days ahead.
Can you put that in Japanese?
Him, too...
And her, too...
What they see may not be reality.
The girl thought to herself that maybe she'll be able to repeat those words to someone else,
"Because the world isn't as terrible as you think."
I didn't hear that you had become a hero of justice.
I believe I entrusted the job to a skilled transporter.
Are you the one responsible
for the previous kid who
jumped off of there too?
Are you the one responsible
for the previous kid who
jumped off of there too?
Are you the one responsible
for the previous kid who
jumped off of there too?
Are you the one responsible
for the previous kid who
jumped off of there too?
No way. The informant, Orihara Izaya, isn't that evil.
Then again, I'm not enough of a humanitarian to stop someone who wants to die, though.
It's been fun, Ms. Skilled Transporter.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our warm bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
I hear the voice of your wonderful heart perfectly.
We're no longer kids, but love is still right here.
It's okay to try to cry. It's okay to try to depend on me.
It was then that I decided to take away your pain.
I'm here
Wherever you may be.
Call me
We'll become one.
Trust me
These feelings for you won't change.
My dear
Just put down
Trust me
those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
This is a work of fiction.
Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Durarara!!
Next Time
Rampant
In Ikebukuro...
He also, she also, I also, you also...
came to this town looking for something, seeking something,
trying to change something.
Next time: Rampant.
Want sushi? It's good!
Mister, long time no see!