Huh?
Kurumi-chan...
Rii-san... Mii-kun!
So...
This is where I'm going to die?
Kei...
I'm sorry I'll never see you again!
Broadcasting
There!
No!
No way...
Taroumaru?
Taroumaru!
Come here, Taroumaru.
You love this hat, right?
You do remember, don't you?
What an awful wound... You've been bitten.
And you feel so cold...
I'm so sorry... I can't help you.
They do remember.
Even if they've lost their minds,
somewhere deep down, they remember.
That's why they come back here.
Right, Megu-nee?
School is now closed for the day.
Any students still on the grounds,
please return home right away.
Fire Extinguishing System
Do you all love school?
I do.
You might say it's weird,
but the school is an incredible place.
The physics lab has all those weird tools...
The music room has all those beautiful
instruments and intimidating portraits...
And in the broadcasting room,
the whole school's your stage.
It's got everything. It's like a country of its own!
There's no other single
building as strange as this.
I love it.
I hate studying, but I like my teachers.
When I forget my homework,
they show me how to do it.
I doze in class and get scolded.
I make friends with my classmates.
I get into fights.
Sometimes we're together.
Sometimes I'm alone.
There are fun times, sad times...
So many of them... And that's why...
I love this school.
Lovely
Yuki
And you all love it too, right?
You'll always, always love it.
That's why you're here, right?
But all good things must come to an end.
It's sad that nothing can last forever,
but I think it's better that way.
So on that note... school is out.
I believe we'll meet again someday.
But for today, school is over.
To everyone still in school...
Hello, thank you...
And goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
Kurumi-chan!
Kurumi-chan! Kurumi-chan!
There, there.
Good morning.
Morning...
Kurumi!
Kurumi-chan, welcome back.
Thanks. Glad to be back.
Thank goodness.
Taroumaru!
Taroumaru?
Rii-san, Taroumaru's going to
be okay too, right? Right?
I gave him the vaccine, but his symptoms
might have progressed too far already.
Taroumaru?
Do you recognize me?
No, don't! You shouldn't move so much!
Maybe he's hungry.
Huh?
See?
That Taroumaru sure can eat.
I'll get it.
Taroumaru
Give him just a little at a time.
Right.
Senpai, water!
Here.
Hang on, okay?
Here's some water.
Welcome back, Taroumaru.
Yuki-senpai told me what happened.
You saved her, huh?
You really are amazing.
Back in the mall, too, you led the others to me.
It's all thanks to you that
I'm here now, Taroumaru.
So you don't have to worry anymore.
We'll always be together.
Taroumaru?
Jeez, what now?
Is that enough?
I think so. Miki-san?
Right.
Hey.
Why don't we put this in with him?
Yes. I think he'd like that.
Rest in peace.
I guess it's time say goodbye.
Ready?
Yes.
Mii-kun, are you okay?
I'm fine. Taroumaru saved my life.
I need to send him off with a smile, right?
Not at all.
If you bottle up your sadness too much,
you'll forget what's really important.
I'm so glad I got to be your teacher.
I'd forgotten Megu-nee's
last words for a long time.
So if something sad happens,
it's okay to feel sad.
You don't always have to be "fine."
Yuki-senpai...
So don't forget Taroumaru's last words, okay?
Words?
Taroumaru didn't say...
Sure he did!
He looked at you, and said...
"Thank you!"
I wanted...
to thank him, too...
There wasn't much food left
in the underground shelter.
Let's all graduate together!!
And since we can't use
the refrigerators anymore,
we need to eat the perishable
foods before they spoil.
We should start with the frozen food.
All right! First come, first served!
Ooh, I found a bunch of Nummy Sticks!
That's not a frozen food!
I guess Yuki-senpai hasn't changed, after all.
I can't have them? Okay, fine.
I'll have one of these other snacks.
Snacks are for after!
Does the stove still work?
It will while the emergency power supply lasts,
but that won't be much longer.
The water supply's in danger, too.
Yes, since it was pumped up from
underground using electricity.
I guess we really will have to leave...
There won't be another place as
well-equipped as here, though.
Actually, take a look at this.
I read through the manual again and found this.
Do you think this symbol is for shelters?
Did... Did Megu-nee leave this?
They're all a bit far from here, though.
Well, we still have the car
we used for the club outing.
Megu-nee was already thinking about
where you all should go next.
Of course. She was our teacher.
Yup.
Let's see... The closest place is
the College of Saint Isodore.
This company, the Randall
Corporation, is close, as well.
Ugh, that sounds totally suspicious!
College or the work force, huh?
Either way, there could be other people
who evacuated before things went bad.
Yes... I'm sure there are.
Do you think they'll take us in?
We have no idea what kind of people they'll be...
Since they'd actually understand us,
it could be even worse than dealing with them.
We can't deny that possibility.
Hey, everyone!
Look at this!
What now...
I knew it! You're eating snacks!
Forget about that. Look at this!
It's got bite marks.
Senpai, I know you get hungry, but...
I-It wasn't me!
I get it. They're not human teeth.
Was it Taroumaru?
No, whatever did this was smaller than him.
Maybe there was another dog
somewhere underground?
This whole time, I've been wondering
why Taroumaru was down
there in the first place.
That's it! Taroumaru must've gone
to visit the one that did this!
Yeah, that must be it!
Otherwise he'd never go
somewhere that dangerous.
He must've been worried about the
puppy and gone to check on it...
Yeah! Taroumaru did love to care for others!
But you didn't see any animals when
you were down there, did you?
No... And if it ran outside,
who knows if it's still alive...
I'm sure it is!
Taroumaru was there, after all.
Yeah... You're right.
Taroumaru was a really brave dog.
You know, we should quit worrying
about what'll happen after we leave.
Taroumaru would laugh at us.
Yes.
Then I guess it's time to say
goodbye to this school, too.
Hey, before we go...
Let's have our graduation!
Let's all graduate together!!
Graduation...
That's right, we still have the ceremony left.
Even at times like this...
You're still the same as ever, Senpai.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
It means you're fine just the way you are.
Wait, I get to graduate, too?
You're really smart, Mii-kun.
You can skip a grade!
Animal Crackers
You really are a true senpai.
Here, I offer you the best "biscuit" I have.
That's "respect."
Then it's settled. The School Living Club's
final activity will be a graduation ceremony.
Yeah!
This diploma certifies that
Takeya Yuki
has graduated from Megurigaoka Private High School
Graduation
Hey, Yuki!
Yes?
Megurigaoka Private High School Graduation
The graduates of Megurigaoka Private High
School will now be awarded their diplomas.
The underclass farewell address
will be read by Naoki Miki.
Yes.
Time certainly flies.
It feels as though I've just met you all,
yet it's already graduation season.
Beyond the walls of this school,
a vast future stretches out before us.
As I think that I'm about to set sail into
the tumultuous waters of society,
I feel both proud and afraid.
You all invited me to join the
School Living Club, where I learned
what it is to believe in your
own strength and work hard,
how to be brave in the face of adversity,
and how the heart can remain bright and
optimistic, even in the darkest times.
So I am no longer afraid.
I thank you all from the bottom of my heart.
Underclass speaker-cum-graduate, Naoki Miki.
Next, graduating class speaker Takeya Yuki.
Yes.
Naoki-san, thank you for that moving speech.
My friendship with Mii-kun...
Miki-kun... Miki-san... is...
Mii-kun is fine.
Sorry.
My friendship with Mii-kun
is very important to me.
Thanks to Mii-kun, Taroumaru, and Megu-nee...
Many people were lost, as well,
but despite that... No, because of that,
I'm so happy that we're all graduating together.
I hope we'll stay together forever!
Graduating class speaker Takeya Yuki.
I look with respect at my teachers,
to whom I owe so much.
So quickly the years have passed
in this garden of learning.
I will fondly remember my
precious years spent here.
Bow to the teachers.
This concludes the presentation of diplomas
Now is the time to say farewell.
To Sakura-sensei
and the Megurigaoka High
School graduation ceremony.
Thank you.
Rii-san, come on!
Okay, let's go!
We're off!
Did you forget something?
Oh, no.
Anyway, they're really gone, huh?
They all went home.
I guess so.
Is it weird to think it feels a bit lonely?
Very weird.
But I sort of understand...
What is it?
Nothing...
Just thinking about how we
really do love our school.
Kei,
I lived, and it was all worthwhile.
Hey, so, this is like our graduation trip, huh?
It is. Where should we go?
America!
Another country?!
Kurumi-chan, where do you want to go?
If it's our graduation trip... Kyoto, maybe?
Kyoto... You sound like a ninja.
Why a ninja?!
An apprentice geisha?
Uh...
Ah, you were considering it, weren't you?
You guys!
We are happy.
Yuki