I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a twist of fate changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
Different feelings and words that won't connect...
Is fighting the only way to get through to each other?
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
I'm sure that meeting
was just a coincidence.
But if you layer an endless amount of
coincidences on top of one another...
I'm sure people pick one at random,
and that becomes the path they travel.
At least, that's how I believe people live.
My life seems to have had one of those coincidences recently.
That's why I feel like I want to keep going
like this, believing I chose the right path.
Of my own free will...
and with my own feelings.
Episode 5
This Is a City of Hot Water, the Uminari Hot Springs!
This Is a City of Hot Water,
the Uminari Hot Springs!
Now then! Japan enjoys
a long holiday season.
Our coffee shop, Midoriya,
is always open for business,
but during the holidays,
we leave our shop in the
hands of the employees,
and go on a big family vacation.
This time, my best friends
are coming with us.
Onii-chan and his girlfriend,
Tsukimura Shinobu-san,
as well as the Tsukimuras's maids,
are also with us on vacation.
For two days, we'll be relaxing at a hot spring inn
that's said to relieve
the stress of daily life.
That's the Takamachi
family's usual vacation plan.
Look, look! It's so green out here!
Really!
Nanoha.
Nanoha, you have to at least rest and take it easy on vacation.
I know.
I'll be fine.
That mage in black I met last week...
Having not been able to find even
a single Jewel Seed since then...
Because I've been
dwelling on these things,
I've decided to take a good,
long rest from everything for a bit,
at Yuuno-kun's suggestion.
Mountain
Inn
It's so big!
Yeah!
For the next two days, I'm going to try
to relax and act like a normal kid.
I think I'm going to play as much
as I possibly can while I'm here!
Ladies Bath
'
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ladies' Bath
No problem. Shall we go?
Yuuno-kun, have you ever been to a hot spring before?
A-Ah, um...
If you count a public bathhouse
as a hot spring, then yes, but...
Hot springs are really nice!
R-R-Really...?
N-Nanoha... really, I think I...
Um... really, I think I'd better go into the
men's bath with Kyouya-san and Shiro-san...
Huh? It'll be fine!
Let's go in together!
Ah! Fantastic!
This is amazing!
There's so much room!
This sure is impressive.
It really is!
Onee-chan, I'll scrub your back for you!
Thank you, Suzuka.
Then, I'll do yours!
Thank you.
Then, I get to wash yours!
Don't worry! I'm good at washing.
Vacations like these are
so nice, don't you think?
Yeah, they are.
And we can leave our shop
to the youngsters, too.
And our own children
are so full of spirit.
And... so are you.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Quite a bit of time has passed, huh?
Yes.
Well... you and the kids don't need
to worry about me anymore.
From now on, I'll only
be Midoriya's owner.
Yes... thank you, dear...
Here you are.
Thanks.
But Noel, you're not supposed to be working today,
so go ahead and take a break.
Yes, thank you. I'll be sure to relax a little while I'm here.
Well then, Onee-chan, Shinobu-san,
we're heading out!
Okay!
We're going to go explore the inn.
Okay. See you later.
All right! Here we go, Yuuno!
That felt so good!
Yeah.
Now that we're out of the hot spring,
wanna go play ping pong?
Huh? Ping pong?
I wanted to check out the souvenirs they're selling...
Um...
Ping-pong...
Hmm, what should we do?
Which should we do first?
Why don't we do
rock-paper-scissors?
Hi, little girls!
Were you the one she was talking about?
You don't look very smart,
not to mention strong...
You just look like some
normal brat to me.
Nanoha, do you know her?
N-No...
It seems my friend doesn't
know you! Who are you?
Sorry, sorry!
I think I have the wrong person!
It's because she looks like someone I know.
Oh... so that's it...
That sure is a cute ferret you have!
Yeah.
There, there. Pet, pet...
This is just a simple greeting.
Let me warn you in advance.
Be good little kids,
and play somewhere else.
If you get in our way too much,
I'll swallow you whole.
Now then, I think I'll go take another bath.
Nanoha...
Yeah...
Nanoha-chan...
Y-Yeah...
What the heck was that
woman's problem?!
Um... she sure was different, huh?
Was she drunk?! And in the middle of the day, too!
Disgusting!
Arisa-chan...
Now, now,
this is a place of relaxation,
so there's bound to be lots of different types here.
Even so, there's such a thing as moderation, you know! Moderation!
Ah... hello? Fate?
Arf here.
Yeah...
I checked her out.
The girl in white you mentioned.
I see... What did you think?
Well...
She didn't look like a big deal to me.
She's no match for you, Fate.
Is that so?
I've made a bit of progress here, too.
I've been able to find out the general
location of the next Jewel Seed.
I think we'll be able to capture it tonight.
Nice, Fate! I expected nothing less from my master!
Thank you, Arf.
Let's meet again this evening.
Okay!
So relaxing...
Oh, they came out.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Oh, no!
I wonder if this would be all right?
And they all lived happily ever after.
Oh, Falin-chan,
are the children asleep already?
Yes, Momoko-san.
They're all sound asleep.
Thank you so much, Falin-chan.
Not at all, I like doing things like this.
Yuuno-kun, are you awake?
Y-Yeah.
I wonder if the person we met this afternoon
is related to the girl from last week?
Probably.
I wonder if things will
turn out like last time?
Probably...
Nanoha, I've been doing a lot of thinking since then.
Really, from here on out, I thin–
Stop!
If you say anything else, I'll get mad.
"I think it'd be best if I worked alone."
"I don't want you involved in this anymore, Nanoha."
That's what you were
going to say, right?
Yeah...
Gathering the Jewel Seeds...
at first, I was doing it to help
you out, but it's different now.
It's something I'm doing
because I want to do it.
If you said you'd leave me behind and
go off to do it on your own, I'd get angry.
Yeah.
Now, let's get back to bed.
Something else might happen tonight.
Yeah.
Bingo! Found it, Fate!
Nanoha!
It'll be fine. Let's hurry, Yuuno-kun!
Raising Heart, please!
Stand by, ready. Set up.
That thing sure is amazing.
So this is the power of a Lost Logia?
This one's unstable, though,
so that's not all of its power.
I wonder why your mother
wants them so badly?
Who knows? I don't,
but it doesn't matter.
I must get them because
Mother wants them.
Bardiche! Awaken!
Yes, sir.
Sealing Form, Set up.
I'm going to seal it.
Arf, support me.
Sure, sure.
That's...!
This makes two...
My, oh my. My, my, my.
Didn't I tell you earlier that you
should be good little kids?
What... are you planning
to do with the Jewel Seeds?
They're dangerous!
Who knows? I don't see
any reason to tell you.
And I was being pretty nice when
we spoke before, wasn't I?
When I warned that if you weren't
good kids, I'd swallow you whole!
As I thought... that woman...
she's a familiar!
Familiar?
That's right. I'm a magical
beast created by her.
She supports my life
with her magical power,
so I give all of my life and
strength to protect her!
Go on ahead.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay. Don't be too reckless.
Okay!
Nanoha! Please take care of that girl!
Do you think I'd let you?!
I'll make you let me!
Teleportation magic...? This is bad!
Proficiency in versatile barrier magic...
You have a strong familiar.
Yuuno-kun isn't a familiar! He's my close friend!
So? What will you do?
Isn't there some way
we can talk this over?
I must collect the Lost Logia
fragments... the Jewel Seeds.
And if you have the same goal...
we'll be enemies, with the Jewel Seeds on the line.
That's what I mean! I think
we need to talk this over,
so we don't jump to such
dangerous conclusions!
Simply talking...
Words alone won't change anything.
They'll never get through!
Flier Fin.
But even so...!
Put yourself on the line and make a bet.
The stakes are a Jewel Seed each.
Photon Lancer, Get set.
Isn't it about time you stopped running?
Why did a mage strong enough to create
her own familiar come to this world?
And what do you know about the
Jewel Seeds... the Lost Logia?!
Shut up!
Thunder Smasher.
Divine Buster.
Raising Heart, please!
All right.
Nanoha's... so strong!
But she's still too soft.
Scythe Slash.
Nanoha!
Put out.
Raising Heart! What are you...?!
I'm sure it was worried and
wanted to protect you.
Let's go home, Arf.
That's my master for you!
See you, little girl!
Wait!
Never appear before us again,
if you can help it.
If something like this happens again,
I may not be able to stop myself.
Your name...
What's your name?
Fate. Fate Testarossa.
Um, I'm...
Bye bye!
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
Nanoha is keeping
a secret from us...
There's nothing we
can do about it.
Everyone has something
they can't tell their friends.
Past events are slowly
being revealed.
And what will be the fate of the two
magical girls who have met once more?
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 6
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Episode Six:
Lyrical magical,
I hope I can reach her...