What's this urban legend?!
The black bike, dude!
The Headless Rider!
You know, the guy who rides that black bike doesn't...
have a head.
He moves just fine despite being decapitated.
Well, it's not really a hard job.
Either way, be careful.
I didn't know you became a Champion of Justice.
What the fuck?
What the fuck?!
The Headless Rider?
Yeah, I've heard of it!
My friend saw it.
Dunno.
I'm really not that interested.
I even took a picture of it.
See?
The Headless Rider?
It's him!
You've heard of it, right?
I think I saw it around the Sunshine building.
Are you serious?
Not sure. Everyone was going "wow," so I guess it was there.
People love to gossip.
Looks like that rumored bike appeared again.
Is it really true that the rider doesn't have a head though?
It's just a silly rumor.
But I've heard quite a few rumors that it's real.
Oh?
Dude, not having a head is impossible.
But if it's not human...
then it's possible.
I heard that people involved with it won't talk about it.
I'm sorry. I don't know anything.
What about you?
What impression do you have of that legendary headless rider?
Scary? Cool?
Or maybe a pretty nice person?
No, rather...
Unsure on what to say?
Today, I'll tell you what I know about the Headless Rider.
I'll be painfully meticulous,
but please listen with an open mind.
Well, let me start by introducing myself.
My name is Kishitani Shinra. I'm twenty-four years old.
I work as an unlicensed doctor.
In other words, I'm an underground doctor who is summoned for various reasons.
I treat people wounded by illegal weapons,
or perform plastic surgery on people who need a new face.
Even if I don't look like it, I'm a pretty skilled and trusted physician.
Well then, let's move on to the main topic.
I'm back!
Right.
I'm living with the Headless Rider,
Selty Sturluson.
I'm back, Selty.
My job was fairly easy this time.
How about you?
Don't peek!
Sorry!
I didn't mean to peek.
Sorry, I was careless.
You seem kind of angry.
Maybe you need some calcium.
Are you telling me to eat eggshells or something?
Actually, that's not a bad idea.
Well, I'm not really interested in dietetics,
so I have no idea how much calcium is in an eggshell,
or how well the body can metabolize it.
Then again, it's also a question of how necessary calcium is,
since we don't even know where your brain is.
Shut up!
Say, Selty... I know I'm being a nag, but...
How does the world look to you, someone without eyes?
I can't tell you something I don't understand myself.
She doesn't have a head,
but she has sight, she can hear, and she can smell.
But it's not like she can see in every direction at once just because she doesn't have a head.
It's just that her field of vision is slightly wider than a normal human's.
This is just my hypothesis,
but maybe that strange, sci-fi substance emanating from your body
emits particles that collect information about whatever they touch,
and then relay that information back to you.
Obviously, objects that are too far away will be blurry.
I don't care.
As long as I can see and hear, I don't care about any of that.
You're always like that, Selty.
I just want to know how different my world
is from yours.
I'm not just talking about sight.
It's also a matter of values.
Not your values as a human,
but as a fairie that has been incarnated in this city.
I'm interested in the values you have about this world as a Dullahan.
What's wrong?
If you want, you can tell me what happened.
Orihara-kun said your job was pretty easy.
I got the job done pretty quickly.
But?
Big props to the transporter.
Things work well for me because you're here for me, and vice versa.
I disagree with the latter.
Oh, don't be so cold.
I'll be asking for your help again.
I want to get along with you.
For a very long time...
Is it just me, or do you creep people out?
Not at all. It's just your imagination.
By the way, have you heard of the Dullahan?
It's a headless fairie from Ireland.
An elderly portraitist over at Yoyogi Park says he saw one a long time ago.
I heard he made a big fuss about how it didn't have a head.
I wonder if he meant the Dullahan's head?
Is he still there?
I don't really know.
Oh, so you are curious about it.
Selty Sturluson isn't human.
She's what's known as a "Dullahan." It's something like a fairie in Celtic mythology.
Do you know of a portraitist around here?
Oh, he left already.
Hey, didn't he say he was going to Yokohama or something?
A Dullahan carries its decapitated head under its arm
and rides a coiste bodhar, a two-wheeled coach that's pulled by a headless horse.
It visits the homes of those due to die.
If you carelessly open the door,
it'll throw a basin of blood on you.
It's not that easy to relate her to a sinister legend about a bringer of death.
Except that neither has a head.
So why did she come to Japan, to Tokyo, and specifically, to Ikebukuro?
And why does she worry so much about her head?
I'll explain that now.
It happened twenty years ago.
She suddenly woke up in the mountains
and noticed that her head was missing.
Then, she realized that many of her memories were gone.
She'd forgotten why she did what she did,
and she'd forgotten other memories to a certain degree.
However, she didn't forget that she was a Dullahan,
that her name was Selty Sturluson,
or how to use her abilities.
What shocked her was...
I've never used my head to think.
That.
Furthermore, she realized that she could sense her head's presence.
After considering her situation, she concluded
that her will had originally been shared between her body and head,
and that her memories must have remained in her head.
So she decided
to reclaim her head, for it held her raison d'être.
From then on, that became her reason for living.
Perhaps her head had separated itself from her body on its own.
Regardless, she could determine this only by finding her head.
He wasn't in Yokohama any more.
So I went to Tama and Chiba.
I always just missed him.
You should have waited until the next day.
I was desperate.
My head might have been there.
I desperately wanted it back.
As soon as possible.
I don't want to live with a hazy memory.
Even though she could sense her head's presence,
she only learned that her head was heading overseas through investigative work.
The ship's destination was Japan.
Smuggling herself aboard would be simple,
but her horse would be a problem.
A Dullahan's horse is something like a familiar that possesses the body of a dead horse.
If she'd wanted, she could have gotten rid of it.
But where would it go then?
The answer probably lays within her head.
All these thoughts made her anxious and unable to move forward.
And then...
She...
spotted that.
In the end I couldn't find it.
However...
Oh, I know that portraitist.
He came to South Ikebukuro Park two days ago.
Yeah.
Want me to come along?
Talking to him would be inconvenient, right?
There you go.
Wow, nice!
You're prettier in that picture than in real life.
Hey!
You're really good at this.
Well, there are still things I can't draw the way I want.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
Come back again.
We will!
Sorry, but it's getting dark.
I've called it a day.
Is it true that you saw a Dullahan?
Yeah, it is.
I saw it in the mountains of Ireland when I was young.
There's no mistake.
What do you mean by "lost its head"?
"Lost its head"?
That's not it.
It doesn't have a head.
A head just doesn't suit it.
Look.
It was a woman.
A very, very beautiful one.
I saw her on the mountain path on a foggy night.
She passed by at high speed.
She was horrifying, yet beautiful.
I felt that she wasn't from this world.
When I returned to the inn and asked around,
I was told she was a Dullahan.
Apparently, she's been living there for a long time.
Why isn't the Dullahan in your drawing carrying a head?
I just can't draw it.
The more I draw, the stranger it looks.
I remember that day as if it were yesterday, but I can't connect with that woman.
What color was her hair? And her eyes?
What kind of expression did she have?
If I could explain that, I wouldn't have tried to draw her.
Speaking of which, some strange man visited me.
He said that the picture was already perfect.
And that she didn't need a head.
What a weirdo.
Why are you so obsessed?
It was the most fascinating experience of my life.
That night was very unique to me.
I want to return to that moment, the recollections of that night.
Thanks, old man.
I see.
But you don't remember meeting him.
No.
Which means that the Dullahan might not have been you.
Or he was just mistaken.
It was me.
It had to be.
I see.
I wonder where I was headed?
What was I thinking? And why...
Do you really need to brood about it?
You're truly an elusive, novel person.
Fact is, your objective is far away from you.
Cut to the chase.
Very well.
Give up.
Perhaps that weird guy is right.
Maybe it's fine to not have a head.
Stop searching for your head.
Let's go somewhere.
Just the two of us.
If you wish, I can take you back to your homeland, regardless of the means.
I'll come with you too.
And then we'll live there together—
I don't dislike you, but living like this is enough for me.
Oh, come on.
It's enough!
Then...
Be a little more femin—
It's enough!
So is there a difference between my values and hers?
Anyway, back to the story.
What happened after she boarded the ship.
No...
Our story.
She managed to persuade the sailor to smuggle her onto the ship,
but she noticed how much she stood out.
It's not that big a deal now that I've known her for a while.
The first time I saw that, I was completely in awe.
Back then, I was four years old.
I was returning to Japan with my father.
Dad! There's a woman in the hatch!
My father, Shingen, was a bit abnormal.
Hurry up! Dad!
I believe the normal reaction would be to laugh at your silly kid.
But my father was different.
I wonder if it was his nature as a doctor,
but he suddenly became interested in my story.
Excuse me, miss.
Is it true that you don't have a head?
My father said,
"If you let me dissect you just once, I'll give you a place to stay."
She accepted his offer.
I'm sure both the benefits and anxiety were on her mind.
She doesn't really remember what happened.
The anesthetic given to humans didn't really work.
I believe the shock was too much for her.
She feels pain, but it is far less than what a human feels.
She doesn't have a heart.
Her organs don't work. They are merely there.
She has veins, yet blood doesn't flow through them.
She is merely flesh.
She's like a living anatomical model.
But look at this.
How is it possible for her to die?
I have a horrible father, don't I?
He told his four-year-old son to dissect her.
But thanks to him, I've learned the skills necessary to become a doctor.
Though I don't know if I should be happy about this.
What's the matter?
I've been attracted to her ever since I saw her.
My feelings haven't changed a bit in the twenty years I've lived with her.
She's been searching for her head all this time while working as a transporter.
I wonder what she's going to do when she finds her head.
What will happen to her?
Does her will come from her head?
Or is it...
What are you filming?
Uh... How should I say it?
I wanted to leave a piece of our sweet daily life for future generations.
I don't really care. Just pipe down a bit.
I can't sleep.
Sorry, Selty.
Well, that's it for now.
I'll continue another time.
Wow!
This is perfect!
What part of this is perfect?
In truth, Dullahan carry their heads.
Perhaps they don't need a head.
That's absurd.
You only say that because you haven't seen one in person.
It was a beautiful woman.
Yes.
But I like her better without a head.
She's more charming that way.
The drawing is perfect.
You don't need to worry.
It's okay if you can't draw it.
Let it be like this.
I'm still going to draw it.
It's fine like that!
You're quite the weirdo, aren't you?
Please, I'm not that weird!
You wanna know about my love-love-get-a-kiss and heart-breaking life?
Then tune your heart to my, Kida Masaomi's, shy and cool channel.
Next time: Weeping Wine and Selling Vinegar.
Don't miss the chance of your lifetime!