After careful consideration of the times, we feel that intense scenes in this show are important to the story.
-Rainbow Production Staff
The six boys stepped up to their greatest challenge yet
in order to save Sakuragi's life.
And that's how Anchan's escape will go.
Whoa, good plan, Baremoto!
That sounds like it might work!
Not might! Will!
But first we need to get outta here.
The door only opens from the outside, you know!
I've got that covered too, of course!
Today's Sunday.
There aren't as many guards, so they only do late-night rounds twice,
at 11:00 and 3:00.
We'll use that chance to sneak out of here!
But how do we get out?!
The guards aren't the only ones with keys.
I've learned that the doctor on duty has the keys as well.
Someone here will pretend to be sick to get inside the infirmary
and swipe the key when the doctor isn't looking.
That's a tall order. Dr. Sasaki is the one on duty today.
Yeah, I know...
All right, I'll do it! I can always bite him with these teeth if I-
I'll do it.
If you go, he'll just give you some pills and send you back.
Quit worrying about me, Baremoto.
I'm the only one who can do it, aren't I?
But, Joe! If you go, that old pervert will get you!
Don't worry, Suppon.
I will unlock this door.
I will!
"My heart won't get hurt any more than this..."
"My body won't get tarnished any more than this..."
"Anchan's life is the only thing that matters," Joe thought.
If this works...
Not if. When.
Make it work...
then we can smoke these with Anchan.
And then we'll all meet up there,
under the tree we all carved our dreams into...
Ouch! It hurts!
Are you okay, Joe?!
Hey guard! You there?! He needs a doctor! Hey!
Dr. Sasaki. Sorry to disturb you.
It's Jo Yokosuka from Block 2, Cell 6.
He suddenly has pain in his stomach...
If it's nothing much, I'll give him some pills and take him straight back.
N- no, let's have a look first...
Well, Doctor?
Oh, yes.
Just to be safe, let's have him spend the night here.
Really? Alright then.
Thank you, Doctor!
Now then, Yokosuka.
What are you after, coming here with a fake illness?
Cigarettes? Speed, maybe?
Umm, if I do what you say, you'll let me out sooner, right?
But of course!
Then... I'll do whatever you want...
Truly?
Yes...
In that case!...
Please wait!
I haven't been out in a while.
Do you think we could have something nice to eat first, Doctor?
Yes, of course...
Man, how can he sleep in the middle of something so important?
Do you think Joe'll be all right? What if...
Quit letting your mind wander, Suppon.
He'll do it just like Baremoto planned.
All we can do is have faith and wait!
Come on, Yokosuka! Isn't that enough? I can't hold back anymore!
O- okay?
Yes, all right.
Okay, Doctor. You get on the bed first.
I'm turning the lights off now.
Come on, now...
Don't tease me too much, Joe!
I know, Doctor.
I'll make it nice and tight for you now!
Don't show your nasty body to me, you creepy old pervert!
Who would ever wanna do it with someone like you?!
You're gonna be the butt of jokes for the rest of your life!
Sorry for the wait, guys.
Your turn next, Mario!
Joe...
Joe! You're okay!
I'd never let that geezer get the best of me!
Okay! Let's go save Anchan!
Yeah!
Soon!...
Soon you'll be dead!...
See you in hell, Sakuragi!
You!
Let's hurry, Mario!
Anchan!
We came to get you, Anchan...
M- Mario...
Your right hand...
No... It's nothing...
Okay! Let's go, Anchan!
We're all breaking out!
You all right, Mario?
You're hurt. He's gotta be heavy for you.
He's light...
I can't believe Anchan's become this light...
Mario choked up at the thought of how light Anchan was on his back.
He swore he would make Ishihara and Sasaki pay.
"We're almost outside the wall!
We'll be free to do whatever we want!
Sign: Infirmary
Is someone in there?
D- Dr. Sasaki!
Mario! Hetai! Good job!
Anchan...
He's really wasted away. We gotta hurry...
The guards on patrol should pass by soon. Hold on until then.
We're done for if we get spotted.
All seven of us are leaving!
Baremoto.
What're those for?
If we do get spotted, it should slow down the guys chasing us a little.
Just a little extra insurance.
You're awesome, Baremoto!
You really are a genius!
It's good to have you as a friend!
Yeah! You're a great guy, Baremoto!
Yeah!
Wh- what brought that on, you guys?
Oh! He's embarrassed!
Escapees! The six from Block 2, Cell 6 broke out! Guard the gate!
You won't escape...
I definitely won't let you get away!
They already found out?!
This is too soon!
Wh- what do we do?!
What do we do, Baremoto?!
Baremoto!
I never expected them to find out this soon!
Now what? How do we reach the gate now?!
Baremoto...
They're relying on me now... On me!...
Just stay calm!
Leave it to me!
Baremoto...
Mario! You take care of Anchan!
You'll have hell to pay if you screw up and something happens to him!
Suppon!
Book: Scam the Genius's Notebook
You better introduce me to some girls when we're on the outside!
One thing I don't want is to die a virgin!
Baremoto! What are you?-
I fully anticipated something like this might happen!
Just leave it to me!
Hey! Wait!
Hey! Baremoto!
That idiot!
There's no time to worry about him!
We gotta focus on Anchan!
I found one!
Over here!
Stop!
Halt!
I knew what it meant.
I knew this plan couldn't succeed without sacrifice!
Anchan was the first person to ever call me a friend.
I will save him!
Hang in there, Anchan!
Wh- what?! What's going on?!
A blackout?!
Was it Baremoto?!
Okay! Now's our chance!
You little shit!
The others should be lurking nearby as well.
Okay! Find 'em!
Right!
Run...
Run!
I was the first to be caught, but there was no other way. This is my role.
Even in baseball you need sacrifice hitters and bunters.
I scam from the very start!
Yes, Ryuji Nomoto is just the name my parents gave me.
That's why my name's Baremoto! Understand?
You still haven't caught the other six?!
No. It's proving difficult without any light.
They intend to escape. If you search the area around the gate...
No... the back gate!
They must have gone to the back gate; there are no guards there!
That sounds like something they'd think of!
Good thinking! Then we'll scour the back gate area!
I refuse to use the back gate!
How come, Mario? Security is light-
For two years...
For two years, Anchan has proudly served his time in here.
I don't want to sneak him out the back like some coward.
Anchan isn't escaping. He's getting released!
I want him to go through the front gate, like a real man!
Sign: Shonan Special Reformatory
Never expected only two people at the front gate.
Mario. Joe. Keep them down.
Hurry, Hetai!
Yeah, I know!
Damn...
Is this it?
Nope...
Not this one either...
Shit!
What are you doing, Hetai?!
Bastard!
Hetai! Hurry it up! They're coming!
Hey! Which one opens the front gate?!
There they are! The front gate!
Mario... Take Anchan...
I'm not smart, so this is all I can do to help...
Cabbage...
C- Cabbage...
Anchan...
You damn kids!
Stay right where you are!
Cabbage!
I won't let you past me!
Get off!
I won't let you past... even if it kills me!
Cabbage...
I got it!
Okay!
Hey! Mario!
What are you doing, Mario?!
Cabbage is...
Mario!
Anchan comes first!
Right!
I broke the key. That'll keep 'em off your backs for a little while.
Hetai! You're!...
Go on!
Cabbage and I will be there someday, at our promised spot...
Hetai...
Damn it! Get the hell off of me!
I'm right behind ya, Cabbage.
Can't do my workouts without you, after all.
Hetai...
What do you think, Anchan?
The outside air's nice, huh?
Now Anchan is safe!
Right, Mario?
Yeah. Anchan is free now.
Baremoto... Cabbage... and Hetai...
...risked their lives for mine!...
I refuse to let you take that away!
Die, Sakuragi!
Ishihara!
It's you! It's all because of you!...
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Mario! Anchan's not looking good!
Anchan!
We have to do something...
We need to get him to a doctor...
What does Baremoto's plan say to do next?
Nothing. It stops at going through the gate.
Oh...
It just means the rest it up to us now!
Everyone else is risking their lives for Anchan,
but only did I not protect him, he saved me!
What are you doing, Mario?!
Quit spacin' out, will ya?!
We gotta hurry!
Quit worrying about it, Mario.
We wouldn't even have an escape plan in the first place if it weren't for you!
Yeah! Even though it was a pretty reckless plan!
It's thanks to you that Anchan is still alive now!
Let's switch, Joe.
I'll carry Anchan now.
"Anchan isn't dead. He's out. He's free.
There are no bad people out to kill him anymore.
Please let a bright future be the only thing waiting for him," Mario prayed.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
A calm, brief moment of life on the run.
Mario steps into the ring to earn money.