One day, an email comes
from Eichi in America!
The unexpected good news
brightens Mitsuki's spirits
and even helps her condition improve!
But then we find out that the email
was actually a fake, sent from Izumi!
Takuto! How do we tell Mitsuki the truth?
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Eichi... The minute that
email from you came,
I got word of a new operation.
It's like you brought me happiness!
Takuto...
What are we going to do?
About Eichi's email being a fake.
Should we tell her?
Yes, Ms. Oshige?
Yes...
What?
I've been nominated for
the Best New Singer Award
in the Fantasia Music Festival?!
Is it really that amazing of an award?
It's not just amazing.
It's the only international music festival
for which Japan is in association
with America's AAS Broadcasting.
Wow.
In addition, what's unique
about this festival is that
the audience gets to vote
alongside the judges.
That's why your performance
on that day is important
in order to get a lot of votes
from the audience.
We have to improve your
condition from now on.
I can't really grasp it all quite yet.
But what I'm about to tell
you will really get you motivated!
You see, the winner of
the Best New Singer Award
will be invited to America.
What?!
America?
America... I'll get to see Eichi.
You have to win! Right?
It's a really big music festival.
Hey! You're so cute!
You're waiting for an email
from Eichi, aren't you?
N-No! That's not it.
It's just that if I hold my cell phone,
I feel like I'm connected to Eichi,
and it calms me down.
Aww, I'm jealous!
Stop it, Ms. Oshige!
Full Moon, we'll start the explanation!
Oh, okay! Ms. Oshige,
please hold these for me.
Okay.
She's been so happy since
she got the email from Eichi.
Yes. On top of that, there's the news
of the new treatment method,
and the Best New Singer Award
nomination.
I'm sure that if she got
about 100 emails from Eichi,
her illness would be cured.
Dr. Wakaoji!
Hi.
Ms. Oshige... Umm...
Did I get any emails?
No.
I see.
Hey, they say no news is good news.
That's okay! Because I'm really happy
with that one email from Eichi.
Hey...
Don't you think we should tell her
that the email was fake after all?
No!
She's so happy!
It's an important time with
the Best New Singer Award.
To tell her that now...
But isn't it crueler to make her
happy with lies?
Takuto!
Full Moon, please.
Okay.
She needs an email from Eichi.
DEAR MITSUKI
I'M ALWAYS LISTENING
TO YOUR SONGS.
GOOD LUCK WITH
THE BEST
NEW SINGER AWARD.
—EICHI
SEND
Hey, hey! Takuto!
Do you want to see
the new email from Eichi?
Not really.
Don't say that!
See, see! Look!
It's kind of short and curt, but...
He's probably just busy, right?
I don't know.
Yeah, because I wrote it! Darn it!
But even though it's short,
I can feel that he's thinking about me.
I understand.
I feel like his true feelings are in
this short email
more than in the long one that I got first.
I wonder why.
Hello? Is this Meroko?
Tomorrow, I'm going to stay at home.
So please stay with her.
Yeah, see ya.
Hey! Oshige!
Oh, Department Manager.
Who's this?
I'm going to make my debut soon.
I'm Yuma Shimazu.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I guess you could say
she's Full Moon's junior.
I've always admired you.
Full Moon, I look forward to
working with you.
I look forward to working with you too.
Thank you.
Wow, what a cute plush toy.
May I see it?
Y-Yeah, here.
Wow.
It's about time for the meeting to start.
Department Manager, I'll see you later.
Yeah.
Don't leave me here!
An email? Could it be Eichi?
Jeez...
It's not easy being in the plush toy form.
Ow! What the...
Meroko! I'm so glad I found you!
I have to go to Narita Airport
right away!
I got an email from Eichi!
He's coming to Japan today!
What?
So please tell Takuto to come
to Narita Airport!
W-Wait!
I'll be back before the show!
That Mitsuki...
I wonder where she went.
This is Oshige.
Oh, Mitsuki? Hey, where are you?
What?
What?! Eiichi is here?!
Yes, I'll definitely return before the show.
So please let me go to Narita Airport.
I understand.
I'll be waiting for you, Mitsuki.
Thank you, Ms. Oshige!
All right!
What's going on?
I don't know! Anyway, she told me
to tell you to go to Narita.
I understand. I'll go at once.
Yay, were you surprised?
Mero, how are you?
Izumi...
Hi!
I can't believe
you were surprised by that.
Maybe you're getting old.
What do you want?
I'm busy now. Bye.
It looks like Mitsuki fell
for the email I sent.
Mitsuki is really innocent and cute.
What did you say?!
About the email?
You told me to quit it,
but Takuto's doing it himself.
That's why I started emailing again.
Takuto sent...an email?
So I collaborated and wrote,
"Today I'm returning to Narita.
I'd like you to pick me up."
How could you?!
What's this?
Mero, aren't you happy that Mitsuki's
feelings are directed at Eichi?
I want you to thank me.
We'll start rehearsal.
Please start, Ms. Komaki.
Our special guest today is the winner
of last year's Best New Singer Award,
The Scanty.
I want to be a Rock n' Roll Princess!
And dance with the rock spirit!
My heart throbs... Oh Rock Star!
Crying out a scream of love!
Meroko!
Takuto!
What in the world happened?
I'd like to ask you!
What's this about you sending
an email to Mitsuki?!
Th-That was...
Izumi jumped on the bandwagon and
sent an email again because you did!
What?!
That Izumi...
Hey, Takuto.
I know what Izumi did was wrong,
but you sent a fake email too, right?
If it's false hope,
then we shouldn't make her wait!
That will hurt her unnecessarily.
For whatever reason you did it,
it's still the same as what Izumi did.
Sorry.
Oh, c'mon!
I have a load of things
I want to say to you!
But before that,
we have to go get Mitsuki!
Thank you, The Scanty!
FULL MOON
I want to scream in
the winter sky that...
I want to see you right now!
FULL MOON
Good work. Please tell Mitsuki the plan
and where she'll need to stand.
And that's all for
the Best New Singer Award!
It's difficult being a manager, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Well, that doesn't usually happen.
Takuto, Meroko...
Hey, hurry up and change me
back into Mitsuki.
I can't meet Eichi like this.
Sorry!
What?
I'm sorry.
I sent that short email.
The first email and...
the one that says he's coming home
were from Izumi.
What?
None of the emails were from Eichi.
And it's a lie that he's coming home.
The emails weren't real? So Eichi is...
We still don't know where he is.
No way!
I thought I was going to see Eichi soon.
H-Hey, Mitsuki...
HEY MITSUKI,
SORRY FOR THE SHORT NOTICE,
BUT I'M GOING TO JAPAN TODAY.
MY FLIGHT LANDS AT 15:45,
SO WOULD YOU COME GET ME
AT THE AIRPORT?
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
SEEING YOU AT THE AIRPORT.
—EICHI
Sorry! By sending the thoughtless email,
I've made you suffer.
I'm really sorry!
Mitsuki...
It's okay.
It's okay. After all,
you did it for me, right, Takuto?
I'm going to the music festival
to sing on stage.
And I'm going to win
the Best New Singer Award for Eichi.
For Eichi? But you...
If we don't know where Eichi is,
I'll go search for him!
Until I met you two,
I had given up hope on everything.
But that's no good...
If I want to see Eichi again,
I have to go to America.
So I'm going to win
the Best New Singer Award!
You've gotten so strong, Mitsuki.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE
THIS EMAIL?
YES/NO
Ms. Oshige!
Dr. Wakaoji. Did you find her?
I returned to the waiting room,
but there was no evidence of her.
It's all my fault.
That doesn't matter now.
Let's search for her together
one more time.
That was the third nominee
for Best New Singer,
The Drill Boys.
Oh no! She's on!
And now, the final nominees.
It's all over!
We can trust that
this wonderful performance
will sparkle like the moon
in the evening sky.
Full Moon!
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep getting stronger.
They're silent like the snow,
but they keep building up.
Hold me tight, if loving someone
was going to feel like this
I wish I never found out about love.
I love you.
My tears won't stop.
If this is how it's going to be,
I wish I had never met you.
If the snow falls forever...
Will I be able to let go of
these thoughts of you?
Hold me tight,
if this is how it feels
to fall in love with someone
I wish I never knew.
I love you,
the feeling of love fills my heart.
I want to scream in the winter sky that
I want to see you right now.
That was amazing, Mitsuki!
Mitsuki, you did very well!
Wow! She did it! That was awesome.
Way to go, Mitsuki.
Eichi, are you listening to my song...
from somewhere?
Congratulations to winner
of the Best New Singer Award!
- Yay!
- Thank you!
I'm drinking today.
I can't believe you didn't return until just
before your performance, you rascal!
I'm sorry, Ms. Oshige. Sorry.
Well, well, let's let it go.
Yeah! You won Best New Singer
with a huge lead!
Yeah, you were number one with both
the audience votes
and with the judge's votes.
I know, I'm not that much of
a stick in the mud.
This is Mitsuki.
Ms. Kazumi?
What?!
Is this really true?
Yes... yes...
Thank you very much!
What's going on, Mitsuki?
Eichi... She said she got
a lead on Eichi!
- What?
- Really, Mitsuki?
Yes! That was Ms. Kazumi!
No way!
This time...
This time, for sure,
we'll find Eichi!
Takuto!
W-What's with you all of a sudden?!
You're so mean!
You know what I'm going to say!
Just give me some breathing room!
Gosh, do you want me to
spell it out for you?
Today is the romantic Christmas!
It's as though the whole town
is celebrating our love!
What?! He's gone?!
Wait up!
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Present from Full Moon"
- Look forward to it!