Ruth, I think it's just about done.
Let's skim off the scum.
Koutarou, you read the script, right?
Time to practice!
Wake up, Koutarou!
Koutarou!
I-I can't get used to this,
no matter how many times I see it.
Why do you have to
sleep like that, Sanae?
Good morning, Your Highness.
Please wake Yurika-san up first.
Sure.
Yurika, wake up.
It's morning.
I couldn't eat another bite.
Stop talking in your sleep.
Like I just told you, I'm full.
You won't wake up, huh?
How do you like this, then?
Coochie, coochie, coo!
I can't.
I can't eat that much.
Wake up!
I can just pick out the meat.
Theia-chan, we'll help!
You need to use shock treatment!
Wake up!
It's morning!
Potatoes are attacking me!
She's still not up!
We need something more stimulating!
She must be a pretty heavy sleeper if that didn't wake her.
It's so warm.
And just like that, I'd spent three whole seasons together with these guys.
Invaders of the Rokujouma!?
Um, what's Christmas?
Invasion Going Well!?
Why do you ask, Ruth?
Well, several members of our class
have been talking about it,
ever since the start of December.
I thought you might know, Kiriha-sama.
Indeed.
I don't know the specifics, but from what I've heard—
I'll tell you!
Christmas is when you get to eat
all the chicken and cake you want!
That's not right.
It's when Santa gives you presents.
Santa?
Do you know this man?
No, not really.
You get presents from someone you don't even know?
What if it's something dangerous?
I-It's not like that!
How so?
Huh?
How...
I heard that Christmas was a formal religious event.
Got the wrong info...
That's a problem.
That's not really wrong either.
It's only recently that couples have
begun to get all lovey-dovey instead.
L-Lovey-dovey?
That's right.
It's a day as sweet as cake!
Everyone's talking about Christmas.
So what are you going to do, Kou?
Huh? What do you mean?
Christmas. What are your plans?
Are you seriously going to
tell me you don't have any?
You're in high school, man.
Well, if I had to say—
It doesn't have to be couples!
You can get together with friends or family
and eat good food.
Yeah!
You have a party with everyone!
A party?
N-No, we can't!
We have to rehearse the play instead!
What? Really?
Of course!
We're going to begin practicing tomorrow.
So much for getting worked up about Christmas.
Wait, you're practicing with Theia-chan, aren't you?
No.
What? You have something else?
Yeah.
I do have plans for Christmas!
Hey, Kou!
The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight
Part 2
We're going to start doing rehearsals again.
I'll be with Satomi-kun.
How about some Christmas cake?
Here you go.
The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight
Part 2
Only three days until Christmas Eve.
The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Harukaze Pastry Studio is taking orders for cakes!
The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight
Part 2
Sakuraba-senpai.
Good evening.
Good evening, Santa.
Are you working here?
Ho, ho, ho.
I just started today.
Please accept this present, miss.
I think I've been a pretty good girl this year.
Am I really just getting a flier?
This is a problem.
I'll take this, then, Santa.
Does it look good on me?
Very cute.
Kinda childish.
You're such a tease, Satomi-kun.
I'm only telling the truth.
Here you go.
We're accepting orders for cakes!
Sorry for bugging you.
I know! I'll help you out to make up for it.
No can do.
I wouldn't be working for myself.
Actually...
There is something I'd like for you to help me with.
I wanted to ask when I had more time tomorrow, but...
What is it?
Koutarou got a new job?
Yeah, according to Makkenji-kun,
he suddenly decided at lunch today to get one.
I've been telling him since this
morning we need to start practice too.
I can't believe him.
Perfect!
It's an etheric stove!
He didn't say anything
until this morning either.
Why suddenly get a job?
Yeah.
Supposedly, Satomi-kun didn't tell Makkenji-kun why either.
I bet there's a reason why he wants to keep it secret.
I just hope he found himself a girl.
A-A girl?
Satomi-san did!?
Yeah, he's going to go on a wonderful Christmas date with his girlfriend,
so he's working hard at his job.
How wonderful. Someone's growing up!
He promised that he'd practice as soon as the script was done.
Her Highness is working so hard, and yet...
He's all lovey-dovey... with a girlfriend.
Um, Ruth-san...
I'm back.
Welcome back, Koutarou.
It must be cold out.
It was freezing out there.
Oh, we're having stew today?
That's nice.
I'm back.
Oh, Ruth-san.
Satomi-sama, could you explain yourself this instant?
Huh?
No, I'm trying to tell you...
It's only a three day part-time job.
I'll keep lunches open for practice.
It's not like there's some special reason I didn't talk about the job I was taking.
Why did you have to get a new job, anyway?
Yeah. It's suspicious.
Well, I kind of needed some money for New Year's.
Is that really the only reason?
I don't believe it.
Huh?
Well...
There's no point in hiding it any longer, Koutarou.
Huh?
Everyone already knows,
so there's no reason to hide it.
Right?
Actually, Koutarou and I have promised to go on a date for Christmas.
Koutarou's working so he can pay for me.
You're so cruel!
You have Sakuraba-senpai too!
No, um, well...
Satomi-sama...
Her Highness has stayed up so many nights for the play, and yet you...
What a ridiculous façade.
It's obviously a lie.
I don't sense anything
mischievous from you two.
You two have seemed like fast friends since the amusement park.
Goodness, everyone's gotten a lot sharper.
Well, who cares about the job?
We'll practice hard during winter break.
Got it?
Y-Yeah, leave it to me!
Anyway, let's eat!
Oh, we don't have a ladle.
I'll go—
Thank you, Kiriha-san.
You helped me out.
No problem.
I wish you would have told me first, though.
Huh?
Anyway, let's eat.
It looks great!
Let's eat!
All my power's being sucked out...
Brother!
Hotpot really is the best in the winter!
Meat! Where's the meat!?
Come on, Koutarou. Let's eat!
Koutarou, I got you some.
Thanks!
Hey, Koutarou. Don't get it everywhere.
Your Highness...
Brother, switch with me.
N-No, thanks.
All right.
That's a nice tree.
Oh, Sakuraba-senpai.
I was able to get it with my pay from yesterday.
Kinda pricey, though.
I see.
I brought these from home, so feel free to use them.
Thank you. You're a lifesaver!
I want to see the smiles on everyone's faces.
Yeah.
Please keep it secret until then, though.
Of course.
It's a surprise party, after all.
Everyone, make sure you keep yourselves in line during the holiday season.
And then it was Christmas Eve,
the day of the closing ceremony.
See you next semester!
Have a happy New Year.
Merry Christmas.
What? A surprise Christmas party?
Yeah.
I was thinking of holding it in the Knitting Club room.
I'm having Sakuraba-senpai help me out, but...
You're not going to ask me to help out too, are you?
You should have asked earlier!
I need more people.
Please!
All you have to do is get everyone to come.
Please?
I have my complaints,
but I'll do it out of the kindness of my heart.
I owe you one!
Okay, see you at the club room at 3 pm!
Huh?
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Theia
Ruth-san
Landlady
Yurika
Theia
Ruth-san
Yurika
Theia
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Huh? Who's Sanae?
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Yurika
Sanae
Kiriha-san
Looks like your guess was wrong.
It wasn't for a girl, after all.
I guess I was just hoping things were finally going somewhere for him.
Who would've thought...
Yeah.
So what are you planning?
Well, I'll help, of course.
But I'll make sure it turns out interesting.
That took a while.
I need to pick up the cake too.
Satomi-kun!
Oh, Senpai!
Are you done setting up the room?
It's terrible.
Come quickly!
Huh?
Sumo!
Knitting Society
Kamibasami attack!
Fullback!
What's going on!?
U-Um, I don't really know either.
Knitting Society
Did they get the wrong room?
W-Well, it seems like they got
permission to use this room.
Wh-What? How!?
Anyway, let's prepare
another room, Satomi-kun.
Yeah, but we don't have much time.
How about your apartment?
Huh?
I see.
Room 106, huh?
Sorry, Senpai, I'll be going ahead.
Please come later!
Okay, I will!
Yeah, I shouldn't have tried to act cool
and just had this party at my apartment from the start.
That's where I met all of them.
I think I met Sanae first.
She's like my little sister now.
I've gotten used to her clinging to me and going into my body.
Theia's grown up quite a bit.
She's a lot kinder and more straightforward than she was when I first met her.
I wouldn't mind serving under her now.
Ruth-san is very dedicated.
I'm glad she's around.
If Ruth-san wasn't here, I don't think things would have have gone well with Theia.
I thought that Yurika was
completely unreliable at first,
but she's surprisingly committed.
Yurika
I don't get bored with her around.
Since that amusement park was invaded,
I feel like I can really talk to Kiriha-san.
Kiriha-san said that we're best friends now.
I wanted to show them how I felt.
There wasn't really any reason to keep it a surprise.
It would have been enough to just have fun with everyone.
Merry Christmas!
Koutarou's surprised!
We got him!
It went better than expected.
Our plan wins!
You're too easy, Satomi-san.
You still have a long way to go, Koutarou.
Sorry for surprising you, Satomi-sama.
This is...
Kurano-san and the others figured out what you were planning!
Makkenji!
You betrayed me!
No, they asked me first.
I didn't betray anyone!
No, you're the one who called all those athletes, right!?
That was me.
I had Sakuraba-senpai help too.
I-I'm sorry, Satomi-kun.
They convinced me it'd be more fun this way.
N-No fair...
Actually, you guys...
Come on!
Don't get so mad, Koutarou.
You were trying to do the same thing, you know?
Yeah. Hoisted by your own leotard.
It's "petard!"
What was the point of me working?
Koutarou.
We brought the tree you got with your earnings.
The Harukaze Pastry Studio Christmas cake is here too!
Cheers!
What would you like, Harumi-senpai?
Thank you very much.
Everything looks great.
I don't know where to start.
Thank you.
These are really good.
Did you make all of this by yourselves?
Yeah.
Jeez, you guys got me good.
Koutarou, I want some chicken!
Oh, sure.
Yay!
That looks great.
Koutarou, what are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I'm going to dig in!
In the end...
It feels like these invaders invaded my heart
instead of the apartments.
We had fun today.
Yeah, it sure was fun being surprised.
Come on, Satomi-kun.
I already apologized for that.
No way, I'm going to remember that forever.
Harukaze
Park
But Santa feels differently.
Harukaze
Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, if it isn't Santa.
We meet again.
Yes, and I have a present for a good girl this time.
Harukaze
Thank you.
Park
May I open it now?
Ho, ho, ho.
Of course.
It's nothing special,
but you can use it right now.
Harukaze
Was this the piece you
knitted at the beginning?
Harukaze
That's right.
So it might be a bit rough here, but...
Harukaze
I wanted you to have my first project.
Sorry for giving you this as my present.
No, I'm really happy.
This will bring back lots of memories for me.
Does it suit me?
It doesn't.
You should have gotten a better muffler.
That's enough.
Why are you talking back to your princess?
Princess Alaia, forgive me.
As long as you understand.
Allow me to give this to you.
Lord Veltorion, this sword will protect you
from any enemy you may face
or from any hardship.
Then I shall protect you with my life and this sword,
Princess Alaia.
Koutarou.
You still haven't remembered, have you?
But that's all right.
You still have places you need to be,
and people you need to meet.
After endless days and nights and distance, someday, again...
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
ano ne ima no koto
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
in his heart
seifuku no poketto
My true intentions peek out
honne o shinobasete
from my uniform's pocket
sotto eri o tadasu
I calmly fix my collar
Harukaze
Shopping
District
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
sonna kantan ni wa
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
and annoying
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
massugu de
so direct
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
nibui ne
yet so dull
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jouken chiratsukase
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
I think we can both win here
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
torihiki shiyou yo
so let's make a deal
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
The Silver Princess and
the Blue Knight
Part 2
Performance Today
G-Guys, are you all ready?
Yes, Your Highness.
Everything's perfect.
The dragon's great too.
You can relax a bit more, Theia.
It'll be fine.
R-Right.
If you forget a line, I'll help you out.
All right, guys,
we're going to make this play happen!
It's the last episode of Mahou Shoujo Love Love Heart.
Too bad!
I'm sad.
I loved everyone.
I know. It's sad.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
The
End
!?
See you again.