It's morning.
Yeah...
We couldn't get any sleep after all of that.
With things like that happening...
What are you going to do?
About today's "Minorin is Scared and a Knight Appears" plan.
If we're this frightened, can we even scare Kushieda?
You talk too much.
If we don't do it, our futures won't change.
That's true, but...
What shall we do?
Something that will scare Minorin...
Something that will scare Kushieda... What's that?
Y-You're up early, Kitamura!
What are you two scheming so early in the morning?
S-Scheming?
Was it your handiwork that got Kushieda all excited yesterday?
I thought so.
Why would you do that?
I feel sorry for Kushieda!
No, that's...
It's a present!
A present?
Actually, Minorin likes horror stuff more than her daily meals.
She said she loves being surprised and scared, so to make some great summer memories...
Hey, Kitamura...
I got it!
No wonder Kushieda's eyes were sparkling so much even though she was frightened.
Alright! Let me join you!
Working together,
let's really give Kushieda the fright of her life!
But...
Yeah, let's get Ami in on it too!
Stupid Chihuahua too?
She knows the area really well too.
Alright! Good things should be done quickly!
But Kawashima probably wouldn't want to...
Leave it to me!
I'll definitely convince her.
Relax!
What are we going to do?
Do?
What can we do?
Seaweed...
Oh my!
I was thinking of making breakfast, but I guess I was too late.
Good morning, Takasu-kun!
Hey...
What are you making?
Lunch.
They said we would spend the whole day at the beach.
You got up early to make that for us?
This won't do!
Chef, please let me assist you!
Your orders, please!
Then, could you slice the onions?
Yes! I'd be delighted to slice the onions!
What is today's menu?
Egg sandwiches and tuna sandwiches and then, using the leftover curry, potage... I think.
That sounds great!
You really cut well, Kushieda!
You're complimenting me?
Along with yesterday's dishwashing, you're really skilled!
Both of my parents work.
When my younger brother was at home, I made lunch too.
You have a younger brother?
He's a hard working high school student, Akechi-kun.
Ow, it got in!
Hey, are you okay?
I messed up!
Takasu-kun?
I need to peel the apples...
You're really good at cooking.
Yesterday's curry was great too.
I didn't do anything that great...
I think it's great that you do those things properly.
I bet the kids in class don't know this side of Takasu-kun.
I feel sort of superior to them now.
The girl who becomes your wife will be happy.
Kushieda!
What? Takasu-kyun!
About yesterday...
About that...
Please don't tell anyone about it.
I've never told anyone about that.
I mean... It just kind of... Slipped out.
But I'm glad it was you who I told it to.
Thanks for listening to me.
Crap!
You're clumsy! Isn't that cute?
Don't call me cute!
Just kidding!
Chef, what shall I do next?
Let's see...
Shall I stir? Round and round!
The sun is strong again today!
Let's go!
Minorin's energetic...
Okay, all that's left is to do it according to the plan.
Where's Kawashima?
She's going to help, right?
Yeah! She told me where to find a nearby cave, so we're going to set the traps there.
Then without her, we can't do anything.
What's she doing?
Don't know...
I'll go get her.
Taiga, I'll leave this with you.
Hey!
Here.
I'll carry it.
It's too heavy for a girl, right?
I-It's okay.
I'm fine.
Kawashima? Are you in there?
Yeah, I'm in here.
Everyone already left.
What're you...
I was just admiring myself.
Do you want to look too?
You're really...
Hey, hey, isn't this almost dangerous?
What do you think about this cleavage?
Isn't it fine?
That's it?
Well, you already saw it when I wore a bikini at school.
It's not that.
But you can take this off.
See!
Put it back! Put it back!
Then you do it.
No way!
You're so cold.
If you're going to be like that, I won't help you out.
Don't... Say that.
Hey...
Why do you want to make Minori-chan happy?
W-Why...
If you don't tell me, I won't help you.
You have five seconds.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Are you sure?
Two...
One...
Zero.
I'm not helping.
Taiga!
Come at me!
C'mon! With all you've got!
It's cold!
What are they doing?
Hey, hey, why?
I don't feel like it.
If you're not there, we won't be able to get around inside the cave.
I drew you a map, didn't I?
Sorry, Yusaku, you're on your own. Good luck.
Hey...
No complaints, right?
It was your own choice.
Sorry, Takasu.
Ami suddenly...
It's okay.
I'll go with you.
It'd be tough by yourself, right?
But... If we both leave, she might get suspicious.
I'll be okay!
It'll work out somehow.
I've already got three prize-winning ideas for the traps.
Kushieda will be half-crazy with fear.
Really?
Hey!
Kushieda! Aisaka!
What?
I'm going to take a piss!
This is really yummy!
Takasu-kun, you're a genius at cooking!
No, you helped too.
Minorin did?
That's right!
Those eggs in that sandwich, I stirred them, round and round!
Having lunch while I'm not here?
Kitamura-kun!
What were you doing?
Loudly announcing, "I'm going to take a piss!" to girls.
Ah, sorry.
All ready.
What's this? What are you talking about?
Oh, Kushieda, actually...
Hey, Minori-chan.
Near the entrance, there's a really pretty cave.
A cave?
It's one of my favorite special places.
Special?
Won't you go there with me for a walk later?
A walk?
Great! I'll go! I'm excited!
Here?
Ami's favorite place to walk...
It's really got an atmosphere.
Right?
Alright! Let's go in.
B-But, it looks like something will appear...
An encounter with unidentified life forms?
If it's something alive, that would be fine but...
You're right. If we can, we should capture them alive.
Letting him help out was the right thing to do.
The way he coaxes her is cool.
Alright!
Let's go, Kitamura's exploration party!
We're going to go find the golden two-headed cobra!
It's dark! It's small! It's scary!
That sounds like a phrase you picked up from somewhere.
It's surprisingly big.
Around here it is.
Hey.
Don't lose your focus. We didn't come here just to scare Minorin.
You got it?
From here on out, the ceiling gets one level lower, so be careful.
Let's start with the first test.
What?
Fried tofu with oil.
I forgot.
Kitamura has a good brain, but...
He's a moron.
Don't badmouth Kitamura-kun!
Hey, isn't it kind of cold?
It's because we've gone deeper in.
Not like that, I mean...
What's wrong?
I smell ketchup.
Hey, what are you doing?
This.
Letters... In blood?
It says "Gyaaa".
This is the second...
He really is a moron.
D-Don't badmouth Kitamura-kun!
Don't sigh!
What's this?
Isn't this...
Hey, what's wrong?
Ta-Ta-Takasu-kun! That is?
No, well...
A woman's hair!
It's the curse of a heartbroken woman who died an untimely death after wandering into this cave and getting lost on her trip of grief!
No! Let me out!
Minorin, calm down.
Nice job, Takasu.
You set some too?
No...
My last trap is fifty meters ahead.
It'll be great!
Yeah...
Hey, Kushieda. Pull it together.
Kitamura-kun is really talented.
Minorin was really scared.
It wasn't Kitamura.
Of course, it's not me either.
T-Then!
This isn't a joke.
Like last night, this is real.
One, two, three, four...
Minorin!
It's dangerous alone, so let's hold hands!
Really? Let's hold hands, all the way!
Alright, my body's warmed up, let's go forward!
Um, hey...
This is so dumb.
I'm taking this shortcut and going home first.
Hey, Kawashima!
Where are you going?
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun...
Are we still going deeper?
The exit is this way.
Right, Ami?
Where's Ami and Takasu?
Ryuji?
Wait, Kawashima!
Do you really know how to get out?
Of course!
Are you really so worried to be separated from everyone?
I'm not really good with dark places...
Then...
If I left you here, what would you do?
Scared?
Worried if you were separated from me?
Lonely?
Would you think that you wouldn’t want to be separated from me?
H-Hey.
Need me?
This isn't the time for that.
Do you want to quickly go back to where Minori-chan is?
I'm saying...
I don't think that girl suits you.
I... Not really...
The one who suits you is...
What?
Huh?
Where are we?
What?!
I can't believe it, we're lost.
Hey, hey, you're joking right?
Even if I were joking, I wouldn't say something like this!
W-What should we do?
Hey...
I-It's okay!
Kitamura and the others will definitely come looking for us.
Don't be scared.
I'm here!
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to apologize!
Being lost...
I lied.
There's no way I'd get lost!
Silly.
Ow, ow!
Ew, Takasu-kun, it's slimy.
This is not the time to be laughing!
But you looked like a little kid!
I was really scared!
Takasu-kun...
You really are a helpless guy.
You, again...
But, that part of you...
I don't dislike.
Just now, I said you wouldn't suit Minori-chan, right?
I was serious.
Because, you are the Moon.
What's with that?
Minori-chan is the Sun.
If you stay by her side,
you would completely burn up and disappear.
After all, you can't do stuff like hit her.
If you only admire her, you'll never be her equal.
You can only be equals with someone like me...
Just now...
That was Kushieda's voice!
Wait, Takasu-kun!
Sorry, I...
It's okay.
Let's hurry!
Yeah!
Kushieda!
Ryuji!
Takasu! Ami!
You're safe!
Kitamura, where's Kushieda?
What happened?
That's...
Kushieda... By something...
What do you mean "something"?
I don't know.
But something is there.
Kushieda might have been taken by that something?
Out of batteries?
Takasu, lend me yours.
What is that sound?
A voice?
Kushieda!
I'm coming!
Hey, Kitamura!
Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun!
What is this!
Everyone stay together!
Let's calm down!
Whatever! I'll do anything then!
Taiga!
There's a problem!
Let's rescue Taiga!
Roger!
Are you okay, Aisaka?
Kita... Kitamura-kun?
Kitamura?
You were late, Akechi-kun.
K-Kushieda?
Correct. I am Kushieda Minori.
Nickname: Minorin.
The culprit is me!
My accomplice is this guy.
The hair in Takasu's room...
The messed up clothes in Taiga's room...
That was all our handiwork, plus a few others!
We are very sorry.
Your method for scaring me was too soft.
So I wanted to teach you, "This is how you scare people!"
You mean... You knew?
Because you two were being so secretive.
So, I got Kitamura-kun to help me try to scare you instead.
But it was fun! Thanks.
You're not mad?
I won't!
I love horror!
It's like making a steamed dumpling of fear.
Ghosts are scary! The occult is scary!
If I say stuff like that, someone will definitely try to scare me.
Then I eat it all up.
Now, the explanations are over!
It got lit!
It's pretty!
Today was really something.
You're right.
They really got us.
What you were saying earlier...
Since I didn't respond properly...
I'd be lonely if you weren't here.
But it's not about whether I'd be lonely or not.
Rather, isn't it about whether or not you would be lonely?
I've never thought about whether I'd be lonely or not.
Then think about it... Properly.
Isn't that tough?
If it gets tough, then you should just express that, honestly.
After all, we're...
Equals?
Hey...
Takasu-kun...
Because, sometimes you're kind.
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
It's the last night! Have some fun.
Kushieda...
Hey...
Thanks.
I was completely fooled, and really scared.
But it's fun being with you.
Whatever the situation.
That's my line.
I really had fun.
And the curry was delicious.
And you listened to my weird story without laughing.
You understood what I was trying to say.
I'm sorry for scaring you.
I wanted to show you a ghost and I got carried away.
Show me?
Because you said you wanted to see one.
Takasu-kun, why did you want to scare me?
That's...
Because Taiga told me you couldn't stand horror stuff.
"Let's play a joke on her!" Like that?
That's not right.
You would never do anything to someone that they would hate.
Because you're the kind of guy who's always thinking of how to make people happy.
So why would that Takasu-kun do that kind of thing?
I really want to know.
I really think it's a mystery.
I wanted to show you... Ghosts.
I wanted to make you believe that ghosts exist.
It's too soon to give up just because you can't see them.
That's what I was thinking.
I see.
Takasu-kun, next time, let's look for a UFO.
Not an artificial satellite, but the real thing.
After a UFO... Let's see.
Maybe a Tsuchinoko.
If I keep searching and finding the things I want to see, if my world starts changing, then...
Kushieda!
It exploded. The UFO.
It's like a dream!
The galatic war begins!
We shall protect the Earth!
Our trip isn't over until we get home.
Don't relax too soon!
Maybe I should just go straight to my parent's house.
See you later!
Let's stop by a supermarket, do some shopping, and then go home.
I'm really tired right now, so don't talk to me about that kind of stuff like some housewife.
Okay, okay...
Hey, there's a special sale today.
I said be quiet.
Cultural Festival.
Getting into the spirit with the band's performance.
Your heart beating fast at the cosplay cafe.
Becoming friends around a campfire.
Becoming embarrassed by pro wrestling!
What are you scheming?