Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
I'll dispense you with the face of mask
kamen no kao de tebanasu no da
We meet only to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume nomama tabitatou
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru utakanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
The water doesn't look too murky.
We're gonna dive, Akari.
I can't tell how far away the exit is.
I am steel.
This is...
The end of the road for you.
Brother Shin?
Are you... Brother Shin?
Why are you here?
Are you in the tournament, too?
Are you after the remains?
I'm not like you.
You're not working for Hartgen, are you?
You still haven't gotten the idea?
I told you... You're not cut out to be a saboteur.
That's for me to decide!
Black Agenda
Toru! Akari!
I have report.
What's up?
Niva fled. Unknown person took away.
Guy? Why would he take her?
Details unknown. Niva, no fear.
What relationship with unknown person?
When we met Guy at the beach and he saw Niva,
he said, "So it was you all who got her."
He must have known that Niva was a weapon.
I always thought he seemed shady...
If Hartgen has the last remains, we have no need for Guy.
Chaika, don't talk to him anymore.
Right.
Find remains location?
Sorry. We didn't find anything.
Explain situation.
We ran into the worst enemy possible.
It seems our mentor is working for Hartgen.
Shocking truth! Fight with mentor?
You don't need to worry.
It's not unusual for saboteurs to become
enemies in battle if they have different employers.
Brother and I have long been prepared for that.
Even if Brother were to become my enemy,
I'm prepared to have him lick my feet and beg for his life
as I beat him, bind him, and drip candle wax on him.
That has nothing to do with a saboteur's resolve.
Toru...
Chaika, do you have enough magic fuel?
Yes. Have plenty.
Good. It wouldn't be funny if we ran out of ammo.
And no using your memories in place of magic fuel, okay?
No worry.
From the look of things, it won't matter who wins the tournament,
I don't think Hartgen intends to give away the remains.
Either way, Chaika and I will enter the tournament as planned,
rise through the ranks, and get close to the remains.
Akari, as soon as it starts,
you and Fredrica find your way into the castle and search for the remains.
If you find them, steal them.
Isn't that just dragging things out?
Toru, can't we just form a contract, beat up the other fighters,
then bust into the castle and take the remains?
No, we don't know the inside of the castle,
and we don't know how strong our enemies are.
It's dangerous to let you run wild.
Aww. What a pain.
The remains probably aren't underground anymore.
Search for them again while we have time.
Right.
Come forth, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Remains, likely, top of castle.
This is the emperor's fortune?
It's not what I imagined at all.
I don't know what you two were imagining,
but that is indeed what this is.
She becomes a weapon?
At the right time, and when the conditions are met,
it is indeed capable of plunging the world into war again.
Conditions...
Those should all come together during this tournament.
Then you have no need to worry.
All because I've had your help.
It has taken a long time...
You have no idea how long I've waiting for war to begin again.
It is ironic, isn't it?
The one who cut off Emperor Gaz's head
and brought an end to 300 years of war,
was none other than you.
Yes... I was foolish.
Back then, I made an irreversible mistake.
Victory is ours!
Yeah!
I should never have ended the war.
Battle is what gave purpose to our lives.
Come, you two.
I can't wait to see your true form.
Listen to me!
The match will soon begin.
There are two battlefields within the second castle wall,
and another within the third.
Only the victors in this battle
will be permitted to enter the castle.
You must defeat three opposing teams,
and take their arm bands as proof of your victory.
Give the armbands you've collected to the guard at the checkpoint.
Those who rank highest may proceed to the next phase.
Devote all your strength to this battle!
King Hartgen will now deliver an address.
I know that all of the warriors gathered here today have not forgotten their pride.
What do you feel in this world that has been immersed in
peace for these five years since the war?
Do you not feel aggrieved to live in a world in which you cannot use
the strength and techniques you honed in battle?
I will transform this tedious world!
This continent needs an absolute ruler.
I will take on that role,
and create a world in which warriors can live as warriors!
I will use my power to seize this continent!
Warriors, those who sympathize with me,
demonstrate your strength to your hearts' content in this tournament!
He wants war, too?
Any who are weak, leave now!
Any who can fight, show me your strength!
Such fools.
Well, no matter. They are Father's playthings.
My wish is...
Dear Sister.
This is where you were?
Yes.
Three this year...
No, more accurately, two and a half.
Yes.
Tell the guards
to come up with some arbitrary reason to bring the Chaikas to me.
You're going to make them fight?
How fun!
Aren't you curious to see which is strongest?
Begin!
Let's go.
Right.
The Shield!
Great job, Chaika.
Yes! Claudia's advice, useful!
Yeah.
Long time, no see.
I thought you'd be here.
You're...
Silver hair... Purple eyes...
Don't say any more than that.
A lot has happened to us.
Why are you guys here?
To capture all of you.
We've infiltrated this castle and are investigating.
When we're done, we'll capture you, so be ready.
But what about you? Why are you fighting?
Goal, win tournament prize.
You're not working with Hartgen?
You took the emperor's fortune from his lab
and brought it to Hartgen, didn't you?
The emperor's fortune?
Don't play dumb!
We know the white Chaika took his fortune, the Gundo, from that lab.
Gundo?
Niva?
She was the fortune?
As I suspected. So where is she?
Niva left with unknown person.
Who's this "unknown person"?
Some shady bastard called Guy.
Did you say Guy?
You know him?
He called me "Chaika."
He seemed to know about the Chaikas.
Unknown person brings me information about remains.
What exactly is he?
I'm not sure.
He shows up out of nowhere and then disappears, like a ghost.
I figured he must be under someone's orders.
Like who?
He had opportunities to take Niva,
but for some reason, the moment we entered this castle,
that's when he took her.
So I suspect Guy is connected to Hartgen.
Did you know that there are twin black Chaikas with Hartgen?
Uh-huh?
Black Chaika exists?!
You didn't know?
Perhaps Hartgen is working with
the black Chaikas to gather the remains, just like you.
Don't think you can get away from us!
Come forth, to strike and crush!
The Slugger!
Toru?
Twin black Chaikas...
What is he after?
Hard to believe he's been doing this for five years.
What sort of man is Hartgen?
I don't know.
I heard he was the man who beheaded the emperor and his daughter.
I didn't see it, though.
I suppose he must have been a worthy fighter.
Given that he holds martial arts tournaments like this,
Hartgen must be unhappy with the fact that the war ended.
Who knows?
What about you, Akari?
Well, I'm...
Die!
Let's hear the report from the Kliemann Organization.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to have my aide,
Miss Bombardier, deliver our report from the Gillette Squad.
We've located Emperor Gaz's secret lab on a remote island
in the waters off the port town of Waronti.
There was a powerful Gundo there that
we assumed to be the emperor's fortune,
but the white Chaika had already taken it from the lab.
What?
This is merely speculation,
but we believe Chaika has fled to the Principality of Hartgen.
She's taking the Gundo to the Principality of Hartgen?!
We can't delay any longer!
We must deal with this now!
Chief Konrad.
Did the King of Hartgen accept your request to
cancel the martial arts tournament?
I believe the Gillette Squad will report to us shortly regarding that.
You're being too complacent.
We should send an army immediately!
My nation would rather not send out any more soldiers.
Then make them contribute weapons or war funds!
Now, wait a moment. Are you dead set on starting a war?
If you attack the Principality of Hartgen,
the adjoining nations will suffer great losses.
We need to think of the continent as a whole right now!
It's plain as day that we cannot just set Hartgen aside!
I agree.
I've heard rumors that forty to fifty thousand soldiers have gathered in the Principality of Hartgen.
No, I find it hard to believe that he has expanded his army
that much in five years since the war.
Regardless, we should avoid
recklessly starting a war or shedding blood in vain.
We should await the Kliemann Organization's report
and reach a decision under the consensus of the entire allied army.
Investigations by our spies have revealed
that the tournament has already begun.
I see...
The Kliemann Organization is too slow.
That man, Fyodor, who took over General Cizeta's position, is too cautious, as well.
Can we afford to be so complacent?
That's what I'd like to speak to you about.
We will contribute wizards and magic fuel to the cause.
Are you asking my nation to send our floating fortress Cima?
Yes. I believe it is necessary to prepare it.
What is this?
The report from the force that subjugated Emperor Gaz,
and a blueprint of a floating fortress that we found in our library.
However, it's over a hundred years old.
A hundred years?
I can't believe that even the Gaz Empire
could have had such advanced technology that long ago...
Yes. But according to the Gillette Squad's report,
several structures resembling this were seen
near the Gaz Empire border nearly a hundred years ago.
The people who saw them called them "overnight castles."
It seems the magical technology of the Gaz Empire exceeded our expectations...
General Fyodor,
many details on Chaika and Emperor Gaz have remained obscure,
and they have been disparaged by the Council of the Six Nations.
But my men have devoted their sincerest efforts to this matter.
Chaika was involved in the Soara incident.
And now, if Chaika is making her way to King Hartgen...
I have met King Hartgen in the past.
He gave me the impression of an honest man...
Enter.
Pardon me. We've received word from the Gillette Squad.
When Matheus and Zita requested the return of the remains and cancellation of the tournament,
King Hartgen placed them in confinement.
Uh-huh?
It also says the white Chaika and red Chaika are in the tournament...
And that there are two girls with King Hartgen
who are believed to be Chaikas.
There were already Chaikas there...
Does this mean King Hartgen also wishes for war?
What is next battle?
This way.
This tournament's surprisingly easy, huh?
Go.
What you do?!
What's the idea?!
Your team violated the rules.
Violated rules?
Your teammate was using probing magic in the barracks
to locate the emperor's remains.
Selma...
Keep walking forward.
That's where your next fight will be.
Let out!
Darn.
We have no choice but to go forward.
Your team may advance to the next battlefield.
To win here, you must defeat two opposing teams.
Those who win, in the same manner as in the previous battle,
are to take the arm bands from the losers.
No one here has any backbone.
It's not the tournament participants we're up against.
It's the guys inside the castle.
Oh, yeah! The guy you and Toru called your mentor is there, right?
That'll be exciting.
Come forth, swirling vortex!
The Tornado!
Come forth, that which bursts and scatters its mark!
The Burster!
Defeat, success!
To a degree, I expected it,
but if there are black Chaikas in the castle,
they'll be trying to gather the remains, too.
This isn't just a matter of stealing remains from heroes anymore.
Yes.
This means, even if we try to steal them,
they might try to steal the remains we have, too.
And they've got Brother Shin, which makes things tough for us.
But I think we should strike first.
Is that all right?
Of course. Must get remains.
Twin black Chaikas, curious.
But, want to overcome crisis with Toru.
I will finish! I must!
The sky is overcast
The bell rings to signal the beginning
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
noroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
The time has come to break a curse
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
kono inochi kono ai mo
This life and this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
Martial arts tournament, finally starting!
Will participate, do my best!
But, feel eyes watching me, somewhere.
Who? What is goal?
Mystery deepens...
The Bells of Contention
Next time: "The Bells of Contention."