[HOMUNCULUS] Don't you even
want freedom... Hohenheim?
Are you going to live out
the rest of your life
as a slave, without the
rights of a real man?
In that case, you're
no different from me,
trapped inside
this stuffy flask.
[ED]
Hyaaaaa!!
[thud]
[FATHER]
I don't understand!
[DARIUS] Alright...!
Clobber that bastard!
[FATHER]
How can this happen
when I've absorbed God...?
How can a mere human...
A meager alchemist...
With his bare hands...
[FATHER]
Oof!
[panting]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
He did it!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS 2] He saved us!
The little runt saved us!
[cheering]
[high-pitched scream]
[GREED] Pull yourself
together, damn it!
Stay on your feet, moron!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS 3]
Uh... Sorry.
[FATHER]
A Stone...
Philosopher's Stonnnne!
[FATHER] Give me
your stone, Greed...!
Be a good son!
[GREED]
Dammit, no!
[LING]
Fight it, Greed!
[GREED]
Let go, dumbass...!
You're gonna get
dragged in with me!
[LING]
No way...!
I'm not letting
you go that easily...
I need you with me if
I'm gonna be emperor!
[GREED]
Just let go...!
My entire being was
extracted from his greed...!
And the power that's
trying to reclaim me
is a hell of a lot
stronger than your body!
[LING] You can't
just give up...!
Tough it out!
Oh, no!
[LING]
My body!
I won't let go!
[GREED]
Y'know...
It's not quite as ideal
as being king of the world...
but I can make do
with emperor of Xing.
[GREED] Let's fight
him together...
Eh, partner?
[LING]
That's more like it--
What are you...?
[GREED] It's time
to say goodbye, kid...
There's no point
in you getting sucked
into my old man with me.
[LING] Hold on
a second, Greed...!
You just told me
we'd fight together!
Didn't you...?!
You can't just
sucker punch me like that!
How could you lie...?!
You always said you don't
believe in telling lies...!
It can't end this way!
[GREED]
Hahahahaha!
You fell for it hook,
line, and sinker,
you little pissant!
[GREED] That was the one
and only lie of my life.
[GREED] Lan Fan has
a Philosopher's Stone...
So you don't even
need me anymore, kid.
[LING]
But I do...
[GREED]
Hahahaha!
[LING]
Wait, Greed.
[LING] No, wait...!
Don't do this!
[GREED]
Hey...! Lan Fan!
Later.
[LING]
Greed, no!
[ED]
No, Greed!
[FATHER]
How could you?!
Greed!
[GREED]
Muwahaha!
I finally got away
from that annoying brat.
[FATHER]
Why Greed...?!
Why would you betray
your own father?!
[GREED] I've always had
a rebellious streak, pops...
Don't act so surprised.
[GREED] I've reversed
the ultimate shield you gave me.
And transformed your body
into the most
fragile carbon there is!
[FATHER]
You crafty devil.
Be gone, fool...!
Return to nothing!
[LING]
Greed!
[GREED]
Ah, damn it...
Looks like this is the end.
[GREED] I could do
without that pitiful look
right now, you pissant.
[LING]
You're wrong, Greed...!
They'll always
be a part of you!
[LING] Friends are
a part of your soul!
[ED] Why don't
you team up with us?
[ED]
You've got nothing...
Why not come with us?
[GREED] I can't
believe I let Ling
and the little runt
talk to me that way.
[GREED]
I've had enough.
Yeah... That's
all I really need.
They gave me
everything I could want.
[GREED]
Thank you...
And goodbye... my friends.
[shattering sound]
[moaning crowd]
[HOHENHEIM]
That's it.
[FATHER]
My Stone...
You destroyed my Stone.
[FATHER] What...?
This can't...
What is this?
[ED] Go back
to where you were born...
Go back to nothing...
Homunculus!
[FATHER]
But why...?
I just wanted
to understand...
this world's knowledge!
[FATHER] I wanted
to experience it!
Free...! I just
wanted to be free!
Free to knowwww!
[HOMUNCULUS]
Tell me...
Why did you
refuse to join me?
Why, God...?!
How did I disappoint you?
[TRUTH] You were incapable
of believing in yourself.
[TRUTH] You stole your
power from others...
You rejected
your human origins...
and chose to covet
the power of what you call God.
[TRUTH] You never grew
beyond your days in the flask.
Did you truly think
you'd become superior
to humans by removing
your seven desires?
[TRUTH]
Don't make me laugh.
[HOMUNCULUS]
What's wrong with that...?
I only wanted
to obtain perfection...
I wanted this world's
knowledge for my own!
Why should
I be punished for that...?!
What's wrong with
craving knowledge...?
seeking perfection?!
Well, speak...!
What are you, anyway...?
Do you even have a name...?
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
[TRUTH]
Who am I?
One name you might have
for me is "the world"...
Or you might call
me "the universe"...
or perhaps "God"...
or perhaps "the truth"...
I am all...
and I am one...
So of course...
this also means
that I am you.
I'm the truth
of your despair...
the inescapable price
of your boastfulness.
[FATHER] Humans who
would dare to play god
must pay a steep price
for their arrogance...
[FATHER]
That is Truth.
[TRUTH]
And now...
I will bestow upon you
the despair you deserve.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Don't do this to me...
I can't... I can't go back!
Please, stop...!
I can't bear
to be bound any longer!
Ahhh!!
No...! No...! Nooo!
[TRUTH] This despair is
reserved for the boastful.
[HOMUNCULUS] Just tell me
what I was supposed to do!
[TRUTH] You brought
this outcome upon yourself.
[HOMUNCULUS]
What'd I do wrong?
What should I have done?!
[slam]
[TRUTH] You simply must
have seen the answer
with your own eyes.
[ROY]
What happened...?
Is it over...? Did we win?
[HAWKEYE]
Yes, sir... Although...
Alphonse hasn't returned
from the other side.
[MAY CHANG]
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
[ED] It's not
your fault, May...
It was Al's decision.
[LING] Ed...
I've got the toll for him!
Take it...
It's a Philosopher's Stone.
Use it to bring him back.
[ED]
I can't.
As much as
I want to, I can't...
I promised Al we'd never
use a Philosopher's Stone.
[ED] There has to be
a way to get him back...
There's gotta be...
Think, damn it...!
Think it through...
Just keep thinking!
[HOHENHEIM]
Edward.
Use my life for the toll...
Use me to save Alphonse.
I've got just
enough life left.
[ED] No way...!
I could never do that,
you dumb ass!
This doesn't have
anything to do with you...!
It's our own damn fault...!
I won't use another
human life to get Al back...!
And I don't care
whose it is...!
Why should you sacrifice
your life for our mistake?!
[HOHENHEIM]
Because I'm his father.
[HOHENHEIM] And that's
the only thing that matters.
You don't know how much
you boys mean to me...
And I just want
you to be happy.
And I do bear some
responsibility for this...
This might not have happened
if I'd just been
there for you...
I'm sorry, Ed.
[HOHENHEIM]
I've lived long enough.
Just give me
this chance...
to act like a father
for once in my life.
[ED] Shut up,
you rotten father!
You say something
that dumb again...
and I'll knock you out!
[HOHENHEIM]
I'm sorry...
Forgive me.
[ED] Now think...!
Come on...!
You're the youngest State
Alchemist in history, damn it!
You've even passed through
your own portal of truth
so you can transmute
with your bare hands...!
There's gotta be some way!
There has to be!
[HAWKEYE]
You better get to it...
You've got plenty of
people waiting for you
and your brother
to get your bodies back.
[ROY] If you believe
the possibility exists...
then you should do
whatever it takes.
[ED] Exactly...
I can't give up...
There has to be some way...
I know it...
I know there is.
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse.
[MAY CHANG] Oh, Al...
Poor Alphonse.
[ED]
May...
I didn't realize she
cared so deeply for Al.
[ED]
Zampano... Mr. Gorilla...
The Briggs Soldiers.
The Major.
Lan Fan... Ling
Teacher... Our Father.
[ED]
May.
Stand back a little.
[LING]
Is that?
[LING] It's a human
transmutation circle!
[ED] I'll be back
in a few minutes.
[ED] This is
my last transmutation...
Stand back and
enjoy the show!
[LING]
Stop, Ed!
[ZAMPANO] Elric!
[DARIUS] Elric!
[ARMSTRONG]
No, Edward Elric!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[TRUTH] I take it you're
here to retrieve your brother?
Just how do you
plan on pulling
an entire human
out of here...?
What's your payment...?
Do you intend to
offer your own body?
[ED] Yeah, I've got your
payment right here...
So go ahead and take it.
[ED] This thing is
my portal of truth.
So I get to make the
decision on how it's used...
That right?
[TRUTH]
Heh heh heh heh!
It's come to that?
And you're
sure about this?
You do realize that
you'll never be able
to perform alchemy again
without your portal?
[ED]
I'm aware of that.
This portal...
I know it contains every
secret alchemy has to offer...
However...
It's also led me astray.
[ED] I saw the truth
that lies within it...
And I became convinced
I could solve
everything with alchemy...
But I couldn't have
possibly been more wrong...
That was just arrogance.
[TRUTH] You're willing
to cast it aside...?
To lower yourself
to a simple human?
[ED] What do you
mean lower myself...?
That's the only
thing I've ever been...
Just a simple human that
couldn't save a little girl...
Not even with alchemy.
[TRUTH] You're sure you'll
be alright without it...?
Think carefully now.
[IZUMI]
Ed!
[ROY]
Fullmetal!
[HAWKEYE]
Edward!
[HOHENHEIM]
Ed!
[ARMSTRONG]
Edward Elric!
[LING]
Ed!
[MAY CHANG]
Edward!
[LAN FAN]
Ed!
[WINRY]
[ED] Who even
needs alchemy...
when I've got them?
[TRUTH/ED]
You've done it...!
That's the right answer!
[TRUTH/ED]
Good job... You beat me.
Go ahead...!
Take him home!
[TRUTH/ED] The back door's
right over there.
Goodbye, Edward Elric.
[ED]
That was crazy, Al.
[AL]
Speak for yourself.
[ED]
Now let's go home...
Together.
[ZAMPANO] Hey...!
He's waking up!
[DARIUS]
How're ya feeling...?
You okay?
[AL] Zampano...
and Darius...
You're all here.
[AL]
Dad!
[HOHENHEIM]
Hey...
Welcome back.
[AL]
Home at last.
It's so warm.
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse.
Alphonse!
[AL]
May!
[MAY CHANG sobbing]
I was... so scared!
[AL]
I bet... Sorry...
It was wrong of me to
put you through that.
It's okay now...
Thank you.
[BROADCASTER] You're
listening to Radio Capital.
To conclude our
coverage of today's events,
General Armstrong
and Colonel Mustang
have taken control
of Central Command
and successfully halted
the military coup de tat
perpetrated by
the senior staff.
[BROADCASTER]
The coup was centered
around an alchemic procedure
which would have sacrificed
the nation's population.
Details of the procedure
have yet to be released,
but General Cremin and
General Edison have been
apprehended as two of
the lead conspirators.
[BROADCASTER] All of
their opposing forces...
have now been disarmed.
[BROADCASTER]
Our Fuhrer, King Bradley...
and his son, Selim...
tragically lost their lives
amidst the day's turmoil.
[BROADCASTER] Colonel Mustang
released an official statement
that he would carry on
with the Fuhrer's wishes,
and that he would
personally oversee
all matters of
national security.
[HOMUNCULUS] You are the
one who gave me blood, right?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Don't you even want freedom?
Hohenheim?
[YOUNG HOHENHEIM]
Okay then,
what is it that
makes you happy?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Well...
I'd hate to be guilty
of asking too much,
but I think I'd be happy if I
could just leave this flask...
[HOHENHEIM]
You were born of my blood...
dwarf in the flask... Homunculus.
[HOHENHEIM]
In the end...
You and I were still as one...
And I'm...
[ARMSTRONG]
Mr. Hohenheim.
[ARMSTRONG] I personally
saw to it that your sons
were admitted to the hospital.
[HOHENHEIM]
Thank you.
I'm grateful for your help.
[ARMSTRONG]
Nonsense...
I'm the one who's
truly grateful.
[ARMSTRONG]
We're all in debt
to the efforts of
Edward and Alphonse...
Without those boys'
relentless courage...
this nation
would be no more...
Thank you very much.
[HOHENHEIM]
Thank you.
Hello, Trisha... I'm home.
So get this...
Ed actually called
me his father.
Although he did
preface it with "rotten."
Living through all of
these endless years...
I always felt like I'd
been struck with a curse.
But then I found you
and we had our sons...
and I suddenly felt blessed...
Grateful for the life I had.
I've had a fulfilling life...
Thanks to you...
It's been enough.
Thank you... Trisha.
But now...
Believe it or not,
I actually want
to keep on living.
I guess I'm pretty hopeless...
Aren't I, Trisha?
[PINAKO]
Hohenheim?
I didn't know
you were back.
Silly old fool.
Well, at least you
died with a smile
on your face, my friend.
[NARRATOR] There's no such thing
as an absolute and final ending,
for it is always followed
by a new beginning.
The future is yours
to shape as you wish.
Craft it with hope upon
a foundation of peace.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
The final episode:
"Journey's End."
Step forward. Embrace your life
and the world that nurtures it.