I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
With strong feelings,
I made a decision...
because I can kind of understand why
you wouldn't want to run away from this.
That's why we're having
our first and final true battle.
I'll bet everything on my magic!
And I'll tell you over and over,
because I want to see you smile.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Mother... my mother...
She was always so kind...
My mother...
The mother who'd call my name so gently...
Look! Isn't this really pretty, Alicia?
Alicia? No, Mother...
my name's Fate...
Come closer, Alicia.
There. You look cute, Alicia...
Well... I guess it's all right...
Because I love my gentle Mother, I will...
Episode 11
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
Memories That Lie Beyond Time.
Looks like the battle's begun...
Yeah.
But it's a little unusual for you to allow
that kind of gamble, Chrono-kun.
Well... it'd be for the best if Nanoha wins...
but either way, it won't really matter in the
grand scheme of things who falls first.
While Nanoha-chan is buying
us time during her battle,
I'm preparing to trace that girl
to find out where she came from.
I'm counting on you.
Don't let her get away this time.
Of course! Just leave it to me!
Huh?
But... is it really okay not to tell Nanoha-chan?
About Presea Testarossa's
family and that accident.
It'd be best if she wins this battle...
Right now, I don't want
Nanoha to have any hesitations.
Photon Lancer.
Divine Shooter.
Fire!
Shoot!
Scythe Form.
Round Shield.
Flash Move.
Take this!
Scythe Slash.
Fire.
When we first met, she was just a beginner
with strong magical powers, but now...
She's different from before...
so fast... and so strong.
If I hesitate now, I'll lose!
Phalanx Shift.
Lightning Bind!
This is bad! Fate's gotten really serious!
Nanoha! I'm going to support you!
No!
Arf-san, Yuuno-kun, please don't interfere.
This is a one-on-one fight to our limits.
This is our battle!
But it'll be bad if Fate's truly serious!
I'll be fine!
Arcus, Cultus, Aegeas...
Heavenly gods who shine over all,
descend upon us now as I guide you.
Baruel, Zaluel, Browzel...
Photon Lancer... Phalanx Shift!
Strike her down! Fire!
Nanoha!
Fate!
Of course the bind would wear off
after you finished your attack.
Now it's my...
Divine...
...turn!
...Buster.
A direct hit!
But I can endure it.
After all, that girl withstood my attack!
Fate...
See if you can take this variation of my Divine Buster.
Starlight Breaker.
A bind!
This is my full power, at full throttle!
Starlight... Breaker!
Wh-What an insane amount of mana!
Woah... can Fate-chan survive that?!
Fate-chan!
Are you all right, Fate-chan?
I'm sorry... are you all right?
Yeah...
I guess... I won, right?
It... looks that way...
Put Out.
Can you still fly?
All right, Nanoha. Secure the
Jewel Seeds, and bring her...
No... she's here!
Fate-chan!
Bingo! I've got her!
All right!
We may be fatally unprepared for
what's ahead, but get those coordinates.
Already got them,
sending them over now!
Armed Enforcers, start mobilizing
at the transport point!
Your mission is to take Presea Testarossa into custody!
Yes, ma'am!
As I thought... my body can't sustain
dimensional magic much longer...
And... my capture is imminent...
Fate... it appears that girl was a waste after all.
It might finally be time to set things in motion...
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Second Platoon, transport complete.
First Platoon, infiltration successful.
Good job.
And... Fate-san, it's a pleasure to finally meet you.
It'd be unbearable for her to
watch her mother get captured.
Nanoha-san, please take her to a different room.
O-Okay.
Fate-chan, if you'd like, why don't
you come to my room with–
All hands have successfully infiltrated the throne room.
We've located the target.
Presea Testarossa!
You have violated the laws of the TSAB.
For causing dimensional interferences and for attacking a Bureau warship,
you will be arrested!
Drop any weapons you may
have and come with us!
Cover that side!
Hey, over here!
Th-This is...!
Don't you dare come near my Alicia!
F-Fire!
You're quite irritating...
You're in danger! Pull back!
This is bad! Bring the Enforcers back immediately!
U-Understood!
Ali... cia...?
Fixed coordinates: 0120 503!
Affirmative! Stand by at Presea's location for transport!
It looks like everything might have
been in vain... we're out of time.
With only nine Lost Logia, we may not
be able to reach Al-Hazard, but...
But it's all right now.
I'll put an end to everything.
To all the time I've spent without her...
and to pretending that doll
I created was my daughter.
Are you listening?
I'm talking about you, Fate.
Even after I went to the trouble
of giving you Alicia's memories,
only your appearance is the same.
You were such useless, unusable scum... my little doll.
During the first incident,
Presea lost her real daughter...
Alicia Testarossa.
In the end, her research and expertise,
especially in the field of familiars...
allowed her to surpass familiars...
with the creation of artificial beings.
And also... the secrets of reincarnation.
The name "Fate" came from
the name of that research project.
You've certainly done your research.
You're right. It's just as you said.
But in the end, it was all worthless.
It didn't go even slightly as planned.
In the end, an artifical
life is just that, artificial.
It can't take the place
of something you've lost.
Alicia's smile was much sweeter than yours.
Alicia could even be selfish at times,
but she listened well
to what I told her.
Stop it...
Alicia was always so kind to me...
Fate, in the end, you really were
nothing but an imitation of Alicia.
Even after I gave you her precious
memories, you were no good.
Stop it... stop it!
You were nothing but a doll I made
to console me while I was working
on bringing Alicia back to life.
And that's why I no longer need you.
So just get out of my sight already!
Please, stop it already!
I'll tell you something good, Fate.
Ever since I created you, I've always...
despised you!
Fate-chan!
Fate...
The Enforcers have all been retrieved.
B-Big trouble! Take a look over here!
We're detecting a large
number of magical reactions!
What is it?! What's happening over there?!
The reactions in the Garden
of Time are all rated A class!
Total number of reactions...
sixty... no, eighty... and rising!
Presea Testarossa!
What are you planning?!
I don't want anyone to interrupt us on our journey.
We are leaving this place!
To the forgotten capital... Al-Hazard!
She wouldn't!
With their power... we will begin
this journey, and take it back...
We'll take it all back!
Dimensional distortion detected...
it's huge, well beyond our limits!
We need impact defense,
activate the Distortion Shield!
All nine Jewel Seeds have activated!
The dimensional distortion
is getting stronger!
Maintain transfer distance, but use evasive
maneuvers if you detect any feedback!
Understood!
Confirming more reactions!
At this rate, it'll become
a dimensional dislocation!
Al-Hazard...
Such a stupid thing to do!
Chrono-kun?!
I'm going to stop her! Open a gate!
The forgotten capital... Al-Hazard...
The land where forbidden
technology slumbers...
What do you plan on doing there?!
Do you really think you can recover your lost past?!
No matter what kind of magic you use,
you can never... bring back the past!
At Al-Hazard, Alicia and I... will reclaim the past we lost!
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
We couldn't stop the
dimensional distortion...
In order to
stop Presea,
we all head towards
the Garden of Time!
Nanoha's world...
our world...
in order to stop their
destruction and many others...
And also, at the
same time, Fate has...!
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 12
When Our Fates Are Sealed
Episode Twelve:
When Our Fates Are Sealed.
Lyrical Magical,
until the very end, for sure...!