Ta-da!
Here we have a Phantom!
Y-Yato?!
Good. That reaction will do just fine!
It's easier to draw borderlines with hate and fear.
Borderlines?
A borderline serves as a
Regalia's shield and only weapon.
You did pretty well the other day, so I think you're ready to learn how to make one.
F-Flattery won't get you anywhere.
First, put your middle and index fingers together like this,
then try drawing a line
between you and the Phantom.
O-Okay.
A...
line!
Wow!
This is a borderline?!
Yup. It's basically a barrier
that Regalia can create.
Phantoms can't pass through it.
Can you do this too?
C-Can I?!
You and I can't.
The ability to create
borderlines is a Regalia power.
Any Regalia can make them,
but creating one this strong on the first try?
Out of all the Regalia I know, this is the first time I've seen something like this.
All the Regalia he knows...
Um, that girl you called
"Nora" is a Regalia too, right?
Oh, her?
She's...
a friend with benefits.
Huh?
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
I'm going to look after Yukine-kun!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
There's no way you could handle him.
No, there's no way you can handle him.
You don't even have a place to live or anything close to a stable life!
What with your ex-girlfriends, your affairs, and your friends with benefits!
Your depravity knows no end!
You're unfit to be his guardian!
Yukine-kun's better off staying with me!
Get away from her!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
I'm tingling all over the place!
Get your clammy hands off of him!
Can't you see he doesn't like it?!
Just look! I'm getting all tingly! Really tingly!
Sheesh!
What's your problem?!
I already told you!
Whenever an indecent thought pops into his head, I end up in a world of pain!
Indecent?
Oh, come on!
A boy and a girl living in the same house?!
Yukine's guaranteed to have
dirty thoughts in that situation!
That's why he absolutely cannot stay with you!
We all know the one with dirty thoughts here is a certain someone in sweats.
Yukine-kun's a good boy.
There's nothing to worry about!
Come with me, Yukine-kun!
Don't do it, Yukine!
Chapter
Borderline
Your house is huge.
Do you come from a
super rich family or something?
Don't be silly.
I'm just an ordinary middle schooler.
This doesn't seem very "ordinary" to me.
Hey, where are your parents?
Lucky for us...
They'll be coming home late tonight.
Huh?! Y-You mean it's just you and m—
Yukine! Shush!
Welcome home, Hiyori-chan.
S-Sasaki-san.
I'm back.
I've prepared the bath.
You can use it whenever you're ready.
Whoa! Awesome!
Feel free to use this room, Yukine-kun.
Huh? Are you sure?
Isn't this your room?
No, it's my brother's.
Brother?
He's a lot older than me.
But he doesn't live here anymore, so don't worry about it.
Huh...
I didn't know you had a big brother.
My room's right next door,
so let me know if you need anything.
Well, see you in a bit!
Okay.
Hiyori sure has it good.
Just as planned!
It looks like nobody's gonna notice!
Not our housekeeper nor my parents!
Oh! Welcome—
We're home!
We picked up a cake, Hiyori!
Mind if I have an after-work drink, honey?
Well, if you must!
Now this is what I live for!
Now for some snacks.
Wait, Dear.
Have you washed your...
Dear!
You should know better than to
grab whatever you want like that!
Oh, I couldn't help myself.
Your mom's pretty sharp.
What are you doing here?!
Gimme a break.
What's the harm if they don't notice me?
It ruins the whole point of me looking after Yukine-kun!
Hiyori.
How's he feel about this?
He's delighted, of course.
Now he doesn't have to sleep in
the first shrine he finds, unlike you.
Unlike this house, shrine grounds and their buildings are sacred territory.
They keep us safe from Phantom attacks.
Even so...
The night is when the Phantoms
that lurk in the darkness come out.
It's a time of devilry.
I don't think he'll be able to handle it.
Huh?
You see, Yukine...
He's...
afraid of the dark.
It's been, like, forever
since I last had a warm bath.
I wonder what he'll do
if I don't go back to him.
Will he use that girl or something?
Then what'll happen to me?
Huh?
Why does this smell seem familiar?
Wait, don't tell me...
Hi-Hiyo... Hiyo...
Did Hiyori use this bath right before me?!
Oh!
Guess I forgot to grab it after my bath!
Hey, Hiyori!
I'm done with the bath now! It's your turn!
Gotta build... strong quads...
Yukine-kun?
Sorry to wake you.
Not at all. What's the matter?
Your dad turned off the
lights in my room just now.
I'm, like, not comfortable in the dark, so...
Oh...
I see.
Want to sleep with me, then?
Huh?!
It's okay with me. Come in!
N-No, I can't...
Hurry up, now. It's getting cold.
B-But...
I can't remember the last time I slept with someone like this!
Oh...
Yukine-kun...
You smell nice, too.
I like this smell.
It feels nice being next to you.
Oh, Yukine-kun?
The hell are you doing here?!
Don't give me that, you little perv!
What were you about to do?!
I didn't...
H-Hiyori invited me into her bed!
You aren't ready for girls yet.
Focus on this dreamboat for now.
You're grossing me out,
you sweats-wearing sicko.
What...
You have a girl too!
Another Regalia, just like me!
It's not like you need me.
Gonna be another stormy night.
Distance to downtown: 0.9.
0.7.
Incoming, on your six!
Let's go.
NORAGAMI
Thanks for coming along with me!
Yeah. Nothing else to do anyway.
Do you want those?
Uh, no...
It's starting to get cold out, after all.
Let's see how much I have...
No, really! It's fine!
I don't need anything!
No, no, let me help you out!
Really, I'm okay!
I mean, no one can see me,
so I can always borrow stuff if I really need to!
Huh?
See?
Y-You know better than that, Yukine-kun!
That's no different from stealing!
Huh? Hey, I'm only borrowing it.
I'll give it right back—
It's still wrong.
Give it here.
If you ever want something, just tell me.
Okay?
Yukine-kun?
Hey.
Fun Friend Park
Yato?! What are you doing?!
Just trying to relax a little!
I was feeling kinda stressed.
You are looking after him, I hope.
Sounds like he's up to no good again.
How did you know that?
I keep telling you.
Master and Regalia share mind and body.
I can feel it every time
Yukine gives in to temptation!
That's just how it works between Regalia and their masters.
Then, does that mean
Yukine-kun also felt it
when you swiped
some of my father's drinks?
Nope.
The pain from immoral thoughts only goes in one direction:
from Regalia to Master.
All Regalia used to be people.
And people sin.
Resentment, fear, envy,
desperation, sadness, greed...
Super Bargain!!
Used Games
Special Sale
Unbeatable Price
Limited Time Only
Temptation is born from these emotions.
The sin of acting on that temptation turns to pain,
which is how we learn through our Regalia
what is right and wrong.
Listen, Hiyori.
You seem to have the wrong idea, so let me set things straight.
People decide for themselves what's right and wrong, but those standards don't apply to gods.
In other words...
gods can do whatever they want.
Including hurting someone...
for taking their life.
Huh?
Someday, I'll give Yukine his punishment too.
Divine punishment.
Yato...
He once killed a Regalia.
He kills people too.
I-I'm...
going to look for Yukine-kun now!
Man...
Talk about forgetting something important.
I wonder if Hiyori's still mad at me.
Crap, it's this late already!
Damn!
Somewhere...
Anywhere that isn't dark!
I'm scared.
It's dark.
Mommy... Please hurry...
You're looking at me?
Shoot!
I knew it!
Everyone else ignores me for some reason!
All these eyeball thingies
try to talk to me instead,
but they're so scary!
She's...
I'm waiting for my mommy's car.
On the 23rd, a young girl
She comes to pick me up
after my lessons are over.
On the 23rd, a young girl
was killed
here in a
hit-and-run
was killed
here in a
hit-and-run
was killed
here in a
hit-and-run
was killed
here in a
hit-and-run
Oh...
Hey, stay with me until 6 o'clock.
Until my mommy comes!
Sure.
Yukine-kun...
Sorry. Mommy's a little late.
Your family must be worried about you too.
My family?
I don't really have one...
When my mommy gets here,
you should come with us, okay?
She'll be here soon, okay?
I... don't think she's coming.
Hey! Hold on!
Yukine-kun!
Here you are!
Don't go over there!
Huh?!
How terrible.
Poor little girl...
Your mommy is over here.
Really?
Come this way.
Come here.
Yukine-kun!
The thing Yato taught you!
Put my fingers together like this...
Damn!
...and draw a line!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that earlier.
It's okay now.
They can't cross that line.
Smells nice...
Smells nice... Smells nice...
You...
smell really nice.
Smells nice...
Come...
You smell nice...
Let me smell more...
Yukine-kun!
Give me... more...
Please...
More—
Boy...
Mommy...
Yato!
You okay, Yukine?!
The Phantom...
A girl went into it...
Boy!
You have to help her!
Please!
All right.
Come, Sekki!
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
H-Hey!
St...
Stop!
Rend!
What are you...
You're supposed to save her!
It's too late for that!
She's been completely possessed!
What are you talking about?!
Killing her's our only choice now!
Yukine...
A soul that's been corrupted
and consumed by a Phantom
will experience nothing but
a living hell! Utter damnation!
That's why...
you need to free her!
Yukine!
Rend!
We've received word from Kuraha
who is presently patrolling the city.
He states he saw Yato slaying a Phantom.
Yato appears to have
obtained a new Regalia as well.
I see.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
Did you have a nice bath, Yukine-kun?
Yeah.
Oh, I used some shampoo.
The rose-scented kind or whatever.
Is that yours?
That was my father's hair-growth shampoo.
That old guy's?!
On the next Noragami: "Scary Person."
Next Episode
Scary Person