Ta-da!
The event for the athletic match will be...
Kawashima-san's suggestion,
the 50-meter freestyle race!
Lucky me.
What did you put down?
Vale Tudo
If I win, I'll hold a screening
of your impressions.
And if I  win, Takasu-kun will be
spending summer vacation with me.
And you'll be all by your lonesome
for the entire summer.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Who Is This For?
All right. If you know the answers,
come write them on the board.
I will.
Thank you for setting
such a fine example.
Oh snap!
Hey.
Idiot.
Read this, 2-C!
Pass to all but those involved!
Round one? The battle for Takasu?
Ami-tan vs. the Palm-top Tiger...
500 Tirol chocolates per bet?
The hell is this?
How is this even a contest?
Ami-tan will dominate in the water!
The tiger will sink like a rock.
I want girls to fight over me...
How do I make that happen?
Damn...
These freaks...
Sorry arl, Ami belongs to me.
Don't you mean "all"?
Buy your way into this school, Haruta?
Pretty pathetic if you can't spell "all."
Haruta, you're...
Forget it.
They're all writing whatever
the hell they want...
What...!?
3000 Tirol chocolates!
Takasu Ryuji
Wh-What is it, Aisaka?
I-If you know the answer,
please come to the board...
A-Aisaka-san?
Don't be scared, Taiga.
It's just like washing your face!
You can do it! One more time!
Easy for you to say...
She can't put her face in the water?
That's just sad...
The outcome is plain to see.
I told you to ignore the crowd.
I know!
She has to at least try,
for Takasu's sake, too...
Who would ever—
What were you about to say?
Ki-Kitamura-ku—
Keep up the hard work with Takasu.
Huh? What?
With him?
Hey! Taiga!
I will never, ever practice during class again!
Going through the motions is good enough!
Say that after you can put
your face in the water.
What's for dinner tonight?
Peas with egg, tofu steak, and miso soup.
Also, spinach and some fried veg—
Less beans, more meat!
Don't be so greedy.
Beans are meat grown in a garden.
Cheap-ass.
Anyway, you'd better practice
during swim class.
Get serious.
I can't.
Not with Kitamura-kun watching...
Isn't that why you should give it your all?
Please...
Don't forget who's to blame for me having to work hard
and eliminate misunderstandings.
And who would that be?
Aren't you doing this to keep Kitamura
from going to Kawashima's beach hou—
Ouch!
Forget it.
Stand there and cook, boy.
Man...
What's your problem?
Get moving. Chop, chop.
I need plenty of nutrients,
so I can train like mad!
July Edition
Visual guide to improving your swim time
It's still raining...
Another day without swim class...
And I was finally ready to put
my face in the water...!
Why can't we use the pool!?
Don't scream at me.
Tickets to the public pool?
Here, use these.
I put my bet on Aisaka.
Wrote it on the sheet going
around the other day.
You were so confident about
Aisaka, I figured I'd join in.
Y-You bet on me?
Sure did.
Wh-Wh-Why!?
I can't even swim!
You're the type who rises to any challenge.
No one can predict how this contest will end!
Can't these tickets be split this way?
Wh-What are you doing!?
- Sh-Sh-Shut up!
- Good luck with practice.
Dummy.
Hey, wanna stop somewhere
on the way home?
How about S-bucks?
Perfect!
The hell?
Why are you sitting down there?
So gloomy.
The tight space is soothing.
Oof.
Oh, jeez. Running on empty?
Been busy the past few days,
thanks to a certain someone.
Oh? Who?
I have nooooo idea.
Give me a break...
The tiger's pretty cute when she's jealous.
Jealous of what?
She just doesn't like you.
Are you an idiot?
No, you are.
Anyway, stop provoking Taiga.
And what was all that crap
about a beach house?
As if you'd actually invite me.
I was serious.
I'm serious about winning, and about
spending the summer with you.
I've already planned out
what we'll do once I win.
Pretty sure it'll be fun.
I mean, I think we hit it off pretty well.
L-Like hell we did!
Gotcha mad!
Now look here...
Man...
Don't spend so much time
making fun of other people.
Gotcha.
Off you go.
I know.
Wh-What are you talking about?
The one who super-sized Taiga's swimsuit...
was you!
Well, that's...
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
No need to hide it.
Elementary, my dear Watson-kun.
After all, Taiga once confessed,
"Ryuji is always there to support me."
Cleaning, sewing buttons, ironing...
Oh, that means nothing.
And yet, it means everything.
Hey, Kushie—
I trust you.
Therefore, I will entrust Taiga to you.
Uh, okay.
I'm the ref, so I can't offer any help, but know that
we're working for the same cause!
You can count on me!
Perfect.
Please don't let it rain tomorrow...
Please don't let it rain tomorrow.
Thank you, little rain doll!
The weather's holding up.
Look, Ryuji.
It's like I'm swimming.
You need to start practicing for real.
Geh.
Ew, what is this?
The race is tomorrow.
A little late to start practicing
the freestyle, yeah?
We've gotta make use of
every available option!
Man, this is lame...
Okay, that's good.
Now, try kicking your legs.
Fine!
Huh? Hey!
Ta-Taiga!?
That was amazing, Taiga!
Your kicks really pack a punch!
You just might win!
Win?
Me?
But I wasn't doing anything special.
Well, we can't get ahead of ourselves, but...
Oh, really...?
I can win...
Yeah...
Taiga?
Yep, I'm going to win.
R-Right!
That's the spirit!
Doesn't look like it's going to
let up any time soon.
And you were finally motivated to practice...
What now?
Head home?
Up for more?
Okay.
Makes sense.
You don't want to waste the
tickets Kitamura gave us.
That's not it!
I mean...
I'm only trying bec—
I know.
To make Kawashima cry uncle.
Forget it.
Nothing I say will make a difference.
What's wrong?
Oh, you mean me?
That's right...
You'll starve to death if I'm not around.
How many times do I have to say...
But that's no reason to
push yourself so hard.
Even if you lose,
I'll be the only one forced
to go to Kawashima's beach house.
I'll ask her to leave Kitamura out of it.
Plus, I can make you food beforehand
and stick it in the freezer.
So don't worry about a thing. Just focus.
A-ha. You've finally shown your true colors.
You've wanted to go to Ami-chan's
beach house from the very beginning.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Well, I personally don't give a damn
about when, where, or who you want to drool over!
Wh-What's with you!?
I'm trying to be helpful here!
Who asked for your help?
You've been acting so weird since
that run-in with Kawashima!
You're still going on about that!?
What the hell is your problem!?
What's my problem?
I can't stand it when someone acts like
an expert on what goes on in my head.
I hate it!
It pisses me off!
Understand that, genius!?
Do you want me to understand, or not?
I don't know!
No one could ever understand how I feel!
After all... After all...
I don't even understand myself...
Huh? What did you just say?
Hello?
Have it your way, then!
I won't compete!
Itchy.
This isn't my fault, right?
Hmm?
Ryu-chan?
Why are you awake?
I'm home!
Taiga-chan didn't come over?
Why not?
Did you have a fight?
Taiga said she doesn't give a damn
about me, and I got pissed, I guess...
Ah, I see...
But you should know better, Ryu-chan.
Taiga-chan always means the
opposite of what she says.
She cares about you.
If she really hated you,
she'd never share meals with you,
no matter how hungry she was.
At least, that's what I think...
Man...
She didn't even wash off her makeup.
Come on, straighten up.
Bet you haven't eaten.
I was hoping for clear skies.
And...
I was hoping you'd be serious about the race.
What I'm trying to say is...
Regardless of how you feel,
I want you to win, and...
Win, and...?
The lunch is innocent, so I'll take it.
But...
It's been raining so much...
I haven't had a chance to
dry out my usual swimsuit.
Does this violate any school rules?
I'm worried...
Our lovely Ami-tan is about to
swim in this very pool, huh?
All so she can take Takasu
to her beach house, huh?
Why is it always you?
Why? Why? Why!?
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Yeah, why? Why is it always you!?
Cut it out, guys!
We don't know if I'll even be
going to her beach house!
Yeah, like Tiger has a chan—
We won't know until...
Until...
she tries.
That dolt...
It's all meat this time.
Aw, c'mon!
How long do we have to wait?
It's so hot!
Why isn't the Palm-top Tiger here yet?
Who cares?
Pretend we came just for the bikini.
You said it.
Hey, we really shouldn't make everyone
wait in this heat any longer...
That's true.
What are you babbling about?
Let's do this, fair and square.
Dumb Chihuahua. No, dumb bikini.
What is that!?
Is she serious?
Taiga!
You're gonna swim like that?
For a second, I thought she came armed.
Looks kinda cool...
All right!
50-meter freestyle race time!
On your marks!
Get set!
Your hair's showing.
Huh!?
Shoo—
In your face!
Suck it!
Unbelievable! Freaking unbelievable!
Wow!
The Palm-top Tiger's combined a late arrival
with a fearsome mind-game tactic!
Damn you, tiger shrimp!
Taiga!
Oh!?
Has Tiger had an accident!?
- Ami-tan has a chance!
- Hang in there, Ami-chan!
Damn it...
You okay?
A leg cramp!?
Let me go, stupid!
I can still do—
You can't possibly keep going!
I can!
But you're...
Happy now!?
Don't give me that!
Your master's pushing herself for you!
Show some appreciation, stupid mutt!
That's it, Ami-tan!
She's finally taken the lead!
Yes!
Okay.
Get going then!
I'll even wag my tail if I have to!
So...
Ami-tan!
Hey! Don't push!
Be careful, dummy!
What!?
Ryuji!
Huh?
Taiga...
Takasu!
Takasu, are you okay!?
Okay, he's breathing.
Aisaka, we need to get him
to the nurse's office...
Don't touch him!
Taiga...?
But Aisaka...
Shut up!
You're all idiots!
Why didn't you notice?
Why didn't you help?
Your eyes were so glued
to that dumb bikini...
that no one saw Ryuji...
Ryuji is mine!
So keep your hands off him!
So...I'll be going to your beach house.
I lost the race, right?
So Ryuji is going, right?
But there won't be anyone here
to take care of me, right?
So then, I'm going too.
Hold on a sec.
I'm, like, totally confused
by your pretentious act.
I see no issue.
The more, the merrier, right?
Oh, I get it.
You're uneasy about being
separated from Takasu-kun!
You did scream that he's yours, and all.
That's right. I admit it.
I mean...
Well, basically...
This is my dog.
As his owner,
I have an obligation to make sure he doesn't
misbehave at someone else's house.
What? Were you expecting something else?
Nope, not a darn thing.
Okay then, let's plan our schedule.
Lemme see!
I'll be working all the time here,
- ...and I'll be busy with softball.
- Darn, looks like we won't get to be alone.
But I'm sure we'll find plenty of opportunities.
And so,
the first term of Takasu Ryuji's second
year of high school came to an end,
and an intense summer vacation
was about to begin.
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Me, at a beach house with Kushieda...
Taiga, will I be struck by lightning
for being so happy?
Kitamura-kun's murky, black seaweed...
What?