When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
All right, I will do this!
I will eat a large one all by myself.
No, I mean I'll charge up my energy
and get ready for tomorrow's exam.
Hayate-kun, I wonder what you had for dinner.
It was supposed to be a dream that was never going to come true for the debt-ridden butler.
It wasn't a dream.
I can go to school again.
This is all thanks to Maria-san writing a recommendation for me.
M-Maria-san?
Therefore...
...go here and learn everything you can.
This is Hakuou Academy's...
My student ID?
Watch me closely, Maria-san.
In order to meet your expectations...
All right.
I will go to Hakuou Academy and become the best butler!
Going to school does not make you the best butler.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
I'll show you all there is to being the best butler.
Aren't you in a good mood, Hayate-kun?
Hinagiku-san! You stayed here last night?
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
B-But what's wrong? You seem to be in a bad mood.
"Why"?
Oh. You disappeared all of a sudden last night,
and you wouldn't return even after it got late,
and we couldn't find you no matter how much we searched,
and you think nobody worried about you?!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. I'm really sorry.
But, judging by looking at you, you did pass, right?
Ah, yes. Thanks to everyone.
Then I'll forgive you.
I'll head home now, but if you see me at school,
make sure you say hi.
Ah, yes. Roger that.
Good.
Students at the same school, eh?
So, you've been holding the student ID the entire night?
Yes. I slept with it in my hands.
Seriously, why are you so cute?
You must have been really excited.
Yes. Right now, I understand the feeling of people in musicals and how they start singing all of a sudden.
No need for you to.
Besides, there aren't any character songs
made for this situation.
And the production of a musical anime involves work.
Oh right. What do I do for my uniform?
Uniform?
Yes. Hakuou has a school uniform, right?
I can't go in my butler uniform.
You don't need a school uniform.
You are right. That would make it easier to spot him.
Don't worry. There are other butlers besides you at that school.
Besides, you're likely to catch everyone's eye with your butler uniform.
But the bigger problem is whether we'll be in the same class or not.
Huh?
She is right.
What are you talking about? I'm in high school.
You're thirteen, so you're in middle school.
Oh, you didn't know?
Didn't know what?
I've skipped grades, so I'm in high school.
Milady! You're in high school?
Don't be that surprised.
But, that's like a setting from a certain 4-koma manga.
Don't say any more than that.
But it can't be true. You're so small.
Don't say small!
B-But... Seriously?
Damn, you're so skeptical of me.
Then take a look at this!
Tada!
W-What-
...a grumpy-looking picture.
You're not supposed to talk about that!
What? That really is a high school student ID!
I told you so from the beginning.
Hakuou has students who skipped grades, butlers, and many other people, so it is very interesting.
I see.
Hey, you don't believe what I say,
but you believe what Maria says instantly, eh?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
Stop making fun of me.
My grades are actually-
Then it'll be nice if we can be in the same class.
Y-Yeah.
I hope Monday comes soon.
And so, let's skip right to Monday morning.
I told you; there's nothing even if you come this early.
We're not doing this again.
That's my new school.
I know that.
Oh, you did?
You knew it already?
Are you all right?
Well, I'm glad you're happy.
But Milady, you're amazing to have skipped grades into high school.
It's not as amazing as you make it sound.
I'm not the only one who's skipped grades.
There are several every year.
And the record holder of this school's grade skipping enrolled ten years old and graduated thirteen years old.
Plus she was the Student Council President
for two years in a row,
and her grades were the best in school by far.
She has three silver watches given to the valedictorian of the year.
I see. So such a monster-like person does exist in this world.
Yes, such a monster-like person does exist, right next you.
Eh?
Oh no, did I catch a cold?
Anyways, in this school, students who skip grades,
transfer in, or get scholarships...
...have a duty to increase the school's average grade,
school ranking, and graduation rate.
On the other hand, when such students do poorly,
they can be dropped a grade.
R-Really?
Come to think of it, I remember
the Student Council members talking about that.
I was happy out of my mind that I got accepted, but it is a prestigious school.
Will I be fine here with my borderline grades?
You'll do fine, Hayate; you can do anything.
What's wrong, Hayate?
Battles are meant to be fought reading two, three moves ahead.
By **** *znable.
It's nice to wake up early once in a while; I met an interesting person.
Do I lose if I comment that he's the most interesting one?
I think so.
And is there a meaning to that quote?
Himuro, is this enough flowers?
Thank you, Sir Taiga.
Himuro thanked me!
Um...
Your outfit. You must be a butler, as well.
Yes. I'm a butler for the Sanzenin family, Ayasaki-
Sanzenin?
Ah, so you're that famous.
Then that means...
What a beautiful person.
Hey! What do you think you're doing to Hayate?
Yes, if I'm right, anyone who can make her cry and apologize can inherit the entire Sanzenin estate.
I won't let you touch Milady.
I will protect her!
Hayate...
To be honest, I have a meal ticket called
Sir Taiga already, so I'm not interested in it.
Meal ticket?
If you space out like that, she'll get taken away.
What? That's my necktie.
How?
What a foolish question.
Isn't it obvious?
Because I'm a professional butler.
Professional butler?
There's no joke involved when one wears a butler uniform at this school.
Let us go, Sir.
Yeah!
Wow! So is that the butler I aspire to be?
Although I'm not sure how that was related to work as a butler.
Milady! Butlers are amazing!
It's not the biggest issue, but he still has your necktie.
Oh no!
And he's gone already.
So this is how professional butlers move.
No, that was definitely robbery.
And don't make me comment on your monologue.
Suke-san. Kaku-san. Korashimete aganasai.
Korashimete aganasai. = Give them retribution.
Finishing line from the samurai show "Mito Koumon".
Itsude mo coffee irete ageruyo.
Itsude mo coffee irete ageruyo. = I'll make coffee anytime you want.
I'm sorry, Maria-san.
Really, what did you go to school for?
There.
Make sure you do not lose your necktie and go to school this time.
Of course! You can count on me!
Are you sure?
You're strangling me, Maria-san!
Hey, we'll be late!
I don't mind not going at all, you know.
Of course I'll go.
Have a safe trip, both of you.
Yes, we're off!
Let's go, Milady!
Hold on!
Listen up!
We have a new member for our class!
A transfer student?
A boy? Or is it a girl?
He is a boy, unfortunately.
Why "unfortunately"?
Katsura-chan, is he handsome?
What? Handsome?
I-It's making me nervous.
I bet he's getting nervous standing out there.
All right, then I'll make an atmosphere easy for him to enter to make up for what I did.
The transfer student is really cute.
It's like, cooking ****taku and **ki's DNA in ****jo, and then added Orl**** and Brad ****.
Just hearing his voice would knock you out.
The sound effect for when he looks to the side is like, BANG!
He's like Gol**, specialized in sniping girls.
And he's the Sanzenin butler and a genius!
His athleticism is incredible, too!
The Sanzenin butler?
And so, come on in, transfer student!
Hello.
What? Hayata-kun?
Didn't he fail the transfer exam?
A lot has happened.
All the eyes looking at me hurt.
So the handsome transfer student was Hayata-kun.
True, he's not ugly...
...But this is one poor-looking Orl**** and Brad ****.
Come and introduce yourself, Ayasaki-kun.
Even if you give me that "I've set the stage up for you" face...
~stare~
So this is what an adverse challenge is!
To introduce myself before a frozen cold room
as if Snow***** was just cast.
Fine. I can't let Milady feel embarrassed.
Ayasaki Hayate has always worked with adults.
Therefore...
Nice to meet you.
This kind of sales smile is his forte.
As Katsura-sensei has just introduced me, I am Ayasaki Hayate.
I work for Lady Nagi as her butler at the Sanzenin's.
Katsura-sensei's introduction was a little exaggerated; I'm not that good with academics.
But I look forward to enjoying studying with you all.
So, I hope we get along well.
Now, we're even.
School is so much fun!
Yeah?
It isn't for you?
No, since there's so many people.
I prefer to be alone, to have peace and quiet,
and to spend the majority of the day on manga and games.
That'd make you a no-good human.
I skipped grades because I didn't want to go to school for twelve years.
Y-You're quite hardcore to go that far.
But I'm happy to be able to go to school with you.
It's all thanks to Maria-san.
And you, too, of course.
Without you setting up the transfer for me, I wouldn't be here.
Thank you very much, Milady.
Well, um... yeah...
I'm also happy that...
You like being away from people as usual, don't you?
Hi-Hinagiku! You!
Hinagiku-san. Hello.
Hello.
And what brings you here?
I was headed to my clubroom.
This is a shortcut.
Wow. So you're involved in a club
while being the Student Council President?
You've got to be able to handle that much at least.
Come to think of it, you're not in any clubs, Milady?
Eh? Why?
I thought the best part of school life is spending time with your friends in the same club.
You idiot! I don't need those anymore!
Oh, but your seat's still open.
Hinagiku!
What do you mean open seat?
She's in the same club as me.
That's bogus! I went one day to see what it's like.
Don't make me a member.
And what club is this?
The Kendo Club.
The Kendo Club?
When I entered high school, there was a time when I thought it'd be bad for me to keep being a hikikomori.
So I thought I'd start a sport during
the new student recruitment period.
Because it looked really cool.
Then why did she quit?
I don't know. Ask her.
Because...
Both the protectors and the sword were heavy, and I couldn't move.
So use a child's size, not the same as mine.
I'd never use a child's size!
Was that the only reason you quit?
Yeah, that was the only reason I quit.
Because I realized soon enough...
...that even if I did the same sport, I wouldn't be able to be like her.
So there was a time when Milady actively tried to pick up a sport.
But if I leave Milady as she is now,
she'll only become a NEET or a MMO'er.
I think I'd be a loser if I went to work.
All right, Milady.
Let's go check out the Kendo Club after school!
Wow, so this is the Kendo Club.
Of course. I would hate it if this was a manga or anime club.
But I don't see many people.
It's not a popular club to begin with in this school.
You look good in the dobog, Hinagiku-san.
What?
Ah... Why thank you.
Then why don't I introduce you to everyone and try practicing, Hayate-kun?
That guy just...
...called Katsura-san...
...Hinagiku!
A-And she said, "Hayate-kun"?!
But Hinagiku-san, what about my protectors?
You can't go without them, Hayate-kun?
Ah... please... Hinagiku-san...
Hinagiku-san...
Hayate-kun...
First of all, let's get permission from the advisor.
Katsura-san.
There's no need to let that guy practice kendo here.
Azumamiya-kun.
Hey, butler.
Fight me!
Eh?
If you lose, never come here again.
We won't come again even if he wins.
Hey!
If I lose here, Milady will probably never try kendo again, let alone any sport.
Then I can't afford to lose.
Okay, I accept your challenge.
Hayate-kun?
Flower petals?
This is becoming interesting.
Become a sword for the sake of the master.
Good mindset.
You're Prince Necktie.
Please give me back my necktie.
Thank you for the unique nickname.
But I don't need one.
And, I'm not sure if Azumamiya
will be good enough for the fight.
What?
Take a look.
H-His fighting spirit is bursting the petals.
Hiten-
Wait!
Don't go any further than that for copyright reasons, too!
But I see; looks like I don't have to hold back anything.
Your name was Hayate, was it?
Yes.
I consider you to be the person I must defeat for my, Azumamiya Koutarou's, future.
A kendo club member, Azumamiya Koutarou, declares himself to be a rival all of a sudden.
How strong is he?
The plot dives into school youth mode.
Heading towards the stereotypical outcome.
Next time, we'll fight against this fated rival.
Wait a moment!
Who said I will fight?
Nonohara!
Come over here, Nonohara.
Nonohara?
My butler.
Your opponent is this combat butler, Nonohara Kaede.
C-Combat butler?
Looks like next week, we'll fight against him.
Himuro, is that enough flowers?
Thank you, Sir Taiga.
Um, can I ask unauthorized people to leave?
What did he appear for?
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
'Sup. It's Sanzenin Nagi.
It's Ayasaki Hayate.
And I'm Katsura Hinagiku.
Hinagiku-san, when did you come?
What? Hinagiku, what are you here for?
I've been put in this section for a while, too.
Apparently Hinagiku-san ranks number one
in a certain weekly magazine.
You're amazing.
Hayate-kun, you won't get anything out of me even if you praise me.
Excels in sports and academics.
I want Milady to be like that, too.
Hayate, time's running out!
What are you mad about, Milady?
Oh well.
So hello, I'm Nonohara Kaede.
I'm a butler of the Azumamiya family.
Go, Nonohara! Knock him out right now!
As you order.
Safety Cutter!
Hayate!
We butlers aren't our masters' tools.
Just doing what they tell us to do isn't everything.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
I Won't Lose Even If I Lose.
Hayate, I have faith you won't lose to that butler.
Wipe away the tears under the mask.