Solitaire
Huh?
You met someone posing as me?
I see.
What a hassle, huh?
You don't know the half of it!
You have no idea what we've been through while you were gone!
We obtained the Magical Lovely Pad!
Ai grew out of her grumpy phase!
Did you even notice that we got a whole new Precure?
A pleasure to meet you, Cure Ace.
I heard about you from Ann.
From Princess Ann?
What do you mean?
As you can see, Ann has yet to awaken.
But I haven't spent all this time doing nothing.
What's this?
One of the Sacred Treasures, the Eternal Golden Crown.
Huh?!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
The Fated Battle!
Ace vs. Regina!
Just where did you find this?
It was shortly after I separated from you girls.
Jonathan...
Ai?
Ann...
I speak to you through Ai's magic.
The girl who shall become love's trump card will soon awaken.
Ai must journey to her.
In the near future,
King Selfish's resurrection will be complete.
Before that comes to pass, Jonathan,
I'd like you to search for one of the Sacred Treasures, the Golden Crown.
And after following Ann's request, I arrived at this Sacred Treasure.
I see.
Let's give it a try!
Okay!
Kyupirappa kyupirappa puu puu puu!
Wow!
This is the last of the three Sacred Treasures!
The circlet said to be imbued with all the wisdom of the world,
the Eternal Golden Crown!
Legend has it that this circlet of gold grants its knowledge only to those whom it deems worthy.
I believe that you girls have what it takes to master this crown.
Also...
Nothing's happening.
You just put it on?!
Be careful!
That treasure is ten thousand years old!
Handle it with delicacy!
Aguri!
Have you awakened?
Grandmother...
Mana and the others carried you here.
I see...
Grandmother,
what should I do?
I've learned everything.
I know who I am and what destiny I was born to meet.
It is a grave, tragic fate...
It is too heavy...
for my shoulders to bear...
I...
No matter how painful it may be, everyone must follow their destiny.
But...
you can either let destiny throw you around
or stand and carve your own path toward it.
It all depends on you.
I'm sure you already know...
exactly what to do.
Thank you, Grandmother.
I'll waver no more!
Hey. I see she called you, too.
Joe...
We're all here.
Why'd you bring Ai too?
So, what's this important chat?
This.
Princess!
What have you done?!
What we saw until now was but an illusion.
A shadow the princess created to stall the Selfish and divert their attention!
The Golden Crown has revealed everything to me.
We will discuss the truth of the hidden kingdom.
Solitaire
No...
It can't be...
I can't believe it...
But if what you say is true,
then all the pieces fall right into place.
Cure Sword, Davi, Jonathan,
I thank you from the bottom of my heart for all you've done for the princess.
I will leave for Trump Kingdom to end our battle with Regina.
I ask of you to see the battle through with your own eyes.
End?
Wait, why are we leaving Mana out of this?
If we tell her, I'm sure—
That is not an option.
Aguri!
Mana would certainly seek a peaceful resolution.
She wouldn't be able to bear either me or Regina falling in battle...
But we cannot avoid a battle we were destined to have.
Don't try to stop me.
If you cannot accept what I've told you, then please leave.
I'll go.
What about you?
They're late.
Where could they be?
I'm certain they're grocery shopping for a New Year's feast!
Bad news!
Ai's gone too!
Excuse me!
Eru!
Is... Aguri here?
Did something happen?
Yesterday, Aguri came to my house...
I drew this shortly after Career Day.
It's a picture of my friends!
Thank you!
But what's the occasion?
I simply wanted you to know how I feel.
Adieu!
Aguri seemed different from normal.
I got the feeling I'd never see her again,
so I came here...
I tried going to Aguri's house,
but she was gone!
Let's look for them ourselves!
Seconds!
Right away!
She seems a bit moody.
Regina, can you come back one more time?
Mana, you've got no idea how I feel...
Well, whatever the case, it sure seems like King Selfish is gonna be back any day now, huh?
Shut up already!
What do you know?
Oh, I'm shak—
It's you!
Why are you here?!
Because it is my destiny to end this battle.
Regina.
You hit your head?
That's...
It can't be...
The Eternal Golden Crown!
It is indeed.
I challenge you to wager your Dragon Glaive against my Golden Crown...
in a duel!
Sounds like fun!
I've always wanted to mop the floor with you!
I accept your challenge.
Ai, let us go.
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
I won't let you interfere!
Stay silent and watch.
Who put you in charge?
Cure Ace is my prey!
You three can stand there and watch.
Let us go!
Now let's see what Regina's made of...
What're you running away for?
You can't end a fight like that!
Never thought you'd be this boring!
Geez!
You've sealed your own fate.
Why you...
Let go!
Get her, Dragon Glaive!
Don't finish us off with her!
You musn't avert your eyes!
But...
This is the destiny she chose!
Seeing whether Regina or Cure Ace proves victorious...
is what we were brought here to—
I know!
I know, but...
even if we truly can't avoid this fate...
it's still too painful!
Aguri!
Those two were here.
Jonathan's gone too!
What happened to the princess?
What the heck happened?
The Ace of Spades?
What's it doing?
Love Kiss Rouge!
Not bad.
Of course.
But you think you can win this?
Your five minutes are almost up.
And you won't remain a Precure once they are.
You underestimate me.
I no longer have any manner of time limit.
With the wisdom of the Golden Crown, the true Ace has awakened.
What?! That's cheating!
Ace Mirror Flash!
It's over!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
You won't make a fool of me!
Is this truly the only way to settle this?
What should I do?
Are we to do nothing...
but watch these two wound each other?
A no-holds-barred battle between two Sacred Treasure wielders won't end with a few bruises.
So if I take both Treasures once they're too weak to oppose...
I'll be Numero Uno.
Selfish!
Go, Selfishes!
Defeat Cure Ace!
And Regina shortly after!
This guy!
He's trying to steal the show!
Ace! Regina!
You promised to stay out of it!
I don't recall saying anything of the sort.
What're you doing?
I don't even know who's right anymore!
But still...
I...
I don't want to lose Aguri or Regina!
Someone... save them!
Mana!
Self! Self!
Selfish!
What?!
Girls!
Girls...
Let's do something about these Selfishes first,
Ace!
I understand.
Get them, Selfishes!
Seeeelf!
Kyupirappa!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Self... Seeeelf!
Nope!
Love love looooove!
Please move.
No way!
Why did you two have to fight this much?!
Because it is our destiny to do so.
What's with all your "destiny" stuff?
Since you've come this far, I've no choice but to tell you.
The two of us are decidedly incompatible.
Because we are the light and the shadow born from Princess Ann!
The princess's...
Light...
and shadow?
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
The memories that the Eternal Golden Crown etched into my mind revealed the truth.
Why King Selfish was born,
and the tragedy that befell Princess Ann...
Mana, you all have the right to know.
If you wish, I shall reveal it to you, as well.
Dokidoki Precure:
Ace and Regina!
The Truth Behind Their Births!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!