When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Let's go easy with the fan service shots and start with last episode's summary.
A mysterious boy and his maid appeared in the mansion to visit Nagi.
Who could they be?
His name is Tachibana Wataru-kun.
He's Nagi's...
...fiancé.
End of summary.
No way, old man. You've got to quit being so shy.
Otherwise, you won't have any screen time.
Y-Yes...
Listen. You're lacking any impact in your character.
You need to exert spirit towards comedy,
even if it means pushing others aside.
Take a look.
Where's my glasses? Where's my glasses?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
I hope my screen time will increase now.
That was it for you today.
Fiancé?
As in the person your parents have decided you're going to marry?
Yes, that fiancé.
I see.
So you do have a boyfriend.
No! Don't get me wrong!
He's a fiancé, not a boyfriend!
In other words, it's something that our families decided, so...
Still, I'm surprised that you were engaged.
Girls of the upper class are different.
To Nagi, his smile appears...
I never heard you were engaged!
Was the relationship with me a game to you?
...as such.
Hayate is furious.
I must resolve this misunderstanding.
But is it all right?
If Milady marries,
wouldn't the Sanzenin's name come to an end?
There is no need to worry about that,
since Nagi isn't the one marrying in.
Ah, then Wataru-kun is going to get taken in by Milady as an in-law.
I'm never going to give myself to Nagi!
But you can't find a chance like this;
someone as cute as Lady Nagi becoming your bride.
Hayate...
A selfish, whimsical manga nerd who thinks she's the most important person in the world will never get married.
What? I never want to hear that from a brat like you!
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Right back at you, you ugly face, ugly face, ugly face!
So the fiancés do get along.
If this looks like they're getting along,
you should go to an ophthalmologist or a neurologist.
Can't you act like a girl a little?
Wataru-kun?
Th-That voice... could it be...
Good morning, Wataru-kun.
What are you doing so early in the morning?
Ya... Ah... Isumi...
Did you come here after hearing
the rumors about Nagi's new butler?
Something like that for me, too.
Note: Wataru was using "Ore", the masculine form of "I", but is now using "Boku", a more childish form of "I".
Boku?
But I just heard a loud noise.
You weren't fighting with Nagi, were you?
O-Of course not. We'd never fight.
Nagi and I are always very good friends.
What's with that big change in attitude?
Basically...
Wataru-kun likes Isumi-san.
He's engaged and yet likes someone else?
It's not a marriage either one wished for.
Then does Milady want to cancel the marriage with Wataru-kun?
Absolutely!
We don't love each other, so why get married?
If Isumi takes a liking to Wataru, everything will be solved, but...
Isumi doesn't see Wataru that way at all.
But in any case, if Wataru-kun and Isumi-san start dating, everything is solved, correct?
Yes. So you finally understood me.
Since we all haven't had breakfast yet,
why don't we all eat together?
Would you prefer a Japanese-style breakfast?
L-Let's see...
Then whichever you like.
I-Isumi, don't tell me you...
Then everyone, please head to the dining hall.
Hold it.
SFX: RUMBLE RUMBLE RUMBLE
You're Nagi's new butler, right?
Yes, my name is Ayasaki Hayate.
How about a little duel before we have breakfast?
Um, is dueling a standard pre-breakfast activity for celebrities?
I'm not sure, but he probably just wants to show off to Isumi.
It's such a waste of effort.
Losing might give him more attention, so just deck him good.
Y-Yes.
Ready, stupid butler?
Just to let you know, Hayate is strong.
After all, he can catch up to a car on a bicycle.
Don't be ridiculous!
A poor man like him can't possibly be strong.
Ever used a sword before?
Let's see.
That's about all I can do.
So what are you going to do?
Sh-Shut up!
Wh-When a man says he's doing something...
...he can't back out of it!
What should I do? Even if it's Milady's request...
Wait a minute, if I manage to get
the two of them to work things out...
Ka** no Kizu!
Isumi, will you...
Yes, I will marry you.
All right! My marriage is cancelled!
Well done, Hayate.
All right, now that's decided!
Here I come!
Watch me good, Milady. Ayasaki Hayate's great acting skill!
Take this!
But,
blades are dangerous, so I have to get that out of the way...
You got me.
Collapse.
What? That's strange.
The path to the happy ending should have opened with this.
My, Hayate-sama.
To lose on purpose in order not to hurt weak, yet violent, Wataru-kun's pride.
How kind of you.
What?
Really, Wataru-kun is so strong I didn't have any chance of beating him.
Wait.
I'll... never... forgive... you.
I will get you one day!
You'd better remember this!
You idiot!
I-It wasn't supposed to end like this.
To deck him mentally...
Hayate-kun is good.
That horrible acting... is he still mad that I didn't tell him that I have a fiancé?
Wataru leaves the mansion alone.
By the way, Saki-san's bath time was...
It was a nice bath.
...long enough to conclude part A.
Aishiteiru to itte kure = Tell me you love me
Aishiteiru to itte kure
Renai Beam! = Love Beam!
Renai Beam!
I think I should go apologize.
I've done a horrible thing to Wataru-kun.
Yes, I do feel bad to leave him alone.
Forget about him.
Besides, for a man to cry in front of others... There's a limit to how weak one can be.
What? "Weak"?
As much as it's true, an apology should come after making one cry.
You're the one that made him cry.
S-So let's say we're going to apologize to him, and so where is his mansion?
I'd call that a building rather than a mansion.
Yes. Wataru-kun lives at the top of the
Tachibana Group Shinjuku HQ building.
Oh, in the middle of the city.
Then the road is packed during this time.
Do you think the train is faster than a car?
Did I say something strange?
Have you ever ridden a train, Isumi?
I've been on the Orient Express and
the Siberia Super Express, but never on one in Japan.
Yeah.
Besides trains don't run that often, do they?
Then what about that?
It's only a game.
Milady, you've never gotten on a train before?
No, but were there that many stops for bullet trains within Tokyo?
Bullet trains?
You weren't talking about bullet trains when you said trains?
I'm sorry to ask this question,
but do any of you know what a subway is?
Subway?
Yes, like the Ooedo Line or the Marunouchi Line.
They're trains that run underground.
SFX: RUSTLE
Do bullet trains run under Tokyo, as well?
No, there are trains other than bullet trains.
What do you see out the window when you're underground?
Nothing really.
Doesn't it only carry **** and prohibit commoners to ride in it?
That's back in the Taishou Era.
This sounds interesting.
I had no intention of going to Wataru's house, but I'd like to ride this so-called subway.
Okay, let's go ride one of these subways!
But will it be all right for only children to ride such an unknown vehicle?
Even if you look only at Shinjuku Station,
approximately 570,000 people ride that unknown vehicle.
By the way, if you break it down,
the Toei Shinjuku Line takes 230,000 people,
the Ooedo Line takes 100,000 people,
and the Marunouchi Line takes 240,000 people.
That concludes my explanation.
You're very knowledgeable, Hayate.
It's as you see, so don't worry.
And I might be able to see some underground inhabitants or dinosaurs.
Th-That's exactly why I'm saying it's dangerous.
W-Well, Isumi-san's here, too, so I'll make sure neither gets lost.
And speaking of Isumi,
Where did she go?
Did she get lost already?
And we only took our eyes off of her for a moment.
We underestimated Isumi's ability.
Maria, contact security.
Hayate and I will search the neighborhood.
Yes!
Wait, Nagi!
I think Isumi must have headed to the subway, but...
What? Do you know how many subway stations there are within Tokyo?
The "subway" I'm talking about now is the image of subways Isumi has.
So she most likely hasn't made it to the real subway.
A triple decker on a cone please.
R-Really?
Yeah. It's impossible for Isumi to make it to her destination on her own.
So follow me, and you'll find her.
Isumi is at the closest subway-like place.
No wait, where is this place?
I-I don't know. But I found a construction worker who sounded like he'd seen Isumi, so...
Um, is this the entrance to the subway?
I had heard you're carrying a subway dinosaur in a bullet train.
Yeah, it is underground for sure.
But under Tokyo is a space that even the government doesn't have a full understanding of, so there just might be...
What? Missy?
And it was a good move of her to buy that construction site and go down underground with her bodyguards, but...
That's Gri****!
Guess I was seeing things.
Lucky or unlucky?
Milady! Where are you?
We need to head back once.
Or else we'll get lost, too.
Milady?
Y-You idiot. Don't move all of a sudden.
I thought you were going to leave me behind.
I'm not good with dark places like this,
so please don't move so suddenly.
But Milady, what do you do at night?
You can't go to bed alone?
Well, no, um... ah...
I can go to sleep alone.
I-I'm not a child, so...
I only have a little trouble sleeping.
And if a black out happens, it's dangerous.
It's fine.
That makes you cute.
But it looks like it was a mistake.
You shouldn't make loud noises underground.
When you do, they get surprised and come out.
I-Isumi-san!
Glad I found you. Let's run from here together.
Hurry, or else they'll catch up.
Oh my.
You're being a little too noisy.
SFX: STOP
Ofuda: EVIL SPIRITS BEGONE
How smart of them.
What?
Wh-What was that about?
That's how our dream about the subway ended.
You're such a fool!
Dinosaurs?
Underground inhabitants?
Of course they don't exist.
Listen, the subways are actually connected to Brazil.
Brazil?
Yeah. That country's on the other side of the world from Japan, right?
So it's connected to there.
But what you have to watch out for is that Brazil is another country.
So you have to show your passport.
Next time you get on the subway, show your passport and ask for one ticket to Rio de Janeiro for a child.
Got it?
Yes, I do, Sakuya. Thank you.
Hayate, if you still insist on going to apologize to Wataru, give this to him.
What is this?
You mustn't open it on the way,
since you never know who's watching from where.
It's the city.
But what is this?
It can't be a bomb to do away with the fiancé, can it?
Hey, it's the Sanzenin's butler.
Saki-san.
To see you here...
Do you have a business with Sir?
Yes, a little.
And I brought a package from Milady.
Then I will escort you up.
Really?
Thank you very much.
The HQ is this way, so please follow me without getting lost.
Ah... Yes.
I don't really get it, but is Saki-san avoiding me?
Um, Saki-san?
I'm sorry!
I'm not trying to avoid you or anything.
How do I say...
You see, it was my first time getting carried by
a male like that, so I'm avoiding you instinctively.
No, I don't mean you. Males in general!
I'm not bothered by it.
I'm used to being hated.
Um...
I'm sorry.
Here we are.
This is it.
Store Sign: Rental Video Tachibana
Um, isn't this a video rental shop?
That's right.
I've returned, Sir.
Ah, Saki. Good work.
What the heck are you doing here?
I-I brought this in place of Milady!
What? Videos I lent Nagi?
Videos?
Yeah. This is Tachibana Group's entertainment section, Rental Video Tachibana. Shinjuku HQ.
Tachibana Group, itself, is on the verge of bankruptcy due to the recession.
This rental chain store is its last stronghold.
Saki. Don't spill too much information.
Then the fiancé deal is...
My parents want Nagi's estate.
They are scared to lose money since the feeling of wealth is soaked all the way to their bones.
But what good can come with such a pessimistic mindset?
Just you watch.
I will make this store huge and make an estate incomparably huger than Sanzenin's.
I'll never become an in-law.
Then, I'm sure Isumi will...
He's badmouthed, but he's a very good boy.
That's why I can't leave him alone.
Saki! Stop standing around and get back to work!
Y-Yes!
Rental video... So the bag I brought in, too?
Yeah, it's our merchandise.
But someone with as much money as Milady could buy rather than rent.
You're naive.
There are super rare pieces of software that don't make it out into the market.
Th-Then the DVD over there, as well?
Yeah, this one is Tengen T-
Bamboo... Bamboo...
Just like that, we have treasures that can't be said out loud lined up in our store.
Genres we cover are anime and special effect movies.
B-But isn't it against the law to rent those out?
Doesn't matter, since I'm only boasting to Nagi personally.
But one day, I will surpass her in money.
Um, I'm really sorry for what I did to you the other day.
To make up for it, please let me be a member of this place.
Well, I guess you are a customer, too.
Ayasaki, was it?
I won't charge you the registration fee.
Hey!
You're already registered.
No way!
I've never registered with any rental shop.
But this is you.
Ayasaki Shun.
What? A different name?
It's my dad!
You have 158 videos that haven't been returned.
¥200 per late night...
...and you owe us ¥1,580,000.
I'm home.
Good work.
What's with the blue face?
We settled by agreeing to replace the tapes.
Monthly payment.
Huh?
Right when Hayate's debt increased,
here was another person having a rough time.
One child to Rio de Janeiro please.
To Rio de Janeiro in Brazil.
Um...
It's hard for people who can't tell lies
to be lied to and live in the current world.
But let's just say it's best for humans
to be honest, and we'll see you next week.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Hayate, you're starting to understand the butler's job well.
Thank you very much, Milady.
But then, you still have much to learn. You don't have time to sing.
Huh...
To begin, you must train because evil can come to attack at any moment.
What? Anime original evil?
That's right, since we don't know when anime original evil
will show up in the anime, Hayate no Gotoku!
They will?
Bye bye.
Hayate, I have a favor to ask.
Yes, what is it Milady?
Could you put these clothes on?
Um, that's a sailor uniform, right?
Oh Nagi, what are you doing?
Maria-san!
Hayate-kun would look better in this frill.
Noooooo!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku!
Cat Ear Mode Sends You to Hell.
I'll serve the Earth's future ~nyan.