Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Closure is necessary
for us.
Very well.
The Big Argument
Chapter Twenty Two
Present (16)/ Destruction
What's going on?
Hey!
What is this?
Explain! Aren't you the head monk?
Myoue...
I did this...
This is happening because I broke in with Raw...
Right, Master?
Hey.
Darling...
Oh, dear.
The Ouji North area has been destroyed.
We can't handle the cleanup anymore.
I'll do it!
No. 12 and 13!
God damn it!
Hey!
Are you all right?
My granny... is gone...
The shrine too...
Did you lose something too?
You sound so strange...
Sis...
It's okay, Koto.
What's okay?
Everything's wasted, Koto.
What?
It's not Koto's fault!
Then whose is it?
This is all Koto's fault!
Shut up! Don't blame it all on Koto!
Yeah!
Wanna go at it, dipshit?
You're gonna regret this.
You're his girlfriend!
Koto...
Thank the Heavens.
What's up?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. It's nothing serious.
The wound will be gone in no time.
And are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Koto?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry!
Why didn't you tell her anything?
Didn't I ask you to care for her when I left?
I'm quite sure I did!
And not just her! You didn't tell me either!
Can't you be a little more communicative sometimes?
I bet you knew my dream would change.
Don't be so angry...
Look at this mess...
Look at this mess!
Of course I'm angry!
But...
There's no "but"!
I'm sorry, okay?
There you go again!
Good grief.
You should be a little more distant after all these centuries.
Look at you.
Father, we are no children anymore.
Don't you think it's about time to explain?
Explain this catastrophe.
Explain the reason you left.
Explain Koto.
Head priest!
You see...
Lady Yase is at the station right now...
How nice! I can see people!
Yase?
What are you doing there?
Greetings!
Who are you?
You're so beautiful.
Yase...
It's affecting her memories already?
That's my girl!
Koto.
Our daughter's amazingly unique!
Are you okay, Koto?
Are you injured?
Come on, what's wrong? Koto...
Sis?
This is all my fault.
Take this for now.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry I got you hurt.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna sort this out.
I'm. Gonna. Sort this out.
Finally!
Hell yeah!
What's going on?
Oh, wow.
It's him...
Shrine...
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Why are Shrine people here?
Enter uninvited guests.
They discovered paradise.
What do you mean?
What does it matter? It's all going to the dogs.
Inari's been keeping this a secret.
The location of this dream paradise.
But paradise is lost.
It's hard to keep secrets from Shrine.
Publicity is the end of wonderland.
What? What are you trying to say?
You're special, Koto.
A special girl.
You were born from a god and a Buddha...
Some real divinity met there.
Why is the head priest here?
You don't understand it, girl?
The other side of the looking glass is a figment.
It's the thirteenth parallel, not supposed to exist.
The thirteenth?
I didn't expect you so early.
How many years has it been since we met?
Quite some.
I would have preferred to meet under different circumstances myself.
Sadly, such fundamental accidents are difficult to deal with even for us.
This is a nice place, Inari.
I can understand your desire to hide it.
Great place, right?
You'd do me a big favor forgetting you ever saw it.
No can do.
Head priest!
Koto?
Why have you come in person?
I'm the startled one here, Koto.
You disappeared the day you were deployed,
only to pop up once in order to smash the control system in the sanctuary.
You and your parents are far to unpredictable for my taste.
To be fair, at the end of it, I couldn't have come here without you.
Let's ignore all that.
Hold on!
You just said "at the end of it," didn't you?
What do you mean?
You have no idea how worried Katsura was.
Head priest!
The Mirror Capital will end here.
That's horrible!
There aren't many options at this point.
Come on!
I bet Kichijouji and the others have some ideas!
Please, head priest! I don't want to smash this place!
Koto, some things—
Isn't it the job of the general agency to protect the stability and harmony of the world?!
I'm a member of your special squad too!
If you won't help, I'll do what I can alone!
Koto!
That's not acceptable.
There are some things we can't allow precisely because we're the general agency.
This place should never have existed.
The thirteenth parallel...
Where did you hear that?
If you know, that makes things easier.
Your father disobeyed his orders to make this forbidden place.
Will you force me to tell it all?
Do your job, observer!
Observer?
Master?
This place, the capital in the mirror,
isn't just some picture world.
It's a parallel I made and kept secret from Shrine.
I would have been in for trouble if I hadn't hid it so deftly.
I never thought you'd go so far,
Koto.
Ordinarily nobody would be able to force their way in.
But you, too—
I only got in because you opened a way from your side.
Once space is sufficiently warped,
it's quite simple, really.
Whom does she take after, I wonder?
So decisive, so bold...
Look,
maybe it wasn't supposed to exist originally,
but can't we tolerate it now?
Can't it stay?
Koto.
Just earlier you called this the thirteenth parallel.
It's all connected.
The other twelve parallels — everything.
Didn't we tell you that you did something crazy?
Chain reactions everywhere!
No way...
Sis!
No...
Do you understand now?
This is what playing house has gotten us into!
You abandoned your mission
and twisted the world instead.
Did you think that was your job as an observer?
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Head priest,
I'm grateful to you.
You overlooked my mistakes and helped when I had a problem.
While Shrine is a real pain,
I have the fox mask to thank for being able to raise Koto so well.
But I realized this.
Our work is crushed by the vastness of eternity, and there's no soul in it.
I wished for a light to shine on it.
Do you have any idea how important it is for some to have someone by your side?
And you accept the distortion of the world?
Head priest, I will not hesitate.
I know what is most important to me.
You're an observer, not a person.
So only human beings
are allowed emotions?
You must be jesting.
Fool.
What's wrong, A? Un?
Master!
Dear!
Koto!
Mom!
Koto?
Don't worry.
It's nothing serious.
You can't be serious!
What's going on?
Oh my, fireworks so early?
Your mother lost all her powers with your birth.
It would seem that you have inherited everything.
She is no longer truly real and can't
exist outside the sanctuary anymore.
Do not tax her.
Especially in this situation.
It's my fault...
I'm the reason Mom was confined to that place.
What a deplorable end for what began as someone's earnest desire to find a home.
How ironic.
You're wrong, Koto...
You're wrong.
You have no idea, Koto, how happy we were when you were born.
Koto!
It's all my fault...
No! Koto, look at me!
Koto!
It's my—
Oh, my!
Koto...
What are you doing?
Are you really the sort to let this get to you?
Hey!
Your parents
are
alive
right there!
My parents and siblings by blood have been dead for ages!
Your parents are alive!
Start helping them while you can!
Back to your old self?
There's still a lot for you to do.
Don't bail on me here.
That's right.
Yeah.
I'll help you, so go convince that guy!
You were useless to Mom, huh, Myoue?
Suppose so.
Head priest!
I made up my mind.
If you don't help the people of the Mirror Capital and Mom, I'll break all the other parallels as well.
Are you nuts?
The Mirror World can't end here.
I'll pull everything else down with it!
What do you say, Shrine?
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
Koto, you've really grown up.
You're my special daughter!
Frankly, it was a bit of an accident on my part that you were born.
I guess I haven't told you yet.
Let me tell you of my dream!
Let's Think of a Solution Together
Next time on Kyousougiga:
"Let's Think of a Solution Together".
I love you, my other me.