♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1
LET'S JAM. ♪
♪ BEEN A FOOL, BEEN A CLOWN,
LOST MY WAY FOR UP AND DOWN ♪
♪ AND I KNOW,
YES, I KNOW ♪
♪ AND I SEE IN YOUR EYES THAT
YOU REALLY WEREN'T SURPRISED ♪
♪ AT ME AT ALL,
NOT AT ALL ♪
♪ AND I KNOW
BY YOUR SMILE IT'S YOU ♪
SO AS A REWARD,
THE TURTLE TOOK HIM TO RIUGUJO,
THE DRAGON TEMPLE.
- RIUGUJO?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WAS LIKE A PALACE,
AND THEY GAVE HIM
A BIG WELCOMING PARTY
BEAUTIFUL WOMEN,
SCRUMPTIOUS FEASTS, BREAMS
AND HALIBUT SWIMMING AROUND.
HE SPENT HIS TIME THERE
AS IF IN A DREAM.
AH!
I HAVEN'T EATEN BREAM
OR HALIBUT IN A LONG WHILE.
THE DAYS PASSED,
AND BEFORE HE KNEW IT,
THE TIME CAME TO GO BACK.
AND AS A KEEPSAKE,
HE WAS GIVEN THE TAMATEBAKO.
TAMATEBAKO?
IS THAT SCRUMPTIOUS, TOO?
NO, IT'S NOT FOOD.
IT'S A BIG CHEST
WITH A TREASURE INSIDE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY TREASURE
IN A LONG TIME, EITHER.
YOU TWO ARE SO CLUELESS,
IT'S PITIFUL.
THIS IS AN ANCIENT FANTASY.
IT'S A FOLKTALE.
TAMATEBAKO'S THE TURTLE?
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT IDEA?
- HEE HEE HEE.
- HUH?
AHH. I SHOULD GIVE UP
THE PONIES.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
HUH?
WELL... HUH?
PAY UP... 6,300 WOOLONGS.
WHAT? WHERE DID THAT
COME FROM, HUH?
SPECIAL DELIVERY FOR YOU.
WELL, I DIDN'T ORDER ANYTHING.
IT WAS C.O.D. TO TOP IT OFF,
THERE'S NO RETURN ADDRESS ON IT.
I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO ACCEPT IT
AND PAY YOUR TAB. HMM?
[ENGINE FIRING UP]
HEY, HOLD ON!
HEY!
I WANT MY MONEY, OR ELSE!
SHE'S A BUSY GIRL, HUH?
A COLLECTION FOR THE LIFE
EXTENSION AGENCY, OR ELSE... NO.
COULD IT BE...
OH, THERE'S JUST TOO MANY PEOPLE
WHO WANT A PIECE OF ME!
TIME FOR FAYE'S FAMOUS
DISAPPEARING ACT.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S ODD FOR A WOMAN
WHO ALWAYS WANTS
OTHER PEOPLE'S STUFF
HERE SHE GETS
SOMETHING FOR FREE,
AND SHE WON'T EVEN TOUCH IT?
YEAH, BUT SHE'S MADE A LOT
OF ENEMIES. THINK ABOUT THAT.
WELL, I'D BETTER RUN
SOME TESTS ON IT
AN EXPLOSIVES TEST
AND A BIOCHEMICAL EXAMINATION.
NAH.
I'LL JUST RETURN
IT TO THE FREIGHT COMPANY
AND TELL THEM
I WANT MY MONEY BACK.
I'LL SAY IT WAS A MISTAKE.
[PAPER RIPPING]
WHOA!
WH-WH-- HOLD IT!
SPIKE, NO... SPIKE!
HMM?
HUH?
HUH. HMM.
WHAT THE HELL IS IT?
IT'S NOT TICKING,
LIKE IT'S ABOUT TO BLOW?
- UHUH.
- ED'S GOT DATA!
- HMM?
- DATA ON THE FREIGHT ROUTING.
THE SENDER IS A...
NON-PROFIT CONVENT ON EUROPA.
THERE'S MORE. LOOK.
HMM. PLUTO PENITENTIARY?
ASTEROID "B" ACTORS STUDIO?
URANUS OBSERVATORY NUMBER 9?
VENUS ACTION NEWS NETWORK?!
FORWARDED AND FORWARDED AGAIN.
THIS THING'S BEEN PASSED AROUND
THE ENTIRE SOLAR SYSTEM.
OH, READ THIS!
"DUE TO THE EXPLOSION
AT THE LUNAR GATE,
ALL DATA ENCODED BEFORE 2022
IS MISSING."
SO IT'S AN ANTIQUE, THEN.
APPARENTLY, IT'S SOMETHING
CALLED A VIDEOTAPE
AN ARTIFACT FROM DAYS GONE BY.
HMM.
SHE RAN OFF WITHOUT A WORD,
SO SHE'S GOT NO COMPLAINT
IF WE SELL THE THING.
YOU THINK IT WILL SELL?
THIS GUY'S CRAZY FOR ANYTHING
FROM THE 20th CENTURY.
HE'LL BUY IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S WORTH ANYTHING.
THE REAL VALUE OF A TREASURE
LIKE THIS
CAN'T BE DETERMINED
BY LOOKING AT IT.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED
HOW MUCH YOU CAN SELL
THIS STUFF FOR SOMETIMES.
ANYWAY, IF IT COVERS
THE C.O.D. CHARGES,
I'LL BE HAPPY.
EXCUSE ME!
- QUIET!
- HMM?
BUT IT'S SO DIFFERENT HERE
THAN WHERE WE GREW UP.
NOTHING IS LIKE IT WAS
IN MINNESOTA.
I'M SO WORRIED.
DO YOU THINK WE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIT IN HERE AND LIVE
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE?
UM... TO BE HONEST, SIS,
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT IT, TOO.
BUT NOW I'M SURE WE'RE FINE...
BECAUSE I'M HERE
WITH MY OWN TWIN SISTER.
HA HA. I'M GLAD,
TWIN BROTHER.
WELL, I GOT TO START WORK
BRIGHT AND EARLY TOMORROW.
- GOOD NIGHT, BRANDON.
- GOOD NIGHT.
OH, GOD, THAT WAS GOOD!
20th CENTURY TV WAS THE BEST!
ON THE OTHER HAND,
OUR DRAMAS ARE SO BORING,
IT'S PITIFUL.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW YOU
YOU'RE GOING TO--
AAH! HEY! YOU-- YOU CAN'T
DO THAT! CIGARETTE, MAN!
DON'T YOU REALIZE THAT SMOKE
CAN SCREW UP ELECTRICAL STUFF?
SHEESH! THIS IS WHY I HATE
PEOPLE WHO DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
AAH! IDIOT, IDIOT!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?!
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU GUYS
WANT HERE?!
WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAINST ME?!
WE'VE GOT NOTHING
AGAINST YOU, PAL.
WE'VE JUST GOT SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT WANT TO BUY.
OH! IS THAT A BETA CASSETTE?
WOW! WHAT AN AMAZING FIND!
WHERE DID YOU GUYS GET
A HOLD OF THIS THING?
IT'S A MIRACLE IT'S
ALL IN ONE PIECE. A MIRACLE!
BETA? HMM.
NEVER HEARD OF IT?
I'LL EXPLAIN FOR YOUR BENEFIT.
WELL, BACK IN
THE 20th CENTURY, YOU SEE,
THEY DIDN'T RECORD
MOVIES ON DISKS.
IT WAS PRIMITIVE.
THEY USED THESE THINGS
CALLED VIDEOTAPES,
WHICH ARE IN CASSETTES
LIKE THIS.
THEY'RE NOT DIGITAL,
MIND YOU.
THEY'RE COMPLETELY ANALOG,
AND THEY'RE ALSO MAGNETIC!
MAGNETIC WOW!
YOU SEE,
IT'S ALL BECAUSE THEY USED
ELECTROMAGNETIC SIGNALS
TO RECORD.
ISN'T THAT WILD? I MEAN, TALK
ABOUT PRIMORDIAL TECHNOLOGY!
HA HA! BUT THE GUYS WHO
CAME UP WITH THIS STUFF
CREATED TWO
STANDARDS BETA AND VHS.
THE BETA CASSETTES
WERE SMALL FOR THEIR TIME,
AND THE DECKS DIDN'T
TAKE MUCH SPACE.
STILLFRAME AND SLOWMO WERE
ALMOST NOISE FREE,
AND SINCE BETA HAD
HIGHQUALITY IMAGES,
SMART USERS
SUPPORTED IT HEAVILY.
BUT THAT'S JUST THE BEGINNING
OF THE TRAGIC HISTORY OF BETA.
NO NEED TO TELL IT ALL.
HUH? OH, MAN.
I WAS REALLY ON A ROLL.
LOOK, BUDDY... ARE YOU
GOING TO BUY IT OR WHAT?
HA HA... UGH.
THERE. WE GOT TO SEE
WHAT'S IN IT, YOU KNOW.
[STATIC BUZZING]
HUH?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
OHH.
SO WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S HARD TO ADJUST
THE TRACKING
ON THESE
EARLY BETAS.
THIS WAY... OR THIS WAY?
UH, THERE WE GO.
OH!
[SEA GULLS CAWING]
HUH?
[WAVES CRASHING ON SHORE]
AHH...
OH!
THE TAPE IS MESSED UP! AAH!
[THUMPING]
THAT ISN'T HELPING, SPIKE.
IT'S NOT? HUH.
[DOGS BARKING]
COME ON. YOU CAN DO IT, BOY.
RUN! YEAH!
HA HA!
DOGS ARE BETTER THAN PONIES!
MY SHIP WORKS BETTER
WHEN I KICK IT.
AHH, RIGHT.
YOU JUST DON'T
KNOW WHEN TO QUIT.
BRUTE FORCE DOESN'T
SOLVE EVERYTHING.
[BEEPING]
HMM?
YOU OWE ME A NEW DECK,
DAMN IT!
YOU BACK AGAIN?
YOU ARE REFUSING TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR BREAKING MY MACHINE!
YEAH, AND HOW ABOUT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY
FOR RUINING MY VIDEOTAPE?
EARLY BETA DECKS EAT
TAPES ALL THE TIME.
ANYWAY, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO PAY
FOR THE COST OF THE REPAIRS!
WE'LL CALL IT EVEN
FOR MY TAPE.
NO WAY! I
THE GUY'S CRAZY.
ED TO BETA DECK.
COME IN, PLEASE!
THERE'S ONLY ONE OF THEM AROUND.
WHERE ARE YOU HIDING, BETA?
YOOM! THE UNDERGROUND
CITY MUSEUM
IT'S THERE IN OLD ASIA.
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT WHAT'S
ON THAT TAPE IF IT KILLS ME.
YEAH? IT JUST MIGHT.
YOU REALLY THINK IT'S WORTH IT?
GO, GO. GO, GO! YES!
I DID IT!
OH, I WONDER IF ALL THIS TIME,
THOSE GUYS WERE
JUST SUCKING UP MY LUCK.
HA HA HA!
YES? HELLO?
ANYBODY? HUH.
HEY, IT'S ME. HELLO!
OH, IT'S FAYE.
WHAT'S UP?
HELLO, ED.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS, ANYWAY?
WE'RE ON EARTH.
HUH?
WE'RE ON EARTH!
EARTH?! WHAT?
YOU JUST TOOK OFF FOR EARTH
AND LEFT ME BEHIND?
SPIKE AND JET ARE TRYING
TO FIND A BETA DECK.
[BEEP]
UNH! HMM.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
ALL RIGHT,
JUST A LITTLE FARTHER.
THINK WE'RE REALLY GOING TO
FIND ONE AT A PLACE LIKE THIS?
WELL, WE'LL NEVER KNOW UNLESS
WE CHECK IT OUT, RIGHT?
28 FLOORS DOWN.
[CLICK CLICK]
IT'S NOT WORKING?
[GRUNTING]
NO WONDER IT'S STUCK.
THE CABLE BROKE.
[CREAKING]
[BOOM]
HUH? AAH!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
UNH...
[CRASH]
AAH!
WHEW.
[GRUNTING]
[BANGING]
AAH!
TELL ME AGAIN WHY IN THE WORLD
WE'RE GOING THROUGH ALL OF THIS.
IT'S A LESSON TO REMIND YOU
THAT TREASURE HUNTS
ARE ALWAYS TROUBLE.
TREASURE HUNTS?
WHAT TREASURE ARE WE HUNTING?
TAMATEBAKO, WAS IT?
WHEN HE OPENS THE TAMATEBAKO,
HE TURNS INTO AN OLD MAN.
NOW I KNOW WHY.
EVEN IF WE TURNED BACK NOW,
WE WOULDN'T BE ANY YOUNGER.
HMM?
THIS PLACE
IS SOME RIUGUJO.
WHERE'D THAT MINX
RUN OFF TO, ANYWAY?
[BARKING]
GO, GO. GO, GO, GO!
OH... GRR!
OH...
WELL, NOTHING I COULD HAVE DONE.
RACES ARE ALL LUCK, ANYWAY.
- SO... IS IT HERE?
- IT'S HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
IS THIS IT?
YEAH. THAT'S GOT TO BE IT.
AND...WHICH ONE
DO WE TAKE BACK?
OOH.
LET'S SEE.
WELL, THEY SAY THE GREATER
SERVES FOR THE LESSER.
HMM.
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE SIZE.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
IT WON'T GO IN.
PUSH HARDER.
BUT IT'S...
AH, THAT'S THE WRONG ONE.
HUH?
YOU GOT A VHS.
IT WON'T PLAY BETA.
HUH?!
[HORN BLOWS]
[BEEPING]
OH, HELLO? IT'S ME.
[BEEP]
HMM.
[EIN BARKS]
MMHMM.
EIN! WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
[BARKING]
WHOA! IT'S FAYE!
WELL, I'M GLAD I REACHED
A LIFE FORM
THAT'S CAPABLE OF SPEECH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
DID ANY VISITORS SHOW UP
LOOKING FOR ME?
VISITORS? HMM.
I MEAN LIKE SCARY GUYS
WHO SCREAM STUFF LIKE,
"GIVE ME BACK MY MONEY,"
OR, "YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!"
MMM... THERE WAS ONE.
HUH? WHAT DID HE SAY?
SOMETHING LIKE, "PAY ME BACK,
GET EVEN, TAPE,
MUNCH MUNCH, GRIND GRIND,
BYE BYE."
HEE HEE HEE.
HUH? OH. OH, WELL.
WHERE ARE SPIKE AND JET?
DISAPPOINTED AND SAD.
HMM? OH, I SEE.
HMM. THAT'S HOW IT IS.
OH, WELL. HUH.
UH, LISTEN, ED.
I GUESS, IF THEY'RE THAT LONELY
WITHOUT ME, I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I'M COMING BACK TO THE SHIP.
[BEEP]
WHAT? ANOTHER PACKAGE
FOR THAT WENCH?
I WON'T ACCEPT IT.
TAKE IT BACK.
OH!
HMM?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
HMM.
DAMMIT, WHY SHOULD I HAVE
TO PAY THE SHIPPING FOR HER...
AND NOT ONCE, BUT TWICE?
THIS SURE IS
A LOT OF PACKAGING.
AH!
- HMM?
- HUH?
- BETA! HA HA!
- WE CAN SEE THE TAPE WITH THIS?
- MMHMM.
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOING, GUYS?
LONG TIME NO SEE.
UHHUH.
IT'S SHOW TIME!
NYOO!
HOLD ON.
HMM?
IF YOU WANT TO WATCH,
YOU HAVE TO PAY
THE C.O.D. CHARGES
31,500 WOOLONGS.
HMM. ALL RIGHT,
THEN I WON'T SEE IT.
HEH HEH.
OH!
WE GOT PICTURE.
OOH. WHAT'S THAT?
OH, LOOK! WHAT'S THAT?
SHH. WATCH AND SEE.
OH, WELL, UM...
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE,
UM... WELL, WE ALL
DECIDED THAT WE'D SEND
OURSELVES A MESSAGE
10 YEARS IN THE FUTURE.
[GIGGLING]
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
DON'T LAUGH!
AHEM.
HA, WELL, UH... HA HA.
THIS IS MAKING ME
FEEL REALLY SHY.
UM, SOMETHING I WANT TO SAY...
OH, UH... GOOD MORNING.
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
NO! WAIT!
GOOD MORNING, ME.
DID YOU SLEEP WELL, AND...
DID YOU WAKE UP FEELING GOOD?
DO THE LIGHT AND THE WIND
AND THE SMELL
AND THE SOUNDS ALL SEEM
LIKE THEY'RE BRAND NEW
AND FRESH THIS MORNING?
IS EACH AND EVERY CELL IN YOUR
WHOLE BODY AWAKE AND ALIVE NOW?
TODAY, YOU ARE
WHO YOU ARE TODAY, SEE?
YOU'RE STILL ME, BUT YOU'RE
A NEWER VERSION.
MYSELF 10 YEARS FROM NOW
THAT'S SO FAR AWAY,
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO IMAGINE.
AM I ALONE, OR IS THERE
A WONDERFUL PERSON NEXT TO ME?
WELL, KNOWING ME,
I'M SURE YOU'RE CAUSING
ALL KINDS OF TROUBLE
FOR LOTS OF DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
I'M SORRY. I DON'T MEAN TO.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S PART OF LIFE,
TOO, ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE NOT PERFECT,
BUT YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO GIVE,
SO REMEMBER...
I'LL ALWAYS BE CHEERING YOU ON.
AND NOW A BIG CHEER
FROM MY HEART.
LET'S... GO... ME!
ALL RIGHT!
DO YOUR BEST, DO YOUR BEST!
DON'T LOSE, ME!
LET'S GO! DON'T LOSE!
DO YOUR BEST!
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
DON'T YOU LOSE,
DON'T YOU LOSE, ME, ME, ME!
GO, ME! YAY!
HEE HEE HEE!
IN YOUR TIME,
I'M NO LONGER HERE,
BUT I AM HERE TODAY,
AND I'LL ALWAYS BE CHEERING
FOR ME RIGHT HERE
CHEERING FOR YOU,
MY ONLY SELF.
YOU KNOW, I'M STARTING
TO GET TIRED OF US
DOING ALL THE PREVIEWS
LIKE THIS.
ONCE IN A WHILE,
CAN'T WE HAVE SOMEONE ELSE?
ARF! ARF!
HUH? OH!
HEY, YOU'RE PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT! HERE, YOU TRY
DOING IT THIS TIME.
ARF! ARF!
ARF!
[WHINING]
REALLY?
[HOWLING]
OH, SO THAT'S HOW IT IS. WOW.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
AN INTERESTING EPISODE.
NEXT EPISODE
WILD HORSES.
WHOA! HE TALKED!