[ED]
Yea, you're right...
[AL]
It does look like her...
[OLDER WOMAN]
She's a darling girl, isn't she?
That's definitely not her!
[AL]
Yeah, I know!
We can't afford to
waste our time here
humoring some old
lady and her stupid cat.
[AL] Come on...
[ED and AL]
Where are you hiding?
[ANNOUNCER]
East City...! East City!
We received new intel on Scar.
[MILITARY POLICE B]
He's still running, then?
Does he never give up?
[smacks]
Ah!
Oh, I'm terribly sorry
about that, dearie.
No ma'am. It was
my fault, really.
That's an interesting
outfit you're wearing...
Where're you from, dear?
Xing, actually.
Is that right?
You're here sightseeing?
There's not much to
look at in East City.
[MAY] No, I'm just here
transferring trains.
I'm heading north right now.
[ANNOUNCER] The train bound
for North City is departing...
Oh, that's me!
Thank you, for all
your help, ma'am!
Take care, dearie.
I've never seen
a cat like that.
[CAPTAIN]
Which way did he go?
[MILITARY POLICE C]
I know I heard footsteps
coming from over that way.
[CAPTAIN]
Look! Over there!
[rumbling]
[crashes]
[KIMBLEE] He was seen
with a middle aged man
who had black hair, right?
Yes... that's what it
said in the report, sir.
[KIMBLEE]
And this was yesterday.
West, huh...
Several of our own
people were injured
while trying to apprehend him.
[KIMBLEE] Scar must
be getting desperate.
But that could help us...
He's leaving us a good trail.
[KIMBLEE] All right...
It's time to get to work.
A suspicious woman...
But that isn't my job.
[bell tolling]
[GRUMMAN] Looks like
a funeral procession.
Well... this is
the place for it.
It's quite depressing...
When you reach my age...
you think about it
being you in the box...
instead of watching it go by.
Surely you can't worry
too much about that...
You still look
plenty young to me.
General Grumman, is that you?!
[GRUMMAN]
The plan was to meet
in front of General
Hughes' grave, wasn't it?
I thought the situation
must be serious
for you to resort to
the last-ditch plan...
so, just to be safe...
I wore a disguise.
Of course...
Now I see why you're
known for being eccentric...
That really is some get-up, sir.
Eccentric...?
I think I'll choose to
take that as a compliment...
Now... what is it you need?
[AL]
Alkahestry...
Maybe they have some
information in the library.
[ED]
Yeah...
If we can't find that
bratty little girl,
I don't see what
other choice we have.
[AL]
I hope we can at
least find something.
[GRUMMAN]
I see.
The Central senior staff
have all turned, have they?
You've gained some information,
but you've lost
too much doing it.
With all the
people you can trust
stripped away from you,
you won't get anywhere.
[ROY] Yes... You've
got it exactly, sir.
[GRUMMAN]
Even Raven, too?
Not too long ago...
I came to Central and
he asked me something...
something I found quite strange.
He wanted to know
if I'd be interested
in a core of immortal soldiers.
Immortals?
[ROY thinking]
Did he mean Homunculi?
The idea of immortality
is simply ridiculous...
I told him as much and
ended the conversation...
And not long after that,
I was transferred.
You mean you were demoted?
Indeed I was, and since then,
I've been stuck with
the inglorious job
of cleaning up the messes
in the Eastern area.
And speaking of messes...
Do you remember the difficulties
that we had in Loire?
A false priest was
scheming for power...
until the Fullmetal
Alchemist uncovered his plan.
[GRUMMAN]
Yes... I remember.
[ROY] Liore fell into
chaos after that...
but from the outset...
forces from the
East acted quickly...
They brought the
uprising under control...
Yes... but then the forces
from Central came in...
and all of the Eastern
forces were dismissed...
Were you aware of that?
Yea. And the peace in
Loire was shattered...
After the Central
forces appeared.
What are they
planning now...?
And what is it they
intend to do next...?
And why can't they hold off...?!
I'm almost retired...!
If they'd only wait,
I'd be free and clear.
Now I know that you're bluffing.
I'm sorry General,
but someone like you...?
You don't know how
to sit by and watch...
You can't do nothing.
Especially when your soldiers
are all hardened veterans...
men who fought in
the Ishval conflict.
I expected you to
come crying to me.
When you sent me that note,
I thought you just
wanted some advice.
But you're trying to get
me involved in this too,
aren't you?
And you know, it's working...
Since things are becoming
so interesting over
at Central Command...
Just when I thought
my ambition was dead...
I'm finding myself
fired up again!
Careful now.
You don't want to
mess up your make up...
Right, ma'am?
Oh my, no!
Do you have an
opening later, sir...?
Maybe you and I could
grab a cup of tea somewhere.
Very sorry, but no.
I appreciate the invitation.
[ED]
No use.
Why is there so
little information
available on alkahestry?
At this rate,
I'm thinking we might
as well just go to Xing...
It'd be hard...
Crossing the desert
in automail sounds hot.
W-What the--?!
Ah ha...
There you are, Edward Elric.
I've found you!
You?! Dammit Major,
what do you want?!
Shh! This is a
library, you know...
Quiet!
I understand you're after
a certain Xingese girl
who possesses a strange
black and white cat.
[ED] Yeah... But how
do you know that?
[ARMSTRONG]
Colonel Mustang informed me...
I'm running errands
for him today.
The word is the
girl is headed north.
According to an eyewitness,
she departed by train
from East City very recently.
North, huh...?
Now that's some
information I can act on!
I appreciate it, Major...
and thank the
Colonel for me, too.
Hold on a second...
There's more.
Take this.
[ED]
What is it?
[ARMSTRONG]
A letter of introduction...
but it might not be much use.
First thing, see her.
Her who...? What d'ya mean?
[ARMSTRONG] Even further north
than Northern Command...
You'll find an officer nicknamed
the Northern Wall of Briggs
who defends our border.
Major General Armstrong.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[blowing whistles]
[SCAR]
Hurry!
There's no escape
for you now, Scar!
[MILITARY POLICE F]
Where are they?!
Report to command.
They jumped on a train
bound for West City.
Damn!
[AL] I can't find any
details about alkahestry!
That May girl's use
of long-range alchemy
was pretty impressive.
I wish we could use it...
I should have asked
her more about it
when we were at
Dr. Knoc's place.
Ling did say it was specialized
for the medical field.
You're wearing a
full suit of armor.
Does that mean you're the
Fullmetal Alchemist's brother?!
Uh... Yeah, I am.
Awesome!
Thanks... but maybe you
should be a bit quieter...
Oh... I'm sorry.
So... what're you
studying? Something cool?
It's called alkahestry.
What's alkahestry?
It's alchemy from
the country Xing.
Oooh... It's from Xing, huh...?
But you and your brother
are already good enough
at alchemy to practice
here in Amestris.
Our country's a major
alchemical power, isn't it?
We've got all sorts
of talented alchemists.
So why would you guys look into
the kind of alchemy they
practice in a foreign country?
[AL thinking] I can't tell
him I'm trying to find a way
to get my body back,
or that we need
to figure out how
to fight against
the homunculi...
So what am I supposed to say?
Well...
Alkahestry's supposed to
have a lot of medical uses...
So, I'm just
doing some research
to see if any of its
properties can be used
to save people's lives.
Oh, wow...!
That's just what I would
expect an Elric brother to say!
[ED]
Al! Hey, Al!
Get ready. We're leaving!
[AL] Quiet, brother.
This is a library...!
So, where are we going?
Look, don't worry about it.
I'll tell you
everything on the way...
For now, let's
just get moving...
First, we'll need to
stop by the hotel...
Hey, who is this kid?
Mr. Armor called you "brother."
Does that mean you're Edward
Elric, the Fullmetal Alchemist?
Yeah.
Aw, cool...!
You are a tiny little alchemist,
just like everyone says!
What was that...?
You... brat...
Say it again...!
Once... more...
I'll send you flying...!
Hear me...?
Your little body'll go
straight out into space!
That's true, too!
You hate being called small,
just like everyone says!
Step away from Master Selim.
[SELIM]
No, wait...! Don't shoot him
Uh, "Master Selim?"...
Are you Selim Bradley?
[AL]
Selim, the Fuhrer's son?
Yeah... that's me!
How did this happen...?
We were supposed
to be heading north!
[AL]
Don't look at me!
[MOTHER]
I'm so sorry.
It's just that
Selim's been in awe
of you for such a
long time, Edward.
Huh...? Me, really?
[AL] Selim... are you
interested in alchemy?
Yes...!
My dream is to learn
how to practice it...
And after that,
I want to become a State
Alchemist just like you, Ed.
Awwww. Just like me?
And then I'll be able to
help my father out, as well!
Yea, Fuhrer Bradley...
Tell me, Selim.
Do you get along
with your father...?
You like him?
Yeah, of course!
[ED]
And what kind of man is he?
An amazing man...!
His job is more demanding than
anybody else's in the world...!
He spends all day,
every day thinking about
the people of this country.
Of course he does.
[AL] The Fuhrer's duties must
keep him very busy all the time.
That is true...
It's something he
always insists upon...
He's determined to
work himself ragged.
At his age, I'd prefer if
he took it a little easier.
It's nothing new...
He's always been
devoted to his work...
That's what he's good at...
but then where
women are concerned...
I'm afraid he's
a bit of an oaf.
The first time we met,
he made me so angry
I actually slapped him.
But it worked out for the best.
He asked me out after that,
and our first date
was amazing...!
Oh... sorry.
Listen to me babbling
like a little school girl...
Dad's home!
Hi, dear.
[SELIM]
Hello, Daddy!
Well hello there my little one.
What are you doing back home?
[BRADLEY] I had some
free time for a change,
so I thought I'd
check in on my family.
And I also happened to hear
that the Fullmetal
Alchemist and his brother
were paying us a visit.
Hello, sir.
[AL]
Long time no see.
Long time?
I just saw you boys at
Central Command, right?
[BRADLEY] So, you ran into
these two at the library, Selim?
Yep!
Are you wondering why
he doesn't look like us?
N-No sir...
It didn't cross my mind.
Well, it's because we
aren't related by blood.
We were unable to have
any children of our own...
So we adopted Selim,
and he's our son now.
I'm proud of my boy.
He's grown into a
fine, devoted son.
Would ya cut it
out already, Dad?
You're embarrassing me.
[BRADLEY]
But it's the truth!
What's wrong, Elric?
[AL] Oh... uh, it's just
that we never see you...
except at the command center...
So this is kind of, you know...
It's a side of you we're not
used to seeing, that's all.
[BRADLEY]
I see. But as you can tell,
even a man like me has a family
waiting for him at home...
I'm sure, of course...
it's quite different from yours.
Aw, Daddy...
you're leaving already?
Yes... You know I have
duties to get back to, Selim.
[BRADLEY] Please...
make yourself at home.
You're welcome any time,
State Alchemist.
Let's go.
Please, come back and
visit us soon, okay?
We will. See you later!
[AL] It's sad. Neither
Selim nor his mother
know what Fuhrer
Bradley really is.
[ED] Come on, let's go!
We're headed north.
We'll catch that
obnoxious little brat
and make her tell us everything
she knows about alkahestry!
We'll be there soon...
Get some sleep.
[KIMBLEE] I see... He managed
to escape us again, did he?
This is an accurate map
of the West Area, right?
Uh, yes sir.
This is the spot where
he was last sighted.
Right here... And
West City is there...
Scar and Marcoh disappeared
somewhere in between
the two places.
Trains slow down
when they turn...
but how much speed
do they lose...?
Is it possible the two
we're looking for jumped off?
It would have been
very dangerous, sir...
But yes, it's possible.
You don't say...
All right then...
after they jumped off,
which way would they go?
North.... Or south?
[AL] This is the first time
we've every been so far north.
Yeah, it is.
I wonder if we'll see any snow.
That would be something...
I might like to see that.
Snow's one thing we
never got much of back home.
[NARRATOR] The pursuer...
and the pursued...
Madness and hatred colliding
in a bleak world of white...
An unprecedented struggle
opening a doorway into
a new, unknown world.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 33...
"The Northern Wall of Briggs."
Her golden hair
shines like fire...
made of ice so cold it burns.