In a distorted world,
What can we do?
CONCERT OF THE DAY
I'm turning off the AC.
Alright, let's go.
Got it.
Starting the track.
Are you kidding me?!
Vocaloid songs are pretty
difficult to sing, huh?
Your specialty is composing,
So I really think we should find a vocalist
who's a good match for your tracks.
I already said no, didn't I?
I see.
Well, can't be helped then.
Let's just keep going with the two of us.
I'm going to take out the trash.
Rupa.
Yes?
Do you really think it'd be better that way?
Here, take a look.
22,738 FOLLOWERS
If you really want to go that far,
it'll be a good start.
AIM FOR THE BUDOKAN!
ANTHEM OF THE
OUTCASTS
So, how's your throat?
It, uh, kinda got better.
Like hell it did.
Subaru, Nina, come to the sauna. It's good for your throat.
Seriously...you're not gonna last long
if you're gonna be like this after every concert.
She's right.
Does it hurt?
It's the good kind of pain.
Really lets that post-concert feeling sink in.
Owie...
Either way, that was one mess of a concert.
It was really fun though.
And Nina really went wild there.
You weren't exactly all
that docile either, you know.
And on drums, it's Pleia-chan!
That's mee!
Well I can't exactly use my real name, can I?
Gotta stay in character.
The super-cute JK, Pleia-chan!
I, uh, think I'm gonna get out now...
Man, she's completely hooked.
- Who, Nina?
- Yeah.
Is that bad?
That's not what I'm saying.
Momoka-san!
What?
I'm going to read you the comments from our concert's video.
"It's not Diamond Dust without Momoka."
"There's definitely more "rock" in her new group
than in the new Diamond Dust."
Hey, someone said Nina's cute.
Gee, thanks.
Anyway, the audience definitely
prefers the old Diamond Dust.
And?
Are you going to ride that wave and start telling
everyone that the new Diamond Dust are fakes?
That they should support us instead because we're more like the original?
Is that bad?
Are you seriously asking that?
Did you see how much followers they have?
Look them up.
20,000.
And it's going up.
Remind me, how much do we have again?
500…
Exactly.
Then what are we supposed to do?
Nothing.
Business as usual.
Writing songs, rehearsals, and concerts from time to time.
And then what?
What's our goal?
Aren't you going to college in the end?
I'm asking what your goal is!
You're annoying.
I just got out of the bath, let me relax.
But you know, I'm kinda curious too.
I mean, you were a professional before.
Why would someone like that suddenly
start a band with a bunch of amateurs like us?
So I was wondering if you have
something specific you're aiming for.
Not really.
No general goals either?
Nope, none.
She's so annoying...
Annoying, annoying, annoying!
You got rice on your cheeks.
What's up with her?!
Every time I try to have a serious discussion
with her, she's always so, so-
And you're way too aggressive.
You're like a bull seeing red.
Moo.
There's no way she'll be honest
with us under that much pressure.
Do you have a better idea?
Slowly lead her into opening up.
Slowly and carefully.
That's called lying.
No it's not!
I wonder how she actually feels...
Before that, what do you want to do?
Well…
To beat Diamond Dust?
Yeah.
That's one high hurdle.
They're pros who already signed with a label.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm home...
"Band goals"
"Band how to become pros"
- Becoming pros?
- Yeah.
Eh, finally got the spark huh?
It's not like we already
decided on it or anything...
I just wanted more info.
Back in my day, people from music labels used to
go around venues likes ours
to scout people, ask them for demos
or invite them for auditions, stuff like that.
But these days, they mostly just reach out to whoever gets popular on the Internet.
Is getting signed by a label that important?
Well, yeah.
You can publish your music online,
but you need labels for the
promotion and collab opportunies.
Well, first you should get to where
Diamond Dust were in their indie days.
They got almost 10,000 followers back then.
That's how they got noticed.
So it's about numbers after all.
Pretty much.
Followers are an indicator of a potential audience.
The more you have, the more offers you'll get.
471 FOLLOWERS
Did... did it go down?
Watch the storm pass by
The city is caught in a whirlwind of truth
Where should we let it lead?
If we can smile upon arrival
Let us hold our hands
It's not a dream
"If nothing's going to come of it anyway, we're better off the way we are now."
"If we're going to get hurt,
we might as well just stay like this."
I don't think you're completely wrong
to think that, you know.
But you'll still have to change that.
Otherwise, that sounds ridiculous.
AIM FOR BUDOKAN!
Do you really think it'll go well?
I can't know that.
Even the most compatible people
sometimes fight and drift apart,
while others without anything in common
might just stay together for life.
But something tells me you'll get
along pretty well with those three.
And why's that?
Gut feeling.
Wanna keep going?
We still have to clean up, so we probably won't have enough time.
True.
Nina, you okay with that?
Nina?
I wanted to ask if we could
discuss our stage outfits.
I'm fine with that,
But weren't you the one
who made them last time?
Yeah, but I thought we could
go for something cuter next time.
Something cuter?
Oh, and by the way, can I pleease upload these photos of you to our socials?
Oooh, nice!
Shining like a star!
This will definitely get us a ton of followers-
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
But you were so into it
when we were taking them...
How about you post your own mug instead!
Sorry, I just thought our fans
would appreciate some fanservice...
And what if my grandma sees it, genius?
Do you really want more followers that much?
We need to be able to attract customers.
In that case, let's all put on school uniforms
and rebrand ourselves to
Shin-Kawasaki Girls' High.
If Momoka-san wore a school uniform, it'd be like we're scamming people...
Girl, that's a low blow.
I'll kick your ass.
But if that's actually going
to work, then maybe...
Are you serious?
Isn't that exactly what the new
Diamond Dust is doing?
I know that.
But we'll never even be on the same
playing field if we can't go professional.
And for that we need a big audience, so...
When did we even start talking so big?
That's the only way we can beat them!
And since when did we start
talking about beating anyone?
I keep telling you,
I'm not holding a grudge against them.
I still don't want to lose to them.
I don't care.
Don't go shoving your daydreams
and personal circumstances on people.
I get it.
But I still don't want to lose to them.
Listen, I understand you and everything, but-
Good evening!
But suddenly throwing this going
pro stuff at her is a bit...
I don't think it'll be all smooth sailing
just because she already was a pro.
And I don't think we can beat Diamond Dust as we are now.
But I hate the idea of just giving up without trying.
We're not in the wrong here.
Medium without onions, please.
Medium for me, please.
Alright, two mediums and-
Huh?
Nice to meet you.
So you were musicians.
Allow us to introduce ourselves.
I'm Rupa. And this is Tomo Ebizuka.
We've been composing on
our own for a while now.
I've seen this before.
Yeah, it got pretty popular.
So you two were behind it, huh.
She's so cute...
That's kind of you.
Wait, so the reason you brought us here is...
You want a band duel?
Nope.
- A complaint?
- Not at all.
Ooooh, I know!
We're your 10,000th customers and-
Wrong.
You're pretty slow on the uptake.
Scouting.
- Is she talking about a-?
- Nope.
S-c-o-u-t-i-n-g.
Scouting?
Who's scouting?
Scouting who?
Wait, are you stealing her?!
No, dangit!
We want all three of you to team up with us!
- No way.
- That's right.
We saw your concert.
No way...
So we talked about it a bit,
and thought it'd be a good match.
No way!
Girl, fix your record...
But can't really bring in a big audience,
and we don't have many followers...
Same for us.
We're in the same boat, huh?
Though we did get offers from a few labels.
Woah...
But once we started discussing the details,
we realized what they had in mind wasn't
exactly the kind of music we wanted to do.
They just wanted us to make things
that would fill their pockets.
That might be a bit harsh,
but that's the gist of it.
Let's just say they weren't
a good match for Tomo-chan.
And that's why you came to us?
Yes. I saw your concert,
and it got me thinking.
You guys definitely play exactly
what you want, just like us.
So maybe we'll be able to you know, have a proper clash of opinions.
You really think so?
Am I wrong?
No, that's exactly the
vibe we were going for.
Nina's definitely an expert when
it comes to clashing opinions.
- Come in.
- Thanks for having us.
I'll turn on the lights in a second.
'Kay.
Was it here?...
Ouch!
Don't just go running around in the dark.
Sorry...
Huh? What's this?
- A lizard!
- It's a gecko!
So you're aiming for the Budokan, huh.
Budokan?
S-So what? Something wrong with that?
Nothing at all.
I think it's really cool.
I never even thought of something like that.
Same here.
Say, how big is this Budokan?
You don't know about it?
Sure do, I heard about it. And saw it on TV.
Country bumpkin...
You're from Sendai yourself, you know...
Wait, you're from Sendai?
I'm from Kumamoto!
Huh? I'm talking about the city in Miyagi.
TL Note : There is another Sendai, which is a small village in the Kagoshima prefecture, deep in the countryside and much closer to Kumamoto where Nina is from. So basically Nina mistakenly thought they're fellow country bumpkins.
Oh come on...
Since we're close to it anyway,
want to go see it up close?
Ugh, it's way too late for going out...
Come on now, seeing your goal up close will be good for you.
BUDOKAN
If we manage to perform here someday...
If we really do it, we'll prove that we weren't the ones in the wrong.
That we haven't lost to Diamond Dust.
I'm sure of it.
Aim for the Budokan!
So, what's the plan?
I'll call Momoka-san!
- Are you really that stupid?
- Huh?
She's the one who said we should get a bassist and a keyboardist!
But their goal is the Budokan.
That's basically the same as going professional.
Do you think Momoka-san will just go along with that?
Fine, then what should we do?
I don't know.
I still want to talk to her.
You're at it again.
Is that the only way you can
think of, Miss Know-It-All?
What other ways are there?
What?
You thought of something, didn't you.
Promise not to call me a liar?
I'll tell you, if you're not gonna
go "it's called lying" again.
They're good.
The mixing is well done, and the
transitions are impressive as well.
I know, right?
Anddd, they're a bassist and a keyboardist.
Sounds like the perfect opportunity to me.
What do you think?
What did they say about it?
They really really wanted-
They'd like to try a session this Sunday.
Can you make it?
Probably.
Great, then I'll keep you updated.
- That's called lying!
- That's called going in with a plan!
So, did she say yes?
Well...not exactly, but she didn't say no.
The heck does that mean?
This is just how I see it, but
I'd say Momoka-san has two halves.
One half is fully absorbed in her music,
giving it her all to create
something amazing of her own.
She wants to see if her music
can resonate with the audience.
But the other half is a full-on realist.
She thinks of herself as having "dropped out
of the fight" when it comes to music.
She wonders if there's even any point
to taking it seriously again.
I see.
That stuff doesn't matter to me.
Is she going to play with us or not?
I don't know.
But I feel like she'll agree
if she likes our sound.
She's a musician through
and through after all.
I see.
I think I understand now.
So we have to start preparing now?
Sounds like a pain...
Huh? What does she mean?
Less questions, more doing as I say.
A FEW DAYS LATER
All ready?
It feels good to play in a studio.
Hey, there's something wrong with this cable-
Wait, isn't that...
What is this photo?
Is it real?
How did you take a picture with her?
Don't tell me…
Exactly.
Tomo-chan watches every episode
at least three times while it's airing.
She always cries at the ending.
No one asked you for the details...
Still, you're really lucky.
Tendo Awa is known to prefer to keep
her distance from her admirers-
Wait, Awa?
That's me.
- Details. Now.
- Yo.
What's going on here?
You're late.
Nice to meet you. I'm Rupa, a bassist.
And this is Tomo, on synth.
Ah, you're the girls from the restaurant…
Thank you for coming so often.
Order something other than a medium
with a beer for once, will ya?
Well, nice to meet you. I'm Kawaragi, a guitarist.
And by that she means she's the great
Momoka Kawaragi of Diamond Dust!
Don't think I forgot about you!
So what are we playing?
Can we do the song from our concert?
I'm fine with that,
but can the new girls play it?
Yes, we practiced a bit before you came.
I'm gonna play it my way though.
- Is that okay with you?
- Just a sec.
Well, we won't know if we don't try.
Agreed.
Alright, I'm ready.
One, two, three, four.
Amazing.
It's insane.
Wow…
The city is caught in a whirlwind of truth
Where should we let it lead?
In a distorted world
What can we do?
Momoka-san.
We were wondering if
they could join the band.
I really want to give it a shot.
I want to prove that you aren't in the wrong.
That your songs won't lose to theirs.
I want to show them!
A festival?
The first step is to get noticed there.
They have an amateur division.
We send in a demo, we get selected to play,
we go on stage, and get attention. That's the plan.
And then we get offers from music labels?
Yes.
Well, festivals are the playground of producers.
So they'll definitely be on the lookout.
Hoping to find a diamond in the rough.
So there we'll-
Diamond Dust.
Nina Iseri: Rina Momoka Kawaragi: Yûri
Subaru Awa: Mirei
Rupa: Shuri Tomo Ebizuka: Natsu
Translation & Subtitling: JSICMF Proofreading: Sarah Courchay
To be continued: "Finding a name".