She's being bullied. And in a totally clichéd way.
I'm turning right!
Well, why don't you tell us about those
human experiments you're helping to facilitate?
It was me. It was definitely me.
Where was I going?
I found you...my love.
Enough with the excuses. Or would you like to become a subject?
Just give up on your head. You're fine without it.
People always lose what's truly important to them, don't they?
Like the umbrella you just bought...
Even though you can always get a plastic one...
Forget about umbrellas; what about winning the lottery?
You tuck your ticket away for safe
keeping then forget where you put it.
Then you find all this useless stuff when you look for it.
I feel like I always lose the important things...
Evenin'.
Is someone looking for something?
I sometimes think...
"While I'm sleeping here, isn't it awake over there?"
I feel like ever since my memory has
become cloudy, so has my sense of time.
When did it start?
I don't even see my whole self in dreams anymore.
Here and there...
What can that part which isn't here see?
What is it looking at?
In a reoccurring dream I've had countless times...
I...try to find out.
Yet...
The dream is always the same...
Hm?
Celty! It's amazing!
Yesterday you said you aren't working today, right?
I just calculated it, and this is your first day off in 265 days!
That's a pretty unhappy expression.
He always reads my faceless facial expressions like this.
I heard that dreaming is a way for people to
put their memories in order, but is that true?
What's with this out of the blue?
Why do people have dreams?
To answer that succinctly...I don't know.
There are still many things medical science hasn't
shed light on, especially concerning this thing.
We do associate dreams with REM. It's widely known
that we have dreams during rapid eye movement sleep...
He's a doctor. Or, to be more precise, a black-market doctor.
But I still don't know exactly what kind of work he does.
He lets me live here, and he's also the
reason I can continue working as a courier.
Anyway, knowing what exactly memories are is also an issue.
Are you listening?
I'm thankful.
Moreover, I've recently started to understand that this is what attachment feels like.
But...
You believe that your memories are inside
your head, but we don't know that for sure.
Of course they are!
That aside, you should get dressed!
We're heading out.
I'll take the day off, too.
See, I'll even turn off my cell phone.
I'll take out the modem, too. That
way I definitely won't check my email!
Peace on Earth. Now we can concentrate on hanging out!
So, where should we go?
Should we ride your beloved horse to the sea?
Or should we go to a hot springs?
I don't want to go anywhere.
Why?
Since it's my day off, I want to make some
food to thank you for always taking care of me.
Home cooking?!
What do you want to eat? I'll look up some recipes.
I'm overwhelmed with emotions, Celty!
What should we have?
Thanks so much for letting me borrow it.
This is a real help.
I slept in today, so...
Don't worry, young man.
It's about time you started feeling the strain of moving to Tokyo.
Actually, this is a great chance for you to get a girl!
Get close to the wonderful girl next to you and let her see your textbook.
And what's this? Is the "no necktie" thing on purpose?
That, too?
Are you okay?
You didn't also forget your wallet, did you?
I couldn't...
Huh? Wha?
Huh!?
It's good. It's Russian su—
Simon!
Have you seen Yuma-chi?
Oh, Karisawa, you want to eat sushi?
No, I haven't.
Not here, huh...
The manager's feeling under the weather.
Today is the first day Dengeki's pocket edition of Accel World goes on sale.
But he's alright. He took some medicine.
We went to buy some together, had tea, then said our goodbyes...
But he couldn't go to the fish market today...
Then the maid at the café came running out to give me this cell phone.
So there's nothing.
We're looking right now.
This is Yuma-chi's, so...
Eh? Then don't try to pull customers in!
Hello. Excuse me.
What are you looking for?
I said I'm—
Who are you?
"Things People Look For?"
Please write what you're looking for here.
Please tell me.
Are you going to be here the whole day?
I'm asking everybody.
My cell!
We're glad to have you back.
What am I looking for?
I'm just happy Kaztano's okay.
I made a promise with Karisawa and
Yumasaki that we wouldn't go investigating.
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals...
There are rumors that it's involved with the Awakusu Association behind-the-scenes and has ties with the North American firm Nebula.
But I'm not going to find anything out by doing this.
Have you seen Karisawa?
I haven't.
I see.
How about some Russian sushi?
Celty! Just cut it with a normal knife...normally.
Delicious! Absolutely delicious!
Delicious.
Wait. Why're you crying?
Hm? I'm crying?
I'm just overcome with emotion.
It's all really wonderful.
This incredibly sweet burdock root,
the bitterly salty taste of the miso soup...
Something's off.
No, your cooking is fresh and original, just like you!
That's not a compliment!
I get it. I failed to season it properly.
That's enough. You don't have to overdo it!
Overdo what? It's really good.
I said, "Don't eat it!"
What're you doing?!
What's going on with this?
You do have a talent for cooking, you know.
What's this? It doesn't even look like it has any watermelon cells.
What? Watermelon?
It's about your sense of taste.
The brain doesn't understand flavors that aren't embedded in your DNA.
Although, you don't have any need to eat, nor is your brain involved.
Don't be so down.
C'mon, let's play a game.
Don't treat me like a child.
That's what angers me the most.
I didn't mean it like that...
You've certainly taught me a lot, but I do have
some vague memories from a hundred years ago.
My head should hold more...
Do you need memories from hundreds of years ago?
What do you mean?
I'm always saying it, aren't I?
That you're fine the way you are.
How would you know?!
I might not even remember my own face soon!
Wait! I was wrong!
Celty?!
You're home, aren't you?!
It's quite troublesome for us if we can't contact you in an emergency.
Is something wrong, Sonohara?
They're not here.
Not there?
What?!
What is it this time, Mikado?
Sonohara's shoes are...
Again?
How sinister...
I think I know who would do something like this.
Kida?
Alright.
W-Wait, Kida!
Kida's acting somehow different from usual and kind of scary, huh?
Really?
He was pretty energetic...
What a hassle, right?
I lost lots of stuff when I was little, and would always sniffle, "It's gone! It's gone!", while my mom would help me search.
You have a nice mother.
Yes, both my mom and dad are.
I'm okay.
I'm going to go home now.
Thanks for helping me search, Ryugamine.
Eh, uhh...
You don't have to bother with finding the culprit or anything, Kida.
No, Sonohara already left.
Eh? I don't know...
Me? I'm still searching for them, obviously...
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
There they are!
What am I doing?
Hey, something's off, right?
You can't remember, can you?
Vacant lots sure are strange.
When buildings go away, you tend to forget what was there.
Didn't that happen just a little while ago?
It was a pretty big one...
What am I doing?
I get mad when Shinra tells me to give up searching for my head.
But I work, I know people I could call friends...
Do I plan on becoming human?
Do you have some business with me?
I remember! There was a tall, thin, blue building here.
Ah, that old thing?
A woman used to sell cigarettes on the first floor.
That's a courier for you.
I definitely...feel my head's presence in this city, but...
Hello. Good afternoon.
Me?
I'm looking...for beautiful Japanese.
Please tell me what you're searching for with all your heart.
Um, can I see it?
Okay!
I wonder if she found him.
I've been looking for lots of things today.
I found some...but not others...
His bag wasn't there, so I thought he was at work.
But...
I felt like something was different...
Fireworks?
Yeah, he was on a rampage.
It took a few people to finally get him here.
All this from some fireworks...?
You sure have some rough employees.
It's such a pain.
He made the odd accusation that his girlfriend had been abducted...
And this was the only place she remembered.
He was screaming, "Tell me what you did to her!"
It's the truth, not just an accusation, isn't it?
You'll make sure he won't remember anything about
our company once he wakes up, won't you, doctor?
There's no convenient way to erase someone's memory.
Moreover, I'll still remember him.
We'll send him on his way.
Although I don't know whether he'll make it home or not.
Doctor, the director and I place our trust in you.
And we're keeping your secret about "that."
Oh, that's right. It seems you're living with a rather eccentric person.
At the time, I'd forgotten.
About my head, about my hundreds of years of memories as a dullahan...
I wasn't thinking about anything.
I was just...just...
Hey, could you keep me company?
They won't complain if I order enough for two people.
I know a good place.
Please, Celty.
Eating by myself...is so lonely.
What's this strange and mysterious food?!
Fried Chicken Sushi, Cheese Sushi, Sichuan-style
Sushi, Borscht Sushi, and this is Sour Cream Sushi.
You don't have to make those into sushi!
What're you saying?
It's a special set. It's really cheap!
And a fortune cookie for dessert, huh?
Jeez...
There's a piece of paper inside with your fortune on it.
It's basically fortunetelling.
Here, I'll break them open.
This one's yours.
Show me.
It means you'll find what you're looking for.
Well, as long as you're happy...
I'm so happy, Shinra!
What's yours say?
Apparently there wasn't one inside...
I...can't shed tears.
When I'm sad here...
Will it shed tears over there?
Thank you.
It's okay if it doesn't.
It's alright if it just smiles.
What's wrong?
You're afraid again.
No one is here. It's just the two of us.
Are you...about to remember something?
You don't have to.
I've told you, haven't I?
I don't need your past or your future.
The present you is fine with me.
We'll be together forever.
I love you, Celty.
That night...
For the first time in a long time...
I had a dream of when I was whole.
I'm right here.
Right here.
My love is different.
It's different from the love where all you do is covet and fawn on people.
It's more complete.
Next Time: Inseparable Love.
The person Seiji needs is me.