What do you think?
Yeah, it looks great on you.
I think so at least.
Ah, um...
I'll get another one.
Come on, hurry up!
We don't have forever.
Yeah, I know.
Jeez, this way!
Did you really look at the map?
Yeah, I did.
I'm gonna look around at that shop.
Alright.
Give me your wallet.
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nice to meet you.
Are you going to bring it all the way?
Yeah.
Okay? I know a good place...
Let's sit over there.
I'll buy you another one.
Stupid.
Sorry about this.
It's okay. It's our fault, after all.
Please don't hold back.
Well, then.
This is good.
You two students?
Ah, yes.
It's a weekday today.
You're skipping.
It's our school's anniversary.
It's boring to just attend the school's party.
I guess.
I skipped too.
Right?
Sorry.
You've got ice-cream on your lips.
Ah...
You're really are careless,
Wallace.
Let's go.
Did you get a grip of the mall's structure?
I've memorized it all.
How many surveillance cameras in Main Street?
68.
There are dead corners, but that won't do for the mission.
Don't get yourself involved with others carelessly.
Sorry.
Let's get back and review this mission.
Our package should arrive anytime soon.
Understood.
Zwei.
Your acting...
It was awful.
By obtaining Zwei, Phantom will be able to accomplish the mission more efficiently.
An ideal combination.
They look like a couple of boring brats,
but I'll admit that our reaching the east coast
five months faster is quite an accomplishment.
That's an honor.
However, is it not risky?
Using Phantom continuously like this.
Just like you said.
We should proceed with extra care, so postponing might be a wise decision.
This might be rude of me,
but if you have your trust in me and Phantom,
will you allow us to do this?
To make sure that everything goes as planned, I will go to the location myself.
Is that so? You're on fire, aren't you?
Very well.
I will leave it to your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
This fake name that has been given to me...
...is Wallace Young.
A student living in Los Angeles.
The same name as the first man I killed.
I kept doing jobs after I killed him.
Assassinations.
Along with her.
I...
Don Lucio.
A mafia boss in Dallas.
He never leaves his mansion, protected by armed guards.
Except in another three days.
He will go to that mall to buy his granddaughter's birthday present.
That will be...
A delivery.
The target will arrive on location at approximately 3:00 PM tomorrow.
We will be entering separately beforehand and will arrange the best spots respectively.
And where do you think the best spots are?
You decide.
Another test?
Master told me so.
We'll approach the target by mingling as customers.
We won't raise any suspicion.
But attacking inside the mall won't do.
Why?
The location is too wide open.
There will be a lot of guards and they have control over the surveillance cameras.
The attack should take place where
there are less guards and less witnesses.
And where is that?
There's only one answer.
The moment the target's guards aren't expecting us.
That's...
Enough.
That's correct.
We should go back now.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Target confirmed.
But I'm being noticed.
I have two men tailing me.
Help me lose them.
The fountain in front of the elevator.
Run!
How long do you think I've been waiting here?
I was looking around the mall by myself!
Sorry.
I don't want to hear your excuses.
So, what will you do to compensate my time that has been wasted?
Like I said...
I'll go home depending of your answer.
Fine.
All your shopping will be on me.
And dinner too?
Okay.
I've found all the shops.
That would save lots of time.
That's your fault, Wallace.
I said, I'm sorry.
The target is at an antique shop on the south side of the mall.
The pickup car will be moved to the south exit.
Shall we continue?
Thank you very much.
I think this one will fit you perfectly.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I will be the one taking him out.
I'll leave the back up to you.
Understood.
The moment the target's guards aren't expecting us.
Now,
let's close the curtain.
Good work, both of you.
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
No.
Nothing.
It's an honor for you to greet us.
It is my job as a superior to show my appreciation for my subordinates.
It was good work.
I appreciate it.
Your words are too good for me.
The boy has taken his shape. I see.
Did it satisfy you?
Well, I guess.
Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
Where are they now?
I have told them to take care of the equipment and return on a commercial flight.
Are you interested in it?
Not particularly.
I see.
She got bored while waiting?
We met yesterday.
Vacation?
This was our vacation.
We're going back now.
Is that so?
Was it a good vacation?
It was.
Very.
I see.
I hope we can meet again.
Well, then.
Yes.
That was...
...good acting.
Two hounds are waiting for orders in their kennel.
That's...
...all we are now.
And then...
again...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Don't mind me.
What Master said was true.
He...
completed the course that took me two years...
...in just three months.
He is...
my old self.
Another...
...me.
I'm scared...
...of the truth.
As if he will see the real me as who I am.
Your eyes are...
...scary.
Killing all the feeling,
pulling the trigger.
Taking away people's happiness.