Why-
Why didn't you tell us?
When was Keigo-san's transfer decided?
After the summer festival.
This wasn't the first time he was asked.
Last time, I was still small, so he refused...
It was a rare chance, but...
I understand what you mean, but-
I don't! Aren't we best friends?!
Shiraishi.
I guess... I guess I was the only one who thought we were.
Haruka...
I don't want to hear it!
Now calm down.
Haruka-chan...
I can't...
I can't think of you as my best friend like I used to anymore.
This will be...
...the end of the Underwear Society!
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Until I Met You
No way...
Today I have two announcements.
Our classmate Hayama Nayu will be
transferring due to her older brother's job.
Since this is so sudden, she has very little time before transferring and will be coming less to school.
And once things are settled, it would be nice to write her a card, wouldn't it?
The second announcement is about last night's fire.
It's highly unfortunate, but Mizuno-sensei's apartment was completely burned down.
I want you all to be very careful with fire!
Now this is big development.
And it's almost winter...
No way!
That's really harsh.
Mizuno-sensei, stay positive!
If you don't mind, you can talk to me about it!
Thank you, everyone.
Since Hayama is transferring,
we're going to have to decide on the next class representative.
Let's begin the vote now.
What are we going to do about today's Underwear Society meeting?
I...
What's going to happen to them?
I wouldn't know.
But, like...
Girl's Locker Room
Hey, could I visit the next Underwear Appreciation Society meeting?
Huh? Yeah.
Oh, right... Hayama-san will be gone, huh?
But you'll keep it going, right?
Um...
Without Nayu-chan...
Shiraishi-san, you've got a cute bra.
Did you make it yourself?
I just made some changes to it on my own.
Just what we'd expect from a member of the Underwear Society.
Terumi, shouldn't you increase your bra size by now?
You can tell?
I'm a regular at the fitting meetings, after all!
Wow, maybe I should go to the next one.
I'm going to be late!
What's up with everyone looking all choked up?
I finally got round to showing up.
Today's a break for the Society, right?
With Mizuno-sensei in that state, there's no point in doing it.
What's more...
Hayama-san isn't here either.
The Society didn't even last an entire year.
Well then, I have a photo shoot, so I will excuse myself.
She seems really busy working with magazines lately.
I'm going home as well.
I have a match coming up soon.
What's wrong with them?
If you compare it to someone's house burning down,
transferring is nothing to be devastated about.
It's got quiet enough for me to study properly.
Can we really not do anything without Hayama?
What's this?
I see. The Underwear Appreciation Society's become inactive. Hmm.
And it seemed like things were starting to get interesting, too.
Haruka-chan
I'd like to see you and apologise properly.
If you read this text, please reply.
I'm really sorry.
It seems that since Hayama-san's busy
with moving, she can't come to school.
Is that so?
Then are you going to confess your
feelings to the senpai you talked about?
It's too early to cry about it!
Besides, what are you doing about living accommodations?
For the time being, you could stay over at my place...
Oi, wait a moment, Haruka!
What are we doing today?
How to Make Nayu and Haruka Reconcile
How
to
Make
Nayu
and
Haruka
Reconcile
Wha-! That's got nothing to do with underwear.
I suppose now's not the time to say that.
Geez, Haruka, how long are you going to sit out there?!
I'll be right back.
How could I have done something like that?
I'm really sorry.
I want to see
you again.
If things stay like this,
I can't-
After all that, what am I supposed to say to you, Nayu-chan?
What could I do for them?
I feel like I've seen this before.
Komachi-kun!
Although you didn't remember my name back then.
You're waiting for Keigo-san?
Yes.
Where's your umbrella?
It was sunny this afternoon, so...
You know, Shiraishi...
She's always just staring out onto the field after school.
And when Forehead tries to talk to her, she runs off.
I've sent her texts, but I haven't got any replies.
I thought that I had finally made some friends,
but I'm back to being alone...
You're not alone.
Komachi-kun...!?
I'll lend it to you for now!
Head strike!
I did it! I finally got a point off you!
Just as you've changed by starting to wear a sports bra,
I'm not the same as I used to be, either!
Have you... got a bit shorter?
This really isn't like you.
Did something happen?
Over time, everyone changes a little.
I guess we can't always stick around in the same place, either.
Something has to change.
We can't let Haruka and Nayu leave on such a low note.
As a warrior, I'll go for all or nothing!
How long are you just going to sit there, Haruka?
Hey, look!
These are the remnants of Mizuno-sensei's swimsuit!
Ah, from the training camp.
I wonder if she'd be glad to have them back.
Yeah, she said that she didn't have anything left over after the fire!
You guys, stop moving your mouths and move your hands!
Everyone, thank you for the kind help.
It's no big deal.
If you find anything that could be of use, it's yours.
Thank you very much!
Why was I forced to help, too?
Oh, don't talk like that.
Once we're finished, let's all go get lunch!
Damn it, Amahara... She's been spouting nothing but complaints.
But if she really didn't want to, she
would have come less prepared, right?
What happened?
Ah! The textbooks I painstakingly stacked!
I'm sorry, Amahara-san!
Oh my.
Geez, Sensei, please clean the living room or somewhere else!
Huh? Aw...
Now really, I came over to help, so why isn't Shiraishi-san over here?
Haruka-chan also has a lot of things to do, I bet.
Help her move out?
Leave me alone already!
Haruka, are you really fine with this?!
All right! Why don't we have a break now?
I'll prepare some tea,
so Nayu, buy some snacks and stuff for everyone.
Okay!
Oh yeah, I believe we had some excellent coffee,
but... I wonder if we've already packed it.
Don't worry about it!
Why did you say something so heartless?!
I suppose you did properly invite Shiraishi-san.
I did invite her!
I went for all or nothing... and got nothing.
They were still fighting, then.
Why don't you force them to face each other?
Yes?
Sorry about calling you at night.
It's fine.
Come over tomorrow.
You will  be coming!
But I...
She's leaving the day after tomorrow.
Tomorrow's the last day you'll be able to talk things out with her.
The last one...
Do you remember the first time I wore a bra?
Back then you sprayed water all over me,
and I wore the bra that Nayu made.
Her transfer makes me lonely, too.
But it's been decided that Nayu will go with Keigo-san,
so I'll send them off with a smile.
That's what best friends are.
Haruka, you should do the same.
Yako-chan...
Once Halloween comes and goes, we'll be preparing for winter.
I wonder what we'll be doing around this time next year?
I've brought her.
Haruka-chan...
Let's get in one of the boats.
Is it okay to leave them alone together?
Probably.
The truth is, they both want to apologise to each other.
It's just that things are awkward between them,
so it's difficult to get it over with.
All they've got to do is take a single step, and yet...
Neither of them has the courage.
You think so?
I think that they'll be fine, though.
They'll be fine.
They care about each other.
I'm sorry about not helping you move...
No, I'm happy with just being able to meet you now.
I was really happy when I got your texts.
But I did such terrible things...
I kept trying to think about how I was going to reply to you after that,
and the days steadily passed.
Oh, no...
I understood how you felt,
but I felt so sad that you were leaving I couldn't stop myself.
I made this...
Can we eat it together?
It's really good.
I was scared... that if I...
...had told the truth, everyone would leave me again...
I'm sorry!
I've done something horrible to everyone!
I'm sorry too.
Friendship between women is pretty tough.
Haruka-chan...
Hey, you two!
Made up yet?
Yup!
Even if we separate, we can still continue
with the Underwear Appreciation Society.
We can text and call.
During summer vacation,
we can meet each other and stuff, right?
She's kind of a troublemaker, but she's reliable about that.
Geez, you had me worried.
Sorry.
You're right.
It's exactly like you said.
I should have told you two right away that I was transferring.
Nayu-chan...
I didn't realise that hiding it would hurt you so mu-
Hey, I was hurt by it, too!
And yet here you are eating fried eggs alone together!
Calm down, Yako-chan!
I'm switching to your boat!
Yako-chan!
This isn't going to work!
They're spreading apart...!
Hayama?!
Isn't this how we became friends?
Your rear end was out in the open, though.
I'll definitely text you all!
Even when you're separated from us, we'll still be together!
Good grief, this is stupid.
Don't go around peeping up people's skirts over there, you hear me?
What's with this reluctant face of yours?!
Got it.
Nayu, it looks like you've got a text.
Amazing! It says that Amahara-san is a magazine model!
That's impressive.
She was probably made to be a model.
Text everyone once in a while.
P.S. The Underwear Society was
kind of fun, I guess.
I'll be heading off now.
Amahara-san...
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
I got these for everyone.
Can I ask you to give Amahara-san hers, Komachi-kun?
You want me?!
Thank you. I'll treasure it.
Everything you've done for me over the past six months will remain a precious memory.
Haruka-chan...
This isn't the end, Nayu.
Yako-chan...
Hayama, I... I...!
Everyone, thanks for everything up until now!
I will never forget the time I spent here with everyone.
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
Hayama!
Handout: Underwear Study Group for Boys
ippungoto ni ne tokei o michau
Minute by minute, you see, I'm looking at the clock.
hayaku tsutaetai koto ga afuredasu
These things I want to convey to you are quickly overflowing.
sakki "jaa ne" tte "mata houkago" tte ne
Just a moment ago we said "see you" and "after school".
te o futta bakka no gogo no jugyou
We just waved goodbye for our afternoon classes.
taai mo nai koto sugu kiechau koto
The foolish things we do; the things we'll soon forget.
dakedo sore ga kakegaenai
However they're all irreplaceable.
nyuusu ni naru no wa
They are noteworthy,
daisuki de daiji na minna ga iru kara
because you're doing them with the people you hope and treasure.
Excuse me...
Would it be okay if I go to the next Underwear Club meeting?
mada mekutta koto no nai kyoukasho no peeji
I didn't turn even a single page of a textbook.
Please do! And take this.
hateshi nai mirai mitai sore de ite chotto kowai
I want to see this boundless future, even though I am afraid of it a little.
Thank you!
Eh? "I"?
dokidoki wa wakariau
I know this throbbing well.
Um...
hazu senai tsuuru
I can't step out of this journey.
Would it be fine if I joined as a new member?
Are you all right? I'm all right! We're all right!!
Keigo-san said that he could come back here on weekends for me.
issho da to nante tanoshii
So long as we're together, every moment is exciting.
Mizuno-sensei also expects that she can visit me every now and then.
Can we all do club activities together again?
dakishimetai dakishimetai
I want to hold it tight; I want to hold it tight.
kyou no chiisana zenbu
Every little thing of today.
wasuretaku nakute kamera muite peace sign
I don't want to forget this. Face the camera with a peace sign.
Do what you want.
Nayu-chan!
Nayu!
demo moshimo wasurete mo daijoubu shiteru
But even if I were to forget, I know it will be alright.
I came back.
wakachiau shunkan wa
These moments that we've shared...
Don't laugh about it!
Don't leave us ever again!
haato de yuuki ni, pawaa ni naru
have filled our hearts with courage and we'll get stronger.
Haruka-chan, Yako-chan.
We know