oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
Hooray, hooray!
What's gotten into you?
Nothing! This is the real "dream festival"!
How is that a punchline?
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Pumpkin Band
Trick or treat!
Wow, you got so many, Kigu!
Yeah!
Trick or treat!
Wow, you got so many, Marii!
Yeah!
Wait, this is just wrong!
Shredded squid...
Spicy chips...
Sausages...
They're pretty strong.
These are all drinking snacks!
The whole dressing room would stink of them!
What am I, some old geezer?!
Does salami count as sweets?
White Pepper
Salami
No way!
White Pepper
Salami
None of these are sweet at all!
This one is.
Sweet Beans
Sugared beans don't count!
Something candy-like!
This one?
Jintan doesn't count!
You shouldn't complain about things you got for free.
That's true...
But snacks made from dried squid don't match Halloween at all!
It's a western tradition too.
It feels off in Japan either way.
Halloween is always about John Carpenter!
How old were you again?
Kigu...
The whole Halloween thing wasn't that popular back we were young.
When did it become so well-known?
I heard it all started in Urayasu.
Urayasu? Ah, you mean Disn—
Shh.
You can't say that on television.
Yeah.
We're responsible adults, after all.
Is that really okay?
We try to tell a joke, and everyone goes, "whoa, hold on, you can't say that!"
We're scared of rumors and bad press, so we're always holding ourselves back,
and in the end that just leads to the decline of our trade.
Then what should we do?
Well, we certainly can't infringe upon the hard-earned intellectual property of others.
But...
Hey, girls!
Stop!
So now we can't even put on a high-pitched voice?
What's wrong with just introducing yourself in a funny voice?
That's true.
You're right...
My voice often goes all weird when I'm nervous.
Hello!
I'm Kukuru!
I'm Marii!
I'm Gankyou!
I'm Tetora!
I'm Kigu!
Who'd buy a whole pumpkin, anyway?
Only to carve it out and make it into a face.
And call it a Jack-o-Lantern...
Where's Jack-o-Frost, then?
Is Halloween just a commercial holiday like Valentine's?
We all have our strings pulled by corporate machinations...
But if that's what's needed to keep the economy going then it's okay, right?
Are they gonna try something new once the Halloween craze dies down?
Like inventing White Day to follow Valentine's.
You mean like Thanksgiving or Easter?
I bet one day we'll end up celebrating the American Independence Day in Japan.
I can actually see that happening.
Or maybe Martin Luther King, Jr. day...
Or even Lincoln Day...
That'd be such a pain.
"Trick or treat", huh?
This whole "give me candy or I'll pull a prank on you" line is so un-Japanese in itself.
What do you mean?
It's what you'd expect from an ego-driven superpower.
Intimidation at its finest.
Ah, diplomacy through intimidation?
"Hand over that land, or we'll hurt you."
"We'll set your country ablaze."
"We'll experiment on you."
What kind of experiment?
If we're gonna do it anyway, we should reinterpret Halloween to fit Japan.
To fit Japan?
How about "give me candy and I'll read you a poem".
Who'd go for that?
Japanese Halloween?
How about "give me candy and I'll come with you!"
Don't do it, Kigu! You mustn't take candy from strangers!
Didn't your teachers tell you that?!
But he's not a stranger. He's really famous!
Even celebrities do bad things!
B-list celebrities are the most dangerous of all!
They might even drug you!
But I was talking about Momotarou!
A
Best in Japan
Oh, Momotarou.
That's a bit too Japanese.
It's Halloween, so why don't we translate it to English?
"Momo" means peach...
But how would we translate "Tarou"?
Just use some really common boy's name in English.
Like John.
Peach... John?
That sounds a bit too ***...
You're imagining things.
Yeah, you are.
Definitely.
Well, there's a manga called Peach Girl, after all.
Don't forget Princess Peach.
And Wedding Peach too.
Eh? Weren't we talking about Momotarou?
But if "give me candy and I'll come with you" is out,
then what should we use?
How about "give me candy and I'll say thanks"?
Wouldn't you anyway?
It'd be strange not to. You're being given something, after all.
But do you think a Halloween based around saying "give me candy and I'll say thanks"
would really work as a festive event?
We can't really give anything major in exchange.
"Give me candy and...
I'll keep quiet."
If you're gonna go down that path, you might as well ask for money.
That'd just be blackmail!
Then how about...
"Give me candy and I'll pray for your health!"
You don't need to give candy for that!
That's just like those palm readers you see in front of the station!
Then we should just do whatever we can do.
I see...
But what?
Okay!
"Give me candy and I'll sing for you!"
Hooray, I got sweets! Gimme more treats!
Sticky sherbert mix, candy in a bowl!
You sound like a kid who just got given her allowance.
That doesn't really work.
I could go a candy bar right now as well!
And it doesn't fit Halloween either.
It's more the choice of song, right?
If you sang death metal, it'd match Halloween for sure.
"Give me candy and I'll sing death metal for you!"
Hell! Fire! Demons! Despair!
That's quite Halloween-ish.
Yeah, this should work.
But nobody can perform death metal on their own, right?
Then I'll play guitar!
I'll take the bass!
I'll sing!
I'll play keyboard!
The drums are mine!
Beef bowl!
But now we just look like the evil counterparts of a certain light music club!
Devils, even!
We're like Krauser!
Don't expect a Kaiser Wave from me!
She meant Detroit Metal City, not Fatal Fury!
A fighting game works too, as long as we play it against the light music club as their rivals!
There's five of us and five of them!
We air on the same company's channel too! We've got a chance!
No! It might be the same company, but it's a different channel!
Really?
And here I was hoping we could go to England.
Then we can't take advantage of their popularity!
Doing a band just won't work!
It's a huge pain just to animate something like that!
You could do it in Kyoto, but not in Musashi-Sakai!
Just animating someone who's turning around is hard as hell!
Then what're we supposed to do in exchange for the candy?
If it's gonna be so much trouble, I'd rather not have any at all!
Here!
Oh no, I took it!
Now what?
Give me candy and I'll give you an orange!
Me?!
Give me an orange and I'll give you a Jump!
Huh? Me?
Give me a Jump and I'll give you an anime DVD!
Give me an anime DVD and I'll give you an anime BD!
Give me an anime BD and I'll give you a PS Vita!
Give me a PS Vita and I'll give you a three day, two night stay at the Yufuin hot springs!
A
*Traveler's coupon*
Three days, two nights
at the Yufuin hot springs
*Traveler's coupon*
Three days, two nights
at the Yufuin hot springs
Give me a three day, two night stay at the hot springs and I'll give you a Bulgari watch!
Give me a Bulgari watch and I'll give you this Hermes bag!
Give me that bag and I'll give you a Van Gogh painting!
Are you the queen of trading sequences or something?!
My candy bar turned into a castle! This is like a modern day fairytale!
We're getting further and further away from Halloween!
Does it really have to be sweets in the first place?
What do you mean?
Remember what we learned in grade school?
"SWE for Sweets!"
Oh, those things you have to remember in case of disaster.
What were they again?
Tell me the SWE in "sweets"!
Stop nuclear plants, V-22 warplanes and extra taxes!
Wrong!
Syria, White House, elder Kim.
That's even worse!
Stop pushing and wait for adults during emergencies.
Yeah, that was it.
But what if it's all a trick?
Take cover, or we'll trigger a trick...
It's a bomb threat!
There must be a bomb hidden somewhere in this room!
But any one of these could contain a bomb!
Run for it!
Well then,
shall I help myself?
Kabukichou
Ah, Kabukichou...
The greatest entertainment district of the East...
Kabukichou
It's quite close to the Suehirotei.
This is my first time coming! Yay!
Kigu, if you act crazy, they might take you into custody.
I don't really come here because I have no reason to.
True. There's no reason for a girl to come here by herself.
Marii's a different story though.
Why me?
Just imagine...
You would totally blend in here.
Since when am I an old fart?!
It looks good on you.
I'd say the Shinjuku Memory Lane fits her better.
Ah, the Piss Lane.
The abrupt way you say that is what makes you sound like some old guy.
At least call it Pee Lane...
Or Urine Lane...
Leaky Lane...
A
Battle of Shinjuku
Why is it called Kabukichou in the first place?
Because it's famous for kabuki, obviously.
But there are no kabuki theaters in Kabukichou.
Really?
There are quite a few places like this that are something in name only.
There's no Kichijou temple at Kichijouji...
There are no universities at the Metropolitan University and the Liberal Arts University stations either.
Or the Mukougaoka Theme Park station...
I wonder if there are any eucalyptus near the Yukarigaoka station since it's named after them...
But hey, even if there's none now, there must've been lots of kabuki theaters here long ago.
There have never been any kabuki theaters in Kabukichou.
It's a swindle?!
Then why is it named after kabuki?
Because it's full of people who behave like kabuki actors?
Not necessarily bad, but it feels off.
Not half bad.
It's like Kabukichou fits him better than the kabuki theater.
That idea feels so wrong.
They planned to build a kabuki theater here,
but the plan fell through and only the name remains.
That reminds me of the Oizumi Academy. The guy tried to start a university but failed.
This is where they wanted to build the theater.
The place of the Shinjuku Koma Theater.
They built the Koma Theater in place of the planned kabuki theater.
Then the Koma Theater was closed too due to aging and poor business performance.
This makes me realize how unforgiving the flow of time is.
What are they building now then?
A hotel and cinema complex.
No theater, huh? Too bad.
Times are changing. Deal with it.
I wanted to see Peter Pan...
The Matsuken Samba too...
The famous somersault too...
The Wanderer's Notebook is performed in the Imperial Garden Theater and a few others, but not here.
Musicals are nice too, but the Koma Theater was the place for enka!
Its holy land even!
Wait a moment.
If you want a holy land in Kabukichou, that must be here.
What's this place?
The Loft/Plus One.
The holy land of subcultures.
They have many anime events too.
Though they focus on deep, hardcore events.
Anime Character
Battle Royale
Hey, they have something on today.
An anime event?
I wonder what.
That caught me off guard.
You were right with the deep and hardcore.
But it'd be nice if we could have an event here too.
We could be the stars of the day.
Bow once!
We beg for your later cooperation!
Not that I come here often,
but Kabukichou feels a lot safer nowadays.
There are so many shops. It's really interesting!
The good old city is mixed with modern aspects.
Killer Khan's Gan-chan!
Karaoke pub
Fuu          shin          Hall
I'm not so happy about it.
Kabukichou was the paradise for the underground people!
It was the Harajuku of racketeers!
What's the problem with improved public safety?
Nothing, but still...
If you want the thrills, go to South Bronx or Johannesburg!
That's far.
They'll get angry at us again if we say the actual names.
That image isn't even the right one.
How would you like Kabukichou to be then, Marii?
Something like...
Hey, Ms CEO!
We have some really nice girls, you know.
It's a telephone card! A card!
Here, here! We have even better!
It'll take you high!
Stop, fucker!
Like this.
That's like Yakuza: Like a Dragon.
There's nothing dragonlike about this.
Nothing.
Nope.
A
Anrakutei Kukuru
We had a hell of a time there!
Indeed, my crotch burns like hell!
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Cavity Shore
Why are you drawing that depressed-looking guy?
Try as I might, I just can't forget his disappointed face from back then...
A
Hybrid ceramic crown:
Durable but not
overly rigid,
which means it's kind
to adjacent teeth.
\80 000
Fully ceramic crown:
Clean, white and
stain resistant.
\100 000
Zirconium ceramic crown:
Extremely sturdy and
difficult to break.
Suitable for most teeth.
\150 000
Which one would you like?
The one covered by health insurance.
When I said the words "health insurance",
the dentist's grief-stricken face was indelibly carved into my memory.
A dentist? But surely a professional wouldn't let his emotions show?
It torments me to this day.
I'm consumed with such remorse
that he even shows up in my dreams,
so by drawing these,
I hope to atone for my sin!
Why are you drawing as atonement?
I guess it's like hand-copying sutras or Buddha images.
June 4
Cavity Prevention Day
I don't really get what you were talking about,
June 4
Cavity Prevention Day
but this week is dedicated to cavity prevention!
What do you mean, "this week"?
If you're gonna go by the airing time, it's in September.
If you mean by the time this goes on sale, then January.
They may have trouble fixing stuff for the DVD release, which would delay it until February.
And if it was not only delayed, but then cancelled as well,
that would be simply laughable.
This is no laughing matter.
Absolutely not.
You're right.
Don't even mention something like that.
What if we end up jinxing it?
Anyway, let's not worry about that.
What's a season or two between friends?
That's right.
Don't worry about minor details.
Don't you think dentists are overdoing it a bit?
Compared to other doctors.
What do you mean?
CheBRUSHka
Stu Dental
Resi Dental
Indepen Dental
Presi Dental
Evi Dental
Pru Dental
Prece Dental
They use so many lame puns.
Is it just me, or do you see even more of that stuff around Kyushu?
It must be because the dialect allows for it.
But their names might be just coincidences.
Even Evi Dental?
And Presi Dental?
Not that it matters,
but that first one was pretty unfair given how they tiptoe around that one American mouse.
Everyone's scared to use him in any way,
but with this one they just censor out the eyes and that's it!
Don't look down on him just because his stuff's not in English!
But they say it refers to an old lady with hair like that!
General clinics do that a lot less compared to dentists.
Isn't it because they're facing off against death, so they don't have room to fool around?
Cavities can cause serious health problems if ignored!
In particular, people like us who make a living out of talking
can't afford to have a single cavity!
Your teeth are really nice, Kigu!
I take good care of them every day,
and if I get a cavity I go to the dentist right away.
By the way, there's one person here who's been looking the other way all this time...
That's such a typical cavity face.
Oh no, Marii, do you have cavities?
Of course not! Don't ask stupid questions!
Poke!
Whaddaya think you're doing?!
So she does have cavities.
Go to a dentist already.
Not a chance in hell!
You can never know when another earthquake might hit Japan,
so you'd better go and get it fixed now while you can!
I've prepared helmets for everyone in case of an earthquake.
That's neat!
An earthquake alert!
Prepare to take shelter!
Protect your head!
Marii, you need to put on your helmet too!
Looks like it was a false alarm. Phew.
I reflexively freaked out from the sound of the alarm.
It's like it was telling us to panic!
That's the opposite of its intended effect.
Then, wouldn't it be better if it sounded a bit cuter?
Chiba   Saitama
Tokyo  Kanagawa  Shizuoka
That's so cute!
But it's too normal. If you kept pets, you wouldn't even notice it.
I see... Then, should it be something otherworldly?
That makes it sound like Jason's about to show up.
Emergency Friday the 13th Alert.
That sound was originally used in Psycho, though.
Then, what if you could customize it like your ringtone?
It'd be a mess.
Why am I the only one with a full-face helmet?!
How long do you want to keep it on?
Don't pull on it!
You should stay like that, then.
You could even perform wearing it.
She thinks Marii's trying to move in on her turf! She's mad now!
It hurts! It hurts so much!
Does anyone have a painkiller? Anyone?
Cold
Painkiller
Oh, so you had some, Kukuru.
Well, I guess you could call it a painkiller,
but it kills only the pain of the heart.
It kills the pain of the heart?
Does that mean it cheers you up?
Yeah, kind of.
Hey there, Mr. Dentist! Hey there, Mr. Dentist!
Won't you pull my cavity? Straight outta my mouth!
What do we do now?! She's on some weird high!
Hey there, Mr. Dentist! Hey there, Mr. Dentist!
You better pull my cavity, straight outta my mouth right now!
The drug wore off.
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts more than before!
Medicine readministered
Hey there, Mr. Dentist! Hey there, Mr. Dentist!
Won't you pull my cavity? Straight outta my mouth!
She's high again...
It hurts! It hurts even more!
Why do I have to choose between being high or in pain?!
You're really suffering from that cavity.
You should just get it extracted.
It'll come out when you stretch in the morning.
Ah, that works.
Can't we use something a little less primitive?!
Yeah, this is a bit old-fashioned.
I thought it might come to this, so I prepared a high-tech machine!
You've just taken the same idea and made it more complicated!
And when did this shot turn into Pythagoras Switch?!
Wait, the string goes outside!
The rest of the machine is outside?!
Immediately—
Abandon Work
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
I'm Haroukitei Kigurumi!
It's my dream to go to a robot restaurant!
It might be even better than the parade in Urayasu!
The lucky snake eyes bring you the eleventh performance of Joshiraku,
which will feature Family Play, Sakai Five and Tree Tragedy.
A
Family Play
Sakai Five
Tree Tragedy