Mizuki Himeji is passionate about everything.
Today, as always, she is reading a handbook about something she doesn't know.
How to deliver a love letter.
I guess the best way is to do it in person.
You're more likely to get a positive reply if you tell them directly...
Studying, Himeji?
Heartbeat Meter
Yoshii!
Yeah, just learning something new...
Right! Now's my chance to
toughen up and give it to him!
Tough up
Heartbeat Meter
Y-Yoshii...
Please take this!
Umm...
Please don't laugh at it!
Heartbeat Meter
Oh my gosh! I messed up!
What's so funny about it?
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Tenth Period
Mock Test and Phantom Thief and Love Letter
Akihisa Yoshii of class F welcomes another new morning.
Wake up, Aki!
It's morning already.
I wanna sleep...
I have no choice then.
I'll wake you up with a good morning kiss.
I'm awake! I'm awake already!
Really?
Then I'll give you a kiss for a safe trip in advance.
I don't care if it's in advance or in installments!
That's too bad.
I guess I'll give up on family bonding for now.
Go change your clothes.
Breakfast is ready.
Breakfast? I thought you didn't know how to cook.
Calorie Maido
I guessed right.
It's healthy and balanced.
I picked up the drinkable type because of how rushed we are in the mornings.
I don't think you can really call this breakfast...
Well, it's nutritious enough, so whatever...
We have to get enough calories to last us the day in the morning.
We don't use a lot of energy at night, so the healthiest policy is to eat lightly.
I guess you're right.
A person needs around 2500 kcals each day.
My idea is that you get 1000 kcal during both breakfast and lunch,
and then only 500kcal at dinner.
One can of this is 200 kcals.
You have to drink five of these at breakfast, which is about a liter.
That's too much...
And you'll have 13 cans a day, which is 2.6 liters. The math works out perfectly.
There's no way I can drink that much...
Don't worry.
I bought a few different varieties so you don't get tired of them.
The main course is composed of normal flavored ones,
the appetizer is the corn soup one,
and the beverage is coffee flavored.
Finally, you can pick either the
caramel or the cocoa for dessert.
That's not the problem!
Oh right... I'm sorry.
I forgot that you're still growing,
so I guess this won't be enough.
Stop! No more, please!
Akihisa's pleasant mornings are but distant memories now.
Couldn't she have at least bought some of the solid type...
Eye
Hmm?
What are you doing, Voyeur?
Eye
Periodic samplings.
Sampling?
A census of the bust size in our school.
You're an A-cup if the top to bottom of your breast measures 10cm.
Add another 2.5cm, you're a B-cup, and another 2.5 makes you a C, and so on.
B C A A B D B B C B A...
Oh, a G!
D A B A...
Wasn't that a D?
That's a phony.
Damn, you're good.
Wow, she's pretty damn flat.
Is that an A-cup?
No. You go down to AA if you subtract 2.5cm from A, then AAA, etc.
She looks like she'd be a quadruple A...
Shit! You're going to pop off my kneecap!
I have human rights too!
Delusion
No looking.
A little more... A little more...
I surrender!
Stop!
Looks like it's pretty lively in here.
Hideyoshi, why are you dressed like that?
Oh, I know.
Heal
You're here to heal me!
Nurse
Heal
The costume belongs to the drama club.
They told me it fits, but it looks like a female one...
Lovely
Nurse
Make that a male nurse!
Male Nurse
Oh? Did I read the script wrong?
No wonder there's no opening in the front side of the underwear.
Front side...
But the upper underwear is openable...
I have no regrets.
Look at yourselves.
Do you have any sense of shame?
I have no regrets.
Sister!
Cut it out, Hideyoshi.
People will think I'm an idiot too if you do stupid crap like that.
I'm not doing stupid crap.
See, that's why you're an idiot. You don't even know what you're doing wrong.
I mean, I know class F is as bad as it gets,
but just look at how many dumbasses you have.
I'm ashamed of even going to the same school as you guys.
That was uncalled for.
The truth hurts.
Or are you saying that your grades have improved since then?
This is a school.
Why don't you study a little harder instead if you have time to mess around?
Let's go, Rep.
Mizuki Himeji is currently reading her handbook.
How to deliver a love letter.
If you're not brave enough to deliver it yourself, you could ask a friend to do it for you.
Friend, huh?
Minami...
What's the matter?
Well, you know... About Yoshii...
That's...
Don't tell me you...
You too!?
...have ones I don't have.
I should ask a friend of Yuuji's, not one of mine...
Sakamoto...
What's the matter?
I have a request for you.
You know, this love letter...
Hold it right there, Shouko! I didn't do anything!
You're mine.
A marriage contract!?
No! Don't do this!
I'd rather die than sign that!
If you find it too hard to deliver the love letter by itself,
you could give him a present along with it.
Umm, Yoshii...
What's up?
Actually, I have something for you.
I baked some cookies this morni-
Huh? Yoshii?
Yoshii!
Where are you!?
I was here first.
Quiet!
If she finds us, we're both dead meat...
Screwing off again, huh, Yoshii?
Ironman!
Great timing.
I need some help moving things.
You could sneak it in his bag or shoebox.
If you do that, he'll think you're the modest type and his affection points for you will rise.
I should've done this from the very beginning...
What are you doing, Mizuki?
Well...!
That's...
W-What...
Yuuji, where are you?
If Shouko gets her hands on this...
My life is over!
I'm finally done.
The complete bust size census. No copies allowed.
I didn't manage to put it in his shoebox...
What should I do?
This letter is...
I'm okay with this...
Wait! Where's my love letter!?
Did I drop it back there?
Seriously! Why always me!?
Feedback!
Oww...
What's that?
Wait, is this a cheat sheet for the placement exam!?
If I read this...
and know the questions beforehand...
I'll be able to ace it!
Just kidding.
That's cheating.
Besides, people would get suspicious if I suddenly got a perfect score.
Oh, the box is damaged.
What should I do?
I guess I'll just take one of the
cardboard boxes in our classroom.
Finally...
You'll see them again during the mock exam.
Better start preparing now.
All right...
Found it!
Thank goodness, I f-
Delivery statement?
What happened, Himeji?
You don't look so good.
Yoshii!
Umm... Well...
What's the matter?
Just ask me if it's something you think I can help with.
Yoshii...
Actually...
I can't find it!
Where the hell is my marriage contract!?
All my hard work put into the bust size list!
My prized photos! They were so hard to get!
Where's my costume!?
What could've happened?
I locked it up in the secure vault and keyed it for more protection...
Key
Oh, those cardboard boxes? Ironman took a few.
What!?
And then...
An important letter!?
Do you remember where you could've dropped it?
I looked in quite a few places, but I only found this.
That's the delivery statement for the mock exams.
Wait... did I mix them up back when I dropped it?
The vault is secured.
Students can't open it by themselves.
What should I do...?
We're going to help.
We can do it!
We're friends, aren't we? You should've told us about it!
Friends have to help each other out.
Yuuji!
Guys!
Stuff of ours got locked up in there too.
They might be worthless to others...
But they hold memories dear to us!
We will get them back no matter what!
Guys...
You're the greatest!
We'll combine our strength!
If not their hearts.
So this is the vault, huh?
Key
Dual-layer protection with a secret password and a lock.
Secret Password
That means we need to crack both of them to get in...
Tough security.
Aki, use your Being to break open that damn door!
I'll be the one taking the fall if I do that...
That's right! I've got a good idea!
What is it?
I've played a phantom thief in a play before.
He used a special technique to steal treasures from inside vaults.
So, what is it?
First of all, you need to prepare some fake treasures.
Then, you show them to the owner of the real treasures
and lie, saying that his treasures are stolen.
He'll rush back to the vault to see if his suspicions are true,
and that's when you actually steal everything.
Wow!
You're so smart!
Even an idiot can understand that!
All righty! Let's follow that plan!
Ironman! Look at this!
This is the mock exam!
Then hand it over.
Umm... You're not going to open the vault to check?
Why would I do that? You're holding the damn thing.
But... Uh... Huh?
That didn't work.
But it worked on stage...
What's the difference?
The scenario.
It looks like we have no choice but to blast it open ourselves!
But how?
There's a key and a password.
What do you plan to do about them?
Key
Secret Password
I'll help you out.
Who are you?
Kyouji Nemoto. 2B's class president.
You just want to open the vault, correct?
Want me to help?
Can you really?
Well, I won't be able to do it alone.
If you guys get the key, I'll deal with the password.
Really!?
Yeah, I promise.
We should help each other when we're in trouble.
Thanks, Nemoto!
Where is it?
That's it!
That's the key to the vault.
You're kidding! Mr. Nishimura's sitting right in front of it!
What should we do?
We're doomed.
All right, let's bait him.
Bait?
Someone has to put their life on the line and attract his attention.
We'll use that opportunity to grab the key.
Hideyoshi is best suited for that.
Why me?
Because we can't let Himeji do that...
And Minami won't work either, she's not hot at- my bad!
Argentina Style Back Breaker
Who's not hot!?
What the hell are you kids doing!?
I can explain this...
It's not on purpose...
Owowowow! My skull!
God damn...
That looks painful.
At least I managed to get the key while you were at it.
Beautiful, Voyeur.
It went just as planned.
I was the bait!?
All right, it worked.
The password's next.
Don't touch anything.
If you enter the wrong password, an alarm will go off.
Damn, you know your stuff.
What should we do?
Take a look at this.
That's...!
Nice camera.
I filmed Ironman opening it just then.
You got the password on the camera!
Right. This is today's secret password.
Found it.
Thank goodness it's here.
Me too!
I need to guard this more carefully...
Found it!
That's great, Himeji.
Yeah, thank you very much!
Really... Thank you...
Found it! My costume!
The bra's here as well!
Oh god! It's a front hook type!
So that's what it looks like...
You've never seen a front hook bra before?
They never had one in my size.
Small hooks won't work because these are too big...
No way! That's not true! The hook is sturdy!
No one said front hook bras are for flat people!
Front Hook
Too big...
So this is it.
What are you doing, Nemoto?
Nothing, just studying a little.
You can't do that, Nemoto!
That's cheating!
What's the point of saying that now?
We're partners in crime.
You all just trespassed into the vault with the exam, after all.
If we get caught, we're both screwed either way.
No... We're just here to get back the things we've lost.
Do you really expect that excuse to work?
Have you stayed in class F so long that their idiocy has infected you?
Results are everything in this world.
How you obtain the results doesn't matter.
No way... I don't care...
Even if I do solve the problems before the test,
I've still used my own ability to do so.
It will merely be a coincidence that I receive the same questions on the day of the test.
That's bullshit!
Are you going to throw this chance away?
That's why you're idiots.
Nobody loses anything if I score a little higher.
No one is going to gain anything from being honest.
If you can't understand that, then you're in class F for a reason.
You're not just terrible at academics, you're complete idiots in every respect.
And that is why you guys have been sent to the school's garbage dump of a class.
You're wrong!
Himeji...
It's true that we have bad grades...
but everyone in our class is so nice!
So caring!
So much fun to be around! So kind...
It's a great class!
Himeji...
We're not the worst! We're not garbage!
Whatever you say.
You guys will be suspended too if we get caught.
Maybe even expelled.
We're in the same boat here.
Listen, I don't know anything about you guys being here.
And you didn't see me here either.
That's all.
You guys better grow some brains.
Yuuji, are we really... idiots?
Why are you asking that?
Of course we are.
I guess so.
Not happy about it, huh?
I don't care if he calls me one.
But it pisses me off that he groups everyone under that category.
Himeji should be in class A.
She just got unlucky and ended up being sent to our class.
So why is she being treated like an idiot too!?
Well, if it bothers you that much, wanna give it another shot?
It's been almost three months.
We'll be able to declare another ESB soon.
Everyone went through a bunch of crap because I screwed up last time.
I'm sorry.
Yuuji...
But we're on the right path.
I refuse to make another
pathetic mistake like that again.
So do you feel like giving it another shot?
Do you even have to ask?
Hell yeah I do!
We're going to win this time and show them we're not just mere idiots!
Let's declare another Exam Summoning Battle!
All right!
We'll settle this for once and for all.
Before that, I need to go fetch Himeji's cookies.
Good idea! We shouldn't be the only ones getting the short end of the stick.
Awaken!
Summoning Being...
Summon!
What's this?
It's the upcoming mock test...
That means if I'll be able to ace it if I know the questions on it!
Jesus Christ, idiots everywhere.
Leaked questions won't be used on the exam.
Did Aki do this?
Yoshii...
Yoshii! Sakamoto! What have you guys done this time!?
I'm sorry!
What the hell is the meaning of this!?
It was just a prank!
We went a bit overboard.
Don't lie! What are you guys schem-
I'm really sorry.
Is there a reason behind this you can't tell me?
No, it's just a prank.
You think I'd believe that? You've never apologized like this before.
Fine.
Both of you are joining me in hell for supplementary lessons!
Prepare yourselves.
I'm going to be stricter than ever.
That'll teach you not to play pranks on people!
All right!
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Nemoto
What's this?
A present from a girl?
I guess I'm popular after all.
I have to finish this before Yuuka discovers it.
The sound of a soul being eaten away.
Question 11:
What was the tactic involving forceful concentration of tanks and artillery that the Germans used in WWII?
Let's go, baby!
Value your life.
Next episode: Arch-enemy and Love Letter and Blitzkrieg.
This will be on your test.