When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
I won't let you have Hayate!
Because he's...
Because he's my precious butler!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Won't you be my butler?
With pleasure, Miss.
Who the?
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
The Delivery Was Made in 29 Minutes,
So Please Pay the Stipulated Fee... Is a Thing of the Distant Past
The story goes back to this morning.
Hayate Ayasaki returns!
Waking up make-up!
Not!
Yes, this is how it should be.
Hayate was taken in at
Isumi's place in the last episode,
but he has returned
to the Sanzenin household again.
I have to continue to serve the Miss
with everything I have.
Oh?
Looks like she's calling for me already.
Um... Miss?
Say, Hayate...
Yes?
I have a quick question.
Have you ever had amnesia?
What? Amnesia?
No, I've never really experienced it...
The truth is,
she's apparently planning to enter
a new manga author contest again.
Indeed, this time, I intend
to attempt an amnesia story,
which is one of the more
cliché manga plot devices.
Yes! For example, she runs
out of the house due to shock
that the sheep she loved got sold,
and she gets run over by a carriage.
Or maybe cryogenic freeze or something.
It's true, this plot device has been used
a disgusting number of times before!
But to that, I boldly say...
That's exactly why it's worth doing!
I see...
So, she seems to be thinking
of a revolutionary story
that incorporates amnesia, but...
I just can't think
of anything that stands out.
Um, shall I go to Wataru's store
and rent a couple videos
that deal with amnesia?
Oh, r-right... No, it's true...
Please ask whatever you like of me.
I am your loyal butler, after all!
Hayate!
Then I shall be going!
Maria, Hayate really is the most
dependable in the universe, isn't he?
Yes, I suppose...
I just hope he doesn't run
into more dangerous situations...
Due to statements he made
in the previous episode,
people are now out to kill Hayate.
Tell this to the other
potential heirs as well!
If you want the Sanzenin fortune,
first, defeat their butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
Hey, Hayate Ayasaki! You sure
did a number on me last time!
That voice! Gilbert?!
I will still be taking
the Sanzenin fortune in the end!
Good grief.
You really don't learn, do you?!
To think you would get into
that mobile coffin of your own will!
Wh-Why you...!
Today's Love Fortune
Today's Lucky Item: Pizza
Let's see... Today's lucky item is pizza.
Today's Lucky Point: Park
Lucky point is the park.
"There might be a wonderful encounter
with your prince on a white horse
There might be a wonderful encounter with your prince
on a white horse waiting for you. Good luck!
"waiting for you."
Could it be...?
Maybe I'll get to see Hayate!
I guess there's no way such
wishful thinking will come true...
H-Hayate?! No way!
What? Miss Nishizawa?
You! Get off me!
H-Hayate?
It's really you, right?
B-But what are you doing?
Why are you fighting that thing?
W-Well, that is...
Hayate Ayasaki!
Prepare to meet your end!
We can talk later!
Let's get away from here first!
O-Okay...
This idea is no good!
Never mind winning a fax machine.
I couldn't even hope
for the small screen-tone set
or the 50 pages of special manuscript paper!
Nagi, you have a phone call from Sakuya...
I'm out of service range. Bye!
Wait, hold on!
Say, is my stupid bro over there?
Your stupid bro?
You mean Gilbert?
That moron's rented some
outrageous ordnance usin' my name.
O-Ordnance?!
Yup, yup, yup.
Ya know, ma'am, business's been bad
as ever. It's been a real ordnance.
That's "a real ordeal", ya moron!
Well, anyway, that aside...
He's probably plannin' to go
after the butler-in-debt again.
If he comes to make trouble,
gently rake him over the coals for me.
Nagi?
Knowing Hayate, I doubt there's
any need to worry, but...
Call the SP!
We're going to look for Hayate.
Found it!
Miss Nishizawa, would you mind
if I set you down for a bit?
S-Sure.
As I recall, Maria gave this to me
for just such a situation...
What is it?
I see, so this is how it works...
Thank you, Maria. This will be a big help.
Hayate, it's coming!
I feel sick.
This mecha's giving me
serious 3D motion sickness.
Set! Arm!
Hayate!
What is this?!
J-Just you remember this!
Hayate, hang in there! Hayate!
A dozen or so millennia later,
having lost his memory,
Hayate was drifting alone
and solitary through space...
No... Nono-riri-hei...
Welcome back!
S-So it was a dream...
That's right! I have to hurry and take
back ideas on amnesia to the Miss!
Wait... Where am I...?
H-Hayate, I'll call an ambulance right away!
Don't die, okay?!
Uh, um...
Thank goodness!
Are you okay? Does your head hurt at all?
N-No, well...
More importantly, this is...
Putting your head on my lap was...! I...!
Ow!
Ow, that hurt...
I-It's been a while since we've had
some time to ourselves, hasn't it?
R-Right...
Hey, I've been wanting
to ask you this for a while now.
You evaded me that time, but...
The truth is...
...I'm only interested
in 2-dimensional things.
Crushed!!
Be honest with me...
H-Hayate, how do you...
really feel about me?
Tell me.
No, well...
Tell me, tell me!
My head!
Hayate?
Where am I? Who in the world am I?
Sh-Shoot! I let my impulse get
the better of me and I did it again!
A desperate ploy like this...
There's no way...
A-Amnesia?
Hayate got amnesia!
What?! You're really going to believe it?!
What'll I do?! I've never seen
a real case of amnesia!
Oh, "Winter Sonata!" Maybe
I should've watched "Winter Sonata"!
Bae! Maybe I should've watched Bae!
Sorry for taking so long!
What?
Thank you for your business!
Huh?
Oh! I was hungry, so I ordered it!
I'd totally forgotten!
Oh? Um, could it be that... you're a butler?
What?
Right? You're a butler, right?
Wow, I've never met a real one!
Which means, this is your mistress, right?
What?
So, should I ask the butler to pay for this?
Um, the bill?
B-Butler Hayate.
Huh?
Wh-What are you doing all spaced out?
Hurry up and pay this man.
Y-Yes, as you wish, Miss.
All right! That's it!
I've always wanted to see that!
Here is your tea, Miss.
What? Oh...
Thank you.
S-So I'm your butler, then...
Th-That's right, Hayate Ayasaki. You're...
You're the butler of Ayumu Nishizawa.
Now I've done it...
Oh, man! I can't find
the right time to call this off!
Oh, man! And it looks like
Hayate totally believes it, too...
Well, no helping it!
I guess what will be, will be!
Mm, yum!
Oh, could it be that the two
halves have different toppings?
That's right. This is called
"half-and-half".
Here, Butler Hayate, don't be shy.
Why don't you try this side, too?
Yes, then I will.
What the? Th-This is delicious.
I feel like this is a flavor
I've never tasted before.
What? Those are just plain anchovies.
Hayate, you've never had anchovies?
What? W-Well...
I saw them when
I was working part-time, but...
It's delicious, Miss Ayumu.
Could it be that this is a brief moment
that God has give me as present?
H-Hayate!
And... It can't be!
You're that thieving hamster!
Miss?!
Hey, Hayate, what is the meaning of this?!
Enough of this weird joke!
What? Um...
I-I won't let you have Hayate!
Because he's...
Because he's my precious butler!
Wh-What?!
This is bad!
At this point, I have to put an end
to this, even if it's a bit forced!
Hayate?!
My head is somehow...
Hayate!
All right! Now's my chance!
Wait... What?!
Hayate!
Hayate has amnesia?! That's impossible!
Just you wait, Hayate!
I'll restore your memories, without fail!
I-I missed my opportunity yet again...
Um, how long should I pretend to be asleep?
Indian curry... (Indo karee wa...)
...is spicy. (...karee zo.)
Elephants are elephantine, you know!
Weak! (Zou wa okkiin dazo! Sabu!)
Ready?
We will now begin the Hayate Ayasaki
Memory Instrumentality Project.
I just happened to be
examining amnesia today.
I've prepared various kinds of missions,
so I'd like everyone to lend a hand as well.
I-I'd be lying if I said that I didn't
feel like I might be in danger...
But the Miss was so committed
to her idea for the manga.
If this will serve to hint
at some ideas for her...
All right!
Huh? Where am I? What was I...
Ah! Hayate, you're awake!
A-Are you all right?
Y-Yes...
Hayate!
Yes?
Right now, due to amnesia,
I hear you apparently believe
you're this hamster's butler?!
What? Uh, yes, that's right.
I am Miss Ayumu's...
Wrong!
Hayate, you are my butler!
Nagi Sanzenin's butler!
Precisely!
Hayate Ayasaki, you are truly deplorable.
I shall restore this man's memories,
even if I have to use force!
Klaus, are you saying you don't think
I can restore Hayate's memories?
With all due respect,
that is exactly what I mean.
Oh-ho!
Interesting! I accept your challenge!
Let us compete to see which one of us
can restore Hayate's memories!
Well, I'll be the winner anyway.
Um... compete?
How about it, Hayate? Do you remember now?
These are your super
favorite clothes, you know.
M-My favorite?
This sweetness...
I feel like I may have seen her
in Episode 8 or maybe not...
I'm so shocked! I-I had no idea Hayate
was into that sort of thing!
Thus, the operation
to restore his memories began!
Rarr!
What's wrong?! Defeat him swiftly
with just one strike!
But I can't just quietly
let him eat me, either...
All right! I'll use this
as the trigger and...
That's enough!
Oh-ho...
I'm so shocked! I had no idea Hayate
had such tiger-killing abilities!
All right!
My memories are com--
They don't seem to have been restored!
The technique is wrong!
Hm, it seems we will have to
wait for the results.
Oh, come on...
Miss Nagi and Klaus fought.
To restore Hayate's memories,
they fought doggedly!
Darn it! So his memories still
aren't coming back!
Since it's come to this,
we'll use shock therapy!
Wait! P-Please don't!
Don't!
Go on!
Oh, the parachute...
Mr. Klaus!
That yell just now... Could Hayate
have regained his memories already?!
Or actually, maybe he never
had amnesia to begin with?
What prodigious deductive powers!
No, not yet!
There's no way Hayate's
memories will be restored
by methods thought up by someone like Klaus!
I-Is that so?
But Hayate's taking a long time
to come to the surface.
Maria, move forward slowly!
We'll begin a search, just in case!
I-Isn't this going too far,
no matter how you look at it?
Um...
Please forgive her.
She's trying her hardest
for Hayate's sake, too.
In her own way.
Hey, Hayate, are you all right?!
If you are, answer me! Come on!
I feel a little defeated somehow...
I guess a lot's happened
that I don't know about.
Between Hayate and that girl...
What's that?
Was there an island like that when
we came fishing the other day?
I-I don't know...
Let's just go ashore and see.
Maria, get the boat to shore for me!
Oh, all right.
Oh, I'm coming, too!
Huh?! What the?!
C-Could this also be because of the
strange ecosystem of the Sanzenin Lake?!
This is not good!
What?! The engine's stalled
at a time like this?!
Those voices...
The Miss and Miss Nishizawa?!
Eep!
Wh-What is this guy?!
Could it be...?
Are you the turtle god?
The turtle god of the island?
L-Let's run! Hurry!
Th-The thing is,
my legs gave out just now...
Ow!
If Hayate... If Hayate
were here, he'd probably...
H-Hey!
Over there!
H-Hey, stop!
This girl is someone important to Hayate!
I-If you lay a hand on her...
...I'll make you pay for it!
Maybe?
Miss Nishizawa...
Hey, hamster, I appreciate the thought,
but don't lose your nerve now!
Stop, you reptile!
Hayate!
Hayate?
You lay a hand on either of them
and you will have to answer to me!
Miss! And Miss Nishizawa!
Are you... Are you hurt at all?
Hayate...
You...
I apologize for putting
the two of you in danger!
I have... I have failed
as a butler of the Sanzenin household!
Hayate, you got your memories back!
I'm so glad, Hayate!
What? But I...
Yes!
If you're back to your old self,
that's all that matters!
Yes!
R-Right! Thank you very much!
All right!
The Hayate Memory
Instrumentality Project is over!
Are you sure about not seeing her home?
Well, as much as I hate to admit it,
that little critter helped me,
so I'll let those two
have a little time alone...
Owowowow...
Well, I'm glad I got to see
how your new life's going today.
I apologize for all the trouble
I put you through.
Say, Hayate, do you remember
what I asked you at the park?
What?
O-Oh, what was it about
again? It's all kind of fuzzy...
Figures.
You care a great deal about
that little miss, don't you, Hayate?
What?
But I also care a lot about...
...I care a lot about you, too!
Miss Nishizawa...
Hayate, next time...
I mean, let's go to a pizza place sometime!
What?
You've never had anchovy
pizza before, have you?
But I'm sure you'll love it!
I just have this feeling!
I really think so for some reason!
Just kidding!
Well, let's meet again somewhere.
Miss Nishizawa...
Leaving Hayate with a bittersweet feeling,
Miss Nishizawa left the Sanzenin residence.
As for Klaus...
A bit to the right...
And so...
...he journeyed on into the far
reaches of oblivion on autopilot.
Starting next time, he'll be
fighting a new turn of events.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Sign: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Magical Change and I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
It goes so fast. This anime has been
around for almost half a year now.
Yes, we've made it half a year somehow,
but we still have a long way to go!
I'll continue to count on you, Hayate.
Yes, Miss!
So, we'll have a new opening
sequence starting next episode.
The story will also switch to
"Hayate the Combat Butler! Asgard Arc",
where butlers fight fiercely
over legendary butler uniforms!
What?! It will?!
Well, probably something like that.
Bye-bye!
Preview
What's this Butler Battle Tournament?!
You're making no sense!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
It's exactly what it sounds like.
I want to check up on the level
of butlers at our school.
She's the Superintendent?!
How dare you do that to my
precious Mistress Kuzuha...
You won't get away with this.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Hayate Rising".
Hayate, I wish to see it for myself
with these very eyes
Hayate Rising
when you win the tournament!
Will you be able to survive?