There's something in this world that nobody has seen yet.
Fluffy bangs give
a gentle expression
Gently capture
women's hearts
This reeks...
...of being fake.
Mould
What the hell? It's getting mouldy again.
I only just cleaned it off, too.
It's something gentle and very sweet...
Where did I put that rag?
...and if you ever laid eyes on it, you'd yearn for it.
That's why the world has hidden it.
To make sure that not just anyone can get their hands on it.
Shit, it's not coming off!
But it's nothing a Takasu can't handle...
But at some point, someone will find it.
The one who is destined to do so will be able to find it.
That's just how it works.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Tiger And Dragon
Eco, eco, eco, ecology.
Inko-chan, you're still asleep?
It's morning already.
I got you!
How cold of you, Ryuu-chan.
I told you last night that I have school as of today, right?
Oh, the opening ceremony.
Congratulations on passing last year.
Should you really be sarcastic about the fact that your son's moving on to a new school year?
Hey, the room is dark. Open the curtains!
They're open.
That's a huge apartment building.
I wonder what kind of people live there.
After it was built, the sun stopped shining here, and our laundry doesn't dry well.
HERE
Every morning there's mould, mould, and more mould-
That sharp look! You're looking more and more like your dad!
...more and more like your dad!
Don't compare me to tha-
Oh, so cool! Even more like your dad!
Are you leaving already? What about my breakfast?
It's where it always is.
That was...
That was the one thing I didn't want to hear.
It's because of this look in my eyes, which you always praise, that I...
Hey, wait up!
T-Takasu-kun!
What the hell are you doing?!
What? Wh-
I didn't mean to!
Please accept this and spare us!
This is all we have! It's true!
S-See? We're not annoying you, right?!
No, I-
We're sorry!
I...
Lost
and
Found
Oohashi
High School
Again? You sure pick up a lot of wallets.
Uh, yeah.
I hope we end up in the same class again!
Yeah.
There it is!
Yes! We're in the same class again!
Crap, not this again...
Hey.
We're in the same class again, right Takasu?
Kitamura.
Oohashi High School Opening Ceremony
And now this year's opening ceremony has ended.
Everyone, please head towards your individual classrooms and prepare for homeroom.
A new class. It seems that I have to start off by clearing up all the misunderstandings again.
It'll be okay.
I already know, so it won't be necessary for everyone.
Yeah, thanks.
That's right. There are people like him who understand.
And in this class...
Hey, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year too!
You're in class C too, Kushieda?
Takasu-kun, right? Do you remember me?
I appear around Kitamura-kun from time to time.
K-Kushieda Minori, right?
Oh, you remembered my full name! I'm so glad!
And with that, let us enjoy youth with high spirits and great passion!
Yeah.
O-Okay.
And then-
What's wrong, Takasu?
Nothing. I-I just need to go the bathroom.
Okay, I'll go on ahead.
What?
Holy shit! He's already heading into a decisive battle!
Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
The two bad asses are already clashing!
Whoa, she's so small... just like a doll, but somehow...
Somehow there's this hateful...
As if you'd get eaten if you missed one step...
Whoa, it's true! The delinquent Takasu-kun and the Palmtop Tiger are-
Idiot!
Ferocity of a tiger
But small
Palmtop... Tiger?
I get it! Palmtop Ti-
Yeah, it fits perfectly.
Okay, that's it for today.
Those who haven't turned in the new questionnaire,
please come to the faculty office later, okay?
Okay, Takasu-kun?
Ah, yes.
Are you okay, Taiga? You were late.
I went to the doctor, and he said that it's caused by house dust.
A modern-day illness, must be tough.
So the Palmtop Tiger is friends with Kushieda Minori.
The one with problems here is me.
You okay?
Yeah, I guess.
But, you know...
They were amazing, Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun!
The Palmtop Tiger sure is strong.
Anyway, Takasu only looks scary. He's not actually a delinquent.
Really?
Seems it'll be easier to clear up the misunderstandings.
Taiga, 'sup?
N-Nothing.
T-Takasu-kun, you aren't lost about where to go with your life, are you?
What?
B-But I really need you to turn in your questionnaire.
All of the other students have submitted theirs already.
Oh, I'm sorry. I forg-
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
You don't want some stranger coming in and telling you what to do...
...while you're still deciding on what to do with your life, right?
Please forgive me!
I'm late!
Time Zero will be ove-
A-Are you okay?
My bag, my bag...
I'll just leave her be.
Wha-
W-What are you doing?
What am I-
I just came here to get my-
That's your bag?! Isn't your seat the ne-
Don't tell me I got the seats m-mixed-
Why does she want my bag?
Hey, stop it already!
Why, you-
A-Aisaka?
H-Hey!
Idiot!
She's a mess.
It's a mess.
Your dad's heaven, you see.
He was so cool! He'd hide weekly magazines behind his shirt in case he got stabbed.
I'm going numb just from the thought!
Just because I look like you...
I'm having mountains of trouble you know!
If I didn't have this face, no one would be afraid of me,
and I wouldn't end up getting involved with the Palmtop Tiger.
I'd have more faith in myself.
Best Driving Collection
-Spring-
And then...
Oh right, the new questionnaire.
What's this?
To Kitamura Yuusaku-sama
To Kitamura Yuusaku-sama...
From Aisaka Taiga
...from Aisaka Taiga?
Oh, I get it.
You put this in my bag by a mistake, right?
I can't imagine what's inside since I didn't peek!
So I'll just return it to you, then!
Shit, I've got to reseal it!
She... She's one hell of a klutz, isn't she?
Gonna sleep.
Yasuko isn't supposed to be home yet, right?
Yay, let's drink more!
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
Let's do it, Mirano-chan!
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
Hey...
The window's...
Ow!
W-What the hell?
I know someone this small...
Aisaka!
Use a tissue!
What the-
W-What the...
...hell...
...are...
...you...
...doing?!
Forget about it.
Forget about...?
Oh, that le-
-tter...
I can't live any longer now that you've found out about that.
I have to die!
Then, don't try to kill me!
I don't want to die, so I've got to kill you!
Or you could forget all about it!
That's impossible!
It'll be okay, I'll just hit you on the head with this.
Even if I can't kill you, I can send your memories flying away.
Don't send them flying!
Listen, that lette-
Shut up.
What?
Shut up! Shut up!
You saw it, right?! You read it, right?!
I'm trying to tell you, I didn't-
No, that won't do.
So you have to forget all about that l-love love letter!
It was empty!
Emp... ty?
Yes. There was nothing inside.
You're lucky you didn't give it to Kitamura.
So let's just leave this failure be and-
H-Hey!
Just how hungry are you?
I got tired of the convenience store.
Convenience store? What, don't your parents fe-
Everyone has their own family issues, I guess.
Here.
If you had just quietly handed over the bag earlier, things wouldn't have ended up like this.
How do you intend to make up for it?!
It's still stuck to your face.
Hearing that from a guy who was born simply for the task of adding the scent of garlic to the oil used in this fried rice...
Now see here...
How is a love letter embarrassing?
Listen, that's not even close to being embarrassing. Just wait.
Behold!
What's all this?
Do you know what that is? You don't, do you?
That's a list of songs I would use if I were to put on a concert for the girl I like.
That's a poem I wrote for her without realising it.
Minidiscs to play while I'm on a car trip with her.
I don't have a license, of course.
I have plans laid out for all seasons of the year.
Disgusting, right?
Since I don't have the guts to confess to her, I can only imagine like this.
It's horribly miserable, but I don't think it's embarrassing!
You've got to have faith in yourself!
You went beyond imagining and took action!
You've got to think about the future with high spirits and great passion!
"I present to this to thee, Kushieda Minori."
Yes, just like Kushieda Minori!
Wha-
So you like Minori?
How impudent.
Learn your place.
Shut up! You're not one to talk!
What's with you?! You said you'd forget!
Shut up! Goose, goosebumps!
I'm sorry, Inko-chan. Did we wake you?
What are you showing me? How disgusting!
What are you saying about my precious family?!
I- I-
That's it! Are you going to present yourself to the visitor, Inko-chan?
Go ahead and say your name!
Inpo!
No, you see, Inko-chan isn't feeling well today...
Whoa, it's already this late!
E-Either way, we're birds of the same feather!
I won't tell anyone about the letter! Can't you be satisfied with that?
No.
Why?! No wait, you've already had a meal, so just leave!
Rather, please leave? My wacky mum is about to come home!
No way!
I can't trust you.
And besides...
What do you think of love letters? They're not fashionable any more, are they?
Why are you fidgeting now?!
I'll give you advice on romantic relationships any time,
but it's already late, so how about tomorrow?
Really? You'll help me?
I will. I will, I will! I'll do anything!
Anything, right? You'll obey me like a dog?
You'll do anything to the extreme?
Yes, I will. I swear!
So, let us just end it at that, okay? Okay?
How did she get in through the window?
Well then...
I'll walk you home.
No, it's okay. It's close, and I've got this wooden sword.
Wait, that's just dangerous.
That hole...
Oh, that? I can just cover it up with some paper.
Here.
You can use this.
If it ends up costing money, I'll pay you later.
See you, Ryuuji.
Yeah.
Wait, did she just call me by my first name?
Yes, this is the Takasu residenc-
Get the hell over here! You're-
Yes?
You hung up, didn't you?
Come over where?
Huh?
The veranda, why?
How?!
You said you'd do anything, just like a dog, right?
Wait, that was the thing yesterday about Kitamura-
If you don't come, you know what will happen, don't you?
I can show you what will happen if you want me to...
Um, you see...
Wait ten more minutes!
The seasoned rice will be done in ten more minutes!
Three?
You want some too?
Whoa.
Excuse me?
Huh?
It's open?
What the hell is this smell?
Aisaka-san, I'm coming in.
Something smells horrible.
Aisaka!
Aisaka, Aisaka, Aisaka!
Your kitchen!
Allow me to...!
Please, allow me to clean your kitchen!
What, sleeping again?
She looks like she was hand crafted...
The sleeping Aisaka really looked like a doll.
The house had no trace of anyone really living there.
It looked like it was part of someone's doll house.
But it was too large to be someone's doll house.
It'll take fifteen minutes, I guess.
All right!
What's this...?
Hey.
I'm still at it, but it's a lot cleaner now isn't it?
It was horrid!
The water clogged up in the sink was rotten.
The drainage was awfully mouldy and all the waste was like hell spawn.
And the room was full of dust-
Trespassing, forced cleaning...
You didn't go around marking the place, did you, dog?!
Dog?
I'll have to apologise to the other dogs.
You're a mongrel of a dog.
Mon-grel.
What an ungrateful bitch, when other people have-
Hey, where's your table prayer?
Dear god of rice and producers of this product, I thank you for this meal!
Oh you...
Hey, your nose stopped dripping.
Yeah, since the room's all clean...
What did you just say?
Shut up!
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira soruto de
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
Ryuuji And Taiga
Disoriented agreement.
Surfacing misunderstandings.
The power of genes.
Taiga, you...
You're one hell of a klutz.
Shut up and rot.