C'mon.
Let's get the hell out of here already.
We'll be in deep trouble if someone
from the army catches us down here.
We're going, Yuuji.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
The Demon
Within
U-Um...
Thanks for saving me from that vampire.
Uh-huh...
I really like you!
Please read this!
Well...
I...
Oh, my.
Just what I expected from the hero who fought off a vampire.
Ever popular with the ladies, aren't you?
Are you going to be breaking her heart next?
What do you mean, "next"?
I've never done anything like that.
Well, I suppose you are a virgin, after all.
Shinoa, you freakin'...
But it'd do you well to remember that virginity is evil, Yuu.
Take the Japanese Imperial
Demon Army as an example,
where we encourage people
to pursue relationships.
Our world was once brought to its knees by an unknown virus.
Strange beasts populated the earth,
and many people died.
Only ruins are to be found beyond these walls, every inch of them crawling with monsters.
This is a world no longer hospitable to humans.
However, we, the Japanese Imperial Demon Army,
will gather the remnants of humankind,
multiply in numbers, and take back our planet!
Now, give birth!
Procreate!
Viva la fornication!
Can I ask you something?
Dealing with that vampire landed me a spot in the vampire extermination unit, right?
So why am I still attending this school?
Please direct any such complaints to the Lieutenant Colonel.
That moron's never at his office!
How am I supposed to bring it up with him?
Certainly not by yelling at me, for one.
Besides...
Your training for the extermination unit
has already begun.
Training that will allow you
to obtain what you truly desire.
What I truly desire...
You want this, don't you?
Th-That's...
This is the demon with whom I have contracted:
Shikamadouji.
I've been wanting to show you this.
So this is one of the Infernal Arms
that carry a vampire-killing curse...
I am a member of the vampire extermination unit, after all.
If I had something like that,
I could kill vampires on my own.
You won't beat them without any help.
You need to start learning what teamwork—
Shinoa.
I'll be taking that.
I'm going to use that scythe of yours
to avenge my family.
You can't use an Infernal Arm inhabited by
someone else's contracted demon.
Then show me what you've got!
Really?
Not bad.
But fighting against an Infernal Arm with a
normal weapon isn't going to get you anywhere.
Shi.
That thing's freakin' awesome.
With a weapon like that, dealing with vampires should be a piece of cake for you.
Oh, not at all.
On the battlefield, they're just as equipped as we are.
Nothing like the unarmed vampire you fought the other day.
They're armed? Seriously?
That's why Lieutenant Colonel Guren
emphasizes teamwork.
So you can operate within a unit first.
H-Help me, Yuu!
Yoichi!
What now, Yoichi?
Are you getting picked on again?
Please hear us out, Yoichi!
We're sorry for bullying you, for real!
So please let us be your henchmen!
Henchmen?
W-Wait, I really... Um, I'm just not cut out for things like that!
I just can't!
Oh, Boss Yuuichirou!
It's Yamanaka!
Yamanaka Satoshi, the guy you saved from the vampire!
Boss?
Seems like you've been getting around lately.
I feel rather left out.
Whatever. You guys were giving Yoichi a hard time just the other day.
How could you possibly ask him to make you his henchmen?
Th-That's true.
But we need someone to help us real bad.
So you're willing to throw away your pride and beg a guy you made fun of for help?
Seems like delinquents these days
have no shame at all.
Yuu, you sound like a pretentious twit.
We know that we have no right to ask, but...
But?
Our friend, Yuuji, went inside the Forbidden Chamber and never made it back out.
The Forbidden Chamber?
I heard that Yoichi had been accepted into the extermination unit, so—
You guys broke into the army's Class 1 Restricted Area?
W-Well...
I don't want your excuses.
I assume this was done as a dare or something, correct?
Unauthorized entry to that area is punished severely.
S-So Yuuji's...
Most likely captured by the army.
No way... Can't you please do something?!
He might even receive the death penalty.
It'd be best if you gave up.
Shinoa, what's this "Forbidden Chamber" thing about?
Haven't you heard of the seven mysteries of the school?
A piano that plays on its own, a living anatomical model,
and a forbidden chamber that you should never open.
Seven mysteries, my ass.
It's just one of those restricted areas that the army manages, right?
So Yuuji went inside, and now he's stuck there?
I believe so.
That chamber is actually used as a training facility for members of the vampire extermination unit.
Should inexperienced personnel enter, they may be possessed by a demon.
What? A demon?
I told you, didn't I?
Your training for the extermination unit
has already begun.
We'll be moving on to the next stage.
Please follow me.
An underground shrine?
What's something like that doing beneath the school?
Well, we just call it a shrine.
Long ago, there was a vast space underneath Shibuya to prevent the river from flooding.
The vampire extermination unit decided that it would become their training area.
Well, actually, the entire school itself is a training area for the extermination unit.
We hold a demon underground, and those unaffected by its evil energy are eventually recruited.
To put it simply, this school only serves as a large-scale human experiment.
Did you really believe that a normal school would exist in a world as depraved as ours?
From this point on, only those selected by the extermination unit or a demon can enter.
Then Yuuji's...
We didn't reach out to him.
The demon may have consumed his heart by now.
Wh-What happens then?
He'll turn into something worse than a vampire.
A mindless, murderous demon.
This is why thorough training is required.
Especially when it comes to matters of the heart.
I wanted to show you two just how potent an Infernal Arm is—
So basically, you just need to win over the demon, right?
I need power in order to get revenge.
As long as it's within my reach,
I don't care if it's from a demon or a devil.
Hey, don't just walk in!
Just observe from a distance, and don't try anything funny.
He'll be rescued by the extermination unit.
Nobody's made a contract with that axe yet, right?
Don't mind if I do!
Hey, wait!
Yoichi,
please call the Moon Demon Company for backup.
There's a garrison behind this place.
Right!
Hand that axe over!
That's pretty impressive.
But it's nothing compared to Shinoa's scythe.
Get out of my way.
Seriously, could you be any worse at getting along?
If you touch an Infernal Arm with your bare hands,
you'll be possessed and end up a demon, just like him.
I'm not gonna lose to some demon.
You will.
You can't defeat them yet.
What?
Your heart is weak.
Demons feed on the corrupt desires within your heart. They'll take advantage of your thirst for revenge.
That's why Lieutenant Colonel Guren won't give you an Infernal Arm,
despite your overwhelming combat skills.
Bullshit.
I'll show you right here and now that I can defeat a demon.
Don't be ridiculous!
All right! It's mine now—
Huh?
Yuu.
What's wrong? You were spacing out.
Hurry up and sit down.
Dinner's getting cold.
Don't let my cooking go to waste, Yuu.
C'mon, Yuu!
It's really good.
Y-Yeah...
Eat up while it's warm.
Isn't this great, guys?
Yuu's with us today.
Yup!
Yuu never comes over to play.
Oh, right, Yuu.
What happened to your revolution?
Jeez, did you forget?
You said you'd become strong and kill all the vampires,
and create a haven here for us.
Yeah, Yuu!
We'll always be waiting for you.
C'mon, Yuu. You haven't touched your dinner.
That won't do, Yuu.
You need to eat if you want to grow stronger.
Y-Yeah.
Have you guys been alive all this time?
What are you talking about?
We're all dead, of course.
Right?
Obviously!
You're being a little weird today, Yuu.
That vampire killed us all,
and you were the only one who ran away.
N-No! I didn't run—
Yes, you did.
And you haven't even avenged us.
Come, now. Repay them for what you've lost.
If you want, I'll even lend you my power.
Just accept me into your heart...
Revenge.
That's right. Revenge.
Yeah...
I need power to get my revenge.
See?
So just accept me already.
But who are you?
Mika...
Mika isn't that kind of person!
He's not like me. He wouldn't tell me
to chase after revenge!
He's smart, but nice to the point of stupidity—
someone who shouldered everything on his own...
Yuu...
So who the hell are you?!
Stop, Yuu.
Shut up!
How dare you make a cheap mockery of my precious family?!
What the hell do you know about them?!
Oh.
Huh?
What just happened?
No way... Did you really come back on your own?
What? Come back from where?
Well, um...
A demon was feeding you hallucinations.
But you managed to break free through sheer willpower and exorcised it—
all without using a contract spell.
And that means?
Is this mine now?
No, I'm afraid it's not that easy.
There are certain procedures
to forming a contract with a demon.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren will be the one to assign you a weapon.
But I defeated a demon.
Well, uh...
Even that dumbass Guren won't be able to ignore this, right?
Er, well... I suppose.
And you did save your classmate...
You'll probably start coming here as of tomorrow.
To the vampire extermination unit's training school.
Hell yeah!
I wonder if I'll get in trouble for not running this past the higher-ups.
Finally...
I've come this far, Mika.
I'm gonna learn how to kill a vampire.
Mika, Mika, Mimika.
I knew I'd find you here.
Did you receive the report?
It looks like they've finally found that
precious angel you've been searching for.
Unsurprisingly enough, he was being used by those corrupt humans.
And by "he"...
I mean Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
Now, now.
How will you weave the threads of your story,
Hyakuya Mikaela?
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Vampire
Mikaela
"Vampire Mikaela."