So the legendary warrior, Precure, lies defeated.
With this, the Great Heart Tree shall wither,
and the world shall belong to us, the Desert Apostles!
The flowers have fallen, so why has the tree not yet wilted?
Seems your luck has run out.
Even if I fall,
other Precure shall appear before you to protect the Great Heart Tree!
Dark Forte Wave!
Cure Moonlight!
Chypre! Coffret!
Pass the Heart Perfume onto the next Precure!
Out of the way!
My fairies... seek out my replacement!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I know it's my turn to cook on Saturday.
Good morning, Yuri.
I woke up early this morning, so don't worry about it.
Let's eat.
What's the matter?
Mom.
Can't you stop laying dad's place at the table already?
Why?
It's been three years since he left to go looking for the Great Heart Tree, you know?
Dad was always so considerate.
If he hasn't contacted us at all in three whole years,
he must already be...
Your father will be all right.
How can you be so sure?
I can just tell these things.
It's hard not to be convinced
when you say it like that, Mom.
Nobody's a match for your persuasion.
I'll be off, then.
Take care, all right?
I have to put on such a brave face.
The Truth is Revealed!
Cure Moonlight's True Identity!
Cure Moonlight...
What's the matter?
cannot possibly still be alive!
You saw her final moments for yourself, did you not?
It's a Seed of the Precure.
Even if she's still alive, as long as we hold her Seed of the Precure,
she will never be able to become a Precure again.
For now, you should concern yourself with defeating the Precure who stand against us, all right?
Okay.
Do not concern yourself with Cure Moonlight.
I'll be leaving now!
Good morning! Sorry to keep you waiting.
Good morning!
Thank you very much for inviting me out to shop today!
It wasn't a bother on such short notice?
Not in the least!
Stop it with the greetings already! Let's get going!
Momo's always so darn impulsive.
The only reason she invited us today is because she got time off work and needed a way to waste it.
Still, I'm really happy I get to go shopping with a charismatic model like Momoka!
You're such a kind and honest girl, Tsubomi.
Hey, cut that out! Tsubomi is my best friend!
Oh, that reminds me.
While we're here, I guess I should invite my best friend as well.
Your best friend? Who's that?
Hello?
It's not often that you're the one calling me, Momoka.
Okay.
Right.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There's somewhere I have to be right now,
so I really can't. Sorry.
Later, then.
She turned me down!
I can't believe anyone would turn down an
invite from a charismatic model like Momoka.
Well, if she turned you down, I have
a feeling we'd get along pretty well.
What was that?!
It was a joke, jeez!
Now, now.
We can have fun with just the three of us.
Oh?
Excuse me a second.
It's from Grandma!
Hello, Grandma?
What?! The desert agave is blooming?!
Yes! Yes!
Desert agave?
I'll be right there!
Momoka, Erika, I'm really sorry!
It seems a desert agave is going to bloom at the botanical gardens, and they only bloom once in decades!
I'm going to hurry over and take a look!
Bye!
Unless you'd like to come take a look too?
Don't worry about us. You go have fun, all right?
Right!
Well, if that's how it's gonna be, the two of us should get a move on.
Right, big sis?
You're creeping me out!
Someone's coming!
We need to hide!
Lord Coupe...
Yuri!
It's been a while.
How have you been holding up?
That reminds me!
I have a favor to ask of you.
Of me?
Well, the thing is...
My granddaughter Tsubomi and her best friend Erika have become the new Precures,
and are fighting against the Desert Apostles.
You know of them, right?
Yes.
Then that makes things simple.
I think you'll be able to give them the advice they need, Yuri.
So your heart hasn't yet healed from the damage it took back then?
The once-in-decades opportunity!
That was quick.
You said that the aga—
Huh?
Aren't you...
You know what the geranium means in the language of flowers, I take it?
Yes!
If I recall correctly, it means "true friendship."
That's just like us, isn't it?
I wonder.
I don't think you understand what that really means.
Thanks to the advice you gave us back then, we were able to help our dear friends!
Thank you so much!
I didn't really do anything...
Is that so?
Really, I didn't!
I just told her what the flower meant, that's all!
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Hold on a minute, Yuri.
A desert agave is about to bloom.
Wouldn't you like to see it with us?
A desert agave?
Help!
What's the matter?!
These weird creeps are running wild at the station!
Weird creeps?
Dark Precure!
So this is what a desert agave's flower is like.
It's beautiful.
I've been raising it since I started my research here at the botanical gardens, and it's finally bloomed.
This is the first one I've ever seen.
So you're interested in flowers too?
It's not a case of mere interest with her!
When she was young, she used to come and visit every day.
Yeah. Well...
Erika, what's the matter?
Huh? The station's being attacked by Dark—
At the station?
Yuri!
Yuri's mother works as a shopkeeper at the station!
What?!
Momo, hurry and run!
Huh?! What are you—
Mom!
Yuri?!
Hurry and get out of here!
Amazing...
Erika!
Tsubomi!
Let's transform!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
I did not let the Snackies loose just to draw you two out.
Now the pests are out of the way.
Why are you so obsessed with me?!
Because you...
Because you are me!
Cure Moonlight!
Yuri is...
...Cure Moonlight?!
There only needs to be one me!
So I shall eliminate you.
Yuri!
You again?!
Everyone!
Use this chance to escape!
There's no point in running.
As long as I have this,
you cannot escape me, Cure Moonlight.
Just who is that pretty guy who keeps saving us?
Well, we know he's not an enemy, at least.
I sense Dark Precure's presence approaching us!
As long as we have Coupe's barrier, she won't find us.
But she's definitely heading straight for us!
It's probably... because of this.
That's...
A Seed of the Precure?!
It'd be really bad if Dark Precure found out about this place!
We have to stop her before she gets here!
Got it!
Yuri, please take care of Lord Coupe and Grandma!
She's close...
Precures?!
We won't let you go any further!
Out of my way.
Dark Power, Gather!
Dark Tact!
Precure Dark Power Fortissimo!
We'll protect Yuri, no matter what!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Stop, Dark Precure!
Didn't I tell you not to concern yourself with Cure Moonlight?
Return to me at once.
Very well.
Luck favors you this day.
Who was that voice that called back Dark Precure?
It was probably the boss of the Desert Apostles, Sabark.
So it's not just Sasorina and the other commanders...
But I never would've imagined that you were Cure Moonlight, Yuri!
That shocked me!
Yuri, please help us to fight the Desert Apostles!
We're begging you!
Yuri?
I cannot fight alongside you.
My mother is probably worried about me, so...
Yuri!
Just leave her alone for the moment, all right?
Grandma?
The damage that Sabark and Dark Precure inflicted on her heart has not yet healed.
And since she lost her Seed of the Precure, Yuri...
can't become Cure Moonlight anymore.
Yuri!
I was so worried about you!
When I went back to the station, you weren't there, so I searched and searched, but...
Sorry for worrying you.
There's no need to apologize.
I just wanted to make sure you were all right.
Yeah.
Will she really never be able to become a Precure again?
You saw for yourself in your dream.
Cure Moonlight fought with her all to protect the Great Heart Tree.
And now that wish has been
passed on to the both of you.
We'll have to fight for Cure Moonlight!
Right!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
It's those wide, beaming smiles that make us feel so happy inside!
It's almost motherly, in a way.
To protect the promises hidden in those smiles...
...and those carnations, full of feelings of gratitude...
...Cure Blossom and...
...Cure Marine will...
...give it their all!
HeartCatch Precure:
Mother's Day in Tears!
Protect the Family's Smiles!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!