[sounds of hammering,
construction]
[Hohenheim] It's been
a long time, huh, Al?
[Al] Yeah.
[Hohenheim] So, uh...
I saw Pinako recently.
She told me about your body.
[Resident]
Hey... There he is.
[Al] Uh...?
Mr. Ho! You think you could
give us a hand for a bit?
Yeah, sure. Um...
Let's catch up later.
[Al] Oh... okay.
[Older Man] You did a helluva
job fixin' up this old radio.
It works better
than it used to.
It doesn't even
pick up static now.
[Al] I'm really sorry...
All this bad stuff happened
because we stuck our noses in.
Mm, don't say that.
You've gotta look
at all the good stuff
that's come from it.
You guys exposed
a corrupt fraud.
People reacted badly
at first, but take a look.
[sounds of hammering,
construction]
Sounds good, huh?
The whole town's working
together to rebuild
what we lost.
And you guys are the ones
that brought us together.
[Al] Mm...
I'm gonna help build.
Rose, can you
take care of Winry?
Well. We might
as well help, too.
[Zampano]
You heard him, Yoki.
Huh? I'm eating.
- [Gerso] Hmph.
- [Yoki] Aaahhh!
[Gerso]
Your food'll taste better
once you've worked
up an appetite.
[Zampano] Quit struggling.
[Yoki] C'mon, I'm hungry
now! Let go! Please!
Really? You mean that
was your son back there?
I'm sorry if we interrupted.
It's been a while, right?
Maybe you should
head back and talk?
I don't know... I left
when he was just a boy
and haven't seen him since...
I doubt that he thinks of me
as his father or trusts me.
I'm not even sure
what to say to him.
[Al] Hey, Dad!
[Hohenheim] Ah?
[Al] I, um... I'd
like to work, too.
[Hohenheim] Huh?
[Al] Here...
Let me carry those.
[Al] Here ya go.
[Winry stretches] Mmm...
[Rose] You okay in there?
How's the water feel?
[Winry] Amazing.
Ah... It feels like an
eternity since I've had a bath.
[Rose] I'll leave some
fresh clothes for you here.
Thank you so much, Rose.
[Winry sighs comfortably]
[Winry] She's so nice
to do all this for me.
I'm really impressed
with you, Winry.
Working as an
automail engineer,
you're so independent
for someone your age.
So did you design Ed's leg?
That's right...
That was back when
we were just
little kids, really.
That's amazing...
You're the one who literally
helped Ed get back
on his feet again...
So you indirectly helped me
get back on my feet too...
I owe you just as much
as I owe Ed and Al.
[Winry] Ah...
[Rose] I was desperate enough
to believe Father Cornello.
He claimed that he could bring
my boyfriend back to life,
and I began to
blindly follow him.
But lucky for me, that's
when Ed and Al showed up
and proved that his
miracles were just alchemy.
Everything I believed in
suddenly disappeared.
I lost all hope.
But then Ed got
furious with me...
He told me to stand
on my own two feet.
He said that? He can
be a jerk sometimes.
I don't know why it's so
difficult for him to be nice.
But he was being nice.
That's just how much he cares.
But you already
know that, don't you?
Huh? Um...
He helped open our eyes...
Mine, and the whole town's.
[sounds of hammering,
construction]
[Rose] We're learning
to stand on our own.
And we don't need any
kind of miracle to do it.
It's all thanks to Ed and Al.
[Winry] Ed...
[Bido] Maybe it wasn't
such a bright idea
to follow those military guys.
I have no idea
where the hell I am.
Where are you,
Mr. Greed? Ah--!
[Bido pants]
[Bido struggles]
[Bido groans]
[Bido screams] Yaaaah!!
[Bido trembles]
[Bido gasps]
[Gardner] The state has
no interest in ethics.
They're too much of a variable
to use as a guideline.
[Gardner] The third tenant
is to prevent someone
from creating their
own army... General.
But... These aren't...
They aren't human, are they?
Correct. They're like
humanoid receptacles...
Powerful dummies that
we can bond souls to.
Not only are they immortal,
they're mindlessly obedient.
They are the world's
most perfect soldier.
Mind if I ask you
a question, sir?
[Gardner] Go right ahead.
You mentioned that souls
would be bonded to them...
Where do you plan on
procuring these souls?
From rival lands, of course.
Citizens from the countries
we ravage during
the course of war.
For one reason or
another, the battlefield
serves as a hunting ground
for the collection of souls.
[Bido screams] Yaaaahh!
This place is evil! Pure evil!
Why did I ever come here?!
Mister Greed would never be
in an awful place like this!
[Hohenheim]
An underground tunnel?
[Al] Uh-huh. And I've got a
hunch that it runs under Liore.
If it does-- well, no,
I'm positive it does--
Hold on, Al... Let's find
someplace more private.
So it's a country-wide
transmutation circle...
And you plan on destroying it?
[Al] Yeah. So I was kind of
shocked to find you here, Dad.
I must have some
good luck after all.
We encountered a man who was
identical to you in Central.
I don't know how you're
connected to him...
but I'm guessing you at
least know who he is, right?
[Hohenheim] Are you sure
you want to know, Al?
[Al] Uh--!
Did it ever cross your mind
I might be on their side?
[Al gasps]
You've given away
your entire plan.
Aren't you the least bit worried
I might leak it to them?
[Al] Ah...!
I'm glad that you feel like
you can still trust me.
Thanks, Alphonse...
[Al] Ah... Sure!
[Hohenheim]
Even though I left them...
This boy still sees me as his
father and actually trusts me.
Now then... I suppose
I owe my sons
the same trust
they've given me.
This won't be
easy to explain...
It would be for the best
for Edward to hear it as well.
[Al gasps]
[Al] Actually,
I hate to say it...
But Brother has gone missing.
[background chatter,
phone ringing]
Next in line, please.
[Teller] Mmm--!
[Darius] I'd like
to make a withdrawal
from the account of State
Alchemist Edward Elric.
His research account.
[Teller] Are you
the account holder?
[Darius] I'm his representative...
But I've brought a
letter of attorney.
Thank you for your
business, sir.
This is the Bank of Amestris,
Northern Branch...
We've just had a very
large withdrawal
taken from State
Alchemist Edward Elric's
personal research account.
No. He claimed to be
his representative...
Well... He was rather
tall and very brawny.
[Darius] Here. That should
cover your medical bill.
[Doctor chuckles]
Well... I could charge
you more, but this'll do.
It better... You're already
ripping us off, doc.
How can you say that?
It's reasonable when you
consider the risks involved.
Sure. And as long as you
guarantee that you're
gonna keep your mouths shut,
then I'm not complaining.
Darius.
Tch. I guess they found us.
Yes, hello...
Oh, you're soldiers.
Do you need a physical?
[Ivan]
We're looking for someone.
Is this man your only patient?
There's no one else?
There's one more resting-- ah!
Are you the only
patient back here?
Yeah. Why're you asking?
What's wrong?
Tell me. Were you at
the bank this afternoon?
[Darius grunts]
Don't move.
Huh?
Hold it... Do you work
at this doctor's office?
Slowly raise your
hands above your head.
[Darius grunts]
[Harris] Have you
seen anyone unusual
frequenting the clinic lately?
He's described as...
Right now! Show me your hands!
...a red coat, blond hair
worn in a braid, and short.
[sound of thud
and body falling]
Check it out.
[Cohen] Harris! Harris,
what happened to you?
C'mon, snap to! Harris!
[sound of thud
and body falling]
Cohen! Harris! What's
going on? Hey, answer me!
[Ivan struggles]
[Ivan exhales]
Well, damn. You just
had to take 'em out
on your own, huh?
You're pretty reckless, kid.
You haven't even
fully recovered yet.
[Ed] Don't treat me
like I'm an invalid.
My injuries are
completely healed...
And I'm revving
at full throttle.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Darius] Thanks for
everything you've done, Doc.
Don't worry about it.
Just hurry up and go.
We've had about all the
trouble we can take for today.
[Ed] That's all
they're looking for?
Someone with a red
coat and a braid?
Guess I'll have to make do
with this look for a while.
[Soldier 1] Freeze!
[Soldier 2] Drop your weapons!
[Heinkel] We took too long.
Get your hands up
in the air! Do it now!
Move it, kid! Those
guys are dangerous!
[Ed chews, swallows]
[Darius and Heinkel grunt]
Stay back or he's dead!
Don't force us to blow
this kid's brains out!
[Soldiers gasp]
[Soldiers yell]
I'll hotwire some wheels for us.
Okay.
[sound of engine roar]
Hey, Gorilla! Step on it!
Don't call me that!
[Ed] Just drive faster!
These guys are from
Northern command.
We're never gonna ditch 'em!
[Darius yells] Aah!
That was a little too close.
How's it lookin' behind us?
[Ed] Not good...
They're right on us!
Damn it.
Turn there! I've got an idea!
What?
[Ed] Just shut up and turn!
Ahh...! This better
be a good plan!
Just park the car
as soon as we turn.
They turned!
What?
[Soldier 6] How...
Where did they go?
They must've turned on that
street up there! Move it!
[sound of engine idling]
Whew... And you doubted me.
Yeah, well can you change it
back into a normal car now?
And why's that? I think
this car looks cool as hell.
[Darius] Just change it back.
Please, we're begging you.
[Ed] Oh, yeah? You guys got a
problem with my sense of style?
[Darius and Heinkel]
You don't have any!
[Heinkel] So I guess this
means we're drifters again.
[Darius] Yep.
[Ed] I never should've dropped
my guard around Kimblee.
Talk about a setback.
And Al... I hope he was
able to safely find Winry.
[Darius] Hey, Fullmetal...
Quit spacin' out.
So what's the next
plan of action?
Well... let's see...
The first thing I need to
do is meet up with Al.
He should be with
Dr. Marcoh by now.
Well... Where are they?
You do know how to
find them, right?
[Ed exhales]
[Ed] If I were Al, where
would I go? C'mon... Think.
Still awake?
[Al gasps]
[Al] Yeah, sorry...
it's just a lot...
You were a slave and now
you're a Philosopher's Stone?
Yeah... Right...
Can't say I blame you
if you don't believe me...
I doubt I would...
I know how impossibly
far-fetched that it sounds...
You'd have to be
crazy to believe it.
[Al] Well, I guess
I'm crazy then,
because I do believe you.
Do you really? That was fast.
[Al] To be honest,
it kind of scares me.
And besides, my situation's
kind of far-fetched too.
[Hohenheim exhales]
[Al] So... What's it like
not being able to die?
[Hohenheim]
Well... It's...
I'm not gonna lie and say
it doesn't come in handy.
But it's not worth watching
everyone I love die before me.
[Al] Like Mom.
[Al] Wait... If you're
a Philosopher's Stone,
you don't have a normal
human body, right...?
So does that mean...
Ed and I...
Aren't exactly normal
humans either?
[Al] Yeah.
You don't have to worry, Al...
It's true that I have
a Philosopher's Stone
fused to my soul...
but not even that
can change the fact that
I am a human being...
Although... My look-alike
beneath Central?
His body is like a leather bag
that's patterned after mine.
[Al] A leather bag?
[Hohenheim] More or less.
And if we can destroy
that leather bag...
then we can defeat
what's inside.
[Al] That makes sense.
Oh, I almost forgot!
Look at this... They're
gonna do the same thing
to Amestris that they did
to Xerxes, aren't they?
We've gotta hurry and stop
them. It's almost complete.
[Hohenheim]
Ho, I'm impressed.
You've really done
your homework.
This a reverse
transmutation circle, huh?
[Al] Destroying the tunnel
seems like the best way
to thwart them. And since
it runs under Liore--
[Hohenheim]
That's not a good idea.
[Al reacts]
[Hohenheim] They've got an
immensely powerful Homunculus
named Pride watching
over the tunnel.
[Al] But still... We've gotta
try before it's too late.
For all we know, they might have
already completed the circle.
[Al] Then why are
you so relaxed?
Because... It's not yet time.
[Al] Huh? How do you know?
Look up, son... You're
too busy looking down
when you need to look up.
[Al] Huh?
If you want answers,
that's where you'll find them.
[Al] Up? The sky? You
mean the Sun God Leto?
[Hohenheim] The man
in Central is waiting...
for the Day of Reckoning.
[Bido pants]
Why is he doing this to me?
What did I do to deserve it?
[Bido cries] Yaah!
[Bido grunts]
[Bido wheezes]
[Greed laughs]
[Greed] Well this is fun...
Most people tend
to curl up and cry.
It's about time that someone
actually fights back...
I do appreciate the chance
to kill my boredom.
[Greed laughs]
The Ultimate Shield?
And your voice sounds
like... What the hell?
You... How dare you
imitate Mr. Greed?
Excuse me? I'm no
imitation. My name is Greed.
The Avaricious?
You got it... I want everything
you could possibly think of.
I want money and power and
women... sex, status, glory--
You demand the
finer things in life!
Huh?
You can't... How could you be?
Alright... Who are you?
[Greed grunts]
It has to be!
You are Mr. Greed...
But how can you look
like someone else?
[Greed] I asked you who
you are, now tell me.
It's me! I'm your friend! Bido!
You haven't been gone from
Dublith long enough to forget!
You're from Dublith!
Ohh. Now it makes sense.
You remember me?
Afraid not... You must've been
buddies with the previous Greed.
But... I thought...
Sorry, pal, but you and
I've never even met.
[Bido] But Mr. Greed...
I'm your... friend.
[Greed] It's nothing personal,
I'm just doing my job.
I am sorry... Honestly.
[Greed grunts]
What the hell?
[Greed gasps]
[Greed exhales]
[Greed coughs, wheezes]
[Ling] What have
you done, Greed?
Are you determined to
prove you're a monster?
What kind of sick creature...
would kill his own friend?!
He wasn't my... friend.
[Greed growls]
Then why do you
remember him?
And are you gonna
try and tell me
Bido was just making
everything up?
[Greed] Those are the
last Greed's memories...
They're not mine!
Then why are you
in so much pain?
[Greed grunts]
Pull yourself together,
Greed... I'm warning you...
I'll take my body back
if you drop your guard.
They aren't mine.
Father purified me
and purged the old
Greed's memories...
Those memories aren't
a part of me anymore!
No, you're wrong, Greed!
It's not that easy... They'll
always be a part of you!
You can't just erase
them from your soul...
They were the only part
of you that you chose!
Look at them! Can you not
hear their souls crying out?!
You abandoned them!
Your real family!
You threw them away like trash!
Fool! If you turned your back
on something you wanted,
you don't deserve to
call yourself Greed!
[Greed screams]
[Mrs. Bradley] I think
you'll enjoy this one.
I was just a bit older than you
are the first time I read it.
It's about an adventurer
who travels the world.
[Selim and Mrs. Bradley gasp]
What is it?
Who is it?
[Greed pants]
[Greed yells]
[Narrator] Fueled by
a relentless anger,
an unexpected battle has
begun and it will not end
until the victor stands over
the corpse of the defeated.
But what truth hides
beneath the rage,
waiting to be discovered
once the dust has settled?
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 45: "The Promised Day."
Your only hope is
to come together
with the people
that you believe in.