[ED]
E-Exposure?
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Yes, that's right.
You got lucky.
You were close to
getting frostbite.
You need to be careful
walking around in a snowstorm...
The flesh that's touching
your automail will freeze...
and you need to oil it...
or it will stiffen.
So does that
Buccaneer guy have a
different kind of automail
or something?
It's no use, Doc.
I can't get this thing unstuck.
[AL]
Hey...! My head!
[FEMALE DOCTOR]
Up here, your automail has to be
flexible and lightweight...
It also needs to be
resistant to the cold.
After some trial and error,
we found an alloy that works...
A combination of dura-lumin,
carbon fiber, nickel,
copper, and so on...
And here I assumed
it was just iron...
It's no wonder I couldn't
do anything with it.
Hey, Doc... Be careful...
Are you planning on telling
him all our secrets?
Why wouldn't I?
He's a State Alchemist.
He has a right to
know, doesn't he?
You're kidding...
He has the pocketwatch.
[BUCCANEER THINKS]
You mean this kid is the
equivalent of a Major?
If you're going to be
in the north for long...
you should switch to a
different kind of automail...
Do you have a mechanic?
Yes, but she's in Rush Valley.
[FEMALE DOCTOR] And she
let you come up north
without explaining
all of this to you first?
Not exactly... I didn't tell her
I was planning
on coming up here.
I'd recommend
you send for her...
assuming that you'd
like to stay alive.
Fine.
That'll be a hundred cens.
Seriously?!
It wasn't even
a good cup of coffee.
This is the north.
Get used to it.
[BUCCANEER] So you come up here
with mediocre automail...
completely ignorant
about the north...
and you try to bypass the
command center.
Oh, come on...! I hike up
here, a State Alchemist
with an official
letter of introduction,
and this is how I'm treated?!
What's wrong with you people?!
Do you have no
sense of propriety?
That general threatened
to tear my arms off!
Hello, little red runt.
L-Little... red...
If you have a problem,
then now's the
time to speak up.
[AL]
M-My hair!
It looks awful.
[OLIVIER] Well now...
From what I hear,
you two are close
to my brother Alex.
Is he doing all right?
Uh... Yeah!
The big, strong guy
we know and love.
[AL AND ED IN UNISON]
Alex is doing just great!
[OLIVIER ANGRY]
No matter... Never mind him.
Tell me why you would bypass
the command center to meet me.
[OLIVIER]
I want to know it all.
Including why
your armor's empty.
Actually... that's something
we don't like to talk about.
There's no reason to worry...
Folks around here have
plenty they want to hide...
Everybody up north has something
that he or she doesn't
like to talk about.
But... if this information
reaches certain ears,
I could be court-martialed.
[OLIVIER]
Even I have secrets like that.
[AL]
Brother... listen.
[AL] I really think
we have to tell her.
[ED] But Winry's a
hostage... I don't know.
Maybe if we
can do it without
mentioning the Fuhrer
or the homunculi...
What are you
whispering about?
Start talking now!
[AL]
Fine... let's just tell her
we're trying to
get our bodies back.
[OLIVIER] I see...
So that's why you're looking
for this girl
with the strange cat.
I understand.
So does that mean
you're going to help u--
I'm not done!
What I understand is this...
You two are a couple
of reckless wretches
who cause trouble
with every last thing you do!
[OLIVIER CONTINUES] I don't
want people like you in my fort.
Honestly...
How could the people at
Central let these
two run around loose?
Get out of here right now!
At least that's
what I'd like to say,
but I'm interested
in alkahestry...
You two... You're acquainted
with this girl from Xing?
You've met her before?
[AL]
Yeah... we have.
She has a skill our
country doesn't... right?
[OLIVIER]
You can never know too much...
Especially here in the north,
where we're right
next to Drachma.
[OLIVIER]
If we use it right...
alkahestry could make
an excellent weapon.
[AL]
Wait a second!
Alkahestry is specialized
for medical purposes...
You can't j--
Be quiet...! You're
nothing but lap dogs
living safely
within your city walls...
But we are the
ones who protect you!
[OLIVIER] We few who
are brave enough
to defend the country's border.
My job is far more
perilous than yours...
I will make use of any knowledge
that I can get my hands on.
Leave the task of finding
this alkahestry girl to me...
You two will stay
here inside the fort.
[OLIVIER]
And, Major Miles...
[MILES]
Yes, Sir?
[OLIVIER]
Put them to work.
"A man who does not
work has no right to eat."
[AL AND ED IN UNISON]
You have a point
[BUCCANEER]
Those two boys haven't exactly
had easy lives, general.
I believe that they
may have witnessed
some carnage in their time,
but I can tell
that on the inside
they remain soft and weak.
[OLIVIER]
And what's more...
They're still hiding something.
Those two have a secret
they aren't telling us.
So, uh... exactly
what kind of work
will you have us doing?
That doctor said
people around here
have a lot of things
to hide too...
So what're you hiding, Major?
[ED] It's no fair for
you guys to ask all
the questions
and never answer any!
You really want to know?
Red eyes!
[AL]
An Ishvalan?!
[ED]
I don't understand.
We were told all
the soldiers from Ishval
were purged before
the Extermination.
[MILES] It's true that Ishvalan
blood flows in my veins...
but my father and my grandmother
were not from that region.
They were a different race.
My eyes are Ishvalan, though...
My grandfather's
blood runs strong.
Amestrian...
It was your people...
who destroyed the
land of my grandfather...
Ishvalan, your people
destroyed our countryside...
and one of you is responsible
for murdering
my friends' parents.
[AL]
Careful, Brother!
[MILES CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry...
but that's the first time
I've heard anyone
give me that kind of an answer.
What, you were testing me?
I know, it was rude...
Since the war,
Amestrians always view me
with a mixture
of guilt and pity...
To be honest,
I'm getting tired of it...
But you're different,
aren't you?
Well, Major... an Ishvalan
tried to kidnap me,
nearly killed me,
and then briefly fought
alongside me...
After all that...
My feelings
are a bit conflicted.
Besides... I think people should
try to ignore their race...
and just treat
each other as equals.
[ED]
Major Miles, were you on
active duty during the
War of Extermination?
[MILES]
Yes, I was...
I've been under
General Armstrong's
command since then.
[MILES] The war began right
after I was posted here...
Many of my relatives,
including my grandfather
were killed in the East...
I fell outside the military's
purge requirements,
so I was spared.
You didn't hold any grudge
against the military?
You don't understand how the
world works, now do you?
I know I'm ignorant
about some things...
If I offended you, I'm sorry.
An "ignorant"
State Alchemist, you say?
(heh)... Interesting.
[MILES] I did resent
the military's actions...
And, I also had doubts as to why
General Armstrong would
keep me as her Staff Officer.
[MILES CONTINUES] The presence
of someone with Ishvalan
blood could cause discord among
the soldiers stationed here.
It would've been easier
for her to get rid of me...
Eventually, I just came
right out and asked her.
[OLIVIER]
This is Briggs.
No matter what happens,
this territory must not fall.
[OLIVIER]
Every soldier here must be
both strong and flexible...
You must move
as one cohesive unit,
following me, your leader,
in all things and at all times.
In short... we do not have the
luxury of discrimination here.
[OLIVIER CONTINUES] The blood of
several races flows within you
and with that comes varying
strengths and values...
You can see this country
in a way that others cannot...
I was born and
raised in Amestris.
In order to lead, I need
someone with your eyes...
Now shut up and
follow me, Miles...
Understood?
Her words made sense...
I knew... she was speaking
without deception.
[MILES] I even went so
far as to ask her...
"What if the
Ishvalan blood within me
cannot forgive what the
military did to my people?"
And do you know want to know
what the general said to that?
Fine then... bring it...
On behalf of the military,
I will accept your
challenge, anytime.
That was it.
What a scary lady...
Maybe she said that because
she had her troops with her...
No... that wasn't it at all.
[OLIVIER] I'll fight
you one-on-one!
[MILES]
The look in her eye...
You know what the law is here?
[ED]
Survival of the fittest?
That's right...
Without power, you die...
And if you have it,
you might survive...
That fact always
remains the same,
three hundred and
sixty-five days a year...
It's a simple life, really.
[MILES] Whether you're a
private or a general,
race, ethnicity, and gender
make no difference.
[MILES] Survival of the
fittest in action...
Your luck was strong,
so you survived.
[MILES] These icicles all
need to be scraped off...
That'll be your
job for today...
When you're finished,
one of my men will show
you to your quarters.
[ED]
Damn, I can't reach!
[FALMAN]
Huh? Is that you?!
[ED]
Officer Falman!
The Elric brothers!
What are you
two doing here?
[ED]
Us? What about you?
I thought you were at the
Northern Command Center.
Uh, yeah... I was for awhile,
but then Northern Command
bumped me up here.
[AL]
They promoted you!
Yeah.
Hey, that's great.
Congratulations...!
But why're you
knocking down icicles?
If they have you doing
something like this,
then that means...
[AL AND ED IN UNISON] They've
taken you off the career track?
Noooooo!
[FALMAN]
The Development Sector
[ED]
Wow...! What's it for?
[FALMAN]
It was General
Armstrong's idea...
This department
researches the country's
latest technologies and
develops them into weapons.
Does that include
combat automail?
Yeah. Now come on,
follow me.
[FALMAN] This is the lowest
level of Fort Briggs.
[ED] It's warm down here...
not like it was up above.
[FALMAN] All the fort's most
important functions,
its lifelines,
come through here...
Even if the fort's attacked...
this area will remain safe.
[BOBBY]
Hey, kid, move outta the way!
Not a great place to stand!
[ED]
Oh... Sorry.
Hey, Bobby, it's this
pipe... over here!
[BOBBY]
It's coming...
...from underground.
[WORKMAN B]
What?!
Sounds like... like someone's
digging through the rock.
Maybe it's spies
from Drachma...
They could be digging
a tunnel under the fort.
It's close!
[SLOTH]
What a pain.
It's so annoying... All this
digging... it's killing me...
But... I guess dying
would be a pain, too.
[FLOOR RUMBLES]
[FLOOR EXPLODES]
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Kimblee, the Crimson Alchemist?
He was severely wounded on
a cargo train headed here...
He was checked into a hospital
at the base of the mountain...
The full cooperation of the
Briggs branch is requested.
[OLIVIER]
Why was Kimblee headed up north?
I thought he was
serving time in prison.
[MILES] Apparently,
he was released...
on the Fuhrer's orders.
I don't like this.
[ALERT BUZZERS GO OFF]
What is it?!
We've got an intruder...!
From under the ground, sir!
We what?!
[CHAINS RATTLE]
[ROCKS MOVING AROUND]
A Homunculus!
[ED THINKS] Damn it... Do they
know we've come here
to find a way
of fighting them...?
This isn't good!
[SLOTH FALLS ASLEEP]
[AL AND ED IN UNISON]
You're sleepiiiing?!
What's this?
I'm guessing... that
creepy guy back in Central
who you call Father
told you about us.
[AL]
But, you see...
we're just here
trying to find a
way to get our bodies
back, that's all.
Why should I care... about you?
Go dig... a hole...
How annoying...
Really... what a pain.
You mean... he doesn't know?
[AL]
No... I don't think he's heard
about us from Father
or Fuhrer Bradley.
Ah hah...! So it turns out that
you really are a Drachman spy!
[AL AND ED IN UNISON]
No, we're not!
[BUCCANEER]
I saw you talking to the
intruder like you
knew who he was!
No we weren't!
[BUCCANEER]
Your lies won't fool me!
[SLOTH]
In the way.
[ED SCREAMS]
I'm not lying...!
We've never even met that guy!
[METAL PIPE CRASHES]
[SLOTH]
What is... this place?
This place... big...
[SLOTH] Uh... Can I stop
digging now that I'm here?
[BUCCANEER]
Fire!
[GUNFIRE ERUPTS]
The guns aren't
affecting him at all!
[SLOTH]
Where... am I?
[BUCCANEER]
This is bad!
That thing's going
up to Development...!
Get him! Go!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
Contact Development!
[ED]
Let's see if we can help!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 2]
And check the hole!
There might be others coming!
[WORKMAN A]
That's all the boxes we have.
Whoa!
It's warm... here.
[OLIVIER]
Don't move!
[MISSLE HITS AND EXPLODES]
Put it out.
Sir!
I know that I hit it.
[BUCCANEER]
It's no use!
Firearms won't work against him!
[OLIVIER]
What?!
Withdraw all noncombatants immediately...
Shut off the alarm!
It won't help anything if the
Drachmans figure out
that we're in trouble.
[TANK OFFICER A]
General...! We have tanks!
[OLIVIER]
Have the trials been completed?
We don't need to
worry about "trials"...
These are the development
team's pride and joy...
Remove the fuses
from the shells.
[TANK OFFICER A]
Yes, Sir!
Ready to go...!
The first round's
locked and loaded!
Fire!
Yeah...! Dead on!
Ou... ch...
[SLOTH]
Pain is a pain.
Pain is annoying.
Don't just sit there...!
Load the next round!
Fire!
Ouch.
Right back... to work.
[SLOTH]
Dig... a hole...
It won't work...!
Try whatever you want to,
but he won't die!
He won't?
Just what are you saying...?
How does a kid like you
know something like that, huh?
Be... because we...
[OLIVIER]
Drop the act...!
You will answer all my questions
clearly and completely...
First off-- How do you
know about that thing...?
Are you a Drachman spy?
I'm not!
[OLIVIER]
Is that thing a spy?
[ED]
I really doubt it.
[OLIVIER]
Does that thing know you?
[ED]
No, apparently not.
[OLIVIER]
What is that thing?
I can't answer.
[OLIVIER]
Who does that thing work for?
I can't answer that!
Why can't you answer me?
I can't answer.
This is my last question...
Are you on our side,
or are you in
league with that thing?
I'm not with him.
I don't want to see
anyone here get hurt.
Then tell me what
that thing's made of.
[ED] His body's structure
and compositional
elements are probably
the same as a human's.
The same as a human's, huh?
Buccaneer, bring me
some tank fuel, now...!
We're going to douse it.
Sir!
I told you, it won't
work, General...
Set him on fire,
but he still won't die.
I understand--
I learned from our
last attack
that we can't kill it...
The best that we can hope
for is to stop or delay it...
So we'll have to hit it with
something even
stronger than fire.
Now you get to see the
"Briggs way," kid.
[NARRATOR] A battle
with the Homunculus
threatens the northern border,
but General Armstrong
is determined
to protect her territory...
Body clashes against body...
Shells explode in the air...
Who will prevail
in this titanic fight?
Next time,
on Fullmetal Alchemist:
Brotherhood...
Episode 35...
The Shape of this Country.
Those who stand in
the way are swept aside...
Such is the law of the north.