What the hell is this?!
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 12
Idiots, a Fool, and Requiem!
The anomaly appeared without warning.
Herro
Something's
strange?
I'd never expect to see Akihisa's Summoned Being wearing such fancy armor.
It's more or less human height now, too.
Head
C'mon guys!
Aren't you missing something a little more important?
Yeah, I got it already, so can you and the head quit staring at me?
Something's
strange?
It won't be much use in that state.
How about a little compassion here?!
Morning!
Good morning.
Good... morning, girls.
Indiscriminate
slapping
I'm sorry, we were a little hasty.
No, I'm sorry for surprising you like that.
Th-That's right! It's your fault for surprising us, Aki!
Is anything weird going on with anyone else's beings?
Let's check it out.
Summon!
T-They...
It seems they've taken the form of fictional creatures that reflect defining traits of their summoner.
I see. So mine turned into a knight because I'm so gallant and chivalrous-
Akihisa, quit lying to yourself.
Or maybe the armor shows my masculinity, and the sword, my strength.
Since he's got no head, it more likely reflects how mindless you are.
He said it! He revealed the truth I didn't want to face!
At times, the truth can be cruel.
Yuuji's being looks pretty much the same as him.
A doppelganger?
What are you guys saying?!
This is demonic Sakamoto Yuuji! That ugly mug and bad attitude-
Aim for the Olympics!
Nadeshiko Japan!
You kicked it! How dare you use my head as a soccer ball!
Don't get so worked up, Akihisa! It's like that saying, right?
"Your friend is the ball."
YOUR FRIEND IS THE BALL
Wasn't it "The ball is your friend"?!
IS
YOUR FRIEND
THE BALL
Wow!
A werewolf!
B-But why did it transform without a full moon?
Did it see something round?
He really is the ball.
Why don't you girls summon yours as well?
I guess I will. Well then...
Summoned Being:
Summon!
Please, don't look!
It's pretty clear what your defining trait is.
No! I know I'm curvaceous,
but I never thought that...
Stop, Himeji-san! Or you'll crush the feelings of someone here with the opposite pro-
Aki, just say what you like; I'm listening.
But really, Mizuki, what did you expect with a figure like yours?
Please don't say that, Minami-chan!
I'm sure mine will be just perfect.
It'll be so cute, just you watch!
Summon!
Not good, if I laugh now she's going to kill me.
Hey, Aki...
Wh-What is it, Minami?
Which of my traits do you think this being represents?
I-I'm not sure...
I'll just have to try and avoid saying anything about it being flat.
Oh yeah!
I'd say that big wall is as sturdy as you are!
Who are you calling "sturdy"?!
Spine
The truth is indeed cruel.
Sp
in
e
Get off of my darling, you pig!
M-Miharu...
Repent for your sins, for drawing my darling's affections even though you're a lowly pig!
Migraine
Ouch!
Shut the hell up!
You guys are...
Who were you again?
Ya tryin' to make fools of us?!
We're Tsunemura and Natsukawa of Class 3-A!
Oh, it's just the Eversummer pair.
Eversummer? Sounds familiar...
Don't ruin our entrance!
The Eversummer pair first appeared in the Refresh Festi...
We can hear you dumbasses whining all the way over in the third-year classes. It's distracting us!
That's such a load of bull.
Huh?
This is Class F on the third floor.
It's on a different floor, and in a different block from your class!
It's hard to believe that you could hear us.
You guys were probably sick of studying and just slacking off in the halls,
then you got worked up from hearing Aki's dumb voice and wanted someone to take it out on, right?
You're making it sound like it's all my fault.
Cut the crap!
You guys are god damn annoying either way!
Last time, you guys all got suspended for peeping!
How are you gonna make it up to us if our admission chances are blown 'cause the school's rep nosedived?
Academy
Reputation
Admissions
You heard him, Yuuji. Apologize to them.
Come on, Akihisa. Go ahead and apologize.
Reputation
Admissions
Academy
Reputation
Admissions
Academy
Reputation
Admissions
Academy
Reputation
Admissions
Academy
We want both of you to!
That's ridiculous.
Don't screw with me!
We'll beat some backbone into you wimps!
The math teacher is here, eh?
Great!
Summon!
Math
Go to hell!
What?!
Math
I'm first in line to teach that pig a lesson!
Don't get in my way!
Math
I don't care if you're my seniors;  If you mess with Yoshii-kun, you mess with me.
Shimizu-san! Wait, why is Kubo-kun here?
Both of their beings look similar.
The Deities of the Lost.
They try to ensnare those who have strayed from the path of humanity.
How fitting.
Natsukawa Shunpei
Tsunemura Yuusaku
Shimizu Miharu
Kubo Toshimitsu
Math
Damn it!
Time to end this!
That's enough.
Principal?!
Save your remaining points for the event I'm going to have you participate in.
Event?
Shouldn't returning the Summoned Beings back to normal have priority?!
This school's gonna wind up being like a giant haunted house.
Oh really? That's not a bad idea for an idiot like you.
I'm organizing an inter-year test of courage using your Summoned Beings!
Inter-year
Test of Courage
What?! A test of courage?!
Inter-year
I bet you just screwed up the examination system again.
Great, I'm putting you in charge of the second-years.
Geh
Now, will it be the second-years or the third-years playing the ghosts?
We third-years will definitely take the role of scaring them.
We need to teach them a lesson.
All right, the third-years will be the ghosts.
The second-years will take up the challenge and take the test of courage.
Inter-year
Test of Courage
Rules
The rules for the Inter-year Test of Courage! Hooo...
The challengers will enter the haunted house in pairs.
If the challengers, whilst inside the haunted house, raise their voices or make sounds above a prescribed volume,
Shriek
Scream Meter
they will be disqualified immediately.
Disqualified
Challengers
The challengers will engage in a Summoning Battle with the ghosts at each of the four checkpoints.
Checkpoint
By winning the battle, the challengers clear the checkpoint and move on to the next one.
Defeated
Challengers
The challengers will win if they clear all four checkpoints.
On the other hand, the ghosts win if all challengers are defeated.
It's pretty dull to leave it at that.
Let's decide on a penalty game in case you lose.
Hold it! It's an official school event. Don't go making up your own rules!
But it'll be boring-
Don't be so disappointed, my seniors.
Wait for us at the checkpoint and eventually you'll fight us one on one, right?
Interesting.
We'll beat the snot out of you!
What? Me?
Question 12
Read the following passage
and answer the question.
Xiang Yu's forces pitched camp at
Gaixia, and were short of men and
food.
His troops were surrounded and
encircled by Han forces
The folk songs of Chu could be heard
on all four sides. Xiang Yu, surprised,
asked:
"Has Han conquered Chu? Why
are there so many Chus around?"
With this, he awoke from his
slumber, and went for a stiff drink
What idiom did Xiang Yu's
predicament give birth to?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
'Chu Song from Four Sides'
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Chu soldiers could hear their local Chu
folk song from all four sides, coming from the
enemy camp that surrounded them. This meant
that their comrades have already defected to
the enemy forces. Originating from this
anecdote, the idiom "Chu Song from Four Sides"
now carries the meaning of "left alone,
surrounded by the enemies, with no means of
escape."
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
The one who strikes first wins.
Teacher's Comment
He didn't strike first.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
The one who strikes first wins.
Teacher's Comment
Also, he's the one who lost.
Okay, so you'll enter the haunted house in pairs.
Since you'll be in pairs, try to match up with the opposite gender if possible.
But the guy would be disqualified along with the girl if she screams.
I think that's fine. That'll just liven things up.
Now, go ahead and pair up!
So what's really going on?
I wanted everyone else to suffer with me.
If you don't pair up with me...
instant marriage.
Contract
The following agreement made between Kirishima Shouko, referred to hereinafter as
"First Party," and Sakamoto Yuuji, "Second Party":
Clause 1 (Objective)
Second Party consents to the following: One, he will always be together with First Party in private and school life as the spouse
of First Party. Two, First Party may monopolize Second Party regardless of the situation.
Clause 2 (Priority Treatment)
Second Party will give priority treatment to the achievement of "First Party and Second Party forming pairs and going for the
goal together" in school events that First Party takes part in, such as "Inter-year Test of Courage."
Clause 3 (Guarantee)
This guarantees that Second Party will marry with First Party as soon as possible and live his whole life together with her if
he commits actions that violate Clause 1 or Clause 2.
First Party) Fumizuki Academy Class 2-A
Kirishima Shouko
Second Party) Fumizuki Academy Class 2-F
Sakamoto Yuuji
What's wrong, Mizuki?
Oh, it's... well...
Himeji-san?
Yoshii Family Grave
I've always been very afraid of ghosts.
I'm afraid I might drag you down by screaming right away.
Himeji-san, you don't have to force yourself if you're that scared.
Y-Yeah!
You don't have to!
Everyone has things they can't... handle... well.
We'll do our best so you won't have to enter the haunted house.
Thanks.
Damn you, Yoshii Akihisa!
I swear I'll send you straight to Hell!
Shimizu-san.
Wh-What is it?
Will you pair up with me?
Let's hear what you've got to say.
Thus, the Inter-year Test of Courage began.
Wow, this is pretty well done.
They're still just props, aren't they?
Their scare tactics are at most just-
Scream Meter
Disqualified.
Disqualified
Beep
The third-years are going all out for this.
This is going to be tougher than I thought.
Damn! Why did I have to get paired with a guy?
Yoko
You're unpopular, that's why.
What did you say? You're the one who got rejected by all 22 girls you approached!
Yoko
I wasn't rejected! It was just a matter of bad timing!
Same here! It's not that I'm unpopular!
Me neither! I'm not unpopular at all!
Me neither!
Yoko
Scream Meter
Me neither!
Me neither! I haven't tried my best yet!
Disqualified
Yoko
Disqualified.
Good. This is sure to 1-hit KO those dimwits.
Really?
All right, let's show them a whole new level of terror.
M-Mikami-san!
Are you all right?
Th-Thank you.
Tsk!
Hey, something strange flashed past just now.
Something strange?
Don't worry. I will protect you, Mikami-san.
These childish props can't harm-
Whoaaa
Th-That bastard's really done it!
That's cheap! Not only is that cheap, but he looks cheap!
It's so scary!
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
Damn.
Disqualified
Our assault forces have been obliterated.
Damn! They all...
What should we do? Is there a way to defeat this abomination?!
Leave that to me.
Muttsurini!
I'll go with you, Muttsurini-kun.
I'll show them what true terror is.
There they are!
Here I go...
Wooooo
What the hell did I just see-
Hey there! Smile for the camera!
I'll upload these to the Internet.
Damn you guys!
I'll get you for this!
Bye bye!
Checkpoint
You're finally here.
Let's get started.
Summon!
Physical Education
Muttsurini-kun, their Summoned Beings look powerful.
They do, but...
Summon!
You guys are no match for us.
Physical Education
Challengers
Aiko & Muttsurini
Pass
Ooh!!
Yes!
You two are incredible!
Yuuji, what just happened?
I didn't manage to see it clearly,
but the Faceless Demon stripped, thrashed them, and put her Yukata back on all in a split second.
Why did she strip?
In that moment, Muttsurini suffered massive blood loss, stopped the blood flow, and completed a transfusion.
That's Muttsurini for you! They're gonna defeat all of them at this rate!
No.
I'm sure they'll have a counterattack.
We'll reach the next checkpoint soon.
What's wrong?
Welcome, little ones.
I am Kogure Aoi of Class 3-A's Tea Ceremony Club.
Are you okay, Muttsurini-kun?
This is nothing!
How adorable.
However, I'm also wearing the clothing of another club.
Another club?!
Actually, I also...
am a member of...
the gymnastics club!
Splurt
Muttsurini-kun!
Scream Meter
I can't... I can't stop the bleeding!
Disqualified
Gymnastics club! Gymnastics club! Gymnastics club!
Woo!
We'll save him!
This is bad! We need to get there fast with a camera!
Sorry, Akihisa. I couldn't really see what happened just now.
The stimulation would be too much for Yuuji.
I kinda understand the situation.
I've got something to counter that!
This is such a drag. I don't really like this sort of thing.
My, a pair of girls, eh?
Sex appeal won't work on them!
Yeah! And that sis of his is from Class A, too!
Fights are not really my cup of tea.
So...
I'll leave the rest to you!
Got it!
Summon!
Chemistry
It may look horrendous, but with that score...
Summon!
Why do you get a cat-eared being while I get a normal cat?!
Because you're always so catty.
Covered with Cats
WHAT- did you say?
An opening!
Sis!
You needn't worry; I'm not that weak.
I also...
really hate bugs.
That was easy. Let's move on.
Understood.
Hold on, Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
Who's that?
Kinoshita Hideyoshi, I've been waiting for you.
I don't know what business you have with him, but finish it quick.
I'll just get to the point.
What... do you want?
Kinoshita Hideyoshi, I'm really...
truly...
...in love with you!
That was the first time in my life...
that I heard Hideyoshi scream.
I heard Hideyoshi's scream...
I heard Hideyoshi scream...
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Everyone's Songs
The Sun and the Sunflower
Before I knew it, I was always chasing after you.
When I think about it, I was always yearning for your smile.
I don't know how to express my feelings with words,
but I still want to tell you how I feel.
I love you, Kinoshita! Everything about you!
I love you from the bottom of my
heart!
Everyone's Songs!
"The Sun and the Sunflower."
Before I knew it, I was always chasing after you.
When I think about it, I was always yearning for your smile.
I don't know how to express my feelings with words,
but I still want to tell you how I feel.
I love you, Kinoshita! Everything about you!
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
S-Sorry. I screamed like a little girl.
Don't worry about that, Hideyoshi.
Exactly. It'd be worse not to scream in that situation.
Everyone's Songs
The Sun and the Sunflower
Before I knew it, I was always chasing after you.
When I think about it, I was always yearning for your
smile.
I don't know how to express my feelings with words,
but I still want to tell you how I feel.
I love you, Kinoshita! Everything about you!
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
I can't believe he'd actually write and recite a poem for this.
Everyone's Songs
The Sun and the Sunflower
Before I knew it, I was always chasing after you.
When I think about it, I was always yearning for your
smile.
I don't know how to express my feelings with words,
but I still want to tell you how I feel.
I love you, Kinoshita! Everything about you!
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
Fantastically creepy job!
The Sun and the Sunflower
Before I knew it, I was always chasing after you.
When I think about it, I was always yearning for your
smile.
I don't know how to express my feelings with words,
but I still want to tell you how I feel.
I love you, Kinoshita! Everything about you!
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
Fantastically creepy job!
It blew me away too.
Yup
It's time we do something about this.
Hey! You losers watching this?
Damn them!
Come get us if you can!
Hey, say something too, Tsunemura.
Kinoshita, I-
Yoshii! Sakamoto! You're watching this, right?!
How long are you gonna make us wait?! Get your asses over here!
Try to make it fun for us, okay?!
Damn them!
Those bastards!
They're on!
Question 13
Review the questions we've
done until now and comment
on how you feel about your
answers.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
I give myself full points in the
sense that I answered them to
the best of my ability, but I
cannot say I am satisfied as
I cannot afford to relax my
attention.
Teacher's Comment
As expected of you, Himeji. Although taking
pride in one's absolute perfection and criticizing
oneself for simply thinking one's always perfect may seem contradictory,
both are important. While some workers would say they are always giving
100%, others might say it is impossible to give 100% forever. Both are wonderful
ways of thinking.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 13: Review the questions we've done until now and comment on how you feel about your answers.
I always get my name right!
It'd be harder to get it wrong.
It'd be harder to get
it wrong.
Next episode: Idiots, Tests, and Summoned Beings!
Idiots, Tests, and Summoned Beings!
This will be on your test.