I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a twist of fate changed everything.
I was handed a red gem,
and with it I was given magical powers.
The unexpected encounter I was drawn
into had been quietly set in motion.
But I've been facing each day as it comes, with my head held high.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Good evening!
Nanoha Takamachi here.
For the most part, I'm just an
ordinary third-grader, but...
as you can see here, recently these kinds of things have been happening.
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical Magical! Jewel Seed Serial XX!
Seal!
Sealing.
Nanoha, good job!
Um... right now I'm what you'd call a magical girl...
N-Nanoha, are you okay?
I'm fine, but...
I'm just a little tired...
N-Nanoha!
Nanoha! Are you all right?
Episode 3
The City's in a Lot of Danger?
Nanoha, it's morning already.
You have to get up soon.
Today's Sunday...
Just let me sleep in a little longer...
Nanoha!
I'm Nanoha Takamachi, a third-grader.
Nanoha! Wake up, Nanoha!
Through an unexpected encounter,
I met a mage from another world, Yuuno.
During the day, I'm just a normal grade schooler.
Nanoha! Come on, Nanoha! Nanoha!
But at night, I become a magical girl,
and help Yuuno search for the Jewel Seeds.
Confirmation.
It's already been a week
since I met Yuuno.
We've managed to find a total of five Jewel Seeds so far.
And ever since I became a magical girl,
I've felt as though I gained something, but...
Nanoha, I think it'd be a good
idea to take today off.
But...
Just rest for today!
We've already collected five of them.
If you don't, you won't be able to last.
And don't you already
have plans for today?
Yeah... you're right.
Then, I guess I'll take a small break
from Jewel Seed hunting today.
Yeah!
Over here!
Here, here!
After it!
My dad's the coach and owner of a soccer team, Midoriya JFC,
and today they have a match.
So me, Arisa, and Suzuka
came out to cheer them on.
Now then, since the stands are
finally full, shall we begin?
Yeah, let's.
Go, go!
Everyone, give it your all!
This is one of the sports
on this world, right?
Hm? Yeah, that's right.
It's called "soccer."
You score points by kicking
the ball into the goal.
The only person allowed to use their hands
is the one standing in front of the goal.
Oh? That sounds pretty fun.
Nice block!
It really was!
Move up, move up!
Do you have sports like this where
you're from too, Yuuno?
We do, but I'm always doing research and
excavations, so I don't play too often.
Just like me, then.
I'm not very good at sports.
Midoriya
Sakuradai
Game over! With a final score
of 2-0, Midoriya JFC wins!
All right!
All right, you guys! Good job!
You played great,
just like we practiced!
Yes, sir!
Well then, who's up for some food to celebrate?
Yeah!
Looking at him closely, he doesn't really look like a normal ferret, right?
Now that you mention it, yeah.
That nice vet lady said
he was unusual, too...
Ah, um... I guess you could say
he's kind of a unique ferret...
Hey, Yuuno. Shake.
So cute!
Such a clever little thing!
So smart!
Sorry about this, Yuuno...
I-It's okay...
Thank you for treating us!
Thank you very much!
Everyone, you were really great today!
Let's practice hard this week,
and win the next match just like we won this one!
Yes, sir!
Well then, that's all for today!
Be careful on your way home.
Thank you very much!
Great job today!
Same to you.
That was just my imagination... right?
Ah, this is fun!
Here you go, Nanoha!
Well then, I guess we'll head out, too?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh yeah, you both have things
to do this afternoon, right?
I'm going out with my older sister.
And I'm going shopping with my dad!
That sounds like fun. Tell me all about it on Monday, okay?
Oh, are you all splitting
up for today, too?
Ah, Dad!
Thank you for inviting us today!
The match was very fun!
Oh, I should be thanking you two
for coming to cheer us on.
If you're both going home,
shall I walk you back?
Oh, that's all right.
I'm getting picked up here, so...
Me too!
I see.
How about you, Nanoha?
I'll head home and relax a little!
I see.
I'm also going back to take a quick
bath, and then it's back to work.
Shall we go home together?
Yeah!
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Nanoha, have you grown a little taller?
Dad! You said that the other day, too!
I don't grow that quickly...
Is that so?
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Nanoha, if you're going to go to sleep, put on some pajamas first.
Yuuno, you should take a nap, too.
Well then, I'm going to
sleep until dinnertime.
Sure enough, using magic is really exhausting for beginners.
If only I were stronger...
You were really great today.
Oh, no, not really...
It's just because we had a good defense.
Still, you were really cool back there.
Oh, that's right.
Here.
It's so pretty!
It's probably just a normal stone,
but I thought it was pretty, so...
Nanoha!
You noticed, too?
What's the matter, Nanoha?
Do you want to come in with me?
Sorry, Dad! Some other time!
I'm going out for a little!
I see...
Have a nice time.
Raising Heart... please!
Stand by, ready.
Set up.
This is horrible...
Looks like it was activated by a human.
If someone puts their strongest
feelings and wishes into it,
the Jewel Seed will
release the most power.
That boy really did have one back then...
I should've noticed, but I...
I might've been able to stop this before it happened...
Nanoha...
Nanoha?
Yuuno, what should I do in a situation like this?
Yuuno!
Ah... yeah. To seal it, you need to get up close.
First, we need to find
where it sprouted from.
But since it's grown this big,
I'm not sure where to start.
It'll be okay if we just
find where it starts, right?
Area Search.
Lyrical Magical! Search!
Find where this growth is worst!
Found it!
Really?!
I'll seal it right away!
It's impossible from here!
We need to get closer!
We can! It'll be fine!
Right, Raising Heart?
Shooting Mode.
Set up.
Go and capture it!
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical Magical!
Jewel Seed Serial X!
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt No. X.
Mode Release.
Thank you, Raising Heart.
Goodbye.
She used long-range magic
that even I can't use...
This girl... just how much talent for magic does she have?
We've caused so much trouble
for a lot of people, huh?
Wh-What are you saying? You're doing
what you can to the best of your ability!
I noticed that he had one...
but I thought it was just my imagination.
Nanoha.
Please, don't look so sad!
I was the one who started all of this...
You're just helping me out with what I have to do.
Nanoha! You've been doing just fine!
Nanoha...
That was my first mistake
since becoming a mage...
Causing trouble for someone... is very painful.
That's how I felt, so I decided to help Yuuno.
I decided not just to give it my best...
but to give it everything I had.
And I wouldn't just be doing this to help Yuuno,
but I'd search for the Jewel Seeds because I wanted to.
So something like this... would never happen again.
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
All of us went to have some
fun at Suzuka's house.
She has an older sister, a maid,
and lots of cats and kittens!
But something really crazy
happened to one of the kittens!
And then we ran into another mage!
What's her goal?!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 4
A Rival!? Another Magical Girl!
Episode Four:
Lyrical Magical, doing my best!