Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Into the Darkness
Are ya okay?
Yeah. It doesn't hurt or anything.
Found ya.
After she grabbed me, Shiori's face looked different.
What?
So I'm the only one who saw it.
There's no doubt about it.
It was the girl I saw at the end of the festival.
What does this mean?
Yer memory was damaged in the fight with Shiori's shadow.
Ya got turned into a dark blob.
But it didn't have time to completely erase me.
I restored my body from the remaining data and came back.
All so I could show ya the truth, Shinpei.
It really started to rain.
That's why I told ya we needed umbrellas.
R-Right.
Impressive. Ya even managed to take a bird's-eye view of time itself.
We're going to the old clinic now.
What?!
In this rain?
That place's deep in the mountains.
It'll be dark soon.
Why's that matter?
Ushio went there.
We ain't got time.
Don't come if ya don't wanna.
Ushio knows the place.
Ya really are something.
Dummy.
'Course I'm coming with.
Okay.
I wonder if the rain'll stop.
Tomorrow's the festival, so I hope it clears up before then.
Are ya going?
I dunno. There's so much going on.
Right.
Sorry.
No, it's fine. It ain't like I have a yukata anyway.
Oh, ya don't gotta worry about that.
I have one that'd be perfect fer ya.
Thanks, Tokiko.
But I...
Please, Mio, stay with me tomorrow!
Tokiko?
Dang it! This sucks!
I'm soaked to the bone!
Jeez.
Are you girls from this island?
Y-Yes.
Wait, Mio!
Who's asking?
Oh, sorry for not introducing myself.
I'm Miura, from the Wakayama North Police.
Do you know the Kobayakawas of Koba Mart?
Sorry fer the wait.
Am I supposed to crack a joke at yer outfit or what?
I'm being serious here!
And what about yer outfit? Yer not armed at all!
No worries.
I'm with him.
Yer armed with Ushio?!
Do Not
Enter
Why were ya trying to search the old clinic?
I actually tried to sneak in during the summer of fourth grade.
Totsumura and his friends invited me to go ghost hunting.
Man, he's a cop.
Didn't he see the "Do Not Enter" sign?
Look who's talking.
But we couldn't go inside.
What are you doing?
My old man found us.
My family owns this land,
so I didn't think much of it back then.
I figured he had any right to be there,
but ain't it a bit weird?
Why would he even come to this abandoned clinic?
Where does a wise man hide a leaf? In the forest.
But what does he do if there is no forest? He grows a forest to hide it in.
What would ya hide in an abandoned clinic?
Ushio, are there shadows nearby?
After Ushio restored her memory, she can now detect shadows.
What do ya think?
There's none right now.
Come on, are ya fooling around?
Yer wearing a swimsuit?
We didn't come here to swim, ya know!
We didn't come here to play baseball either, now did we?!
Calm down.
This is my battle outfit! Underestimate me at yer own peril!
She's so scary! She ain't like Mio at all!
Explain it to him, Shinpei.
Wearing real clothes interferes with her transformation.
I could wear armor, but my real body is a shadow.
I'll die if it's stabbed.
So a swimsuit's best fer fighting.
I can transform as often as I need into anything I copied once.
As long as I have the mental capacity, I can expand my repertoire.
Amazing, ain't she?
Yeah, but also a bit distracting.
Hey.
Wow, this place was left as is.
Some of this probably has historic value.
It was built over 100 years ago during the Meiji period.
It was abandoned in the 1960s.
Is there anything here that might be related to shadows?
The stairs collapsed.
Guess we can't check upstairs.
Can ya use shadow powers to get up there, Ushio?
Wha... I... Um...
Scared of ghosts, are ya?
Ain'tcha just the cutest?
I shouldn't've told ya that.
Well?!
Cool!
Oh?
It's a medicine shelf.
This is...
corrosive sublimate.
Corrosive sublimate?
It's mercury dichloride, extremely toxic and no longer used.
I can't believe this is just sitting here.
Old medical records and prescriptions.
"Appendicitis. Bronchitis. Pneumonia."
Nothing about the shadow sickness.
Sh-Shinpei?
What is it?
Look.
What's that?
That's creepy.
Looks to be a wooden statue.
Seems really old.
There's a fish in its left hand.
A sea bream?
This reminds me of the god that... What was it, again?
Brings business prosperity, I think.
Ya mean Ebisu?
That's it!
Ebisu (Webisu)
1. One of the Seven Gods of Fortune. Typically portrayed wearing
kariginu with a fishing rod in his right hand and a sea bream in
his left.
2. God of outpatient care.
3. God of fishing. Defied sea bream.
Also a whale in ancient times.
4. Yorigami. Believed to have drifted ashore
from the ocean.
It's the god of fishing.
But ain't Ebisu a chubby old man?
This one's more feminine.
I've never heard of a female Ebisu.
What is it?
Hiruko
The first god created from Izanagi and Izanami when Japan
was created, according to the Kojiki. However, he was a
weak child and was soon put onto a boat of reeds and
cast out to sea. This section from Kojiki describes Hiruko
as a leech-like with no arms or legs, giving birth to
the interpretation that Hiruko is heteromorphic.
Hiruko
The first god created from Izanagi and Izanami when Japan
...........from Kojiki describes Hiruko
...rms or legs, giving birth to
Hiruko is heteromorphic.
It can't be.
This is Hiruko!
Hiruko? Why's it here?
I dunno. It's just a guess.
But if this is Hiruko...
What's Hiruko look like anyway?
Ain't ever seen an image of it before.
"Leech-like with no arms or legs. Heteromorphic."
Why would a god like that become a god of luck?
Jinjou Elementary......
Japanese Language
Textbook
Ministry of Education,
Science, and Culture
This is a recipe book.
Did a family live upstairs?
These are old photos of the Hishigata family.
Hey! Ushio!
What's up?
So creepy!
This way.
What'd ya find upstairs?
There's too much up there to search in a day.
Can ya slip into this space?
Yer making me work so much.
Ya owe me some octopus dumplings tomorrow.
I'll buy ya as much as ya want.
Seriously?!
That's a promise, okay?
Well? Anything?
Something's on the floor.
What is this?
It's too dark to tell.
Can ya do the flashy thing?
Ya don't have to copy anything.
Oh, yeah.
There's a keyhole.
This wall might be a door.
Come back fer now.
I guess we can't break in.
We need to find the key.
Damn.
This is definitely suspicious.
Working so hard made me hungry.
Take this seriously!
Here.
A rice ball?! Why?!
Let's eat dinner.
Not ya too, Shinpei.
Yum!
That's good.
Rice really is the best.
Fills ya up real good.
Ya ate too much.
I'm so full!
Ya said it was feminine, right?
What?
This statue has a big stomach.
Maybe it's pregnant.
Ya could be right, but was Hiruko a god of fertility?
Hold on.
Shadow scans go deep inside.
That's how we copy human bones and organs.
Something's inside its stomach.
I'll copy it to see.
Using her hair?
Wh-What's that?
The key!
It's a hidden door!
Bet this hole leads underground.
Be careful, guys.
I can sense shadows down there.
A door that can only be opened by a shadow.
Why's that here,
Dad?
Ushio.
I'm not afraid, as long as I'm with ya.
Let's go.
Summer Time Rendering
Don't look up!
I heard there were a lot of underground trenches dug during the war.
With the entrance closed,
most likely no one has come here for many decades.
Or is this a passage only shadows can use?
Do ya sense any shadows?
Over there.
I got a bad feeling.
Both of ya listen to me.
If things get bad, Ushio, just protect yerself.
Sou, do everything ya can to save her.
Ya saw my powers!
I'm the one who'll protect ya!
If I die, I'll just loop back, but what if ya die first?
Can ya follow me back?
Otherwise, I won't see ya until
the fireworks show on the 24th.
No, it could be even worse.
Worse? How?
I may never see you again.
Yer power is irreplaceable.
I wanna avoid losing that.
Hurry up and spit out what yer trying to say, okay?
I am.
That promise I made...
I'll see that through.
What promise?
I'll protect ya fer sure this time.
Shinpei, that's...
I don't get it, but I won't let ya die.
Will ya let him protect ya, Ushio?
Wh-Whatever. Do what ya want.
A black stain in the shape of a person.
This is really old.
Someone was erased by a shadow here.
Just a rat.
Don't scare me!
It's there.
I sense a shadow where the rat went.
Did it notice us?
Dunno.
I'll take a look.
I told ya. I'll go.
Be careful.
Three shots to the shadow.
Three shots will stop its movement.
Did ya see it?
Yeah, I saw one.
It's eating.
Ushio, if ya can sense shadows,
does it also sense that yer nearby?
Not sure.
There's no point in thinking.
The present calls for action!
We're striking first!
I'll stop its movement.
Ushio will finish it off.
Sou will be backup.
No response.
That means it hasn't noticed us.
It ain't hiding its shadow.
Good.
The bigger the target, the better.
Only five or six more steps to go.
This is bad.
It uses smell!
It hid its shadow!
It's like hitting a baseball!
Nice! I made solid contact!
Oh no!
Stay back, Ushio! We'll take care of this!
Crap! It's gonna kill Sou!
Calm down.
Take a bird's-eye view.
It's now or never!
Your hands are shaking.
You won't hit the target like that.
Relax and focus.
You've always been doing this...
ever since Mom and Dad died.
I learned how to do this...
and make anything seem like nothing.
Look.
Ushio!
Gotcha!
W-We did it.
Shinpei! We killed it!
Y-Yeah.
All right!
Sorry I shot ya.
Don'tcha worry.
Everything worked out in the end.
Ya were really calm!
I did get a bit worried when ya missed yer first shot.
I knew ya'd hit it.
Ya stayed up practicing all night.
Ya saw that?!
Say something next time. I'm so embarrassed.
Ow.
Something wrong?
It's too early to relax.
The shadow I first sensed is still here.
I got a really bad feeling.
Sounds like nails on a chalkboard.
Where's the sound coming from?
That way.
I think it's to the left up there.
Okay.
Hey, Shinpei!
He went straight to it.
It's because he's seen it.
The future that'll occur if we don't do anything.
Don'tcha wanna protect Mio too?
'Course I do!
I'd give my life fer her!
Then ya ain't got time to be afraid.
Ya just gotta go forward!
It's the wound made by the shadow Mio!
When my powers returned,
I printed a new arm from Ushio's data.
Was it just superficial?
Have I not recovered from the damage my body took yet?
Go away!
Hey, Shinpei. I got a question.
Can't Ushio copy the nail gun?
If she could, we'd have two.
Yeah, we tried that, and she was able to copy it.
But it didn't fire.
From what she said, as long as the original exists,
copied machines are just fakes.
Ya need to erase the original fer the copy to function.
Original
Copy
(unusable)
Original erased
Copy
(usable)
So we can't use both.
If we only need its shape like the key, it wouldn't matter,
but fer items that use electricity or gas or whatever kinda energy, the original needs to be erased.
What about that nail gun?
This is actually a copy.
There are a lot of benefits to using a copy.
Ushio can restore the nails or the gas canisters by reprinting the original data when I run out.
What was that?
A gunshot.
Shinpei!
This area feels way different.
This is a natural cave.
I smell the ocean.
Is it nearby?
Oh no.
Since when?
Huh?
I sense shadows all around us.
We're surrounded!
H-How many are there?
Run, Ushio!
Run!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Dinner Time