Pardon!
Kanata!
I've missed you so!
Wake up, sleepyhead!
Good morning!
M-Morning...
You'd better hurry!
The new semester's starting soon!
New semes...
I-I slept in!
Yui, why didn't you wake me up sooner?!
You were smiling so peacefully
that I'd feel bad for disturbing you.
Did you have a nice dream?
Huh?!
Yeah...
Bonjour.
I'm pumped for the new semester,
so let's go!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Hand in your summer homework, if you'd please.
This is mine!
It appears to be completed.
It is!
I played hard and studied even harder!
It seems you're a bit closer to being a model Noble Academy student.
How pretty...
The Fall Semester!
A New Dream and a New Threat!
Now then, let's commençons la princesse lesson!
The raison d'être of la composition florale is to draw out la flowers' beauty!
I'm done!
How is it?
It is not mauvais, but je cannot call it bon.
Neither can I...
I really like flowers, but arranging them might not be my strong suit.
It's something you've gotta have a knack for.
How pretty!
But of course!
Siamour...
Oui?
How is that boy doing?
He's still in dormir.
I never would have guessed that Lock was actually a fairy.
Yeah, talk about a shocker.
If this is his true form, he must have been controlled by the power of despair.
But he was freed thanks to vos valiant efforts!
He shall have moi to watch over him until he awakens.
Things are lookin' up!
We've got a new power, the Princess Palace, on our side!
You're all a step closer to becoming Grand Princesses!
We've obtained all of the Dress Up Keys...
and even discovered new ones...
I'd like to meet my brother as soon as I can.
You will!
I saw Kanata in my dream this morning!
I think it's a sign that we'll see him soon!
Yes, it must be.
Okay, time to get pumped...
and weed the flower garden!
Why are you going weeding?
I haven't been tending to the garden lately.
As such,
I've got weeds to pull!
Huh? It's weed-free.
Did someone else straighten up?
Is that...
Bonjoooooour!
I'm sorry!
W-What're you apologizing for?
You saved me a load of work!
Thanks, Hanae!
I love how your name means "the blessing of flowers"!
Th-Thanks.
It might be my name's fault that I like flowers so much.
I love flowers too!
If I knew I had a classmate
I could get along this well with,
I would've talked to you much sooner!
Thanks!
I think we're done with the summer flowers.
What should we plant next?
You gotta have cosmos in the fall!
Cinerarias can withstand the cold, too!
I think some tall snapdragons would look great behind them and give them more presence.
Presence? You sound like a pro!
Hanae, do you want to become a florist?
Huh? I've never thought about it...
You don't have any dreams for your future?
Not really.
Even after all my time at Noble Academy, I'm still not good at anything.
That doesn't matter one bit!
Dreams are treasures that we all carry!
Treasures?
You might be right.
Aaaah!
Don't tell me...
the person who arranged the flowers in the classroom...
was you?
Yeah.
I knew it!
Those flowers were simply splendid!
I loved them!
It's nothing, really.
I know!
How about becoming a floral coordinator?
Floral coordinator?
It's a job where you decorate offices and stores with flowers and design floral arranges for weddings!
How wonderful...
Isn't it?
You'd be a perfect fit!
I know you can do it!
It's strange...
Hearing you support me makes it feel possible.
Really?
Oh yeah, I've been trying to arrange flowers too,
but I just can't get it right...
Can you give me some advice?
Sure.
If you think I can help, at least.
Of course!
Okay, I'll be right back, so wait here!
Sure!
Perf, what's wrong?
I feel like something bad is about to happen...
What's... going on?
Look out!
Haruharu!
Towie!
Girls!
Found you, Cure Flora.
Huh?
He couldn't be...
Impossible!
You're kidding!
There's just no way!
I came back from the depths of hell, Princess Precures...
to defeat you once and for all!
Close...
Why...
is Close here?
But the Precures already defeated you!
Cure Flora...
I'll drench your dream in despair!
Girls!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Ah, that transformation takes me back.
Too slow!
Ice!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Shooting Star!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
So you're Cure Scarlet?
I'd hoped your flames could heat things up...
but they're mild!
Scarlet!
It's over.
Coming out myself was a waste of time.
He's strong!
Come!
Stop!
Freeze!
Dyspaaaair...
Vil!
Dyspairvils?
They don't look like ones!
The strongest Dyspairvils are born from the fiercest dreams...
But those born from the freshly seeded are not to be trifled with.
Go.
Right!
Floral coordinator, huh?
Stop!
Freeze!
What?
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to make beautiful arrangements!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
The dream has ended.
Hanae!
Dyspairvil!
Flora!
Dyspair...
Vil!
Girls!
This Dyspairvil is strong!
How could you use flowers for evil?
Every blossom will one day wilt.
Why bother?
But even then...
more flowers will yet bloom!
Dyspairvil!
Rose!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
Dyspair...
Use the power of the Princess Palace!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming!
Adieu.
The dream did not end.
We failed to end it.
However...
you despaired.
Huh?
More flowers will yet bloom, but so will despair.
Despair nurtures despair...
as it grows ever stronger.
What do you mean?
Open!
The door to your dream!
Hanae, make your dream blossom.
I never thought Close would come back...
What did he mean by despair nurturing despair?
I've lost my castle and have naught left but emptiness.
Oh, whatever am I to do?
Keep imprisoning dreams like you've always done.
C-Close! How did you—
I revived.
Revived?
Isn't that...
He mighta been a good-for-nothing traitor,
but he did his part.
His own despair was enough to top this off.
You can't mean Lock!
Despair never disappears.
It creeps up on dreamers without a sound, and then...
it's suddenly...
before their very eyes.
Th-The Forest of Despair!
Accept my offering.
Welcome back, Lady Dyspear!
Close.
You've served me well.
I've sown the Seeds of Despair as you wished.
With time, they'll bud and flourish...
in their world.
You three shall follow Close's command.
Right!
What? Me too?
I think it'll look good if you put this in the center.
I see!
So if I move this here...
Yeah, exactly.
What about this?
Good!
It's done!
Is it good?
Yeah!
It's wonderful!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Who's the new guy? Minamin's boy toy?
B-Boy toy?!
Oh, it's him...
It seems he's to marry Minami. Congratulations!
M-M-Marry?!
Pardon, I need to speak with him alone.
Wait, Minami!
Go! Princess Precure:
Minami's Fiancé?
The Nobleman Makes His Return!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Tokyo - Chihiro (Age 6)
Tokyo - Momona (Age 7)