Now, we're going to raise
Kaleido Star's curtain.
When you watch Kaleido Star, you
should keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Everyone, have you ever thought
"I can't do this anymore"?
Even though you work to your limit,
there is nothing you can do about it.
But there is somebody waiting for you.
Someone who encourages
you and is tough on you.
Friends should be able to trust each other.
Because I'm not the only
one having a hard time.
I'm not! I'm not!
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Then I'll go to the river and do the laundry.
Okay.
Charlotte, Julie.
So you were here.
Oh...
It's like, been awhile.
What happened to Kaleido Stage?
Did you quit?
Well, you know...
We couldn't agree with that Yuri guy.
Well, it's more like we were fired.
Shush!
How is Sora?
Is she working hard?
She's way past "working hard."
It looks super miserable.
If you ask me, it's pretty extreme.
If it were me, I'd like, die.
I don't know how she can endure that.
I've got a bit of renewed respect for her.
That's right. That's right.
What kind of training is she doing?
"The Amazing Intensive Training Continues."
Until the day they perform
the legendary great maneuver,
we're holding special events every day.
I really want everyone to come.
The atmosphere at Kaleido
Stage is really heating up.
By the way, what's all this about
making the tickets non-refundable
even if they can't perfect
the legendary maneuver?
I personally feel pain when I think of
how they suddenly cancelled "Freedom"
even though it was the
previous owner's fault.
Refunding the money at that time
was very tough financially.
So we made everything clear this time,
and sold the tickets only to those
who understood the situation.
Then have you gotten any complaints?
None.
According to rumor,
the last person to attempt
this great maneuver
was your father.
Yes.
But he died in an accident during practice.
Oh my...
So the maneuver is that hard.
That's why I definitely want the
performance to succeed this time.
This channel will be broadcasting
live on the day of the event.
So how is the progress of the
legendary great maneuver?
Well, I doubt they will perfect it.
I'm 99% certain that the
performance will be cancelled.
Thanks to the publicity about
the legendary great maneuver,
the attendance is picking up again.
Also, sales of related
merchandise are going well.
All thanks to this legendary great maneuver.
After the cancellation,
I'll announce that Layla and I
will attempt the maneuver again.
By doing so, we can generate
even more publicity and--
That's enough, thank you.
When we cancel the performance,
we can end Kaleido Stage too.
We're going to sell Kaleido Stage.
But...
If we keep letting you manage it, I'm
afraid that we'll lose a lot of money.
I bet old man Kenneth knew this was coming.
That's why he backed out of
the investment so quickly.
Next!
Okay.
Sora!
Oh... Mia, Anna...
You're here.
Are Jonathan and everyone doing all right?
You don't need to chitchat.
What is this?
This? Special training.
Special training?
You're terrible, doing
something like this to Sora.
Stand up, Sora.
Unless you work hard, you can't
catch up with Miss Layla.
I know.
Sora...
This is reckless!
Being reckless is my specialty. So...
Sora!
Ken, please let Sora rest!
Let's take her to the lodge!
Okay.
Even though it's training,
I can't believe she did that until
she became so bruised and tired.
I can't believe Ken, either.
I thought he would protect her.
Oh, shoot!
Why am I sleeping?
I have to practice! Otherwise...
Sora!
Where are you going?
I can't catch up with Miss Layla!
Wait
No! You have to get more rest!
I have to catch up with Miss Layla...
Calm down, Sora!
If you don't rest, you'll break down, Sora.
You're doing too much.
Thank you, but I'll be okay.
'Cause Miss Layla has already
advanced to more difficult training.
Sora!
Miss Layla is practicing too,
bruising herself all over.
That legendary great maneuver...
It must be a much harder
maneuver than we ever imagined.
Yes...
What should we do about that story?
I know...
I think it's better that we don't tell her.
You're probably right...
Good!
I did it.
It means nothing if you did it by accident.
So I want you to try hard until you
can do it ten times consecutively.
Yes!
I'm starting.
I'm beginning to understand what
the legendary great maneuver is.
If I could do that kind of maneuver,
it would be truly wonderful, but...
I can't do that with my
partner in her current state.
Miss Layla,
aren't you going to eat any more?
No...
It seems I have lost my appetite today.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll take my meals in my room.
Oh... Yes.
Miss Layla...
You did it!
You did it ten times consecutively.
We will advance to the next level.
Hurry!
I want to receive the applause
that makes my whole body tremble.
Sora, no matter what happens,
I'm going to perfect the legendary
great maneuver with you.
Yes!
Just keeping the posture
itself is hard enough.
But to swing that high on top of it...
Just how long are you going to rest?
Yes!
Don't you think Miss Layla
seems irritated somehow?
She even said she wanted to
have meals all by herself.
Charlotte's cooking is kinda bad, you know?
You're lying! You serious?
I don't think it is.
She's right. Your cooking is pretty good.
That's what I thought.
Now I feel better.
Miss Layla is irritated
because I'm not good enough.
I wonder if I'm really able to be
Miss Layla's partner like this.
After a week, she finally
started showing stability,
but it looks like she's lost her motivation.
I can't watch!
Let's go help Charlotte and Julie.
Okay...
Miss Layla,
why won't you say anything?
Something like, "Try harder,"
"be strong,"
or "you can never be my
partner if you're like that."
Please say something.
Say anything!
Please, Miss Layla!
Sora...
I have nothing to say.
Mr. Kenneth...
What business brought him?
Is something wrong, coming all the way here?
What's with that woeful face, Sora?
What?
You look like you have no
fighting spirit at all.
Your eyes are empty.
You hardly look capable of doing
that legendary great maneuver.
She's tired now because she
just finished training.
I guess everything is just
the way those guys wish.
Those guys?
Those squirts who are
investing in Kaleido Stage.
None of them think you will perfect
the legendary great maneuver.
What?
Even if the maneuver is not perfected,
they think it will be all right
as long as they can make a profit
through the events leading up
to the day of the actual event.
That's horrible...
Rather, they're thinking it'll be better
if the performance is cancelled.
That way, they can save on the expenses.
But what about the audience?
Can you say with confidence that you
will never disappoint the audience?
will perfect that maneuver with Layla?
Well...
Can you say with confidence
that you're Layla's partner?
Something like, "Try harder,"
"be strong,"
or "you can never be my
partner if you're like that."
Please say something.
Say anything!
Please, Miss Layla!
I have nothing to say.
I...
Sora!
How could you ask her something like that?
She's desperately trying to rouse
herself even though she's discouraged!
Well, I think I'll go
inside and get some rest.
What? Wait!
Bring me some coffee, boy.
My name is Ken Robbins.
Sora...
I couldn't answer.
I couldn't tell him that I
would perfect it by all means.
Miss Layla called me her partner,
and I just let it go to my head.
Having come this far, I finally realize that
my abilities are completely inadequate.
I just feel like running away now.
I can't forgive myself!
You're doing more than enough, Sora.
But, if it's too tough, I
think it's okay to back out.
I'm sure Miss Layla will understand.
Miss Layla told me once...
It's a nuisance if you're going to prepare
yourself with a half-baked attitude.
If quitting is better for Miss Layla, I...
It's very kind of you to
come all the way here.
Oh, that's fine.
Anyway,
I knew Sora was very a talented
girl and I expected a lot from her,
but I never realized she was so good she
could attempt that legendary great maneuver.
Me too.
So is this the first time since Arlon Brass?
Yes.
Does that accident still weigh on your mind?
My feeling of regret has not disappeared.
He was reliable and very responsible,
but that challenge was reckless.
What?
The one who died attempting the legendary
great maneuver at Kaleido Stage
was Arlon Brass, the top star at the time.
Yuri's father.
I confirmed the story with Jean,
so there's no doubt about it.
Those investors at Kaleido Stage
must have heard the story from Yuri.
It's understandable why they don't
believe in the success of maneuver.
So don't worry about it.
So that's why...
I'm counting on you.
I expect you to perfect the
maneuver without a hitch.
Nobody, including Mr. Yuri, thinks I'm
able to perfect the legendary maneuver.
Well, the problem is how
Sora will react after this.
Whether she can rise out of the depths, or...
If she can't do it,
there is absolutely no way that she could
perform the legendary great maneuver.
That's right.
After all, you guys are the ones who created
"Freedom" when you were at the bottom.
I'm counting on Sora.
Did you back out of the investment
so you can let us experience how
we can rise up from the bottom?
That's part of it.
But I don't feel like doing
business with those guys.
Then I will deliver this to Miss Layla.
Okay.
Sora said she doesn't want dinner tonight.
Let's leave her alone.
Yeah...
Yes.
What is it?
Well, I was told by Miss Layla
not to talk about this, but...
Miss Layla,
I want to talk about something.
Miss Layla...
Ken...
Miss Layla is not here right now.
She's out running.
Running?
At a time like this?
Yes. She's trying to lose weight.
Losing weight?
That's right.
Probably, the greater the weight
difference of the two performers,
the lower the chance of success
of the legendary great maneuver.
I bet Miss Layla realized what
the legendary great maneuver is.
I think it's almost time
for her to come back.
You know, Miss Layla has been eating
her meals in her room these days.
Yes.
But I heard she's not
really eating most of it.
What?
Charlotte told me,
even though it seems she was
told not to talk about it.
Miss Layla is doing all
of this because of me...
Don't you think it's wrong to blame yourself?
Partners are supposed to be equal.
You're trying to be a good
partner for Miss Layla,
and she's also trying to be your partner.
Miss Layla?
I've admired her for a long time.
It's true. You have
something I don't possess.
This is a real fight between us.
When I was a child, I saw
Kaleido Stage with my parents.
It was so wonderful. Like a dream.
It will not be my last
show, unless I wish it.
Right now, I have a partner
who can make it possible.
Miss Layla!
I think you guys are the best partners.
Thank you, Ken.
Miss Layla!
Sora!
I'm sorry!
I tried to run away.
Because the special training
is hard and painful,
I made excuses and told myself that I
don't have the skills to be your partner!
I tried to run away by myself!
I'm sorry!
I'll never doubt myself again!
I'll work much harder and catch up to you!
And I'm going to perfect the legendary
great maneuver by any means!
We came all this way to do just that.
Yes.
I'll eat a lot and build up muscle.
So please don't lose any more weight.
All right.
She really rose up.
Thank you so much.
It was worth coming all the way here.
A person who rises up from
the bottom is tougher for it.
What? You mean you did this on purpose?
I'm wide awake now.
Bring me some bourbon, boy.
My name is Ken Robbins!
As partners, let's not keep
any secrets from now on.
That's a good idea.
It's a promise.
Not yet...
I can't give you qualification
to attempt that maneuver yet.
Moreover,
it seems like fate is trying to put
you through a more rigorous ordeal.
If you're able to overcome
it, the time will come.
However, it is a brutal ordeal.
The reversed Empress.
Miss Layla!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Didn't you just hit your shoulder?
I just lost my balance and
scratched it a little.
Don't worry.
But still, I think you should go
to see a doctor for just in case.
I don't have time for that.
Now let's continue.
Yes.
Good.
She seems to be doing okay.
Damn.
Since I lost weight, I
passed out for a moment.
It seems my shoulder can somehow hold on.
"Next Kaleido Star"
Please... a little longer...
Please last a little longer.
And so, it's the day before the actual show.
But Miss Layla's injuries were worse than
anybody expected, and it was hopeless.
In spite of that, just what...
Just what drives you to go so far?
What's the real reason
behind the heroic decision?
What? What?
Next time on Kaleido Star, "An Amazing Bond."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing