If I don't kill her,
she'll kill me.
Are you awake now?
Training
Don't be afraid.
I won't attack you anymore.
You are...
I don't have a name.
If you want a name, call me Ein.
It's what I've always been called.
Ein...
Why did you attack me?
To test your skill.
Skill?
You have a natural-born talent within you.
The talent to kill someone.
The talent to survive.
The talent to become an assassin.
No way...
What are you talking about?
And how would you know?
Didn't you almost kill me?
In that situation,
a normal person would have panicked and been killed by me.
But you weren't.
In that situation, you thought clearly and didn't die.
Zwei.
Zwei?
That is your name.
No,
don't call me by such a weird name!
I have a real name...
My...
...name...
You no longer have one.
Trying to remember will be a waste of time.
What are you talking about?
Actually...
...your memory...
...was erased by Inferno.
Wonderful.
Your Phantom is the best,
Scythe Master.
I am honored, Mr. McGwire.
This could not have been done by ordinary kids.
You're right.
That is why she was given the title of "Phantom".
Your achievements are amazing.
You were able to create such puppets.
No...
Without Ms. McCunnen, this would have never been possible.
You have a good subordinate , Claudia.
Speaking of which,
has that reporter been taken care of?
There doesn't seem to be any progress.
No,
that isn't true.
Didn't he witness an assassination
by a Japanese tourist?
I don't know where you heard it from.
But the witness has already been killed.
Even the corpse is gone.
Oh? Wonderful.
Was Phantom also used for that?
Yes.
You were to be killed.
So that there would be no witnesses.
But,
Master discovered your talent...
and decided that killing you would be a waste.
Master?
Scythe Master,
my superior.
Master took away your memories...
but prepared you a new identity.
Members of Inferno...
...live the life of assassins.
Assassin?
Me?!
You are my counterpart.
Zwei is your name.
Don't say crazy things!
Why do I need to? Kill people.
You can refuse.
But if you do...
I'll follow the original plan...
...and kill you.
Right here, right now.
If you want to live, you'll need to change.
You've already become someone...
...who cannot live without killing.
I...
...don't want to die.
A dream.
It's a dream.
This is just a bad dream.
If that makes you feel better, then think that way.
We'll say everything is a dream.
But...
...it'll be a very long dream.
Change into those.
Starting today you'll be with me.
You will follow every order.
Understand?
Let's begin.
Everything is going well with Zwei.
He is training diligently and very well-behaved.
He faces training so rigorous that thinking will cause him pain?
That's right. These are the basics.
Let me have you look at the results,
Ms. McCunnen.
It's about time.
My pawns are your pawns.
This is for the fate of Inferno.
Hold it like this.
Don't rest your finger on the trigger.
Put your strength in your hands, not your shoulders.
Lift your right hand up with the left as support.
This is the rear sight.
This is the front sight.
Align the sights to your target.
Lift your right arm up when shooting,
with your left arm supporting.
Hold the gun still.
Also, focus your strength...
in your hands not your wrist.
Don't rush when shooting.
Be as calm as if you were dead.
Shoot.
You have five bullets left.
Keep shooting.
You hit every target.
After accuracy, is speed.
I hit six targets in four seconds.
Let's concentrate on accuracy first.
You're still too slow.
You did hit them, obviously...
...but you'd already be dead by then.
Repeat.
Repeat...
I'll do everything
you tell me to.
If I keep doing it,
I won't have to think.
If I do that,
it'll be easier.
I'll forget all my questions.
Every day, I...
...lose more of myself.
I'm leaving. The training is the same.
Leaving?
For a job.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
That man...
...is Scythe Master.
This is an overdue mission.
But to you, it won't matter.
The target is 700 yards away.
A Remington .308 caliber has been prepared for you.
The weather is cloudy with a slight wind.
The weather channel says there will be no change until morning.
All the information is in there.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Good.
How is Zwei doing?
The basics have already been completed.
Starting tomorrow, we'll be doing something new.
Seems about time to have his test ready.
Don't mind me. Continue on.
I believe this is the first time we've met.
My name is Claudia McCunnen.
Wouldn't you like to know anything more than my name?
No.
But aren't you at least interested about Inferno?
If you don't talk, I'll assume you are.
We at Inferno...
Well...
We are a group of nationalities outside that of law or morals...
...supposedly.
Among the various gangs and mafia...
Inferno appears to be a new nation.
Inferno's goal is to unite the underworld.
Not long ago, that was but a naive dream.
What made this possible was...
...Phantom.
That's right.
Your teacher.
Phantom's power...
...is absolute.
She thinks nothing of herself and only of the target.
To Inferno, she is our greatest hope.
To the enemy, their greatest fear.
She is the undisputed top assassin.
But...
Huh?
She is still just being used by you.
Phantom and I...
...can only live as slaves.
It is true that we are only providing you with one option to live...
But, you are not slaves.
Even you have one freedom.
Progression.
Progression?
Even on a predetermined path, your goals and desires will allow you to thrive.
Your position doesn't matter, you can still give effort.
You could probably even reach the top.
No matter what, remember that as your one freedom.
You can't keep thinking of yourself as a slave.
If you keep thinking like that...
...you will only prevent any chance of your success.
There's still a lot I want to say...
...but I have work to do.
Goodbye, Zwei.
Even cars are something that people drive.
And not puppets to be controlled.
Even on a predetermined path, your desires and goals will allow you to thrive.
Your position doesn't matter, you can still give effort.
Desires...
Effort...
I've long forgotten them.
Ein.
What is it?
Today's mission...
Did you kill someone?
Yes.
How did...
...you become an assassin?
I don't know.
No one has told me what happened before I became an assassin.
So then...
Yes, the same as you.
My memories were also erased to create an assassin.
But, what about it?
I'm still alive.
That's what matters.
As an assassin,
...things of the past and future...
...do not exist.
But,
the person named Claudia...
Claudia?
She visited this afternoon.
She told us we weren't slaves...
...and that we still had freedom.
Believe it if you want.
But,
...eventually you won't be able to feel anything.
The same will happen to you.
Once you've killed someone, you'll understand...
Shooting a gun is easy.
Only, these targets are just bricks.
But...
Shoot.
Go ahead, shoot.
Zwei.
Practice
This is...
...a continued dream.
Until you die...
...you shall never awake from it.