I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
A star just fell from the sky.
That is not an ordinary star, my son.
That star is the tear of a warrior.
What warrior is it?
A lost soul who has finished his
battle somewhere on this planet.
A pitiful soul who could not
find his way to the lofty realm
where the Great Spirit awaits us all.
The report from Callisto
went directly to Vicious.
He is requesting an arrangement
for some Red Eye.
30,000 Woolongs per gram,
7,500 grams total.
Why did he send you to make the deal?
He's a Titan veteran.
We were in the same squadron.
Why does he rely on you now?
Callisto is in a financial depression.
When he can't see the future, he worries.
All the more reason for us
to keep our hands off the planet.
In truth, Vicious, are you
not the one who's worried?
It appears that you
do not have the authority
to make your own
decisions in this matter.
No matter who they are,
those who go against the will of
the Van will be severely punished.
You think I'd betray my own mentor?
Then Mao's case was merely bad luck.
Lin, you shall accompany
Vicious on this journey.
- Yes.
- Wang Long!
Callisto is a frigid planet, Vicious.
You'll need special clothing
for the arctic conditions.
Cold climates do not concern me.
True, your heart is
colder than any planet.
Colder than the eye of
a snake about to strike.
Vicious.
Remember, a snake cannot eat a dragon.
I'll be fine by myself.
I'm going with you.
Then be aware.
If you want to survive,
you'll have to betray me at times.
No, never. That would
go against the will of Van.
Such old-fashioned thinking
makes me nauseous.
Those damn corpses.
I will protect you for the
honor of the Red Dragon.
Honor, huh?
Well then, it's up to me
to sever them all.
Man, it's hot.
Where is everyone?
What a depressing group.
What's with the humidity level?
It's so muggy, I couldn't sleep.
We're experiencing technical difficulties.
It'd be hard to see you, so I'm
leaving without saying goodbye.
Please, please, do not look for me.
Free at last.
She sucked all the antifreeze
from the cooling system.
It'll be offline for at least half a day.
After this stunt, we're not
gonna look for her, right?
She emptied out the safe, too.
Nana, hachi, kyu,
konichiwa to you...
Are you sure you're looking for Faye?
Ichi, zero, ichi, ichi, sayonara...
Or are you just wasting time?
Is there anything else to do right now?
- Ah! Success!
- Is it her?
Who could this be...
Let's see... code name...
Julia!
Where's that coming from?!
Let's see...
It's pretty close. Looks like
the Blue Crow on Callisto.
Who's receiving it?!
I got cut off.
Hey, wait!
But... there aren't any
girls at the Blue Crow?
Really? No kidding!
Hey, Spike!
Am I done now?
Hey, hold on, Spike!
That's a common woman's name.
Come on, now. What about Faye?
We can't just leave her.
This is a lawless region. A woman
can't make it out there all alone.
- You know I'm right, Spike.
- You're worried about Faye?
I'm worried, all right.
About the money she took!
I want it back!
Spike!
- I'm gonna go look.
- You're not!
I'm gonna go look for my woman.
You can go look for the other one.
So you're not gonna help me, are you.
That's it! You've really gone too far.
Then don't come back.
There won't be a place for you.
That's your call, pal.
Anyway, at least you won't be lonely now.
- Not with your weird roommates.
- My roommates?
That's why you've been staying here?
You're being stupid!
It's been three years
since I teamed up with you,
but I never knew you had such
ridiculous ideas about this thing!
What a joke!
And I thought you were
the one who was lonely!
I'm glad we cleared that up.
Good riddance!
Least I'll be able to keep
some food in the place now!
I never did understand you,
right to the very end!
I don't understand either.
Goodbye!
I don't know any woman.
Like I'd know!
Not even a rumor?
I don't have any luck with them,
I'll tell you that.
I'd rather hook up
with a spiny armadillo!
Have you heard the name Julia mentioned?
You should've asked me that right off.
There's a Julia out in front
of Tony's place every night.
Sorry, sirrah. I'm not Julia.
Ju-li-us. My name's Julius.
My mistake.
Well, if you're looking for company,
you're just my type.
Thanks, but I already have plans.
You know, Gren's really the one
who might be able to help.
- I've seen him with women on occasion.
- Gren?
- Whew, it's cold.
- Yeah, let's call it a night.
Oh, a customer?
Afraid not, darling.
Can't you see he's straight?
Come on, let's try another corner.
Wait, who's Gren? Where is he?
You want to be my date?
He plays sax at the Blue Crow.
Take care.
Yeah, that was a pretty close one.
If someone sneezes and
no one says "take care,"
that person will turn into a fairy.
That's what they say
around here, you know.
Then there's no problem.
I'm already a fairy.
Don't you know that?
I'm not as simple as I seem, Mr. Saxophone.
Women aren't my style, I'm sorry.
Oh? What a pity.
However, the others
are all quite interested.
Didn't you know?
There are no women in this town.
Mmm, then I should be very popular.
You should be very careful.
Thanks for the tip, Mr. Saxophone.
I'm searching for something.
There's nothing around here.
Just some stale bread,
a broken-down car,
and some old whiskey
that tastes like gasoline.
Ever met a guy named Gren?
Can't say that I have.
Oh well.
So, you boys need something?
- You're Vicious.
- What did you say?!
Where's the money?
Hand it over, or you
won't live to spend it!
You think I'm Vicious?
You don't know what vicious is!
Start talking!
Why the hell do you think I'm Vicious?
I heard a big deal was coming
down for some lunar Red Eye.
They said Gren was selling it
to Vicious for big bucks.
I wanted to get my hands on the money!
Take a look. Do I really
look like I have money?
Why not? All foreigners are rich.
And the code named Julia?
Sounds like some sleazy
wench's name, doesn't it?
Yeah, it really does.
Hi, amigos! All 300,000 bounty
hunters in the star system...
I want a cowboy.
Forget it. There are no
bounties heads around here.
Whiskey with light cream.
That kinda cowboy.
Right. Yeah, you couldn't possibly
be a bounty hunter, could you.
Who's our new bounty head today?
Grencia Mars Elijah Guo Eckener.
- What a long name!
- He escaped from prison three years ago,
and the statute of limitations
is about to run out.
- And the bounty?
- Sho' nuff, it's now double high!
Don't miss this opportunity!
Though I hate to admit it,
I kinda hate to see him go.
What a shame.
Whoa! Judy, what are you saying?
This buckaroo's an escaped convict!
I'm aware of that.
But my word, what a handsome guy.
- Oh, just look at his picture!
- Let's see... Are you kidding?
Hey, Sp--
Hey, listen, can you turn that thing off?
Calm down. Sorry about that.
Don't worry.
That guy passed out on
the bar over there is a cop.
Yeah, and what does that mean?
Actually, there's a bounty
on my head, too.
This place is a hideout
for all kinds of fugitives.
- That's fascinating.
- So you can rest easy. No worries.
Who, me?
What's the deal?
I wanted to work off all this
frustration, but no one's coming.
Oh, yay! You're all here.
Madam, your appearance
is harmful to the eyes.
Or are you trying to entice us?
Oops, you found me out.
Just hold on a minute.
If I don't put these on,
I just might chip a nail, you know.
Okay, here we go.
Come here!
Hurry!
Mr. Saxophone!
Why did you bring me here?
Because you said you were a fairy.
Why did you come with me?
'Cause I've got no place to stay.
Oh. And you trust me, just like that?
You said you weren't interested in women.
I could take your money.
Or try to kill you.
Good luck.
Despite how I may look,
I'm not such easy prey.
I'm afraid it's broken.
You came to such a
slummy neighborhood alone?
I am alone.
I don't need any comrades.
They're not worth it.
I end up worrying
about things I shouldn't...
You know, me being
such a prize and all that.
All the guys end up
fighting over me like dogs.
They say humans are social animals.
They can't live alone.
But you can live pretty well by yourself.
I tell you, instead of
feeling alone in a group,
it's better to have real
solitude all by yourself.
When I'm dealing with them,
I swear, it's nothing but trouble.
And I get nothing out of it.
So it doesn't matter if
I'm there or not, right?
You were just afraid they'd abandon you.
So you abandoned them.
You distanced yourself
from the whole thing.
You're a strange one, aren't you.
You think so?
I don't know why I'm telling you all this.
I feel like I'm in a confession booth.
You're not a preacher
by any chance, are you?
No.
Take care, Faye.
You wanna take a shower?
No, thanks.
Could be peeping toms around here.
Make sure you're not one of them.
Well, I can't really guarantee that now.
Gren, where are you?
Vicious!
I'm out with honroutou along with
mangan and the reverse dragon.
It's 32,000. I'll be waiting.
Are you seeing Julia behind my back?
Spike!
Lin. You've gotten pretty big.
He doesn't work under you anymore, Spike.
Things are different now.
Like you using her name
for your scummy drug deals?
I truly pity her for that.
If there's anyone who
needs pity here, it's you.
We still haven't settled
the score from last time.
Make your move.
Lin, get outta the way!
Julia was here. Right in this town.
Step aside, Lin!
Lin...
A woman?
Which one are you?
I'm both at once,
and I am neither one.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
Hey... how are men
and women different?
Hmm... I think women are hiding
more vital secrets than men are.
Uh-huh... but there are
women who aren't feminine.
And men who aren't masculine.
What about those who
aren't usually feminine,
but show that side of themselves
in some chance circumstance?
- I like that.
- Really?
- I'm not talking about you.
- Who then?
Maybe it's me!
Next episode:
"Jupiter Jazz, Part 2."
Maybe it's me!