10th Street
The Finger-Pointing Geriatric
Humans pray to beings they cannot see
or whose existence they cannot prove.
God, Buddha, or even mysterious
forces from outer space.
If one's prayers are answered, they believe
in the existence of their guiding force.
If not, they doubt whether
their prayers were sufficient.
Either way, they continue to believe.
Please, let Arashiyama and I
become closer this summer.
I don't mean "closer" in
an impure way, though.
But if I had to say one way or the other,
I wouldn't be against the idea,
I just wanna take it slow.
Something like that.
No wait, I don't mean like a
"just friends" type of thing-
Of course I'm totally serious-
I mean, I honestly value her feelings too-
If I just meant that in naughty
way, that'd make me a creep-
Wait, that's not the
point I'm trying to make.
Uhh, I kinda lost my train of thought,
but since you're a god,
I'm sure you understand.
Anyway, I beg of you!
Whatever beings they may be,
the hard part isn't granting the wish,
but first figuring out what the wish is.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
"Holes" (From Vol. 2 Ch. 18)
We are being watched.
For the next 9 minutes and 16 seconds.
Separate from the cage of your body and its
perception, and surpass the boundaries of common sense.
For we shall now set foot
into a world of mystery.
Guided towards a realm of
neither truth nor fiction.
Welcome to the Maruko Shopping District.
Live Breaking News
Mysterious Holes
Found in Empty Lot!
Can you see this, ladies and gentlemen?
Last night, several perfectly circular
holes were discovered in this empty lot.
An apartment complex was slated
for construction on this lot,
but there appeared to be discord between the
developers and local residents opposed to the construction.
We've also received reports that a young
woman's scream was heard during the night.
Just who made these holes,
why, and how did they do it?
This phenomenon just keeps
becoming more and more bizarre.
That's all for now, reporting live on scene.
That was Miss Suekane, reporting
from the scene of the crime.
We have with us an expert on
digging, Professor Majima.
Digging Authority
Prof. Taichi Majima
Please share with us your expert opinion.
Certainly. I've dug countless holes
of varying types over the years,
but to dig holes of this size and in near-perfect
circles, one would require large, sophisticated machinery.
Something wrong, Hotori?
No, nothing's wrong.
If you don't hurry up and eat,
you'll be late for school again.
Finally! The day has come!
Did you watch the news this morning?
Hey, I'm asking you if you saw it or not!
Kon, you're very "orange" today.
Orange?
It means the opposite of "blue".
In that case, you've been "blue" all day.
You on your period?
No, I'm not.
You can tell I'm depressed, so how
about a little more consideration?
That's not the time for this!
You live near that lot with
the weird holes, don't you?
Where is it? C'mon, take me there.
Forget it.
What's your deal? Don't you
normally love stuff like this?
I know I do.
I always knew something like
this would happen one day.
Like waking up with horns coming
outta my head or something.
And today, something finally did!
That report convinced me that I
was meant to see that empty lot!
C'mon, show me!
Do you hate living a normal life THAT much?
I do.
Jerkface!
I don’t know what crawled up your ass,
but you could at least tell me about it.
If only to get it off your chest.
We're friends, aren't we?
Kon!
Hotori?
I can't take you to the empty lot!
'Cause I'm the one who made those holes!
Whaaat!?
You see, last night, I went to buy some
Koala Ice Cream from the convenience store.
Oh yeah, they don't sell those
at the Green Mart by my place.
Koala Ice Cream
strawberry
What flavor did you get?
Strawberry.
You idiot! Vanilla's obviously the best!
Whatever, just listen to me!
So anyway, I started back towards my house.
With that stupid doofus grin.
Just shut up and listen!
And that's when I came across
the mysterious device.
Hmm? What the heck is this?
A laser gun?
Awful heavy for a kid's toy.
There's no trigger or muzzle either.
Maybe it's a model from some movie.
Bang.
Huh!? What!?
Y-You want this?
You're saying you want me
to give this back, right?
That must be it.
Can he understand me?
Here, you can have it back! You
can even have my ice cream.
It's the most delicious food
on the entire planet, yup.
I'm not sure if you'd like it, but
please try some before it melt-
Oh crap, there's another!
Another one! A black one showed up!
Umm, w-who s-should I give it t-to?
Can one of you just take the ice cream?
No dice, huh? Guess not. Nope.
It's armed!?
Oh no, I did it again.
And so all that remained was me,
the holes, and my ice cream.
Oh, so that's what happened, huh?
You actually believe such a ridiculous story?
Yeah. Normally, I'd just
kick you good and hard.
Am I gonna be arrested
for making those holes?
What is that? A present for me or something?
Dream on.
I found it yesterday.
Looks like the same material as
that laser gun was made from.
Relax, this thing isn't dangerous.
Lemme see one of the chopsticks
you were eating with.
You mean this?
Check this out.
What the heck are you doing!?
My mom's gonna kill me!
Relax, it'll be fine.
No it won't! Please don't give
me more stuff to agonize over!
Watch this.
No way! It's fixed!
It's back to normal!
This is the reason I
believe your crazy story.
Maruko Shopping District
The very next day after I found
this, I saw that news story.
That's why I figured something
exciting was about to happen.
I've finally broken free from my boring life!
And I'm at the center of
this bizarre phenomenon!
Well, you're the one who actually
got to have all the fun.
I'm basically just tagging along.
Oh well, that's good enough for me.
I'm just glad that I can be a part of it.
Hey, the holes are being repaired!
If, perhaps, Hotori placed a tiny headstone
in the Maruko district's empty lot,
it would be in memory of the departed alien.
Now everything's good as new.
Thank you, Kon!
All's well that ends well...
This incident actually took place,
right in our very own backyard.
Whether you choose to believe
it or not is entirely up to you.
"Grandpa Smart-Ass" (From Vol. 3 Ch. 28)
That your account leger?
You sure aren't living the high life, are ya?
You've never been able to
make it work, have you?
Before the 100 yen shop, you
tried running a liquor store.
And before that, you tried selling futons.
COMBS ARE FOR PEOPLE WITH HAIR!
Ignored again... figures.
Oh, you can see me?
I'll take that as a "yes".
What happened to your tail, fella?
I don’t know where or how you
lost it, but it must've been rough.
Zenji!
Speak to me!
Please, carry on my dream...
Zenji!
A place where everyone can relax and co-
What?
Comoony.
Cocoa?
Comyunee.
Kelp?
Comyumee.
Do you mean "communicate"?
Yeah, that's it.
Am I dead?
I blew my last chance...
I couldn't remember the word,
and never got to say it.
I was a stubborn fool ‘till the very end.
Well, I don't really have any regrets.
They've come to pick me up, huh?
Huh?
Guess they weren't here for me.
Ah-
Hey, where's MY escort!?
I don't know who caused that screw-up, but for
the past 10 years I've been wandering here, all alone.
Pretty neat, huh?
I guess we've both been through a lot.
Found you!
Coban!
Why are you always running off on your own?
You're fickleness incarnate.
What are you staring at, anyway?
See ya. You hang in there, okay?
Are you following something?
Hey, you're freakin' me out!
Don't tell me you see a ghost or something!
Well excuse me for being a ghost!
Come to think of it, I do
often meet eyes with animals.
But not once have people ever noticed me.
Not even the priest notices me.
C'mon, Josephine, run!
She's hell-bent on just walking, huh?
We're not gonna walk you if you're
not getting anything out of it.
Hey there!
Guess there's animals that are oblivious too.
So? What about this girl, now?
Oh, right. She's something else, I tell ya.
How do I put it. It's almost like...
Like what?
A rock lobster!
What kind of analogy is that!?
Hey, nice timing.
You gotta work on your vocabulary.
Hey Takeru, you got the hots for her?
I do not! You always have to bring that up!
There we go...
I thought of making deep-fried tofu today.
But apparently, Hotori wolfed
it down sometime yesterday.
She's quite the handful, that girl.
No big deal. Old fashioned tofu is just fine.
The men from the shopping
district were at it again, too.
They just won't pay attention
when I tell 'em to shut up.
Why can't they just argue
at their own stores?
They can't help it. Men just never grow up.
If you were still here, I bet you'd
be in there making a fuss too.
Y'know, I think it's finally
starting to get livelier again.
Just like when you were there.
Hey, it's been ten years already.
If you keep praying that hard,
I'm gonna have to move on.
Well then, goodnight dear.
Let's see... where'd I put it?
This'll work for today, right? You
always loved bananas, didn't you?
I'm pretty sure.
I think so.
Maybe you're not praying THAT hard...
Guess you're at the age where
you start forgetting my habits.
I didn't forget a damn thing.
Ack!
You've never even bothered
to show up in my dreams.
Some husband you were.
How about right now!?
Oh well, you're probably just
goofing off on the other side.
Yup, ever since I yelled
at heaven the day I died,
I've just been doing whatever I please.
Well the communication's
only one sided, though.
Maid
Café
Seaside
Hey, cut the crap, man!
Kobuhei's my disciple!
You just don't get it, do you?
I SAID he's MY disciple!
Besides, I made up that nickname anyway!
You're screwed no matter
who you go with, huh pal?
I can't believe you were late again today.
And you yawned during class even though you
came late. No wonder the teacher got mad.
But I thought he'd let it slide
since the week just started.
Not a chance.
I know...
Dream on.
The hell he would.
Okay, I get it...
You're seriously gonna be held back.
Good evening!
There's lots of folks to
chat with up here, huh?
Hey now, you're gonna get it
from that blonde lass again.
Toshiko.
Yes, ma'am?
Would you please fix a cup of coffee
and leave it by the back booth?
You mean this one?
Yeah, thanks dear.
Uki...
You can see me?
THAT WAS FOR YOU!?
Ahhh. Good stuff.
Red King crabs aren't real crabs.
Humans pray to beings they cannot see
or whose existence they cannot prove.
If one's prayers are answered, they believe
in the existence of their guiding force.
If not, they doubt whether
their prayers were sufficient.
Either way, they still choose to believe.
Please, let Arashiyama and I
become closer this summer.
I don't mean "closer" in
an impure way, though.
But if I had to say one way or the other,
I wouldn't be against the idea,
I just wanna take it slow.
Something like that.
No wait, I don't mean like a
"just friends" type of thing-
Of course I'm totally serious-
I mean, I honestly value her feelings too-
If I just meant that in naughty
way, that'd make me a creep-
Wait, that's not the
point I'm trying to make.
Uhh, I kinda lost my train of thought,
but since you're a god,
I'm sure you understand.
Anyway, I beg of you!
The gods sure have it rough.
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!
And the Town Still Turns
Next Episode
The novel I read yesterday had
such a sad ending, it made me cry!
Has that ever happened to you, Kon?
‘Don't think so.
What about crying during soap operas?
What about movies?
Good question.
The stoic type, hmm?
I guess.
Even the "stoic" Kon cries for
her mommy sometimes, doesn't she?
Hey! What are you talking about!?
It's a secret.
Cafe Seaside
Next time: 11th Street.
"Kon's Summer of Tears".
Round 'n round, all together now.