Sleepy...
Jeez...
By the way...
you left a tissue in the pocket of
the skirt you threw in the laundry.
It made a huge mess.
Yeah, yeah...
And you've gotta remember
to separate the colors.
- Darks go in the orange basket.
- Ugh, fine! Shut up!
You're so nitpicky!
- Guys should be more...
- Big hit comin' up!
Hey, hey, hey!
Big hit comin' up!
Comin' up!
Hey!
Big hit comin' up!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't sweat it!
All right!
It's my turn now.
Fight hard, Captain!
Well, well.
I appreciate your support, comrades.
Kushieda...
Okay, hit me with your best shot!
That bright smile...
Right on!
Kushieda...
That glistening sweat...
First base, hey!
Second base, hey!
Rounding third, and then home run!
That off-key singing...
Score!
Ahh, Kushieda...
You're shining today, as well...
Those are perverted eyes, you sick mutt.
Kushieda, about the co-ed
practice this weekend...
Oh, Kitamura-kun.
I was about to...
Hey! Did you hear me, you stupid dog!?
Hey! Stop it!
Hey!
I said wait!
They're not in any club, but they still
choose to get plenty of morning exercise.
Health before all!
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Your Song
Decorating cell phones?
You're good at making
intricate stuff, Minorin.
Well, yeah.
I'm much more intricate than I look.
What is...
Kushieda doing?
Oh yeah!
That's one down!
Time for the next one!
Whoa!
Why do you sound like
you're being strangled?
Oh...
I-It's nothing...
I've got an idea!
Want me to do yours too, Takasu-kun?
Huh?
I have a "part-time job" as
a cell phone decorator.
D-Decorator...?
I'll spell out "Ryuji" using purple
Swarovski crystals.
Ryuji
LOVE
Kushieda would do that...for me?
Nah!
I-I'm...
Kushieda.
Can you do ours?
Oh, more orders!
All right. Write down your name,
desired color, and a general concept.
Well, I want pink with a
big heart-shaped stone.
Make it super lovely.
So she's a cell phone decorator
on the side...
My shining Kushieda, surrounded by
shimmering, decorated cell phones...
That's one deadly combination.
Ya-chan had to go to work early today,
so she won't be here tonight, right?
So let me have her share of—
And she said "Ryuji"...
She actually remembered my first name.
Only because I call you that all the time.
So let me have Ya-chan's share—
Man, we talked so much...!
Hey, Taiga.
I wasn't acting weird
when we were chatting...
right?
Listen when someone's talking to you!
And just so you know...
You were tripping all over your tongue!
So is dinner ready, or what?
That hurt!
Jeez, it's almost done.
We're just having rice bowls, so we're
good to go as soon as the rice is...
What!?
What's wrong?
The rice cooker's broken...
Welcome! Good evening!
Hmm, what should I get?
We didn't have to come
to a family restaurant...
We couldn't make rice,
but we still had bread.
Whine all you want for now, mongrel.
You'll bow down and thank me soon enough.
What?
A special delivery for two!
We haven't even ordered...
What!?
Don't tell a soul,
but this is the Taiga Special,
with extra-extra ice cream.
Don't let the other customers see it.
Thanks again, Minorin.
Again?
Huh? Not a fan of the
sweet stuff, Takasu-kun?
Want French fries instead?
I'll give ya extra.
Extra-extra!
N-No, I'm...
You work at a convenience store
and a karaoke club too, right?
Right!
And I started at a shabu-shabu
place last week!
That many?
I'm actually holding back!
After all, as captain of
the girls' softball team,
I can't miss any club activities!
Are you working so hard because
you want something?
I have a lot of time.
I need to toil away!
Toil...?
Yep!
Double, double, toil and trouble.
The kind of toil that invigorates you.
Anywho, you two sure are close...
Aren't ya?
Waitress! More water!
Well, take your time.
Dammit...
My eyesight definitely got worse today.
A mongrel shouldn't be drooling
over Minorin in her work uniform.
I was just...
admiring that dazzling smile of hers.
N-No! Not my eyes!
Any more and my fingers
will be contaminated.
Dammit...
But why is she working so many jobs?
Double, double, toil and
trouble, like she said.
Maybe there's a reason
she needs the money.
Something family-related, maybe?
Like she's helping out her
sick mom or something?
She said she needs to toil away.
But...
You need to stop making assumptions.
Huh?
"I'm the only one who can
truly understand her."
That crap.
It only intensifies your creepiness.
Ew, ew, ew.
Don't walk so close to me.
You're gross.
Hey!
Taiga, what's with the attitude?
You're being cruel.
I said to stay away!
And when have I not been cruel to you?
Good point...
Okay!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Inko-chan.
Time for dinner.
I'll give ya extra.
- Extra-extra!
- In—
Ink-Ink...
Oh, can you do it!?
You're gonna do it, aren't you!?
Ink-I...!
I pooped!
Maaaan...
Went out for breakfast. Food in the fridge.
- Ryu
The mornings on days off are so refreshing.
Right, Taiga?
I should never have told you...
You say something?
Skipping out on making breakfast so you
can see Minorin at the restaurant again...
The rice cooker's still busted.
What else could I do?
Shouldn't we head to an
appliance store, then?
Besides, you said you don't like bread.
I don't mind it for breakfast.
What're you so happy about, anyway?
That outfit looks horrible on you.
Uh, I forgot something...
Man, you're such a pain...
I'm begging you, let me go!
It doesn't matter what you wear!
Hey there, lad.
Aren't you Mirano-chan's son?
Oh, Mr. Inage!
Who's Mirano?
That's Yasuko's stage name.
Mirano-chan
At her job.
Bishamon Heaven Snack Bar
Hi!
Leave the station through the north
exit and it's 200 meters ahead!
I'm Bishamon Heaven's Mirano-chan.
How old do I look?
Twenty-three?
Bingo!
What a great way to start the day!
Time to cop a feel of
Mirano-chan's DNA!
Excellent. Very nice. Tight and firm.
Youth is a wonderful thing!
Let's go.
This old man's really annoying.
Hold on, you two!
If you haven't eaten breakfast,
I recommend this fish sausage.
It's chock-full of DHA and calcium!
Huh?
What?
Fish Meat
Kushieda?
Minorin?
Inage Liquor
Here, carry this.
Wh-Why...?
There you are.
One more!
Uh...
Maybe I should carry those...
You're Mirano-chan's son, so you're fine.
Have some tea or something.
Why...do I...have to do this crap!?
I ask her to help out just on the weekends.
Kushieda! Put your back into it!
Yessiree!
You got it!
Yeah!
It's been pretty busy lately.
And I'm short-handed.
Short-handed?
Oh, young lady.
If you happen to be Kushieda's friend,
would you be up for working here?
The pay's good!
Yes!
I'll work!
So will she!
I can't do this anymore!
Hey, don't start any trouble.
It'll make Kushieda look bad.
Then you should help her on your own!
Hey tiny, I need you to make a delivery!
Three of those cases of beer!
Sure thing! Right away!
Okey-dokey.
That should do it.
Be careful.
What's wrong, Taiga?
You...
You can't ride a—
Shut up!
So what if I can't ride a bike!?
I just need to deliver the goods!
That's wrong!
You're doing it wrong!
Wow Taiga, you're on fire!
That's intense...
Well, I guess it'll be safer
if she's pushing the bike.
Oh, that's right.
I need to restock the shochu.
Uh, I'll...
I'll give you a hand.
I-I mean, I'd feel guilty
if I just stood around.
All right. Thanks for your help.
N-No problem!
Um... Where's the sweet potato shochu...?
It's kind of dark, so it's hard to tell...
Yeah, we don't use this place that often.
It only gets opened up once a week or so.
Oh...
We'd be in big trouble if we got locked in.
Yep, it'd be like getting
stranded on an island.
That tiny kid must've left the door open.
Hey!
We're still inside!
SOS! SOS!
Calm yourself, Takasu-kun!
Kushieda?
It's times like these we bust
out the alma mater!
The school anthem?
Right.
This is stupid...
There's no reason for me to try so hard.
I can't take this crap anymore...
Take what anymore?
Ki-Kitamura-kun!
Wh-Why are you h-h-here?
In the middle of a workout.
I was wondering...
Is that yours?
Uh...
Oh...
Y-Yeah...
Well, I guess you could say that...
So you've learned how to ride a bike.
You've made remarkable progress.
Uh, well... I wouldn't go that far...
But how did you know
that I can't ride a bike?
Oh, I spent a lot of time
watching you last year.
Bikes are wonderful.
They open up your world.
So long, Aisaka.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Last year, he was...
D-Damn it!
Ouch...
Damn!
What's the point in opening up my world...
if Kitamura-kun isn't watching me!?
Damn it!
Hey, took you long enough.
Uh, what happened?
Nothing.
Anyway, where did they go?
Oh, good question...
Where did Kushieda run off to?
Ryuji-kun aside...
That mongrel's been slacking
while I worked my ass off!
What are you talking about?
Anyway, I need you to make
a delivery to a place on 3rd...
Ryuji!
The hell are you doing!?
Ah-ah...
A bridge to the future...
That's Ohashi, Ohashi...
My throat's totally sore.
We've been yelling at the top of our
lungs, but he hasn't heard us...
Oh, he's usually listening to the
horse races this time of day.
I see...
Boy, it's starting to get chilly.
Oh, I can lend you my—
Okay! Let's warm up!
Pitcher's gettin' scared!
Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, hey, hey! Gettin' scared!
- Gettin' scared...? But you're the pitcher...
Hey!
Pitcher's gettin' scared!
Hey, hey, hey!
- Pitcher's gettin' scared! Hey, hey, hey!
- Could it be that...
- Pitcher's gettin' scared!
- you actually are scared?
Huh?
Your hand's shaking.
P-Please...!
I'm shaking with excitement, that's all.
Here I go!
Strike!
Okay, change sides!
We switch now.
Oh.
All right.
And anyway, getting scared is pointless.
Huh?
That's why...
I'll bat my fears right outta the park!
Kushieda?
Maybe...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Couldn't we get out through there?
Where? Where!?
Where!? Where!? Where!? Where!?
WHERE!?
Look, Takasu-kun.
I hear you...!
Maybe that glow I always
see around Kushieda...
isn't because she's always
so bright and cheerful...
L-Look out!
Kushieda! I'm sorry!
You okay?
Whoa!
Y-Your nose is bleeding!
Oh, no problemo!
No problemo?
A nosebleed just means
your heart is sweating.
C'mon.
We're almost there.
Stack! Stack away, Takasu!
O-On it!
I understand...
Bat her fears out of the park, huh...?
All right! We're gonna get
out of here in one piece!
Yep! You know it!
Fight!
Y'know, I go, "Fight," and you go...
O-On?
Yep, yep! That's it!
Fight!
O-On!
Yeah...
Kushieda's always been surrounded by light...
from the moment I first saw her.
Fight!
Even now...
On!
...she continues to shine.
I. Have. Found. You.
Taiga! How did you get inside!?
Huh? I used a ladder...
Yippee!
Takasu-kun, we can get out now!
Uh, but...
Thanks, Taiga!
This is our ladder to the future!
Um, Minorin...
C'mon! Get up, Takasu-kun!
Um, listen to me!
The ladder fell down when I jumped in...
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
A memory locked up deep inside...
known only to the two
people who were there.
Oh, I told Takasu about that.
Ki-ta-mu—