Rematch time, Sora!
I'm going to put you through the same shame you've put me through,
using Jibril's game of materialization word chain!
Yeah, yeah.
I was the top student at Academy, you know.
I won't lose in knowledge.
It'll be a best of three.
She really is a loser.
That's Steph for you.
Acciente.
Acciente
I swear by the oaths
Materialization Word Chain
Round 1
Tentacles
Tentacles.
Materialization Word Chain
W-Wait, where is it touching?!
S-Stop!
It's so slimy...
Th-This is nothing...
No, not there!
Thirty seconds have passed.
My brother wins.
Materialization Word Chain
Round 2
Bubble slime
Bubble Slime.
Materialization Word Chain
Bubble slime
Species native to Disboard. Only melts clothes. Harmless.
No! My clothes are melting!
A-All my precious parts are showing!
Thirty seconds have passed.
Species native to Disboard. Only melts clothes. Harmless.
My brother wins.
Materialization Word Chain
Round 3
Beep.
Materialization Word Chain
A mysterious white liquid. Might be harmless.
Huh? What is this liquid?
Wait, the tentacles are getting back up again—
I'm not going to lose to tentacles again!
Once it gets this far, she really doesn't give off any eroticness.
All the food shown
was eaten by staff
Your level of disgrace is honourable.
But man, Flügel technology sure is impressive.
Thank you for the compliment.
Can it really materialize anything?
Yes, as long as it exists.
Hey, Jibril, can I test something without
the whole word chain thing?
Yes, I just have to tweak it.
Updating
There we go. All done.
What are you planning?
Forgive me, Sis.
There's a dream every gamer — No, every guy has.
If this really exists, I would die to see it.
I can't hold back this feeling.
Sora's hand
Now, comeforth...
A cutie who would wake me up every morning, be good at cooking,
and shrug off an accidental fondle with
"Oh, dummy":
a childhood friend!
I'm sorry, they don't exist...
There's no such perfect organism.
Still, I wanted to believe...
I-I can't go on any longer...