The Shadow That
Snuck Up Too Close
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ore no na ha Saitama
My name is Saitama
Kono yo ni habikoru aku o taosu tame
I'm here to defeat the evil that's infested this world,
Shumi de hero o yatteiru mono da
a guy who's a hero for fun.
Mainichi kakasazu hibi tanren
Everyday is the same daily training
Aircon kinshi ha kotaeta ga
along with shutting-off the A/C
Tsui ni te ni ireta kono kobushi
Finally, I've obtained at last
Attouteki chikara
overwhelming power!
Wasurecha naranu ha gomi dashi hi
Never forget when it's garbage day
Super no tokubaibi
and the supermarket's special bargain time
Aa, yasui yasui yasui yasui
Ah, discounts discounts discounts!
Konbu no kouka de kami hero
Let's use kelp as a hair-growth remedy
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
Hanashi ga nagai no ha nigate da
I hate listening to long speeches,
Nijyu-moji inai ni kanketsu
ni matomete de naoshite koi!
shorten it to 20 words or less and try again!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
One-Punch ah March
Wanpan ah ondo