The Shadow That
Snuck Up Too Close
Could she have checked my call history without asking?!
Damn it. We've lost the alien 's location.
There it is, standing in front of the spacecraft!
This is trouble!
Your mom got a call from someone
saying she was your fiancée!
No, it can't be!
And the alien's been taken out.
She contacted me too!
"Everyone in my way has been eliminated."
"I can't wait for our date tomorrow."
I never agreed to any dates!
The woman's more dangerous than the aliens!
Man... Stalkers really are scary.
Come to think of it,
I've been feeling eyes on me lately, too.
I've defeated a lot of bad guys in the past.
Maybe someone's got a grudge against me.
It's no big deal if it's just someone with a grudge.
But if that grudge or anger
turned into some kind of warped love, like in that movie,
would I be able to handle it?
This place is getting pretty messy.
It has been three days
since I started investigating the
secret of Saitama-sensei's power.
I have yet to gain any information
and time is ticking away...
Is he purposely being cautious so no one can find out?
I hope I come up with something soon.
As I suspected, he is on guard.
I must hurry.
Investigation Day 4.
He is eating out for the first time.
I see.
Perhaps the secret of his power lies in his food.
Right now we have specials on steak.
They're all very good!
Uh... I guess... just give me...
whatever's cheapest.
The 150 gram steak?
Uh, no...
This.
One side order of French fries.
Oh, that's all.
Time to start looking for a job again, huh?
Damn it.
Enjoy.
Seriously? The portion's so small.
This is ¥300?
Plus there's only one long, soft one like I like.
The rest are all short and crispy.
It sure isn't my day today...
Is that it?
Huh?
The nice long one is...
...gone!
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm missing...
a fry.
Huh?
Yeah, my fries.
The long one...
There was one that was on the longer side,
and while I was in the bathroom...
Uh...
You didn't eat it, did you?
What?
I mean, did anyone eat it?
Would you like me to call the manager?
Oh, no... it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
He makes a special trip to a chain restaurant
and orders only French fries.
No normal person would dream of such behavior.
And in that case...
There is...
a strong possibility that this is a special foodstuff
and that it holds the key to Saitama-sensei's power.
Its appearance seems normal.
Could there be a secret ingredient?
No...
No matter how I look at it, all I see is a regular French fry.
Perhaps there is no secret to his diet?
I will send the data and have it analyzed.
Who the hell ate my fry?!
And did it have to be the only long one?!
Wait...
Don't tell me I really do have...
a stalker?
Thieving bastard!
I'm so gonna kick your ass!
I'll hide right here until he comes past.
The area around here is deserted,
so I should be the only one around.
In other words,
if someone shows up at my house,
that person has got to be my stalker,
no, my French fry thief,
for sure!
No one's coming.
Sensei, what are you up to?
The same position for two hours now.
Is he engaging in some kind of visualization exercise?
Is the analysis complete?
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll head back now.
Dangit.
No one came.
What's going on?
My face...!
I'll make you all dry as dead leaves!
Better be careful.
It's been a bad day
and I'm in a bad mood.
That head...
I finally meet it again!
Huh?
You don't remember me?
Six months ago, you beat me with a single punch.
I am Men's Esthetician Man,
the wanted B-Class criminal!
The shock of being defeated by you
made my luscious skin completely dry out!
Ever since, I have kept to a strict
training and moisturizing regimen,
all the while searching for you!
So you're—
That's right,
you remember now?
As I wandered about looking for you,
I turned into a much more powerful monster!
So that's what happened.
I knew that
if I kept causing random incidents
you'd turn up again.
Everything adds up now.
It was you.
I doubt you can keep up with this smoother, softer me!
I don't remember you at all.
But it was you, wasn't it?
You're the one who stole my French fry.
You're the stalker!
Main ingredient: potato.
24 kcal.
Sugar: 1.8 grams.
Carbohydrates: 4.2 grams.
Sodium: 0.035 grams.
Protein: 0.32 grams.
Damn!
It is just a French fry!
He has a normal diet.
It is no different from an average person's.
I have not discovered a single thing.
Could Sensei be a cyborg like me?
There is only one thing left I can do.
I don't care how many times
you come back to challenge me.
But let me just say this...
Don't you ever go around stealing people's French fries again!
If you're gonna come at me, come at me straight.
If I continue being a hero,
this won't be the last time someone's
out for revenge against me.
That is my fate. It can't be helped.
I just need to change how I think.
Right! I need to think positively.
I just have to believe
there will be people in this world
who appreciate all the things
that I do.
I became a hero three years ago.
I'm not saying I need fans,
but it would be nice if someone
noticed what I've been doing...
Oh yeah, there was that guy
who wanted to be my student.
Investigation Day 5.
I have prepared myself for the worst.
Sensei!
You really showed up.
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ore no na ha Saitama
My name is Saitama
Kono yo ni habikoru aku o taosu tame
I'm here to defeat the evil that's infested this world,
Shumi de hero o yatteiru mono da
a guy who's a hero for fun.
Mainichi kakasazu hibi tanren
Everyday is the same daily training
Aircon kinshi ha kotaeta ga
along with shutting-off the A/C
Tsui ni te ni ireta kono kobushi
Finally, I've obtained at last
Attouteki chikara
overwhelming power!
Wasurecha naranu ha gomi dashi hi
Never forget when it's garbage day
Super no tokubaibi
and the supermarket's special bargain time
Aa, yasui yasui yasui yasui
Ah, discounts discounts discounts!
Konbu no kouka de kami hero
Let's use kelp as a hair-growth remedy
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
Hanashi ga nagai no ha nigate da
I hate listening to long speeches,
Nijyu-moji inai ni kanketsu
ni matomete de naoshite koi!
shorten it to 20 words or less and try again!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
One-Punch ah March
Wanpan ah ondo