Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
My dream!
Year 1, Class 1, Kamogawa Asumi.
My dream is to become a rocket driver!
That's because I've heard that the Earth is very
pretty when you look at it from space.
So I want to become a rocket
driver and go into space!
I want to take people to all
sorts of different planets!
And when they're on my rocket,
my dad and Lion-san will get special free rides!
The end!
Memory of a Distant Day
W-Why?
Why dominoes?
These have nothing to do
with being an astronaut!
Ah, it's no good. This is complete nonsense.
What's in this box?
I should've known...
Use all of the dominoes in the boxes
to make a domino line ready to be toppled
within the seven days allotted.
What? With all of these?!
You've got to be kidding me!
What are they trying to
make us do with this exam?
They want to make us line up dominoes, right?
You know...
I see...
So that's what it is.
Asumi?
Lion-san told me, right?
The most important qualities
for an astronaut to have
are perseverance and a
cooperative spirit, little one.
They must be trying to test those here.
Hey now, Asumi...
Don't tell me this thing
has gotten to you already?
That's not it, Kei-chan.
It just got a little fun for me...
What? Fun?!
Yes. Very!
Asumi, you really are a strange one.
Sorry.
No, there's no need to apologize, it's just...
You think this is going to be fun?
What is it?
What? What?
Is this some sort of emergency?
It's probably just time for
lights out, don't you think?
What? If that's all, they should say
so before turning out the lights!
Now then... Asumi, where do you wanna sleep?
I'm fine with whichever is
left after you two choose.
Well then, sorry, but could you
let me take the bottom bunk?
I'm really bad about sleeping in high places.
Ah, which one do you want?
Really, she could at least answer us.
I dunno how to put it,
but these beds are so compressed that
it's almost hard to breathe in them.
Yeah.
Hey, you know, we still haven't heard her name.
That girl...
Right...
It would be hard to ask now...
Should we just give her a nickname?
Think about it, Asumi.
Well... her hairpin is cute,
so how about Pinko-chan?
Pinko?! That's a little...
Isn't there anything else we could use?
Ukita Marika.
I won't say it again.
Right. Then, how should we address you?
Whatever. You can use my family name.
Kamogawa-san.
What did you mean when you said that there
was no way that you would be wrong?
Ah, what do you mean?
The room number.
There's no way I could be wrong.
At that time, you didn't hesitate at all.
Ah, right.
You know, all of the numbers written
on the rooms are distances to stars.
This room is the distance to my favorite star...
The distance do Spica, which
Lion-san told me long ago.
350 light years.
Ah, I found Spica!
Wow. Very well done, little one.
It's out there, 350 light years away!
That's right. Shining so beautifully that
it was also known as the "pearl star."
It's the alpha star in the constellation Virgo.
But there's a secret behind that star.
Secret?
Actually, Spica isn't just one star,
it's something called a binary star.
Binary star?
Yes, a binary star.
Two stars rotate around, chasing
each other at incredible speeds,
so if you look at it from as far away as Earth,
they look like one big star.
Anyhow, their rotation speed is so high that
the stars aren't perfectly circular,
but actually oval-shaped instead.
The twin Spicas support each other
to give birth to that radiance.
They'll continue on and on like
that until one of them disappears.
What's wrong, little one?
Was that explanation too difficult for you?
Lion-san, you...
You aren't going to disappear
and go off anywhere, right?
We'll always, always be together, right?
Yeah. I won't be going anywhere.
As long as there are stars up there, okay?
It's like I'm a princess!
Asumi...
Asumi! Asumi!
Asumi! Come on, Asumi!
It's morning, Asumi.
Good morning, Lion-san.
Lion?
What are you sleep-talking about?
Come on, stand up! Let's go wash your face!
I can walk by myself, Kei-chan!
Just come with me. One, two! One, two!
Good morning, Ukita-san.
Good morning.
She really does rub me the wrong way.
The least she could do is properly greet us!
I'm sure she's just shy.
Huh? She's just a contrary neat-freak!
Ukita-san just kind of reminds
me of someone I know.
Who?
A friend I used to play with...
Just the atmosphere about her.
Kasane-chan!
I couldn't understand how she felt,
and I ended up hurting her very badly.
We ended up going separate ways, so I don't
know what she's doing now, though.
But I think I could understand
her a little bit better now.
Not with words, but with feelings.
Also, it may just be coincidence that we
ended up together, but since we're here...
I'd rather be friends with everyone.
Kei-san, and Ukita-san both.
So, let's have breakfast and
get started on those dominoes!
Yeah!
Or so I said...
But looking at how many there are,
I can't help but feel a little depressed.
Where's the paper that had the
project procedures written on it?
Ah, I have it.
Use all of the dominoes in the boxes
to make a domino line
ready to be toppled within the seven days allotted.
You are free to line them up however you wish.
However, there should be one line
connecting the start and finish points.
Hm, within seven days, huh?
Is there something wrong with that?
I wonder what we're supposed to
do if we finish before then.
They wouldn't give us a project
that we would finish too early!
That's true, but...
Hold on, there might be
something written in here.
It's certainly true that seven days is
a long time for something like this.
So that means that there must be something
that won't let us finish in seven days?
It doesn't look like there is
anything else written about it.
Well, I guess we should just
give it a shot, anyway.
Also, it looks like we can manuallly
push that box into the wall there.
How many times does that make, Kamogawa-san?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to worry about it, Asumi.
It was because we thought that might happen
that we're lining them up separately.
Yeah...
When we're making them into one long line later,
we'll have to be more careful, though.
But really, I wish they had at least
given us some stoppers too. Really...
With this much done, it's looking more like we might
get that break that you were talking about, Asumi.
This isn't as big of a deal as I thought it would be.
Ah, this is so irritating!
Why do we have to tediously line up dominoes,
closed up in a room with just us three guys?!
I didn't come here to do these
tedious little projects!
I came here to do something bigger!
Really, you've been really obnoxious lately.
Get working on this some more, you moron.
Who's a moron, you little...
You with the monk haircut over there, moron.
What'd you say, you little...
Do you understand what will
happen if you get me mad?
I can have you all drop out alongside
me with a push of this button, okay?
W-What is it, Suzuki?
Just try it.
I won't have any mercy
beating the crap out of you.
It was just a joke, man.
Don't get all scary like that.
You shouldn't get so serious about it...
Hey, Suzuki, why did you...
You can call me Shuu, Fuchuuya-kun.
Suzuki, why did you want to get into this school?
I told you to call me Shuu...
Don't stop working, moron.
Well, everyone wants to go into space, right?
"Right?" Who are we talking about, here?
Oh? Then why did you want
to come here, Fuchuuya-kun?
I don't want to tell someone like you.
Ah, I see.
Could it be a little seagull
that's the surprising reason?
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
For me, it would have to be...
The photo that Armstrong took
of the first moon landing.
I got the feeling that I was
on the moon myself from it,
and I was pretty moved by it, even as a child.
Buzz Aldrin, standing at the
edge of a small crater...
Humanity's first step...
The pale blue Earth floating above the horizon...
With my personality, looking at it like that...
I couldn't just leave it alone.
I thought that I'd love to take my own picture
of the Earth just floating up there.
Wow...
Well, that's my motive, I guess.
How about you, Asumi?
Ah... Going to space has been a dream
of mine ever since I was little.
I wanted to become a rocket driver!
A rocket driver?
Call it a pilot, at least!
Someone else told me the same thing once!
Most people would say that...
Um, how about you, Ukita-san?
Why did you want to get into this school?
It has nothing to do with you, does it?
Could you please be quiet now?
You happen to talk a lot in your sleep, too.
You don't have to worry about that, Asumi!
I'm not bothered by a little talking in your sleep.
I guess I really do talk a lot in my sleep...
Just a little...
Really, it's nothing to worry about, though!
That's right. Compared to your nocturnal
tooth grinding, it's pretty cute, at least.
Asumi, do I grind my teeth at night?!
Ah, well...
You do it a little bit, I guess.
That's "a little bit"?
That's the first time anyone's told me that...
What a shock! I can never get married now!
I told you to be quiet already.
Ah, um...
Well...
Finally halfway done, huh?
Yeah.
I'm really sorry, that was all my fault.
No, there's no helping it.
Also, I think that they gave us seven days because
they figured that things like this would happen.
Right. Thanks.
But now that four days have passed,
this really has gotten annoying.
We don't know what the weather is like outside,
and I feel like the pilot who
asked them to put a window in.
Just what meaning is there
to doing this, anyway?
It's useless to think there's
any kind of meaning to this.
This is just an overly difficult project that they're using to
weed people out since there were so many applicants.
You really are a dry woman.
As parched as the Gobi Desert, you are.
I thought I should say something earlier,
but would you start addressing me by name?
Huh? Then what do you want me to call you?
Shall I call you Lady Marika or something?
You neat-freak!
Kei-chan!
What are you doing?!
Why don't you cool your head off a little?
You little...
How dare you do that to me?
I only called you a neat-freak!
Stop it, you two!
Say that once more, why don't you?
I won't let you off easy.
I'll say it as many times as I want,
you neat-freak neat-freak neat-freak!
You've done it now!
Please, stop it!
First off, whose fault do you think it was
that we had to do that all over?
Why? We should all be after the same dream...
I wasn't the only one to do that!
Don't group us together!
Why?
What?
The dominoes...
Mist?
Ou-Ouch!
What's wrong, Kei-chan?
My teeth...
Kamogawa-san!
My head feels so heavy...
My arms and legs are going numb...
My vision too... What is going on?
What in the world is going on?!
I feel sick... This is not normal at all!
Something must have happened...
This is an emergency.
We have to push it!
Wait a minute.
This is a test, I'm telling you.
It'll calm down in a minute.
What basis do you have for saying that?!
We're not gonna die.
Of course we won't!
I won't put up with it!
So that's what it is...
What was that just now?
It made your teeth hurt and made you feel sick...
And all of our carefully lined up
dominoes... gone in an instant.
They probably did a sudden
decompression of the room.
Sudden decompression? An accident?
This is another part of the test.
A test? This?!
The number of collisions between spaceships
and debris has been increasing each year.
So it's not unthinkable for there to be a major
accident sometime in the future anymore.
Debris?
Space garbage, like abandoned
satellites and parts.
I-I know that much at least.
If you can't keep yourself together,
even under those circumstances,
you have no business going into space.
But no matter how you look at it,
that's going a little too far!
Asumi?
Oh man, why are you shaking like that?
What's wrong, Asumi?
Asumi!
Come on, Asumi!
Hey, come on...
Asumi?
Mo... ther...
Everyone... died...
Mother...
Mother!
I remember.
A memory of a day long, long ago.
That was...
The Lion...
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
Mom...
I don't know what my late
mother's face looked like.
Family Drawings
In art class, we ended up having
to draw our family's faces,
and so I began to draw my mother's face.
After all, I met my mother in a strange
world where only dead people can go!
Next time on Twin Spica:
My Mother's Face.
My Mother's Face
End