kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
It's coming...
Phone Duty
State of Emergency Declared
Mis-sion-to con-firm-op Er-a-tion-al-sta Tus-of-di Rect-com-mu-ni
Ca-tion-line-for-high Ly-ur-gent-state Of-e-mer-gen-cy-or Ders-from-head Quar-ters?
Wh-What an incredible name.
It's an incredibly important mission!
If we fail, the whole platoon will receive something similar to a large penalty.
Depending on the situation, a Level-One Alert could be declared.
The entire Imperial Army could mobilize and descend upon us.
That's right.
It's an incredibly important responsibility.
Wh-What sort of mission is it?
Well, it is...
Phone Duty.
You know that this phone is the only hotline in the town, right?
Till now, has it ever rung?
It has not.
That's right. Something to be grateful for.
Could it be...?
Yes. While it would be bad if it rang,
it would be even worse if it didn't ring when it's needed.
That's why they do this every six months, and confirm that the communication line is still operational.
And that is called...?
M-Mission... Well...
Geez. Make sure you remember it correctly.
Mission to Confirm Direct... huh?
That's wrong. It's Mission to Confirm Operational Status of... Comm... huh?
Mission to Confirm Operational Status of Direct Communication Line
for Highly Urgent "State of Emergency" Orders From Headquarters.
Right?
Here! Here, here! Here!
Please allow me to undertake that mission!
I've always wanted to try talking on a telephone!
Is it really something to get excited about?
It's a basic procedure and similar to Takemikazuchi's intercom.
It's just that the other person is farther away.
But it's still amazing!
It's wonderful to be able to talk to someone so far away.
Well, it's true that when you talk to someone you can't see, it gives you a strange feeling.
But it's no big deal if you're used to it.
But the problem is we don't know when it will come today.
Will you still do it?
Of course!
All right. Then for today, your job is to stick by the phone.
Ring ring ring!
This is the Helvetia Army's 1121st Platoon.
Private Second Class Sorami Kanata speaking!
Then, when the call is complete, place it back on top like the way it was.
Got it.
Fi-Fili—
Aww... It's only 'cause you're so cute!
Filicia-san!
What are you doing? Acting so sultry...
The train is going to leave.
Train?
There are some documents we have to send to Command right away.
But Klaus-san isn't coming until next week.
So we're going to the station.
We're counting on you to perform the Phone Duty.
Right!
In the worst case scenario, if it goes unanswered, they might conclude we've been attacked.
Do it properly!
Leave it to me!
Hey.
Y-Yes, ma'am?!
I'm not sleeping! I'm not sleeping at all!
Have you seen Noël? She's not in her room.
U-Um...
The hangar again?
Oh well.
Well, Kanata, do you have any requests for lunch?
Ah, I-I'll do it!
Don't worry about it. It's my turn.
But...
Hey, why is it that both you and Kureha won't let me do anything when it's my turn to cook?
Before you girls arrived, there were no complaints.
You see... it's...
If it's the taste, it shouldn't be that bad.
W-Well, it's true that it doesn't taste as bad as it looks...
What?
No! The taste is very distinct! It's great!
Right?
Well then, today you can count on my cooking being even better than usual.
Hey, is anyone there?
Yes!
Senpai! It's Naomi-san.
I'm busy.
But I...
...have to stay by the phone!
Hey! I'm a guest here!
Tsk. I guess I have to.
Right! I'm coming!
I don't want to eat another cutting board sandwich.
This is...?
Drink some. It's apple cider.
It's handmade by the same farmers who sell apple juice to us.
Then this is related to our calvados?
Ah, I see. So she found out.
It's okay to give two away as refreshments, right?
Ah... that's fine.
Refreshments?
For the guildmaster of the town's commerce guild.
As thanks for his accommodating us, we've gotten in the habit of giving him a gift.
Remember that.
Right!
What's this? Those girls were trying so desperately to keep it hidden until now.
How did you find out?
Th-That is...
Well...
If there's a chance, perhaps someday...
More importantly, would you like to have lunch with us?
What? You're saying I have to attend as well?
Well, after this week's news, it seems everyone wants to hear a proper explanation from the military.
News?
The Armistice Council is having a rough time.
Is that so?
They can't decide how to split the reparations or territory borders.
It seems like all they do is drag on.
Well, it's probably only because the old men at the guild want to ogle you.
In any case, because of your role as the Flame Maiden at the Water-Dousing Festival, your fanbase has grown.
That's troubling. Good grief...
As she said, it seems that I have no choice in the matter but to go.
I'm now a maiden of the fort in both body and soul as well.
I'll show you that I can complete this mission on my own!
Understood. I'll leave it to you.
Right!
Kanata, I'll give these to you.
I'm sorry that they're just my old copies.
This is... a trumpet...
Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Thank you so much!
You and your bugle have gotten surprisingly better.
That's a reward for practicing so diligently.
And if you have that, you'll be able to go without sleep.
Um, this is... C, D, E, F, G...
A...
Summer's already over, isn't it?
Iliya?
I guess I drank too much.
Noël-chan? Are you there?
It's raining! The laundry will get soaked!
It's inside the operational area.
Ka~na~ta! Let's~play!
O-Okay!
H-Help me!
You really saved me there.
No. Keeping the laundry safe is more important than anything.
It really is... eh?
I-I'm sorry for having you help all of a sudden!
Don't worry about it.
I'm also sorry for coming over so suddenly.
Since I must return to Treize in the morning, I came to give my regards.
Th-Thank you deeply for the assistance.
There's no need to greet the oppressors.
That isn't true at all, Seiya-san.
Since this child has been disrespectful to you fine soldiers,
I thought I would come apologize on his behalf.
Where is everyone else?
Everyone has gone out.
Even Rio-san, the black-haired girl?
Yes.
Is that so? If possible, I had wanted to—
Is this book... yours?
What is it?
A trumpet book.
It's something I got from Rio-senpai.
I see. As I thought...
No, no. Forgive my rudeness.
I'm just rambling to myself.
Are you by yourself?
That's right. Um, you see...
It's the "Mission to Confirm Operational Status of...
...Direct Communication Line for Highly Urgent 'State of Emergency' Orders from Headquarters"
that I'm currently doing!
So, in other words...
You are waiting for this to ring?
Yes.
But it's my first time using it, so I'm kind of nervous.
And I kind of wonder "Can I do it right?"
Then how about practicing?
Then Yumina-san also went to the guild meeting?
Yes. We've received donations from many of the guild members.
Here. Please have a drink.
It's good!
Isn't it?
Seiya-kun, have some.
I'll drink some, but I'm not making peace with you!
What are you doing?
Do the two of you understand?
It's a phone!
Is this really one?
Yeah, it's a phone.
Since the children seem to enjoy it, we occasionally make these to show them how they work.
Now, Seiya-san.
A phone, huh?
Hello?
Cool! This is cool, Seiya-kun! I can hear you clearly!
That's wrong. You have to say "Hello" first.
It's proper phone etiquette.
H-Hello?
Hello.
This is great! It truly is!
I can hear his actual voice!
Why don't you go ahead and practice with that?
Right.
Um, this is...
Hello!
H-Hello. This is the Helvetia Army's 1121st Platoon.
Private Second Class Sorami Kanata speaking!
See? That wasn't hard.
I-I am honored to be able to take your call!
See? That wasn't hard!
And then... Well, um...
Wait, little bird!
Mishio-san!
No! Mishio-chan!
What happened?
The phone!!!
Excuse me? Are the pastor and our—
Yes?
Oh my dear Lord in Heaven...
Just what happened here?
You just came to say thanks and goodbye.
But you played around and inconvenienced others instead!
No dinner for you tonight.
Yes, ma'am.
Me too?
It's fine now. Thank you.
But your clothes are all wet now.
It's fine. I have another...
I have a good idea!
This is... so embarrassing!
That's not true at all! How eye-catching it is!
But thank you, Yumina-san.
I will definitely wash this dress and return it.
No need. I'm giving it to you.
It's too big for the children.
Plus, I don't think I'll ever find someone more suitable than you to wear it!
Sorry, Kanata. Can I still come over to play?
Sure. Seiya-kun can come again too.
I-I'll...
I-I'll come if I have time.
Well then. Please excuse us.
May the Lord bless you and your platoon.
Th-Thank you very much.
Well, time to wrap things up.
I forgot.
The bathroom...
It's coming...
Someone... hurry...
Hurry!
Those old men are so unbearable.
What the... Kana...?
Senpai... I beg of you...
Please, help me!
What's... wrong, Kanata?
Can't... anymore...
I'm about to wet myself!
Then go! You'll get sick!
Thank you very much!
She's been holding it in all this time?
Is she that sedulous, or just foolishly dutiful?
What happened?
I-I'm... all right.
Kanata!
It's... impossible. I can't move anymore!
This phone call sure has great timing.
Hello? This is the Helvetia Army's 1121st Platoon. Sergeant Major Rio Kazumiya speaking.
It's been a while, eh?
When I heard they were confirming your connection, even if this proves futile...
Are you running away?!
You're wrong! I'm not running away in the slightest!
I understand. You still haven't forgiven me.
After everything, what do you expect?
I beg you. For our country... I want you to save Helvetia.
Morning, Kanata.
Noël-chan.
Don't tell me that all along...
Ever since morning...
Yeah. I rested well in the bathroom.
No way!
We're... Oh my!
Why are you wearing such cute clothes, Kana-chan?!
Rather, what are the two of you doing in the hallway?
Kanata fell. Can't stand.
Did you hurt yourself?
Then just stand up!
You're unbelievable. Geez.
You're so spoiled.
No... Don't...
Ready, set!
No!
Let’s remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let’s move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You’re just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know you know we’ll be happy!
let’s make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you count my precious hours?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
A Passing Typhoon
Perceived and Actuality
Next time: A Passing Typhoon · Perceived and Actuality