Tsukuyomi Shrine
Daily Duty Log
kept by Mitchan
Tsukuyomi Shrine Daily Duty Log...
Kept by Mitchan.
kept by Mitchan
Master Ruza Tsukuyomi has stopped going outside
since the incident from the other day.
Now all he does is lounge about,
flipping the channel every now and then,
munching on potato chips, saying stuff like
"I don't feel like working" all day long.
According to the statistics,
the phrases Master says the most are:
"I don't want to work",
I don't want
to work
"I don't want to do my best"
I don't want
to do my best
and "I want to die."
I want
to die
He's said the phrase "I don't want to work" 132 times",
"I don't want to do my best" 1032 times
and "I want to die" too many times to count.
Ah, I want to die.
I want
to die
Countless times...
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
Deatta kouya no hana
Kowakute yasashikute
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 8                                              Ganbaranai
"STRATEGIC SOLITUDE"
I haven't gone hikikomori,
but I'm barricading myself in.
THE ONE WHO TRIES
TO ENTER MY ROOM
SHALL BE CURSED
SASAMI TSUKUYOMI
I'm not going to let anyone enter this room.
That's reckless, Lady Sasami!
The Yagami sisters are extremely powerful gods!
There's a high possibility that they'll break in!
Don't panic, Rookie.
It's a do-or-die situation for me this time.
I'm going to exert all the power of God
that I've kept suppressed all this time
and stop them from coming in!
It's about time!
This spring break, I'm NOT going to do my best!
I'm going to cuddle in my blanket and be lazy all day!
And I won't let nobody stop me!
Sasami! Sasami!
I will not do my best no matter what!
Whoa, he's dead.
Are you okay, Papa-lin?
I haven't talked to Sasami for 34 hours...
I haven't touched Sasami for 76 hours...
I haven't taken a bath with Sasami for 127 hours...
Please get a hold of yourself.
Sasami?
Sasami... Sasami!
Sasami! I missed you so much!
Oh, Sasami's scent, Sasami's body heat,
the texture of Sasami's skin.
I adore you, Sasami! I love you!
Y-you idiot...
Yawn...
We've got two issues right now.
The first issue is that my sister has gone down
to the Underworld and hasn't returned yet.
The second issue is this
unknown fortress set up by Sasami.
Take a look at this.
That's the residence of Mr. Kamiomi and Sasami.
This black thing is "Ama-no-Iwato",
the "Cave of the Sun Goddess Amaterasu".
It is the materialization of Amaterasu's feelings
such as not wanting to see anything,
not wanting to see anyone
and not wanting to get involved.
The ultimate barrier that emerges when you
absolutely want to avoid contact with the outside world.
That's a big problem!
So it took you less time to comprehend it, Tama?
Y-yeah!
As always she's not getting it.
At this rate the world is going to look like it was
abandoned by the Supreme God.
That would trigger many unwanted Alterations,
which would most likely create chaos.
This heavy snow must be one of the signs.
We're going to break through Ama-no-Iwato
somehow and check on Sasami.
Hang on to me, everyone.
Now we're off.
Here we go!
This doesn't look good!
Warning!
Sasami!
I will attack you if you get any closer!
Just leave me alone!
I don't want to be away from you even for a second!
I'm going to die unless I inhale your breath
and take in your fluids like your sweat and tears!
Shut up, perv!
Sasami, you need to stop sealing yourself away
and unlock the Ama-no-Iwato!
Just leave me alone!
It's not like I'm doing this because I want to!
Tell me... are you dealing with
an enormous issue right now?
An issue so enormous that it makes you
want to reject the whole world!
Don't treat us like strangers.
If something's bothering you, feel free to come talk to us.
We will help you out.
But that's an unwanted favor this time around!
Just get out of here or I'll attack you!
Fine! Now we'll force our way in and
make you regret giving us that brash attitude!
I'm going to spank your butt
and make you plead for forgiveness in tears!
And we'll still save you from
whatever issue you've been dealing with.
Just forget it and go home!
Who're you talking to, you trigger-happy fool?!
Don't tell me you're going to melt my clothes?
What are you thinking?!
No!
If you don't give up and go home,
I'm going to take off all your clothes,
share that image all over the internet
and start promoting you as
"Unknown Flying Nude Model Excellent Kagami"!
You're heartless!
That's cruel, Mama-lin! Stop teasing Big Sister Kagami!
Please, I beg of you... Take my clothes off, not hers!
Don't take them off!
I took mine off already!
Get out of here, you perv!
I'm going to bring all the powers in the world
and make Excellent Kagami a worldwide idol sensation!
Exclusive interview!
Returns from L.A. after one-month stay
NOT RETIRED
Kagami returns
Note: a now-iconic image from Miyazaki's The Wind Rises (2013), which would
not play in theaters for another four months after this episode aired
The movies! The social phenomenon! The legend!
If you don't like that, go home!
That's awful, Sasami! I thought you were my friend!
Forgive me, Kagami!
Thank you for waiting!
Big Sister Tsurugi!
It's difficult to dispel an attack blessed
with the Power of God using only an Alteration,
but that's a whole different story with THIS sword!
Divine Sword Ame no Murakumo!
Big Sister, how?
I've returned from the Underworld, using this as a lifeline!
Normally it's difficult for gods
to break through the Ama-no-Iwato,
but New Gods can take that impact.
Tama, drill a hole into Ama-no-Iwato!
Okay, Big Sister Tsurugi!
Kagami, get us close to the Ama-no-Iwato!
Got it!
Cut it down! Ame no Murakumo!
Thank you for the food!
They broke through!
We're coming in!
Now explain what's going on, Sasami.
I won't forgive you depending on your answer.
You don't need to corner her like that.
I'm sure Sasami has a good reason for it.
Hey, show it to them.
Umm...
I didn't know what to do!
The pizza I ate yesterday was so good,
but I looked like this when I woke up in the morning!
I tried to Alter it, but that didn't help.
I thought everyone would hate me and
even my Big Brother would abandon me.
I just couldn't talk to anyone about it.
I wanted to gather my thoughts!
But you guys totally ignored the situation
and came to see me!
You morons!
Get out! Just get out of here!
I-I understand how you feel, but we're friends, aren't we?
You should've come and talked to me.
Kagami...
No matter how much you eat,
that shouldn't happen overnight.
There's a possibility it's some type of
unknown change or disease.
I'll explain it to you.
The cause is that Tsukuyomi priestess.
What?
There are some things I need to take care of.
You're going to help me out, Sasami.
W-what's going on?
Are they the people of the Tsukuyomi Shrine?
What's wrong, Juju Tsukuyomi?
Why don't you show that power of yours?
The one known to be the most powerful in history?
What?
Don't think I'm just some puppet
that's inherited the Power of God.
What?
Don't think I'm just some puppet
that's inherited the Power of God.
What?!
Don't think I'm just some puppet
that's inherited the Power of God.
Is that... me?
What? What's going on?
Where are Tsurugi and the others?
This is... I'm Mom?
Am I in the past?
Juju Tsukuyomi.
I, Baron Samedi, the lazy gravekeeper,
will turn this place into your grave.
Get her, my zombies!
A living corpse is a dead person.
A dead person belongs to...
Is this...
Chikaeshi no Juhou?
Chikaeshi no Ookami is the enormous rock
that had been placed to seal Izanami away
after she tried to come back from the dead.
It is most effective on the dead!
O god of strange lands!
Repent your sin and get out of this country!
What a bother.
Unbelievable...
But why did Tsurugi send me back to the past?
What is it that she has to take care of?
Lady Juju!
Where are you?
Is that Mitchan?
Hey, Lady Juju!
Lady Juju!
Achoo!
Mitchan!
That was scary! I thought I was going to die!
You normally should've.
I'm sorry, Lady Juju.
They may be degraded, but monsters are still gods.
You must pay close attention in handling them.
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
Tsukuyomi Shrine is still intact.
So that does mean that this is... the world of the past.
By the way Mitchan, you came
all the way to come see me.
What brought you here?
Yes, Lady Juju, actually Lady Sasami is...!
What?
Me?
This way, Lady Juju!
Sasami always collapses, so it's not that unusual.
She's been sneaking out of the shrine
to go to town lately.
She must've caught some strange illness or something.
Actually, no doctor or priestess
has been able to make her better.
If this is some kind of curse,
it could be dangerous to mundanes
like yourself, so stay away.
Okay. Please be careful, too, Lady Juju.
Mom...
Did I wake you up?
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's all right. I'm a Tsukuyomi priestess,
but also your mother.
Just go to sleep.
Hurry and grow up, Sasami.
That's the only thing you could do.
By the time you become an adult,
things should be better.
I'm sorry for giving you trouble...
I'm sorry that I'm weak.
Don't apologize.
Being weak is not a sin.
I'm foolish for not being able to
change a world that harms you.
I'm not going to apologize about it,
but instead I'll do my best.
Mom!
I wonder which will come first...
Sasami becoming an adult or me dying.
Mom, back then you were already...
That's...!
Big Brother...
Stop sneaking around.
You're a strange one.
I know you're harmless,
but if you ever bring us misfortune,
I'll personally destroy you.
I don't pity you or feel sorry for you.
I just hope that you'll be saved one day.
I'm satisfied with my status in life.
I see, then I'm not going to say anything.
Well, I'm going back to take care of Sasami now.
Does his emergence mean that
Sasami has been chosen?
What?
I'm hungry...
I didn't know that was you.
Negative. A Tsukuyomi priestess
has no need for personal desire.
I abstain from any desire and
always keep my mind and body clean-
Mitchan.
Wh-wh-what can I do for you, Lady Juju?
There there, relax.
Do you have anything to eat?
The dinner for the night shift workers
will be ready soon, so wait just a little.
Oh yeah! Why don't we make some rice porridge
for Sasami as a night snack?
Sure. Easy to digest food
might be best for Sasami right now.
Mom...
Right, Mitchan! You make it!
No!
YOU make it for her, Lady Juju.
I can't cook.
I'll show you how.
Sasami is a mama's baby. I'm sure she'll
be happy if you make it for her.
Although I can't guarantee that; I'm not familiar
with the parent-child relationship.
Because you were spirited away.
"Spirited away"?
An evil god spotted you, who were born
with high psychic powers, and kidnapped you.
Then he sucked all the power out of you.
He sucked everything including the memories
of your own name and your parents.
That's why I truly understand someone like Sasami,
who's in the same situation as me.
"Same situation"?
Everyone around me is better than me, so I'm worried,
but I'm determined to do my best.
So I understand how anyone would
put pressure on themselves in that situation.
It would be nice if I had my own family
to help me cope at a time like that, but...
Purifying, organizing and stabilizing Hell
as much as possible
before I have to send my own daughter there one day.
That is the only gift that I could give her.
Actually... That's been my excuse for avoiding her,
though she's been genuinely trying to be close to me.
However, I'm a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I just can't be an ordinary woman or her mother.
Mom...
What am I supposed to do?
Lady Juju...
Mom, you were always thinking about me.
Always doing your best, trying as much as possible
to make the world a better place
because you knew that one day I would take over
and become a Tsukuyomi priestess,
but I betrayed you...
Stand back, Lady Juju!
What?
Mitchan!
Why you...!
Is that me?
Let my daughter go!
That's not going to happen!
Help is not coming... I ordered people to stay away.
I know this shrine is being protected
by a powerful barrier!
Where did you come in from?
While Baron Samedi was distracting you,
this girl was out roaming around in the town,
so I entered her then.
No way... So this is my fault?
No, wait! I don't remember an incident like this!
This is not my past!
After I entered her,
I successfully infiltrated this place
without being detected by anyone.
No one in the actual future history
knew anything about me, either.
"Actual future history"? What are you talking about?
Oh, I'm not talking to you.
I know you're there, Sasami Tsukuyomi!
What? How...?
M-me?
I'm here to make a deal with you.
What's going on?
I'm an assassin sent by Arahabaki,
the evil occult society.
I'm the spirit that haunts this Killing Stone Golem,
Note: the cursed Killing Stone formed out of the corpse of the legendary nine-tailed
fox after she was hunted down for crimes committed against the Emperor
the golden furred, white faced nine-tailed fox,
Kyuubi no Kitsune!
Kyuubi no Kitsune?
Also known as Tamamo-no-Mae!
She who toys with the balance of this country!
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey, have you ever wished that
you could change the past?
Sasami, it's time for the ending theme!
Don't you lock yourself in! Just come on out!
No matter how fat you are I still love you so much!
Actually I want to be enveloped in that flesh!
I want to die being crushed under your weight!
Yawn... Please calm down, Mr. Tsukuyomi.
Since this episode was something
about the Ama-no-Iwato cave,
so it may be a good idea to lure Sasami
out of there based on that myth.
Note: in the myth, Sun Goddess Amaterasu hid herself in a cave,
sulking over the latest outrages of her brother, Susanoo.
I understood that perfectly!
Note: she was lured out by the raucous partying of the other gods outside,
spurred on by the bawdy and comical dance of the goddess Ama-no-Uzume.
What should we do?
I'm not even going to ask you.
Well, basically you just have to make
a lot of fun noises around the bed.
If you do that, Sasami might get curious
and come out of the blanket.
Understood! Now let's sing together!
You in front of the TV sing with us, too!
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomademo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
Oh? Mama-lin isn't coming out at all!
Don't tell me she's sleeping in there!
Sasami! How could you fall asleep
while you're on the air?
Now I realize that my sister is sleeping too.
I wonder what kind of dream she's having.
She said something about a nine-tailed fox in her sleep.
Fox? Yip! Yip!
Yawn... Now I'm getting sleepy...
Next Episode
Preview
It's time for Ganbaranai Shopping.
Ganbaranai
@Shopping
Ganbaranai@Shopping
Today's item is this: Ganbaranai vacuum EX.
Ganbaranai Vacuum EX
Ganbaranai@Shopping
Do you want to know what makes this vacuum
so "ganbaranai" (unenthusiastic)?
When you push the retract button of the cord,
it stops right in the middle
without going back all the way in,
therefore the cord would be out halfway
and it's quite annoying.
It's recommended that you use it
when you want to be irritated.
Next time
Episode 9
Next time, Episode 9:
"It's Not That I Can't Do It"
"It's Not
That I Can't
Do It"