On a night illuminated by countless
stars and a fleeting crescent moon...
"Fumizuki Academy"
I was being pressured by the
slightly emboldened girls in my class.
Aki... Can we do it?
Akihisa... I'm begging you. Can we do it?
I can't... do that.
Why not?
You don't... want to?
I couldn't do that.
If you won't, we'll do it with Tsuchiya instead.
Is that okay, Aki?
Yeah... that's fine.
So he said! So Tsuchiya,
how about we do one more?
This is ishi-daki, also
known as soroban-zeme,
a form of torture used in the Edo era.
I will not permit an affair.
Akihisa, you too, please.
The girls are... kinda bold tonight.
Hi!! Mondai: hitori to
futari docchi ga suteki?
Colorful mawari dasu watashi no shourai
Doko made hanasou ka? Minai furi?
Assou, ookina sekai
wa kibun de hirogaru
Kyou mo daisuki, hontou ni daisuki
Watashi no baka...
Hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
Sunao ni narezu ni,
kimi to aruku yume o mita
Gomen ne... Datte!
Koi to shiranakattanda
Kotaette kimi to nazo tasu
watashi wa mugen no JUMP!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
Turning back the clock, that morning
was a little different from usual.
It was the day before
their academic training camp.
On that day, Akihisa Yoshii received a letter.
In the letter, there was a
message that gave him a small shock.
"I'm holding your secret."
Why the heck did
I receive something like this?
What's the matter, Akihisa?
You're in low spirits this morning.
N... Nothing's wrong!
You're acting strange, Aki.
What'd you hide just now?
What're you talking about,
Minami? I'm not hiding anything.
Hmm... You received a
love letter... or something?
Watch what you're saying, Minami.
Look at these guys. They're bloodthirsty now.
I guess not, huh? There's no
way you'd get a love letter, right?
That's not true! This morning, too,
there were several letters in my...
I won't miss next time.
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
Then give me an honest answer!
T-To tell you the truth, what I hid was a bla--
When you receive a blackmail note,
you aren't supposed to tell anyone, right?
On TV, too, the bad guys say that a lot...
Bla-what?
Bla... Bla...
When we humans have
our backs against the wall,
we replay memories from our past.
This is called a kaleidoscope of memories.
A Bla... Bla... Black competitive
swimwear society invitation...
That's what I was hiding.
Huh?
Akihisa watched the documentary,
"Competitive Swimmer,
24-hour close-up" the night before.
Are you going to join them?
S-Sure... since I've been
interested in them for a while.
I see...
Oh no... I'm reaching the point of no return.
What do you find so interesting
about competitive swimwear?
Huh?
The most impressive thing was...
I-Its tight fit...
That sounds like a perv!
Shimada... Everything he just said was a lie.
What? It sounded so real
that I was almost fooled!
"Crack, crack, crack..."
This time, you'd better spit
out the truth! What did you hide?!
To tell you the truth,
I received a blackmail note.
Oh, good.
So, what did the blackmail note say?
Yeah...
"Don't get any closer to
the girls around you," it says.
Hmm... From how it sounds,
this is probably out of jealousy.
There are only two girls in
this class, Himeji and Hideyoshi.
So in other words, it's from
someone who likes one of them, huh?
Akihisa... Shimada went to get a metal bat.
Was my guess wrong?
So what are you being blackmailed about?
Come to think of it, I'm not really sure.
"If you refuse to heed my warning,
I'll release these pictures."
Those are the ones from
the last school festival, huh?
Wh-When did they...
They wouldn't have
anything crazier than this, right?
It's trunks, so it's okay. It's trunks,
so it's okay. It's trunks, so it's okay.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Well, these kinds of pictures are still okay.
Hm?
Nooooooooo!
Don't look at it! Don't look
at this shameful picture of me!
I don't know what's going on,
but calm down, Akihisa.
What a frightening power... What are
they engineering such a dirty plot for?
You're imagining things.
Anyone would wear a maid
costume at least once in their lifetime.
Good morning, Akihisa, Kinoshita.
Ah, Himeji.
Good timing. Let's have Himeji prove
that these pictures aren't something
you should get worked up over.
What's the matter?
Himeji, what if there's a picture in
which Akihisa is in a maid costume?
Well, I'll buy a scanner first.
Huh?
Otherwise I won't be able to disseminate
Akihisa's charm to the world via the web, right?
Calm down, Akihisa!
Let go of me! I don't think I can go on living!
How about asking Muttsulini for advice?
Oh yeah... Nice advice, Hideyoshi.
I'd expect nothing less from my wife!
Isn't that supposed to be "husband"?
I think both are wrong.
Oh shoot...
Oh, there you are, Muttsulini!
I'd like to ask you for advice.
Come back later. I'm first in line.
Hm? You're asking for advice?
Seems like Yuuji's wedding is coming up soon.
That's something that's already been
decided, right? I'm in bigger trouble!
As it stands, people will think that
I'm a perv who likes to dress like a girl!
You being a perv is already a fact, right?!
Shut up, you married man!
Go back to the graveyard of life!
Shut up, you super perv!
Go to your maid café job already!
If you were gonna get hurt, both of
you should've kept your mouth shut.
In any case, I confiscated this from Shouko!
If I win the tournament, I'm gonna
propose to you. I love you, Shouko!
What?
These are the words that
Akihisa and Hideyoshi fabricated
on the second day of the
Fumizuki Academy's school festival.
Kirishima is cute, isn't she?
To think that she wanted to
record those words for her memory...
No, looks like she's going to play it
for her dad as proof of our engagement.
It's hard to think that she recorded
it herself when she's bad with machines.
There's gotta be a another perpetrator.
What did you want to talk to me about, Akihisa?
To tell you the truth, an underwear
picture of me in a maid costume
is about to be disseminated
to the world via the web.
What happened?
Sorry, I skipped over too many
details. In sum, blah-blah-blah-blah...
I see... So, where's the picture?
This is the one.
This is...!
What's the matter, Muttsulini?!
It's taken from a better angle than mine...
Ahhh! There's an
unexpected enemy in my midst!
Don't worry. I don't
distribute the pictures for free!
So you distribute them?!
You distribute them for money?!
I see... You're in the same
boat as I am, huh, Akihisa?
Victims of blackmail. In addition,
wiretapping and sneaked photos.
Muttsulini, can I ask you to investigate?
As a reward, I'll bring some
dirty magazines that you might...
I'll take care of it.
I'll give you the treasure
collection 2 that I obtained recently.
I'll definitely take care of it.
So that's about it for
academic training camp.
So our training camp will be
held in Uzuki Highlands, huh?
That's a trendy summer resort.
Whoa! I'm really looking forward to it!
Make sure you go to the right meeting
place, since it differs from class to class.
Class A will go by a limousine
bus or something anyway, right?
I wonder if we, Class F,
are going by a small microbus...
Kiddie seats or straps...
No, maybe even the trunk or a bike rack...
Class F will meet on site.
We don't even get transportation?!
This is an unequal society.
There's nothing to do.
I'm bored.
Hm? What're you reading, Minami?
A psychological test book.
Oh? That sounds interesting.
Ask me questions.
--Okay. Well then...
--Super excited. Super excited.
Among the opposite sex, who do
you associate with following colors?
1: green, 2: orange, and 3: blue.
Green, orange and blue, huh?
Let's see... Orange is Hideyoshi, blue
is Himeji and green is Minami... I guess.
Could you explain why
Mizuki is blue and I'm green?
Huh?
If I say I saw her wearing
green underwear before,
she'd get upset, right?
I won't get upset, so tell the truth.
Because you were wearing
green underwear before.
Sakamoto, open the window.
Okay.
Are you gonna ditch me? Are you
gonna ditch me from the window?!
Let's see... Green is your friend,
orange is your energy source, and blue is...
Ahh, no! Give that back to me!
Akihisa, she said "among the
opposite sex," so who's orange?
You, Hideyoshi.
I'm at a loss since
I'm kinda happy to hear that.
Then, Minami, what does it mean
when you pick someone for blue?
Question 2!
Looks like she doesn't wanna answer.
From 1 through 10, say the
two numbers you think of in order.
5 and 6.
In my case, 2 and 7.
1 and 4 for me, I think.
3 and 9 for me.
"Akihisa" "Hideyoshi" "Mizuki" "Yuuji"
The first number indicates how you normally show yourself to others.
Sakamoto's 5 indicates cool and cynical.
Kinoshita's 2 indicates a
calm, commonsense person.
Aki's 1 indicates... you should die.
Mizuki's 3 indicates gentle and careful.
Hey, didn't you just hurl an insult at me?
"Yuuji" "Hideyoshi" "Akihisa" "Mizuki"
The next number indicates your true self that you don't show much.
Sakamoto's 6 indicates fairness and kindness.
Kinoshita's 7 indicates strong feminine charms.
Aki's 4 indicates... you should die tragically.
Mizuki's 9 indicates strong will.
Hasn't your insult towards me escalated?
Looks like he's up.
Good morning, Muttsulini.
I was awoken by hunger.
It's about time, too.
Shall we have lunch now?
Actually, I made lunch, so if you like...
Whoosh!
S-Sorry, I made my lunch myself, too.
Sorry, I brought mine, too.
I've already finished making mine.
So, Himeji, let Akihisa have it.
Actually, I brought sandwiches, too.
"Chomp"
Sorry, Akihisa. My hand slipped.
Be careful, Yuuji.
Oops! My hand, too...
I'll hold your hand tight so that it won't slip.
Geez, why are you guys acting
so silly? I guess it can't be helped.
Aki, would you like to have some of these?
Yaay! They look delicious!
Y-You can eat as much as you like.
Thank you!
Listen, Aki... I have to gather
my courage to tell you this, but...
...If you pick wrong, you'll get...
...one with lots of hot mustard.
Are you an idiot?!
Ahhh! It's hot, hot, hot!
Akihisa, you might've gotten lucky in a sense.
I see!
It might be okay now since my taste
buds have been completely destroyed...
Akihisa, please have mine, too.
Yep! Thank you!
300 joules, clear!
Wh-What on earth...
When you started deliriously
repenting your sins from your former life,
I thought you were a goner.
Where am I?
The inn for the training camp. While you
were hovering between life and death,
we arrived here.
And this is the room
assigned to the four of us.
Well... now that Akihisa has
woken up, let's start, shall we?
Start what?
The operation to find your
photographer and my wiretapper.
I've managed to dig up some intel.
Really, Muttsulini?!
I found traces of the devices
I believe were used by the culprit.
Even based solely on his MO
and the kind of devices used,
you can conclude that both crimes
were committed by the same person.
So who's the culprit?
Sorry...
Yeah... I guess you wouldn't be
able to figure it out that quick, huh?
All I could figure out was that
the culprit is a female student
who has a burn mark on her butt.
What on earth did you investigate?
I set up a small camera
within the school premises.
Then something like this was...
This is...!
This video is from
inside the girls' locker room.
What's this censorship?
If you wanna see it, you have to pay.
We're friends, right?
Hm? Could this be... Shouko?!
That cell is Shouko's!
You're right. I'll blow it up.
Let's see...
"Order form: I'd like to have
another 'Yuuji's marriage proposal.'"
Send...
That darn Shouko!
Looks like she got a reply.
"Thanks for your order. I'll give you a
discount since this is your second order.
The training camp starts tomorrow
so I'll give it to you next Monday."
That was close! I was
saved by the training camp!
There are many others, too.
What the heck are these?!
I can no longer get married!
With this, it's confirmed
that it's the same culprit, huh?
Here is the important scene.
She's writing back.
"All your pictures are wonderful.
But it'll be a problem if they find out."
"Mail sent"
The person wrote back already!
"Just between you and me,
my mother found out the other day.
I received a moxa treatment
on my butt as punishment.
Because of that, I still
have the mark from the burn.
Don't you think it's cruel to
treat a young lady like that?"
So this is all we have.
I see... By "young lady," it has to
be a female student or Hideyoshi.
A girl with a burn mark on her butt, huh?
But flipping up their skirts isn't gonna...
Even if we use an infrared camera,
we can't see the burn mark.
Oh yeah! It's almost bathing time,
so we can have Hideyoshi go and check!
Why are you making plans
assuming that I bathe with girls?
Akihisa, read the training camp guidebook.
Hm?
The bathing time for each class is...
Ahh!
They've got a Hideyoshi
bathing room in a place like this, too!
Why just me?
Don't move!
All of you, put your hands
behind your heads and lie down!
Wh-What the...
We said, put your hands
on your heads and lie down.
Kinoshita, come this way quickly.
Wh-What?!
What the hell is the meaning of this?
We know you guys are the culprits.
Culprits?
We're talking about these.
They were set up in the girls' changing room.
That's... a hidden camera!
Who on earth would do such a thing?!
Who else are you saying
would do it besides you guys?
That's not true! Things like
peeking or setting up a hidden camera...
Things like that...
I can't say they wouldn't.
Whaaaaaat?!
Is that true, Akihisa?!
There's no way that
Akihisa and the others would...
It's not true, right, Aki? I believe in you.
Wh-Why... do you have torture
equipment when you believe in me?
How cruel, Akihisa!
To think that, of all times, you picked
right after I ate a lot for dinner to peek...
I-I'm normally more slender, okay?!
That's what you're upset about?!
M-Me, too! My breasts are normally bigger!
No, that's a lie.
Girls! Get them!
Shoot! What I really thought just slipped out!
Yuuji! Let's somehow...
I will not permit... an affair.
No... it's too late for him. Ugh! Me, too!
We'll...
...teach you a lesson but good.
Ahhhhhhhhh!
What a terrible false accusation that was...
though I don't understand
why I was treated as a victim.
Really, that was a terrible misunderstanding...
...and we hadn't even peeked yet.
Even though they didn't find my camera...
Those replies, I think, are just barely true.
If that's their attitude, fine!
What're you talking about, Yuuji?
They already made me do the time,
so I might as well commit the crime!
Do it...? Don't tell me...
Yeah! I'm really gonna
peek on the girls bathing!
If you want to see Kirishima naked,
you might just wanna ask her.
D-Don't be ridiculous! I'm not
interested in Shouko's naked body!
Are you trying to find the culprit
with a burn mark on her butt?
That's right. I originally thought
that peeking was crossing the line,
but if they have that kind of
attitude, we don't have to hesitate!
I'll peek to my heart's
content and find the culprit!
That video camera and microphone...
They're the same ones the blackmailer used.
What?!
Does that mean that the
one blackmailing Yuuji and me,
and the peeping Tom from
earlier are the same person?
Now there's no reason to hesitate!
All right, let's go!
"Women's Bathing Room"
Bathing time ends in 30 minutes.
The girls' bathing room is ahead of here.
We don't have much time left.
Let's bust right in there!
Stop.
Where do you think you're going?
That's the chemistry teacher, Mr. Fuse!
Don't mind him! Knock him down!
You should mind me.
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
That's...
...an Avatar...!
Just like probationary students'
Avatars, Teachers' Avatars are
capable of physical interference.
Now that it's come to this, let's
crush Mr. Fuse along with his Avatar!
We'll leave it to you, Yuuji!
Hold on a sec. Just in case,
let me hear your chemistry test score.
With one more point, my
chemistry test score the other day...
With just one more point...?
...would've reached 2 digits.
Go on ahead, you idiot!
It'll probably be tough to fight
alone against a teacher. I'll help you.
Thanks, Hideyoshi.
Summon!
Okay, Muttsulini! Let's go on
ahead and... Huh? He's already gone!
Stop right there.
The health and physical
ed. teacher, Mr. Ooshima...!
Give it up, Tsuchiya!
Mr. Ooshima... this isn't peeking!
Then, what is it?!
Health and physical ed. practical training.
Summon!
Go, Akihisa! I'll take this one.
Muttsulini... Okay.
Guys...! You can do it!
Without fail, I'll... I'll...!
I-Iron Man!
Seriously... You guys are quite a trouble.
I can't afford to lose today!
Summon!
Huh? Where's your Avatar, Mr. Nishimura?
For various reasons, I have no score.
I see... Then, with my everyday grudge...
...die, Iron Man!
Wha...
Yoshii...
Do you know why I don't revoke
your summoning permission?
Huh?
I'm glad that you're a probationary student.
If it's an Avatar, it won't be
considered corporal punishment if I beat it.
Clench your teeth!
The impertinent one will take a remedial class!
The three of you there, too.
Thus, the first day of the
training camp came to an end.
But the false accusations on Akihisa
and the others haven't been cleared yet.
How will this end? Will they
find the blackmailer? Da-dum!
Hirameite, kagayaite, denkyuu pikkanko
Shinten shinai yo.
Dareka jama shiteru... No, no!
Zenzen tarinai, sore
ga mondai no koubaisuu
Ryoukai sorenai. Nani ga
hontou no koto... Baby?
Mitetara koko de zukai shite yo, Baby!
Kotoba mo kazu mo kimi o arawasenai
Kokoro ga biribiri
suru S to N no jiryoku de
(S, S, Super kuttsuite
Number, I say No. 1 boy!)
Omedetou! Imakara kimi
wa My, ma-my "otakara"
Tokubetsu nanda, dou nattemo
Gyutto ne gyutto ne hanasanai
Watashi wa koi shitai.
Yume ni genkai wa iranai
Tokubetsu dayo ne, acchatta mon
Konna watashi mo yurushichae
Hirameita, kagayaita, seikai pittanko
Idiot Test!
"Women's Bathing Room"
Ahh... the bath felt good.
The large bath feels good, doesn't it?
Question 6.
"Things repeat over time."
Provide a proverb with this meaning.
Transmigration of the soul.
Are you going to be in
Class F in your next life?
Next episode!
"Me, Peeking, and Guys' Friendship!"
This will be on the test.
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi
Please join us again next week!"