Are you gonna do this all day?
I really thought I was gonna die, you know!
It started blowing hot air at me all of a sudden.
It's broken...
It was so hot I couldn't sleep all night...
Well don't go compensating for it now.
Yeah, we have a song to polish before the festival.
What do you mean?
I think it's great.
You mean it?
What do you dislike about it?
Umm, how do I put it...
Sounds a bit too mainstream, I guess.
Tomo-chan, what do you think?
That's it, I've had it with your nitpicking. I'm out.
Same here..
It's fine, isn't it?
A CRESCENT MOON CAME OUT
Why didn’t you say anything?
You told me before something was bothering you about that new song.
No reason.
I thought it was fine.
I see. That's good then.
Still not eating, huh.
You're gonna die at this rate.
Who could that be?
The neighborhood notice?
TL Note: In Japan, sometimes neighborhoods have a bulletin/notice that circulates between residents, usually through the mailbox.
Ah right, our mailbox is damaged. Could you get that?
Yes?
- Good evening, it's Nina!
- Sorry, we're not interested.
Wait, I haven't even said anything yet!
The hell do you want?
Aah, it's so cool here...
Stop sucking in our cold air!
Eh, it's not like you'll run out.
Keep your voice down you public nuisance!
You’re way louder than me!
Stop ringing it!
I'm in heaven.
Cool off and leave, will ya?
Come on, don't be so cruel...
The AC guy said he'll only come next week.
And how is that my problem?
Does Momoka-san have one?
She does, but she works at night.
By the way, I've been thinking...
isn't yours a bit too weak?
DON'T TOUCH
See, now this feels good.
Much better than your old piece of junk.
It wasn't a piece of junk!
You can't even turn it up, what else do you call that?
It literally said "DO NOT TOUCH".
So as you can see,
both our ACs are out of commission at the moment.
So if you don’t mind, we’d be grateful
if you'd let us cool off for a bit.
Just for a tiny little hour, please!
It’s all this thing's fault, just for the record.
Okay, fine. But just one ho-
OOOOOOOOOUUUUURR?!
He's Tomo-chan's pet.
Apparently he really can't stand the heat.
Don’t just let him out like that!
Powerful.
You’re annoying.
This is one impressive apartment.
Yeah, it's real nice.
It's from Momoka-san.
She said she'll stop by since she works around here.
Got it.
Momoka-san, the other three
barged in here since their ACs broke. Want to come too?
I work close to the Shinagawa
Prince Hotel, I'll be done in 30 minutes and head over there.
Really?
Might as well eat here together then, shall we?
SOUNDS GOOD.
And when did I agree to that?
I remember you saying something about one hour.
Here, just take the- oh.
Oops, guess the last train's gone already.
Seems so.
This was your plan all along, wasn't it?
Now, now, I even brought us some cards to pass the time.
Someone's well-prepared.
We never really had the chance to do something like this if you think about it.
Alright, there's four of us, so-
Count me out.
I’ll be borrowing the bedroom.
I got Ametaro's Rail too if you want. Wanna do the 100-year challenge?
Reference to the Momotaro Dentetsu: Showa, Heisei, Reiwa mo Teiban! Nintendo Switch game. The 100-year challenge is a very long game mode.
Are you planning to stay here all night?
Did I do something wrong?
I can think of a few things.
Don’t worry, it wasn't your fault.
Are you sure?
I’ll go talk to her.
Heading to bed already?
Not really.
You don't need me for your game night, do you?
I want to be alone.
As you wish.
If you have complaints, I'm all ears.
Complaints? What made you think that?
The loser pays for the food!
Rupa: 20, Nina: 2, Subaru: 10
I lost.
What is even going on here?
Nina, that's what.
If you want to blame someone, blame my AC!
You should have at least tried to suck it up for a bit.
I did!
I killed some time in a convenience store,
I even sat on a bench doing nothing for an hour.
But being outside is super boring when you're broke!
Where’s Tomo?
She went to sleep.
Did she say anything about the song?
Not really.
I see.
She looked like she had something to say back then.
Where are you going?
To the fridge.
It'll be a waste if it gets warm.
And what do you think will happen if my grandmother sees it?
It's fine, it's not like there will be any beer left in them by morni-
A snake?
Tomo-chan's pet.
Don't worry, he's calm and not venomous at a-
SNAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAKE!
Phew, saved it!
Momoka-san.
Momoka-san!
Come on, get out of there.
Get rid of it! Hurry!
So she's afraid of snakes, huh...
How traditional.
It's a freaking snake! Are you all just completely fine with this?!
Yup.
This is nuts!
In what world can four out of four girls be okay with snakes?!
You'll get used to it.
There’s a snake right behind you, you know.
IT'S JUST A HAIRDRYER
She opened the-
door?!
Nice beer!
Hey, wait, wait!
- Momoka-san!
- Just get rid of it!
Hey, if you break anything I'm the one who's gonna get it!
We put it in Tomo-chan's room for now.
Just come out!
You’re going to break the door...
I. Said. No.
You’re too old for tantrums!
- You're seriously going to-
- Nina, heads up!
How do you like that!
You gotta be kidding me.
All of you, out, NOW!
Vexing, aren't they. Just like you.
Never come again.
- I’m hot...
- And whose fault is that?!
You get along so well.
No we don't!
Well, I’m off to work.
Good luck.
Get rid of the snake, will ya?
Speaking of which, where did it go?
Subaru-san said she's willing to keep it for a while.
I wish I was a snake.
Alright, time to scatter.
Rupa, let's go.
We should check on the apartment.
You’re gonna ditch me?
And why would we want to see your face outside of rehearsals?
Momoka-san said hanging out together is good for the band, you know.
If you have time, want to watch me practice?
I'll go get my guitar!
An acoustic guitar?
Yeah.
Mine-san told me I should constantly practice if I want to get good.
She said it's a good guitar, even though it's old.
The second string's out of tune.
Really?
You're amazing.
You’ve been playing piano since you were little, right?
That has nothing to do with it. Anyone can hear this much.
Anyway, the guitar is amazing isn't it?
I’m actually starting to get callouses on my fingers from practicing so much.
Is it better now?
Still a bit off,
but I guess that's the best you can do.
Alright, here we go.
What do you think? I thought I could try playing for our next concert.
You've really improved a lot.
I'm all for it.
An extra guitar will definitely spice our sound up.
No way.
Playing at a concert at your level? Are you serious?
Tomo-chan.
Tomo-chan!
How was it?
What do you think?
It's not exactly my area of expertise.
Well, guitar isn't mine either.
But you know music theory, right?
I guess...
I guess it's fine, for an amateur at least.
An amateur?
So I can't play on stage?
Do you want to play on stage?
Seeing Diamond Dust's concert really made me think.
I want to get better.
To stop relying on Momoka-san,
and be able to stand proud next to her.
With you all, of course.
So if there's something I need to improve, tell me.
It was alright.
C'mon, tell me!
If you just keep playing pretend like you are now...
...even your entire life won't be enough for you to learn properly!
I see.
Girls Band Cry.
How many times do I have to tell you? Take it seriou-
Don't judge us by your own standards.
Not all of us won piano awards as kids.
I’m done with this.
- Wait-
- You just shut up.
You know,
We were talking yesterday, and...
It's gotten a bit cooler now, hasn't it?
You think?
It doesn’t hurt to go without the AC for a bit sometimes.
You can feel the gradual change in temperature on your skin.
Still hot in here
Thank you for today
I think Nina was happy, you know.
No way she was.
You got some nerve showing your mug here again.
I, uh, wanted your advice on something...
Wait, wait, I promise I didn’t come for the AC.
Really?
I seriously need advice. Band-related advice.
I’ll definitely pay you back (in 36 installments please). Iseri Nina.
How is it?
What did Tomo say?
That I might as well be playing pretend.
And that I'll never get anywhere like this.
Dang, she sure didn't sugarcoat it.
I guess that's just how she is.
Did it demotivate you?
Why would it?
Well, if that's your reaction, you'll be fine.
So? What do you think?
I guess I kind of agree with Tomo.
I see.
I practiced a lot, so I thought I'm ready for the stage at this point...
You know, even a year or two might not be enough.
Especially if you're trying to go pro.
But you're managing somehow, aren't you?
I'm not so sure about that.
Tomo would probably have a ton of things to say about my playing.
But she never did, right?
Well, that's because I never went out of my way to ask her to like you did.
She’s a bit of a coward in that sense.
She prefers to keep her distance out of fear of being disliked.
And she'll never approach you herself.
On the other hand, if you approach her...
She's a bit like me.
Yep, you were like that at first too.
Sorry for the trouble.
I put him in a terrarium in the back.
He hasn’t eaten anything though, is that okay?
I guess.
Oh, Tomo-chan.
You're still at it, huh.
Yeah.
Subaru-chan gave me some feedback.
Ouch.
It's fine.
Just play on stage if you want to.
Why are you lying to me?
Tomo-chan?
It disbanded?
She came to Tokyo and recruited members online
to start a band.
Is that how you two met?
Yes. There was also a guitarist and a drummer.
They both said they wanted to go pro, but...
Well, that's how it goes. Everyone says that at first.
Really?
You know, people who make it love to say
that they didn’t do anything special to succeed.
Except if that were true, success would be within everyone’s reach.
Exactly.
And Tomo-chan is fully aware of that.
That’s why she’s so strict with us.
She thought we were all on the same page,
so she became more and more demanding as time went.
Yeah, I can see that.
But you still stayed with her.
She did say she wanted to go solo at one point.
Her age was a bit of a problem though.
A guarantor?
I don’t want to contact my parents.
I promise I won't be a burden.
That’s how we moved in together
and created our duo Beni-Shoga.
We were lucky to get some offers,
but she ended up wrecking it every time, huh.
As a result,
she became afraid of saying what she really thinks.
Afraid that if she does, it'll ruin things again.
What do you think?
About my playing.
Would it work live?
Are you seriously asking that?
I figured as much.
I'm back.
Aren't you a bit late?
He's eating it.
Look.
He is!
Being cautious and scared is fine,
but standing still won't get us anywhere.
What do you mean?
Come on, let’s take a walk.
Still as hot as ever, huh.
Starting tomorrow, we're back to rehearsals.
Hopefully it won't rain.
I'm not wrong, you know.
I just told her what she’s worth, period.
She's not good enough.
Then why did you suddenly change your mind after that?
Well…
That's what Nina wants, isn't it?
She wants to play together with Momoka.
That's why she came to you in the first place.
She wants to improve.
That's what everyone says.
"I'm serious", "I want to get better", they all say that.
But in the end, they just want the praise that comes with it.
To sing whatever and however they want.
Hear that?
Ouch.
Umm...
Like this, this, and this dangit!
Do what I say you dumb fingers!
Seeing them play as a trio
made me understand something.
They're serious.
Even if they're far from perfect,
they still give it their all on stage.
I think what you've been looking for all along is exactly that.
You suck!
You'll see, I'll get better!
You suck.
I'm definitely enjoying this.
What's wrong?
I dunno, something's still bothering me.
What exactly?
Nothing, forget it.
Let's take a break.
Momoka.
As it is now, I think this song is boring.
I know, right?
Nina Iseri: Rina Momoka Kawaragi: Yuri
Subaru Awa: Mirei Tomo Ebizuka: Natsu
Rupa: Shuri Tomo Ebizuka: Natsu
Next up: "Wandervogel".