[glass breaking, explosion]
[grunt]
[glass and metal falling]
[Bradley] A smoke bomb
and a grenade in one.
[Bradley] That reckless fool
is beginning to annoy me...
Do you think you can
follow their scent?
[Gluttony] Uh-huh.
[Winry sobbing]
Here officer...
Take her someplace
she'll be safe...
Winry... Al is still fighting,
so I have to go... Okay?
[Ed] I'm sorry... When this is
over, I'll explain everything.
[Winry] Why... why is waiting
the only thing I can do?
[radio] We have a girl in
custody in Sector Eight
who appears to be a friend
of the Fullmetal Alchemist...
Escort her to
Central Command...
Repeat. Sector Eight... We
have a girl in custody
who appears to be a friend
of the Fullmetal Alchemist...
[Roy] It's just about time.
Go and back them up.
Right.
[Roy] There's a vacant
house outside of town...
That's where we'll meet
up. Don't be followed.
[Hawkeye] 'Kay.
If something goes wrong...
I'll let you know.
Alright.
[door closing]
And sir, please stay
out of the field.
I know, Lieutenant. Now go.
[running, heavy breathing]
He won't give up.
[Ling] This area looks deserted.
A dead end. We're trapped.
[footsteps]
[explosion from far away]
Hm?
Scar again?
Gluttony- Go see what
he's up to this time...
And I'll take care of our
two little friends here.
[running, blood dripping]
What happened to me?...
[Ling] What's wrong?
To my arm?...
My lord... I'm useless
to you now.
What're you talking about?
[Lan Fan] You cannot
burden yourself with me...
If you do, they'll
only get you too...
A king is no king
without his people,
but a people without their
king would be lost as well.
You can't do that to them...
My lord, think of our clan...
You must live for their sake.
I won't leave you!
Sometimes someone must be left
behind. For the greater good.
Lan Fan! What are you
planning? No! Don't do it!
[explosion]
[screaming]
[stone crashing]
There's nothing
inside that armor.
You're hollow aren't you?
[Scar] You poor boy...
Alchemy trapped you
in that metal prison
and yet you still
have faith in it?
[clap, transmutation sounds]
[water gushing]
[Al] True, there are plenty of
things about this body
that are inconvenient.. but it's
nothing I can't live with...
[Al] I don't need pity from
anyone... least of all from you.
My brother used alchemy
to save my life...
To regret the form I have now
would mean not only rejecting
alchemy but also turning
my back on him...
I believe in my brother,
and I believe in alchemy.
I will not lose faith...
I want to believe!
Oh, do you?
[gasp]
[explosion]
[Ed yelling]
[Al] Brother!...
Where's Winry?
She's safe. No thanks to me,
though... I made her cry again.
[Al] You really should be
more careful, Brother.
[Al] She doesn't like to
see you fight like that.
Yeah...
[Ed] But she's gone
now... Let's end this.
[Gluttony] Oooh! I found you!
[crash]
[slobbering] Ishvalan!
You again!
[Al] Look at his tattoo!
A Homunculus!
[yelling]
[transmutation sounds]
[crashing and grunting]
[hurried footsteps]
[blood dripping]
[explosion]
It's Ling!
Go! Move it!
[explosion, blood splattering]
[transmutation sounds]
Get me some strong cable!
[Ed] Right!... On it.
[transmutation sounds]
Your own regenerative ability's
working against you...
Your flesh won't
stop expanding,...
It'll keep you tied
up nice and tight.
You're mine now... Homunculus!
[dog whimpering]
That was well played, girl.
I.. beat you...
How does it feel
to be tricked?...
You lose this round.
[Scar] What?...
That thing is a Homunculus?
[engine revving]
[gunshots]
[grunting in pain]
[brakes squealing]
Put him in. We're
getting out of here.
[shocked yells]
[yelling with effort]
Hold on a sec, Lieute--
Shh!
[engine revving]
[Al] Wait! What's going on--
[Ed] Al!
The MPs are watching... Just
pretend we don't know her.
[Soldier] They're getting
away!... After them!
[MPs] Right!
The colonel may be a
creep and a jerk,
but at least we can trust him...
We have something to do.
[crash, transmutation sounds]
[Ed] We have to get him Al!
[Al affirmative grunt]
[clap, transmutation sounds]
You killed the Rockbells and
Nina, among many others.
[Al] You're going to answer
for your crimes!
[crashing, grunting]
Are these two giving you
trouble, servant?
This is the servant of the
man who saved my life.
You better leave him
alone, puny little boy!
Wait a sec!.. Who
you calling puny?!
[MPs] Where'd that
kid come from?
[MPs] Get away, girl...
It's dangerous!
They've got us outnumbered...
It's time for us to retreat.
[transmutation sounds]
[explosions]
[yelling, coughing]
[coughing] What kind
of alchemy was that?
[Al] She did it from
that far away?
Here, follow me.
I can't see! Scar!
[honking]
I know who you are,
Ling Yao...
Don't worry... We're on our
way to a secure safe house.
My friend... I left her
behind!... Go get her!
What?... No, we can't.
We don't have time.
Make time!... She
could be dying now...
She's still waiting
there for me!
You had better make it quick.
[honking]
[Bradley] That woman driving...
I'm sure she's Mustang's.
I'm tired of playing
games with that upstart.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[transmutation sounds]
[Scar] Her eyes... Is
that how mine looked?
No matter what I do...
Hatred only breeds more hatred.
There you go. I think I
managed to stop the bleeding.
Thank you.
Sir!... The MPs are all
closing in on us...
We need to get going!
[Soldier] He took
a shot to the leg.
In his condition, he
couldn't have gotten far.
Comb the area for him!
Sir!
[Yoki whispering]
Quickly, sir, quickly!
Shao May, where are you?
Oh no!
[Al] Look what I found, Ed.
We're a little busy right now to
be adopting panda bears, Al!
[Al] I couldn't
leave her alone
in the middle of all
that mess back there!
First stray cats, and now
this?!.. Just how many animals
can you stuff into that armor of
yours, huh?!.. Get rid of it!
[Al] What a heartless
thing to say!
[Al] Look how sweet
and gentle she is!
[chomp]
[Al chuckling] It's all
right... You're safe now.
[clang]
[shocked yelling]
[MP] This way... follow me.
[Ed] Thanks.
[Al] You can stay
in here, okay?
[excited gasp]
Hey! Winry!
Oh... hello there,
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Fuhrer Bradley.
This is a surprise.
[Al] What brings you here?...
I heard that a childhood
friend of yours was under
our protection here at
the Command Center...
As a friend of such an
important alchemist...
[Bradley] she deserves
our every courtesy.
I should be on my way now... If
you'll please excuse me, miss.
Oh.. of course... sir.
That's a nice, honest
friend you've got there...
Make sure you both take
good care of her.
[Winry] Ed...
You promised... Tell me
everything about my parents...
What happened to them?
[Winry] I see...
They did everything they
could to help others..
Right up until the end.
But I... I just wish they could
have come back to me alive.
Is that selfish?
More waiting... That's
all I can ever do.
[front desk] Ah!...
Perfect timing!...
Miss Rockbell,..there's a
telephone call for you.
For me?
Yes, hello?... Oh, Mr. Garfiel!
[Garfiel] I'm sorry
about this, Winry.
I know you've got
a lot going on
and I tried to handle
it myself, really.
[crowd] Where is she?
Isn't Winry back yet?
Look at this! Winry's the
only one who can fix it!
[Garfiel] ...but I can't
take this anymore.
Your customers are so needy!
[crowd] Please hurry back,
Winry! We miss you!
[Tetsu] You there, Miss Winry?
Tetsu?
[Tetsu] Please come back
to the shop soon...
You do a much better job working
on my leg than Mr. Garfiel can!
We need you here!
Another thing, Winry.. We
still need an outer covering
for that model leg
you made for me.
My arm needs work too!
Hey, hold on a sec.
I was first!
[crowd] I miss you, Winry!
You idiot, of course you
miss her!... We all do.
Isn't that the truth!
I'm sorry... I'll be
back home soon.
[Winry] Just hold on...
I won't be much longer...
I'll help everyone...
Thank you all.
[train whistle]
[Winry] Thank you both...
for stopping me back there.
I forgot there were still
people who depended on me...
If I had done it...
I wouldn't have been able
to face them again.
[Al] Of course.
I expect you to take good
care of your automail!
Yep.
Oh, and I'll send you some
good polishing oil soon, Al.
[Al] Great!
And no dying, okay?
Right.
Oh, and...
the next time I make
you cry, I hope...
[bell ringing loudly]
Wha?...What?... I
can't hear you!
[Al] Brother?...Wait
up!... See ya, Winry!
Oh..kay. Geez... Come back,
Edward! What were you saying?!
The next time I make you cry, I
hope they'll be tears of joy!
And Al and I will be back in
our normal bodies,
[Ed] and I'll make you cry
out of sheer happiness!
That's a promise!
[laughing]
[train whistle]
Give me a new arm and a leg.
I need one year!
Well... there's no turning
back for us now, brother.
[Ed] What are you
crying for, Winry?
[Winry] All this time, have
I been... falling for him?
[car engine, brakes squealing]
[Ed] Colonel?
Get in the car.
[Roy] Someone's
badly injured.
I came to you because
we need a doctor.
[Knox] Got yourself
in trouble again...
Just can't help yourself.
I know you have a family.
I wouldn't want to
endanger them...
If you'd rather not get
involved, I'll understand.
[Knox] Wait here...
I'll get my instruments.
Are you sure about this?
My wife and I split up
not long after I came back
from duty in Ishval.
[Knox] You let her
wander around the sewers
with her arm cut off?!... Don't
blame me if she gets lockjaw!
[Lan Fan groaning in pain]
I'm afraid, the only
patients I've had lately
have been corpses... so this
might be a little rough.
[screaming through gag]
[whimpering from other room]
I'm sorry.
No, Don't apologize.
I'm the one who
suggested it, remember?
We both had something to gain
out of it, so it made sense...
When I went in search
of immortality...
I knew I must be ready to
make certain sacrifices.
[Ling] But I... I wasn't
ready for this...
Lan Fan was though.
She made the decision that
I was too weak to make.
[Al] She's awake!
You okay?...is there
anything we can do?
That old trap of yours...
worked pretty well.
But I'm useless
without my arm...
I'm going to need to
find a replacement.
You know... I can introduce
you to a great engineer.
[footsteps]
I'm with the State Military...
Name's Colonel Roy Mustang.
And my name is Ling Yao,
the twelfth son of
the Emperor of Xing.
I appreciate you
finding a doctor.
It was no problem.
Thank you for helping us
with the Ross incident...
And also...
[Roy] for bringing
this thing in.
[Knox] Hey, what
do we have here?
[Ling] That's Gluttony...
He's a Homunculus.
He and his friends appear
to be have connections
among some of the
military's senior staff.
Just some, you say?.. It
goes far deeper than that.
Your Fuhrer, King Bradley...
I believe it's possible
that he's a Homunculus too.
[gasps]
I saw his eye.. The
one under the patch.
It had an Uroboros tattoo...
He and Gluttony came after us,
and they were working together!
No way!
[Al] Our ruler.. a Homunculus?!
Although... Bradley doesn't
have the same sort
of inhuman presence that
you get from Gluttony...
At his core, he still feels
like a regular person.
[Al] Another thing... If the
Fuhrer is a Homunculus,
how can he possibly have a
son?... It said in that book
that the Homunculi have no
reproductive capabilities.
[Knox] No... The Fuhrer's
son, Selim, is adopted...
There's no direct blood relation
between him and his father.
Whether he's monster
or human...
either way, these new
developments will make it
easier to remove him
from the seat of power.
First, we get information
out of this one...
and I'll take his stone...
It may prove useful
in treating my man.
Hey, you! Lan Fan lost
her arm to get him.
[Ling] He's our captive! We're
taking him back to Xing!
[Ed] Hold it! He could help
us get our bodies back!
We've been working on
that for a long time.
I'm not going to let you
just waltz off with him!
[Roy] That's right!
Think about it, Ling!
You're an illegal alien.
[Knox] I'm too old
for this kinda thing...
Good luck, Mustang...
I'm going home.
Colonel Mustang.
Mustang was one
who killed Lust!...
Mustang must pay for
what he did to her!
[cables straining,
Gluttony grunting]
[Gluttony] Roy Mustang!
[Shao May whimpering]
[explosion]
What was that?!
[Narrator] What lies safely
hidden behind lying eyes...
behind fake smiles and
feigned friendship?
Finding out will
be no easy task...
Enter the forest... Grope in
the darkness for the unknown.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 24... Inside the Belly.
If you move carelessly...
nothing but pain will await
you in the inky blackness.