Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
It's a little late, but happy New Year!
Please cheer us on a lot this year too, okay?
Well, well, well. How did
you all spend your New Year's?
Shrine visits? Special New
Year's meals? New Year's gifts?
Well, as for myself, I'm not
in jolly spirits much this year.
My sister was born this year,
and it's our first New Year's all together.
But as I am now, not able to do anything...
I know it's not okay to let
things stay like this, but, but, but...
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Both of you, you did well.
With you following up Layla and Yuri, we
won the competition twice consecutively.
You did a good job.
I want you to start rehearsing for the New
Year's show right away, starting tomorrow.
This show will be your triumphal performance.
Needless to say, we're going to
use the Demon Spiral for the climax.
All right, Mia?
Yes.
Excuse me... How about Sora?
Sora...
Sora is going to appear on stage with us, right?
Because as far as I'm concerned,
the festival contest isn't over yet.
I can't believe you withdrew. You're the worst.
You disgraced the festival.
You ran away from the stage
where a serious match was.
It's also a place where you
destroy the dreams of others.
I told myself that I would fight to the finish.
I feel shame.
But in the end, for me...
I'm disappointed in you, Sora.
I'm sorry for the trouble I caused you.
"Amazing and Sad Homecoming."
Boss! Sora just...
I know.
What?
Tell Mia.
We're removing Sora from
the New Year's show cast.
So now I've come home.
All right.
Sora?
Sora...
Um...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Please don't shock me like that.
At least call if you're coming home.
Sorry...
All of a sudden... What happened?
Oh, well... I thought...
Since it's the New Year...
But, doesn't your next rehearsal start soon?
Well, I decided to skip it this time.
Skip it? Did something happen?
No, nothing in particular.
Yume's gotten so big!
I'm home, Yume. It's your big sister!
I just thought that once
my mother had a baby...
There would be no room for me...
Sora, both your mother
and her baby are trying hard...
Let's cheer them on.
Hey, Sora.
What?
Can you name the baby?
Me? Are you sure?
I always wanted you to name my baby.
Okay.
Thank you, Yume.
Thanks to you, I feel like
I finally became a part of the family.
Both my mother and father
were hoping for me to come home.
I think I'll just stay here from now on.
I won't go back to the stage anymore...
Yes, this is Naegino.
What? Oh...
Just a moment...
Sora.
Miss Mia... Isn't she one of
your friends I met over there?
What?
Hello, Mia...
Sora?!
Everyone, I found her.
Really? Oh... That's good.
Sorry, I made you worry.
Why did you leave without telling us?
Well... Uh... there was a lot of
stuff I wanted to think over, I guess...
Sora, you are coming back, aren't you?
When are you coming back?
Everyone's waiting for you.
Well...
At any rate, I'm fine, okay?
So, everyone, don't worry about me. Bye...
Sora!
Well... I never expected you'd be home.
I thought I was dreaming.
You're exaggerating.
How long can you stay?
Well, I was thinking of taking
my time and staying for a while...
Really?
Honey, can you get me another beer?
Well, that's unusual.
The whole family's gathered after a long time.
It's all right to cut loose
every once in a while, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
This reminds me of the old days.
Well, this is a nice room.
It just looks like it belongs to a girl.
Fool, did you hide in my luggage again?
I always wanted to come to Japan once.
Anyway, I have to check
out the geisha and the kogals.
You're wasting your time staying with me.
The stage... I'm not...
Did you really decide
that you're not going back?
Yes, I did.
I see.
Well, the answer will
make itself known naturally.
If you've given up the stage,
soon you'll no longer be able to see me.
Demon Spiral!
Don't worry, Mia. I'm sure Sora will be back.
Yeah.
Excuse me!
Don't just stand there!
If you don't give instructions, I won't know
how the show's supposed to fit together, will I?
Oh... Sorry.
Are you trying to drag me and Leon down?
If you're not interested in this, quit.
What's wrong with her?!
Acting like she is so important...
There's nothing we can do.
The fact of the matter is,
she became No. 1 in the world.
So she's full of confidence.
I wonder if it's true.
I'm relieved she's gone.
The end of the year is getting close.
So much has happened this year.
That's true. It's sad to say
goodbye to this year, but--
Happy New Year!
This is even more lavish
than our usual New Year's feast.
Mother, your ozouni soup really is the best.
Please eat a lot.
Yes.
So, this is the town where Sora lives.
It's not too bad.
I wanted to come here all by myself.
You don't have time to space out.
Didn't you come here to see Sora?
But, the only thing I know is her address.
I don't know how the
roads here work or anything.
I'm a police officer. Let me handle it.
Happy New Year.
Sora, why don't you take a bath?
Really, one should begin a new
year by cleansing one's body and...
Fool, how long are you going to stay here?
I'm not going back to Kaleido Stage anymore.
So why don't you find somebody else?
Then why are you still training?
This... this is my after-meal exercise.
I see...
Then, I think you should take a
shower after your exercise and feel clean.
Sora, you have a phone call.
Yes.
Well, I guess you could say
that this is very Japanese too.
Who is it?
Miss Kurata.
What? Manami?
Manami... How are you?
I can't believe this! If you're
back, you could at least call!
Oh... Sorry.
I will be there with Sayaka and Miki.
So let's have a New Year's party at your place.
Oh...
Excuse me!
Again? Japan has a bunch of weirdoes.
Well, no, I think that's a natural reaction...
I'll try this time.
Um, excuse me...
What can we help you with?!
Who's this?
Don't you think he looks super cool?
Wow! Maybe he's a foreign
soccer player or something.
No, he must be a movie star!
I can't believe this! Take a picture, a picture!
I'm going to take a picture with him.
Uh... Excuse me...
He is cute!
Do you know Sora?
Would you mind taking one more picture?
Sora!
Happy New Year!
Wow... I haven't seen you guys in a long time!
Please come in.
Thanks for letting us in.
Wow... But, I never expected
Sora would really go to America.
Really?
Usually, nobody believes something like that.
I was very surprised too.
Even though I've heard that being
a Kaleido Star was your dream...
Manami, you saw Sora's show, didn't you?
Yes. I saw that legendary great maneuver.
Hey, how was it?
Well, how should I describe it?
I felt as if I was flying in the sky with them.
Wow...
It's strange, but I felt some kind of
energy through my body as I watched it.
Wow...
I wish I could have seen.
Getting to play the leading parts and
stuff from the very beginning, I'm jealous.
What?
Sayaka joined a voice actors' agency.
Wow... That's cool!
Will you do anime voices and stuff?
Well, you know, in the last round of auditions
I made it to final callbacks for the lead role.
But I didn't get the role.
Come on, don't get so down.
There'll be other shows!
Yes.
Well, I guess it means I need
to improve my skills more, huh?
Come to think of it, you wanted
to be a manga artist, right Miki?
I'll go to junior college and get a
job after that like everybody else.
I decided to keep drawing manga as my hobby.
But Miki, you're good at manga!
That's such a waste.
But, you know, when it becomes your job,
you have a lot of tough times, right?
And I think if I went through that,
I'd end up hating manga.
But I want to keep loving manga forever, so...
That sounds like you,
Miki, you're such a realist.
Well...
So, how about you, Sora? You made
your dream come true really fast.
Yeah, why do you look so gloomy?
Well... How should I say this?
See, I have many reasons.
Hey, why don't you do something and show us?
Oh, that's a good idea since it's a new year.
Would you, please?
Okay...
Wow!
Amazing!
How can you do something like that?
Wow!
Wow... You're so cool.
Oh... This applause...
It's different from when I was in the festival.
I wonder what is different.
The audience applauds for the same reason.
So I am the one who's different?
I'm enjoying it now.
I'm enjoying it with Manami
and the rest of my friends.
That's right. The shows that everybody enjoys,
that's the Kaleido Stage I like.
I wanted to be in more shows like that.
Bravo!
I can tell you're a real pro.
I'm so impressed.
Then, we have to go this way.
Okay.
One day, I will come to see your show.
Me too. Me too.
Bye!
Bye.
You know, I've decided to go to college.
It's not like I gave up a
dream to be a hair stylist.
I decided to take time and
talk with my parents and decide.
Hm...
I started thinking like this thanks to you.
Me?
That's right.
When I was watching you working so hard,
I started wanting to chase after my dream too.
Sora, you gave me a dream.
I did?
The reason you came back to Japan...
Does it have something to do with the fact
that you quit in the middle of your
performance at the Circus Festival?
Oh, do you know that?
Well, I found out about it on the internet.
Yeah... Well, that's not the only reason.
Your mom was worried about you.
I got a phone call from her.
She asked me to spend time with you to
divert your mind, since you looked upset.
You must be worried about something.
I ran out on Kaleido Stage.
I think that's fine.
As long as you don't have any regrets about it.
You'd rather just do
something than think about it
because you didn't want thinking
about it to make you hesitate,
so that you end up not
doing it and regretting it.
You've always said that,
ever since we were in school together.
So, if you don't regret your decision,
I have no problems with that.
But, if you're regretting it now,
why not try doing your
best to give it another shot?
I think you should just shamelessly tell them
"I changed my mind and want to come back!"
The fact that you can
do things like that, Sora...
I think that's so cool.
Manami...
When I met you in America,
I told you that I came to see
your regretful face. Remember?
Yes.
You may think I'm selfish,
but I don't want to see your regretful face now.
What the hell are you thinking?!
I guess I'll end up leaving without seeing her...
Biting someone's head all of a sudden!
Don't underestimate me because
I don't understand Japanese!
If you don't watch out, you'll be sorry.
Mr. Policeman?
Oh, Sora! I was looking for you.
I brought Ken along too, as sort of an extra.
Oh, it's true.
"Extra"?
Sorry. I keep worrying everybody.
We've basically wrapped up
the New Year's show rehearsals,
so I decided to try coming here.
New Year's show?
It's May and Leon's triumphal performance.
Hm...
Since the opening day is
tomorrow, I have to leave now.
What? But we just met up.
Unfortunately, we already
purchased the airline tickets back.
I see.
You are coming back, aren't you, Sora?
Sora... I hope you didn't...
The way I am now,
even if I come back to Kaleido Stage,
I'm afraid I'll get in everybody's way.
When you dropped out of the festival,
I was actually a little relieved.
Because I think in that situation,
crying and not being able to
go on is more like the Sora I know
than being totally fine with it
all and being able to perform.
If you don't like battles,
why don't you create a show without them?
Create one? Me?
I want to see more of
your cheerful, fun shows, Sora.
Sora, when you're flying
through the air looking so bright, I...
I...
I like you.
Ken...
I like you lots too!
I like to see you like that too.
I like it lots and lots and lots!
As your number one fan, I want
to see a Sora show like that soon!
Right, Mr. Number Two Fan?
What? Me?
Fans like us always love Sora.
Oh... What I meant was...
We love Sora!
I'm going to create a fun
Kaleido Stage with no battles.
Please be my dream, Sora.
I know you can become a true Kaleido Star.
All the answers are inside you.
Keep going after your dream without being lost.
If you do that, I'm sure the road to
being a real Kaleido Star will open for you.
Yes.
I'm going to create a Kaleido Stage
with no battles that's fun for everyone.
That is my real dream.
And if I do that, the road to being a
real Kaleido Star should open there too.
What's wrong?
Thank you, Ken!
I will go back to Kaleido Stage
one more time. I will for sure.
We're waiting for you.
When you do, we'll come
to the airport to pick you up.
Yes, thank you.
Really... I see. I think that's fine.
Thank you, Manami.
You did the same for me.
Let's do our best.
So, that's why I came back this time.
I'm sorry it's such a pathetic story.
Then... After thinking a lot,
I feel like going back there. And...
Honey...
Here, this is for you.
What's this?
Sora, since you didn't even visit
a shrine early in the new year...
A good luck charm...
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Do it until you're satisfied.
Yes.
Yume, your big sister will
try her best one more time.
Oh, Yume.
One more time... I will try one more time.
This time, I will never lose sight of my dream.
Never!
It seems the fog of confusion has cleared.
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
That's not going to get anyone excited!
Don't take your audience lightly!
And so, thank you for waiting.
I'm back. My name is Sora Naegino!
I really appreciate everyone
who has been waiting for me.
The way I do things, the way I feel,
no one can stop them! No one! No one!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"My Amazing Fresh Start."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...