This tapioca drink fails.
The straw’s so thin that the tapioca bunches up and I can’t drink it anymore.
So Nodoka also joined the Chupa Research Group?
Nodoka!
It can’t be…
What’s wrong, Yue?
Haruna!
Haruna, all of a sudden, everyone disappeared! I could’ve sworn they were just here, too!
They suddenly disappeared…? Do you think a chupacabra showed up and did that?!
Wha?
I’ll explain it in detail. I’m gonna go get my memo!
Hey! You got it all wrong!!
by Setsuna
An illusion has been created once again.
There, the classmates, under a subordination spell, wait.
A subordination spell means… vampires and… the Star Crystal!
The unknown fairy shows some kind of hostility towards Negi and the others! What exactly is happening at Mahora Academy?!
Everyone, stop it, please!
It’s impossible now.
The girls here are all under my control.
Your words cannot reach them.
Why are you doing this?!
Hmm.
Wonder why.
Please! I beg of you, return the girls!
I don’t...
think...
that’s an...
option.
I just...
want...
to...
see...
that...
disappointed...
look...
on...
your...
face.
But why…?
Ha.
JUST USE ONE PERSON AT A TIME TO TALK!
Negi, let me transform!
Asuna-san!
If I don’t power up, then we’ll be done for at this rate!
I wanna join in, too, Negi-kun!
Me, too!
Alright, then.
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna; Miyazaki Nodoka; Konoe Konoka! Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
Ouch; all of ‘em are Suka Cards.
Why does it have to come up now?!
Uweh! I feel so embarrassed!
Aww, you guys are so cute!
Augh, what are we gonna do?!
Well isn’t this
a brave set of people.
Come attack us to your heart’s content!
Ha!
What are you doing at a time like this?!
Prepare yourself!
Like the Sand Master revolving the wind, like the foam fusing in the water...
figure of mine, conceal within the darkness!
Tel Ma Amoris!
We should be fine from here now.
Ojou-sama transformed into this…
How saddening…
Ah… I’m gettin’ kinda shleepy…
No more… I’m so hungry I can’t move…
Me too…
Motsu, what are you doing, mya?
Don’t you just want to smash all the bubbles...
in this bubble wrap that you see here for nothing in return?
Yes I do, mya.
Now, I’m fighting that temptation with all the power I have.
I see.
By bearing this intensely unbearable temptation...
we shall gain the will of power to stand above mankind!
I’m sorry… I’ve lost to the temptation.
Sucks for you, mya.
I wanna win next time.
Speaking of which, is it alright for you to not go where Negi-kun is right now?
There’s still more bubbles.
Light a fire. Ardescat!
Itadakimasu!
It’s a good thing we had those eggs!
Even better that we had soy sauce on hand!
But soy sauce isn’t used for fortune telling.
Isn’t it that salt goes best with sunny-side up?
Eh? So you guys don’t put sugar…
Despite having three partners, it doesn’t do you any good if all of them are Suka Cards, huh?
You can’t help it; you’ll never know what card you’ll get.
Oh yeah! I got a real good idea!
How about Secchan and Negi-kun exchange a provisional contract, too?
EH!?
What are you talking about, Ojou-sama?!
Well, the more we have, the better the chance of us getting something good.
Um… well, she’s got a point there, but…
I guess you should consider the person’s feelings after all…
Secchan, if you exchange a provisional contract with Negi-kun...
it means you exchanged an indirect kiss with me.
An indirect kiss…
…with Ojou-sama…?
…with Ojou-sama…
N-n-n-no! Such unladylike talk… You mustn’t, Ojou-sama!
No! That’s a perfectly good idea!
Setsuna Ane-san! This is a critical time we’re livin’ in, so why not exchange the contract?
You’ll become stronger than before!
“Stronger than before”?!
And the more contracts are exchanged, I’ll be 50,000 Ermine bucks richer; what an opportunity!
Thanks, but no thanks.
Eh?
I’m fine the way I am now. I have the power to protect Ojou-sama.
There’s no way I’d do something like become someone else’s partner.
Secchan…
Hey, Negi… are you sure you know where we’re going?
Of course; like the back of my hand!
I used to play around here when I was younger.
So wait; were we really transported to Wales?
Of course not!
There isn’t a mage in existence that could travel between Japan and Britain in an instant!
See, the shadow of that rock!
Eh? What’s in here?
There’s a snake in there!
And if you knock on that tree…
Like this?
…a bug falls on you!
Ah! And in front of that thicket…
What is it this ti- WHOA!
…there’s a really deep pitfall!
TELL ME BEFOREHAND!
Rather, aren’t you the bold one, Ane-san?
Hmm? Negi-kun, what’s this?
This is me; this is Nekane-oneechan; and this one’s Anya.
It’s all exactly the same as my memory.
So does that mean we really are in Wales…?
No. That’s not it.
Why not? It’s exactly as you remember it, isn’t it?
I’m not sure why, but I have a feeling we’re not in Wales.
It’s more like a dimension created by my memories.
Who would want to do that?
I’m not sure. But it could’ve been someone who knows me all too well…
Impossible. There’s no way that…
Where are we?
At a castle ruin. When I was younger, I would play hide-n-seek here a lot.
This is the first time I’ve seen a European castle…
It’s so different compared to Japanese castles…
Watch out!
Took you long enough...
Negi Springfield.
We thought that...
you would...
show up...
here.
You guys…
Now...
this is your...
final stage.
Better prepare...
yourself!
Negi, this time I’ll win! I’m not gonna let it slide if it’s a Suka Card!
Eh?! But that’s…
Stop whining and hurry it up!
And to think she’s our partner…
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna; Miyazaki Nodoka, Konoe Konoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
They’re all Rare Cards this time!
Alright!
Are these… encyclopedias?
I kinda feel stronger now!
We can’t lose with this!
Here it comes!
Jou-chan, that’s…
I’ll predict the enemy’s movements with this.
Negi-sensei! To your right!
Konoka-san! To your left!
Asuna-san, the book says she’s going to feign and come from above!
Kaede-san! Chisame-san!
Negi! This way!
You two! We’re gonna flee from here!
We should be fine with this.
Ojou-sama.
Ah, it seems like a dead end.
We’ve made a mistake, then… Hee hee!
Ojou-sama, this isn’t something to go “Hee hee!” about.
There isn’t a way out of here where we are, so let’s look for one!
But Jou-chan, those encyclopedias you got are awesome!
Whenever I read this it’s like I can understand everything!
Ah, if that’s the case, do you think you can read up on how to get out of this world?
Okay, hold on please.
In order to leave this world… Ah! I found it!
Are you serious!?
It is essential to be tolerant to everything and have a strong heart.
Thinking only about what you’ve gained or lost will cause you to suffer instead.
Wha!?
Ah! I made a mistake!
That wasn’t the way to get out of here!
It was really the way to live in a tough world!
What the hell is that?!
Pappa pa, Pappa pa…
Um… se… se… se… "seikoutoutei"...
"Sekigahara no Tatakai"…
"Sekihin arau ga gotoshi"
I found it!
"Kono sekai kara dashitsu suru houhou!"
If you seal the fairy, the illusion will dissipate, and you will be able to return to your own world!
“Seal the fairy”?
Aniki!
We’ll take care of those three.
Sensei, focus on sealing the fairy.
You guys! But-!
NO OBJECTIONS!
Y-yes, Ma’am!
Here we go!
Splendid job.
Thank you, even if it was ill-prepared.
Hasegawa-san is just being manipulated. If you can understand her true feelings and call out to her, she’s sure to open her eyes…
Hasegawa-san’s feelings… Ah, found it!
“If I take advantage of this opportunity and defeat Miyazaki Nodoka,
I can reclaim my title and be the number one ‘net idol again!”
Uh? Eh?
Aniki!
Negi-sensei, you have too many opportunities.
Setsuna-san!
I’ll finish this. Hurry and seal the fairy.
Okay!
Wait!
Can’t run anymore!
Now it’s time to seal you!
Dang it…
A trap?!
Secchan! Oh no…
Just give me some time! I’ll save you-
Ojou-sama!
I… can’t go on like this…
Konoka!
Not good! Our time’s been cut!
N-Negi-sensei!
Ojou-sama!
You guys!
How do ya like that, Negi?
Isn’t it interesting to watch...
your cute little students in conflict?
STOP IT!
Negi-sensei!
No good, aniki! This cage is protected with a spell.
Your magic will be reflected
Negi… sensei!
How in the hell… could you do this?!
Ojou-sama!
It’s no use, Aniki! Magic isn’t effective!
There’s no way I’ll…
…ever give up!
Negi-sensei!
Negi-sensei…
If I were to exchange a provisional contract with you, I really will become stronger than before, won’t I?
Setsuna-san…
If I become your partner… I can help you, right?
I’ll be able to rescue Ojou-sama, right?
I beg of you. Give me strength!
Setsuna-san…
Chamo-kun!
Alright!
Pactio!
Provisional Contract Complete!
Partner: Sakurazaki Setsuna. Show me the power within you!
Contract…
Activate!
We got it! Another Rare Card!
My power is… overflowing!
Hiken: Hyakkaryouran!
Shinmeiryuu Ougi: Hyakuretsu Ouka Zan!
Weighted light, travel; go beyond the door, and send it far away!
Tel Ma Amoris!
Ojou-sama!
Secchan?
Are you alright?
Eheh… I guess you had to save me again in the end, huh?
Ojou-sama…
Such pretty wings… you look like an angel…
Are we… back from where we came?
Uwah… thank god we’re saved!
I was so scared…!
This isn’t good, Aniki! We’ve been seen again!
Eh? My magic?!
Now you’ve done it!
Now you’ve done it, mya!
Shi-Shichimi and Motsu-san!
You’ve finally been caught, mya!
It’s time for the annual tribute, after all.
In a good way.
Ah! I inadvertently dozed off de gozaru. Where… am I de gozaru?
Ah! Last I remember, we were searching for the chupacabra, and I remember the part when we said “50 yen discount” but…
Ah! SoftMacho’s about to close!
I gotta hurry!
I guess they don’t recall what happened when they were put under control.
This may be a lame present…
but please, take it.
Negi, is everything okay? I’m always wondering if you’re doing alright or not.
Even if you think your training is painful, try your best! I’ll be cheering for you!
Thank you, Oneechan. I’ll do my best.
Negi and the other students, who have been able to safely return to their own world...
have managed to seal the fairy, yet some mysteries still remain.
What exactly is remaining? And is that lovely treatment really…?
Wait until next time, even if I can't!
So!
Was it this guy you saw?
I told you before; that’s not it…
The sign of sunset is always unclear, but the sign of a morning glow is rain, isn’t it?
Next time: “Um… There are things that are okay if unseen...
but I also think there are things that are just fine if seen.” by Sayo
I wish tomorrow has clear weather!
Today, I’d like to discuss the actions we must take in the event that we find a chupacabra!
Maybe we should… befriend them?
Haruna, would you be satisfied with just that?
What do you mean by “satisfied”?
When we’ve worked so hard to find one, do you really think you would be satisfied with just befriending it?
Isn’t it cruel if we tell them “let’s be good friends”? If that’s the case, then saying “I hate you” instead would be for the best.
And what’s that supposed to mean?
It’s like protecting a friendship by making a safe refusal to a person you’re not interested in.
Tada! I had Zazie make it, aru!
CHUPACABRA?!
I hate it!