♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY AND
THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1
LET'S JAM. ♪
[RATTLING]
[TOILET FLUSHING]
COME ON OUT!
YOU CAN'T RUN ANYMORE!
WE'LL SHOOT!
IT'S ALL OVER, ABDUL HAKIM.
[CRASH]
AAH!
WANT TO FIGHT?
YOU'RE CRAZY.
[GRUNTING]
ATTENTION.
[AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICES
CONTINUE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
HI, AMIGOS-- ALL 300,000 BOUNTY
HUNTERS IN THIS STAR SYSTEM!
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR "BIG SHOT,"
THE SHOW THAT TELLS
ALL ABOUT FUGITIVES.
SHUCKS, HOWDY!
BUT FIRST TODAY IS THIS HOMBRE:
ABDUL HAKIM, A NOTORIOUS
SERIAL PET THIEF.
IN HIS LATEST CRIME SPREE, HAKIM
NABBED AN INNOCENT LAB ANIMAL
FROM A RESEARCH FACILITY,
AND HE IS STILL ON THE LOOSE.
OOH! AND THE GOOD NEWS IS,
HE'S WORTH A WHOPPING
8 MILLION WOOLONGS!
[WHISTLES]
THE TERMS ARE STANDARD:
YOU MUST BRING THIS FUGITIVE
IN ALIVE AND UNDAMAGED.
IF YOU KILL HIM,
KISS THE REWARD GOODBYE.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST
REWARD THIS SEASON,
SO GO OUT AND GET
HIM, BUCKAROOS.
WELL?
IT'S HISTORY.
MAN, EVERYTHING'S BROKEN
AROUND THIS PLACE.
[BEEPING]
HEY.
YO, DOC. YOU GOT SOMETHING?
YEAH, ON ABDUL HAKIM.
I'LL TAKE IT!
300 WOOLONGS
THAT'S A DISCOUNT.
I'VE GOT HIS FACE
POSTPLASTIC SURGERY.
I'M LOW ON CASH, DOC.
CAN YOU SHAVE IT?
[GROANS]
ALL RIGHT, 280...
BUT ONLY IF YOU MAKE
ME A SOLEMN PROMISE.
LIKE WHAT?
PUNCH HIM OUT FOR ME!
HE TRAMPLED ME WHEN
HE RIPPED OFF MY LAB.
GIVE HIM THE ONCEOVER.
IN FACT, DO IT TWICE.
I GOT THE GOODS,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
THIS ONE'S A SURE-FIRE WINNER.
I'LL SEE YOU IN ABOUT 6 HOURS.
HIS CARRYING CASE
WAS VERY DISTINCT.
THIS INFO'S
NO EXTRA CHARGE, RIGHT?
OH, ALL RIGHT THEN.
THAT CASE IS BIG ENOUGH TO
CARRY A SMALL PERSON INSIDE.
OR A TREASURE.
CAN'T REALLY SAY.
THE WAY HE HANDLED IT
SEEMED LIKE HE HAD
SOMETHING SPECIAL ON HIS MIND.
[BELL RINGS, DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES, BELL RINGS]
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
IF YOU FEEL RUNDOWN,
HAVE SOME GINSENG, HAYSOY.
IT WILL KEEP YOU UP FOR A WEEK.
OUT OF WHACK? OH,
TRY SUGARCANE, HAYSOY.
ATE TOO MUCH? HAVE
PINEAPPLE, HAYSOY.
GIVE ME SOME LAUCHU.
MOMENTAI.
HERE YOU GO.
OH! AAH!
SORRY THERE, BRO.
A LITTLE SLIP, YOU KNOW.
HEY, I SAID I WAS SORRY, HUH?
OH, YOU THINK YOU'RE TOO GOOD
TO TALK TO ME. IS THAT IT?
HEY! WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU WANT TO FIGHT
OR SOMETHING?
HERE. IT'S MY TREAT.
HUH?
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
[CRUNCHING]
DRINK IT.
[GAGGING, RETCHING]
[GASPS]
[CRASH]
UNH!
WHEW! HA HA HA!
ALL RIGHT!
HMM, LET'S SEE WHAT
KIND OF LOOT I GOT.
[ANIMAL GROWLING]
HUH?
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
EVEN IF I OVERHAUL
THIS WHOLE SHIP,
I'LL STILL HAVE
CASH LEFT OVER
AT LEAST ENOUGH FOR,
LET'S SAY, SOME PEKING DUCK.
DON'T COUNT YOUR
CHICKENS, SPIKE
OR SHOULD I SAY,
DON'T COUNT YOUR DUCKS?
I'VE GOT THIS ONE NAILED.
TAKE YOUR BEST SHOT, KID.
SO ALL 3 OF THEM
WENT DOWN, EH?
SEEMS THAT WAY.
AND HAKIM'S STILL
OUT THERE, EH?
SEEMS THAT WAY.
DAMN IT! HE HAS NO IDEA
WHAT THAT THING IS WORTH.
PET SHOP? WHAT KIND?
THE SHADY KIND.
LISTEN, BRO, HERE'S THE DEAL.
YOU CAN BUY ANYTHING HERE ON
MARS, FROM GUNS TO HUMAN LIVES.
AND, OF COURSE,
CHOICE INFORMATION
CAN BE PURCHASED AS WELL,
SO IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
SOMETHING, LET ME SEE SOME CASH.
HMM. LONG CHAIN ON THIS ONE.
WAY-OF-THE-DRAGON MODEL?
HEY, PRETTY GOOD EYE!
THAT'S A RARE ONE FROM
BACK IN THE MID-THIRTIES.
YEAH, IT'S AN ANTIQUE
FOR SURE.
TRY A STORE CALLED
ANIMAL TREASURE.
IT'S OFF SIPHON ROAD,
PAST THE CYBERMALL.
PRETTY SURE YOU'LL FIND
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BARKING]
HMM. I'LL LOOK,
BUT THAT'S ALL.
I'M NOT PROMISING I'LL BUY IT
NOT TILL I'VE SEEN IT.
RIGHT, FINE.
[AQUARIUM FILTER BUBBLING]
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
HUH?
UH... AAH!
DID YOU RUN OUT OF FUNDS FROM
ALL THE PLASTIC SURGERY, HAKIM?
YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG!
I'M NOT--
DON'T MOVE.
PRETTY SLIPPERY, THE WAY
YOU CHANGE YOUR FACE AROUND,
- BUT YOU'RE NOT
SLIPPING OUT ON ME.
- WHAT?
NOW, BOTH OF YOU,
STOP THIS FUNNY BUSINESS.
MY BABIES ARE VERY
SENSITIVE. PLEASE!
OPEN THE CASE.
WHY ME?
THIS IS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
DO IT!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
[GROANS]
ALL RIGHT. I'LL OPEN IT.
[CLICKING]
UH, UH...
[SECOND LATCH CLICKS OPEN]
[GROANING]
AH! MMM!
OOH!
OOH?
A WELSH CORGI.
THEY'RE VERY SWEET, BUT
YOU SEE THEM EVERYWHERE.
I'M AFRAID THEY'RE
HARDLY A RARE BREED.
WELL, HOW MUCH IS
IT WORTH? I MEAN...
YOU COULD SELL
HIM FOR ABOUT... TWO.
- 200?
- NO, NO. TWO WOOLONGS.
NO WAY!
YES WAY, AND IF
YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
TAKE HIM BACK,
EAT THE POOR THING.
IT IS JUST A PUPPY.
SORRY ABOUT THE GUN THING.
HAVE A NICE DAY, HUH?
UH, UH...
DIDN'T REALLY WANT
THAT PEKING DUCK ANYWAY.
AT LEAST GIVE ME 200.
SORRY.
- 150.
- NO CAN DO.
120-- OOH!
ZERO.
I'LL TAKE IT BACK.
OH, NOT AGAIN!
WHAT NOW?
[GROWLING]
[BARKING]
AAH!
[GUNSHOT]
[CRASH]
MY BABIES ARE
ALL RUNNING AWAY!
SOMEBODY, HELP! OHH!
- THERE IT IS.
- ALL RIGHT!
HMM?
UNH!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
HUH?
THAT WAS HAKIM.
WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON AROUND HERE?!
[SONG BEGINS]
♪ YOU SAID YOU
WANTED TO SEE PARIS ♪
♪ SO I TOOK YOU TO THE MOVIE ♪
♪ BON AMI OR SOMETHING
FRENCH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ THEN YOU SAID
YOU WERE EMBARRASSED ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I NEVER
BOUGHT YOU JEWELRY ♪
♪ TELEVISION SHOPPING
FIXED ALL THAT ♪
♪ FUNNY THING... ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU LATELY ♪
♪ WHEN I CALLED YOUR HOUSE
IT WASN'T YOU WHO TOLD ME ♪
♪ I HEARD IT ALL FROM YOUR DAD ♪
♪ I USED UP ALL MY MONEY ON YOU,
BABY, AND I WANT IT BACK ♪
SO, ARE YOU A BOUNTY HUNTER...
OR SOME ANIMAL RIGHTS CHUMP?
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
MAKE ME LAUGH, HAKIM
RISKING YOUR LIFE FOR A DOG
THAT'S ONLY WORTH
A FISTFUL OF WOOLONGS.
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
NOTHING BUT A GIGGLE,
BUT YOU'RE WORTH A BARRELFUL OF
WOOLONGS YOURSELF, MY FRIEND.
[GRUNTING]
[THROWING PUNCHES]
♪ I COULDN'T
TAKE YOU TO MIAMI ♪
♪ BUT TOOK YOU TO THE OCEAN
AND WE HAD SOME... ♪
NOT BAD, HAKIM.
[DOG BARKING]
- HUH?
- WHAT?
DAMN IT!
♪ LET ME THINK... ♪
AAH!
♪ IF I ADD UP
ALL YOU OWE ME... ♪
[SNARLING]
[BARKING]
AW, SHUT UP.
I'M NOT IN A GREAT MOOD
RIGHT NOW, ALL RIGHT?
[DOG WHINES]
HERE YOU GO, A NICE
LITTLE COLLAR, ALL RIGHT?
GOT A DOG INSTEAD
OF A DUCK, HUH?
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
WELL, I'VE GOT PLENTY.
THIS IS A WELSH CORGI
100% MONGREL.
100%?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL THE PERCENTS
THERE ARE.
DAMN! THIS WHOLE THING
GIVES ME A HEADACHE,
AND ALL BECAUSE OF
THIS WORTHLESS MUTT.
[CRUNCH]
AAAAHH!
THE DOG IS WORTHLESS, SPIKE,
BUT THE OWNER IS
WORTH A FORTUNE.
HUH?
YEAH, THINK ABOUT IT.
AND TRY TO MAKE FRIENDS WITH
THE POOCH, WOULD YOU?
[DOG WHINING]
I HATE KIDS AND PETS.
THEY'RE ALL A ROYAL
PAIN IN THE BUTT.
OH! I GOT SOMETHING!
WHOA! IT'S BIG!
ALL RIGHT!
HERE IT COMES.
PULL IT IN! COME ON!
COME ONAAAHH!
[CHILDREN WHIMPERING]
WHAT TIME IS IT?
[WHIMPERING]
IT'S-- IT'S 4:00,
RIGHT ON THE BUTTON.
JUST TWO MORE HOURS.
- AAAH!
WHO WAS THAT RUNNING WITH
HAKIM; ONE OF HIS BOYS?
SEEMS THAT WAY.
WE HAVE NO CLUES.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND IT.
IF IT FALLS INTO POLICE HANDS,
WE'RE IN VERY DEEP SHIT,
MY FRIEND.
SEEMS THAT WAY.
ALL THAT WORK,
THE EXPERIMENTS
IT WILL ALL BE FOR NOTHING
IF THIS GETS OUT IN THE OPEN.
SEEMS THAT WAY.
HE HAS NO IDEA
HOW MUCH BLOOD AND SWEAT
WE PUT INTO THAT DATA DOG.
WHY DON'T YOU DO
THIS PART OF IT?
COMPLAINING AGAIN.
DIDN'T YOUR GRANDMOTHER
EVER TELL YOU THAT A GOOD BOY
HAS TO FINISH WHAT HE STARTS?
MY GRANDMOTHER DIED
BEFORE I WAS BORN.
MY CONDOLENCES.
WE'VE GOT OUR GUY EXACTLY
WHERE WE WANT HIM, SPIKE.
FOR ONCE, JUST
STICK TO THE PLAN.
CODE NAME SNOOP.
PUT ME THROUGH.
IT'S ME.
YEAH, I HAD
A LITTLE TROUBLE.
NO, IT'S NOTHING
I CAN'T HANDLE.
[DOG BARKING]
HUH?
STOP, MIKEY! COME BACK!
COME ON!
I NEED TO RESCHEDULE
THE MEETING ONE MORE DAY.
NO, IT WASN'T A BIG DEAL.
I JUST...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IMPOSSIBLE?
WHY?
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
[CLICK]
UNH!
REALLY GREAT PLAN HERE, JET.
HEY, YOU!
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR, ISN'T THERE?
SOMETHING YOU NEED TO FIND.
WAIT! DON'T GO!
MY LITTLE PICO CAN HELP YOU
FIND THE OBJECT OF YOUR SEARCH.
YES, MY LITTLE PICO
KNOWS ALL ABOUT IT.
WELL, DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW WHERE IT IS OR NOT?
TIME'S RUNNING OUT,
MY FRIEND.
GOOD DOG.
WHEREVER YOU GO,
HAKIM WILL FOLLOW.
YEAH... AND I'LL BE
TRACKING EVERY MOVE.
THAT'S RIGHT
IT'S DOG EAT DOG.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE HAVE TO USE...
THE DOG WHISTLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT COULD MEAN.
IT'S VERY RISKY.
I DON'T CARE.
IT WILL DRAW ATTENTION.
IT'S OUR ONLY OPTION.
WE'RE READY TO GO.
THEN DO IT.
IS IT ON? I CAN'T HEAR IT.
IT'S TOO HIGH-PITCHED.
ONLY ANIMALS CAN PICK IT UP.
I KNEW THAT.
I WAS TESTING YOU.
WELL, HERE'S ANOTHER GREAT
MOMENT IN THE LEGEND OF SPIKE,
FAMOUS BOUNTY HUNTER
AND DOG WALKER.
HUH?
HMM.
IT'S THE... MOVING CARD.
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR IS ABOUT TO MOVE.
[ALL BARKING]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SOMETHING'S UPSETTING
MY BABIES! OH!
WAAH!
HEY, WAIT! COME BACK!
[DOG BARKING]
[ALL BARKING]
JET! HE GOT AWAY!
- HUH? YOU MEAN HAKIM?
- THE DOG!
IT'S CLOSE.
IT'S VERY CLOSE.
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
IS DRAWING NEARER.
IN FACT, IT IS HERE!
IT IS RIGHT HERE!
[DOGS BARKING]
WAIT A MINUTE! MY MONEY!
I'LL PAY YOU WHEN I'M RICH.
OH, NOT AGAIN.
[DOGS BARKING]
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
WHAT THE HELL? HAS EVERY DOG
GONE CRAZY OR WHAT, HUH?
[APPLAUSE]
ARE YOU HAPPY, DEAR?
EVERYTHING'S PERFECT.
HMM?
[ENGINE STARTS]
EXCUSE ME...
HAROLD!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
WHAT THE DEVIL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
HAKIM!
UNH!
YAAH! UNH!
[BOOM]
DAMN IT!
TIME FOR A DOG NAP.
HAKIM!
SPIKE!
HE'S HEADED FOR
THE CAUSEWAY.
TRYING TO OUTRUN ME, HUH?
I DON'T THINK SO.
NOW, DON'T GET
TOO HOTHEADED, SPIKE.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
HOTHEADED YET, JET.
THERE'S OUR MAN.
IT'S PAYBACK TIME, HAKIM.
[SNARLING]
[GUNFIRE]
HEY, BACK OFF!
THIS POOCHBAGGER IS MINE!
[SNARLING]
[BARK]
WHAT THE...
GET HIM!
GET OFF!
UHHH...
DAMN!
THIS IS WHY I HATE PETS!
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
[BANJOS PLAYING]
HI, AMIGOS. ALL 300,000 BOUNTY
HUNTERS IN THIS STAR SYSTEM!
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR "BIG SHOT,"
THE SHOW THAT TELLS
ALL ABOUT FUGITIVES.
SHUCKS, HOWDY!
THE BIG NEWS IS ABDUL HAKIM,
WHO CHOSE A FLASHY WAY
TO TURN HIMSELF IN LAST WEEK.
MMHMM, HE SURE DID!
BEFORE HIS CRIME SPREE
CAME TO A CRASHING HALT,
HE STOLE A MYSTERIOUS DATA DOG,
WHICH WAS DEVELOPED IN
AN ILLEGAL RESEARCH LAB.
WHOA! WHAT IS A DATA DOG?
IF I TOLD YOU THAT,
I'D HAVE TO KILL YOU.
BUT SERIOUSLY, THAT
INFORMATION IS CLASSIFIED,
BUT WE DO KNOW IT IS
A VERY CANNY CANINE.
COLLECTORS WILL PAY
A FORTUNE FOR IT.
WOW! FANCY THAT A
GENIUS HOUND DOG!
I'D LIKE TO OWN
A DOG LIKE THAT.
I'M AFRAID THIS ONE
DISAPPEARED WITHOUT A TRACE.
ANOTHER MYSTERY!
WHERE DID IT GO?
HA HA! NO ONE KNOWS,
BUT... SHUCKS, HOWDY!
IT'S TIME FOR A COMMERCIAL.
HMM. I DOUBT IT.
YOU KEEP MOPPING,
AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE,
FEED THE KOMODO DRAGONS.
WATCH YOUR FINGERS!
I AM GOING TO WORK
YOUR BUTT OFF!
[SIGH]
HEY!
[DOG BARKING]
GET DOWN! NO DOGS
ON THE TABLE.
THAT'S COLD!
AWW.
THAT'S WHY
I SAID I DIDN'T WANT
ANY STRAY
MONGREL MUTTS IN HERE!
BUT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO BROUGHT HIM HERE.
ANYWAY, WE'VE GOT TO
DO SOMETHING ABOUT THE TICKS.
TICKS NOW?
LET'S JUST SALT HIM AND EAT HIM.
TIME TO HIT THE ROAD.
SEE YOU NEXT TIME!
SAYONARA!
[GUNSHOT]
SHOW NO MERCY.
WHEN IT COMES
TO HIGH ROLLERS,
THAT'S THE WAY
THE GAME IS PLAYED.
THE BELL TOLLS EVEN
FOR THE GREAT ONES,
FOR THEY, TOO,
MUST FALL ONE DAY.
MONEY MAKES THE WORLD GO ROUND,
BUT BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
YOU CAN BE BURIED UNDER
A MOUNTAIN OF DEBT,
WANDERING THROUGH THE FARFLUNG
REACHES OF SPACE.
THAT'S WHERE I MET A COWBOY.
A STARDUST SESSION PLAYED
IN AN OFFKEY MELODY
"HONKY TONK WOMEN."