It's you, Kiritsugu.
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You really...
...came...
...to see me again.
Yes,
that's right.
Thank you.
The final thing I must do
is return this to you.
From here on out,
the one who will need Avalon is you.
When you begin your final battle,
I'm sure it will aid you.
You know...
I really am happy.
To love...
To be loved.
To have had a husband and daughter
for nine whole years.
You...
gave me everything...
All the happiness in the world,
that was never meant for me.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to show you more of the outside world.
No... It's good enough.
If any happiness remains, which I had to leave behind,
give it all to Ilya.
Your daughter...
Our beloved Ilya.
Someday, bring Ilya to this country.
Show her everything
I was never able to see.
The cherry trees.
The summer clouds...
I will.
Okay, I'll be back.
Yes.
Be careful.
My love...
Saber is heading to Rider's hideout, right?
Yes. She's on her way.
I'm going to kill Tohsaka Tokiomi.
If Rider and Saber fight,
there's a good chance Archer will appear there.
I'll hit him there.
You continue to watch Iri.
Understood.
Um... Kiritsugu.
You...
finally look like your old self...
I don't feel the presence of a Servant.
No barrier?
What is this?
Is that good?
Nope. It's awful.
Japanese food isn't that good.
You know where we are, right?
This is where I summoned you.
This is the place in Fuyuki which you are most attuned to, right?
You should be able to recover much faster.
I'm staying here all day.
Just sleeping, not doing a thing.
So take as much mana as you want, as long as you don't kill me.
It should help you recover.
If you noticed earlier, you should have mentioned it.
Finding out later that someone's been on to you the whole time is, well...
It's a bit embarrassing.
You idiot!
You should have just told me...
If you aren't at full strength when I need you,
I'll be the one in danger!
Why didn't you say anything?
I thought I could hold out a little longer...
But the fatigue from the river battle was greater than I expected.
Ultimately, your Noble Phantasm uses a ton of prana...
At first, I just ignored it.
I thought the reason it wasn't affecting me
was due to its efficiency.
Rider,
the prana that I should have supplied
actually came from your own reserves, right?
And you acted so recklessly twice...
Well, you know...
If you get involved when I start going all out,
it could endanger your life.
I'm fine with that...
This is a battle I started.
If I don't shed blood or make sacrifices
and yet end up winning, there's no point.
I just...
I want to prove it.
That I...
That even I...
...can win sometimes!
But, kid,
that only applies if the Grail truly exists.
You know, I once did something similar,
fought for something that may have never even existed.
Okeanos.
That's right.
I told them I'd show them Okeanos,
and they all believed in me and followed.
Many died...
All dreaming of Okeanos until the very end.
When I gained this era's knowledge, that really hit me.
I'd had no idea the land was round and closed.
What a bad joke.
But even so, when I saw the map, I had no choice but to accept it.
I'm done with letting people die for fairy tales.
Were the Grail's location certain,
I'd have no objection to you risking your life.
But unfortunately, it isn't.
Even so...
Even so, I...
I'm your Master!
Boy...
Learned to talk back, have you?
It's true, your Magic Circuits are more powerful than usual.
If I rest while the sun's out,
I'll be completely ready by nightfall!
And?
Ready? What do you plan to do next?
Hmm...
Let's begin with Saber.
At this rate, how much will you recover by tonight?
If I only use the Gordius Wheel for flight, there shouldn't be a problem.
However...
I think I'll only be able to use Ionian Hetairoi once more.
I see...
We should probably save it for the fight with Archer.
Then, Rider...
Why do you want to fight Saber?
I must defeat Saber.
As a Heroic Spirit, it is my responsibility.
What does that mean?
If I don't show that stupid girl
the right path, she'll never learn.
That would be too sad.
Well, do what you want.
I am the alienated.
The scorned.
The despised.
Who are you?
My name is unworthy of praise.
My body unworthy of envy.
I am the shadow, cast by the Heroic Spirits' light.
The darkness born in the shadow of a shining legend.
Thus, I hate.
Thus, I resent.
I feed on the cries of those who sink into darkness,
and curse those who shine so brightly.
You are the sacrifice!
Healing won't help me.
I'm going to die soon.
Damn it...
Really, what a pathetic finish, Kariya...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not blaming you.
Honestly, I never would have imagined that you'd last this long.
And so,
I shall give you the ace I've hid up my sleeve, kept secret for just such an occasion.
Now...
Looks like it's working well.
The worm I just gave you
was the first to feed on Sakura's purity.
How does it feel, Kariya?
For an entire year, it's been devouring the girl's life energy.
It's a magnificant prana source.
Now go and fight, Kariya.
Make good use of the life you've stolen from Sakura.
Use every ounce of your flesh and bone to acquire the Grail...
As if a failure like yourself even could...
Hey, Maiya...
Why do you fight for Kiritsugu?
Because I have nothing else.
I do not remember my family,
or even my own name.
Hisau Maiya was the name
on the first passport that Kiritsugu made for me.
All I remember
is that it was a terribly poor country.
The wars never ended.
There was no money to maintain the armies.
But each day, they continued to kill one another.
And then, someone had an idea.
Rather than conscript and train soldiers,
it was cheaper and faster to kidnap kids, then arm them.
Maiya, you...
Aim at the enemy; pull the trigger.
That was my sole function.
I threw everything else away.
The human part of me is already dead.
But the body continues to move...
Still working like it did before.
That is my life.
But Kiritsugu took me in anyway.
So however he wants to use me is fine.
And that is the reason I'm here.
In truth, Madam,
your passion surprised me, too.
You've been secluded in the castle where you were born,
knowing so little of the outside world.
So I can't imagine
why you would fight this hard for Kiritsugu's dream,
to change a world you've never really seen.
I...
That's right...
I cannot truly understand
Kiritsugu's ideals.
It's as you say.
I...
I know nothing of the world that
Kiritsugu longs to change.
All my ideals
are merely words that I learned from Kiritsugu.
But don't let him know that.
I've always told him he was doing the right thing.
I've told him those ideals were worth my life.
I've pretended to understand him.
Then, Madam,
have you no wish of your own?
A wish?
Yes, I do.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber
to win the Holy Grail.
You wish for the Third Magic to be attained,
as the Einzberns have always desired?
No.
What I desire is an end to conflict.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes true,
and fighting ceases everywhere...
The fight for the Grail here, in Fuyuki City,
should be no exception.
I hope for this fourth battle to be the final Holy Grail War.
For your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail,
it will be Ilya's turn next.
That is the destiny of an Einzbern homunculus.
So I wish to be the last.
If that comes to pass,
she'll be able to live out her life as a human being.
Maiya...
What will you do after Kiritsugu reaches his goal?
I don't expect to survive.
Even if I do, I'll have lost my reason to exist.
The world that Kiritsugu will create
has no place for me.
No, that isn't true.
You think so?
You must look for your real name and family!
Those aren't things you should forget.
You must remember them.
And make others remember.
So live, Maiya.
For my sake as well.
I'll do my best.
But that won't be until after the battle ends.
Right now, we must be cautious.
We must stay on guard, both he and I.
The one who died here...
was Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Really, you are...
Maiya!
Iri!
By my Command Seal, I order you, my puppet...
Saber,
return to the storehouse immediately!
Kiritsugu...
This is...
Maiya!
Saber?
Don't speak.
Hurry.
Follow him, outside...
Rider took Madam...
But then...
I'm fine.
And Kiritsugu will...
So, hurry.
Maiya,
please wait until Kiritsugu returns.
I shall bring Irisviel back.
Did Rider really...
Rider...
Yes, I understand.
You can't cry.
Save those tears for your wife...
You can't cry here...
You're weak.
So you can't cry yet.
You can't break...
I...
This morning, you finally looked like your old self.
You can't waver now...
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, your task...
is over.
Maiya.
Maiya...
Episode 20
Return of the Assassin
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
Where is Irisviel?
Don't forget... Tonight, at midnight.
And nothing can stop me!
Don't underestimate me,
King of Conquerors!
Because of him...
If it weren't for that man...
Oh, scary, scary.
Next Time:
Knight on Two Wheels
Are you happy now, Kariya?