I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Credit Roll of Fools
1887 A Study in Scarlet
1890 The Sign of Four
1892 The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
1893 The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes
1901 The Hound of the Baskervilles
1905 The Return of Sherlock Holmes
1914 The Valley of Fear
1917 His Last Bow
1920 The Mysterious Affair at Styles
1922 The Secret Adversary
1923 The Murder on the Links
1924 The Man in the Brown Suit
1925 The Secret of Chimneys
1926 The Murder of Roger Ackroyd
Whodunit Theater
The Mysteries of Tarot
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Tea Room Hifumi
A Scandal in Bohemia
The Red-Headed League
The Noble Bachelor
The Boscombe Valley Mystery
The Five Orange Pips
The Man With the Twisted Lip
The Blue Carbuncle
The Speckled Band
A Case of Identity
The Copper Beeches
The Illustrious Client
The Blanched Soldier
The Mazarin Stone
The Three Gables
The Sussex Vampire
The Three Garridebs
Thor Bridge
The Creeping Man
The Lion's Mane
The Veiled Lodger
The Red-Headed League
The Three Garridebs
The Man With the Twisted Lip
The Blanched Soldier
The Three Garridebs
The Noble Bachelor
The Five Orange Pips
The Speckled Band
A Case of Identity
The Three Gables
The Veiled Lodger
No. 31: How to handle violence?
No. 32: How many dead bodies?
One... 6 Two... 10 Three... 3 More
All of them... 2
A hundred... 1
Three... 3
Ineligible votes... 1
Puppet Show
Sleuth Theater
Come, great detectives!!
Can you solve this mystery?
"Mayuko has logged in."
"Please insert name here has logged in."
"Mayuko: Thank you very much."
"Mayuko: It's all because
I made the script like that."
"Please insert name here: It's okay."
"It may not have been the movie
you were hoping for, though."
"Mayuko: That's not true."
"Mayuko: What I was hoping for"
"Mayuko: was to cheer with
everyone when it was done."
"I have to say, you
really are something else"
"Nah, never mind."
"M-e-♪ has logged in."
"Please insert name here has logged in."
"Please insert name here: Hello."
"M-e-♪: Yoo-hoo."
"M-e-♪: Sounds like it went well."
"Please insert name here:
Thanks to you, Senpai."
"Please insert name here: However, I"
"Please insert name here: think I did
something inexcusable to him."
"♪: Do you really think that?"
"Please insert name here: It's no use trying to
bluff someone on the other side of the world, is it?"
"M-e-♪: Of course not."
"M-e-♪: So, no lying to someone
on the other side of the world."
"Lying, you say?"
"You didn't ask for my help because you
wanted to protect the scriptwriter, did you?"
"♪: The whole problem in the first place
was that the script was dull, right?"
"♪: You wanted to reject a script that fell flat
in a way that wouldn't hurt that girl, right?"
"♪: Well, it doesn't sound like
the dummy caught on, anyhow."
"I wasn't in"
"any position to"
"let the project"
"fail"
"I wasn't very well in any position
to let the project fail."
"Senpai?"
"M-e-♪ has logged out."
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Those Things Piled Up Endlessly