Ah...
Having the cameraman be the
seventh person was entertaining,
and the scene when all of the characters look
into the camera at once did have a lot of impact.
But...
The rope didn't feature in it
that way at all, did it?
W-Well, nothing's to say that
the rope was part of the setup...
If that's so, then why was
Hongo-senpai so adamant about it?
It's because it was critical
to the plot, isn't it?
Still, I could be wrong about that, too.
Anyhow, I was entertained
by that idea of yours.
That finale took me by surprise.
But I just didn't think the twist
fit in with the rest of the story.
Yeah...
Well, I have to get to my Manga Club.
See you tomorrow, Oreki.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Credit Roll of Fools
How could I have forgotten about that?
Did I unconsciously ignore it?
Did I distort the problem
to make it fit Kaito?
Hotaro...
Hotaro! Hey, hold up!
Hotaro!
Huh? What's the matter?
It's nothing. Did you want something?
Yeah, I kind of wanted to ask
you something. Where's Mayaka?
She said she was heading to Manga Club.
Well, this works out perfectly.
It looks like Chitanda-san left, too.
Meaning that this is something you
don't want Ibara or Chitanda to hear.
Well, yeah. I didn't want to bring
this up in front of the others.
So, what is it?
About that plot twist... did you mean
for it to be Hongo-senpai's idea?
Or was that just your idea?
It was Hongo's.
Oh.
Hotaro, that plot twist was
not Hongo-senpai's idea.
I don't know what the right answer is,
but I can say that that wasn't it.
You must have something
you're basing that on, right?
Yeah.
There's that critical of an
inconsistency, and I didn't see it?
It's not an inconsistency.
I'm not lying when I say
I thought it was good.
But it wasn't what
Hongo-senpai was thinking.
Meaning what?
Do you know what a "narrative trick" is?
A way to fool the reader by the way
the text is presented, right?
That's right.
Like in the movie, where the killer
is actually the cameraman:
that was a narrative trick.
Well, I suppose so.
Hotaro, what books did
the amateur Hongo-senpai
use to study how to write a mystery?
Holmes, right?
Right. Hongo-senpai hasn't
read anything but Holmes.
Now listen, Hotaro...
Narrative tricks don't exist
in the Holmes stories.
1887 A Study in Scarlet
1890 The Sign of Four
1892 The
Adventures of Sherlock Holmes
With very few exceptions,
1893 The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes
1901 The Hound of the Baskervilles
1905 The Return of Sherlock Holmes
narrative tricks began in Christie's era.
1914 The Valley of Fear
1917 His Last Bow
1920 The Mysterious
Affair at Styles
1922 The Secret Adversary
1923 The Murder on the Links
1924 The Man
in the Brown Suit
Which is to say after entering the 20th century.
1925 The Secret of Chimneys
1926 The Murder of Roger
Ackroyd
I don't know Hongo-senpai.
But I find it hard to imagine that
she's in Christie's league!
Personally, that movie
was right up my alley.
If that was your idea,
then I won't say anything.
But if you're passing it off
as Hongo-senpai's idea,
I have no choice but to say you're wrong.
Hold on a second. We don't know
what Hongo has ever read.
Maybe she came across that
narrative trick in some other book!
Or, hell, maybe she saw it in a movie...
Hotaro!
Do you really believe that?
If that's what you believe in
your heart, I'm okay with that.
That's all I wanted to say.
Well, I'll be going now.
What's the matter?
I thought you had already left.
Um, Oreki-san,
there's something I want
to talk to you about.
You, too?
You wanted to talk about the movie, right?
Yes.
You didn't like it, right?
I'm not saying that.
Don't hold back. Ibara and
Satoshi already talked to me.
They say that it wasn't what
Hongo intended. And I...
am beginning to think it isn't, either.
I don't think it is, either.
Would you mind telling me why?
The day is still young. Why don't
we go for a stroll along the river?
Oreki-san, do you know what it was
that had me curious about all this?
How the movie was going to
end up concluding, right?
That was the reason you came.
No. The truth is, I didn't care
how the movie ended.
That's why I thought that your
idea was a very good one.
Then what were you curious about?
I was curious about Hongo-san, the girl.
I thought this whole affair was
unusual, any way you cut it.
I didn't understand why Irisu-san didn't
ask someone close to Hongo-san,
someone like maybe Eba-san, what the
setup of the plot was supposed to be.
In order to let Hongo have her rest, right?
If you have something on
your mind, then speak up.
I think that Hongo-san had a clear view
of her script right up to the end.
Even if she had taken ill halfway through,
I think they could have still asked her.
And if she really wasn't
in any condition for that,
I think that Eba-san, who says
that she is her good friend,
would be so angry that she could not
put up with the rest of the class.
At least enough so that she
wouldn't escort us to them.
Yeah...
Did Hongo-san really not tell
anyone what her plot setup was?
Are you saying that Hongo intended
to write the script herself?
No, the Hongo-san that we heard about
was too faint-hearted for that.
I don't think that a girl like that
would have the backbone to
keep her classmates waiting.
Then maybe she wasn't confident
about her conclusion.
That's something that I considered, too.
But the others in her class are fine folks.
I doubt that they would
slam Hongo-san's idea.
Fine folks, huh?
If that was the conclusion that
Hongo-san came up with,
I'm sure she would have had the
confidence to tell the others.
That's how good it was.
But I don't think it was that,
which is why she couldn't tell them.
And if that's the case, then what was it
exactly that pushed Hongo-san too far?
That's what I wanted to know.
And I think that the regrets, the screams that
Hongo-san had about having to stop writing
before she finished it are
hidden somewhere inside!
But the movie we saw didn't
answer that question.
If it appears that I didn't enjoy it,
I'm sure that's the reason why.
While I was trying to discern
the truth about this movie,
Chitanda was thinking about Hongo.
What about me?
I saw the script as a mere literary
problem to be solved, didn't I?
Whodunit Theater
The stage setting...
The featured characters...
The murder case...
The setup...
Whodunit Theater
The killer is among you!
I never even considered that Hongo's
feelings might be included in the script.
Hell of a detective I was.
But I'm not blaming you
or anything, Oreki-san.
That resolution scene was quite surprising.
It may not have been what
Hongo-san was thinking,
but I do think that it ended up
being a good ending.
It's not as though I was
brought on to be a scriptwriter.
What I did do was a bang-up job
of getting everything wrong.
But what did I get wrong?
I can't get my head around it.
No flashes of insight, either.
Who really cares, anyway?
They're already done shooting it.
However hard I think
about it now, it's academic.
Thinking it through logically is a waste
of time, and not energy-conserving.
Aw, damn it!
Ow...
Maybe reading a book
will get my mind off of it.
The Mysteries of Tarot
So Sis has a book like this one?
Let's see...
"The Empress... maternal affection,
a fertile mind, sensitivity...?"
From what I've seen, that's not
at all a match for Irisu.
So, Ibara was "Justice."
"Equality, righteousness, fairness..."
Mm-hm, not necessarily wrong.
Satoshi was "The Magician."
"Initiative, originality, interest," huh?
Hm. And Chitanda was "The Fool."
"Curiosity, impulse to
action..." That follows.
Now for me...
"Inner fortitude, fighting
spirit, bonds...?"
What is this? That doesn't
fit me at all, does it?
Why would Satoshi pick this for me?
"'Strength' is represented by a picture of a
ferocious lion being controlled by a kind woman."
Satoshi! No, I am not controlled by them!
Not Sis, and not Chitanda, and not Irisu!
Maybe I am "Strength."
It's quite fascinating.
Is he using the meanings of the Tarot
illustrations to imply something about me?
That would be just like Satoshi.
It's not like he changed my viewpoint...
Change my viewpoint...?
Hey.
It's been a little while, hasn't it?
Hi there.
The movie turned out well, didn't it?
All because of your help. Thank you.
Listen, this Saturday,
we're having a launch party.
Won't you join us?
I won't be going.
Hm?
Irisu-senpai, I need to talk to you.
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
Tea Room Hifumi
One Yunnan tea.
One green tea.
Please enjoy yourselves.
So, what would you like to talk about?
The last time we had tea here,
you said I had skill, remember?
Certainly.
What skill did you mean?
Are you going to make me say it?
The skill of deduction...
That's not true, is it?
I wasn't your detective; I was
your mystery writer, wasn't I?
What gave it away?
Holmes.
Is it okay if I spoil some
of the Holmes stories?
Yes, I don't mind.
There were some notes tucked away
in the novels that Hongo-san read.
I copied some of them down on this.
At first,
A Scandal in Bohemia
The Red-Headed League
The Noble Bachelor
The Boscombe Valley Mystery
The Five Orange Pips
The Man With the Twisted Lip
I thought she was picking out ideas that she could use.
The Blue Carbuncle
The Speckled Band
A Case of Identity
The Copper Beeches
The Illustrious Client
The Blanched Soldier
The Mazarin Stone
The Three Gables
The Sussex Vampire
The Three Garridebs
Thor Bridge
The Creeping Man
The Lion's Mane
The Veiled Lodger
However, I was mistaken.
From what Satoshi told me,
The Red-Headed League
The Three
Garridebs
The Red-Haired League and
The Three Garridebs had the same plot.
So why did Red-Haired
League get a triangle,
and Three Garridebs get a double-circle?
I found out from asking Satoshi about their content
The Man With the Twisted Lip
The Blanched Soldier
The Three
Garridebs
that the double-circled stories are
ones where the characters survive,
The Noble Bachelor
The Five Orange Pips
The Speckled Band
A Case of Identity
The Three Gables
The Veiled Lodger
while in the ones marked with an X, they die.
Here is my interpretation.
Hongo wasn't taking into
account the plotlines.
She preferred the happy endings,
and disliked the tragedies,
particularly the stories where people died.
Once I thought of it in that way,
a number of things made more sense.
One was the small amount of blood.
Another was the unusual
outcome of the questionnaire.
Outcome of the questionnaire?
So you managed to come by this, did you?
No. 31: How to handle violence?
No. 32: How many dead bodies?
They were generous enough
to let me borrow it.
So, regarding the questionnaire...
No. 32: How many dead bodies? One... 6 Two... 10 Three...
3 More
Having over 100 people die would be impossible.
All of them... 2
A hundred... 1
There are
only about 30 people in the class, after all.
Yet it still got one eligible vote.
Three... 3
Ineligible votes... 1
So then, what is this
ineligible vote, here?
A vote for there being
zero dead bodies, right?
That was the vote that Hongo cast, right?
No one was supposed to die in her script.
I'm impressed.
However, her classmates adlibbed
and added in violence.
I heard that Hongo didn't
come to the shoot.
And most of all, it doesn't say
in the script that Kaito died.
But in the actual film...
Yes, indeed. That arm was quite well-made.
That's something that Ibara said, too.
From any angle you look
at it, Kaito was dead.
From this point on is just what
I imagine. I don't have any proof.
But, Senpai, I can't help but say it.
Hongo couldn't bring herself to
tell her classmates to reshoot it,
since it deviated from her script.
She was too timid and earnest.
I think that she felt guilty about
ignoring the questionnaire tally.
And so, Irisu-senpai,
that's when you stepped in.
The way things were headed,
Hongo would end up as the villain.
You set Hongo up to fall ill,
leaving the script unfinished.
You then got your classmates together,
and held a deduction meeting.
But in fact, what it was
was a scriptwriting contest.
Once you discovered that
everyone's script was poor,
you dragged us into it, too.
No one even... Not even I realized
that I was doing your writing!
That's because our viewpoint
had been changed by you.
Then, you swapped my creation
for Hongo's script,
so that she got off without being hurt.
Isn't that right?
I haven't yet said you were wrong.
You said something to me, remember?
That when people are capable
and they don't recognize it,
it's caustic to those who are incapable?
You have to be kidding, right?
You don't give a damn about the
feelings of those who are incapable.
All that you look at is the
bottom line. Am I wrong?
Is something the matter with that?
Then, when you said that I have skill,
was that all for Hongo's sake?!
When you said that everyone should be aware
of who they were, was that a lie, too?!
I did not mean it sincerely.
If you wish to call it a lie,
that is up to you.
I am relieved to hear that.
Puppet Show
Sleuth Theater
Come, great detectives!!
Can you solve this mystery?
Mayuko has logged in.
Please insert name here has logged in.
Mayuko: Thank you very much.
Mayuko: It's all because
I made the script like that.
Please insert name here: It's okay.
It may not have been the movie
you were hoping for, though.
Mayuko: That's not true.
Mayuko: What I was hoping for
Mayuko: was to cheer with
everyone when it was done.
I have to say, you really
are something else
Nah, never mind.
M-e-♪ has logged in.
Please insert name here has logged in.
Please insert name here: Hello.
M-e-♪: Yoo-hoo.
M-e-♪: Sounds like it went well.
Please insert name here:
Thanks to you, Senpai.
Please insert name here: However, I
Please insert name here: think I did
something inexcusable to him.
♪: Do you really think that?
Please insert name here: It's no use trying to bluff
someone on the other side of the world, is it?
M-e-♪: Of course not.
M-e-♪: So, no lying to someone
on the other side of the world.
Lying, you say?
You didn't ask for my help because you
wanted to protect the scriptwriter, did you?
♪: The whole problem in the first place
was that the script was dull, right?
♪: You wanted to reject a script that fell flat
in a way that wouldn't hurt that girl, right?
♪: Well, it doesn't sound like
the dummy caught on, anyhow.
I wasn't in
any position to
let the project
fail
I wasn't very well in any position
to let the project fail.
Senpai?
M-e-♪ has logged out.
What?
Oh, nothing.
"I am curious what kind of script
Hongo-san thought up," right?
Huh? No, it's not that.
What then? This isn't like you.
This isn't like me? Yes, you're right.
Oreki-san, this isn't like you, either.
Not like me, huh?
Hmph.
Well, let me ask, like me.
I am curious what kind of script
Hongo-san thought up.
Oreki-san, please tell me.
I can only imagine,
but by assuming Kaito isn't dead,
it solves the locked-room problem.
Konosu is the culprit, and the
entry point is the window.
Huh? But the window was...
The window in the right-side sitting room.
There are two of them,
so it doesn't matter which.
Konosu uses the rope to sneak in,
chases after Kaito, and knifes him.
One blow, not enough to kill him.
Then she uses the rope to climb
to the second floor again,
and meets up with everyone
looking nonchalant.
That's all.
Ah, that must be why Hongo-san
wished Konosu-san luck.
Huh? But what about the seventh person
that Hongo-san was looking for?
Yeah, they turned up, even in
the unfinished version.
But it was only those first
six who ever appeared.
The cast doesn't necessarily
just consist of the actors.
There was a narrator, too, right?
Ah, that's right!
Then, why was the door to the room
that Kaito-san was in locked?
Kaito went to stage left wing
on his own, and locked the door.
Why did he do that?
Normally, it would be to keep
the culprit from pursuing him,
but that's probably not it.
Ah...
What's wrong?
Oh, it just seems like I understand
Hongo-san's feelings a little bit better.
Oh.
Most likely, after Kaito-san is stabbed,
he talks to Konosu-san,
and asks her why she stabbed him.
Then, to cover for Konosu-san,
he sends her back up,
then goes to stage left wing
on his own, where he collapses.
Huh? But then, how does he explain
away the fact that he is hurt?
The injury is simple.
There was glass scattered around the room.
Oh, now that you mention it, that's right!
He could say that he cut himself
on the glass when he fell.
So that's how the story went.
Though we'll never know
why Konosu stabs Kaito,
nor the reason why Kaito forgives her.
That will remain a mystery
until Hongo tells someone.
I guess there's no getting
around that, is there?
Why would someone stab another?
Why would the person who was
stabbed let their attacker go?
I'm very curious as to how Hongo-san
was trying to depict that.
By the way...
Yes?
Did you know anything else
about this whole incident?
Huh? No, I didn't know anything.
Why do you ask?
You weren't convinced by any of
the other detectives' theories.
That's not the way you usually are.
Was your empathy for
Hongo the only reason?
Oh, I get you. Well, um...
Please don't laugh at this, okay?
Okay.
I think that Hongo-san and I are alike.
Ah, this is a little embarrassing.
The truth is,
I don't like stories where
people die, either.
That is like you.
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Those Things
Piled Up Endlessly."
Those Things Piled Up Endlessly