It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I believed in the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
I wished for a very small feeling
to reach its destination.
The beginning of the journey
must always be so sad,
but I'm sure the feelings
have gotten across.
So I'm sure goodbye is
the word that begins something.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
Please, everyone!
Hurry up and escape!
Fate!
Fate! Fate!
Fly! Over here!
Call My Name
Looks like the earthquake is over.
You're right!
The Garden's destruction is complete.
Everything has been absorbed
into the imaginary number plane.
The dimensional tremor is ending.
There are no dimensional faults.
Roger.
Escaping at Speed Three.
Returning to our patrol course.
Where's Fate?
She's in the brig with Aruf.
Since she is a key witness
in this incident...
I'm sorry, but she will be
detained for a while.
But that's... Ouch!
Nanoha, stay still!
This incident was a major case,
where one mistaken step
might have caused the creation
of a dimensional faulit.
The Time-Space Administration
Bureau has to be very careful
about the treatment
of all involved parties.
You understand that, right?
Yeah.
Amy, do it over!
Darn.
And so, all sorts of things
came to an end.
From the day that I met
Yuuno until today...
Now that everything's over, it seems
like it all happened in an instant.
We spent several days
aboard the Arthra,
until the aftershocks of the
dimensional tremor subsided.
Rice bowl...
Since then...
You demonstrated outstanding
service in the resolution of this case.
Even if it's a bit informal,
I'd like to award you for
your distinguished service.
Miss Nanoha Takamachi,
and Mr. Yuuno Scrya,
thank you!
Chrono, what's going
to happen to Fate now?
Though she had her reasons,
it's an undeniable fact
that she was part of a conspiracy
in meddling with the dimensions.
It's a serious crime.
Usually, you get locked up for
several centuries, if not more.
That can't be!
However!
The situation is rather special,
and it's clear that
she wasn't party to the dimensional
crimes of her own will.
What we have left is to figure out
how to get the higher-ups
to understand those facts.
But I'm pretty confident
on that score,
so you don't have to worry at all.
Chrono...
The Time-Space Administration
Bureau isn't a group
of cold-hearted people who'd pin
a crime on a girl who knew nothing,
and was just doing her best
to grant her mother's wish.
Chrono... Can it be that you're
actually a really kind person?
What...
That was just stating
the obvious as an Enforcer!
There were no personal
feelings involved!
You don't have to be embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed!
What?! Don't laugh!
The dimensional tremor aftershocks
will be subsiding soon.
I think we can get back to your
world by tomorrow, Miss Nanoha.
That's great!
However, the route to Midchilda
hasn't stabilized quite yet.
It looks like that will take some time.
I see.
A few months, maybe half a year...
It looks like it will take that long
before we can cruise safely.
I see.
Well, my clan is full of people
who wander all over the world
in search of archaeological ruins,
so there really isn't a definite
necessity for me to hurry back.
But I can't really have you host me
on this ship for that long...
Then you can stay at my house,
like you have been!
Is that all right, Nanoha?
Yeah!
As long as you're fine with it, Yuuno.
Then, well...
Um, please take good care of me!
Sure!
Geez, it's because you slept so much!
But I was pulling so many all-nighters!
I'm still sleepy.
The place called Alhazard
that she was aiming for...
You know of it, right, Yuuno?
Yes, I've heard of it before.
They say it existed in previous
centuries, by the old calendar.
The land where many spells that
have been lost now still rest.
But they also say
that it fell into a dimensional fault
long ago, and fell to ruins.
Hey there!
They say that there is no wish
you can leave ungranted
using the powers of the
secret spells of Alhazard,
with all sorts of magic
in its ultimate state.
Magic that can turn back time and
space, and even rewrite the past.
Magic that can bring back to the living
a life that has been lost.
Those were the things
she wanted, right?
Yes...
But everyone who learns
magic knows for a fact
that turning back time and
raising the dead is impossible.
That is why, seeking
both of those ideals,
she could only rely on
such a fairy-tale legend.
She had no choice but to rely on it.
But a mage of that level was
risking her life in that search.
Perhaps she really had found
the path to Alhazard.
Though there's no way
for us to know now.
I'm sorry, this mealtime story
has gotten quite long.
Let's finish our meals
before they get cold.
I'm sure this will be your last meal
aboard the Arthra, Nanoha.
Yeah...
If parting ways makes you lonely,
you should honestly just
come out and say it.
Chrono, you're so shy!
What?!
Nanoha, you can always
come by and visit us, okay?
Yes! Thank you very much!
Amy! The Arthra is not a playground!
Well now, it's all right.
When our mission is to patrol,
we're always full of idle time!
Ca... Captain! You as well?!
And the morning where Yuuno
and I were going home...
Well... Thank you so much for
everything you did this time.
We appreciated your support.
I'll inform you of Fate's treatment
when it's been decided.
It's all right, I'll make sure that
nothing bad happens to her.
Yeah... Thanks.
Yuuno, when you want to
go back, please contact us.
I'll let you use our gate.
Yes! Thank you very much!
Then, I guess we're
about ready to go?
Yes!
Then...
I'll see you again, Chrono,
Miss Amy, Miss Lindy!
Should we go home now, Yuuno?
Sure.
I'm home!
Nanoha!
And what comes back
is my everyday life.
It's the same as it had always been,
but adding everything
that has happened,
Mom, I'm hungry!
but adding everything
that has happened,
Mom, I'm hungry!
everyday life is just a little bit
different from before.
Welcome home.
Were you a good girl?
Yeah!
Nanoha!
I'm home! I came back!
The time that you're
engrossed in something,
after it's all over, seems like
a fleeting moment...
But in my heart,
it surely remains true.
How we met... How desperate
I was... All sorts of things.
It's been a while since
I slept in my own bed!
Yuuno, you should rest up tonight too!
Right.
Thanks for all the hard work,
Raising Heart!
Thank you for all the
hard work, Nanoha.
The one thing that's
still on my mind...
About that girl with the gentle eyes,
that must surely be very kind.
Several days later...
Incoming Call: Time-Space
Administration Bureau
Yes, this is Nanoha!
Really?!
Yeabh, it's been officially decided on
a few moments ago.
Fate will be transferred
over to headquarters,
and there she will face
questioning and a trial.
Fate will probably - no, almost
definitely - be innocent.
Everything will be all right.
Because Chrono was working
overtime to gather all the evidence.
Amy! You don't have to mention
unnecessary information like that!
Thank you, Chrono!
The questioning, trial, and everything
else will take quite a bit of time.
But, before that...
Yeah...
Yeah!
I'll be right there!
What's up, Nanoha?
Fate is going to be transferred
to headquarters for a while.
But before that, I can see her
for just a little bit!
I see.
She's saying that
she wants to see me!
Fate!
There isn't much time, but
sit down and have a talk for a while.
We'll be over there.
Thanks!
Thank you.
There were so many things
I wanted to talk to you about.
But it's funny.
When I saw your face, Fate,
I forgot all of them.
L.. Let's see...
I can't put it into words well, either.
But I was really happy.
That you looked at me
so straight-forwardly.
Yeah! I thought that it would be
great if we could be friends!
But today, you have to head out
right after this, right?
That's true. It will be
a pretty long trip.
But I can see you again, right?
It's a bit sad, but I can finally
begin to be my own self.
I had you come here so that
I could give you an answer.
The words that you told me...
That you wanted to be my friend.
Yeah, yeah!
If it's possible for me...
if you're okay with me...
But I don't know what
I should be doing.
So I want you to tell me.
How do you become a friend?
That's easy.
It's really easy to become friends.
Call my name.
In the beginning,
that's all you have to do.
Not "you" or "hey, you"
or anything like that.
Look directly at the person's eyes,
and clearly call them by their name.
I'm Nanoha Takamachi!
Call me Nanoha!
Nanoha...
Yeah! That's it!
Yeah...
Nanoha!
Yeah!
Thank you, Nanoha.
Yeah...
Nanoha...
Yeah!
Your hands are so warm, Nanoha.
There's something that I figured out.
When a friend is crying,
you're sad in the same way.
Fate!
Thank you, Nanoha.
We'll part for now, but I'm sure
we'll see each other again.
When that happens, can I
call you by your name again?
Yeah, yeah!
When I want to see you,
I'm sure to be calling your name.
So Nanoha, I want you
to call for me too.
If something is
troubling you, Nanoha...
I'm sure that this time,
I will save you, Nanoha.
Your girl over there...
Nanoha...
She sure is a good girl.
Fate is smiling so much right now.
It's time. Are you about done?
Fate!
This is all I have that I can use
as a token of our memories.
Then, I should too.
Thank you, Nanoha.
Fate...
I'm sure once again...
Yeah! I'm sure once again...
Thank you!
Miss Aruf, you stay well too!
Thanks for everything,
Nanoha, Yuuno.
Well then, I'm on my way too.
See you later, Chrono!
Yeah.
Bye-bye, see you later...
Chrono...
Miss Aruf...
Fate!
Nanoha?
Yeah!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, don't look down as
you walk, it's all right
The courage that you handed to me
that day is still in my hands
Nanoha!
The courage that you handed to me
that day is still in my hands
Coming!
Each time I blink,
more kindness is born
See, this love is something I want
to nurture always, forever
Make a little wish
Wearing the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep glimmering with
a twinkle and keep on as your energy
Make a little wish
On rainy days and dawns
when I couldn't fall asleep
Because you were here with me,
I was able to smile my best
Just like this
Whenever we're apart, I still have
something I can believe in
See, our hearts are always,
surely together as one
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
Let's turn them into warm tears,
and make them spices for smiles
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic