I wonder...
what they're doing right now.
There were seven men who survived through rather grand days...
at the bottom of the cauldron of Hell,
inside a cell, fifty years ago.
The things that supported them...
were courage, guts, and their bond.
They placed their hopes upon the seven-colored rainbow and swore to survive.
You can't make out the text anymore,
but the dream which they held
was undoubtedly carved in this tree.
July, 1955
How is it?
Does it taste good?
Really?
She likes it!
Pardon us!
Aren't they criminals?
They're criminals!
This is blasphemy.
This is a public bus for God's sake.
Look away, Hana.
My doll!
He even tried to steal from a kid?!
Have they no shame?
Really...
Thank you very much!
Hey, you!
What the hell were you thinking?
You bastards have no right even to touch another person's belongings!
Ten years after Japan lost the war, the nation was still in poverty,
and the ones who were affected the most by the war the adults waged...
Sign: Shonan Special Disciplinary School
were those without power, like seniors, women, and children.
With empty stomachs and scarred hearts, the six youngsters were placed in a special disciplinary school.
The sight was as though...
fallen leaves were being swallowed up into a whirlpool.
Take a bow!
These are the six new guys.
Dr. Sasaki, if you will!
I'm Sasaki, the doctor in charge.
First and foremost, you must be wary of your health here.
I'll be performing an inspection right now...
to see if you have hemorrhoids or parasites,
not to mention if you're hiding any weapons.
Is that okay?
Don't worry.
It won't take long.
Now...
Let's start with you, big guy.
Wow, I'm quite surprised.
I didn't know you maggots could actually feel shame.
Hey!
Move! You fucking fat-ass!
Please, that's enough, Inspector Ishihara.
I cannot allow you to harm these precious children.
Now, next...
You, with the blue eyes.
You're next.
Subjected to a sham inspection,
the youngsters had no way to refuse,
and had a glass rod driven up their anuses.
After such treatment, none of them could maintain their resolve,
and they were stripped of the will to resist.
At the time, they must have been going through something unfathomable.
However...
this was only their beginning at the bottom of the cauldron of Hell.
COMPOUND TWO, CELL SIX
Ask the guy already in there about what will happen now.
Got it?
So...
what do we need to do?
Hey, old-timer.
Why don't you introduce yourself instead of showing us your back?
I don't speak with kids or monkeys.
Say that again?!
You're all just fucking kids full of pride,
even though you've already fallen so low.
Or...
are you indeed just monkeys?
You better shut that mouth.
What about you?
Aren't you also a shithead who's fallen so low?
Well?
Then as fellow shitheads, no one would mind any of us killing each other, right?
Do you even realize the situation, old-timer?
There's no way in hell you could win against the six of us!
What's so funny, bastard?!
True.
No matter how many of you shitheads die, no one's gonna give a damn.
Dammit...
You morons...
seem to need a good fight to learn a thing or two.
Come and get me.
Is he... a boxer?
A boxer?
So what?
I won't...
by any means...
be underestimated anymore!
What's wrong?
You scared?
I'll fucking kill you!
Minakami Mario, age seventeen, nickname Mario.
Minakami Mario （17）
When Mario's teacher attempted an act of violence towards a female student,
Mario inflicted grave injuries on him
that required three months of recovery.
Damn it!
Tohyama Tadayoshi （17）
Tohyama Tadayoshi, age seventeen, nickname Soldier.
Detained for acts of violence and false imprisonments.
He ruthlessly struck his mother's boyfriend, seriously injuring the man.
Maeda Noboru, age sixteen, nickname Turtle.
Maeda Noboru （16）
Detained for theft, con, dine-and-ditch,
and many other crimes which could not be fully investigated during his detention.
Goddammit!
Yokosuka Jou, age sixteen, nickname Joe.
Yokosuka Jou （16）
Detained for violence and improper intergender relationships.
He inflicted injuries requiring three months of recovery on the person who attempted to violate him.
Matsu'ura Mansaku, age seventeen, nickname Cabbage.
Matsu'ura Mansaku （17）
Detained for violence and underage drinking.
He performed an act of violence while drunk, leaving the victim with grave injuries.
Nomoto Ryuji, age seventeen, nickname Uncovered.
Nomoto Ryuji （17）
Detained for con, usurpation, and theft.
He frequently committed crimes in shopping centers.
All they could believe in was themselves.
This was survival of the fittest.
Losing was not an option.
What's wrong, kiddies?
Where did your guts go?
Kill me.
Kill me now.
It's not like... living will do me any good.
Um...
Please... take this and spare me.
A cigarette?
Yes.
Quite a mess you made here.
It would've been better if one or two of you had just died.
Under normal circumstances, you would all be sent to the isolation chamber for fighting,
but today's your first day, so...
I'll show you right here what happens to those who break the rules or talk back to us.
Take a seat.
Hey, are you deaf?
Take a fucking seat!
Now, you six...
watch carefully!
You shithead!
Now, it's your turn to beat him!
Don't be a bunch of softies!
He hit you!
Now hit him back!
No one cares about his life!
Do it!
N-No.
Come on!
Do it, dammit!
Do it!
Hey!
You do it!
I can't.
You bastards...
You won't do as I say?!
Stop!
S-Stop.
They... did nothing wrong.
You...
That's enough, Inspector Ishihara!
D-Dr. Sasaki.
Didn't I tell you before?
You mustn't harm the children.
How many times must I tell you?
We need to take better care of them.
The rain's finally gone.
Oh, you wiped the blood off me.
Thanks.
Sure...
Oh, yeah...
Hey, four-eyes.
Hey, you.
Go keep watch.
Keep watch?
Be on the lookout, you know?
Use this.
If a guard comes, tap your foot once.
Got it?
Um...
May I ask... what your name is?
This is why you're a fucking kid!
When you ask someone their name, it's common courtesy to tell them your name first!
I-I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Here.
Hurry, take a puff.
Don't take all of it for yourself though.
Now, everyone!
Tell me your names!
Oh, sure...
Here.
You're the last guy.
I'll keep watch, so make it quick.
You think you're our boss now?
What the hell do I gain from bossing you dumb kids around?
Don't you think...
that I know what you've gone through outside?
Go on!
Make it quick.
It's burning away.
It's good...
My name's Sakuragi.
Sakuragi Rokurouta.
Nice to meet you.
Let's hope that by summer, two years from now...
we'll be out on the streets.
This was how these six met Sakuragi Rokurouta,
whom they referred to as Bro.
Bro was strong, yet benevolent.
He had the heart of a mature man, something the six youngsters weren't accustomed to.
However...
in this place, the rainbows in their hearts were but momentary illusions.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Escape...
It gives the impression of hopping away, thus everyone refers to it as "rabbit."
Joe runs...
He runs to see his sister.