What's wrong?
Nothing...
I just finally finished the book
I've been reading all this time.
I bought it back at that mall...
But I finished it a lot sooner than I expected.
So, what was it about?
Oh, um...
It's a foreign book that
takes place during a war.
It's about some children who lose their home
in a fire, and go traveling with their dog.
The ending is really painful to read, though.
It's a sad story, then?
Yes, the dog...
I'd read the translated version already,
so I knew it was coming, but...
Of course the original would end the same way.
I see...
It was so nice out yesterday,
but today, it looks like it'll rain.
Yes...
Yuuri-senpai, you always seem
so melancholy on rainy days.
It was raining the day we lost Megu-nee.
It was when we were first
putting up the barricade.
Kurumi, Yuki-chan, Megu-nee,
and I worked together,
gradually expanding our safe
zone beyond the rooftop
to the point where we could
actually manage to live here.
Maybe that made us careless.
It started to rain that evening...
We didn't understand much
about them at the time.
Before we knew it, they had poured into
the school building and surrounded us.
If Megu-nee hadn't protected us, we'd all be...
That was when Yuki-chan started
acting the way she does.
Will we be okay today?
There've been more and more of them lately.
You've noticed it too, Miki-san?
Yes.
On the day when they first appeared,
school had just let out,
so there weren't many students on the grounds.
But as time has passed, the ones who
had gone home are returning here,
driven by their memories of coming
to school when they were alive.
Everyone really loved this school.
Huh?
It's like Yuki-senpai said.
We all come to school because we love it here.
I don't remember liking school all that much...
But that may be true.
Let's all graduate together!!
Write 100 pages each!
I can't write that much!
Regardless, we can't stay here forever.
Even with water and power,
there's only so much food.
We need to at least decide on
a plan, a course of action.
Do we, um... need to reinforce
the barricade or anything?
We've used just about all the
desks and chairs we can,
and we're out of boards and nails, too.
Don't worry.
All of our hopes and Megu-nee's
love went into that barricade.
It won't break that easily.
Morning.
Morning, Yuki-chan.
Good morning.
You're up early for once.
Are you hungry?
That doesn't mean you can eat
Taroumaru's food, Senpai.
No, I just noticed that Taroumaru
wasn't in his bed when I woke up.
House of Taroumaru
Only his collar was lying there,
so I thought he might be in here.
Taroumaru
School Living Club
#10
Rainy Day
It's raining.
It is?
Yeah.
All the sports teams are heading for cover.
Very few vitamins left
Taroumaru!
Breakfast!
What's Taroumaru up to?
Normally he'd smell the
food and rush right over.
Yeah...
What could he like more than food?
Maybe he's on a date?
There are no girl dogs around here.
He's too smart for his own good.
We put that collar on as tight as we could.
I'm going to look for him.
I don't want him to get lost.
Me, too!
It's raining, and he'll catch
a cold if he gets too wet.
Okay, let's go find him.
What if he really left the
school building, though?
It'll be fine.
He's a smart dog. He wouldn't go
anywhere dangerous for no reason.
You and Yuki can focus on this floor.
'Kay!
Right.
I'll check the other floors.
You'll be okay alone?
I'll be fine.
But it's raining today.
I know. I won't do anything reckless.
He's one high-maintenance pup, though, huh?
Hey, Taroumaru!
Where'd you go?
It's time for breakfast!
Get out here!
I doubt he opened that door
to come out here, but...
Taroumaru!
Hey!
I guess he wouldn't be over here.
Huh?
Megu-nee, you cut your hair.
It looked good long.
You think so?
Well, I'm a teacher, after all.
So what?
I felt it was a bit childish,
so I went for a more mature look.
Childish, huh?
It's fine for you, Ebisuzawa-san.
So what was it again? The School Living Club?
Yes.
It was Yuuri-san's idea, and I was
hoping you'd join too, Ebisuzawa-san.
Yeah, sure.
When you have a... purpose,
or something like that,
it's easier to get motivated.
Yes.
And maybe she'll cheer up a bit,
instead of crying all the time.
Don't you think so, Megu-nee?
Yes.
But, Ebisuzawa-san, please call me—
I know, I know. Sensei, not Megu-nee, right?
Sheesh!
Your hair looks good short, too, Megu-nee.
He may be a little runt,
but he's a club member, too.
Watch over him, Sensei.
Hey! If you don't come out soon,
Yuki's gonna eat all your food!
I've got a ping pong ball. Let's play catch!
Those are Taroumaru's.
He couldn't have...
Seriously?
We've never been down these stairs.
This is...
that room from the manual.
SCHOOL ONLY
Staff Emergency Evacuation Manual
Taroumaru!
Man, don't worry us like that!
You...
What do I do?
What should I...
I'm sorry!
Tarou...maru...
Think! Think! Think!
You...
You did this to Taroumaru!
Damn it... Are you kidding me?
This is where you've been?
Why?
Why?!
We're back.
We couldn't find Taroumaru.
It's already after noon.
Taroumaru still hasn't come back?
No. I just got back myself.
Where's Kurumi-chan?
She's not back yet.
Maybe she's still looking for him.
I'll go back out to—
Kurumi?!
Kurumi-senpai!
I screwed up...
No...
Yuki-senpai...
Where's the first aid kit?
There should be one in the staff room.
Got it!
Miki-san, lend me a hand!
Okay!
Megu-nee...
It was... Megu-nee...
Rii-san, is there anything I can do to help?
No... Not right now.
Could you go boil some water, then?
Okay! I will!
Are you okay?!
I'm sorry...
It's okay.
I can't be like this.
I need to get it together.
You're doing great, Senpai.
But you should rest for a bit!
No. I can't make Yuki-chan do all the work.
I... failed...
Sorry... Taroumaru...
No...
Emergency... shelter...
Megu-nee was... Damn it!
Gardening Club
Kurumi-chan's gonna be okay, right, Megu-nee?
What is this place?
Taroumaru?
Taroumaru, I finally found you.
Where have you been?
Open... the door...
Sensei... loves you...
M-Megu-nee?
Why...
Why won't you... open the door?
Please... open... the door...
N-No... Stop...
Stop it!
Um... I read through this again.
O-Oh?
Kurumi-senpai said that
she found Megu-nee in the
emergency shelter, right?
Yes, what about it?
It says there's medicine down there.
What?!
Where?!
Right here.
I'll go!
No, I will.
Yuuri-senpai, watch over Kurumi-senpai.
You can't go alone!
I'll just look around. I won't do anything rash.
That's what Kurumi said!
I think Kurumi-senpai got injured
because it was Megu-nee.
I won't have that problem.
Please let me go.
I boiled some water.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
The club room. I need the shovel.
Rii-san, are you okay?
I'm going to borrow this, Senpai.
Taroumaru
I... failed...
Sorry... Taroumaru...
Taroumaru...
It hasn't rained this hard in a while.
Not since that day...
That day?
That's cold...
Huh? The window's broken...
Next Time
Yuki-senpai is amazing.
With her around, we feel upbeat,
no matter what happens.
No matter what.
Next time on Episode 11 of SCHOOL-LIVE, "Scar."
#11
Scar
We are here.