REVISION
Akihisa and the gang suddenly find themselves taking part in a Test of Courage tournament,
where they face serious problems with the cunning strategy of the summerfags and other third-years.
Roll, roll, roll. No!
Please let me go, Milord!
Thump.
What do we do now, Yuuji?
The third-years have beaten most of our forces already!
It's all right. I have a secret weapon.
A...
se...
...cret...
...weapon?
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
through a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Question 13
Idiots, and Tests, and Summons!
So...
he was talking about us.
W-What? This isn't scary at a—
Are you all right, Minami?
You've got it wrong! I'm just not used to Japanese monsters.
If only it was something German—
I-I can't breathe, M-Minami!
I want to go back, Aki!
What the? She's acting differently from usual.
Why am I so flustered—
That sure is a direct way to come at us.
Akihisa
I will purge the pig who dares to ensnare my darling.
Time to run, Minami!
You're not going anywhere, Sissy!
I'll save you from that pig, no matter what!
Shimizu, you look more monstrous than a real monster.
I could've sworn they went this way.
Well then, let's search somewhere else, Shimizu.
Darling!
It looks like we're safe now.
Are they really gone?
You should really get used to Japanese monsters too, Minami.
It's okay. I'll just go live in Germany instead.
But that'd be so lonely.
I won't be lonely at all! I have friends in Germany too, you know.
Um, that's not what I meant.
I meant we would be lonely without you here.
You're just trying to be nice!
It's true, though!
We've been together so long that I can't imagine a life without you.
Together so long?
What's the matter, Minami?
Then what if I said I'd never ever leave your side?
But there's always a draft around my desk, so it's really cold, you know.
That's not what I meant! I'm asking you if—
Yeah?
If you... lo-lo-lo-lo—
Minami? What—
I'm back!
Welcome back, Akihisa. Where's Minami?
I'm letting her rest in the infirmary. She's totally pooped.
Good job, Akihisa. The operation's going well.
Hand Sissy over!
She isn't human.
So they were the "secret weapon"?
Yeah, pretty much.
Huh? I can understand Shimizu is roaming around looking for Minami,
but why is Kubo with her?
Don't tell me Kubo is in love with Shimizu?!
Akihisa, thou art most inhumane.
I pity Kubo.
How cruel.
About time you showed up!
We let our guard down this morning,
but we'll show you the real power of a third-year—
Excuse me. Did Yoshii and Shimada pass by here?
You bastard! Let me finish!
You think you're being funny?
We'll show you how to pay proper respect to your seniors!
Summon!
Staff
Physics
You leave us no choice.
Summon!
What?!
They're over 400!
What, 400?
They're model students in science!
Fucking restless brat! Give it up already!
Now it's your turn!
Summerfags
I didn't think Kubo would lose.
At last...
it's our turn.
That's right! You two haven't had a turn yet!
Sure, Shouko will be fine, but I have at most 150 marks in Physics.
This won't be easy.
If only we had one more pair, just in case.
There is a pair left!
Right here.
Me?
It's true I quit halfway, so I haven't actually been disqualified.
But Minami won't—
I see! Akihisa, is there not another thou canst team up with?
One who hath not been disqualified either.
One more?
Um...
Are you talking about me?
But Himeji is really scared of monsters.
We shouldn't force her to—
I'll do it!
While I was watching Minami, I realized something.
I need to do my best too!
I'll enter the haunted house with you, Akihisa!
Please walk really slowly, okay?
Sure.
I'm not scared. I'm not scared.
Akihisa is right next to me, so there's nothing to be afraid of!
Um, Himeji?
Yes?
Thanks for doing this.
Not at all!
I'm always relying on you for everything, so...
Nah, that's okay.
I'm glad you rely on me.
You're pretty, smart, and really sweet.
I feel like I'm a prince protecting his princess.
Well, I'm sure you'd rather have someone better than me around—
Himeji?
I'm nothing like a princess.
I'm stupid, I'm jealous, and I can't do anything right when it really matters.
I have nothing but faults and weaknesses.
You aren't like that—
I am!
You don't understand at all!
You don't realize because we're not close at all.
Not close?
You're so considerate of me, careful, and nice,
but when you look at me, aren't you thinking about someone else?
Akihisa, what do you think of me?!
Himeji?
Question 13:
Consider the following situation
and answer the question.
"You are all alone with your
beloved boyfriend on a trip.
However, you two were
in a hurry to get on the plane,
and you now realize that
you left something behind.
What did you leave behind?"
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
"Medicine for headaches, stomachaches, etc."
Teacher's comment:
This is a psychological test to find out what
qualities you seek in the person you love.
What you forgot represents the qualities you lack.
The fact that you forgot them in a rush to leave represents
how you expect your beloved to compensate for those qualities instead.
It looks like you seek peace and calmness in the person you love.
Kirishima Shouko's answer:
"Handcuffs."
Teacher's comment:
Your mistake wasn't to accidentally
leave them behind, but to think
about taking them with you
in the first place.
Kudou Aiko's answer:
"I forgot to wear my undies."
Teacher's comment:
Just what are you looking for
in your beloved anyway?
Himeji!
Huh? Was this wall here earlier?
Thank goodness.
I'm glad you're—
ugly.
Shut up, and let go of my hand.
Yuuji! Huh? Where's Himeji?
Wait, what?
Where are we?
Himeji should be with Shouko right now.
Don't tell me...
Yeah, the summerfags did it.
Neither Shouko nor I would scream loud enough to be disqualified.
That's true.
That's why they turned off the lights and made us swap.
I see.
Well, Shouko and Himeji make the strongest team, anyway.
Everything should be fine.
So what's the real reason?
For some reason, I just couldn't shake off the fear...
that being alone with Shouko in a haunted house would involve lots of beatings with a nail-bat.
Hey, Kirishima's there on the other side of that wall.
Akihisa Barrier!
Yup, I understand you loud and clear.
Mizuki, it's all right.
Y-Yeah, I guess.
That sounded like...
Hi—
Himejiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
Himeji...
I don't hear anything!
I don't hear that creepy whisper! Not at all!
Stop that! You're making it worse!
If you scare her too much, she'll scream and get disqualified!
Fine. Then let's tail them from a distance.
Go! Like a ninja...
Don't be scared, Mizuki. It's all right.
A thousand curses on you!
I'm fine! I'm not afraid! Not afraid!
Good girl, Mizuki. There's a good girl.
Himeji...
I can see you're worried about her,
but at least she's giving it her best in her own way.
In her own way?
To become closer to us, and to help us with our own problems.
Yuuji, did you hear what she was talking about earlier?
Himeji was really concerned about it, wasn't she?
That she's always a burden to the rest of us.
Himeji...
It's all right, Mizuki. Don't be afraid.
Okay, I'm not afraid.
I won't give up.
You can do it. You can do it, Himeji!
Final checkpoint
Is this it?
Bah!
Weren't you two disqualified already?
This is damn annoying.
I thought I was gonna fight those losers, Yoshii and Sakamoto, first.
They must've run away.
Spineless losers.
Those boys aren't losers.
They aren't losers!
They aren't losers?
They keep making problems for everyone, and they suck at studying.
What do you call losers like that?
How about this?
Instead of "losers," the "trash of society."
No, that would be rude to real trash.
Oh, come on. What are you just standing there all silent for?
No shit. Just being in the same class as those loser trashy good-for-nothings—
How can you say such mean things?!
It's true that Akihisa and Sakamoto are bad at academics.
Yes, they make trouble for everyone around them.
But does that give you the right to say such horrible things about them?!
You don't even know...
You don't even know how sweet and kind they really are!
Huh? Aren't you the one who doesn't know how stupid they are?
Why can't you see past their grades?
Grades aren't everything! There are much more important things!
Oh, stop your yapping! We have better things to do than worry about those pieces of shit!
Those two boys...
are neither losers...
nor trash!
What a noisy little girl!
You're disqualified! Get the hell out!
We don't need your permission.
Let's go, Mizuki.
You hear that, Yuuji? Apparently, we're sweet guys.
Never heard that before.
I'm not quite as bad as you, Akihisa, but I always thought I was a first-rate loser.
I'm not as bad as you, Yuuji, but I still thought I was a pretty worthless guy.
Man, those girls went too far again.
All that effort turned into nothing.
I know, right? This stupid game isn't worth getting that worked up about.
Let's go, Akihisa.
Right with you, Yuuji.
We're coming for you, assholes!
How long are those idiots gonna make us wait?
They won't show up after seeing our grades.
Yo, guys!
Took you long enough. Let's get right down to business, then.
Summon!
Wait!
Let's decide on a penalty for losing, first.
Penalty?
You two aren't planning something stupid, are you?
What are you so worried about? You were the ones who wanted a penalty, remember?
What will it be then?
How about the losers do whatever the winners tell them to?
Hah! Just perfect.
Let's get on with it already!
Summon!
What's with those marks?!
You're nowhere close to our level—
They're more than enough.
Let's go, Akihisa.
Okay, Yuuji.
Run!
What— They ran away?!
You're not getting away!
Hold it!
Where'd they go?!
Tsunemura! That way!
Fucking annoying brats!
Don't tell me you're tired already?
They're on the other side!
Where are they?!
Hey! We're over here, guys!
Don't fuck with us!
Wow. They're surprisingly into this.
Hey, you're being rude!
I didn't think they'd make it this far.
They're not even at full power yet, right, guys?
Yoshii! Sakamoto! Get over here!
How about you use those precious brains of yours to find us?
I'm bored of this game.
Still can't find us?
You know, we've already...
...seen through your crap!
They vanished!
We're outside the physics summoning field!
Too bad. This was a decoy.
We've seen through yours.
When did they—
Mr. Hasegawa! Please permit us to fight!
Permission granted!
Summoned being, summon!
This is the math field!
Being good at physics won't help you here!
You dirty little—
That's cheating!
There's no rule against changing the subject of a checkpoint's field.
Or are you too scared to fight if it's not physics?
You fool! We're good at math and science!
We won't lose to you at math!
Summon!
Crap!
Oh shit! It's because we fought that four-eyes this morning!
They remembered that?!
Dammit!
Go to hell!
It's too late to cry about it now!
What did you say?!
Idiots are amazing, aren't they, guys?
They can get absorbed in one thing and focus all their energy on it.
When you call someone a karate idiot or a judo idiot,
you're actually praising them!
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
In short...
His head!
You messed with the wrong idiots!
How did...
...we lose...
...to these idiots?
We win. I hope you remember our deal.
Bah! What are you gonna make us do, then?
That's obvious enough.
Himeji...
Yoshii!
Kirishima!
Mizuki is on the roof.
Hurry.
Thanks, Kirishima.
That was very tactful of you.
Not really.
I just like a person who can give it their all, even when they're really scared.
I really do.
I don't really have anything I'm afraid of, nor do I try really hard at anything.
I'll just leave it at that.
Akihisa!
Everyone's going to eat crêpes to celebrate.
Those third-years came and apologized to me a while back.
You made them do that, didn't you, Akihisa?
I'm really sorry! I'm always causing you trouble!
No, it's not like that!
You were right. You're not really a princess, Himeji.
No princess could've spoken out to her seniors like you did.
That was just... Um...
Thank you. It touched my heart.
Both Yuuji and I were able to win because of what you said about us.
Thank you! I'm glad you think so.
Shall we go, then? Everyone's waiting.
Um... I just want to ask you something first!
Really? What is it?
Yes. Um...
When will you start calling me Mizuki?
You call Minami by her first name, but not me!
That's kinda hard to explain! It's just that...
What is it?
Um... Uh...
Look. We were together when we were in elementary school, weren't we?
Yes.
So, it was embarrassing when I called you Mizuki like I used to back then.
Of course not!
You haven't called me that once since we started high school!
Well, that's...
Promise you won't laugh.
I won't laugh!
Promise?
I promise!
Actually, I...
Yes?
...was practicing at home earlier...
...to call you by your first name.
Yes?
Never mind! Forget I said anything!
Then I'll tell you a secret too.
My first...
crush is still going strong.
Come on! Let's go, Akihisa!
W-Wait, Himeji! What did you just—
Aki, where have you been?!
Minami?
Didn't you promise to be by my side forever?
What's she talking about, Akihisa?
Akihisa, get outta my way!
We didn't win the tournament together as a team, so we're going to get married.
No fucking way!
Wait!
We'll grow old together.
Hey, hold it!
What's the meaning of this?
I'm telling you to wait!
Goodness! They never change.
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making
any progress
Someone's
getting in my way
It's not
enough at all!
That's the
root of the problem
Do you understand
what it really is, Baby?
If you do, draw
your answer here, Baby
Neither the words
nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
With the magnetism
from S and N
Congratulations!
You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special
No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight
and won't let you go.
I've fallen in love
I don't want
any doubts in my heart
You're special; I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway
Sparkling, glittering
The right answer is pop!
Run!
No running in the halls!
Good grief!
What a bunch of idiots.
Idiots