Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well, you've all
given someone a present, right?
You wonder if they'll be happy to get it,
and you feel like you've
put all your feelings into it.
In my case, it's this stage.
If I could give all the people
who've come to watch us
and all the companions
who've given it their best with me
a stage that they could smile
and say "That was great" about,
that would be so awesome!
I mean... I mean...
I am a Kaleido Star! Star! Star!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
98...
The daytime practice
isn't enough on its own?
It's nowhere near enough.
"The Amazing Injured Swan."
If you overtrain that much,
of course it's going to hurt.
Yes, ma'am...
Because you're trying to force your
body to compensate for the basics you lack,
you're working your feet too hard.
I see, your center of gravity is unstable,
and you're controlling that
with the tips of your toes.
These blood blisters are huge.
You should really rest
your feet for a few days...
I don't have time for--
Okay, okay.
Then how about we at least protect the affected
parts so you don't put too much weight on them?
Please!
Maybe we should put balance
work on your training menu too.
One, two, three, one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two, three,
one, two, three, one,
two, three, one, two, three,
Hey, I've got a question for you.
What?
What scene will Rosetta be in?
She won't be in this.
What do you mean she won't be in it?
There was originally a diabolo
scene in the script, but she withdrew.
It was a scene Mia put
in specifically for Rosetta,
so it was superfluous
to the story, and we cut it.
Does Sora know this?
Yes.
Stop!
Sorry, but I'm going to
rethink this configuration again.
Will everybody please drop this
and switch to individual practice?
What's the problem?
This is the third time!
Oh, I have someone
I want to introduce to you two.
My feet hurt, but I feel like I'm
getting a better and better grip on this.
I want to practice more and more!
Sorry I'm late!
We'll resume your special
training this afternoon.
Rest until I tell you that you can start again.
Okay...
Welcome, all you gloomy housewives!
Save your gloomy expressions
for your old, tired husbands.
When you're with me,
show me your maidenly smiles!
I'm asking this knowing
that it won't happen.
You'd think there'd be some training
goods geared toward Sora's problems...
This guy's got a sharp tongue,
but he's pretty handsome,
so it's just hard to hate him somehow.
Everything is squeaky clean with Clean Finish!
From your children's doodles
to the past doings you
can't tell your husbands about,
everything's wiped away in no time!
Come on, do a little serious help and...
Go on to the next pile of garbage, Junk Baron!
It isn't garbage, it's treasure!
It's Anna's dad!
Huh? What?!
They don't look a thing alike!
This is our next treasure.
With this, that flabby
flesh will firm right up!
This is it!
Jack!
Sorry I'm late, Anna!
Wow, it's the real Jack Baron!
It looks like work is going well.
Yeah. The comedy channel has
asked me if I'll do a half hour program.
Amazing!
You'll be busy, then.
I'll definitely help you out.
If I refused a request from my beloved
savior, God would be sure to punish me.
Savior?
Anna is my angel.
I'm ready!
It, like, looks like the
lesson is finally going to start.
Wasn't that a long break?
Perhaps that means they're close
to perfecting the Angel's Maneuver.
This will be the final stage of the
special training for the Angel's Maneuver.
Already?
I knew it.
What's the matter? Hurry up.
Right!
I'll change the way I channel
my strength each time.
You sense that and adjust for it.
Right!
Let's report this.
Yes.
Like, farewell.
Huh?
Again, please!
Rosetta.
What?
I hear you're not going
to perform in Swan Lake?
That's right.
This show is an important one for Sora,
so I don't want to get in the
way with an unnecessary scene.
Hmmm, how adult.
But considering your lofty intentions,
you seem to be sneaking around a
lot peeking at everybody's practice.
It's none of your business, is it?
If you're all right with that, then fine, but...
I've already made my decision.
Amazing... The Angel's Maneuver
has really started to take shape.
But her balance seems to be
getting worse and worse. Why is that?
It's okay for someone unattractive
to play a handsome man.
But the opposite is pretty difficult.
Especially with someone as handsome as me!
But you can take anything
and push it over the top,
and it will become funny.
The stage direction is being
outdone by Sora's energy!
Right now it's nothing but a nice
little setup that follows the rules.
The only ones who will accept
this kind of textbook construction
are the professional critics!
It has to be more...
Hold that pose and maintain it!
Right!
That's enough.
The Angel's Maneuver training is over.
What?
Mr. Leon, what do you mean, "over"?
The Angel's Maneuver is perfected.
Now spend your time until opening
day fine-tuning it and resting your body.
Perfected?
Don't worry about me, I'll keep going!
Mr. Leon, please wait!
It's over now? That can't be...
You're saying you're going to break
off the Angel's Maneuver training?
Even at her current level,
I would think she can
maintain it for five minutes.
And if she saves her strength,
she can manage the two daily shows.
It's enough.
Can you really call that the Angel's Maneuver?
She's compensating for
her lack of basic balance
by forcibly holding the
poses with her leg strength.
In that sense I can't call it the real
thing, but the audience won't know.
That doesn't satisfy me.
If she overextends herself, the show will fail.
You can just think about giving it the widest
publicity you can and raking in the profits.
Can you make good on your
promise to your little sister like that?
It's none of your business.
Sora?! Hey, what happened?
Where's Leon?
He said my special training was over.
I see...
But that can't be right.
He gave up on me.
Show me your feet.
What is this?!
Your balance was getting worse,
so I thought something was off.
You've torn the skin from your toes!
If you've come this far and Leon's
given you the okay, isn't that enough?!
It's no good at all!
Like this, it's completely...
There's no way I can wake up everybody's
angel hearts with a maneuver at this level.
Like!
The special training is over?
Yes, miss.
That's definitely what Leon said.
But Sora...
...like, didn't seem to accept that.
I see.
Miss, you're so beautiful!
From the reports of her
training I've heard up until now,
Leon has minimized balance training
and spent that time
strengthening her legs instead.
He's trying to modify
the Angel's Maneuver into something
she can do at her current ability level.
But there's no way Sora
would accept a fake like that--
something that's only
the appearance of the thing.
If Leon can't completely become
a demon, there's only one way left.
The angel herself has
to become a demon, Sora.
The Angel's Maneuver is
going to be changed out?!
If that happens, we'll have
to rework the entire stage plan!
How is Sora doing?
We're making her get treatment for her feet.
She's ripped up the skin of her toes,
and in this condition she
can't give a proper performance.
But...
I can still go on.
I can still do it!
Do your feet still hurt?
Enough of this. I'll be back!
Sora, where are you going?
I'm going to try asking Mr. Leon one
more time if he'll continue my training.
Sora...
Oh my, you startled me.
Miss Sarah!
I have a delivery.
A present from that guy over there.
Ken got me a present?
Well, I was looking at catalogues
and I just kind of bought them.
I couldn't resist, so I bought some too!
I thought I'd recommend it to Leon
as a method of improving her balance
while not putting too much
of a burden on her feet, but...
I've decided I'm definitely going to
ask Mr. Leon to continue my training.
So I'll try recommending this too!
Because the special training isn't over!
What are you doing?
I thought I told you to rest.
Mr. Leon, please continue my training.
Please.
There's no need.
The Angel's Maneuver has been perfected.
That can't be true!
Right now it's all I can do just to
somehow fake the appearance of it.
I don't own this maneuver at all.
I can't believe that I can give
everyone a good time with this.
If I say it's over, it's over.
In that case, I'll continue
my training by myself.
What?
I'm going to do it until I'm satisfied.
And I will master the Angel's
Maneuver before opening day.
So well that I'll get you
to acknowledge me too.
Do what you want.
There's a limit to the amount of pain a
person can put herself through of her own will.
You're a fool.
Shut up.
Obviously I won't be able
to get it right on the first try.
If I incorporate balance training
into my daily life like this...
The Fool aims for heights yet unseen.
First you have to get
completely used to the shoes.
Right!
Rosetta, can you get the drinks?
Sure.
Your balance has gotten a lot better, huh?
Yep!
It seems as if the special training
isn't over, just as Miss Layla predicted.
Here it comes!
What do you think, Sora?
It's good!
Now that I'm doing this,
I can really tell I've been working all my
muscles unnecessarily hard this whole time.
Now switch legs!
This is the feeling of it.
If I get it this way even without these shoes...
Here it comes again!
Right!
Don't let your pose slip.
Rosetta...
I think I'll do balance training
again starting tomorrow.
You're really fired up, huh?
Do you think you'll be able to do
the Angel's Maneuver as planned?
Of course that's what I mean to do.
I'll do my best, so that I can
get Leon to acknowledge me too.
I'm sure you can do it, Sora.
Thanks!
I'm going to practice more too,
and someday I'll be onstage
with you on the trapeze.
I'm looking forward to it.
I try to force myself to do it on
strength alone, so I can only do 100 reps.
If my whole body is balanced,
I should be able to do more.
She's got way more fighting
spirit than she's had up till now.
The really hard part is from here on out, Sora.
Because you can't relax your attention to
any part of your body, even for an instant.
My whole body is straining...
I feel like one rep is
tiring me ten reps' worth.
The special training is moving backwards.
I don't get it.
She like, looks like she's having
a harder time than she was before.
Miss! Miss Layla!
I'm all right.
So Sora's started balance training again?
Yes, Miss.
That's my Sora.
But after you've learned to fake a technique,
retraining your body to do
it correctly is no easy thing.
I have to master the technique
of instantaneously sensing the
flow of my partner's strength soon too.
Because without that, the
Angel's Maneuver won't be perfected.
Sora is... Sora is...
Stop!
Why?
Why are you going that far?
Why are you and Sophie so
merciless toward yourselves?
I thought you were going to
let Sora do what she wanted.
Every muscle in your body must
be creaking with overstrain by now.
If you keep doing this, you'll
never be able to stand onstage again!
Even if that happens, I can't
show the audience something fake.
Leon, are you telling me to
show them something fake?!
A fake is enough.
No it's not.
With something like that, there's
no way the stage without battles...
Then the stage without
battles can't become real.
I was fighting all along,
where Sophie couldn't see me.
I struck down those who tried
to involve Sophie in their battles!
Leon, I'm definitely going to become a
true star and create a stage with no battles.
Yeah. I'm sure you can do it, Sophie.
When all's said and done,
I never believed in this "stage
with no battles" thing for a moment.
Now stop this.
It's only natural that you can't believe in it.
Because nobody's ever seen it.
I don't know what it's like either.
But that's exactly why I want to see it.
I want to do anything
I can to make that happen.
I think Miss Sophie wanted to see you
standing on a stage without battles, Mr. Leon.
Promise me, Leon...
I think that was Sophie's dream!
Her goal of becoming a
true star, and that promise...
You're saying that was all for my sake?
Sophie probably knew all
about your fighting and...
Thank you.
I've changed my mind.
We'll start the special training again.
Yes, sir!
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
It looks like Sora is fighting
with something, doesn't it?
And so, the difference
between fighting and competing,
the difference between hating
each other and improving each other...
We know why we fight,
and why we tackle challenges.
The audience's smiles are
waiting for us! They are! They are!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Our Amazing Futures."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...