Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
Rika-chama
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
There we go!
It's fall now.
Huh?  So then your father was a tank rider?
Yup!
He was one of the legendary heroes
who freed over a thousand civilians and soldiers
from the completely-encircled Waldenborough.
And with only six Milivets!
That's amazing.
Isn't it?
And also, when my father was honorably wounded in the midst of battle,
he was sent to the hospital where my mother was working as an orderly, and that's how they met!
And then from the two of them...
you were born, Kureha-chan.
Yup!
Wait, are you comparing me to a potato?!
Oh, my.  What a fine-looking potato.
It's all thanks to your earnest and diligent care of them, Kana-chan.
With this, it looks like we'll be able to share some with the citizens, too.
And Krause-san is coming, as well.
Shall we take some as a present for him, also?
He'll be here?
Kureha-chan, you really like Krause-san, don't you?
I-It's not about like, it's about respect!
Poke.
Rio-senpai...
Wow, so she's able to play songs like that, too!
Rio-senpai's amazing!
Yeah...
The wind's picked up, hasn't it?
The weather doesn't look like it's going to hold up for much longer, either.  Shall we head inside before that happens?
Okay!
Okay.
Noel-chan, you too.
Yeah.
What?
Like I was saying, don't you think something's up with Rio-sempai?
Like what?
Like her trumpet-playing and all...
It's just wonderful!
Sounds so cool...
She's seems to be kind of depressed...
It's normal for her not to waste words.
But...
Oh, I know!  Dinner!
Was delicious, wasn't it?
Tempura.
Yeah!  And the potatoes were so crispy...
Wait, no!
Here you are, Rio.  Eat it while it's hot!
Yeah, thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Good, I'm glad.
She was scarfing down those green peppers!
What?  Rio-senpai was?
Yeah!  The same Rio-senpai who, no matter how finely chopped up they are, always finds and takes them out!
That... could be a bad sign.
Poke.
Oh?
Is this... Krause-san?
Yup!  That's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Krause!
On his left pec is a wolf-head tattoo that represents the unity and glory of the 481st Platoon!
Isn't it cool?
You can't have it!
I don't think you need to worry too much about it.
I mean, the whole thing with the captain was because we worried too much.
And this time, it's Rio-senpai.
She's so cool and awesome and sexy...
Oh, right!
I bet she's even gotten over her dislike of green peppers and is able to eat them now.
Kureha-chan, you really like Rio-senpai, don't you?
She's my idol after all!
I mean, she's mine too...
Hey, what do you think, Noel-chan?
P... oke.
Be careful!
Noel-chan's already out.
I guess there's no helping that.
She can share my bed.
Kanata, you get that end?
You forgot to turn off the heating fire for the bath.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
How you seem so focused and steady, yet sometimes slip up, is one of your charming points.
But lately, it's been happening too often.
I'm sorry.
Do you regret it?  Hanging up on your father?
Well, I guess there's nothing to be done.
I'll cover for your mistakes at work.
But at least stay a cool senpai around those children, okay?
I wonder if that's the wind?
I don't think so.
Sorry for coming by so late.
It's a Class-1 Priority.
Who's it for?
Sergeant Major Kazumiya Rio of the 1121st Platoon.
Take it.
Major, for the moment, please come in.
You can't possibly travel anymore in this weather.
Even if you are the Desert Wolf.
I've told you not to call me that anymore.
I apologize.
To make up for it, how about a bath and some hot tea?
Thank you for completing your mission in this typhoon!
Um, sorry that all we have to offer you are leftovers from dinner... but please, partake!
You should've woken me up when Krause-san got here!
Well done!
Despite the fact they're cold.  Even the green peppers are good!
Really?!
I was the one who picked them and fried them!
You'll be a great wife one day, Kureha.
Is that the new paper?
Yes, the Major brought it here for us.
How are the armistice arrangements going?
The conference still appears to be going through some rough patches.
It seems like neither side is willing to compromise on their conditions...
If only Princess Ilya were still alive, those talks might be going differently.
Princess... Ilya?
Do you really not know who that is?!  The hero of Vingt?
The first princess of His Royal Highness, the Archduke Arcadia!
The goddess of victory for the Helvetian army!
A tank rider goddess, right up there with Desert Wolf Krause!
Kureha, that's actually—
Is everyone here?
There's an emergency!
Rio!
What's all the fuss?
One of the kids from Yumina's place has been missing since this morning.
Will you help us search for him?
What?!
Yumina-san, who's missing?
It's Seiya-san.
The river's swelled quite a bit.
I'm sure the fields downstream haven't been harvested yet.
If the dam breaks, they'll be completely destroyed.
I'm unfamiliar with the city.
I'm counting on you, Kureha!
Right!
I'm so sorry!
I only took my eyes off of him for a second...
Disaster relief also falls under military duties.  Leave it to us.
Let's go.
Right!
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
Wow... the water's risen this much...
If he fell...
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
W-W-What was that?
You!
You know something, don't you?
You have a lead, that's why you came out, right?
Tell me!
Where's Seiya?
At the fields.
"The fields"?
Eggplants are Yumina-oneechan's favorite food.
So we used all of everyone's allowances and bought seeds...
I'm sure Seiya...
Where is it?
What's wrong with you?!
Coming to a place like this in the middle of a typhoon!
I'm gonna protect the eggplants!
What are you saying?!  You idiot!
Everyone's risking their lives for you!
I never asked you to come!
You came here on your own!
What did you say?!
You'd better cut that out—
Listen...
Kids without parents need to be stronger than those with them.
When you cause trouble for others, they'll naturally say that's to be expected from someone like you.
And they won't say it just to you.
They'll say it to others too, like your sis, Yumina.
Kureha...
I know because I'm an orphan too.
Now, let's get going.
But...
Are you still complaining?
Hold on a second.
Something you've worked for and raised can have as much value as your own life, you know?
These have grown large enough to be eaten.
If you turn them into pickled vegetables, they'll be delicious.
Thanks, mister!
Major...
Seiya-kun's started climbing.
Major, please, you go first!
Sure...
N-No... you go ahead.
Leave the rear to me.
Okay!
Somehow, they're both still safe.
However...
Now their way back up is gone.
This is... a terrible situation.
Thank you.
S-Sure...
The situation's taken a turn for the worse, but...
But you are with me!
I'm sure things will work out!
You're wrong...
Huh?  Did you say something?
Nope...
Listen up!  Don't be afraid.
You're with Miracle Krause now!
Right!
The ground won't hold much longer!
Another disaster, huh...
Dammit!  This is why I hate kids!
Kids who don't listen should just be tied up and locked away!
Rio!
What will saying that to them do?
Those kids are always looking up to you.
I'm sorry... that was too far.
B-But I'm sure that things will be okay, right?
Krause-san is called a miracle person and all!
You're wrong.
He's not the Desert Wolf or Miracle Krause.
He just coincidentally happens to have the same name and a similar appearance...
When they first met, Kureha just started calling him that on her own and got all excited...
And Krause isn't much of a talker, you know?
He never found the right time to deny her misconceptions and time went on...
That's...
Anyway, now we need to think of a way to save the two of them...
The one only a courier, but with many years of continuous service,
and the other with a lot of enthusiasm, but no experience.
Hand them... a rope?
There's no firm footing above them.
And it's too far to send them one from here.
To get a rope from here over to there...
There's a way!
When I first met you, Krause-san,
I thought, if my father were still alive, I'm sure he would be just like this.
I speak to everyone as if I knew my father really well, but...
But well, it's really all just passed-down information and I don't actually know who he was that well at all.
By the time I was old enough to know what was going on, he was already gone.
Kureha...
Pay attention to... the upper-left?
Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!  Heave-ho!
The Takemikazuchi!
Stop!
Noel-chan, how is it?
Anchoring linear coil ready.
Targeting systems B7 to F5 partially active.
Initiating alignment.
It'll work.
Prepare to fire the wire anchor!
Kanata, do it!
Right!
It's coming!
In place of your late father, I will protect you!
Right... Major!
Ready...
Fire!
Come here!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Pull up the anchor!  Hurry!
Hey... Kureha...
Things worked out somehow, so I'm going to go ahead and say this...
I'm...
You really are...
someone I admire!
A blue sky after the typhoon, huh?
You kept it up til the end, after all.
To be honest, I'm surprised.  I wasn't sure you had it in you...
When I saw those eyes that watched me with such complete faith,
I became more afraid of destroying her dreams than of dying.
That's why I was able to play it out til the end.
I guess I'm a coward, after all.
That's not true!
Krause-san, you were wonderful!
Listen here, missy.
Most of the time, what you see when observing someone from the outside
and what the person is feeling inside are different.
Watching someone through lenses of admiration always makes your vision out of focus.
Someday, when you're looked at through such lenses, you'll understand how hard it is.
Could you at least stay until Kureha-chan wakes up?
Can you tell her for me?
That this is the most honorable wound I've received in my entire life!
Next time, Departure: Around the First Snowfall!