This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old.
Recently, she recorded a
TV show for the first time.
She failed time after time due to her lack of experience.
She almost didn't get to sing Myself.
However, after receiving words of
encouragement from a former idol...
Full Moon's  TV debut was a big success.
I'm starting to become
a little used to this business.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Furuta from Guitar Fighters
Scoop!!
Revealed
Hot Love
Furuta from Guitar Fighters
Scoop!!
Revealed
Hot Love
Furuta from Guitar Fighters
Scoop!!
Revealed
Hot Love
Furuta from Guitar Fighters
Scoop!!
Revealed
Hot Love
Thanks to these pictures you took...
The Guitar Fighters' popularity has gone down.
Is that so?
You really stabbed them in the back, huh?
Aren't you afraid that their spirits will come back to haunt you?
If I was afraid of ghosts...
I wouldn't be in this line of work.
Well, what do you want
from me, Mr. Superstitious?
I want some new faces.
If we have no scoops,
our weekly pictorials won't sell.
Well, how about this girl?
Our next target, huh?
Full Moon.
A sixteen year old idol who debuted recently.
But, her real name and her background information are unknown to the public.
I see.
Full Moon, huh?
Alright, alright! You're listening to Radio Name!
Next, we have a question
by Furuta Muntaro-kun.
"Full Moon-san, what kind of
artist do you want to be?"
That's what it says...
So, how about it?
Do you have any goals?
Ah, well...
Well, for now, I just want to keep on singing...
...and keep on sending my feelings.
Sending your feelings?
Are you singing for someone special?
Eh?
That's...
That's a secret.
A secret, huh?
By the way, Full Moon-san...
How about your real name?
Ah, right, that's also a secret.
Hmm, I see.
Everything is a secret, huh?
Yes.
Dangerous Lens
Tomorrow is your magazine cover photo shoot.
You'll be with Shounen Drill's Shirakawa-kun.
Wow, really?
That's right.
A collaboration for the first time!
We're going to take the long way, okay?
Eh?
Ooshige-san, is something wrong?
We're being followed.
Eh, followed?
Don't look!
You're going to get your picture taken...
...by a tabloid photographer, Saegusa.
Whether it's an artist's private life,
or rumors of an actor's relationship,
he's a bastard who'll get the dirt on anyone.
He's probably been following us from the studio.
Surely, he has been taking Mitsuki's picture the whole time.
Eh?
This is bad.
Ooshige-san?
They're late!
Geez, they're late!
What are those two doing
by themselves anyways?
You
have
no
new
mess
ages.
Lens.
What's this?
Lens?
He's really persistent.
If he keeps this up, I won't be able to drop you off, Mitsuki.
This is kinda scary.
All right.
Damn it!
Looks like we lost him.
Saegusa won't let you go that easily once he targets you.
Just like a hyena.
There is no celebrity who can get away once he sets his eyes on them.
But, I don't have anything for him to aim at.
Mitsuki, you haven't said your real name, or profile in public, right?
For a guy like him, that's like hitting the jackpot.
That can't be...
It's okay.
If anything happens, everyone in the office will do anything to protect you.
You aren't alone.
Right.
Thank you for the ride.
Mitsuki.
Yes?
Maybe I should take you to your house?
No, that's all right.
I see.
Well, if anything happens, contact me immediately, okay?
If anyone finds out my real name, I might not be able to sing anymore.
I'll make sure that'll never happen.
Hey, whatever you do, don't look behind you.
Eh? What's wrong?
You're being followed.
W-Why?
Looks like we didn't lose him.
Oh no, what should I do?
Just keep walking like normal.
Turn at the corner.
This is bad.
I can't change you back in this situation.
No way...
What should I do?
Hey, over there!
Go underground from there!
Okay.
There, everything's fine now.
Let's go.
It's him.
Like I said, everything was fine, right?
Yeah...
But... I was scared.
Hmm...
Sounds like trouble.
But, Takuto helped me out so I got away.
Don't mention it.
Well, I have to get up early tomorrow.
I am off to take a bath.
Hey, Takuto.
What is it, Meroko?
I couldn't say it in front of her.
We have a new task.
Does this have something to do with delaying her death?
Hmm, what's this?
The letters are backwards.
Right.
Backwards means they're the opposite of the usual pattern.
In other words, it's not something that will delay her death.
It's something that will bring
about her death sooner.
Bring about her death sooner?
It's "Lens".
"Lens?"
That Saegusa guy's camera?
It'd be best for her to take a break from work tomorrow.
What are you saying?
I can take on that bastard myself.
It's no use.
You're still new at this.
It's absolutely impossible!
Then, what are you planning on doing?
I'll figure something out.
Is this really gonna work?
But... this is the only thing we can do.
This, and this, and this...
Ah, this one too.
Okay.
A dream, huh?
No, it's not a dream!
What are you doing, Meroko?
Ah, well, I...
I just wanted to try going out
as Full Moon  today.
Why?
I-I just thought that you should take a break every now and then.
Your job is tough, right?
I'm fine.
I like my job.
I'm sorry to say this...
I'm doing my job, too.
Hmm, your job?
No, it's all right, Meroko.
Takuto?
Looks like you're going to stay home.
But...
It'll be fine.
I'll definitely protect her.
What's wrong with Meroko?
It's nothing.
Well, let's hurry.
Okay.
Whatever happens...
I'll protect you.
Okay. Good job!
Thank you very much.
Eh? You were followed by that Saegusa?
Yeah... it was such a bother.
We had the same problem.
Thanks to him... one of our
staff members had to quit.
Really, he is such a bother.
Ooshige-san!
Mission accomplished!
Is that so?
Well, that's all for today then.
Okay.
Well, I'm going home now.
How about a ride?
Nope, I'll be fine.
I see.
Well, be careful on your way home.
Okay.
I'll be leaving then.
Ooshige-san worries a lot, doesn't she?
Yeah.
Although we haven't seen
that bastard Saegusa yet.
Um...
Um... you're Full Moon-san, right?
Can we take a picture with you?
Uh, s-sure.
All right!
Smile for us, 'kay?
Get a bit closer.
Okay, I'm taking one now.
Yay!
Say "cheese."
Keep up the good work!
Thank you so much.
We're gonna cheer for you.
T-Thanks.
Geez, I got all worked up for nothing.
Ah, that surprised me.
I thought it was that Saegusa again...
It's him!
Let's go!
O-Okay!
Damn!
If my secret is uncovered,
then I can't sing anymore.
And if that happens, Eichi-kun...
It's no use.
You're still new at this.
It's absolutely impossible!
You think that's gonna stop me?!
Hey, what are you doing?!
But...
At this rate, he'll catch up to us.
All right, let's go!
Eh? W-W-Wait!
When we get the chance, I'll turn you back into a 12-year-old!
O-Okay.
Sign: Mid-season's Big Sale
Summer Clothing Summer Sale!!
I
You can hide over there!
But...
Hurry up!
Just to make sure, wear this thing!
Now!
Right.
Yeah, perfect!
I understand.
Then, bye...
Crap!
Did he find out?
Let's make a run for it!
It can't be!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. I'm very sorry!
I'm positive that girl is...
This isn't good!
You bastard!
Take that!
What the hell?
And that! This one too!
W-What?
Run for it!
Okay!
All right, here's some more!
Bastard!
Here's a present!
What's going on?
Who's that guy?
What? Is he a freak?
How pitiful!
Scary.
A pervert! A pervert!
N-No, I'm not!
I didn't do it!
That girl, where did she go?
Eh? Which way was the train station at?
Damn!
That sucked ass!
I ended up losing that girl, too.
After all I had to...
Hmm?
There she is!
Lens.
I have a feeling that Takuto...
Will they be okay?
Eh?
Where is this place?
What should I do?
Takuto's not here either.
I know! The whistle!
Hey, you...
Mitsuki!
Where is she?
You... It was you yesterday, right?
At the underground tunnel.
Actually at the time, the idol
Full Moon  was there.
You didn't notice her?
That's strange.
When I got there, you were the only person left.
I-I don't know!
If that's the case, why are you running away?
Perhaps, you're one of Full Moon's  associates?
You won't answer me?
I-I really don't know anything...
Well, will you at least hear me out for a sec?
No!
H-Hey!
Oh no!
If my picture is taken,
I won't be able to see Eichi-kun!
Why you little brat!
Hurry! Hurry!
I've been waiting for you.
Well, give me back my camera.
I got it.
You won't listen to me anymore, huh?
Come on, that's enough, okay?
Hey, it's dangerous over there!
Come on, come back here!
Takuto, help me!
Takuto!
Man...
You got me worried!
That bastard!
W-What?
She's floating?
W-What are you?
I AM THE VENGEFUL SPIRIT OF THE CELEBRITIES YOU HAVE RUINED.
Vengeful spirit?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I AM HERE TO TAKE MY REVENGE.
What are you going to do to me?
UNTIL YOU TASTE MY SUFFERING,
I CANNOT FORGIVE YOU.
S-Stop it!
I beg you!
F-Forgive me, I'll do anything!
L-Like this...
THEN SWEAR THAT YOU'LL NEVER DO ANYTHING LIKE THIS AGAIN.
IF YOU DON'T, I'LL HAUNT YOU FOR ALL ETERNITY.
Got it!
I understand!
I'll never do it again!
WELL, NOW GET OUT OF HERE!
That should do it.
You did well.
Lens.
It disappeared.
You did it, Takuto!
Now we continue where we left off last week, we have Full Moon-san with us again.
Good to have you back.
I'm glad to be here.
By the way, Full Moon-san?
Yes?
About your secrets,
could you tell us one of them?
I think I will keep them secret!
So you're always gonna be the mysterious Full Moon-san, huh?
Yep.
Well, how about playing a song?
Full Moon's "Myself".
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
If it's about Saegusa,
you don't have to worry anymore.
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I don't know what happened, but he said he gave up his job and left the city.
Is that so?
Looks like he couldn't handle his own medicine.
Probably.
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I couldn't sing at all
Nani mo utaenakatta
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
It happened to be the place where I was
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
The desolation lying in your eyes
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Wait!
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
We can't enter Mitsuki's house!
Wait a second, I'm checking on it.
Eh?! A barrier from a saint's stone!
What's that?
Generally speaking, it's like a barrier we can't get through.
That's bad.
We have to go back and transform her quickly!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Spring Onion Ramen and the Saint's Stone
Look forward to it!