I want you to carry out one more task in LA sometime soon.
I thought the focus of our activities would shift to the East Coast.
This operation isn't coming from McGwire and the others.
Well, this is to score points personally.
So you want to make an unexpected contribution
and let your seniors owe you one, huh?
Yeah. So we need to carry this out secretly.
I rather like that sort of scheming myself.
I figured as much.
Understood. I'll do everything in profound secrecy.
This operation will show how great Phantom is, won't it...
The Past
So that was the seven day weather forecast.
Now for the latest news.
Bringing a large-scale shopping mall to Santa Monica...
It's a topic that is getting the attention of the locals.
Although the West Coast has many tourists throughout the year...
Who was it?
There was a shift change at my part time job.
They asked me if I could come in now.
I see.
I'll drop you off... I was planning to go out to practice driving anyway.
You don't need to.
If a couple lives together, they do at least that much, right?
Yeah, you're right.
The drug market on the West Coast
has long been monopolized by the Chinese mafia.
However, the Japanese mafia has been stepping in more frequently lately
and fights have been breaking out in Chinatown and surrounding areas.
Sources also point out that this can grow into a large conflict...
Be careful.
Don't worry. I won't goof up and get dragged into it.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want people to discover this place because you started a small fire.
Y-Yeah...
Going out?
Ms. McCunnen...
Would you like to come with me?
I'm sorry, but I have to practice driving.
Then, you can practice using this car.
What?
I'll walk.
How is it? Do you like this car?
You feel like you can keep on going forever, right?
Doesn't it make you feel like you're the king of the world?
No way. I'd just be thrown around in a car like this.
I'm impressed that you were able to stop the car. It was almost all over for you.
Over?
Nothing would be over... even if I died...
It'll only reduce the number of murder victims a little. That's all.
No!
Don't die for nothing. I'll decide the place for you to die.
A man who has won my trust has earned that much.
Now, go. Keep running, Zwei.
This is an unexpected mission, but... Just consider it a part time job.
Okay.
Claudia seems to be infatuated with Zwei.
Be sure not to let her steal him...
Even if that happens, there's no problem...
as Zwei's existence isn't a must for carrying out missions.
You're right.
You working as a duo with Zwei
was only a product of coincidence to begin with.
Go ahead and play with this car a little longer.
Come back within an hour.
What's going on?
Get familiar with this sort of thing.
Yeah...
Enjoy your drive, Zwei.
Quite a car you showed up in.
Is it okay to meet up openly like this?
Please don't worry.
I do put up a degree of smoke screen.
So it's okay for you to speak without hesitation here.
That's great.
I thought about the plan you came up with very carefully.
In short, you'll get the weapons and other arrangements ready.
And we'll prepare the soldiers.
Those are the terms, right?
Yes.
If we do that, we can have 500 kilograms of cocaine,
which is worth about 200 million, all to ourselves, huh?
Ha! In that case, we won't have any problems with funding for a while.
Right?
Yes sir.
You think this is fishy?
It's just that I can't see it, Ms. McCunnen.
What would you gain by suggesting such good terms for us?
I want to do you, the Godo Family, a favor for something in return.
The Godo Family's principle is loyalty. So I'm trying to have you owe me one.
Oh?
So you want backing, huh?
Yes.
I'll give you 200 million dollars.
But I'll gain something that's worth more than that.
It's true that it makes sense as a business deal.
Well, that's all right... since we've made our decision either way.
We'll take part in your plan.
You working as a duo with Zwei
was only a product of coincidence to begin with.
I'm an INN reporter.
Wha-?!
I have a favor to ask. Take this and...
Huh? I- What...
Give this to the police. That's all. Please!
Ah! Wait!
Why... is this...
I can't stand this anymore. I'm hungry.
What day is it today?
I want to go back... to Japan...
It's quiet... If I go now, maybe I could...
No... If I go out now, she'll find me right away.
She'll... kill me.
He's given Phantom such a hard time and he's still alive.
I'm impressed.
By suppressing even fear and hunger,
he chose to continue staying at this place.
He assessed that it was the only way to survive,
and his instinct made him continue to suppress his impulses.
Interesting... Such an interesting subject.
Zwei... Zwei... Wake up.
We're going out. Get ready.
O-Okay.
We've got a mission. We'll do it tonight.
We'll go check the site before it gets dark.
At 22:00 tonight, 500 kilograms of cocaine will be brought in here.
And Inferno will snatch it.
Our duty is to back up the assault unit.
Are the guys in the assault unit reliable?
Claudia seems to be infatuated with Zwei.
Be sure not to let her steal him.
I was told nothing about them.
So this is a mission only Phantom can carry out.
Let's go back. We have to get our weapons ready.
Ein... do you sometimes have dreams?
Dreams?
You see scenery that you've never seen or meet people you don't know.
I wonder if... those dreams are... my memories...
I don't know.
Haven't you had... a dream like that?
Sometimes... I have a dream about colors.
Colors, you said?
That's right. Colors.
And...
Wind.
Blue, white and green.
That's all there is in that place... There's nothing else.
But it's dazzlingly bright there
and there's a wind blowing. A strong wind...
I wonder if that scenery is your homeland.
I don't know.
But...
What about it? What will we do after knowing our homeland?
Don't you want to go check...
the place that remains in your memory?
There's no place for us there.
The place for killers...
is nowhere else...
but here.
There's nothing. Dreams are illusions.
All they do is interfere with reality.
Hey, it's me.
Lizzie...
I've got a message for you from Clo.
Go to Clo's house at 8 o'clock, Zwei.
This is on a really short notice. What's going on?
We're changing positions. I have to attend a big dealing tonight.
It's been decided that you'll be Clo's guard in place of me.
Hold on a second. We've already got orders for tonight.
What? No-one told me that.
Who gave you those orders?
Scythe Master.
Humph! He must be acting on his own.
You don't have to bother, as Clo is your boss.
But...
8 o'clock. Don't forget.
Go, Zwei.
Ein...
I'll carry out the mission given by Master by myself.
You follow Ms. McCunnen's instructions.
But... it's dangerous.
I'll be fine.
Doing it all by yourself...
It's not us...
who decide that.
Yes. It seems that he's doing quite a bit without involving me.
Scythe Master isn't a fool.
He probably tries to act ahead of the others.
Yes.
Then humor his little ambition under your management.
Take the car that we're hiding on Fifth Avenue.
Okay.
It doesn't matter if it's money or drugs. Just let him have his way.
But once he goes beyond those things...
Yes. I'll fulfill my duty.
I will bury Scythe, along with his puppet, immediately.
Ein...
Be careful.
You too...
Sudden Change
Next episode
If I come to know my past...
If I come to know about myself...
I'm not sure if I can continue being myself.