When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Let's stop with the chit-chat,
And now let's quietly observe.
If you're looking for a romance, it's already begun.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
This one is an original episode planned by Mister Hata.
Right?
So I hear.
Damn it.
Damn it, what's wrong with this game?
The graphics really suck; are you sure this is a *S3 game?
No, it isn't.
But I got tired of high-definition games, so I felt like playing an old game.
Oh, so recent games aren't good enough for you.
Then you can go play outside-
That makes me tired.
You got that right, but...
Rather than doing such a thing,
I want to play an old game and gain a new perspective on the high-definition games around the world.
Game Cartridge: Large Size of 4MB    New Dragon Hero Quest
I got a hold of an old rare game in an attempt to cleanse a dirty mind with its old nostalgic feeling, but...
Rather than you call this rare, the quality is you-know-what.
Simply put, that's what it is.
I have heard that the quality is you-know-what, but this game is worse than I'd thought.
Isn't that the good part about retro games?
But then, the sound is cheap, and the movements are blocky.
The graphics are so poor, you can hardly tell where you are.
Shut up Kansai person.
Go eat octopus puffs with white rice.
What'd'you say?!
Are you mocking the people of Kansai?
Sakuya, don't jump on a game.
You stop blaming the game when you suck.
Midget.
What did you call me?!
Damn you! Damn you shitty game!
I'll forever only put "AAA" in any name slot!
Um, the food's ready.
What are you two doing?
Nothing much. We were only removing an evil from this world.
What?
Anyway, what's for dinner?
Bell peppers stuffed with beef.
What? I don't like bell peppers.
You don't grow because you're selective with food.
And possibly more than just your height is at issue.
Wh-What are you implying?
Stop staring.
I haven't said anything, yet.
What did you think I was talking about?
The next morning!
The sun...
Why does it rise every morning?
What are you doing, complaining to great nature the moment you wake up?
The sun just doesn't understand!
Because you get rid of or take a rest from things from time to time,
when it does come back to us,
only then do we take pleasure from it.
W-We really shouldn't be putting thoughts like that on the airwave.
In any case, please get changed and get ready to go to school.
Sakuya-san and company are waiting.
Makita, Kunieda!
I'm off to school now!
"School", "school". Whatever.
Maria, am I having a déjá vu?
This scene is familiar looking.
Apparently this episode takes place during the same time frame as two episodes ago.
So they're zapping.
Anime's getting complicated, too.
The world has Digital broadcast, EP recording, digital coloration,
exportation to other countries in gross quantities,
storyboards being bid on net auctions, and a Minister of Manga.
I see, fine. I'll go along with this then.
Looks like I'll get to skip out of school, too.
Oh, so that's your reason this time?
"I'm off to school now!"
Sakuya exuberantly runs out of the room,
but she suddenly feels the urge to watch ***'s DVD, and turns back to the mansion's 2nd floor.
And she opens the door to the game room, and there she finds-
So you've seen me.
You...
I won't let you out of here alive.
Makita. Kunikita.
Ah! NO! You're going to break me!
Oh, it wasn't a fire?
Hey you! You're a game console!
What do you think you're doing talking?!
I'm so sticky ~tima.
"Tima"?
What kinda ending is that?
Is that the latest trend?
I get it. You must be the demon or something from that game, aren't ya?
Super observation.
Tima! How did you know?
And looks like she was right.
So I'm right?
I bet since you're such a shitty game, the hate to it got accumulated,
and what happened last night awakened you as a monster.
That ought to summarize it, eh?
S-Super observation ~tima.
I already said that.
So you know, I'm smart enough to reject an offer from Hakuou.
And I don't even have any status.
Makita, Kunieda. Break this thing before it does anything.
Aim for the reset button and the plug.
Don't come ~tima!
And that "Tima" ending is really pissing me off.
Tima~
Punishment.
The Demon's Castle!
I can't move! Can't get out ~tima!
A punishment! A punishment! A punishment!
Geez, shut up, shut up, shut up!
I was finally able to come out to the real world!
The Hero shows up at the end of the world.
That's right ~tima. I'm the last boss.
And this castle is the stage for the last battle.
If I defeat the Hero...
Tima~~
I might really be able to get out of here ~tima!
No, I think you'll go back to the title screen.
Now that that's settled, I first have to capture the Hero ~tima.
She's not listening to me.
Press.
It's set.
Um, Sir Hero! Please get caught!
Tima~
What do you think about this, Maria?
That looks good.
Tima!
Where are you going?
You can't walk around the house in that sailor uniform, can you?
Timama!
Tima! Tima! Tima!
Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima!
Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima! Tima!
Demon, The Great Stygian of Abe (Temp) wept.
This is horrible. Nobody notices me ~tima.
Punishment.
Geez, shut up, shut up, shut up!
Is someone here, ~tima?
No one's coming.
Eh? And we came all the way to see Nagi-chan's new butler.
We can't do anything about it, then.
Let's give up and instead go to Ekoda.
We shall and skip the rest of the classes.
What's this?
Miki-chan?!
Miki-chan, your underwear's sexy.
It's a new pair.
Let me see.
Owee...
What happened?
You're heavy.
Th-Thank you for noticing me.
Ahem. Now, Heroes. Your mission is to come find me at the Demon's Castle ~tima!
I hear breast-bouncing noises.
What's that?
This is horrible.
Wow, a graphic is moving.
No, from what I think, an old mistreated shitty game...
And abbreviating the rest.
What? Then we're inside the world of a game?
Now Heroes, time to fight that monster.
Fine. This happened because I picked up that controller.
I have no choice.
Y-You can't, Miki-chan! You can't fight alone!
Oh great Demon! She's the Hero!
Oh no!
Risa is dead!
The rest is up to you two.
Wh-What?!
Oh no! At this rate, the Heroes that finally came will die ~tima!
Punishment!
No they won't!
Press.
Hey, are you all right?
Somehow.
That was close ~tima.
Punishment!
Someone has it easy.
Risa-chin, you're cheating.
What! It's actually tight in here and not so comfortable!
I want to revive and fight with you all.
Y-You do?
I'm sure it's painful for you right now,
but we promise to find a village and revive you soon.
Thank you.
By the way, can I ask one more favor?
W-What is it?
I'm thirsty, so go buy me Poka**.
You're so mean, Risa-chin.
Stop playing a game inside a game.
No! This is, you know,
research to see if I can contact the real world.
Don't lie.
While the trio were arguing inside the game,
there was one person who noticed something was going on inside the mansion.
What should I do? I got lost the moment I woke up.
And to bring it up, this power I sense; it must be a ghost.
It must be in here.
I was wrong.
You'll find out the top three in part B!
Sumeshi Beam!
Sumeshi Beam! = Vinegared Rice Beam!
Old gag by comedy Trio, Dachou Club.
Musshu Mura Mura
Today's Fortune Countdown!
The third is Cancer.
Your lucky spot is a hot spring.
You might meet destiny.
In second place is Taurus.
A happy day where everything you do will work out.
If you're going to quit being a NEET, today's the day.
Be courageous!
And first place is!
Happy smiles.
Great selection.
At Rental Video Tachibana Shinjuku HQ,
we wait to see people who can tell the difference.
Now please continue to enjoy Hayate no Gotoku episode 10,
Witnessed the Tear of the Snake Woman.
The Student Council Trio trapped in
the game finally made it to a village.
Where's the church?
I want to revive my friend out of the casket.
No matter who I talk to, they only say "Nunu"!
Looks like this game is beyond our capabilities.
Fine, then I'll have to...
I am very heated up right now!
Kin* Squasher!
Hello. Yes, it's me Miki.
Sorry, but please come here right now.
Here I am.
So?
So fast!
Um, Hina-chan, didn't you get attacked by something strange on the way?
Yeah I did, but I shooed them away with this.
So what's this all about?
Give me a good explanation.
Don't be surprised hearing this.
We're inside a cursed game,
and *mumble mumble*, abbreviating the rest.
There's no way such an unscientific thing could happen.
U-Um...
This is, you know, must be a elaborate
surprise event set by Nagi, since she loves games.
It has to be.
But this is really well-made.
That's our President for you.
How are these moving?
She's so down-to-earth.
In a way, it's an amazing talent.
By the way, you three weren't intending to skip afternoon classes, were you?
A-Absolutely not.
Then let's take care of this and go back to school before lunch break ends.
Oh, but where's the goal?
S-So reliable.
She is suitable to be the Hero ~tima.
Punishment, punishment, punishment.
If she comes here, I might be freed from this noisy skull and this annoying "tima" ending ~tima.
Press.
Banner: Over here ~tima
Equipment came falling from the sky all of a sudden.
I see. So you want us to use those to get to that tower.
Is that what those are for?
All right then, let us all go beat the Demon!
Hakuou! Fight!
F-Fight, oh!
Fight!
Hinagiku's so diligent.
Fight, oh!
Looks like we can leave the story to Katsura-san.
Yup.
Since we have some time now,
why don't we take the chance to read our fan mail.
From Tokyo N-ward, penname Tama Lover.
Hayate-kun, Nagi-san, and Maria-san, hello.
Hello.
I always watch Hayate no Gotoku and have lots of fun.
Thank you.
By the way, I saw the profile on the official web page and I was surprised.
Maria-san is only 17...
Yes, I'm 17.
Is there a problem?
You looked so calm, I thought you were over 20.
Maria-san, how about acting like a 17 year old from time to time and say things like "Eww, that, like, so sucks."
Tama Lover! Maria is young! She's young!
I mean she's-
I see...
I seem that old?
I'll repeat myself, but I'm 17.
I'm still fresh.
I'm not old. I'm just stressed from the daily workload.
Thanks to you know who.
I'm sorry. And I'm always grateful to you.
Right, Hayate?
Hey, why aren't you talking?
Since most of the characters play the dumb role, in order to make story funny, I play the jab role.
It's only natural, since I have the most common sense.
But then, a small girl sent us a letter like this.
Sure, that's fine. I'm only...
Hayate! Why aren't you speaking?!
Ah, here's the next letter.
From Tokyo K-ward, Sgt. Furuicchi.
I love Maria-san.
Battle!
Over the sea, through some dungeons, and after about 100 hours of play time,
the Student Council party made it to where the Demon lives.
It's finally the moment of the last battle, where lies the fate of this universe.
Demon, The Great Stygian of Abe (Temp)!
Fight us!
Just the way I want it ~tima.
Take the wrath of my ultima te attack.
Press.
Demon has been defeated.
So weak! The Demon's so weak!
You're amazing Hero. Your strike was unseen before ~tima.
I haven't done anything yet.
I can give up now.
I can head to the underworld without regret ~tima.
On a second thought, I don't want to go ~tima.
But I feel like it's okay to go ~tima.
But...
Make up your mind!
This isn't getting dramatic at all.
Punishment for not being decisive.
Katsura Hinagiku
And the Student Council Trio
Defeated the Demon as such,
And traveled through time
And made it back to
Reality.
Losing all memory of the adventure
In the game...
Thank you, oh Hero.
Thank you, oh Hakuou Gakuen Student Council.
Some kind of thanks and some kind of finale.
But your battle has only started.
Next time, we'll fight for the seat of main character.
It was fun.
It all ended well.
Yeah.
Hey! Aren't you forgetting somethin'?
I'm sorry. I opened the door without thinking.
What kinda ending is this?!
Haven't we been mistreated recently?
From the beginning.
Next week, we'll go back to the main story and give you the heartfelt tale of a butler.
Nagi's
Butler Network!
Hayate's missing today, so I'm going to use this section as I like.
Oh no, that's a problem.
Now's the only moment you can be relaxed.
Eh?
Since I'm leading this section today, I'm free to do whatever I want.
As fans have requested, I'm going to insert Maria's service shot.
Oh no.
Probably nobody wants it, but here's Klaus' bath scene!
NO!!!
If you keep doing this, you'll never catch up
with the production schedule.
That is a problem.
Let's not use Klaus anymore.
Bye bye.
Nagi, how about you visit the main house where your grandfather is once in a while?
It'd be good to introduce Hayate-kun, too.
Don't wanna.
Besides, why go say hi to that old man now?
Man, it's been a while since I last met Old Mikado.
I'll rip some cash off of him.
What Saku, you're coming, too?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
My Life is Priceless.
So your life is worthless, I take it.
An armor surrounds your heart.