Okay! Try introducing yourself to everyone!
Um... I-I'm Akemi Homura...
I, uh... N-Nice to meet all of you.
Akemi Homura
Akemi-san was in the hospital for a long time due to problems with her heart.
She hasn't been to school in a while, so I'm sure there will be times where she'll be a bit confused.
Everyone, make sure you help her out.
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
Were you in any clubs?
Did you play any sports? How about art?
Your hair's really long. It must take a lot of time braiding it every morning.
I, uh...
Akemi-san, you need to go to the nurse's office, right?
Do you know where it is?
Huh?
No...
I'll take you there, then.
I'm the health officer for this class.
Sorry everyone,
Akemi-san has to take medicine at the nurse's office during her breaks.
Oh, really? Sorry for keeping you.
Talk to you later, Akemi-san.
Sorry about that.
They're not trying to be mean.
It's just rare to have a transfer student, so they're all excited over it.
No, it's okay...
Thank you.
No need to be that nervous.
We're classmates.
My name is Kaname Madoka.
Call me Madoka.
I...
It's fine.
Could I call you Homura-chan?
I... haven't been called by my first name very much.
It's a really weird name.
What? That's not true.
It feels really exciting and cool.
I'm nothing like my name then.
You shouldn't say that!
You have such a wonderful name, so you should just be cooler to match it!
How about you try this problem?
Oh yeah, you were away from school, weren't you?
Make sure you borrow notes from a friend.
She got light-headed during warm-up exercises? That's pretty bad.
Well, she couldn't do much but sleep for half a year. She can't help it.
...so you should just be cooler to match it!
I can't do that. I can't do anything myself.
I just cause trouble for everyone else and embarrass myself.
Why...
Will I always be like this?
Then it'd be better if you just died, huh?
Maybe it would.
Yeah, you should just die.
Just... die...
W-Where... am I?
What?
What is that?!
No!
That was close.
It's okay now, Homura-chan!
Y-You're...
They're magical girls.
They hunt witches.
Who knew someone would find out about our secret so quickly?
Don't tell our class, okay?
Tomoe
Mami
Kaname-san, do you always fight those things?
Always? Well, Mami-san's the veteran here.  I only contracted with Kyubey just last week.
But the way you fought today was much better than before, Kaname-san.
You're fine? You're not scared?
Well, we're not fine, and we do get scared,
but when we destroy a witch, we save a lot of people.
It's worth it, don't you think?
Kaname-san needs to become a magical girl in
her own right before the Walpurgis Night comes.
I'll be going, then.
You can't...
Tomoe-san died.
That's why I'm going.
I'm the only one left who can stop the Walpurgis Night.
You can't win against that alone! It's hopeless!
You'll die too, Kaname-san!
I'm still a magical girl.
I have to protect everyone.
Please... let's run away.
We don't have any other choice.
No one would hate you for it.
Homura-chan, I'm glad I could be friends with you.
I made it there just in time when you were attacked by that witch... I'm still proud of that.
So I'm glad I became a magical girl. I really am.
Kaname-san...
Good bye, Homura-chan.
Be well.
No! Don't go, Kaname-san!
Why...
You knew you were going to die.
I wanted you to live...
...instead of saving me...
Is what you're saying true, Akemi Homura?
Would you be willing to trade your soul for that wish?
If you have a desire so strong you would be
willing to accept a fate of combat, I'll help you.
If I contract with you, will any wish I have really be granted?
That's correct.
It seems that you qualify.
Now tell me, with what wish will you make your Soul Gem shine?
I...
I want to relive meeting Kaname-san for the first time.
Not as someone she protects, but as someone who can protect her instead!
The contract is complete.
Your desire has overcome entropy.
Now release your new power!
Where am I?
I still haven't been released from the hospital...
Mitakihara Junior
High School
Entrance Guide
It wasn't a dream!
Okay! Try introducing yourself to everyone!
Akemi Homura, nice to meet you all.
Akemi-san was in the hospital for a long time due to her heart-
Kaname-san, I became a magical girl too!
Let's work hard together!
Uh...
Here I go!
What do you think, Mami-san?
Stopping time, huh?
It's pretty amazing, but the question is how to use it.
Yeah.
Mami-san, right now!
Okay!
Akemi-san, your turn!
R-Right!
We did it...
We did it?
We did it!
Good work.
That was amazing!
That was amazing, Homura-chan!
What's wrong?
Hey, Kaname-san! Hang on!
Why...
What?
Why did this happen?
I have to tell them. Everyone's being tricked by Kyubey!
Uh, so why exactly would Kyubey lie about something like that?
That's because...
Are you trying to turn us against each other by telling us something weird?
Wait, you're not working together with that Kyouko girl, are you?
N-No!
Sayaka-chan, we're starting to fight with each other.
Either way, I'm against teaming up with her.
Mami-san and Madoka-san use projectile weapons, so it's okay,
but having explosions appear in front of you out of nowhere is a little much...
Who knows how many times we were almost hit by them?
Akemi-san, do you have any other weapons besides explosives?
I'll think of something.
What the hell are you?
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Sayaka-chan, stop it!
Please remember!
This isn't something you'd want to do!
I'm sorry, Miki-san.
Sayaka, damn it...
This is...
This is terrible.
It's too much.
Tomoe-san?!
If the Soul Gems give birth to witches, then we all have to die!
Both you and I!
Stop it!
I've had enough.
I've had enough of this...
It's okay.
Let's work together.
Let's work together to take on Walpurgis Night.
Yeah.
It looks like it's over for both of us.
Do you have any Grief Seeds?
I see.
Do you just want to become monsters and destroy everything in the world?
We'll destroy everything, and we'll keep
destroying it until it looks like all the bad things...
...all the sad things-never even happened at all.
Don't you think that sounds nice?
I lied just then.
I had one saved.
You can't...
Why did you give it to me?
Because I wanted to ask you to do something I can't.
You've said you can go back to the past, right, Homura-chan?
You've said you can change history so this all won't have happened, right?
Yeah.
Could you save my stupid self before I get tricked by Kyubey?
I promise.
I'll definitely save you.
No matter how many times I have to repeat all of this, I'll protect you!
I'm glad...
Could I ask you for one more thing?
Yeah.
I don't want to become a witch.
A lot of horrible and sad things have happened,
but there are so many things I had in this world that I wanted to protect.
Madoka!
Homura-chan, you finally called me by my name...
I'm happy...
No one will believe the future.
No one will be able to accept the future.
Then I'll have to...
W-Who's there?
Madoka, if someone appears promising
you a miracle, you mustn't do as he says.
What...
I won't depend on anyone any more.
There's no need for anyone to understand any more.
I won't let Madoka fight any more.
I'll take care of all the witches by myself.
And this time, I'll stop the Walpurgis Night myself.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
toki o koete
...transcends time,
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
How awful!
There's nothing you can do.
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
It was too much for her to handle alone.
This is too awful! It shouldn't be happening!
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
Madoka, don't listen to what he's saying!
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
If you give up, it'll be the end of everything.
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
But you have the capacity to change fate.
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
This unavoidable destruction, this sorrow-you can change it all. You have the power to do that.
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
Are you telling the truth?
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
Don't be tricked! That's what he wants!
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
Can someone like me really do something to stop this?
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
Can I really prevent everything from turning out this way?
Of course you can! Form a contract with me and become a magical girl!
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
negai
...the light.
No!
Transformed Madoka was really amazing.
I had predicted she'd become the strongest magical girl,
but I never would have imagined that she'd end Walpurgis Night in one hit.
You did that knowing what would probably happen?
Sooner or later, the same thing would have happened, either way.
She defeated the greatest enemy as the strongest magical girl.
Of course she'd have to become the worst witch after that was over.
Madoka, in this form, will probably destroy this planet within ten days or so.
Well, the rest is your problem; humanity's problem.
We've pretty much hit the quota of energy we needed to collect.
Aren't you going to fight?
No, my battlefield is not here.
Akemi Homura, are you...
I'll repeat it. I'll continue to repeat it over and over.
Visiting the same time again and again, searching for the single way out.
Searching for the path to save you from a fate of despair.
Madoka... my one and only friend.
Homura-chan?
If it's... If it's for you,
I have no problem being trapped eternally in this maze.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 10     I won't rely on anyone any longer
Illustrator     Mura Kuroe
Did you not feel anything watching over them all that time?
Did you not try to understand how much pain everyone was in?
Episode 11     The final sign left
The final sign left.