I'll hold them off. Go on ahead.
Women's
Bath
Women's     bath
Women's           bath
bath
UNAUTHORIZED
They changed the password!
What?!
Doesn't it bother you to betray your allies?
I'm not the fool you think I am.
Leave me and run!
Shouko!
Oh, no! Someone changed the shampoo and conditioner.
What?! Who could've done it?
Madam Principal, prepare for evacuation.
Damn you, Punishment Inspector!
Oh! I see the rear with the burns!
She's the one who threatened and framed us!
Huh? Akihisa wasn't the peeping tom?
I'm sorry for doubting you, Aki.
It's all right. I'm just glad you understand.
All right, fellas. You can peep on the girls' bath as much as you want today.
Yay! Coming in, ladies!
Argh
A
Peeping tom
holding
stone slabs
Welcome back to the world of reality.
Episode 7
Me, peeping, and the distant Shangri-La
It's the third night
of the school trip.
Damn! They even got Ms. Takahashi to help them!
It should be illegal to hit us that hard.
But what can we do? If this keeps up, you'll be terrorized by that spy for all eternity.
I'm not gonna give up, of course.
But tomorrow is the last night for the girls to bathe.
I've finalized my next plan,
but we need more than just the boys of Classes D, E, and F.
Voyeur!
Leave the photographs to me.
Akihisa, call Himeji and Shimada.
What are you gonna do?
We'll bait the boys of the other classes with photos of the girls to join us.
I see. Thou planst to make use of their lust.
Well then, here you go, Hideyoshi!
I believe we were going to bait the boys.
I'll email Himeji and Minami.
"I have something to talk about. Can you come to my room?"
Send.
Hey, Himeji replied!
Okay! I'll bring some sweets over too!
Minami too.
I don't mind, but what do you want to talk about so late?
She's suspicious. How should I reply?
Huh? A message from Sugawa?
Yoshii, why are you so desperate to peep on the girls, anyway?
Why? Come on. Isn't it obvious?
Because my heart tells me to.
Calm down, Yoshii Akihisa! Think carefully about what just happened!
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Did something happen, Akihisa?
Yeah, you just fucked me over big time.
My bad, my bad! Give me a sec, and I'll fix it.
Never mind! Just lend me yours!
Here.
I need to tell Minami it was a mistake.
Huh? The address book only has Kirishima's info.
What? Damn that girl, messing with my phone!
I thought she was horrible with electronics!
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
By the way, Yuuji, do you remember Minami's email address?
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
Do you remember Shouko's?
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
Come to my room,
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
Come to my room,
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
Come to my room,
Yeah, I figured as much.
COMPOSE NEW MESSAGE
Kirishima Shouko
Sakamoto Yuuji
I want to propose to you.
Come to my room,
Shouko.
Hey! What did you send just now?
Now I can't tell her it was a mistake, you retard!
Right back at you, Yuuji! Right back at you!
Keep it down!
Yes, sir.
Fuck! I gotta message Shouko right now!
Lend me a phone!
I haven't bought one after I threw the last one away.
I don't want it ringing during my covert ops, so...
It's over. My glorious life is over.
Come in!
Good evening!
Come on in, Himeji.
Huh? Didn't Ironman stop you?
I gave him some sweets, and he let me pass.
Farewell, Ironman. Rest in peace.
So, Akihisa, what did you want to talk about?
Oh, just come here for a sec.
Just like that, the boys got their photographs, and night turned into day.
But before that...
Aki! Aki!
Are you asleep?
Hey! Wake up!
Wake up!
I said, wake up!
Shh! Not so loud!
Don't go back to sleep!
M-Minami, what are you doing here?
Wait. I know!
First, I sent that weird email to her.
Second, Minami got mad.
Third, she snuck into the room under the cover of night.
Next, she's gonna whip out weapons out of nowhere,
so I should just...
Please make it quick and painless.
Who the hell do you think I am?
Huh? Am I wrong?
I had to muster up all my courage to come here, you know.
So, tell me...
and not through a text message...
I want to hear it with my own ears.
She wants to hear my last will and testament!
Is there anything I can use to save myself?
Hideyoshi's sleeping with such a cute face.
Voyeur's busy taking more pictures.
Kirishima's taking off her yukata and climbing onto Yuuji's bed.
Damn! Everyone's busy doing their own thing!
I'll save you, darling!
Not another one!
Miharu, why are you here?
I crawled into your bed, but it was empty,
so I thought you might've been in this room.
Didn't you already crawl in last night?!
Did she crawl in last night too?
Darling, let's hurry back and snuggle our naked bodies together!
Of course I'm not gonna let you sleep.
Come on! Take it off!
I won't let you sleep either.
What be all this hullabaloo?
Keep it down, guys! If it gets too loud, he'll—
What's going on?!
What's all this racket?
This is bad, Akihisa!
We can't let him find us with four half-naked girls in the room.
Are you counting me again?
Yuuji and I will distract him.
You girls run when you get a chance!
Let's go!
I hope you're ready, Yoshii.
I... am... not!
Then clench your teeth!
We don't have a choice. Let's hide in a room Ironman can't enter!
What room is that?
The girls' room!
Good idea! Ironman can't go in the girls' room.
If I hide in the girls' room in my boxers—
That'll be like entering the seventh circle of Hell!
Let's go!
No fucking way!
Oh, all right. Wear this!
Thanks!
All right, you can hide now.
Hold it! This is worse than if I was fully naked.
All right, time to split up!
Oh no you don't!
I don't want to be seen together with a pervert.
Then give me your yukata, you bastard!
Hey, stop that!
Shut up! Take it off! Take it off!
What are you...
doing exactly?
I know this doesn't involve girls, but you still shouldn't do that in public, okay?
No, wait! We can explain!
It was a midsummer night's dream. Whew whew!
Are the two of you all right?
You need to be in shape to take the tests and improve your grades.
We've had Ironman's remedial classes for three nights straight now.
It's been horrible!
However, we've achieved our objective.
Good job, Voyeur!
Let's talk with the guys and get them to join us!
Thus, the four-day campaign of the school trip reaches its final stages.
I discovered something from the last battle.
These are the records of the unit stationed on the second floor.
It's from when the science and humanities squads were intercepted by the girls of Class C.
The teacher's summon could interact with real-world objects. 'Twas impassable.
Oh! Mr. Takenaka's wig!
Watch closely!
The summoning field... disappeared!
If the fields set up by teachers of different subjects touch each other, they cancel out.
I see. They interfere with each other.
This is our last chance.
The enemy will surely set up an impenetrable defense.
We'll fight them in the summoning fields,
and push through a single route with our forces.
This is how their forces will be positioned.
Our room is on the third story.
The objective is in the basement.
Ms. Takahashi, Mr. Ooshima, and Ironman will be standing guard there.
We have the boys of Classes D, E, and F on our side.
It all depends on how much support we get from Classes A, B, and C.
It shall be a tough battle.
I'll take care of Ms. Takahashi.
Mr. Ooshima is the PE teacher, so I'll leave him to you, Voyeur.
And Akihisa, you'll take care of Ironman.
Me?
Only you, the Punishment Inspector, can defeat him. Please!
But...
In return, all of us will cover you, so you don't get a scratch until you find Ironman.
We're ready to sacrifice ourselves to keep you from harm before your battle.
Yuuji!
Will you do it, Akihisa?
Yeah!
'Tis time! Operation is go!
All right! Are you dogs ready to fight?!
This is our last chance! I won't accept anything but victory!
Whether girls or teachers, they will fall before men!
Our final operation, on this fourth night of our school trip,
begins now!
Here they come!
The four ringleaders!
This is as far as you go.
Summoned being, summon!
Summon!
Die, puny Class F!
Say that after you've studied some more!
We don't have time to mess with the small fry!
Hold it right there, Sakamoto!
Class D's rep, Hiraga!
Leave him to us! Go on ahead!
Thanks! We shall meet again in Valhalla!
They do have high morale, nay?
It's because everyone is united.
The real battle starts now.
We're not gonna last long without more reinforcements, though.
You boys again?!
Mr. Fuse, please prepare yourself.
You too? Why?!
Kurosaki from Class C!
Voyeur showed me pictures of girls in yukata.
I didn't know it would warm my heart so!
I realized I wanted to see what was under those yukata!
Thank you for your assistance.
I'll entrust our rear flank to you!
And I shall entrust my dreams to you!
Men of Class C, make a path for them!
A road to glorious victory!
I guess all the classes are gonna help us.
No, we still haven't heard from Class A.
Those photos had no effect on Kubo.
How can that be? Does Kubo have an even better collection already?
MAIN
BATH
WOMEN'S BATH
What took you so long?
Class B is here too!
Yuuji, that's enough naughtiness for today.
Shouko!
Himeji!
We won't let you pass, Akihisa!
We can't hold on any longer! There's no way... we can beat those two.
Nemoto!
This was doomed from the start!
Was there even a point in peeping if Himeji and Kirishima weren't in the bath?
Don't give up! I know those two aren't in the bath, but there are still a lot of girls!
You're just saying that.
There is no girls' bath not worth peeping on!
So please... please...
Akihisa, we have lost so much. Why dost thou not give up?
Even if we find those pictures now, thy reputation is already dirtier than mud.
You're wrong, Hideyoshi.
You're right. At first, I wanted to find the pictures in that camera, apprehend the spying girl, and clear my name.
But when we got so many allies,
and when those very allies sacrificed themselves for my cause, I realized something.
Akihisa!
I know what I'm doing is unforgivable, but I won't betray my heart.
Right now, I really, honestly, for the sake of my libido,
want to peep on the girls' bath!
Thou art a bigger fool than I thought.
So you want to peep on Minami and not me?
I'm going to punish you!
Peeping is wrong!
I don't give a shit about society's rules!
I... will live true... to my heart!
Well said, Yoshii.
Who's there?!
Sorry I'm late, Yoshii.
I attest to your declaration of your true feelings.
Kubo! You came!
I was confused before, but your words have opened my eyes.
All 24 boys of Class A... belong to you!
Everyone! Back him up!
Thanks, Kubo!
I should be thanking you.
Just like you said, I'm being true to my heart.
Even if society shuns me, I will love what I love!
Don't interfere with his punishment!
Summon!
I've sworn to protect Yoshii. I won't let you have your way with him!
Now's our chance! Move!
Well!
I didn't think Class A would join you too.
No matter. You won't get past me.
Summon!
Nope, I'm coming through!
Run! Akihisa!
Summon!
Oh no you don't!
I almost thought you weren't coming, Voyeur.
Kudou's here too!
Proceed with the plan.
Go on ahead, Akihisa.
But—
It's all right.
I'll defer to Voyeur and let you pass.
Go.
All right. Don't die on me, Voyeur!
I'm disappointed in you, Tsuchiya.
Do you really think you can defeat a teacher?
Who decided that?
Who decided that a student can't defeat a teacher?!
That's rich. Come at me!
Summon!
His grade is 774!
I've never seen someone with such high grades in PE!
Faith can move mountains.
You brat. When did you gain that much power?
I don't have time. It's time to put an end to both of you!
I bet you're wondering how I managed to come here.
I always assess the abilities of my opponents first.
You're an idiot, but I acknowledge that you have spunk!
Why, thank you!
I know you're not an average stubborn guy either!
You missed your only chance!
I haven't even given it my all yet!
In that case...
I'll make you give it your all!
You moron. You'll be suspended if you're caught peeping!
No, I won't. There's no way you'll find the real peeping tom if there are so many of us.
Fool, do you really believe that?
You're distracted!
I'll beat you all to pulp until I find the real one!
You're finished, Yoshii.
How... can I defeat him?
I don't expect someone so underhanded to have much concentration.
Concentration? It's not from lack of effort...
Concen—
I know! I must concentrate.
I need to change my focus.
My summon and I will now converge our attacks.
We're gonna focus on your crotch!
What?!
You bastard. What the fuck are you saying?!
Get ready, Ironman!
Die!
Just kidding.
I did it!
I will not let you take my darling's chastity!
Shimizu!
Withdraw! Otherwise, I'll spread these photographs and your social standing will be history!
My picture!
Don't tell me that... you have a burn on your butt, Shimizu.
How do you know that?!
So you're the one who threatened me!
And you installed that secret camera in the girl's bath!
You know too much. I can't let you live.
Come with me quietly—
Well done, Akihisa!
Yuuji! Guys! You're all right!
Of course!
Now that we're all here, they won't know who's really peeping, will they?
Yeah!
We have nothing to fear as long as we're together! Let's go!
It was a hard and painful battle, but at last, they've won.
The men walk with pride in their hearts with no one to stop them.
What on Earth are you boys doing?
It wasn't worth it!
Circular on Punishment
All 149 second-year boys
of Fumizuki Academy
are to be suspended for one week.
Principal   Toudou Karura
All 149 second-year boys of Fumizuki Academy were suspended for one week.
CONFIRMED
Here with my egg on rice
In the middle of the day
I was alone in this stall
I was surrounded by the scent of solitude
My worthless lunch makes me sick
But the guy next door started eating his curry
Gotta be shittin' me
Hold your horses
This curry-guy has no respect for me
I'm here to be alone
I have nothing else, ya'know?
I'd have nothing, not even this.
Gathered my courage, gathered my all, and banged on that wall
That's when I took a look-see.
It was just another me.
Write a
summary of
your third day
at the
training camp.
Question 7:
Tsuchiya Kouta's
entry:
Omitted. Continued by
Sakamoto Yuuji.
Teacher's comment:
So this time you pass
the answer to
someone else?
You never run out of good ideas, do you?
Sakamoto Yuuji's entry:
Then Shouko loosened the waistband       of her yukata         right in front of me.
I grabbed her hand and tried to stop         her. Meanwhile, Shimada was inching closer to Akihisa nearby.
The atmosphere was getting tense.           Continued by Yoshii Akihisa.
Teacher's comment:
Just what was happening to you boys? I'm really curious now about the part Tsuchiya omitted.
Yoshii Akihisa's entry:
Omitted.
Teacher's comment:
Don't leave me hanging like that.
Akihisa!
It's been a week, Himeji! How are you?
Akihisa, I'm sorry!
Huh? What?
We thought you were peeping on us on the first night of the school trip.
I'm really sorry!
Nah, we did peep in the end.
Aki!
Hey, Mina—
Question 8
Answer the following
question.
What were your hopes
and dreams when you
first entered the
academy?
Himeji
Mizuki's
answer:
My constitution had been frail at the time, so I
wished to lead a healthy school life with everyone.
Teacher's comment
That's a good answer. Well done, Himeji.
You did seem frail at the time, but I'm glad you've been
in good health these days. You also seemed quite
reserved back then, but looking at your lively group
of friends now, I can see you have grown in that
respect as well. I hope you'll continue to have a good
time at school.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
I knew I was special. I was waiting for my genius to be recognized and applauded.
Teacher's comment
Time to wake up.
Question 8.
Please write what dreams and hopes you had on the day you entered this academy.
I knew I was special. I was waiting for my genius to be recognized and applauded.
Time to wake up.
Next time: Me, Japan, and words I don't know.
Next time:
Me, Japan, and Words I Don't Know
Words I Don't Know
This will be on the test.