It's summer.
I want to die.
Don't be so depressing, Tooru.
cover: "Swimming at the Beach"
Since it's summer, why don't we go to the beach?
I don't want other people to see my skinny body.
Gosh, don't worry so much!
Everyone in the world is unique.
You should take advantage of that!
Run-chan.
Plus, people with certain fetishes...
I didn't need the last part!
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
ふわふわ　浮遊して
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
きらめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
一つになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
私の行方は彼方
Let's go together.
issho ni ikou
一緒に行こう
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
セカイのSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　集まるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
おはようと　さよならの　間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
私たちだけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
生まれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ち合わせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振る君へと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
取って置きの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
おしゃべりが始まる
Ta-dah!
That's why I bought a swimsuit for you, Tooru!
I picked the smallest size, too.
Let's go to the beach with this!
Here!
I'm sure it'll look good.
Go on, try it on!
O-Okay.
It looks great!
But it's... a little... loose...
I'm coming in!
I bought some ice cream!
Er...
What's this?
Tooru, she's got ice cream!
I-I-I'm not hungry right now!
Hey, what's wrong with Tooru?
Well, this and that...
Ah, this is the new one they came out with this year!
I always wanted to try it!
That's why I decided to buy some.
What a coincidence.
Want to split it, then?
Sure!
On second thought, I'll have some!
Wha...
Why are you naked?
Beach
Gym
Math
Eng
Elec.
Chem.
board: "Pool"
Pool time!
She changed fast!
Goodness.
Getting all worked up over the pool, even in high school.
It must be blissful being Yutaka.
What are you saying?
When it comes to summer, it's gotta be the pool!
Did you forget this is a class?
It's still the pool!
Hm?
Toorun, your swimsuit is faded everywhere but here.
Is it a hand-me-down?
This is... because I've been wearing this since elementary school.
Ow!
Gosh! That's dangerous!
Floating feels so nice...
Yutaka, your breasts sure are big.
They sure are.
Hmph. All that fat floats, so it must make swimming easier.
Backhanded compliment, huh? Jealous?
O-Of course not- hm?
No fat at all!
So hot!
Gym is really harsh in the summertime.
So the first-years have swimming class.
Ah! It's Tooru!
You're right! The pool sure looks refreshing.
All right, gather 'round!
Must be nice.
I'm jealous.
What's this, Nagi? I thought you hated the pool.
I do hate the pool.
Or rather, I don't want to wear a swimsuit.
However!
Toooruuu!
Splash water on me! Buckets of water!
Nagi's gone crazy from the heat!
Stop it, Nagi!
Let go! Let go, I say!
Tooru! Water! Water!
Well, whatever.
Huh? The beach?
Yep! Summer vacation starts next week, so let's all go!
I'm in!
Huh?
I don't have any swimsuits I can wear at the beach.
I don't want to wear one, period.
What are you two saying? I'm sure that's not true!
W-What?
I'm sorry, did you hear that?
Just because she's got such a nice body...
Just because she's so fair-skinned.
Gosh, what are you saying?
It's not about that!
My, how modest.
Geez...
I'd rather go to the beach with everyone.
Thank you very much!
All that walking's made me hot.
Sorry for making you come with me.
Nah, I bought some stuff too.
Shall we take a break somewhere?
Huh?
Nagi?
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
All the cold air's gathered here. It's nice!
I'll take a break here.
Wha-Nagi, stand up! Please!
That girl back there was tall!
She's probably over 170 centimeters.
People must think I'm huge.
Nah, I'm sure they're jealous.
You're slender, and both your height and chest are impressive.
The chest part was unnecessary.
These give me a lot of problems, you know.
Really?
These bras are nice!
Plus they're cheap. Maybe I'll get one?
You're right. I want one too!
Hm? What is it?
Lingerie
In-stock
items only
These only go up to size D.
Sizes
only
In-stock
items only
Sizes
only
I guess being small can be convenient sometimes.
Let's go home already.
Hey, want to go take a look?
What now?
I thought we decided not to go to the beach.
Oh come on, they're so cute!
Well, I'm not buying anything.
Hey!
Nagi!
How's this?
Looks fine.
Really?
I'm gonna try them on, so can you take a look?
Sure.
How is it?
Perfect.
Really?
In that case...
How about this one?
Just right.
In that case...
How about this?
Like it was made for you.
Really? It's so hard to decide!
I'll go try some different ones.
Just wait for a bit, 'kay?
Sure.
Okay!
Nagi! Thanks for waiting!
Huh?
I-It's not what it looks like! I-I'm just...
I was just taking a look...
I'll try some on.
Right!
And I bought one.
It's fine! It looked great on you!
Thanks.
Oh yeah!
Texting someone?
Yep. Asking Run and Tooru if they want to go to the beach.
What?
I can't wait!
Just two more kilograms.
Not happening, is it?
Run says okay!
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Run-chan was just here.
Did she already leave?
Yeah. She just had something to give you.
This is a swimsuit I used to wear.
I think it'll fit you perfectly!
Let's race to that island, Tooru...
Play hard, learn hard,
and I look forward to seeing you all full of energy at the start of the next semester.
board: "Summer Vacation!!"
Wait up!
Ocean! Ocean! Ocean! Ocean! Ocean!
Ocean! Ocean!
What are you, a kid?
The ocean!
Ocean!
Huh?
It's so pretty!
We're in the middle of the road.
Streetcar mode, I guess.
You're right.
Wow! It goes on the road!
I wonder when they attached them?
Huh? Attached what?
The tires, of course!
There aren't any.
Yahoo!
We're here!
The beach!
All right! Time to swim!
Being at the beach always gets my spirits up!
Me too!
Run-chan.
Thanks for lending me your swimsuit.
No problem! I'm glad it fits.
Sorry the design's sort of childish.
It's fine.
After all,
it's from when I was in elementary school!
Hey!
What are you doing? Let's hurry up and go!
Coming!
Elementary school...
Take that!
You got me!
Yah!
Gosh, that tickles!
And up you go!
What gives?
That looks like fun, Tooru!
Let go... of me...
Tooru? Nagi?
Look at your head!
What?
Seaweed.
Huh?
Ugh!
It looks good on you, Nagi!
Looks good!
Seaweed...
Let me have a time-out.
Aw, come on, Nagi, tired already?
I woke up at 5 AM!
I'm running out of steam here.
I'm still doing fine!
Well, I'm a weakling.
Then let's take a breather.
I'll go buy some juice!
Ah, then get me a melon soda, please.
Sure thing.
Sports drink for me.
Okay!
She really must have been tired.
Melon Soda
Fried Noodles
Grape Juice
Cola Float
Melon Soda
Fried Noodles
Grape Juice
Cola Float
Welcome!
House on the Sea Enojima Center
There's a lot of choices.
Which should I get?
Run-chan. That one.
Swe~et Amber Candy Juice
Citrus Soft Drink
Ramune
Cola
Swe~et Amber Candy Juice
Citrus Soft Drink
Ramune
Cola
I never imagined that here, of all places,
I would encounter the legendary amber candy juice!
Uh-huh.
Nagi-chan! We're back.
Hey.
Huh?
Yuuko's sleeping.
She really is.
Honestly,
she was all, "I'm still doing fine!" a minute ago,
but as soon as she sits down, this happens.
She looks comfortable.
I know!
Hm?
This feels wonderful!
There are no crowds, plus it's quiet.
You can't beat a tropical island.
W-What's this?
Leaves.
Gosh, what's the big idea, Tooru?
It tickles!
Y-You're heavy...
Y-You're all heavy!
Huh?
A-A dream?
I must have fallen asleep.
A-A castle?!
Get it off!
Don't move.
We're almost done.
Get this off me already!
Take that!
Attack!
Here!
Sorry.
Don't sweat it!
What's up?
It feels like it's tugging at you. It's so much fun!
Is it really that fun?
Nagi?
M-Me too!
Lunch time!
When you go to the beach, you gotta have ramen!
Fried noodles.
Taco-rice, a real tropical dish!
I brought a bento.
Same as usual, huh?
Really?
Don't worry! Leave it to me!
Huh? What are you going to do?
Well, we're at the ocean, after all!
Fish!
What?!
What kind of landscape are we hoping for?
Look, we can see the horizon now.
Our hearts leap on the hot sand.
Even when I blink, I can still see the sun.
It's as if I've been holding back the urge to play my heart out.
I'm bursting forth with a new self that no one has ever seen!
There's a blue sky in my heart, waves are splashing high,
and my feelings are overflowing.
Let's go, Sisters. Our tan lines
The people are thinning out.
Well, it's evening already.
will join our hearts together.
Feels like we played a ton today.
Amidst the countless sparkles,
It was worth coming early.
Right?
let's paint a rainbow.
The beach was lots of fun!
Yeah!
Well,
I guess it was fun.
Let's come again together some time!
Yeah.
Yuuko, hurry up!
Hang on a second!
Hurry, hurry!
We made it.
It's all empty.
Yuuko-chan, you're not going to sit?
Ah, no, I'm fine right here.
We won't arrive home for a while.
Well, I still have energy left...
Is it all right, Yuuko?
Yeah, it looks fine.
Cuticles!
Huh?
Are your cuticles all right, Yuuko-chan?
How do you expect her to tell?
I-I think they're all right.
Yuuko-chan, your hair is long and pretty,
so you gotta take care of it!
Her skin's white, too.
Th-Thanks...
Oh yeah, I wonder if I got tanned?
I'm sure you don't have to worry.
You put on sunscreen and all.
I guess.
What about you, Run?
She's not tanned at all.
Run, what kind of sunscreen do you use?
Don't use any.
How'd you keep your skin like this without sunscreen?
I can't believe it.
That tickles!
I'm the type that doesn't tan easily.
Really?
What are you, an alien?
What? No, I'm not!
Run-chan is an Earthling.
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
The hats hanging from the tall rack
akane ni narabu
あかねに並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kakeboushi
背高かけ帽子
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
楽しい一日の終わり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　おしゃべり
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigatou
いつもありがとう
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれてよかったな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
るるるん
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風と　心ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
次の角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
I wonder why swimming makes you so sleepy?
Especially during lunchtime after swimming class!
This must be the fearful beginning.
What's that mean?
If you fall asleep at lunchtime, then you won't be sleepy that night,
but if you don't fall asleep at night, next lunchtime you'll be sleepy...
Ah, that happens, doesn't it?
Next time on A-Channel!
"A Midsummer Night's..."!
When that happens, you just have to sleep from noon till the next morning to fix it!
How much do you plan to sleep?
See you next week!