Manga Club
Welcome to the Manga Club!
I'm sorry. I don't have it.
You couldn't find your
A Corpse By Evening?
I must have taken it with me when I went
out to the country during summer vacation.
Hm...
Is that right?
Yes.
Oh. Well, help with the posters.
The posters?
Yeah, the moe ones.
I'm going to step out for a bit.
Senpai... remembered the title.
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Chitanda-san, Mayaka,
Wild Fire
the cooking contest starts at 11:30, okay?
Right.
Ah! Fuku-chan, I'm sorry. I have to
draw posters for the Manga Club.
Huh? You do?
Let's see, then... If we put
you in last position...
If you can be there by
12:10, we'll be fine.
All right, I'll try my best. Bye!
Well, I need to go pop in with the executive
committee, myself, so I'll be off.
He sure is having a ball.
Conference Room
Would you take that to the gym for me?
I'll do that.
Guest shoe covers
By the way,
aren't you going to have a look around?
I have all sorts of little
things popping up.
I do get a look at things
occasionally, though.
Why, do you have any interesting stories?
Any interesting stories?
Ah, a thief apparently struck the Go Club.
Oh?
They stole some go stones,
and left a confession note behind.
Oh, you don't say. The Go Club, huh?
Yes. Although, I think one of their
club members pulled it off.
No, I heard something else from Okano.
Apparently, the same sort of thing
happened to the A Capella Club.
Huh? Is that right?
Yeah. He said that a drink
was taken from their cooler.
Was there a confession note there, too?
They said there was an odd note inside.
Things just got more interesting.
What is it, Fukube? Why are you smiling?
Oh, nothing at all.
Classic Lit Club Anthology
Hyouka Vol. 46
Now on sale
Today's the day I'll come through.
'Blind Spot to All'
Now Showing
2-F's self-produced
'Blind Spot to All' Pamphlets ¥50
All right, very well.
You mean that you'll accept them?
Yeah.
Th... Th...
Thank you so much!
Thank me after they sell. So,
how much, and how many?
They are ¥200 each, and we printed...
200 of them.
That's a lot.
We got that many by mistake.
That's why we'd really like
to sell them somehow.
I... I...
Lower it to ¥150, and give me 20.
I'll sell them together with
our pamphlets for ¥200.
Okay.
What are you doing? Give me a copy.
Huh? Oh, is that what you meant?
I'm sorry, I didn't bring one.
From now on, keep one
with you as you go around.
Things can vary greatly
depending on the way you ask.
Irisu-san...
W-What?
Irisu-san, you are good at
asking for things, right?
Urgh.
Would you please teach me
how to ask people for things?
Huh?!
Eh?
What's going on?
Yeah, okay.
Listen, no matter what you're asking for,
you prompt the other guy
to get them to volunteer to do it.
Prompt them...
To do that, you have to provide them
with a sense of emotional contentment.
There are many ways to do this,
but the thing that would work best for you
is "expectation."
Expectation?
Yes. Make the other guy think
"she's expecting it of me."
Make them think...
If you can do that, they will
readily commit to the rest of it.
Commit to it...
Yeah. However, don't let on
that the problem is all that large.
Don't let on that it's large...
Best to look like it's
a minor detail to you,
but a fairly big deal to them.
There's one other thing...
If possible, ask someone of the
opposite sex, out of public view.
Right.
Now hurry and bring me those anthologies.
Very well.
Thank you, that was terribly informative.
Trick or treat!
Yay!
Who are you guys?
Door-to-door salespeople
for the Confection Club.
Would you like some cookies?
How much?
Heh, ¥100 per bag, sir.
Wow, what is this? How cool!
Oh, that would be great
to carry on our sales calls!
If you like it, I'll trade it
to you for two cookie bags.
Act now, and I'll throw in
an anthology with the pistol.
Huh? Are you sure?
Kerblam!
Okay, here.
And as a symbol of our pumpkin gratitude,
Cake flour
we'll give you this, too.
Flour?
Yay!
Trick or treat!
Kerblam!
High-speed poster-making showdown!
Witch-girl vs. Panther
The Manga Club's vaunted artist, huh?
That's nice.
There, all done.
Maya...
All right, let's do this!
Hosted by the Cooking Club
Where is Mayaka-san?
It looked like she was still busy.
I see.
Let's put our faith in her.
Hey, Fukube!
This is Suhara, son of a restaurant chef.
Oh, yeah? That's remarkable.
Well, do the best that you can. Bye.
The best we can, right.
All right, our entries today are...
Hey, look over there.
Number one,
Team Ajiyoshi!
Number two, Team Fata Morgana!
Number three, Team Astronomy Club!
And number four,
Team Classic Lit Club!
The rules are that each
team of three people
has each member cook for 20 minutes.
After their 20 minutes is up,
they switch off with the next person.
It is against the rules for the others
to talk to them while they are cooking,
so please be mindful of that.
Fukube-san, what are you cooking?
I'm so glad you asked.
Fukube-style hoisin fried rice.
As I understand it, we'll have
to boil the rice from scratch,
which means that you'll go last
as our anchorman, right?
No, I'm going to lead us off.
Since I can't make hoisin
fried rice anymore,
it doesn't make any difference when I go.
I look forward to whatever you do.
Each team member will
make at least one dish.
Ingredients are in the baskets on the center
table, and are first-come, first-serve.
Once they are gone, we will allow you to procure
others, as long as they are on school grounds.
All right then, first contestants!
On your kitchen!
All right!
Okay, here we go!
Wild!
Fire!
Fire...
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
Okay, Wild Fire is underway!
We are truly looking forward to
seeing what dishes each team
is going to present to us.
Oh, Team Classic Lit Club is pulling the heads
off and cleaning the dried fish individually!
Such precise work!
What do you say, President?
This is important prep
work, Vice President.
Team Fata Morgana is preparing clam meat!
Could he be preparing some
daikon radish miso soup?
Ah, Fukube-san! You
shouldn't be doing that!
You haven't peeled the daikon!
Fu...
No, no! Talking is against the rules!
Daikon radish... peel... peel it...
Fukube-san!
Ha! Did he figure it out?
Huh? Is he peeling each one
of them separately?
The water is going to boil over!
Team Classic Lit Club, that looks like
it is going to take some time!
Ah, stuck inside a Möbius loop!
Done. Let's see...
We're still not sure what
each team is making.
Uh-oh, Team Classic Lit Club
is tilting their head to the side.
Ow, that's hot!
Ah, I get it.
He's making miso stew.
Oh, Team Ajiyoshi is making
a standard meat sauce!
I'm not going to make it at this pace.
Leadoff cooks, your time is nearly up!
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
Change element!
Sorry, I was only able to make one dish.
That's okay. Leave it to me!
It's up to you, Chitanda-san.
That is incredible!
Team Classic Lit Club's second cook
is paring that daikon like a pro!
The true form of the
daikon... quite beautiful.
She could even skim a polluted river,
given how cleanly she's paring that thing.
That's amazing. She's
already made one dish.
Ah, that's Chitanda-san, all right.
And now, the Classic Lit Club
is hand-washing their rice!
They've already prodigiously gone through
the six liters of water they started with!
That shows a firm commitment
to the flavor of the rice.
Oh! Team Astronomy Club's second cook...
What's going on there?
What are they cooking?!
Such intense fire!
Meanwhile, is that giseyaki that
Team Classic Lit Club is making?
That's a down-home taste!
Hiromi!
I've never even heard of giseyaki before.
Now it's Team Fata Morgana!
Their yellowtail teriyaki
is nearing completion!
Brilliant!
Team Classic Lit Club appears
to have finished their giseyaki.
I'm really starting to get hungry!
Just who is this second cook of theirs?
She's Miss Chitanda Eru, daughter of
the farming tycoon Chitanda family!
And don't forget it!
Meanwhile, Team Astronomy Club's
avant-garde cooking continues!
Let the darkness swallow them up!
Team Classic Lit Club is now rolling
boiled potatoes in starch
and putting them in a mortar!
Now they're making imomochi cakes!
The Classic Lit Club displays
a practiced hand!
Oh, but could this be trouble?
Trouble? What?
Team Classic Lit Club,
any help is against the rules.
It's no use. I'm not getting through.
40 minutes have now elapsed.
Please switch to your anchormen.
Fukube-san, how did I do?
You were amazing, Chitanda-san.
I had no idea you were
so skilled at cooking.
I like to cook.
Mm-hm, well done, well done. It's just...
Just what?
There aren't any ingredients left!
Mayaka, I'm sorry.
Okay, at last, we have
reached the anchormen!
Finished!
Excuse me! Please excuse me!
Oh, my! Team Ajiyoshi is preparing
some apples for their dessert!
Those bunny rabbits are taking
shape right before our eyes!
Is Team Classic Lit Club's anchorman
anywhere to be seen yet?
Oh, my, in addition to the bunny rabbits,
Team Ajiyoshi is also hollowing
out a flower hedge!
Leaving Team Classic Lit Club and
their missing anchorman behind,
Team Ajiyoshi is preparing their dessert!
Mayaka!
What's this? A girl in civilian
dress has just shown up!
Is she with Team Classic Lit Club?
Is this the Classic Lit Club?
Mayaka-san!
It is the Classic Lit Club!
Team Classic Lit Club's
anchorman has finally arrived!
Uh-oh, Team Classic Lit Club, out of
the frying pan and into the fire!
There are no more ingredients left!
If she doesn't cook anything,
the anchorman's score will,
of course, be zero!
After such a hard-fought battle, is this
the end for Team Classic Lit Club?
Is this all?
Team Classic Lit Club has
picked up a small onion.
What do I do? But what can she
make with just one small onion?
She is just standing there;
can she not think of anything?
What will you do, Classic Lit Club?
If you do not cook something,
you will be disqualified.
What do we do?
What can I make?
What does Mayaka-san plan to do
with just those ingredients?
Now I'm curious.
Huh?
And whose fault is that?
The Classic Lit Club anchorman
has not moved an inch.
There it is! Fata Morgana
produces an omelet!
Think! Think!
Has Team Classic Lit Club
reached the end of the line?
Something... There has to be something...
Team Classic Lit Club is out of options!
The time remaining is a mere ten minutes!
Can they do nothing but wait
for time to run out?
Toshi!
Fukube-san, did you just hear
your name being called?
Huh?
Satoshi!
There!
Team Astronomy Club is boiling
bananas in soup stock! Really?
Excuse me!
Bana...
What is it?
Be quiet for a moment.
Satoshi!
It's Oreki-san!
Over there! In the club room!
Satoshi!
What?
What's that?
Huh?
Satoshi! Get over here!
Get under the window!
Move it!
Fukube-san!
Mm-hm.
What is it?!
Make sure you catch this!
Nice catch!
So, what is this?
Team Classic Lit Club's leadoff
cook has returned! Mayaka!
What?!
Oh, my! What an astounding turn of events!
Could that be a bag of flour?
The rules say it's okay! It's allowed!
All right!
And now, seven minutes remain!
As each Wild Fire team
enters their final stages,
Team Classic Lit Club
at last goes into action!
Under such disadvantageous circumstances,
what kind of heroics
are they going to display?
I'm quite curious, myself.
What's this? She has pulled out
the shrimp heads!
What on earth is she planning?
Kakiage tempura.
Is that it? Kakiage tempura?
Only five minutes still
remain in Wild Fire!
Hey! Cooking Club!
At least provide us with a ladle!
The Classic Lit Club obtains a ladle
and sets about the next step!
The pressure is on Team Classic Lit Club!
Playing a furious game of catch-up,
they rally from behind!
It's kakiage over rice!
Will Team Classic Lit Club make it
in time? Only one minute left!
There's very little time remaining!
She scoops it up!
And after setting it into the bowl...
3... 2... 1...
It's over!
Yes!
Oh, yeah!
Mayaka-san!
Great job!
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
All right, we will now
announce the results.
The well-deserved victory goes to...
Team Classic Lit Club!
I'm exhausted.
It was underdone.
Hey, for being out of time
and options, that was fantastic.
Yeah, but I didn't have a ladle!
If I'd only had a ladle, it would
have turned out perfectly.
It took a whole minute
for them to bring me one.
I was such an idiot. If I didn't
have a ladle, I should have...
Hey, I'm really sorry about that.
I thought we had checked everything.
We should have given it
one last going-over.
Yeah, I thought it was odd too, at first,
Excuse me a moment...
so I should have checked, as well.
No, that's all right.
Huh?
Isn't that...?!
What?
Ah!
The Cooking Club has already lost its
ladle.... Jumonji
A confession note!
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "The Jumonji Affair."
The Jumonji Affair