I am Jibril.
What can I do for you, Sora and Shiro, le nouveau roi et reine of the Imanity?
You know who we are?
Well, that makes it easier, then.
I'll just cut to the chase.
I want this library.
mawaritsuzukeru haguruma ni wa narisagaranai
I never wanted to become just another cog in the machine
heikin enjiru kanjou kara hajimatta jigoku
My life had become hell because I was pretending to be average
asobihanbun de kami ga michibiita
But then God frivolously took me to a new stage
danjou no sekai no no no game no life
To the world of no game no life
nurui heion wo bassari kirisutete
Where I can do away with my boring everyday life
eikou e no kaidan ni sonzai kizamunda
And engrave my name on the stairway to glory
me ni utsuru no wa kanzen shouri no unmei
I now see a destiny of flawless victory for myself
nani mo kamo keisan doori kaete yaru
I'll change everything precisely the way I want
somaranai kuuhaku de
As an untainted blank
riaru made ni kyuusai nante iranai
I no longer care about salvation in my real life
donna michi osotte mo kateba ii dake no hanashi nara
I don't know what the future holds, but if all that matters is to win
kakehiki to sainou ga muhai izanau
Then I'll put my strategy and talent to work and stay undefeated
umarenaoshita inochi de tanoshimu sa
I'm enjoying my new life to the fullest
jibun dake wa jibun shinjiteru
Believing in myself
You want meine Bibliothek?
What a sudden demande.
Steph, the Flugel were
god-killing warriors, right?
Th-They're supposed to be!
I must look like a pigeon that took
a balle to the face—I mean, la faccia.
Interesting
She corrected herself.
The way you're talking reminds me of someone famous,
so if you're doing it on purpose, then please, stop.
Qué?
I had thought it an avant-garde and unique way
of speaking, but someone else beat me to it?
No need to get upset over it.
Let's get back to the point.
So, you want my library.
Are you challenging me
to a game, human?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Before the ten commandments were introduced,
we Flugel collected severed heads.
Now that murder is forbidden, though,
we value knowledge above all else.
It's not exaggerating to say that books,
which contain that knowledge,
and the place where they are held,
are as valuable as one's life.
You want me to wager my life,
so what are you offering in exchange?
More than forty thousand
books from another world.
That's disgusting.
It's okay, Shiro.
In our business, that's a prize!
F-Forty thousand?
...Th-That sure is a lot...
Where do you keep them?
Right here.
I used them to study for quiz games.
There are dictionaries,
...medical books, philosophy books...
It's filled with information
from our world.
Are you saying that you two
are from another world?
Yes.
That's impossible.
Hey, what's she talking about?
...Um...
Summoning a living creature
from another world
and keeping it here requires
a tremendous amount of power.
Even the Old Deus would
find it extremely difficult.
That kinda flew over
my head, but I can prove it.
Take a look at this,
if you can read it.
What are you saying?
I can speak every one of the
...over seven hundred languages—
It... It's a language I don't know?
An encyclopedia from
a world I don't know?
This little board contains
all that knowledge?!
And forty thousand books of it!
...H-Hey—
You're drooling! You're drooling!
E-Excuse me.
I see.
I'm very interested in this thin board, but I still
don't believe that you're from another world.
What do you want from us, then?
Let me check your bodies.
Check our bodies?
Why would you do that?
What are you checking, anyway?
Your erogenous zones.
Do it for as long as you'd like,
and then do it some more!
You sure changed your tune quickly.
...Bro, that'd be 18+ only...
...Oh, right...
Leave the pants on, then.
And, since I'm letting you touch my
erogenous zones, let me touch yours!
...What the heck?! There's no way—
Sure, that's fine.
Wait, it is?!
...Hey...
What?
Do you not enjoy
how it feels to the touch?
No, it feels wonderful.
Surprisingly so.
But... well, I guess
I just feel a bit betrayed.
A bit let down.
Is this not one of
your erogenous zones?
I'll just say that admitting so
would hurt my manly pride.
Besides, I was actually hoping
that you'd touch me somewhere else.
...But...
All of our power comes from
what we call "Spirit Circuits".
And our wings, where they
...all collect, are a very erogenous—
Master of Touchscreen H-Games
Yeah, you like that? Right here?
...When you touch them like that, it...
What on Earth are you doing?!
All I'm doing is
touching her wings, right?
Yep. It's entirely wholesome.
What are these two doing
...to this god-killing weapon...
My investigation shows that there are
absolutely no spirits within your bodies.
In other words, you two aren't even
strictly defined as "life" in this world,
though you have the
appearance of Imanity.
...So that makes us...
What?
Unknown!
Unknown
You are the unknown!
The source from which
new knowledge is born!
Nothing in this world is as
wonderful as the unknown!
So I guess we've proven that
we're not from this world?
Yes, you have.
Please accept my sincerest apologies
for assuming you were mere Imanity.
Mere Imanity
I will certainly accept the game.
But I don't really have anything worth
forty thousand books from another world.
...Look, all I want is the lib—
How about I bet "everything I have"?
For real?
...Lucky me...
Get a Flugel
Is that fine with you?
Of course. We want
full rights to you, personally.
Get a Flugel
Thank you!
Oh, and may I add in that you two
have to come by for tea every so often?
I want to know more about you.
You're talking like
you've already won.
All right. So if we win,
we can add another demand too?
Of course.
There's no way you'll win, but if you
manage to, then you can have whatever you want.
We'll play word chain,
but not your average word chain.
We'll play Materialization Word Chain.
Materialization Word Chain?
Yes. The rules are simple.
It's just like regular word chain, where
if you use a word that's already been used,
Use a word that's already been used
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
fail to answer for thirty seconds,
or cannot continue, you lose.
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Use a word that's already been used
Cannot continue
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Can we use words
from any language?
Yes. However, purely fictional
objects and concepts don't count.
Flight Stone
Remember, we're playing
Materialization Word Chain.
Materialization Word Chain
If you say something
that's here, it'll disappear.
Tallow
If it's not, then it'll appear.
Whale
I'm sure you understand what this means.
Once the game's over, everything will return to as
it was, so don't hesitate to show off your knowledge.
All right.
'kay, Shiro. Come over here.
We'll play together,
as we always do.
That's fine.
You're powerless humans, so be sure
to enjoy yourselves, and try not to die.
...What? W-Wait...
Die?
You cannot directly cause someone to
die—or rather, to be unable to continue.
I don't need to be here, then, right?
...That's only dangerous for—
...Now, then...
Yeah.
Let's get this game started.
Come and get us.
Listen to me!
Steph, sit!
Oh God, I can't run away now!
I've had it with this!
You can go first.
Pick any word you like.
...All right...
...Well, I'll start with...
Hydrogen bomb.
Hydrogen bomb
What's this?
Bkulians!
Self-destruction on the first move?
That was Bkulians,
the highest-level sealing spell.
Hydrogen bomb
Bkulians
(Eternal Fourth Protection)
If I hadn't been nice enough to protect
you all, the game would be over already.
"Nice enough"? Please.
Bkulians!
I was just banking on the fact that you'd think ending
the game in a single move would be terribly boring.
I see.
I figured as much, though it doesn't seem like we'll
be able to stop you from keeping this game going.
I'm glad you understand.
Please try not to bore me.
Don't worry. I wouldn't dream of it.
Bkulians
(Eternal Fourth Protection)
Spirit Circuits.
Spirit Circuits
Well, looks like
you don't waste time.
It's a word I just learned.
I hope that won't be a problem.
No. It just limits my physical abilities
a bit and prevents me from flying.
I still have spirits in my body,
so it's no problem whatsoever.
It just makes me a bit uneasy, is all.
Oh, like when your cell phone
can't get reception.
Cell phone? Reception?
Is that related to that
thin board of yours?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You're too close!
Beat me and I'll tell you.
...I think she's...
Yeah, this is getting even more fun.
Hey, Jibril. It's your turn.
Spirit Circuits
R-Right.
Here's an easy one. Stallion.
Stallion
Okay. Nether r*gions.
Nether r*gions
Well?
...Wh... Wha—
What the hell are you thinking?!
I'm getting a bit
tired of all this dust.
Let's have some fun.
Beach
Beach.
Yes, it's beautiful, but it's too much
for someone who never goes outside!
Beach
Okay! Hooter-nub!
Hooter-nub
I'll play along, then.
Bikinis
Bikinis.
Jibril, don't you get it?!
If you wanna see her in a bikini,
you need to get rid of her clothes!
Oh! I'm so sorry. I couldn't understand
what you were getting at.
Would you two take this just a little bit seriously?!
Bikinis
Whatever. Suitcases.
Suitcases
...Let me see, then...
How about "squall"?
Squall
Hey, what are you doing?!
It all worked out, Jibril!
Steph's not wearing any panties,
so without the bikini, this would be 18+!
But seeing just a bit of bikini
under a skirt is nice too!
I'm glad to hear it.
And now, it'll be complete!
Squall
Ladies' clothes!
Ladies' clothes
No!
What do you think of that, Sis?
There aren't any privates, and we've
still got shoes, knee socks, and a collar!
It's even better than pure nudity!
Suitable for all ages!
Very wholesome!
Moderately sexy, but not dirty at all!
...We should call this...
The "Super Wholesome Space!"
Bro, omega good job!
What on Earth are
you guys trying to do?!
Hey, Jibril, do you get hungry?
Mantle.
Mantle
Please, don't worry.
Unlike you powerless Imanity,
we don't need to eat.
Mantle
Eccentric moth comic.
Eccentric moth comic
Let's be together!
Oh, I see. You do get tired,
though, right?
Eccentric moth comic
The sun's rising soon.
Shouldn't you just surrender?
Crust.
Crust
If you're tired, then you're
more than welcome to forfeit.
Crust
I didn't expect to have this much fun
with a weak Imanity.
Timepiece.
Timepiece
It's a bit annoying how you
keep saying "weak" and "mere".
Extraterrestrial.
Extraterrestrial
Well, I'm sure we at the bottom must look like
mere ants to a mighty sixth-ranked race like you.
...Thank goodness...
But who decided that ants
are weak and powerless?
I'm sorry. I didn't consider that you Imanity
would consider yourselves anything but weak.
If you honestly think long life and durability give you
power, then I'm afraid you're the stupid one here.
Are you saying that I'm
inferior to the Imanity?
My feelings toward you are best
described as curiosity, not respect.
Don't forget that I could
end this game any time I like.
Extraterrestrial
Lanterned mall.
Lanterned mall
And that's exactly why you're weak.
It's what makes you an
empty-headed academic.
Empty-headed academic?
Yep, empty-headed academic, meaning you don't know
how things work in the real world. Keep that in mind.
Empty-headed academic
I know what that phrase means.
How am I an
"empty-headed academic", though?
Instead of respecting the unknown,
you're merely curious.
It's time for a little lesson.
You'll see just how
weak you really are.
Thanks for all the hard work, Steph.
We couldn't have won without you
keeping all those dangers off of us.
You think you've won?
So, Steph, this might kill you a little,
but take one for the team, okay?
Huh?
Lanterned mall
Lithosphere
Lithosphere!
Lithosphere.
The surface of the planet.
You didn't understand
what they meant,
so I was able to strategically erase
the mantle and crust beforehand.
You fail to fear and
respect the unknown.
That's your "empty-headed"
weakness, Jibril!
I see.
That's why you got rid of the
Spirit Circuits to cripple my wings.
It has a core temperature
of 6,000 degrees,
and a surface temperature
of 3,000 degrees, I suppose.
You can't kill me
that easily, though.
I won't let morning come just yet.
Lithosphere
Eos lumo.
Eos Lumo
Oxygen.
Oxygen
You stopped me from breathing,
but it's useless.
Oxygen
I'll have a little more fun with you.
Nodes.
Nodes
Damn it... Sepia.
Sepia
You're making this easier
than I thought.
Sepia
Okay, then.
Air.
Air
Once the air comes back,
I can breathe.
Why?
I was right! Jibril doesn't
know atomic theory!
You thought that you just needed
to bring back air to breathe,
but I only got rid of oxygen.
The rules say that what's there
disappears and what isn't there appears.
Okay, then.
Air.
The other gases disappeared,
and oxygen came back.
All that's left here is oxygen, which is
toxic at tremendous pressures and purity!
...This is the same for you too, though...
Wh-What?
Circular breathing.
This is the difference
between you and us.
Let's go, Shiro.
Air
Rest of the atmosphere
Rest of the atmosphere.
...The atmosphere...
The zero-pressure environment
created by the disappearance of the atmosphere
will cause the air inside you to expand and burst.
You had no idea why we got rid of all the air in our bodies, did you?
It's no use.
My voice?
You can't speak in a vacuum.
Use a word that's already been used
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Cannot continue
Use a word that's already been used
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Cannot continue
Use a word that's already been used
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
Cannot continue
...And if you can't answer in thirty seconds...
Fail to answer for 30 seconds
I suppose I lose.
I see.
It's a shame you're just Imanity.
This time I'll answer you
with thanks and respect.
Rest of the atmosphere
Empty-headed academic
Do you understand?
This is something that the Imanity
will never be able to overcome.
You have no way to answer me.
In the end, you will lose because of the
soundless world and burning land you've created.
So I win.
Empty-headed academic
Coulomb
Force
When Coulomb force vanishes, leaving only
the nuclear force that draws atoms together,
the result is the astronomical phenomenon that normally only
occurs during the gravitational collapse of supermassive stars.
A hypernova, capable of destroying
stars dozens of light years away.
It's got a temperature of fifty billion
degrees Celsius, rivaling the dawn of creation.
Just try and survive that, Flugel!
So that was it.
He's right.
Even if I die only a fraction
of a second earlier, I still lose.
That first explosion was simply him trying to see
if he could use words that his opponent didn't know.
That explosion gave him
all the information he needed.
Everything that happened after that
was simply a farce to keep me distracted.
The game was over after
the first move, wasn't it?
People from another
...world—no, the Imanity...
They truly are a terrifying race.
I died.
Oh, welcome back.
You used me as a decoy,
and then just went and killed me!
You monster! The inhumanity!
I mean, in-Imanity!
Steph, beg.
Still a pet dog for the day
We're still doing this?!
To Sora and Shiro, "Today" means "Until they go to bed"
I know you've got some complaints,
but if it weren't for you, we'd have lost.
Thanks, Steph.
I lost.
No matter how well you tried to tempt me,
there was never a guarantee that I'd
answer with "empty-headed academic".
You're insane, you know that?
I'm challenging God.
I couldn't do that if I were sane.
You're... challenging God?
It was Tet who called us to this world.
Our only option is to beat him.
So, Jibril, in accordance with the commandments,
everything you have is now ours.
Oh, and by the way, the books on my tablet
were just bait. You can read them all you want.
You're free to use the library too.
O dear, departed master!
Artosh, the one who created us.
At long last, I've fulfilled our long-held dream of
finding someone worthy to serve as our new master.
An Imanity, who looks down
on the elves, and on me,
and who will overturn
everything we think we know.
My master, my lord,
I, Jibril, member of the Council of Eighteen Wings
of the Flugel, ranked sixth among the Exceed,
offer you everything I have.
I will find no greater pleasure
than carrying out your will.
Yeah, leave it to us.
Right, Shiro?
Yeah.
Leave it to us.
How much longer do
I have to act like a dog?!
dare ni mo mienai
With a loneliness
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That no one else could see, I was crying all alone
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, we delved into our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshieatte
And shared all the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furu deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By piecing together the fragments of expressions we find
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuitekun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
Like we're praying to the sky
tobou eien ni
Let's soar high into eternity
Sacrifice
I used to be a gamer like you,
...then I took an arrow in the knee...
Stop!