Even before my tan from the drawing camp faded,
there's yet another doujin spot sale.
What tan are you talking about?
How's your manga, this time?
It was fun to draw!
I'm not asking if it was fun - how will your sales be?
Of course it's going to sell.
Twice as many as usual.
So, ten copies...
Cheer up, brother.
It'll work out somehow.
I mean, it was an accident.
Just tell them how sorry you are, they'll forgive you
The artist and lead editor have spared me.
See?
But the artist is already too busy with another job to fix this one.
I could have put it in a clear case or some other way...
The millions of fans who are eagerly waiting...
It's my fault they won't get their favorite manga.
It's all my fault...
B-but... the night doesn't last forever,
and after the winter, there's always spring.
The soil hardens after a good rain.
I'm sorry!  I take that back!
I didn't mention rain!
But besides that, I must find a replacement artist.
Is that like a fill-in?
Right.
But it's too sudden...
I can think of someone.
Thank you very much!
I've sold one already!
I'll be right there with you!
That's what I'd like to say,
but today's manga is the one from drawing camp.
Honestly, it's a little rough, still.
But I'm under the same circumstances.
Come on! Envy me more!
No really, I'm jealous.
You're lying! You don't seem jealous at all!
Eh?
I'm jealous that you're not jealous of me!
What the heck is that...
Well, when Hoshi-kun gets here,
he'll buy all thirty books right away.
You're always relying on Hoshi-san.
Najimi-san!
Hoshi-kun.
Najimi-san.
Did you snap your tongue at him?
Oh, this is from the drawing camp.
Yup.  I fixed it up and I'm proud of it.
That's not what you said before.
Your brother is here, too.
He doesn't seem too well.
Yes, this is Najimi-san's manga.
Ok!
Thank you, Beauty Love-sensei,
for taking care of me all the time.
I wonder what he means by "care."
Hey!
Tiger's Den sales department?
Yes!
I figured you were a college student.
I was a T University student until recently.
So you were smart?
But I realized my calling in life was to spread Najimi-san's manga around the world.
So I quit.
You're not very smart.
Amazing decision making!
You're embarassing me.
But are you okay with quitting such a good school?
No problem at all.
Well, my parents look at me strangely now...
With sadness.
But it's my life.
Hey...
There's something I need to discuss with you.
You're not thinking that Najimi can be the replacement artist?
Yeah.
Don't be stupid.
She's an amateur no matter what you think.
Think of the situation, brother.
You'll take any chance you can get, won't you?
Chance?
I'm going to publish any chance I can get on my magazine?
Hoshi-san.
You shouldn't force him.
We're in agreement.
You're totally forcing it.
Thank you very much!
We're sold out.
Justice! We're sold out!
Yes. Thank you, Sora.
Justice!
Sora-eyy!
Tiger's den.
Distributed sales?
Yes!
Alright! Good job, Hoshi-kun.
Wha- really?
It's alright.
I've got the okay, with the condition that if they don't sell out, I'm fired.
Seriously?
Najimi-san's unknown book will be read by many and be a huge hit!
Then you'll debut as a professional artist!
I'm honored to be a part of this!
Here, brother! Take a good look at it.
The drawing camp book got so much better.
Hoshi-kun's remaining life will be as Najimi's right hand man.
The burden's too much...
Ah... Junichirou, this is...
No good?
No, it's not that...
It's no good.
No good! No good! No good!
I don't agree with Najimi-san's manga being a big hit!
Why's that?
I don't agree with it, either.
There would be too much wrong with the world if Najimi's book made it big.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, don't take it the wrong way.
I can't take it any other way.
Well, we'll be selling thirty units to start things off.
Thirty units?
Yes, today I'll be leaving after I take a sample copy.
Please send the rest another day.
Thirty units, eh?
Wasn't his brother an editor at a magazine?
I need him to read mine!
Older brother!
Yes?
It's not fair to get all worked up about Najimi.
Take a look at mine, too!
Now I've got a chance at a pro debut, too!
Until next time, Najimi-san.
Thank you.
Uh, Uhm... Next time...
I was thinking of introducing you to my parents, not just my brother or something...
Here it is!
Erm, well...
There's hype on the internet about a manga that only has faces drawn from one angle.
We're fans, now!
Well, that's...
I'd like one of this.
Eh? S-sure!
I'd like one, too.
Right! Thank you very much.
I guess things like this DO happen...
Same for me.
Thank you!
Najimi-san's ultimate manga.
I'm gonna do my best selling it!
What's wrong?
You've been quiet for a while.
Yeah, that girl who sold me this book.
Nidou-san?
Yeah...
It's quite troublesome.
Troublesome?
She totally digs me, too.
Huh?
She also totally digs me.
I don't get it.
Your eyes are just decorations, aren't they?
She held my hands, with tears welling up...
"It's not fair to get all worked up about Najimi!"
She said.
She said...
But what are you thinking? What about you?
You're going to make me say it?
Najimi-san definitely isn't what you think.
Brother, you misunderstand.
You're the one who's misunderstanding.
As she is right now, Najimi Osana has no chance.
Also, I've got some ideas on who the next great artist is.
Was Nidou Kaneru her name?
OK then, if you're pushing Najimi Osana that hard, convince me!
Understood.
Distributed sales?
That's great news.
Well, I don't know if it'll work out.
Kaneru-chan, what's wrong?
It's probably because her new work isn't selling.
Hey!
That's it too, but...
So that's it.
Your manga not selling isn't anything new.
Why you!
Nidou-san, want something to drink?
Najimi-san, you're acting strange.
Huh, Me?
No, you're the one acting strange!
Najimi-san, you sold all your books, but you don't seem happy.
Wow, it's true.
Congratulations, Najimi!
Yeah, there was some hype on the internet.
Selling out because I suck is awkward.
You're going far away!
Najimi-san, you're going far away!
W-what're you saying?
Kaneru-chan, Najimi's not going anywhere.
Now now, relax.
Najimi-san.
What's wrong, Hoshi-kun?
Forget something?
You forgot to buy my book, right?
I doubt that.
It's about the distributed sales...
Oh, It's a no-go huh?
Figures. It'd be bad to get fired over something like this.
Make it one hundred units!
Forget thirty units. I'll take one hundred!
Wow!
But, that's a little...
Please have a hundred books sent to me.
And could I have another sample book?
Uhh, I sold out just a minute ago.
She's sold out.
What is?
Her new book.
Whose?
Najimi's.
Why?
I have no idea.
That's amazing!
This is good!
Very good!
Umm, Hoshi-kun.
Why a hundred units, all of a sudden?
I promised my brother.
Promised?
Yes, if your book finishes selling within 3 days,
my brother's magazine will publish your story until it ends.
Najimi! You're flying away!
There are as many separations are there are meetings.
Next time, the final episode...
Or the beginning.