This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
So, Chitanda,
you're saying you can put a stop to the mysterious thief, Juumoji?
Yes, that's what we're trying to do!
With everyone's...
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
With everyone's help, I'm sure we'll be able to catch Juumoji!
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Radio broadcast
Strategy meeting
Sound confident
Emphasize everyone's role
Pumpkin
Full of confidence, I see!
Which brings us to: What do you think Juumoji will steal next?
We've prepared just the thing!
The Classics Club has some copy papers for just this occasion.
Copy papers?
Yes, the copy papers we use for our anthology, Hyouka.
Huh? There's less?
Target: Sell all 2OO copies!
114 sold
Our anthology features a story that's just as exciting as the Juumoji incident,
On air
so please take a look at it if you get the chance!
I think you'll all enjoy it!
Advertise Hyouka
Pumpkin
Wow! We'll be thinking about that one for a while!
I hope you'll all check out the Classics Club's anthology, Hyouka!
I'm sure you'll like it!
By the way, while we wait for Juumoji to pay us a visit,
there's something those of us in the Classics Club need your help with.
You need help?
Yes. There's only four of us, so we can't really keep a thorough watch.
That's why I'd like to ask you all to come to the Classics Club!
You're our only hope!
I see! The more people watching, the more they'll see!
Yes! We're counting on your help!
How could let a young lady's pleas fall on deaf ears?
And, if you could...
Please buy our anthology too... Okay?
The final target, the Classics Club, stands ready to intercept the thief!
Chitanda, we wish you luck!
Thank you! I hope you'll all support us!
And that was Chitanda Eru!
That's a wrap!
That was pretty good!
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Hyouka
I was just wondering if it really was good enough...
Kudryavka's Order
Juumoji vs The Classics Club
I'll take one.
That'll be 200 yen.
This, please.
Please.
Whoa! They really are selling!
Almost there! We've nearly sold them all!
Is he really gonna turn up?
At this point, what can he even do?
Yeah, he's got no chance.
How long's he gonna make us wait?
Does Juumoji even exist?
What if they made it all up?
I can totally imagine that!
I'm getting fed up with this...
Sorry, that's just my phone.
You're not going to answer?
Nah, it's just—
They're burning! They're burning!
Put it out!
Water?
We got hit.
Take a look at this.
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
The Classics Club has lost its copy papers.
The ten letters are complete.
Juumoji
Juumoji's calling card.
Did you really know?
You know, I was thinking that Juumoji might be a girl.
Classics Club Defeated
They sold out.
Would you have preferred to sell them at full price?
No! This is more than enough!
Just... Thank you very much!
Stop it.
And also...
Yes?
I guess I should tell you.
What?
I heard you on the radio show.
Really? Thanks to your advice, I—
Yeah, it's about that.
I didn't think this through all the way.
I'll make this clear:
You are ill-suited to manipulating people in this way.
When you try to do it, you just come across as demanding attention.
Demanding attention?
Is that really how it sounds?
Only a little. A mere fingernail's worth.
But as it happens, if you keep up such an act for too long,
you may find, in the end, that it becomes the real you.
Okay.
What I'm getting at is, don't base everything you do on my advice.
You might consider it a weakness that you can't help but be straightforward,
but at the same time it's also a rare and powerful weapon.
Do you understand?
Yes. I was thinking the same thing.
Pretending to be someone else really doesn't fit me.
I guess, to put it simply...
I've had enough of it.
So in the end, not even you could catch Juumoji.
Acting Troupe
Marching Band
Closing Ceremony
End of Festival
Marching Band
Closing Ceremony
Acting Troupe
Marching Band
Closing Ceremony
End of Festival
Marching Band
I expected more of you.
Oh well. I do regret that we couldn't live up to your expectations.
All the same, this culture fair sure was a lot of fun.
I'll pay you back for the cooking thing one day.
See you around!
Who's that?
Tani.
He sucks at Japanese, I guess.
Where'd that come from?
He uses the word "expectation" much too easily.
Does it matter? There's no rule against—
People who are confident in themselves never talk about expectations.
"Expectation" is a word rooted in giving up.
It leaves you with no other choice. It makes it obvious that you're powerless.
Fuku...
Speaking of expectations...
Houtarou should be around here.
There!
Let's get straight to the point.
You are Juumoji, aren't you, Tanabe?
Are you just guessing?
No, I have my reasons.
Tanabe?
First of all, these cards.
Why do they say "lost" and not "stolen"?
lost
Who knows?
The next issue is "ku". That letter was skipped.
That alone pokes a hole in Juumoji's pattern.
But what if there was something beginning with "ku" that we didn't consider?
Such as?
Wasn't the whole Juumoji incident in itself a code?
The whole thing was designed to convey one message:
that someone beginning with "ku" had already lost something beginning with "ku".
That's quite a difficult code.
Impossible to break, even.
Unless you know how to decode it.
Let me say this straight:
I think that was the plot of Kudryavka's Order.
You're wondering how I knew that title?
Kudryavka's Order is a twist on Christie's famous book, The ABC Murders.
In the Juumoji incident, the culprit focused on Kudryavka's Order.
That is to say, the recipient of the code. Someone beginning with "ku"...
Kugayama Muneyoshi, the student council president.
The illustrator for Dead at Dusk.
Am I wrong?
But if every other target was a club, why would he target a person for "ku"?
Juumoji never said he was only targeting the clubs.
You're trying so hard.
Not at all.
You gave us the list of potential targets.
You didn't just copy the order from the ABC Schedule.
The schedule itself is the list of victims.
All the victims were chosen from these pages.
A Capella Choir. Go Club. Fortune Teller Club.
Gardening Club. Cooking Lab. News Poster Club. Magic Club.
And then, Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Kugayama Muneyoshi
If someone figured all that out, it wouldn't be hard to find you.
It'd be too much of a coincidence that all the victims ended up being on this page.
But who has control over the contents? Only the General Affairs people.
But there are 20 people on the General Affairs Committee.
Yes. That's where this manga, Dead at Dusk, comes into the picture.
President Kugayama worked on this with the author, Anjou Haruna,
so he must've known about Kudryavka's Order as well.
Which means President Kugayama would be able to decode Juumoji's message.
I'm just guessing, but maybe he lost the script for Kudryavka's Order?
Maybe Juumoji caused this scandal to condemn him for that.
Which means the culprit's message was this:
"Kugayama has lost Kudryavka's Order."
Finally, the afterword.
It was written by the person who helped draw the backgrounds.
Anjou Haruna. President Kugayama.
He was the only one beside those two who knew about Kudryavka's Order.
Therefore, he's the only possible candidate for Juumoji.
Then there's this.
Ajimu Takuha. What a strange pen name.
It's made from the first syllable of each of the authors' names.
So?
Ajimu    Takuha
Anjou
Haruna
Anjou Haruna: "a" and "ha".
Ajimu    Takuha
Ajimu    TakuHa
Kugayama Muneyoshi: "ku" and "mu".
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
Ajimu    Takuha
AjiMu    Takuha
Ajimu    TaKuha
If you subtract those from Ajimu Takuha,
you're left with the two syllables of "ji" and "ta".
Ajimu    Takuha
Ajimu    takuha
Someone who was around for last year's fair, so at least a second-year,
a member of the General Affairs Committee,
and someone whose initials are "ta" and "ji".
Furthermore, they would have to be close to President Kugayama
and know that he was making a manga.
There's only one such person.
And that would be you,
Tanabe Jirou.
Well done.
I didn't think anyone but Mune and Anjou would be able to figure it out.
Seriously, you outdid my expectations, Houtarou.
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
The Cooking Lab has lost their ladle.
Juumoji
Why did you use such a roundabout code?
You've got some idea, haven't you?
Is it to do with your feelings for Anjou Haruna, who transferred?
Yeah, that too.
Plus, I wanted to pull a grand prank for the culture fair.
But...
It was mostly because I couldn't say it myself.
Very well. There's something I'd like to discuss.
I have a request for you, Tanabe.
What is it?
Please purchase these.
Our anthology, Hyouka. 30 copies, all up.
You want me to buy my anonymity with those?
Yes.
Though, the General Affairs Committee would be the ones buying them.
That's impossible!
It's not impossible.
Haven't you been selling various items off the culture fair website?
You can simply buy them and put them up for sale there.
I can't just buy them without a reason.
They'd need to be a popular item that people are talking about.
Precisely.
But people will be talking about Hyouka.
What do you mean?
The Juumoji incident, of course.
The Classics Club will be the final target.
I'll help you, and I'll get Fukube Satoshi in on this as well.
With insiders at your target,
nothing could be easier.
People will flock to the Classics Club out of curiosity,
and sales of the anthology will rise as a result.
That should be enough reason to stock it on the website.
And you can complete the sequence of thefts cleanly and without issues.
What do you say?
That...
sounds quite good.
We'll bring the Juumoji case to a close,
and our online store will get something new in stock.
Our goals coincide.
Good to hear.
And how do you plan to assist Juumoji?
We'll get some copy papers ready as the target item.
It'll be guarded so closely that no one could even get near it.
Oh? So?
According to this,
the Chemistry Lab will be demonstrating the effects of mixing sodium with water.
I've seen it in documentaries before. It reacts quite spectacularly.
You're planning to use sodium?
Yes. Please get some any way you can.
I also believe that someone at the Candy Club has a water pistol shaped like a handgun.
Please arrange to borrow it from them.
You're planning something dangerous.
It's a festival. Time for some fireworks.
Oh boy.
I'll find a way to hide the sodium between the pages of the copy papers.
When we've sold enough copies, I'll signal you like this.
When you see that, shoot the water pistol.
Everyone will be watching the papers, though.
That's right.
Then we'll put Satoshi's smartphone near the entrance of the room.
Before you shoot, give him a call.
The ringing phone will draw attention away from the papers.
Got it. What about Juumoji's calling card?
The place will be in an uproar.
You can just hide it in a copy of Hyouka and drop it on the floor.
Very well.
Then please purchase said copy.
That'll be 200 yen.
You never miss an opportunity.
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
What was your name again?
Oreki Houtarou, from class 1-B.
You mean expectations, like the ones you have for Houtarou?
That's right. How did you know?
I can tell just by looking at you. It's you, after all.
You wanted to beat Oreki?
It's not that I wanted to beat him. He's not better than me in every way.
But I guess you wouldn't understand.
You guessed wrong.
Well, I've been careless.
I forgot one important thing:
A database can't draw conclusions.
54th Kamiyama High School Culture Fair
I'm pleased to announce that this year's Kan'ya Fair reached its end without trouble.
Closing Ceremony
Though, I believe there were a few strange incidents here and there.
Nice job!
Anyway, it's all over now!
As of this moment, the 54th Kamiyama High School Culture Fair is concluded!
I may be a bit late, but I've finally got it.
I believe that this manga's author could write a great masterpiece one day.
You really had it?
Yes. I just borrowed this one, though.
You knew about this manga, right?
Yuasa couldn't keep her mouth shut, huh?
You were friends with the author of this manga, right?
Friends? Yeah, I guess.
I hope Haruna's doing all right. Haven't heard from her for ages.
Have you read this manga?
I kind of understand where you were coming from.
That "good" and "bad" are in the end subjective definitions.
But I still can't accept that as the truth!
If that's true, then what's the point?
Is that why you brought up Dead at Dusk?
But that's a serious story.
If I were a comedy buff, I wouldn't even read it.
That's what I meant.
If you read it, you'd understand! I'm positive!
There are stories that have the power to appeal to everyone!
Only if you're someone who knows the difference.
Kouchi!
I'm kidding.
Did you think I seriously believed that?
You have no sense of humor, Ibara.
I don't think Ayako really meant it.
I can't get away from it, can I?
I never finished reading that manga.
I stopped midway.
Do you know why?
No...
You said if I read it, I'd understand.
I really did. I really started to understand.
But I don't want to admit that.
What about you?
If you had a friend who didn't even read manga, as far as you knew...
If she made an original script...
You know, if she wrote it...
You'd think it couldn't possibly be any good, right?
So it's in my closet, buried inside a box at the very back.
I pretended I couldn't see it and that there was no such thing as a true classic.
What a crazy twist of fate.
You must've gone through some trouble to get that,
but sorry, I'm not gonna read it.
You know, if I'd read it, I'd have ended up calling her...
But even if I had called her, you know...
I can't just say, "Hey, you're amazing! I'm looking forward to your next one!"
...Can I?
That's from Body Talk...
Truly exceptional manga have been exceptional since the beginning!
Body Talk. Yeah, this'll do.
Mine don't hold a candle to either.
Are these all that are left?
Yeah.
We've... We've come so far!
Amazing! We moved that mountain of anthologies, stone by stone!
This is a bigger success than I ever expected!
Expectations...
Expectations, huh?
I can't tell Chitanda I sold them through blackmail.
Oreki!
You said I planned this incident because Kugayama lost the manuscript for Kudryavka's Order.
That was just a guess. I have no clues as to your motives.
No surprises there.
I guess only Anjou could understand my feelings.
Not President Kugayama?
Yeah.
But the code was meant for President Kugayama, right?
Yes.
Then why?
Mune... Kugayama hasn't picked up a pen since we finished Dead at Dusk.
Anjou is a genius, but I didn't know Mune could draw so well.
I pale in comparison to him.
The manuscript has been there all along! It's not lost!
If he felt like it, he could make something even greater than Dead at Dusk!
But for Mune, drawing manga was just a one-off thing he did for fun.
That was just "fun"?
It's a waste, isn't it? A shame, right?
But Mune doesn't draw anymore.
All he had to say was, "Let's do it!" and I'd do anything to make it happen.
But I was too scared to ask him.
I didn't want to believe he might not notice my message.
From desperate differences, expectations are born.
I've had expectations all along.
Then your true message was...
"Kugayama, have you read Kudryavka's Order?"
Very well done.
And his answer was?
Oh, that's right.
Mune hasn't even opened the manuscript that Anjou put all her effort into.
The code wasn't broken.
He never received my message.
Oreki, thanks for letting me borrow this!
Say thanks to your sister too, please.
Sure.
What?
Don't worry, I'll tell her.
What should we do about these four?
Now that we're not gonna sell these anymore,
why don't we all buy one more each?
And now we've sold them all!
Hooray!
Now all that's left is the Juumoji incident!
With nothing else to worry about, we can start thinking about it full-time!
Um... Actually...
Actually, Houtarou managed to find out a few things about it.
Really? Oreki!
Oh well...
We can talk about all that later,
so how about we go out to celebrate selling our entire stock of Hyouka?
Satoshi!
Bear with me for this, at least.
I'm for celebrating!
I barely got to spend any time at the Classics Club,
so I'd like to hear all your stories!
Then why don't we go to my house?
It's decided!
It is?
Okay! Let's drink ourselves silly!
You drink?
All the time! Mostly oolong tea!
Was that supposed to be a joke?
Sold out!
Next time: Does the Sun Shine on the Peaks?
Does the Sun Shine on the Peaks?