Oh, are you here to see Kamijou-kun?
Y-Yeah...
I'm sorry, but the date of his examination was moved up, so he's in the rehabilitation area right now.
I see... Thanks.
She sure visits a lot, doesn't she?
Yeah, but I'm glad she does. That patient is difficult to handle.
I hope she's cheering him up.
He was a violin prodigy before the accident, right?
Even if he were able to walk again,
it's likely he'll never be able to play an instrument with those fingers.
Out of all people, why did that happen to Kyousuke?
No matter how much I move my fingers, they don't do any good to anyone.
Why did that happen to Kyousuke instead of me?
If I use my wish to heal him, what would he think?
Would he just tell me, "Thank you"? Would that be it?
Or do I want him to say something more?
I'm... a horrible person.
Now that I think about it, back then, I still didn't know anything;
just what it meant to wish for a miracle, and what it would cost.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 4  There are such things as miracles and magic
Is that a mole?
There, I got it.
Madoka?
Huh?
If you don't hurry up and eat, you'll be late to school.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong, Nee-chan?
W-Was the food bad?
No, it's good.
It's really good.
Because I'm alive, I get to experience my dad's great cooking...
And like, I kept telling Yuuka and she still didn't get it.
She was almost crying, like, "Huh? What? Did I say something weird again?"
I was trying so hard not to laugh.
Sayaka-chan, about yesterday...
Sorry. Not right now. We'll talk later.
That's totally weird, right?
Yeah, that's kind of...
While it's true that our understanding of a woman's prime childbearing age is based off of scientific evidence,
using this to estimate a woman's age of marriageability is a huge mistake.
Thus, women over thirty plainly still have the chance for a loving marriage.
Which means that you shouldn't be using the past perfect here,
but rather the present progressive tense—
It kind of feels like we're in a different country now.
School, Hitomi-chan... Nothing has changed since yesterday.
But it feels like I'm surrounded by strangers.
Nobody knows what we know.
Nobody knows about the witches or Mami-san.
We know, and nobody else does.
It's like we're living in a different world, seeing different things.
Sayaka-chan...
It all changed a long time ago.
We should've realised it sooner.
What about you, Madoka?
Do you still want to become a magical girl?
Yeah... That makes sense.
I know it's not fair... It's pretty selfish for me to back out now,
but... I just can't...
Just remembering how she died... I can't breathe.
I'm so scared.
I hate this.
Mami-san was really kind.
As an example of the resolve we'd need to fight, she...
Hey, Kyubey, what'll happen to this city?
Who will protect everyone from the witches now that Mami-san's gone?
This has been Mami's territory for a while now,
but now that there's no one here, the other magical girls will act.
Others hunting for witches will come here soon.
But they're just after the Grief Seeds, right? Just like that transfer student.
It's true that Mami was a rare breed.
Normally you'd be less inclined to put yourself in danger if you didn't stand to gain something from it.
Everybody wants to be rewarded for their actions, after all.
So...
But I think only another magical girl would really be able to criticise that.
I understand how you two feel.
It's unfortunate, but I can't pressure you into it.
I guess this is it.
I need to go search again for girls who need my contract.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
Me, too. I'm sorry for getting you involved.
It was short, but it was fun being with you, Madoka. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Tomoe
Mami
British Tea Life
A Tea Magazine for
the Modern Adult
I'm sorry I'm so weak...
I'm sorry.
Homura-chan...
You're blaming yourself too much for this, Kaname Madoka.
Huh?
There's no one who can criticise you for your choices.
If there was, I'd never forgive them.
You listened to my warning.
Yeah.
If I had listened to you sooner...
That still wouldn't have changed Tomoe Mami's fate.
But you were able to change your own.
I'm happy I was able to save at least one person.
Y-You know, Homura-chan...
You seem like a veteran, but in a different way from Mami-san.
That might be true. I won't deny it.
Have you seen a lot of people die like yesterday?
I have.
How many?
Enough to give up on counting.
I wonder if her room will stay like that forever.
Tomoe Mami only had distant relatives.
I'm sure it'll be a while before anyone reports her missing.
No one... will notice that she died?
That's just how it is.
If someone dies in there, there is no corpse left behind.
She'll be deemed forever missing in this world.
That's what happens to magical girls in the end.
That's horrible...
She fought alone to protect everyone, but no one even realises it...
That's terrible.
That's the contract we made to receive this power.
It's not for anyone else.
You keep fighting for the wish you made for yourself.
Even if no one notices, even if no one remembers you at all, that's just how it is.
I'll remember.
I won't forget Mami-san.
I never will!
I see.
Tomoe Mami's lucky to have someone who thinks that.
It's enough to make me jealous.
I won't...
I won't forget you, either!
I won't forget how you saved us yesterday!
Homura-chan?
You're too kind.
Huh?
Don't forget that kindness can sometimes bring forth an even greater sadness.
What are you listening to?
(The Girl with the Flaxen Hair)
La Fille aux Cheveux de lin.
Oh, Debussy, right?
That's a pretty song.
Everyone thinks that I don't listen to classical music. I mean, take a look at me.
So sometimes people get really surprised when I know the name of a song.
It's so unexpected that people really start to respect me for it.
It's because you taught me all about it.
If you didn't, I probably would've never had the chance to really appreciate this type of music.
Sayaka, you...
Huh?
What is it?
Sayaka, are you making fun of me?
Why are you still making me listen to music?
Are you trying to harass me?
Well, you like music, so...
I don't want to listen to anything anymore!
I just sit here listening to music that I can't even play anymore!
I just... I just...
I can't move my fingers anymore.
I can't even feel pain.
My hand is worthless!
It'll be okay.
It'll all work out.
If you don't give up, I'm sure someday...
They told me to give up.
They told me to give up on performing again.
My doctor told me personally that with current medical science, it just won't happen.
I won't be able to use my hand again.
It won't get better unless there's a miracle or someone uses magic.
That's possible.
Miracles and magic do exist.
I think we could be friends with Homura-chan if we just talked.
I wonder why she ended up fighting with Mami-san.
Huh?
Hitomi-chan...
Hitomi-chan!
Didn't you have practice today?
That's what happened to that woman from before!
Hitomi-chan!
Hey, Hitomi-chan!
Oh, Kaname-san, good day.
Wh-What's wrong?
Where are you trying to go?
Where? Somewhere much better than here, yes.
Hitomi-chan...
Oh, I know. You should come with me.
Yes, that would just be wonderful!
What should I do?
Isn't this...
If I could just get a hold of Homura-chan...
No, I can't! I don't know her cell number.
That's right. I'm worthless.
I couldn't even run this one small factory right.
There's no place for me in this world anymore. Not now.
Listen up, Madoka.
If you handle these things improperly, some of them can cause terrible things to happen.
Everyone here will die.
Don't get it wrong, okay?
No!
You can't do that!
You mustn't interrupt them.
They're performing a holy ritual.
But that's dangerous!
Everyone here will die!
That's right! We are all going on a journey to another wonderful world!
Do you understand just how wonderful that is?
Our living bodies are holding us back.
Kaname-san, you'll understand soon!
Let go of me!
Wh-What should I do...
What should I do?!
N-No!
This can't be happening!
No! Someone save me!
I wonder if this is a punishment of some sort...
I'm sure this happened because I'm weak... because I'm a liar.
That's why... I'm being punished.
Sayaka-chan?
This is the end!
Sorry about that.
That was close, wasn't it?
Sayaka-chan... you're wearing...
Huh?
I guess you can say I had a change of heart.
It's fine.
I did fine for my first time on the job, didn't I?
But...
You...
Hmph.
Pretty late, aren't you, Ms. Transfer Student?
I didn't expect you to come, of all people.
I heard Mami kicked the bucket.
I came all the way out here, too.
I mean, what gives? This isn't what you told me.
Sorry, but there's already a new magical girl in this area.
She just made a contract not too long ago, though.
What the hell? That really pisses me off.
But you know, I don't think I want to give such a great spot to a rookie.
What are you planning, Kyouko?
Isn't it obvious?
All I have to do is... beat the crap...
...out of her.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Illustrator Kobayashi Jin
I'm flying high!
Magical Girl Sayaka-chan will do everything she can to protect Mitakihara City!
Episode 5        There's no way I regret anything
There's no way I regret anything.