Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
I want you to keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Hello everyone, I'm Yuri Killian.
Today is the day the
Circus Festival will take place.
Three years ago, on this
day, I was here with Layla.
And our glory also started from here.
This time, my partner is Sora.
There's no way to erase the
mistakes I made in the past,
but this time I intend to do everything in
my power for Sora, Layla, and Kaleido Stage.
But, I wonder if Sora really
can tolerate this cruel stage.
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Too slow.
It's too early this time!
"Cruel Amazing Festival."
The school Yuri's attending
should be around here, but...
I found him.
Why don't we stop here today?
Not yet.
Okay, then, one more hour.
Then let's end today's training.
Resting is another part
of practice, after all.
Yes.
So this is the practice room
for the school Yuri is attending.
What kind of maneuver are they working on?
Anyway, I'm glad to know Sora is safe.
Mr. Mute and Miss Alice,
thank you for helping us today.
You're welcome. By the way,
can we come tomorrow too?
Oh... You don't have to.
We learned a lot. So,
please? Say it's all right.
Is it okay with you?
Since they're nice enough
to offer their help,
it's impolite to say no. Don't you think so?
Yes... That's true.
Then please come and help us.
Great!
See you tomorrow, then.
Yes. Good night.
Good night.
Sora, I'll walk you to your hotel.
Well, but I didn't book a hotel.
What?!
Then, why don't you stay at my place?
Well... but... it's like
I'm asking you too much.
--Hi, Sora!
--Ken?!
What a coincidence!
What are you doing?
Well... I was... taking a walk.
Taking a walk?
But you're breathing hard. Are you okay?
Yeah...
Anyway, if you need a place
to stay, I'll find a place for you.
Well, but...
It doesn't bother me even
one bit if you stay at my place.
No, Sora is a part of the Kaleido Stage cast.
Kaleido Stage will look after her.
Thank you for everything!
Get a good night's sleep.
Okay!
Yes, there is.
Oh, good.
Sora, you've got a room.
Really? Thank you, Ken.
So shall we charge the room to Kaleido Stage?
No. Please charge it to me, Ken Robbins.
And please keep this secret from her.
Yes, sir.
An angel's maneuver.
I'll make sure to perfect it.
And I'm going to win.
So I guess the ones I need to
watch out for are Mr. & Mrs. Patrova
and the street performer
pair, Mute and Alice.
Well, I did refine my Demon
Spiral even further, after all.
We'll be the victors, no mistake.
What is this?
I'm going to compete against the
maneuvers of the world's top stars,
and yet I'm not quite fired up.
Something is missing. I wonder why.
Don't try to force a jump.
Okay!
Feel out the moment when your
body gains the most power, then jump!
And maintain a beautiful pose as you go up.
Sora...
Are you aware of your weak point?
Yes. Ken told me before.
Since I've only been doing big
maneuvers, my body's unbalanced.
Yes. But even with only the
basics they teach at circus school,
you shouldn't lose this much balance.
In Japan, there are hardly any
circus schools, so I haven't gone.
Really?
To think she was able to perform
the legendary great maneuver without...
I'll work hard. I'll endure
it no matter how tough it is.
This maneuver is called
the "Angel's Maneuver"
because it gives the
impression of weightlessness,
just like the feathers of an angel's wings.
Just like a ballerina, in order to
make your body seem light as a feather
and maintain a beautiful pose, you
need strong grounding in the basics.
I even endured Mr. Leon's
special training and passed!
Just like I did then,
no matter how tough it gets,
I'll cover for my lack of
basics through force of will!
So, please, Yuri!
Sora, when it's you saying it,
I start to feel like you really can.
All right. Then, let's continue practice.
Yes!
I have to master my timing.
And I have to pose beautifully.
What?! What does this mean?
Why's Sora's name registered?
Her partner is Yuri.
I see... there was that method.
So she still hasn't given up on victory.
Interesting.
I know now... what was
missing in this festival.
Sora... it was you!
Fool, try to knock me
down by crashing into me!
Okay!
Please crash into my back.
What?
And I was this close too...
Yes!
Too fast!
Too slow! Pay more attention!
Yes!
Demon Spiral!
Her move has changed.
What's this feeling?
I can hardly wait for the festival.
I want to compete with
Sora in the festival, soon!
I want to compete with Sora.
Don't forget to pose!
Yes!
In only a few days, she
managed to reach this point...
Impressive as ever.
Now, if she can just
maintain that beautiful pose...
Amazing... I've never seen that maneuver.
It really looks like an angel's wings.
I can do this!
The day has finally come.
Everything will be determined today.
Sora!
Hi, Sora!
Mia, Miss Sarah, you came?
Where is Anna?
Un, deux, trois, un, deux, trois...
un chien!
Mr. Charlie. He's the real thing!
It seems she was able to meet
the clown she admired, Mr. Charlie.
Anna looks happy.
Yuri, it's been a long time, hasn't it?
Yeah.
Thank you for coming. I know
traveling expenses are not cheap.
If you're concerned about travel expenses,
Miss Sarah negotiated that with the Boss for us.
So all expenses are paid by Kaleido Stage.
What? Really?
So I'm the only one paying
everything out of my own pocket.
Well, I guess there's nothing I can do now.
Sora, make sure you win!
So we can participate in the
festival together three years from now.
Yes!
Oh!
I forgot to bring my good luck pendant!
Oh... I might be done for.
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
Oh, excuse me.
Hey, that's Yuri Killian.
It sure is...
He should stay in retirement.
The partner he's with...
Isn't she the girl who paired with Layla
Hamilton in that legendary great maneuver?
Yep, that's right.
So they're a pair of big shots.
That stinks.
Sora...
May...
Sora, I see you don't
know when to give up either.
We're going to win!
We will not lose to the two of you!
I can't wait to see the result.
Leon...
Yuri Killian...
Hi. Long time, no see.
What?
Did you meet each other when you
participated in the festival three years ago?
Leon?
Whoever thought that we'd
see each other at this place again?
Perhaps a match with you
is my unavoidable destiny.
Then, do you want to pair with me?
With me as I am now, the
one they call the God of Death?
You have changed.
I learned from you.
You taught me what I need to
do to climb to the top in this world.
You should place more
value in your current partner.
What's going on?
Did something happen between
Leon and Mr. Yuri three years ago?
I... don't know. I don't. I don't.
By the way, maybe, you don't
know that Miss Layla is here.
Really?
Yes. To present the trophy to the winners.
I wonder which one of us is going
to receive the trophy from Miss Layla.
And now, for the opening of
this International Circus Festival,
we'd like the previous winner,
Miss Layla Hamilton, to say a few words!
Layla!
This is a very cruel place.
But there's also a step forward that we
can't take unless we overcome this place.
Compete with each other,
train each other, improve each other,
and in order to take the
first step toward your dream,
give this everything you have.
Sorry, sorry. My hand slipped.
But I see they don't call you
the God of Death for nothing.
Even if you destroy your partner,
you're certainly not destroyed.
Entry No. 5, Mr. & Mrs. Patrova.
Mr. & Mrs. Patrova always look
like such a happily married couple.
Very soon, it will be May and Leon's turn.
Then after that, it will be Mute and Alice.
Then Sora's turn will be after that.
Oh... This is more nerve-wracking
than when I'm in competition.
I know, I know.
Sora, you want some water?
Oh, thank you.
What's wrong?
Well... Since Mr. Mute and
Alice aren't here yet,
I wonder what happened.
Now that you mention it...
Leave them alone.
Don't worry about other people.
But they helped me practice every day.
If something happened
to them because of that...
Oh... Did you exploit your rivals' goodwill?
For you, that's not half bad.
You're wrong. I didn't mean it like that.
What? Don't pretend to be
little Miss Goody Two-Shoes.
In the end, it's the same
as if you used them, isn't it?
It'd be nice if they just didn't show up.
Let's go.
Yes.
I never meant...
I'll step out and check on them.
No.
Leave them alone.
Mr. Yuri...
They'll be here.
What?
Sorry for being late. No. 8, Mute and Alice.
Be ready and stand by in the waiting room.
They made it.
Mr. Mute and Miss Alice,
I'm glad you made it.
Oh, nice... costumes.
Both of you look like... angels...
That's right.
Excuse us, but we will do the
Angel's Maneuver before you do.
Since you used us,
don't you think it's only fair?
Oh... I never meant...
Did you think we'd just
help you with good intentions?
In order to make everyone's
dream come true, we cannot lose.
We did nothing against the rules.
Sora, are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
What's wrong with me?
I felt a little sick.
Oh... but I think I'm...
I'm fine now. So...
I told you, don't screw up the timing!
I did it right!
If we can't win this year,
we don't have another chance.
I already know that.
Honestly. I hate that Kaleido Stage.
Finally, after Layla Hamilton retired,
they had to send two pairs this year.
Oh, you're here...
Thanks to you, our dream broke into pieces.
Thanks a lot.
Are you satisfied?
Nobody is wrong. This is that kind of world.
You were prepared for this, weren't you?
Yes.
Well, it's almost time to go.
This is a very cruel place.
But there's also a step forward that we
can't take unless we overcome this place.
And in order to take the
first step towards my dream...
Demon!
Spiral!
What kind of maneuver is this?!
Can he grab her?
It's impossible.
It's even more amazing than before.
The hall is dead silent.
Everyone's been enchanted by a demon.
By a demon...
What is this? I feel out of place.
It should be the same applause as usual,
but I'm afraid to win this applause.
During the practice,
we almost managed perfection.
So, we're going to perfect this here.
We can do it!
The Angel's Maneuver...
No, this isn't even close
to the Angel's Maneuver.
Alice!
Mute, hold on!
Ouch...
I screwed up.
Mute...
Mr. Mute...
We never thought of imitating someone.
But, because you suddenly
decided to participate...
Stop, Alice.
Sorry, Sora.
We want to win in the festival
and get the world's attention,
and organize a performance team
with these guys right here, and travel.
That is our dream.
Excuse us, but we will do the
Angel's Maneuver before you do.
In the end, it's same as
if you used them, isn't it?
Thanks to you, our dream
broke into pieces. Thanks a lot.
No...
No. This isn't the place I was aiming for.
The stage I was aiming for is...
The stage I saw with my mother
and father was more fun, and...
Sorry, Miss Layla...
I should never have come here.
She's not coming down.
Why?
The Angel's Maneuver...
I think I heard about it before.
Angel's Maneuver?
Sora!
Give me your hands!
Can you still continue?
Sorry... I can't.
Sora...
She's going to quit?
Sora... Is she crying?
Isn't it the Angel's Maneuver?
I've never seen it before.
I didn't know Kaleido Stage
had that kind of talent.
I wonder why she quit in the middle of it.
If she did it all the way
through, she might have won.
What? Did she just give up?
Mastering the Angel's
Maneuver to that extent...
Come in.
Well...
Miss Layla, I'm sorry.
I can't believe you withdrew.
You're the worst.
You disgraced the festival.
You ran away from the stage
where a serious match was.
I'm disappointed in you, Sora.
I'm sorry.
I thought walking Miss Layla's
path could take me to my dream,
but I don't know anymore.
What should I aim for?
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
Sora, do you really intend
to just end things like this?
And so, I ended up coming back to Japan.
My old friends...
Welcome back, Sora.
A loving family....
This... this is fine.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing and Sad Homecoming."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...