How long you gonna stand there?
Come on...! After the AC
stopped working at my place...
...I really thought I was gonna die!!
It's broken...
I couldn't rest during the entire night,
I need some sleep...
Not here!
She's right. We need to fix up our
next song in time for the festival.
...Fix it?
I already like it as it is though.
Really?
Something about it
you aren't happy with?
Uuh... how do I put it...
It comes off a bit... generic.
What do you think, Tomo-chan?
Look, I just can't deal with you
anymore, "sensei" wannabe. I'm quitting.
Yeah, I'm quitting too.
Not really, it's good enough.
Why didn't you say anything?
9: THE CRESCENT MOON RISES
You said earlier that something
felt off with her music, right?
Not really.
I think it's good enough.
If you say so. Better that way.
Ignoring her food as always...
...You're gonna die at this rate, you know?
Who could it be?
A salesman?
WATER TROUBLE? CALL US ON THE DOUBLE!
Since the mailbox is broken, can you go check?
Sure...
- Hello, it's me, Nina!
- Not interested.
Hold up, I haven't even
said anything yet?!
What do you want?
Ah, I can feel the AC...
Don't steal others' air without permission!!
Come on, don't be a hoarder~
Shut up, you neighbor complaint magnet!
You're the one screaming here!
Stop ringing!!
Paradise!
If you've freshened up,
go home already!
You're evicting me??
The AC won't be fixed until next week...
That's not my problem!
Doesn't Momoka-san's place have an AC?
Yes, but she works night shifts.
Hey, is it just me or...
...should we raise the AC?
Power (DO NOT TOUCH)
Told you, you can't beat this cool.
Your pathetic AC could never.
Pathetic??
A little push and it gave up entirely!
That's why the remote said "DO NOT TOUCH"!!
Long story short,
Both of our ACs have sadly passed on.
We would be most honored if you
could host us in your humble abode.
Just for an hour!! I'M BEGGING YOU!!
This is all her fault, so...
Fine... just for an hour thooOOOOAAAHH
Ah, that's Tomo-chan's pet!
It hates the heat too, so...
Who told you could let that in?!!
POWERFUL!
Do you ever shut up?
Your apartment's impressive.
These girls, I swear...
Ah, it's Momoka-san!
She said since she works close by she's dropping by later.
Subaru: The other three said they broke their ACs,
so they just occupied my apartment ._.
You wanna come too, Momoka-san?
Momoka: I'm working near the ShinPrince Hotel,
I'll be done in 30 mins so I'll drop by later
Subaru: ROGER THAT!
Oh, really?
Then let's eat together while we're at it~
Momoka: WEY, WEY, LET'S GET SMASHED
Since when did we agree on that?
What happened to "just one hour"?
Come on, go...
Oh damn, the last train's gone!
What a shame.
You were planning this all along, you devious...!
Come on chill out, I brought cards!
You DID plan this!
When you think about it, we've never
done something like this together~
So just the four of us for now, right?
I'm good.
I'm borrowing this room.
I've also got Monopoly
if you want! Maybe Risk?
You gonna sleep in there?
Did I do something wrong?
Did you not?
No, this isn't your fault, Nina-san.
...Really?
I'll talk with her a bit.
Need to sleep early?
Not really.
The three of you are enough
to play cards or whatever else.
Leave me alone.
I see.
If you've got something to say, say it!
Something? I should be asking the same.
Loser pays for dinner!!
RUPA: 100 POINTS / NINA: 2 POINTS / SUBARU: 10 POINTS
I lost...
What the hell happened...?
Nina being Nina.
I didn't do anything! It's all the AC's fault!!
You could've just dealt with it!
I tried to!
I tried killing time in a conbini!
I tried chilling at a bench for an hour...
But being out when you're
broke is just TOO boring!!
Where's Tomo?
Sleeping already.
She end up saying anything about the song?
Nothing specific...
I see...
I could swear she didn't
vibe with it though...
Where are you going?
To the fridge.
They'll taste bad otherwise.
And what are you gonna do if my grandma finds out?
Don't worry, I'll drink them all by tomorro...
Snake?
That's Tomo-chan's pet!
Don't worry, she doesn't bite... or is venomous, I think.
SNAKEEEEEE!!!
- Don't waste it!
- AAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!
Momoka-san?
Momoka-san!
Do you mind not locking yourself in?
Just get rid of it, quick!!
Momoka-san is scared of snakes?
She's buried herself in there.
I mean it's a snake! A SNAKE!!
How can you be so calm??
- Pfft, not really?
- How am I the weird one here?!
There's no way all four of you are okay with this?!
You just need to get to know her!
Momoka-san! Isn't that a snake behind you?
(Just a hairdryer)
Ah, she let... go?
BEGONEEEEE!!
- NICE PITCH!
- Hey, wait!
- Wait, Momoka-san!
- Get out already!
Hey, if you break something,
I'm the one who has to pay here!
Look, we left the snake with Tomo-chan, so just...
Please get out already.
Like I said, if you break something...
I'm not risking it!
Stop acting like a kid!
- You're gonna brea--
- Nina-san!
How you like that?
You're kidding me...
I'M GONNA KILL YOU ALL!!!
You also like hiding away, huh?
Never come back again.
- It's so hot...
- WHOSE FAULT IS IT?!
What a merry band.
Merry HOW?!
Ugh, back to work I guess.
Good luck...
And keep that snake away.
Actually, where's Snake-chan?
Subaru agreed to let her stay, at least.
God, I wish I was a snake.
Guess we're going back home, then.
Let's go, Rupa.
We need to check up on our apartment.
You're leaving me alone?
Why should I even bother seeing
your face if we don't have practice?
Uuh, Momoka-san said it was important
to meet even outside of practice, right?
If you're free, do you want to see me practicing guitar?
I'll go grab my guitar real quick!
An acoustic guitar?
Yeah.
According to Mine-san, the key is to practice regularly.
It's an old guitar, but a good one.
The second string is off.
Oh, really?
You're incredible, Tomo-chan.
You said you've been studying
piano since you were little, right?
That has nothing to do with it.
Anyone could tell something's off.
Still, guitars are incredible.
I'm already starting to get calluses
on my fingers from practicing.
Is this better?
It's still a bit messy, but...
That's the best you can do for now, right?
Alright then.
What do you think? I bet people
are gonna love this at our concert!
You've gotten so good!
If we had another guitarist,
We could really heat things up!
Denied.
And performing like this in front
of an audience? Are you joking?
...mo-chan?
Tomo-chan!
How was it?
What do you think, Rupa?
I'm not qualified enough to say...
And I look like a guitar expert to you?
But you are in music theory, right?
I guess.
I guess... it sounds good enough for a hobby.
...For a hobby?
You don't think I could play on stage?
Do you want to?
Mm! You see, when I saw DD playing live I thought...
That I want to get a lot better.
I don't want to keep relying on Momoka-san,
I want to stand alongside her instead.
Ah, alongside everyone too, of course.
So let me know if there's anything I should improve!
Nothing, really.
Come on, Tomo-chan!
If you keep fooling around like that...
...you're never gonna get anywhere!!
...I see.
Girls Band Cry.
How many times do I gotta tell you, take this seriou--
Get that stick out of your ass already!
Not all of us get the luxury
to be taught piano since childhood.
I can't do this anymore.
- Wait...
- You shut your mouth.
Look,
I tried talking to her yesterday too, but...
It's cooled down a bit, at least.
Has it really?
At the very least, it's not all bad to live without AC.
Getting to feel the changing weather on your skin...
Nina: I'll wait in the park in front of the apartment
Rupa: Sure thing~
Nina: THANK YOU FOR TODAY
Nina: It's still boiling in here
Nina-san seemed very grateful.
There's no way she was...
Bold of you to show your face again.
You see, I've got a little problem...
Hmm?
Wait! I mean it! It's not about the AC!
You swear?
I need some serious advice
regarding the future of our band.
I'll definitely pay you back (in 36 payments) - Iseri Nina
So?
What did Tomo say?
That if I keep fooling around like this...
...I'm not gonna get anywhere.
The truth stings.
Well, she's not the type to mince words.
Have you lost motivation?
...Why would I?
Well, if you say so, that's good enough!
And what do you think, Subaru-chan?
Well, I have to agree with Tomo.
...I see.
And here I thought I practiced
enough to give it a shot...
Anyone would need at least a year
or two to get good enough...
Especially if you want to play it professionally.
But you seem to be able to wing it so easily...
Do I look that way?
If I asked Tomo, I'm sure she'd have a whole
grocery list of things to say about my playing.
But she's never said anything, has she?
Because unlike you,
I've never asked her for feedback.
Tomo's a pretty shy person, all and all.
Since she doesn't like being left out,
she always keeps herself at a distance.
She won't approach you on her own.
But if you try to approach her instead...
RAWR!
You look just like her...
You used to be like this too, you know?
Sorry to intrude again.
I've cleaned out the terrarium,
so you can take her back.
Is it a problem she hasn't eaten anything?
Not really.
Ah, Tomo-chan!
You're still at it?
Yeah!
I wanted some feedback from Subaru-chan too.
Ouch...
I guess you're good enough.
Shouldn't be too big of a deal on stage.
Why are you lying to me?
Tomo-chan?
Her old band quit?
When she came to Tokyo, she recruited members online,
And formed a band.
Wait... is that when the two of you met?
Yes. Alongside another guitarist and drum player.
We said we were gonna go pro, but...
Well, yeah. A common story.
Is it that common?
It's easy to say "You're just not working hard enough"
When you're someone successful.
But if that were true,
everyone would have an equal chance.
Indeed.
And Tomo-chan knows this well.
That's why she's always harping
about this and that never being enough.
Since she assumed that all of us
were just as serious about making it,
She just kept becoming more
and more demanding with them.
Well, sounds like her alright.
And yet you stood by her side.
Even if Tomo-chan said she wanted to go solo...
She was just too young.
A guarantor?
I don't want to contact my parents again.
I promise I won't bother you, so...
So she came to live with me,
We started our duo Beni Shoga,
And even got an offer to go pro.
But to get this far, she's had to
butt heads with a lot of people, huh...
As a result of that,
I feel she's become scared to speak her mind.
Like even her own feelings aren't good enough now.
What do you think, Momoka-san?
Of my guitar?
Do you think I'm good enough to play on stage together?
Are you serious?
...Of course.
I'm back!
You're late.
Oh! It's finally eating!
Look!
She is!
No matter how careful and timid you can be,
You won't get anywhere if you just freeze up.
What you getting at?
Come on, Tomo-chan. Won't you join me for a walk?
Hasn't cooled one bit.
From tomorrow, we're back to practice again.
I'm hoping it doesn't rain though...
It's because I know I wasn't wrong.
If I'm saying it's not enough,
it's because it isn't!
Because it's just not enough!
Then why did you lie to her?
That's...
I mean, that's what Nina wanted to hear, right?
She wants to play on stage with Momoka...
But that's exactly why she asked you.
Because she wants to improve.
Everyone always says that.
"I'm serious!" "I want to improve!"
But they really just want to be complimented!
They just want to be showered in comfort...
You can hear her, right?
Ouch!
From the top!
Like this, like that, and like-- fuck!
Heed my orders, you stupid fingers!!
When I saw the three of them playing live,
Something became crystal clear.
These girls... they're serious about this.
They don't care about "can'ts" or "enoughs",
When on stage, they're just their real selves.
That's all you've been looking for... right?
YOU FUCKING SUCK!!!
Thanks! I promise I'll become better!
You really suck...
You love to see it.
What's wrong?
It's just... something's really bugging me...
What exactly?
Ah, forget it.
Let's just take a break.
Momoka.
I think as it is now, this song is just too boring.
Damn right!
NEXT: "WANDERVOGEL"