Nishimi... Nishimi.
You're back at the top of the class.
I was worried with your grades dropping there for a while,
but it looks like you've straightened out your act.
Maybe it's because entrance exams are looming,
or maybe it's thanks to the disappearance of that impediment to your studies?
Pass it here!
I never thought they'd agree to open up the roof, but they went right for it.
I heard a third-year thug was monopolizing the key up 'til now.
Hi, Richie-boy! I'm playing volleyball with the girls.
How about joining in?
No. I'll pass.
Richie-boy!
I know you're lonely without Kawabuchi, but you have to get over it.
You're right. Thanks.
Mukae!
Want me to get Nishimi for you?
No, that's okay.
It's cold!
I love drinking milkshakes when it starts getting cold outside!
Hey, Ritsuko? Are you awake?
Yeah.
You've been worried about Kawabuchi since he disappeared, haven't you?
Y-Yeah, there's that too.
I know! It's Nishimi, isn't it?
Like, you haven't been able to talk at all or go home together recently?
Ri, you can't just wait.
You need to make things happen yourself.
Hey, look!
Isn't that him?
Ri.
Were you eating sweets?
You've got whipped cream on your mouth.
Um, Kaoru... You're not coming to the basement today, either?
No. Sorry.
With entrance exams coming up, I've decided not to go for a while.
I see. That makes sense.
Tell Pops that I'm sorry for not being able to come.
See you around.
Wait!
Kaoru, um... Why not study at my place?
The shop's closed today? Where's your dad?
He's off buying up stock, so it's just me today.
Give me a second. I'll clean up here.
That's my favorite photo. I always have it out here.
Both of you look so happy in it.
Just look at Sentaro's face.
Stop talking about him.
Shall we get started? English and Math, right?
So first of all, the word order is reversed.
This "so" comes first, and the subject and verb change places.
What?
Um... I'm sorry about before.
I wasn't thinking about how you felt when I showed you that photo.
His disappearance hit you the hardest, didn't it?
I'm fine.
He may not be around, but I still have you.
W-Wait, Kaoru!
Don't! Hey!
Kaoru, wait!
I'm glad he's gone.
Now I can be alone with you whenever I want.
Stop it!
How? How could you say that?
You're happy that he's gone?
Even if you're joking, I don't want to hear such a thing!
I'm sorry about that.
Ri, I haven't been able to say this before,
but I'm going to a college in Tokyo.
I'll go home for today.
I'm scum!
The lowest of the low!
Damn it! Why did things turn out like this?
East
High
Gradu-
ation
They didn't call Kawabuchi's name, huh?
What's the difference?
Everyone's going their own way.
We'll all forget being here in no time.
Nishimi.
I won't ever forget your performance at the school festival last year!
Excuse me.
Maruo? Could I have the second button on your jacket?
Sure, if you'd be satisfied with mine.
I did it!
I wasn't sure if I'd be able to ask you.
I was crying my eyes out.
I'm so happy!
Farewell and good riddance to this damned hill!
Don't go trudging up the thing tomorrow out of habit!
I see.
So you're going off to a college in Tokyo too, huh?
Well, it'll probably get a little lonely around here.
Nah, we can't get gloomy about it.
It's great news, isn't it?
Oh, that's right. Ritsuko was accepted to the college here.
Hey, Ritsuko! Come down!
Richie-rich got into college! Hey!
Ri! You can stay there, but just listen!
I'm sorry about the other day.
You may not want to hear anything from me, but just let me say this!
The reason I started coming here is because I wanted to see your smile!
It's always encouraged me, even when things were rough.
I never knew that feeling before meeting you.
Thank you, Ri.
Meeting you was a blessing.
Call us as soon as you get there.
I will.
Kaoru, write me, okay?
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you for everything.
The sleeper express train, Sakura, will depart for Tokyo on track one.
Its next stop will be Haiki.
All passengers, please get on board.
Hey!
I made it in time!
Here, a little going-away gift.
Thanks, Pops.
Um... Is Ri...
Nope. But there's a lunch in there that she made for you.
Well, take care, Richie.
I will. You too, Pops!
See you again!
Ri!
It's okay.
When you're sick, you're apt to lose heart,
but like they say, sickness and health start with the mind.
Doctor, you have a good head on your shoulders for someone so young.
Oh, no. I'm still a rookie.
Dr. Nishimi, we've got an emergency.
Okay, I'll be right there!
Hey, there's a free bed in the nap room.
Why don't you get a little rest?
No, if I lie down now, it's all over.
I won't be able to wake up.
Yeah, being a resident on the night shift is even harder than I heard it'd be.
It takes a lot of stamina.
Tell me about it.
Our guest is a popular star who both sings and acts.
Matsuoka Seiji joins us in the studio today!
Guest: Matsuoka Seiji
Hello! I'm Matsuoka Seiji!
I want to start right off with a question.
Which do you like better, singing or acting?
What's wrong?
Th-That's...
I like them both...
a classmate from high school.
Huh? My little sister goes nuts over that guy!
And I like jazz too.
Hey, get me an autograph!
Oh, jazz?
I see. So Matsuoka's dream came true.
Dream...
I don't believe it.
Kaoru? Kaoru, is that you?
Yurika.
How wonderful! You've become a doctor!
Um...
Oh, I'm six months along.
Junichi wants a girl, but I wonder...
I think he'd spoil her rotten.
How about you? Been doing good?
Do you still play the piano?
No.
I'd heard that Sentaro had taken off,
but you've never seen him since then?
Oh, that's right.
This is no time to be catching up.
There's something I've been carrying around to show everyone.
A friend from back home sent me this photo,
but don't you think the person on the far left looks like someone we know?
U-Um...
Can I borrow this photo?
What the hell am I doing?
I've been trying to forget him all this time...
but my heart's racing now.
There's no way I can stop this rhythm in my heart.
The church is at the top of that hill.
Young priest? Dunno.
The priest here has been around for years and years.
Yeah, I think he helps raise the orphans from around the prefecture.
He raises children?
Yes, you mean the priest-in-training.
I hear he does nothing but cause trouble for the poor priest, though.
Th-Thank you!
Could it be...
Could it be him?
Don't see this every day!
Lucky!
Pick me up too!
What's wrong?
I always thought this day might come.
Looks like it's today.
Enough! What do you two think you're doing?
I told you that you can only play on special occasions, but you keep doing as you please!
Uh-oh! Run, Richie!
Hey, wait! Sen!
You changed me so much I don't remember what I was like before we met.
The breeze caresses our cheeks.
Lullaby of Birdland...
As we run down the slope,
our flimsy shadows extend.
It's like a neverending summer vacation.
It feels like when we snuck into the pool.
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
It's an intense spiral of temptation.
A beat pierces my heart. A strange one.
It vanishes after a quick spark.
It's been a long time. How are you? I'm writing now because
there's something I want to tell you, Ritsuko.
A friend of mine from back home got married at a church,
and in a photo of the ceremony that she sent me, there's a priest
who resembles Sentaro. I'm not sure of it,
but thought it would be worth looking into.
The church is on a small island, so it should be easy to find.
I just wrote this postcard to let you know.
If you find anything out, please write back.
Yours truly,
Fukahori Yurika
Even on bad days, I dress up
and dance to some swing. The music quickly surrounds me.
What is this dance exactly? I can't stop it.
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
The melody...
is like love.
I was waiting for you on that slope.
We made a promise to meet after school.
The goodbye blurred into the distance.
So weak, so twisted, so fragile
had I been back then,
but you gave me a small pair of wings.
I'm searching the sky beyond the twilight
for the faint flicker of light
because I want to tell you I love you.
I wrote a letter to you in my textbook margins,
but I could never give it to you.
It's still just there.