Tina!
Bonjour, Tina!
That dolphin is Minami's friend!
She really is the Princess of the Sea!
I'm so happy I get to meet your parents!
They're the head honchos of
world-renowned Kaidou Group, to boot!
We're here!
It's huge!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
A pleasure to see you again, Mother and Father.
You look well, Minami.
Same as ever?
Yes, every day is a blessing.
Sorry, Wataru. I know you must be busy.
Come now, I'll always come running for my dear sister.
Thank you, Brother.
I've never seen a family so splendid in my life!
You can feel the billionaire aura!
Wow!
Our apologies for making you wait.
N-Not at all!
A pleasure to meet you!
M-My name is H-Haruno H-H-H...
Stuttering on your own name?
Can you blame me?
What a delightful young lady.
We humbly thank you for your invitation.
Are you certain we're not imposing?
This party is for friends and family.
Allowing my daughter's dear friends to go uninvited simply would not do.
Now please, enjoy the festivities.
Tides of the Heart!
What Minami Fights to Protect!
It'll look beautiful on you, Minami.
You didn't have to go through the trouble of making me a new dress.
But it's my little girl's big day!
Hearing that you wanted to join the Kaidou group...
couldn't have made me happier!
Oh, Mother...
A pool on top of the deck!
A movie theater!
And a dance hall!
It's huuuuge!
Having fun, I take it?
Sorry, I just...
This ship is called the Seadream.
Can you guess why I named it that?
Huh?
Guests should enjoy the sea as though it were a dream.
I named this ship in the hopes that they would.
Your smiles are our pleasure, after all!
Your brother's certainly splendid,
but your parents are simply splendid as well!
I can see why you look up to them so much.
Thank you.
You're going to work in the Kaidou Group when you grow up, right?
Yes.
I want to serve society just as my parents and brother do.
That's always been my childhood dream!
What a magnificent dream!
Dream?
Tina!
Who could she be?
Goodness!
You're really something!
I've never seen a wild dolphin be so friendly with someone.
Tina's been my friend since I was a little girl.
So, her name's Tina.
And yours is?
Oh!
I'm Kaidou Minami.
Kaidou, huh?
I'm Kitakaze Asuka.
Nice to meet you, Minami.
The pleasure's all mine.
Oh!
I gotta get back.
See ya later!
Do you have somewhere to be?
Yeah, my job.
Your job?
I'm a veterinarian.
I work at the nearby aquarium.
I'm like a doctor for sea critters.
What's that like?
If you wanna know, why not tag along?
Can we?
Of course!
Hooray!
Let's all go together!
Thanks for the offer, but...
What?
But I wanna go together!
We have an important party to attend.
We've got plenty of time.
I'll inform your parents, so go ahead.
Can we go? Huh? Can we?
Well, just for a bit.
There are so many fishies!
Oh, that crab looks like he's dancing!
Where?
What are you looking for?
I'm checking for any sick-looking fish.
Observation is key!
That fish seems to be swimming a bit sluggishly.
You're right.
Good eye there!
I'll check on her later.
Hey, he smiled!
Seals are so cute!
Those are sea lions.
They're bigger than seals and swim with their front fins.
They also have tiny earlobes.
Wow!
Oh, there are turtles over there!
Really?
My, how large!
Let's check them out!
Turtles!
You're right about the fins and earlobes!
Sorry.
He ate it!
My, how charming!
That was cute!
But I feel a tad guilty...
Well, yeah...
If everyone did, nobody would eat.
We live off of the lives of others.
Fish aren't the only living things we consume.
The circle of life spins for man and fish alike.
It's so natural that we take it for granted.
But as long as you never forget to show your gratitude for the food you receive, it balances out.
I'd never thought about it that way before...
Well, neither have most people.
Incidentally, what is it that you're writing?
I'm recording how much these little guys eat.
Why is that?
If they don't have an appetite,
I'll need to check if they're injured or sick.
These animals can rest easy
knowing you're taking care of them.
I wouldn't say that.
Sometimes medicine works, but sometimes it doesn't.
And there's still so much we don't know about the sea and its creatures.
You never stop learning.
If studying these guys can progress our research,
we may be able to find ways to protect endangered species.
It sounds like a very rewarding line of work!
Interested?
How about it?
I think you've got a knack for this.
What makes you think that?
A hunch.
It ate it!
All right, next stop!
Okay!
Pardon us for interrupting the festivities,
but I'd like to introduce you all to my daughter.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kaidou Minami.
How pretty!
Soon, I'd like to join hands with you and my family to work toward the future as part of the Kaidou Group.
That's been my sister's dream since she was a child.
When that time comes, we hope you all may provide your guidance.
Let's work together as a family.
We thank you for your continued support of the Kaidou Group.
Asuka!
Sorry I'm not fitting the dress code.
What are you doing here?
Well, I didn't plan on doing anything...
My, if it isn't Dr. Kitakaze!
Doctor?
Hey there!
Do you know each other?
Dr. Kitakaze is a world-renowned oceanographer and veterinarian.
We didn't think you'd join us today.
You never seem to bother much with events like these.
Well, I don't most of the time,
but I happened to have work nearby.
Have you reconsidered our offer?
We'd be honored to have your brilliance working for the Kaidou Group.
I'm sorry, but my answer hasn't changed.
I'll have to decline.
We'll provide full funding to your research.
Well, I can't say that doesn't sound tempting!
But...
I want to stay true to my heart.
To your heart?
I'm sure I can do great work under a corporate flag,
but I'd be tied down with so much red tape there that I'd lose sight of my dreams.
Dreams...
I want to understand the sea.
To see it with my own unrestrained eyes...
To feel it with my body and soul...
If the mood strikes me to dive into the brilliant blue...
I want the freedom to do so.
There is laughter, indeed.
It brims with dreams, indeed.
Huh? Nobody told me this was a costume party!
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to understand the sea!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Minami? Minami!
Is something the matter?
What?
That's a new one.
Never seen you space out.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Dyspairvil!
That again!
Asuka!
The dream is over...
But the despair's just begun.
Not on my watch!
I'm taking Asuka back!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
What is that?
You're in danger! You have to run!
No, you escape first! I have a duty to protect this ship!
Who the devil are you?!
Dys?
Dyspairvil!
Who...
Evacuate the guests!
I swear I'll protect this ship!
Now hurry!
Thank you!
Dyspair!
Luna!
Precure!
Full Moon Humming!
Vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair...
Dyspair!
Vil!
Dyspair...
Dyspairvil!
You'll have to go through me!
Dyspair!
Dyspairvil!
My mother and father built this ship
with the sole dream of giving others joy!
I won't let you harm it!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Ice!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Dys Dys...
Girls.
Right!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
The dream did not end.
We failed to end it.
However...
you despaired.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Thank goodness you're safe.
I want to understand the sea.
Whatever could have happened?
You girls must have been horrified!
Not at all! The party was super fun!
But where did those girls disappear to?
You said the blue one saved you?
Yes...
I'm glad we could meet again.
Same here.
Truth is, I came to the party
because I wanted to see you again.
Huh?
I'm always drawn to the denizens of the sea.
Call it curiosity.
And, well, you remind me a bit of myself.
So if you wanted to make that step,
I'd be right here waiting...
But that train of thought didn't last long.
Working with your family in the Kaidou Group...
is your childhood dream, right?
Yes.
Fantastic!
That's a fine dream.
And that dress looks great on you.
Thank you very much.
See you around.
You too.
Adieu, Asuka.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
O Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
Go! Princess Precure:
Haruka's the Star?!
The Slapstick Romantic Play!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!