What should I do?
What's up?
Yuri-chan, 29 years old,
made some curry and took it to the house of a guy,
whom she is madly in love with.
Were you waiting?
Here I am.
However, she was turned down at the door and didn't get a chance to show off her curry.
This isn't some 80's story, this is just too old-school.
He said it's not curry if the potato is all mashed,
but I thought it tasted better that way.
She's 29 and still cares about such miscellaneous things.
Curry tastes differently depending on the household.
There's Indian style, south-east Asian style,
and British style, which tastes completely different.
There are also variations which have fish paste,
fermented soy beans, and some even have hormones in them.
Again with the know-it-all. Why don't you go put on a turban?
You're already 29, don't cry!
Anyway, why don't we go and have some tasty curry?
Yeah!
Hurray for Gluttons
In India
It's curry with the right hand, toilet with the left
It keeps pouring, the way of curry !
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for gluttons!
In India, its curry with the right hand, toilet with the left.
It keeps pouring, the way of curry!
The curry here is the best!
Welcome.
Tasty!
I can really taste the apple and honey!
Seconds please.
I don't think there's any in this.
Oh, the 29 year old Yuri-chan-sensei is with us, 29 years old.
Oh, Kushieda, you're looking so cute today.
You don't have to repeat it,
it just makes me feel even more depressed.
Seems you would feel down when you're 29.
Your skin gets worse, your butt starts to sag, then you can't even face going outside, and you get more wrinkles.
Shouldn't you find a boyfriend soon?
You think?!
You're right.
I've thought about it a lot. I'm 29 and was beginning to wonder if it's all right to be waiting this late.
Well, it doesn't really matter to us, as we're still in our teens.
You're too blunt.
I can... I can still land a man!
I love it when they're like this!
So what's on the menu today?
Takasu-kun said that we'll eat curry today.
The curry here is delicious, right?
Even Indians get surprised at how good it is.
You... big idiot!
Yeah! Yeah!
You don't understand anything about curry.
Real curry is as deep as the 4,000 years of Chinese history.
Let's have a duel!
I hate spicy food.
Well, I'm going to try both.
Me too!
First you should try some of "Jonny's Super Sweet Imperial Curry" that I've chosen.
Tasty!
It's great to be alive!
Huh, way too sweet for me.
This flavour is for children. I've had enough.
Curry
Curry has been favoured as a lunch option since olden times,
and so, in the 1970's, the way of "Triangle eating" was employed.
Triangle Eating
You would have bread, a side dish, milk,
bread, a side dish, milk, in that order.
People did not mind bread,
but said that rice did not go well with milk,
so the idea did not hold its ground.
In recent years,
Education about eating
being educated about having a good diet has become more important.
The word "Shokuiku" has been around since the Meiji Era.
Meiji Era
In 2005, a law was passed dictating levels for healthy eating.
Due to this, the masses changed to a life concerned with the health of the mind and body.
And is currently pushing towards an abundant lifestyle.
With that came the idea that meals should be balanced.
So a healthy eating lifestyle became possible.
Realisation of a healthy eating lifestyle
The combinations of foods that people would eat...
Stop blabbering! Are you trying to sound like a government official?
That's right, it's important to know how to eat well.
You shouldn't normally take him seriously.
The first match was child's play.
Try my "Jonny's Super Special Spicy Curry"!
The smell is...
It's so spicy my eyes won't open properly.
What's in this that makes it so red?
It's so spicy I might die.
Shouldn't have eaten it!
Is there no mild version?
Curry commercials usually target couples and families,
but recently the number of women getting married late has increased.
However, there's nothing to fear,
this change can be seen all over the world.
Individualism, higher education, and the imbalance in the supply and demand of curry are the main causes of this social instability.
From now on there will definitely be more late marriages.
The point is, if you want to get married then do so, if you don't then don't.
There's no way to deal with those who can't get married.
We are freedom! Freedom is...
Why is she trying to make a stand, is she trying to prove she's great?
This really gets to me. I can really sympathise with her.
You don't have to take her seriously, all right?
Anyway, which curry should we choose?
No, if I give him this one to eat, he'll dump me!
You're not even going out with anyone.
It's just that my heart isn't ready yet.
Piranhas are known for their ferocity,
but it apparently the natives of the Amazon use sharp piranha teeth as hairdressings.
You don't just eat the water buffalo.
Which is why this duel is a draw!
TTL Note: Karee can mean both curry and spicy, hot.
The curry is hot!
That was a joke!
Why don't you take a dip in the sea?
They don't really eat curry in India.
What!?
Are you serious?
Today's Inko
Maguro-maguro-maguro-maguro
Tuna
Japanese chestnut shaped steamed yeast bun.
Curry Manjuu
To be continued