Now then.
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
Shall we set out as well?
Hey, hey, just a minute.
When did you become our comrade, anyway?
Hmph.  What are you asking this late in the game?
I'm obviously making up for your incompetence.
Did you forget already, you trash?
Wretchedly disappear like toilet paper!
What'd you say!?
Listen up you two...
Kanade's out there doing her best for us.
With this opportunity...
We'll need to find every SSS member we can.
What?
What's going on, you guys?
We're thinking we're ready to call it quits.
We understood after hearing your speech.
We made our decision.
That's just the kind of group we are.
Even without hearing it, we kind of already understood.
Our vocalists disappeared already, after all.
There's no replacement for Iwasawa-san and Yui.
But man, her singing was pretty bad.
Every day was as exciting as the Culture Festival.
It was lots of fun.
But, those outside our group might be tough to convince.
I suppose so, huh?
If you're going to do it, do it to completion.
If you don't...
it'll just look like you persuaded us for nothing.
If this Warfront that's continued for so long is to disappear...
I want to think this world, and you too, will have fulfilled its purpose.
And we'll feel like it's started to become a better place.
For us, even for a short time...
the adolescence that we weren't able to experience before...
Being able to feel that we at last had an enjoyable one...
I think that's more than enough.
What are you talking about?
I'm sure I have no idea at all.
Of course not.
Well, we won't know what happens from now on.
We're gonna be on our way, now.
That's all there is to it.
See ya,
new guy.
We'll form a band next time around, too.
Yeah.
I'm sure I'll love it again, too.
See ya.
So you saw off the commoners.
Good work.
Your personality is seriously bankrupt!
My personality isn't bankrupt!
What do you think you're saying to God!?
Quit messing around and let's go.
What's with these numbers?
What's going on?
Where's the NPCs?
At this point, it looks like these guys are all that remain!
What it is we're planning to do...
It looks like they've realized it.
Hmph.  Peasants.
Noda!?
We can always count on you, Noda!
You're gonna fight for us!?
Don't be an idiot!
I only move when I can be of use to Yurippe!
Haha.  Gotcha.
You sure are devoted.
Ooyama?
I know I don't have any redeeming features...
But if I'm able to do well here,
I wonder if even God will be astonished!
Yeah.
Show him what you're made of!
It won't do for you to forget about me.
It seems like nobody would notice if I disappeared at this point!
Now I'll...
WOOHOOOOO!
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, COME OOOON!
Knocking on Heaven's door.
That's Bob Dylan...
But it's very appropriate for this situation.
What's it mean?
Who knows!?
Looks like everyone's starting to gather.
What's with this world?
What's going on here?
More like what's going on with you?
Who the hell are you?
I was training in the mountains for a while, but...
there was hardly anything to eat there.
You're... Matsushita-godan!?
Tastyyyyyy CANDY!
You've lost a lot of weight.
Is your body alright?
Yeah.  In fact, better than ever.
Right now, I feel like I could take on a 100-man Kumite!
That's Karate, isn't it?
Well whatever, it's helping out.
At any rate, these are the troops we've got to work with now.
Let's tear it up and get outta here.
With all of us.
Yeah.
Goodbye Wild Heaven.
Alright!
Let's break through!
The Guild...
Passageway to Guild - B2
It was the perfect place to hide out, but...
Now it's enemy territory.
This is supposed to be our base.
I suppose I should expect them here.
In swarms.
Dammit.  There's no end to them.
Contact Bridge 1
Otonashi-san.  Look down!
They're multiplying faster than ever.
Behind you!
One hundred men.
What?
100 men.
Think of it as though you're now 100 men stronger.
Huh?
You don't understand?
I've got it from here.
Go!
Shiina...
Alright.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Follow me, Hinata!
Right!
Where are we going?  Otonashi-san!
Passageway to Guild - B7
Their numbers increasing must mean...
I'm heading the right way...
I'm running low.
With those numbers...
I'll never make it through with just a handgun.
What do I do?
Yurippe.
Chaa?
The Guild has been apprised of the situation.
Right now all members are making for the surface.
I see.
Take this.
Thank you!
Is the fighting going to end?
Yes.  It's ending.
I see.
In that case we'll be disbanding as well.
We were able to come this far because you all were fighting for us.
Thank you for everything.
If it weren't for you...
We never could have gotten started in the first place.
No...
I've always been nothing more than a lone fool.
Goodbye.
Time to go.
Academy Cafeteria, Inside
Did I go too far?
Old Guild
Time for a short break...
Tenshi...
No... Kanade-chan.  I wonder if she's fighting too.
I wonder what would have happened if I had understood her sooner.
It's possible we would have gotten along well.
We're fellow girls, after all.
Even in this world...
Maybe we could have looked for clothes together and stuff.
But...
In the end, maybe it couldn't have happened.
God...
I can't forgive him.
That's why...
Damn it.
Disappear.
Disappear!
Disappeeear!
UTW Presents:
Therefore... this formula is very important to remember...
Huh?
I feel like I was thinking about something...
What was it?
I'm gonna erase this now.
Alright?
Huh?
What is it, Nakamura?
Can I erase it?
Uh, yes, go ahead.
Awww damn it!
How embarrassing.
Hey, Yuri.
What were you doing in the middle of class?
Nothing, really.
I was just thinking about something.
Thinking about something?
It looked to me like you were just being absent-minded...
Was it love?
You were thinking about love, right?
Stupid.
If I had one I'd like to think about it...
Hmm... I think Fujiwara-kun would be a good match for you, Yuri.
Are you listening, Yuri?
Hey look.
Fujiwara-kun is all alone right now.
Fujiwara-kuuu-
Hey don't do that, ...
Wait... who are you again?
Huh?
I'm Hitomi.
Uh... oh.  Hitomi.
Right.
Is something wrong?
Maybe.
Just like I thought...
You're about to say it's love again, aren't you?
Correct!
Go back to your seat.
'Kay.
And so...
make sure you remember this part well.
Huh?
Nakamura.
Where are you looking?
Hey, Yuri.
Huh?
Alright, Nakamura.
Read the next page from the top.
Hmm?  What's wrong?
This is really quite peaceful, huh?
Umm... what are you talking about?
This is really a peaceful scene.
It's too much for me.
You're all living in the moment.
It must be nice.
I'm truly jealous.
If I disappear from here...
I wonder if I can try it all again.
This happiness that seems so natural...
Can I really accept it?
Nakamura...
Yuri?
Lose my memories...
Change my personality...
In that case I could do it.
But then...
Can you call that making a fresh start?
It's not my life anymore.
It's somebody else's.
I believe we only get one life.
It's right here...
Only one.
This is my life.
I won't hand it over to anyone.
It can't be taken, either.
I can't force it on someone else.
I can't forget it.
I can't erase it.
I can't trample it underfoot.
I can't laugh it away.
I can't pretend it was good.
I can't do anything about it!
It's all just what it is...
Cruel, but irreplaceable.
All we can do is accept our one and only life.
Sensei... do you understand me?
That's why I fight.
That's why I'll continue to fight.
Because...
A life like that...
I could never accept!
Give me your hand!
Yo!
Looks like we made it.
Otonashi-kun and... Hinata-kun?
I'm here too, but...
I made it...
back...
Your voice... no...
Your memories just exploded, and...
Kanade was worried and brought us here.
Kanade-chan?
Yeah.
I see.
It's thanks to you all.
You saved me.
But, you guys, why are you down here?
We left it up to them.
The others, they're carrying on our will for us.
And that's why you came to save me?
We all fought together.
Isn't that the same as always?
I suppose it is.
We can't help but worry about you, Yurippe.
For the time being, do you want to fix your clothes?
Okay, we're moving out!
Y-Yeah...
Man.
She's the same as always.
Passageway to Guild - B20
Hey...
Down there...
Doesn't it seem like they're protecting something?
Why what a coincidence.
I was thinking the same thing.
But... we'd need a carpet bomb to take care of all those...
Well then, I'll be right back.
Huh?
Kanade-chan!
She's crazy.
Is she trying to kill herself?
No, hang on a second...
Yeah!
That girl's combat power is greater than a bomber?
Let's go.
Damn it.
There's even more!
Yuri, you go ahead.
We'll take care of these guys.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Yeah, leave it to us.
Computer Room 2
I'm being mocked.
But... this time, for sure.
How the heck many did he take?
There's no question about it.
Well done making it this far.
Are you trying to mock me?
Making that ostentatious nameplate...
Well this is a school, after all.
You seem to have some interesting values.
No no, that's simply a rule.
Of this world's...
God?
God.
Does he exist or not?
It's quite a profound question.
Very interesting.
However, I'm in no position to determine the answer.
I merely abide by the established rules.
Your actions have been programmed, haven't they?
It's precisely as you've surmised.
Who programmed you?
Even if I give you a name, it won't make a difference.
It's a person from long, long, ago.
Angel Player...
What is that software?
As you already know...
It's a software that can create and alter the materials of this world.
How can it do that?
Who knows?  I'm not the developer, after all.
However, you people create weapons out of earth.
It's probably the same idea.
In the end, we've both been exploiting the same rules.
Was the developer of that software trying to become God?
Who knows?  I have no idea.
Fine.  I don't have much time, so let's move to the main question.
Under what circumstances is your programming activated?
I don't know the contents of the program.
Let me rephrase my question then.
What happened in this world that made you awaken?
In this world...
Love has begun to bloom.
Huh?
Love?
Yes, love.
That isn't supposed to exist in this world.
I see.
That's true.
If we could remember love, we'd all have disappeared right away.
But, if that began to blossom, what would happen to this world?
If love were to blossom here...
This place would become an eternal paradise.
However, this world can't become such a place.
Because this is a place where...
we have to eventually graduate.
There was someone who believed that, huh?
However...
If there was someone who lived their life for the sake of others...
and was sent off to their final reward...
but lost their memory and came here...
That's when bugs can start to appear.
And that's the programmer of Angel Player?
I'm amazed.
You have quite an insight.
That person became aware of the bugs in this world, and began to amend them.
If someone experienced the bug, Kage would turn them into an NPC.
In other words, a reset.
Yes.
Then, what is it?
Among the NPCs, there's others just like us?
Yes.
There is.
Only one.
The poor soul.
It's the programmer.
What?
He's been waiting the whole time.
For a girl he loved, who left this world.
What?
There's no possibility of meeting again.
It's an astronomical number,
but the odds are not zero.
However, the time spent waiting for her was too long
and he was unable to retain his sanity.
That's why he created a program to turn himself into an NPC.
Or maybe he did that first...
And then applied measures to ensure that such a thing would never happen again?
It's a possibility.
Will the day come when that person is fulfilled at last?
Who knows?
It's hard to know what's right here.
I don't know what's right or wrong any longer.
However, you, who have managed to make it this far...
You may be able to discover the answer.
What do you mean?
Depending on your own will, you could be able to change this world.
That's what I mean.
Change it, how?
You can choose the path he was unable to.
You mean... I could become God?
In other words...
Could I turn this world into an eternal paradise?
He rejected that option, but...
I won't.
No...
Perhaps I should say I don't possess the emotion to reject it.
God?
I, this world's God?
Is something wrong?
It's finally in my grasp.
This world.
I've finally...
The reason I fought so long was all for this moment.
I could even beat Tenshi.
With the power of this system...
I'd be the strongest.
I'd never do such a thing.
Even Kanade-chan,
I can't do that to her.
Because I...
The reason I came this far is...
I'm...
Hmm?
I just felt love.
The strongest I've ever felt.
It's magnifying at a terrifying rate.
What is it?
Because...
the reason why I've come this far...
It's so I can protect everybody!
Ahh, so you're the source.
Well, what are you planning to do?
Shut down all the machines.
Immediately.
Are you sure?
Have you thought this through?
You still have plenty of time.
Eternity, in fact.
Let me teach you something.
We humans...
Even for 10 minutes...
We can't even wait that long!
With this...
Is it over?
I'm sure...
Everyone is safe now.
Now they must have safely...
Made it out of this world.
Even so...
What a blunder.
Your sister...
Just as much as you three.
I came to see everyone as just as precious.
Even though I wanted to make you all proud...
By being a sister that would always love only you...
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつもひとりで歩いてた
I've always walked alone
Ah... what is this feeling?
What's happened to me?
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返るとみんなは遠く
When I turned around, everyone was far away
All the things that were driving me...
They're disappearing.
If they disappear...
soredemo atashi wa aruita
それでもあたしは歩いた
Even so, I walked on
I won't be able to stay in this world any more.
Even though life is so unfair.
Even though you were stolen away from me.
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That's what it was to be strong
Even so...
The time I spent with everyone was...
Irreplaceable.
mou nanimo kowaku nai
もう何も恐くない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Now I...
Want to try to catch up with everyone.
sou tsubuyaite miseru
そう呟いてみせる
That's what I try to tell myself
Thank you.
You've done more than enough.
You don't need to be the only one suffering anymore, Onee-chan.
You worked hard for a long time, Onee-chan.
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Eventually, everyone will be alone
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They'll continue to live only through their memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru youni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
So I can love and laugh even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakau n da
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenai n da
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 174] The time we spent together... was truly wonderful.
[c 174] Thank you all so much.
[c 174] Representing the graduating class... I'm Otonashi Yuzuru!