Blades drawn. Now.
It'll happen in the blink of an eye. Be ready.
Go! Move it!
Holy shit!
How the hell are we supposed to
pull evasive maneuvers in here?
It's catchin' up!
Captain! Engage the ODM gear?
Captain!
Where you goin'?
Rear Reinforcements!
Captain! Your orders!
It's dangerous! Let's take it out!
Tell us to engage, sir!
She's gaining on us! Let's just take her out!
That's the whole reason we're here, isn't it?
Right, sir? Captain!
Your orders, sir! Please!
Everyone cover your ears. Now.
Huh?
Was that an acoustic round?
Remind me, what is our mission?
Is it to simply act on impulse in the heat of the moment?
Let me answer that question for you. It's not.
This squad's mission is to keep this brat alive,
whatever the cost.
Don't forget it.
It's not just to police me?
We keep pushing forward, on horseback. Is that clear?
As a bell, sir!
But for how long? We can't keep running forever!
She's right on top of us as it is.
If we don't do something soon...
No!
They keep coming! They're all gonna die
unless we turn around and do something!
Eyes front! Stop lookin' behind us!
Seriously?
Keep pace with the group!
Maintain top speed or we're all dead!
Eld, please! Help them! If the Levi Squad can't
stop this thing, then who can? Those men need us!
Another one!
Damn it, he didn't have to die!
Come on, there's still one left.
We can save him before it's too late!
Do as you're told, Eren! Eyes forward!
How can all of you just ignore
what's happening back there?
Are you tellin' me to abandon my comrades? Is that it?
Damn it, yes!
Stop whining and do as your captain tells you!
Why are we letting people die?
If this is part of some bigger picture,
why can't someone explain it to me?
"Ask not the reason why, ask but to do and die!"
You'd understand what that meant if
you weren't such a useless greenhorn!
Now stifle it. Behave like a soldier!
No.
I can do this without them.
I don't need to rely on anyone else.
I'm a squad all to myself!
No, Eren! Stop!
You're only permitted to assume Titan
form when your life's in extreme peril!
That was the agreement! You swore an oath!
Eren!
I wouldn't blame you.
Do as your conscience dictates.
But Eren, listen. You are not inherently evil.
You're ability to change doesn't make you a monster.
That said, it could be the other way around.
How're you supposed to know where to draw the line?
Whether you lose control or freely give it up.
Maybe it's the same.
And slaughter every Titan that crosses my path!
Look, Eren. We don't agree because our
experience brings us to opposing views. That's life.
At the end of the day, there's no
reason to go against how you see it.
The choice is yours. You can trust yourself.
Or you can trust the people willing
to put their lives on the line for you.
I don't know which way is better. I never have.
Should I act on my own instincts, or put
myself in the hands of my comrades and trust them.
Either way, there's no guarantee.
In the end, you choose what you choose.
If afterwards, your regrets
are at a minimum, good for you.
Eren!
Trust us.
Good news. There may be a way
to stop you without killing you.
Sir?
In your Titan form.
We may have some middle ground after all.
A fail-safe if you will.
The method I've come up with
will only leave you mutilated.
Well, at least in theory. Depends on individual skill.
Essentially, we cut the entire
nape from the body, with you inside.
Your arms and legs'll be severed halfway
down in the process, but you'll survive.
As a matter of fact, they'll probably just
grow back, lizard-style. Creepy little bastard.
Hold on a sec.
I'm not really sure how they do it.
I mean, they might but maybe it's
not worth the risk that they won't.
Oh, I see. You're only up for this
if there's no risk involved whatsoever.
No...
Then be prepared. We're in the same boat.
If you go on a rampage you could kill us. So we're even.
Yes, sir. Seems perfectly fair to me.
Just to be clear, I have the go-ahead, right?
We can't afford not to run tests. So yes, you're good.
Just try to keep him from going
rogue right out of the gate.
Oh, not to worry. I have a plan.
Eren. I know you're still a mystery
to yourself, but we learn as we go.
Knowledge is always worth the risk. I believe that.
You ready down there, my dear?
When we're good to begin, I'll fire off a smoke signal.
What happens after that's entirely up to you.
Ready when you are, Commander!
If the boy loses control, this well
should hold him 'til he wears himself out.
If not, we'll go with Levi's method. Perfect.
Alright.
It's been a while. Since Trost, actually.
I've got to keep a hold of myself.
The Levi Squad's well within their
jurisdiction to kill me if I lose control.
Hmm.
I don't understand it. Perhaps he missed the signal?
Perhaps. Or perhaps we're just naive
to expect he can turn it on and off.
Eren! Enough! We're done for today.
Did something go wrong down there?
I'm sorry. I don't think I can do it now.
You're telling me the bite wounds
on your hands show no sign of healing?
None, sir.
No offense, but you're not much good to us in this form.
If you can't change, our plans
for Wall Maria go up in smoke.
Pull it together. And yes, that is an order.
Yes, sir.
C'mon, don't lose heart, kid. You'll get it.
Maybe, I don't know.
Well, that's one hell of a way to
learn you're more human than suspected.
Look at it this way, it's a lot better to find out
now than in the field. Back to the drawing board, huh?
He's right. No such thing as being too
careful when so much is ridin' on you.
How... How can they all be so damn calm?
Are they actually relieved I can't turn into a Titan?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
What the...?
Titan steam?
What the hell's going on over there?
Dammit why now?
Calm down.
I'm sorry, Captain. I... I don't know how I...!
The situation is complicated. Now, calm down.
Please be what I think it was.
Eren! What the hell do you think you're doing?
Sir, please.
No one gave you permission to transform, did they?
I said calm down...
Answer the question, Eren! What got into you?
Leave it. Explanations can come later.
First thing's first. You need to persuade us
you're not hostile like your life depends on it!
Huh?
Prove it or we kill you!
The burden of proof is yours, kid!
So much as twitch an arm and I'll lob your head off!
This is the first and only warning you'll receive!
I can end you in a heartbeat! Do you understand me, boy?
Oruo! How many times do I have to say it...
Captain! I need you to step away. You're too close!
Right now, I believe you're the
ones who need to step away. Do it.
Why on earth...?
A gut feeling!
Eren better say something!
I don't... Don't try anything cute!
Prove you're not hostile!
Now!
Seriously, I don't...
This is serious! We will kill you!
I'll do it! I swear to god!
Are you with us or not?
Can you not hear me?
That's it! He's dead!
Be quiet! All of you just be quiet!
Eren!
I wanna touch the arm! I wanna touch the arm!
Pretty please with sugar on top!
Let me touch this glorious thing!
I don't think that's such a good... Wait, no!
Argh! Son of a bitch!
That mother is hot when there's no skin!
This is the best day in the history of science!
You're a maniac! You hear me? A maniac!
Are you not burning up? What's it like?
How is it connected to your hand?
Oh you have to show me! I really, really wanna see!
Wait, yeah. I should just be able to pull it out.
Come on!
Are you ignoring me? Don't try anything stupid!
No! What are you doing? That's too soon!
I wanted to put it under the knife!
Sorry, Captain.
So you feelin' okay or what?
Not... exactly... No...
That was quite a wake-up call, let me tell ya.
'Til their blades were drawn,
I had no idea how little they trusted me.
And what did you expect?
A suspicious nature was the top of my criteria.
Traditionally, you're not considered
a real Scout 'til you come back alive.
But out there, there's always so little intel to go on.
So many uncertainties and unknowns
it's a miracle any of us come back alive.
You have to be reactive, quick.
Hit the ground running while anticipating the worst.
That doesn't make them heartless, though.
They're not just a bunch of mindless machines.
Whatever that might've looked like out there today,
I can promise you that every
single one of them was conflicted.
Captain Levi.
Hm?
Section Commander Hange would like a word, sir.
Man. How long of a shit were you taking, anyway?
Oh, long enough to get the job done.
Thank you for asking.
Meeting the brass can do a number on your bowels.
But enough about that.
Feast your eyes on this.
That's the spoon, right?
The very one.
Your spontaneous Titan arm erupted
into being while holding it. Like so.
Resting between the thumb and the index finger.
The world operates on chance,
so coincidences are expected.
But this begs something more.
This utensil wasn't warped by the heat or by the pressure.
Any thoughts on the matter?
Uh... All I know is that I went to pick it up.
When I did the arm came out of nowhere.
Interesting.
This might explain why you couldn't change in the well.
I'm certain of it.
Slaying Titans.
Blocking cannon fire.
Lifting big rocks.
In each instance before assuming Titan form
seemingly at will, there was a distinct goal in mind.
I believe it's possible that self-harm
isn't the only catalyst of transformation.
It appears as though a clear objective
is a crucial ingredient as well.
I think you might be on to something.
This last time was a lot like
the time with the cannon ball.
But I...
I transformed into a Titan just to pick up a damn spoon?
That's insane.
So, uh. What I'm getting out of this is what
you pulled wasn't something you did on purpose?
No, sir.
What the...? What the hell you think you're doing?
Ow.
'Kay, that hurts like a son of a bitch. Damn, kid.
I'm impressed you can sink your
teeth in that deep without shrieking.
We made a judgment call today and it was wrong.
Consider this our way of apologizing.
That is if you can find it in your heart to forgive us.
Huh?
We have to make spur of the moment decisions, okay?
Make the best call we can with what we know.
It's our job to keep you in check!
The fact is we were scared.
That's no excuse, I know.
You've every right to be upset.
But... All that aside,
we're doomed if we can't trust one another.
Just as you are if you can't trust us.
Eren.
I'm asking you.
Trust us!
Eren! C'mon! Make up your damn mind!
I'm with you!
No!
Forgive me!
Target is accelerating!
Just keep moving! We'll outrun the bitch!
Outrun it? Are you kidding me?
We keep riding with our backs to her like this,
we'll be crushed before we know what hit us!
No. We're at death's door.
We've seen our comrades die left and right.
And we're still moving forward.
They trust the captain, and he trusts them.
That's what this is about.
That's why they can all keep moving.
I... I need to be a part of it.
I need to trust them, like they trust me!
Fire!
Everyone hitch your horses a bit further on.
Switch to ODM gear.
I have to break away for a little while.
Eld's in charge 'til I get back.
Tuck Eren somewhere out of
sight, away from the Female Titan.
And see to my horse.
Wait, what?
They're going to take her alive? Seriously?
So what do you think of us now, Eren?
We managed to outsmart the damn thing!
Let this be a lesson to you, greenhorn!
Don't ever underestimate the Scouts!
Never again! Agreed?
Agreed!
She's not putting up much of a fight.
That's no reason to let our guard down.
Good work leading her here.
I'm more than a little impressed.
We couldn't have without the rear contingent
whose lives bought us time. This belongs to them.
I don't intend to ever forget that.
That so?
Yes.
Because of their sacrifices,
we can expose whoever this really is.
Ten to one they're in there
pissing themselves right about now.
Erwin Smith's top-secret plan to
capture the Female Titan has succeeded.
But as the Scout Regiment
attempts to reveal her true identity,
they find a nasty shock waiting for them.