“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Where did Masaomi go?
He went home a little while ago.
There was something he had to do.
If we leave them alone, those ashes will smoulder, and smoulder...
We're already through... Finished.
You did what you thought was right.
Is this from the leader of the Dollars?
If it turns out the Dollars are backing them up,
then we'll crush the Dollars as well!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Over here!
That way!
You guys go that way. Block off the entrance!
Why...?
Why is Kida-kun...?
A girl runs
to get away from the shadows that pursue her.
She only wanted to know...
the truth.
Come on, this is pointless.
Where'd she go?
She's not getting away from us.
Why is Kida-kun...
She felt nothing.
Why?
Only the shock of what she had just seen echoed in her mind.
The Dead Blue Sky
How nice! You recovered a lot faster than we thought.
Thank you very much.
I enjoyed your hospitality.
Here.
Thanks!
Since that night, the slasher incidents had come to a sudden halt,
and the town had regained its serenity.
Even for Sonohara Anri,
life would go back to being uneventful and normal.
Sonohara-san!
Good! I made it!
We're falling behind in student council affairs.
Ryugamine-kun.
I heard you're coming back to school starting tomorrow.
Are you really okay?
Yes. I'm fine now.
I'll carry your bags.
No, it's okay.
Let him carry them!
Mikado-kun only came running because he wants to hold them.
Anri, since this morning, how many times do you think he's said,
"Sonohara-san leaves the hospital today!"
"I wonder if she's well enough for school?"
"Anri-san is so erotic and cute!"
I never said that last one!
Ryugamine-kun and Kida-kun,
thanks to both of you for coming to see me so often.
It's... nothing.
Speaking of which, Masaomi, didn't you just come from the hospital?
Yeah. I must've just passed her inside.
That's right. Sonohara-san, if you want the notes from when you were gone,
you can borrow mine.
My writing is sloppy, so it might be hard to read,
but if you don't mind that, go ahead and use them.
Wait a second. I know they're in here.
There's something different about Kida-kun.
The girl sensed something uneasy about the boy.
She had known when he came to visit her at the hospital.
Okay, this should be fine.
Kida-kun?
Anri...
How did you...
It's nothing, really. I just met the slasher...
But it's really nothing, I promise.
Sorry, guys. Got some minor business.
I'll let Prince Mikado have the honor of taking the Princess to her castle.
Don't think you'll get another chance like this in a hundred years.
Well, later!
See you tomorrow!
And with that, a peculiar insecurity befell her.
Don't let them do anything until I get there.
Got it?
The Kokinzoku have grown in numbers lately, haven't they?
Yeah, they have.
From what I can see, they stand out more than the Dollars do.
Well, they've been around a long time.
It feels like they've changed somehow.
Like they've changed?
It's hard to explain.
They're not the same as the old Kokinzoku...
I mean,
it feels like they're more violent than they used to be.
Saika-san, good evening.
Good evening!
Welcome!
Good evening.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
She wasn't used to the Internet at first,
so she downloaded a virus and started spamming, right?
There's nothing that could have been done.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You say sorry too much.
By the way, Saika-san,
do you know about a color gang called Kokinzoku?
Is it those people around town wearing the yellow rags?
Yes, yes, that's them.
There's another gang a lot like them called the Dollars.
Thanks to the last few slasher incidents, those two organizations
are in a lot of trouble.
What do you mean?
Cut it out, Kanra-san.
There's no use telling someone who doesn't know about them.
No, no.
If she lives in Ikebukuro, she has to know!
They haven't caught the criminal behind all the slasher incidents, have they?
And both the Dollars and Kokinzoku have had casualties from them.
It seems both gangs think that the other is responsible.
I don't think the Dollars are all that worried about it, though.
I just think that they have some misunderstandings since they don't know each other very well.
Anyway, if the perpetrator never gets caught by either gang,
then at this rate, blood will be raining on Ikebukuro.
How scary!
That's what you call a fight!
It's nothing for you to worry about, Anri-chan.
They're all being violent for no reason.
There's no reason for you, who isn't even the real criminal, to turn yourself in.
Don't be hasty.
Because, right now, the police are really intimidating...
Really intimidating,
and really scary!
Especially traffic cops!
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
That's right.
Remind me to teach you about private messaging later.
I'm sorry. I have to go now.
Okay.
Saika-san, thanks for coming.
G'night.
Bye.
Well, I'd better get going too.
Later then.
Good talking to you guys.
Kanra-san,
About the slasher incident...
If I find anything, I'll tell you.
For a nominal fee.
The real culprit is somewhere in this town.
I think we can avoid the misunderstandings between the Kokinzoku and Dollars if we catch him.
Do you really think it's that easy?
Neither the Kokinzoku nor the Dollars are really that stable.
There are those who act alone and extort others for money under the pretense of fighting.
If things keep going like they are,
it'll end up as a real fight.
I won't let it.
You won't?
I'm not so sure that you can stop it anymore.
There's certainly no way you can stop the Kokinzoku.
Even so, I won't let it happen.
That I'd like to see.
She had to do something.
This girl, who kept a demon sword within her body, thought...
This girl, who had come to see the world through a frame, thought.
However...
The boy who had entered her world through the frame,
had already been seized...
by a heavy burden also known as his past.
He could no longer run away.
Hello?
Right. Got it.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry! My friend says he has an emergency.
Really?
If you're going to get mad, get as mad as you like at my friend.
It won't cost you anything to get mad, and it won't hurt me.
You'd be killing two birds with one stone, giving one man two wives!
One man, two wives?
Well, I'll see you tomorrow!
Is it really that urgent?
Don't you think Kida-kun has been acting strange lately?
Really? Maybe it's just you.
I'm sorry.
There's something I have to do.
See you.
I hear a couple of the Dollars got mugged by the Kokinzoku last night.
Yeah, one of them was on the verge of death.
But the Kokinzoku think that the slasher is really one of the Dollars.
It couldn't stay that way.
The boy who lead the Dollars knew that.
However, he still didn't know that even he was just a piece on a chess board.
Customer, you eat sushi!
Sushi is the heart of Japan, yes? Enka, yes?
I wonder if they really do a Cossack dance for you if you have them deliver?
Enka makes you think of mountain tea.
Still, those kids from last night were with Simon while he was making a delivery.
If you swing this stick, you'll become sushi toppings, yes?
Human sushi. That hurts. That's not good.
I don't think they were with him for very long.
Man. I don't like where this is going.
Is there someone who knows about the Dollars and the Kokinzoku?
Anyone?
Our boss is Kida Masaomi.
I've seen him with you, Mother.
He said he was becoming enemies with one of your close friends, Mother.
How can that...
Of course, she couldn't believe it.
However, the children were incapable of lying to their mother.
Where's Kida-kun?
He's coming to a meeting today.
Take me to that meeting.
And so...
She learned everything.
Kida-kun is...
Maybe she's in here.
She had to escape.
I love everybody.
Why is... Kida-kun...
I will cut open these yellow children, and love them as well.
What would happen if she were caught?
I will love them for you, you who cannot love.
I don't want to hurt anybody!
The boy would find out that she's a monster.
She trembled in fear of that.
It's too narrow. I can't fit.
I'll go.
Kida-kun?
Help me.
Somebody help me!
Hey, look.
Standing in the rain was a Dullahan woman.
All this cornered girl could do was ask someone who, much like herself,
supposedly didn't exist in the world, for help.
She came in over the fence!
She can do that.
Here she comes.
Are you serious?
Celty-san!
We can talk later.
Let's go. Get on the back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hang on tight.
I've been watching you for some time now.
I've always thought that rider suit of yours looks too slim for a man.
I don't care about men,
but if you're a woman, that suit's enough to make me fall in love with you!
If you love a nun, you gotta love her habit too.
This is the guy who's always with Mikado...
I see. She doesn't want him to see her face.
I'm not sure why, but I understand.
What in the...?
You monster!
Stop!
She looked just like a legendary headless knight.
In the blink of an eye,
all the fragments of information came together for them.
An invader who wielded a blade like the slasher's.
The black rider who came to save her.
And the rumor that the biker is with the Dollars.
They all arrived at the same conclusion.
The slasher is with Dollars.
The boy wasn't sure if he came to the right conclusion.
All he knew was that no matter what he thought,
he could no longer sway his comrades after what they had witnessed.
Hey, do you know about Dullahan?
No, I don't.
I hear they show up at the houses of people who are about to die,
as headless knights who ride headless horses.
I guess they're like the grim reaper.
The boy had a sudden thought.
One of them might die.
Why do I want to see Saki so much at times like this?
"The blue sky has died."
The sky is dead.
That is the slogan from the Three Kingdoms
that the Kokinzoku took as their own when they were first formed.
It really isn't blue.
Well, it isn't yellow either, though.
Good evening!
Oh, is it just you, Taro-san?
Good evening.
That's how it looks.
Private messaging now, are we?
There's something I want to ask you.
Have the Kokinzoku always been in Ikebukuro?
Only the last three years or so.
At first they were a lot more mature, though.
Thus, the boy who lead the Dollars,
learned of the horrible battle between the Kokinzoku and the Blue Squares.
Unaware that the girl who was sacrificed was his best friend's lover...
Unaware that the man who told him about it controlled that girl's heart,
and has wounded his friend beyond recovery.
So long story short, all that's left is the Kokinzoku, and–
But the Blue Squares aren't quite dead.
What do you mean?
The Kokinzoku's leader got sick of fighting.
And after he left,
they all joined the Kokinzoku.
You mean they merged together?
Simply put, yes.
Of course, nobody would care about who had been in which gang, besides those that were in charge.
They took off their blue clothes, and said:
"We want to join the Kokinzoku."
After that,
everything was okay.
But the leader who left them...
Probably has no idea.
That the men who put his lover in the hospital
are mixed among his allies now.
You should be careful too.
It looks like there are some people who claim to be both Dollars and Kokinzoku.
That's why I think we should tell all the Dollars that we have nothing to do with this,
so those people can tell the Kokinzoku.
As long as it's really not the Dollars.
The Dollars have no rules, and it's not like you can control the actions of all your members.
Somewhere, without you knowing,
some part of the Dollars
could be acting as the slasher.
In other words, that's the Dollars' system.
At this rate, if you plan to come to this side,
you should be prepared for that.
I'll keep that in mind.
Good morning.
Good morning!
What's wrong? You don't look too happy.
Are you feeling okay?
That's not it.
Morning.
Good morning.
I just ran into Kida by the train station.
He said he's skipping today.
Why?
Dunno. He didn't say.
Really?
See you.
Thanks.
You can't run away from your past, Masaomi.
Even the things you're worried about now are still related to the past, aren't they?
Since you can't run away from it,
you should fight and take it down.
If I could settle your past by fighting you too,
I'd want to.
Why can't you?
There's no way I can fight you, Saki.
He just wanted a place where he could belong.
Each time he told his friend about the new town,
he had doubts about the persona he'd borrowed from the town.
Now he understood...
that the only place he's ever called home within what was once the Kokinzoku,
now lay with the person named Mikajima Saki.
He was acting for the sake of a close friend who had become his new home.
Man. It's started raining again.
Kadota-san.
You've come back?
Yeah.
Because this is where I say goodbye.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time:
Durarara!!
Rise of the Yellow Sky
A great person once said, "The world is fictional."
Someone great once said, "The world is a symbol."
A terrible past is the product of delusion.
That reality never existed, but isn't that all right?
Next time: Rise of the Yellow Sky