Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono ude de
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne to
So happy for them
Staff Building
Principal's Office
Why's the new song a ballad?
No good?
Not for a diversion...
Excuse me... what do you mean by diversion?
Weren't you listening during Operation Tornado?
She gets her band together inside the school,
and they get the attention of all the regular students.
We don't put them directly in harm's way,
but we use them occasionally, and when they're in the way we need to remove them from the scene.
That's when we use the girls as a diversion.
They're pretty trendy for NPCs...
At any rate, that's the merit and appeal of her band.
Huh?
So?  It's still no good?
A ballad won't quite do.
If we hear something so solemn, we'd barely be able to fight.
I see.
Well I guess that's out.
Okay, let's regroup and I'll start the briefing.
Otonashi-kun.
Hm?
Close the curtains.
The next operation will be, "Operation Revenge for the Tenshi-area Infiltration Plan".
The mission will commence in 3 days.
It's that operation, is it?
But last time was-
This time he'll be accompanying us.
Nice to meet you.
From behind the chair?!
An egghead.
Yurippe, what kind of joke is this?
How are we gonna use a weakling like that?
Now now, don't say that.
In that case...
Let's test him!
You don't really have friends, do you?
3.1415926535897932384626433832795028841971693993751058209749445923078164062862089986280348253421170679821480865132823066470938446095
Stop that!
No way!  He's reciting Pi?!
What an egghead.
Please stop him!
Noda's a moron!
That's right.  Our weakness is that we're all stupid.
That's true, but don't say it...
The last time we tried this operation, the deficiency of our intellect was exposed.
HOWEVER!
This time we have a boy who aspires to the name of "Hacker Genius"!
Handle name: Takeyama-kun.  He's now part of the planning team.
He'll conduct a thorough investigation of the area.
That's not his real name?
Please...
... call me Christ.
Look at that.  He ruined his own cool handle name.
Yurippe sure knows how to pick 'em.
And, what's "Tenshi-area"?
Tenshi's residence.
Tenshi's residence?
W-What kind of place could she live in?
Wait a sec... do we really need a hacker for a place like that?
The core is controlled by a computer.
It's mechanized?
And it surely contain a means of contacting God.
This plan sounds huge!
But it's our second attempt.
Tenshi will be more alert than the last time.
We'll need GirlDeMo to be especially showy for us.
Roger.
Good chance and luck!
Below Connecting Bridge
Alright.  Doing good.
Wait, aren't I getting a little too into this?
Ah, well.  Those guys aren't as bad as I first thought.
Student Building B - Bulletin Board
So this is part of that showy distraction, huh?
Ah, sorry.  Did I startle you?
Oh, it's you.
Huh?  You know me?
Yeah!
That senpai who's always carrying a big axe around
says you bring disaster, and that I should be careful or something around you.
That idiot, huh?
But wait, using the gym?  Is that really okay?
It's totally dangerous!  It's totally unprecedented!
And it's not their usual guerilla concert.  It's scheduled, and everything.
The teachers probably won't let this go unpunished, so we don't know what obstacles we'll face.
But, I heard this operation needs a lot of people to gather together.
Girls Dead Monster, huh?
By the way, um...
It's Yui!
I'm still just an underling in the diversionary squad...
But, I'm still happy with that!
After all, I'm helping out the great GirlDeMo.
Do you know about them?
Girls Dead Monster are amazing!  Shortened to "GirlDeMo".
They're all girls, and they're incredible performers.
And no matter how you slice it, Iwasawa-san on vocals and guitar is stunning!
She even writes the music and lyrics.
My favorite is "Crow Song".
The climax of that song is just so passionate.  I love it.
And the lyrics, too!  They're surely about Iwasawa-san.
And another thing that's great, too...
Alchemy!  Alchemy!
Hey, I'm not done yet!
Alchemy is...
Do I look like I need to hear all this?!
Go get back to work for your precious GirlDeMo!
Oh!  That's right!
Alright, see ya!
Hm?
Student Building A - Unused Classroom
Oops.
Sorry.  I'll fix it up quick.
Alright, let's take a break.
You guys were really fired up.
It's no wonder the students are so wild about you guys.
Before I even realized it, I stopped to listen.
Thank you.
You... don't have memories, right?
More or less...
You must be happy.
Are your memories... like...
Did you hear about someone's memories?
Yeah... Yuri's.
Yuri's, huh?
That was just horrible.
Mine aren't nearly as bad.
Not as bad?
I'm saying it wasn't anything big.
I couldn't sing what I wanted to...
That's all it was.
My parents, they were always fighting.
I didn't have my own room to hide in.
In the midst of all the shouting, I'd curl up in a corner, and cover my ears.
All I could do was retreat into my own shell.
There was nowhere else I could rest.
During a time like that, I discovered a band called "Sad Machine".
I heard that the singer had been raised in an unloving family like mine.
When things got rough, he would cover his ears with headphones, and escape to the world of music.
I tried the same thing.
It was like everything just flew away.
The vocals were shouting out in the way I couldn't.  Singing for me.
All the common-sense people were wrong.
It was those who cried out that were right.
It was the lonely ones like us who were truly human.
The music shouted back and fought against the injustice of the world for me.
The music... saved me.
When I first found this guitar, it had been thrown out in the rain.
I began to sing for the first time.
In a life I thought was so empty, I had music.
Are you sure?  With your grades, you could go anywhere...
No.
I don't want to rely on my parents.
I worked different jobs to save up money,
and auditioned at countless record studios.
I thought for sure that when I graduated, I'd get out of that house, leave it behind, and...
... live for music.
That's what I believed.
Huh?
I must be tired...
If this keeps up, I won't be able to play the guitar...
I'd better take tonight off and... rest.
The next time I opened my eyes...
I could no longer speak.
Cerebral contusion.  An aphasia from a stroke.
The cause was a chance blow from one of my parent's fights.
I cursed my fate.
There was nowhere I could run.
And just like that, my life ended.
Iwasawa?
Ah, Hisako.  Okay!
We were getting sick of waiting.
No memories!
Take it.
That story just now...
That's why she's rebelling against the unfairness of life.
She had a sad life, too.
Nobody's afraid of becoming a water flea.
Everybody here... everyone...
They're choosing to fight against God.
They're fighting against...
... accepting their cruel lives.
UTW Presents:
Come on, President.  You can overlook something like this!
That's right!  GirlDeMo concerts are all we have to look forward to.
Don't take that from us!
That's right!  Yeah?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
It's like I'm the bad guy...
Gymnasium
Understood?
We're going in with the smallest number of people this time.
We strike tonight at 1900.
Operation start!
Too few people.
You get a front row seat.
It's time.
Alright.
Let's rock it out!
Clear!
Alright.  Infiltration successful.
Huh?
We've infiltrated Tenshi-area.
Close the door already!
Takeyama-kun, you take care of the computer.
Please, call me Christ.
Wait... uh...
Isn't this just a normal girl's room?!
This is criminal activity!
What are you doing?!
Girls Dorm
This is the girl's dorm!  Kill those lights!
And what do you mean controlled by a computer?!
It's just one little PC!
Password?
Last time nobody could figure it out.
I see.
It's time for me to show my power.
Analyzing now.
Huh... looks like we can use him for something.
Come on, haven't you heard of privacy-
Oi, wait up!
You're too loud.
If you keep this up, I'll slit your throat.
What the hell?!
I was just starting to change my opinion of you guys, too!
Why?
Why won't more people come?
Alchemy?  Already?
Yeeaah!
Mugen ni ikitai
I want to live forever
Mugen ni ikiraretara
If I could live forever
Subete kanau
All my wishes could come true
Demo ironna mono ga
But all sorts of things
Atashi wo oikondeku
Are driving me into a corner
Alchemy!
With the time I have left to live
Ikiru nokori jikan
Yume no zahyou wo kurue
All my dreams are being scattered
Zenbu daiji na mono na no ni
Even though it's all so important to me
Iza kokora de chotto
Now, let's go somewhere here
Amaimono tabete yukou
And eat sweet things
Souiu shikou teishi akari to tooi ni natta
I've stopped such thoughts, and they went far away with the light
Hey!  What do you think you're all doing?!
Behave, and go back to your dorms!
No way!  We've got to see this!
That's right!  You're the ones who should go!
Yeah!
She's here.
Everyone, give us more!
No.  Nobody can do that for us.
It's something only WE can do!
Tenshi has appeared.
Roger.
Takeyama-kun?
Right now, I'm running a high-speed password cracking program.
It'll be done soon.
Also, please call me Christ.
We're in!
Well done, Takeyama-kun!
Alright, copy all the data!
That'll take too much time.
At least an hour.
Also, please call me Christ-
Should we take out the hard drive?
We'll be discovered!
What to do?
At any rate, at least show us anything suspicious, Takeyama-kun!
Call me Christ!
A list of students?
The NPCs?  No, we're in here too.
It's just a regular student registry!
There's nothing suspicious about that.
This is nothing but criminal activi-
Shut it!
The Diversionary Squad has been suppressed.
Tenshi is returning.
This is as far as we go, huh?
And we didn't get anything this time, either.
We're dispersing.
Damn it!  You gotta be kidding!
Stop it, please!
They're doing it for us!  Let them go!
Their music is what keeps us going!  Please!
We're just being lenient up until now.  Don't push our patience!
We're seizing all the instruments.
This isn't a damn school festival.
You won't be doing this again.
You won't mind if I toss this out, right?
Don't touch that.
Huh?
I said...
I SAID, DON'T TOUCH THAT!
Stop her-
Stop!
Hand it over.
Joushiki butteru yatsu ga waratteru
The masters of common sense are laughing
Tsugi wa donna uso wo tsuku
What lie will they tell next?
Sore de erareta mono
Do they dress up the things
Daiji ni kazatteokeru no
That they have thus obtained?
A new song?
Hito wa soredemo susumanakya naranai
But no matter what, humans have to move on forward
Dakara kou utau yo
That's why I'm singing like this
Takeyama-kun!
Got it!
But call me Christ!
Naiteru kimi koso
You must be crying now
Kodoku na kimi koso
You must be lonely now
Tadashii yo
That's what's right
Ningen rashii yo
That's what being human is
Otoshita namida ga
The tears that have fallen
Kou iu yo
Sound like this
Konna ni mo utsukushii
They're so beautiful
Uso janai hontou no
It's not a lie, it's true
Bokura wo arigatou
For us, we thank you
This is my life.
Continuing to sing like this...
Thats... the reason I was born.
Just as I was saved...
I'll be able to save someone else.
I finally...
Finally...
Found it.
Iwasawa?
So what have we learned, Yurippe?
Tenshi developed her powers on her own.
It's the same as how we make our own weapons.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure...
I can't say yet.
Why not?  You're being secretive, Yurippe.
If she needs to use the same methods as we do,
then the only thing we can infer is the worst case scenario.
God doesn't exist anywhere.
Why doesn't Tenshi get her powers from God?
Why does she need to develop them herself?
Well, then.  There's another matter of concern.
Where did Iwasawa-san disappear to?
Didn't Tenshi erase her?
In the middle of a concert?!
Then, what happened?
Just who would do that to Iwasawa-san?
Nobody.
She consented to it.
That's all there is to it.
In order to disappear, one does as Tenshi instructs, and leads a normal student life.
But it can't be that simple.
Itsumo hitori de aruiteta
I've always walked alone
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turned around, everyone was far away
Soredemo atashi wa aruita
Even so, I walked on
Sore ga tsuyosa datta
That's what it was to be strong
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetting/Editor: Nikon
Timer: Tranquility
TLC/QC: Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 136] Play ball!
[c 59] I'm gonna learn to fight!
[c 57] It's baseball.
[c 118] Don't stop dancing!
[c 78] It's a challenge, boy...
[c 5] I heard he's Iwasawa's replacement...?
[c 40] We'll make the strongest team ever.
[c 117] It's a complete mystery what I was doing when I died!
[c 68] Yui, nyan.
[c 159] Just who are we fighting...?
[c 28] Fired, huh?
[c 183] Your team isn't registered to participate.
[c 33] A game with penalties scarier than death
[c 244] ...You scared?
[c 290] This... feels so damn good.