Yeah.
Okay! Try introducing yourself to everyone!
Umm... I-I'm Akemi Homura...
I, uh... Ni-Nice to meet all of you.
Akemi Homura
Akemi-san was in the hospital for a long time due to problems with her heart.
She hasn't been to school in a while, so I'm sure there will be times where she'll be a bit confused.
Everyone, make sure you help her out.
Akemi-san, where did you go to school before?
Were you in any clubs?
Did you play any sports? How about art?
Your hair's really long. It must take a lot of time braiding it every morning.
I, uh...
Akemi-san, you need to go to the nurse's office, right?
Do you know where it is?
Huh?
No...
I'll take you there, then.
I'm the health officer for this class.
Sorry everyone,
Akemi-san has to take medicine at the nurse's office during her breaks.
Oh, really? Sorry for keeping you.
Talk to you later, Akemi-san.
Sorry about that.
They're not trying to be mean.
It's just rare to have a transfer student, so they're all excited over it.
No, it's okay...
Thank you.
No need to be that nervous.
We're classmates.
My name is Kaname Madoka.
Call me Madoka.
I...
It's fine.
Could I call you Homura-chan?
I... haven't been called by my first name very much.
It's a really weird name.
What? That's not true.
It feels really exciting and cool.
I'm nothing like my name then.
You shouldn't say that!
You have such a wonderful name, so you should just be cooler to match it!
f(x) is defined by... Calculate:
Given that p is a prime number, and n an arbitrary natural number, prove that (1+p)^p - n^p -1 is divisible by p.
How about you try this problem?
Oh yeah, you were away from school, weren't you?
Make sure you borrow notes from a friend.
She got light-headed during warmup exercises? That's pretty bad.
Well, she couldn't do much but sleep for half a year. She can't help it.
Homura-chan, you should just be cooler to match it!
I can't do that. I can't do anything myself.
I just cause trouble for everyone else and embarrass myself.
Why...
Will I always be like this?
Then it'd be better if you just died, huh?
Maybe it would.
Yeah, you should just die.
Just... die...
Wh-Where... am I?
What?
What is that?!
No!
That was close.
It's okay now, Homura-chan!
Yo-You're...
They're magical girls.
They hunt witches.
Who knew someone would find out about our secret so quickly?
Don't tell our class, okay?
Tomoe
Mami
Kaname-san, do you always fight those things?
Always? Well, Mami-san's the veteran here.  I only contracted with Kyubey just last week.
But the way you fought today was much better than before, Kaname-san.
You're fine? You're not scared?
Well, we're not fine, and we do get scared, but when we take out a witch, we save a lot of people.
It's worth it, don't you think?
Kaname-san needs to become a magical girl in her own right before the Walpurgis Night comes.
I'll be going, then.
You can't...
Tomoe-san died.
That's why I'm going.
I'm the only one left who can stop the Walpurgis Night.
You can't win against that alone! It's hopeless!
You'll die too, Kaname-san!
I'm still a magical girl.
I have to protect everyone.
Please... let's run away.
We don't have any other choice. No one would hate you for it.
Homura-chan, I'm glad I could be friends with you.
I made it there just in time when you were attacked by that witch... I'm still proud of that.
So I'm glad I became a magical girl. I really am.
Kaname-san...
Good bye, Homura-chan.
Be well.
No! Don't go, Kaname-san!
Why...
You knew you were going to die.
I wanted you to live...
instead of saving me...
Is what you're saying true, Akemi Homura?
Would you be willing to trade your soul for that wish?
If you have a desire so strong you would be willing to accept a fate of combat, I'll help you.
If I contract with you, will any wish I have really be granted?
That's correct.
It seems that you qualify.
Now tell me, with what wish will you make your Soul Gem shine?
I...
I want to relive meeting Kaname-san for the first time again—
not as someone she protects, but as someone who can protect her instead!
The contract is complete.
Your desire has overcome entropy.
Now release your new power!
Where am I...
I still haven't been released from the hospital...
Mitakihara Junior
High School
Entrance Guide
It wasn't a dream!
Okay! Try introducing yourself to everyone!
Akemi Homura, nice to meet you all.
Akemi-san was in the hospital for a long time due to her heart—
Kaname-san, I became a magical girl too!
Let's work hard together!
Uh...
Here I go!
What do you think, Mami-san?
Stopping time, huh?
It's pretty amazing, but the question is how to use it.
Mami-san, right now!
Okay!
Akemi-san, your turn!
Ri-Right!
We did it...?
We did it?
We did it!
Good work.
That was amazing!
That was amazing, Homura-chan!
What's wrong?
Hey, Kaname-san! Hang on!
Why...
What?
Why did this happen?
I have to tell them. Everyone's being tricked by Kyubey!
Uh, so why exactly would Kyubey lie about something like that?
That's because...
Are you trying to turn us against each other by telling us something weird?
Wait, you're not working together with that Kyouko girl, are you?
N-No!
Sayaka-chan, we're starting to fight with each other.
Either way, I'm against teaming up with her.
Mami-san and Madoka-san use projectile weapons, so it's okay,
but having explosions appear in front of you out of nowhere is a little much...
Who knows how many times we were almost hit by them?
Akemi-san, do you have any other weapons besides explosives?
Shafuto
Industries
I'll think of something.
What the hell are you?
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Sayaka-chan, stop it!
Please remember!
This isn't something you'd want to do!
I'm sorry, Miki-san.
Sayaka, damn it...
This is...
This is terrible.
It's too much.
Tomoe-san?!
If the Soul Gems give birth to witches, then we all have to die!
Both you and I!
Stop it!
I've had enough.
I've had enough of this...
It's okay.
Let's work together.
Let's work together to take out the Walpurgis Night.
Yeah.
It looks like it's over for both of us.
Do you have any Grief Seeds?
I see.
Do you just want to become monsters and destroy everything in the world?
We'll destroy everything, and we'll keep destroying it until it looks like all the bad things—all the sad things—never even happened at all.
Don't you think that sounds nice?
I lied just then.
I had one saved.
You can't...
Why did you give it to me?
Because I wanted to ask you to do something I can't.
You've said you can go back to the past, right, Homura-chan?
You've said you can change history so this all won't have happened, right?
Yeah.
Could you save my stupid self before I get tricked by Kyubey?
I promise.
I'll definitely save you.
No matter how many times I have to repeat all of this, I'll protect you!
I'm glad...
Could I ask you for one more thing?
Yeah.
I don't want to become a witch.
A lot of horrible and sad things have happened,
but there are so many things I had in this world that I wanted to protect.
Madoka!
Homura-chan, you finally called me by my name...
I'm happy...
No one will believe the future.
No one will be able to accept the future.
Then I'll have to...
Wh-Who's there?
Madoka, if someone appears promising you a miracle, you mustn't do as he says.
What...
I won't depend on anyone anymore.
There's no need for anyone to understand anymore.
I won't let Madoka fight anymore.
I'll take care of all the witches by myself.
And this time, I'll stop the Walpurgis Night myself.
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
How awful!
It can't be helped.
Now that you've drunk every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
It was too much for her to handle alone.
This is too awful! It shouldn't be happening!
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
Madoka, don't listen to what he's saying!
If you give up, it'll be the end of everything.
I want to see you, smiling with the power to shatter even darkness,
But you have the capacity to change fate.
This unavoidable destruction, this sorrow—you can change it all. You have the power to do that.
like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was young.
Are you telling the truth?
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
Don't be tricked! That's what he wants!
Can someone like me really do something to stop this?
that now lays in my frightened hands.
Can I really prevent everything from turning out this way?
Of course you can! Form a contract with me and become a magical girl!
This wish will awaken that light.
No!
Transformed Madoka was really amazing.
I had predicted she'd become the strongest magical girl,
but I never would have imagined she'd destroy that Walpurgis Night in one hit.
You did that knowing what would probably happen?
Sooner or later, the same thing would have happened, either way.
She defeated the greatest enemy as the strongest magical girl.
Of course she'd have to become the worst witch after that was over.
Madoka, in this form, will probably destroy this planet within ten days or so.
Well, the rest is your problem—humanity's problem.
We've pretty much hit the quota of energy we've needed to collect.
Aren't you going to fight?
No, my battlefield is not here.
Akemi Homura, are you...
I'll repeat it. I'll continue to repeat it over and over.
Visiting the same time again and again, searching for the single exit out.
Searching for the path to save you from a fate of despair.
Madoka... my one and only friend.
Homura-chan?
If it's... If it's for you,
I have no problem being trapped eternally in this maze.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 10     I won't rely on anyone any longer
Illustrator     Mura Kuroe
Did you not feel anything watching over them all that time?
Did you not try to understand how much pain everyone was in?
Episode 11        The final sign left
The final sign left.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: guymam
limitbreakingcat
Timer: kozu
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
goof