Kurumi     Yuki      Rii
School Living Club
#8
Future
Not in this room, either...
Staff 2S
What does this key go to?
Wait up!
Dirty
Looks like this is as far as you go, Taroumaru-kun.
Give it up! Er...
Huh?
Splat
You two, no running in...
Rumble
the halls.
You're open!
I finally caught you.
You're both filthy. What happened?
Well, Taroumaru slipped out
of his collar at some point,
and I found him swimming
in the pond up on the roof.
Pond? Oh, the water tank.
In that algae-filled water?
So I was going to give him a bath...
And then you started chasing him again,
and that's how this happened.
Yeah...
I'm sorry.
What's done is done.
I'll take care of the hall.
You give Taroumaru a bath.
Okay!
Jeez, Taroumaru, it's your
fault the hall's such a mess.
Yuki-chan...
Oops! I'm still in my rain boots!
How's the water?
Now hold still, and it'll be over in no time.
Hey! Come on, we're almost done!
Wow, you're soaking wet.
Oh, Kurumi-chan.
Want me to help?
Yeah, thanks.
N-Never mind. This is my job.
Oh, okay.
Do you realize I just saved you
from some serious trouble?
You ingrate!
Don't jump on my face again!
Uh, Kurumi-chan?
Sorry. I could use your help, after all.
Okay. You can count on me.
Uh, leave the shovel out there, though.
Aww...
Okay, what should I do?
Can you hold him down?
Okay.
There.
Now, time for round two.
Staff
Whoa, Mii-kun, hang on...
Please hold still. It'll be over much quicker.
Y-Yeah, maybe, but...
Mii-kun, be more gentle.
If we don't dry you thoroughly,
you'll catch a cold.
Just use the blow dryer.
Taroumaru's using it.
Huh?
No, Taroumaru.
No messing with Yuki's hat.
Thanks, Kurumi-chan.
If you eat something this dirty, you'll get sick.
Kurumi-chan?
I just washed it. It's not dirty.
Anyway, it's a good thing
the clothes dried so quickly.
Yeah.
The sun is blazing today.
Sure is making it hot, though.
You think so?
What is it, Mii-kun?
You're too careless, Senpai.
Huh?
Stop sitting around half-naked
and put your clothes back on.
Okay. Thanks.
Let's all graduate together!!
You can't keep acting like this, Senpai.
Graduation Album
Write 100 pages each
I can't write that many
You all graduate next year, remember?
It's okay. Tomorrow is another day!
Senpai...
Don't put off until tomorrow
what you can do today!
This school is equipped
with so many resources.
You have to take advantage
of them while you can.
For your own future.
There's so much you can do before graduation,
and so much preparation to do.
Let's keep it together.
That's true.
There's a lot we could be doing to
prepare. We need to study, too.
Hmm...
I guess I'll talk to Megu-nee about it.
Are you going to attend college, Senpai?
Lately, I've been thinking I'd
be better off getting a job.
That way I won't have to take exams, right?
There are job placement exams.
Huh?
I hear job hunting is pretty tough.
Huh?!
Maybe I'll just stay in high school forever...
So you're just a quitter.
Okay! I'll be your classmate, Mii-kun!
No, thanks.
College or the work force, huh...
Rii-san, what are you going to do?
Huh?
Why would you ask such a...
What's your plan, Kurumi?
Find a job, I think.
Are you going to get a job where
you can work with Shovel-kun?
Don't sell me so short!
With the recession, I hear they
won't be hiring many women.
No, listen!
There are other options, like...
j-job-hunting forever, or getting m-married...
Married?
To Shovel-kun?
Why does it keep going back to that?!
What do you want to do, Miki-san?
Huh?
My future?
The concept still seems vague,
so I can't say for sure...
Yes... Someday, we'll all...
A club?
What a great idea! We'll start a club.
Yes. It'll be more motivating to have a
concrete goal, rather
than just passing the days.
Yes! I was thinking of continuing lessons,
but a club sounds much more fun!
What shall we call it?
Well, we'll be a club that lives at school, so...
Hmm...
The School Living Club.
We didn't even have to plan that one.
We had the same idea.
I know what you like, Sensei.
You and I are alike.
Thank you.
Here.
Club Proposal Form
What's this?
Take care of this,
President of the School Living Club.
I-I'm the president?
I think you're the best candidate.
I understand. I'll do my best.
Student Council
School Living Club
All done!
Now, everyone line up in front of the door.
I'll take a picture.
Okay, here we go.
Sensei!
Wakasa-san?
Trade spots with me.
We need one with our advisor.
Megu-nee, c'mon!
Takeya-san...
Okay, here we go.
Say "cheese."
You startled me, Takeya-san.
Sorry.
It's ready.
Were my eyes closed?
Should we take it again?
Wow, there it is!
You show up nice and clear, Megu-nee!
Yuuri-senpai, you're still up?
I couldn't sleep.
What about you?
I couldn't sleep, either.
I can't stop thinking about something...
About what?
Staff
Here.
Thank you.
Remember when I said earlier that the
school's equipped with a lot of resources?
Yes, I do.
I realized it after I said it.
Doesn't it seem too well-equipped?
I took another look through
the school guidebook.
Solar batteries, a giant rain-collection
tank with a water purifier,
crops on the roof, food supplies...
It's like the school was designed to accommodate
people living here for extended periods.
That's...
I know!
I know you think it sounds ridiculous.
But once I started thinking
about it, I couldn't stop.
And I wasn't sure what to do...
Yuuri-senpai?
I understand. I've thought the same thing.
Huh?
Each of those things would
make sense, on its own.
Any new office building might be
equipped with one or two of them.
But all of them in one facility is another story.
Is that the key we used before?
Yes. Something tells me this key is
a clue toward finding some answer.
I was planning on talking to everyone
about this in the morning, but...
Will you come with me for a bit?
But you've already checked
the staff room, haven't you?
Yes. The key says "staff" on it,
so I checked here first.
Then what's the use in coming back here?
But the only place I really
checked was Megu-nee's desk.
We can search in earnest tomorrow.
Tonight, let's just look until we get tired.
Okay. Neither of us could sleep yet, anyway.
Let's split up.
Right.
Is this woman Megu-nee?
What're you two doing?
Yuki-chan?
What's wrong, Senpai?
I woke up from a bad dream...
Then I noticed you were both gone,
and I got worried.
Oh, my. I'm sorry, Yuki-chan.
Sakura-sensei asked us
to find something for her.
Th-That's right.
She wanted us to figure out what
that key Miki-san has unlocks.
So it's a treasure hunt!
I'll help, too!
Maybe this?
Did you find a clue?
What do you think?
I guess not.
What's with the teddy bear?
Isn't he cute?
I'm not sure what to say.
Please put him back.
Aww!
Maybe it's this?
What is it this time?
This. This right here.
Yuki-chan...
Have you forgotten about the key?
This sleeping bag is amazing!
You can walk around with it on!
Ah! This has to be it!
This is it, right?
No.
No, it isn't.
Mii-kun, take a picture of me with that camera.
C'mon, take it, yo, yo.
Check it, check it, one-two, one-two.
All of you watching TV, can you hear me?
What are you doing? This is
a camera, not a camcorder.
Huh? Really?
I'm taking it.
Say "cheese."
Hey, Mii-kun! Don't take it
when I'm not ready!
You asked me to.
Smack
It's blank!
Calm down, Senpai.
Look.
Wow! That's amazing!
I dub this the "super camera"!
It's called an instant camera.
Look, Rii-san! This is amazing!
Rii-san?
Hey, don't you remember?
That camera... The time we all
took pictures together with it...
And what happened afterwards?
Rii-san, what are you...
Come on, Yuki-senpai!
You've done nothing but goof around,
and now Yuuri-senpai's getting mad.
Oh! I see!
It's already late. Let's hurry up and find
whatever this key is supposed to open.
Roger!
Yuuri-senpai, that wasn't like you. What's wrong?
It was right after this.
Right after we took this picture...
Megu-nee was...
There are more and more of them lately.
I can't find anything that looks like it'd fit.
No?
We may as well call it a night, then.
Yes...
Hey! Is this...
What now?
We already looked down there.
You'd think that, right?
A false panel...
With a safe inside...
Surprised?
Yes. Very surprised.
Thank you, Yuki-chan.
You really are amazing, Yuki-senpai.
Oh, really, don't mention it.
Yuuri-senpai, let's try it.
Well, what is it?
A DVD for class, and a list...
Is that all Megu-nee wanted us to do?
Y-Yes...
Okay, I'll go tell her we're done.
I guess that was a swing and a miss.
Yuuri-senpai?
SCHOOL ONLY
Staff Emergency Evacuation Manual
Um, is this...
Hurry and wake Kurumi up.
"Due to the nature of the biological weapon,
casualties may exceed estimates..."
"If initial containment efforts fail, the infection
may explode into a full-scale pandemic..."
"Complete and total isolation is key."
"Those in the vicinity of the infected
must also be quarantined..."
"Preservation of the human race takes
ultimate priority over the lives of individuals..."
"The lives of thousands, millions,
rest on your shoulders."
"A kind and sympathetic heart
is no longer a virtue."
Biological weapon...
Hold on!
What is this?
What the hell is this?!
We found what you asked us to
look for, Megu-nee. It wasn't easy!
Oh, yeah! And I found some
cute stuffed animals!
I should've brought them back.
I'll show them to you later, okay?
Next Time!!
Because it's hot, if it's hot, when it's hot...
Senpai, calm down!
Well, it's hot! On days like this, we need...
Ghost stories?
No!
Next time on Episode 9 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Holiday."
#9
Holiday