I found big business at Big Site!
I said it to those that may or
may not know about the value of money.
I'm going to make
a huge profit with dojin!
It's fine that I made the statement, but...
...I've only drawn in school during class.
By the way, it's this.
Where did you get that!
Hey!
Wait!
Papa, Mama, Najimi, John
Come on!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
I was surprised when Najimi said that...
...she was all of a sudden
going to start drawing dojinshi, but...
...as for me, I was happy.
Even if your motive is moneymaking...
But to make a manga,
you need to have knowledge...
...and have the references you need.
First, maybe it's good
to look into a good example?
Najimi?
Enforcement Bloomers
Are you serious?
No, that's...
Um...
You told me to read it.
You were the one that wrote it,
but I'm the one that's looked at like a perv...
Miss, you dropped your erotic book.
2nd Edition
The Naked Princess
Why did you have to go out of your way
to say that so everyone could hear!
I didn't say a lie though.
Here, it's in the
basement of this building.
Hold on a second.
I need to prepare myself for it, you know.
Huh?
Wait, Tsuyuri!
I can't believe her.
How could she leave me when
it's my first time at a store like this?
What am I going to do?
I don't have the courage to go in alone.
Huh?
We're going up.
Ah, okay...
I remember she was saying basement.
So there are people like them normally.
This whole time I thought that
it was this totally erotic thing, but...
...that was a narrow viewpoint.
Oh Father, Mother...
I have learned today that you shouldn't
assume anything with prejudice!
I take back what I just said!
Najimi?
What? Ah...
Yeah, um...
Why am I startled by
something on this level?
It's okay. It's okay, Najimi.
That's right. Everyone has an objective.
There's no one looking at me.
There is!
He's really looking at me!
What is?
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
He was looking at me.
On top of that,
he was pretty good-looking.
But after all, he is a stranger.
People that know me won't...
Oh, Najimi, it's you.
God, you are so mean!
Here, this is my recommendation.
Go buy it.
Wow, they sell stuff like this.
Mamimu Maid, No. 1 selling erotic game!
But it's really selling well...
You say it so easily.
Justice!
Sora!
Sorry to make you wait.
I was lonely!
I'm sorry, Sora.
When you grow older,
you can come in with me too.
We're going to go buy
some art supplies now...
...but what about you ladies?
I'll go too.
What about you, Najimi?
I'm going to go home.
I'm a little tired.
Okay. Then we'll part here.
See you.
Hurry and head home so you
can enjoy your 18+ game debut.
Don't say it out loud!
Though it's totally nerve-wracking.
I know it's reference, but I never thought
I would buy such an erotic thing.
If I ran into a friend right now...
Najimi!
You see them, right?
So I came to buy a computer, but I can't
figure out which one is good at all.
I know what you mean.
I get it, so let's say bye soon, Tomoko.
Today is...
Najimi, what did you buy?
Why!
Why?
'Cause you were shopping, right?
That...
Ah, yeah...
Let me see, let me see!
Don't!
Wh-Why?
Something bad is going to happen.
I-I understand.
Oh yeah, I have to
take care of some stuff.
What is it?
It's that...
Crab!
Crab?
I need to...
...go walk the crab.
Take it for a walk?
A crab?
That's right...
Are you serious?
I want to see!
I refuse!
Wait, Najimi!
Where are you going?
I have to?
No! Please stop, Master!
If you put such a thing in...
If you put red bean paste into the stew...
It's a mess! It's a mess!
Yes?
You can use the bath now.
O-Okay...
I can't...
It's too dangerous at my house.
If it comes down to it...
What? You're coming to my place?
Right now?
If you want, you can.
Now I can relax.
I won't see people
I know during the night!
They shouldn't be able
to stop me at this speed!
Okay, please stop.
That's how you come to me, huh?
Let me quickly confirm something.
Well, I guess it's okay.
As long as this bag is safe.
What's inside this?
Emergency situation occurring!
Are you going to look?
I'm sorry. This area
hasn't been safe recently.
Could you open it?
Don't trouble me!
W-Wait, miss!
What the heck am I doing!
It was whatever just popped into
my head and it's the worst decision!
I'm sorry!
Hold it!
Are you serious?
Why is it turning out this way!
I didn't do anything bad!
That's right. I'm not doing
anything wrong, so I just need to explain.
What am I doing
against one police officer?
He called backup!
Father, Mother...
I might be getting arrested.
Please come visit me at least.
Please make any gifts sweet things.
Miss, why did you run?
Well, um...
There's nothing in there.
I forgot it at home!
What, Najimi?
Tomoko...
What's wrong?
Right now, I don't have
the energy to talk about it.
Najimi, you didn't...
It's okay.
Nothing as drastic as what
you are thinking happened.
In a way, it's more than
you can imagine, though.
Then get home safely.
Yes, I'm sorry for your trouble.
Really...
But why did you run
if there was nothing in it?
The item inside that bag can only
be seen by those who are superior.
Najimi?
Oh, there you are!
You dropped this on the street before.
It most likely fell out of that bag.
I'm glad I found you.
Hey, I'm superior, huh?
Great!
I also like that game.
Father, Mother...
I'm going to drink tonight.
I can't not drink.
Alcohol is for 20 or older.
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
If you're going to watch anime...
...you have to brighten up the room
and sit away from the TV.
Depending on the item,
in a different room from your family.