When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright and
sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for watching "Hayate
the Combat Butler" again today!
Now, let us sing the theme song together!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
I Hear That Those Who Rule the
Summer Rule at Entrance Exams
I wonder what Miss Nishizawa's
doing right now.
One family sort of group...
Five to six customers...
Two couples...
One old man...
Full house...
No customers...
Welcome.
Let me see...
Anmitsu with ice cream, egg-drop
New Year's soup, tokoroten jelly,
kudzu mochi, Abekawa mochi,
isobe-yaki rice cakes,
country style zenzai, and a cream soda.
I'd like all those things, please.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
I wonder what Hayate's doing right now.
Come to think of it, I wonder what
Miss Nishizawa was doing here.
...and take this girl...
...and lick her all over!
Hayate!
Lightning Kick!
Oh? Miss Nishizawa?
I-I'm so glad! It is you!
And the commotion with the
Miss on top of that...
The Miss...
and Miss Nishizawa...
A delivery for you.
Thank you very much.
Hakuou Private Academy
Miss Nagi Sanzenin
Still, I feel bad about doing
that to Miss Nishizawa...
I love you, Hayate!
What?!
I don't want this to be good-bye!
So won't you please go out with me?!
But right now, I have no business
going out with a girl anyway.
What?! Uh, um...
I'm sorry.
What?!
The truth is...
...I'm only interested
in 2-dimensional things.
Crushed!!
There must have been a better
way to turn her down...
Hayate, you jerk!
But I have no idea what I should
do in situations like that.
But why did I think of
the Miss right then...?
Is that you, Hayate?
Yes.
Miss, a delivery has arrived for you...
Oh, thanks. Go ahead and open it for me.
Miss.
You are technically a girl,
so please don't read like that.
R-Right...
I bet this is how it feels to be a big
brother worried about his kid sister.
It'll be a long time before I
have time for a girlfriend.
I have my hands full with the Miss already.
By the way, what is this?
It looks to be some documents
from Hakuou Academy...
Oh, the transfer application,
right? For you?
Oh, for me.
Wait! What do you mean, for me?!
They're documents for you
to transfer into Hakuou.
No, no, I haven't heard about this.
This is news to me!
And I'm delivering the news!
B-But I was dismissed from my old school!
I already know that.
What?
Because I sent for documents
from that school, too.
Oh, look. Here they are.
B-But what about the tuition?!
I don't have those kind of financial means.
What are you saying?
I'm paying for it, of course.
B-But...!
Honestly! What's the problem?!
Don't you want to go to school with me?!
Besides, this is sort of
my way of thanking you,
so don't worry about it.
I'll get to go back... to school...
Miss... Thank y...
Whoa! What are you crying for?!
Because... Because...
What did you do to make him cry?
No, no! I didn't make him cry!
Hayate just started on his own!
According to this document,
it seems you'll still have to
take a transfer admission test.
Well, if he is to claim
to be a Sanzenin butler,
he had better be able to pass a mere
transfer admission test from Hakuou.
Oh, my, Mr. Klaus!
You're alive!
Please don't go killing
me off so thoughtlessly.
So, well... If he doesn't pass,
let's just say he'll be fired.
Hey! After all this time?!
That's fine.
If I don't pass after everything
you've done for me,
it would be inexcusable!
As a butler and as a man!
So I shall put it on display for all of you!
My... My most earnest effort!
Incidentally, Hakuou Academy requires
a standard score of over 65.
I...
I will be fine!
Fine!
Incidentally, the transfer
admission test is tomorrow.
A f-fart in a windstorm
is not necessary, Miss.
But I wonder if Hayate
really will be all right.
Considering his grades at his last school,
it's honestly going to be tight.
Where's Hayate?
He's studying.
I see.
Come in.
How is it going?
Well, it's coming along.
Please try not to let your
nerves get the better of you.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll listen to Maria's advice
and leave it at that.
H-Head Butler!
Please wake up! Please
wake up! This is my bed!
Good morning.
It is not morning yet!
Please leave!
Hayate Ayasaki, you misunderstand me.
What?
I, too, want you to be
admitted to Hakuou Academy.
I want you to pass tomorrow's
transfer admission test!
Do you really mean that?
Do these eyes look like those of a liar's?
You're scaring me.
Sorry.
If you have my best interests at heart,
please leave and let me sleep.
I have your best interests at heart
and that's why I came to relate the
story of my entrance exam experience!
No, thank you!
Yes, thank you!
You're being unreasonable!
Oh, really! This is not necessary!
This was back when I applied to enter
a prestigious private kindergarten.
Aw, he's started already.
There was a problem I just couldn't solve.
The end of the test period
was fast approaching.
Even then, as young as I
was, I could not solve it.
But just as my time was about to be up...
Klaus, you passed.
Are you trying to say that one
mustn't give up, no matter what?
Head Butler!
Mr. Klaus!
Get out!
My rare appearance has me feeling shy.
Deluxe animation! Tama's house!
Sine, cosine, tangent.
The test's probably going to
cover some of that stuff.
That voice!
Tama! How'd you get in here?!
I thought I'd tell you the
Hakuou entrance exam trends
and teach you how to deal with them.
I don't want to learn anything from you!
Beat it!
That should do it.
Hayate! Hayate!
It's not morning yet, so you've
got plenty of time to sleep.
Hakuou Academy
Are you okay?
I'm just a little short on sleep.
A streetcar?
The campus is big, after all.
Well, I did everything I could, but...
I wonder what kind of test it's going to be.
Probably pretty normal,
like English and stuff.
I don't think that study guide will
help you pass at all, though.
You think Hakuou Academy's
transfer admission test
would be something so normal?!
Little Nagi?
Good of you to come,
ex-suspicious individual!
And Little Nagi!
I'm your test administrator for today!
The beautiful world history
teacher, Yukiji Katsura!
The b-beautiful?
Don't turn that into a question!
You say it's not normal, Miss Katsura?
But I took a normal test to get in.
Keep looking back at the past
and you'll have nothing to gain
from the future, Little Nagi!
I don't know about the wisdom
of only looking ahead, either.
At any rate!
We're going to begin the transfer
admission test, so come with me!
Your assignment is none other than
a Redmond-style interview exam!
A Redmond-style interview exam refers to...
a test that has been rapidly adopted
by businesses in recent years,
which uses logic questions to test
the true intelligence of applicants.
"Why are manhole covers round?"
Such tough brainteasers must
be answered logically,
and the test is used to judge
fundamental intelligence
in a way that does not
rely on memorized facts.
I see. Hakuou Academy's
prestige isn't for nothing.
Even their transfer admission
test is a bit different.
By the way, why do you suppose
manhole covers are round?
Because if it were square, the slightest
shift would cause it to fall in, right?
Since the diagonal length of a
square is longer than its sides.
On a circle, it's the same,
even if it shifts, so...
Ah! You're very smart, Miss!
Of course.
I'm not attending Hakuou
on a whim or for show.
All right, then we'll begin the test.
It'll be taking place inside the classroom.
The test will begin the moment you enter
and everything you say and do
will be subject to scoring!
Bear that in mind in
tackling this challenge!
And now, your first problem...
...is this!
SNAP
CRAAAAASH
Are you mocking our Hayate?!
Can't show you!
Or are you permitted to do whatever
you please because you're a teacher?!
Little Nagi, your jabs are harsh.
However, this is the
prestigious Hakuou Academy!
And this is a Redmond-style interview
exam to test your true intelligence!
If you want to give the answer that
just occurred to you, feel free.
But do you really think
that's the correct answer?
Yes, it's true.
By the normal way of thinking,
you use a tool to get the banana.
It's an intelligence test for monkeys.
However, in Redmond-style interview exams,
the first answer that occurs
to you is usually wrong.
In which case...
I have it.
The key to this problem is none other than
the height at which the banana is hung.
The banana is actually at a height
that you can reach by hand.
So the tools lying around
are all red herrings.
The correct answer is none other than
"grab it with your hand
without using any tools"!
This is the correct answer.
Growl~
Monkeys enduring hunger,
unable to cleverly reach the food.
The only food around.
Oh, damn it!
So that was the catch.
I see.
Which means, after everything
I went through,
it's been a while, but I'm going
to get all bloody in this episode?
But you know...
If I don't win this fight, I won't...
...get to go to school!
Here I come!
I didn't imagine he would choose
to fight instead of fleeing.
More like, this is animal abuse.
But your butler sure is putting up a fight.
Well, he's got a lot riding
on this test, after all.
I see.
Then, shall we cut the joke
short and get on with the test?
What?! This was a joke?!
Well, yeah. It'd be easy if you could
test for intelligence like this.
Then why did you make me do this?!
I sort of wanted to loosen you up
as thanks for what you did for me.
I don't need this sort of thanks!
Thus, in pretty poor condition,
both mentally and physically,
Hayate tackled the test.
Calm down!
Just calm down!
How did it go?
Well, I managed to answer all
the questions somehow, but...
If I don't pass after everything
you've done for me...
What shall I do, Miss?
What kind of discouraging
comment is that now?
You're certain to have passed.
I saw the promise in you.
So let's go to school together!
You're right, Miss.
Huh? Madam Superintendent...
Superintendent's Office
I'm to deliver this notice
to the Sanzenin residence?
But Madam Superintendent...
Not Accepted
Perhaps this is my imagination,
but I feel like there is
one word too many here...
Well, he fell short of a
passing mark by one point.
It's too bad.
I-I see...
If he had taken the test
in a calmer frame of mind,
maybe he would have passed...
It's really too bad.
So, there you have it.
I will be counting on you
to do this, Miss Katsura.
In the meantime, at the Sanzenin
residence, not knowing this...
We're getting ahead of ourselves, but
shall we celebrate your acceptance?
What?! Really?! I'm so happy!
...they were already plunging
into celebration mode.
If my dreams have taken your heart
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Hayate, did you have fun studying
for the entrance exam?
Yes, it had been a while since I got
to enjoy feeling like a student.
Thank you very much, Miss.
Thanks is not necessary, Hayate.
We'll be able to go to school
together every day now.
What?! Well, I suppose so.
This will be good-bye to days of
all-nighters and internet gaming.
That's not good.
What?!
All right! You're going to skip
school with me from now on!
What?!
Bye-bye!
Preview
It was just a tiny prank! It
was meant to be a little joke!
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
I never imagined he would fall short
of passing by just one point!
So, you want me to come
with you to apologize?
Yes, if you please, that is
exactly what I am asking!
We will be holding a
magnificent party today!
And we owe it all to that boy
gaining acceptance into Hakuou!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Hey, hey! I hafta go to a party.
Hurry up, seriously".
This situation makes bringing up the
subject even harder than I expected.
Hey, hey! I hafta go to a party.
Hurry up, seriously
Absolute destiny: Apocalypse.