Bauanne
Collection
In Depth!
Bauanne
Collection
In Depth!
RIGHT: Stella during last year's
Bauanne Collection. White's been
trendy this year, a color her dress
emphasizes with regality and elegance.
The long coat-esque detail is just
what you'd expect from Bauanne.
RIGHT: Stella during last year's
Bauanne Collection. White's been
trendy this year, a color her dress
emphasizes with regality and elegance.
The long coat-esque detail is just
what you'd expect from Bauanne.
This year's show is finally hitting Japan! It's a given
that Japan's top model, Stella, will appear on stage,
but so will the teen hit Amanogawa Kirara!
This rising star is Stella's own daughter, and this show
marks their first time competing on stage together,
hence the buzz. Creative Director Baurollo Bauanne had
this to say: "Japanese fashion has developed and evolved in its
own unique manner. Dreamy Hill in particular is a splendid
city for fashion given its distinct blend of varying styles."
This year's show is finally hitting Japan! It's a given
that Japan's top model, Stella, will appear on stage,
but so will the teen hit Amanogawa Kirara!
This rising star is Stella's own daughter, and this show
marks their first time competing on stage together,
hence the buzz. Creative Director Baurollo Bauanne had
this to say: "Japanese fashion has developed and evolved in its
own unique manner. Dreamy Hill in particular is a splendid
city for fashion given its distinct blend of varying styles."
Bauanne
Collection
In Depth!
Bauanne
Collection
In Depth!
RIGHT: Stella during last year's
Bauanne Collection. White's been
trendy this year, a color her dress
emphasizes with regality and elegance.
The long coat-esque detail is just
what you'd expect from Bauanne.
RIGHT: Stella during last year's
Bauanne Collection. White's been
trendy this year, a color her dress
emphasizes with regality and elegance.
The long coat-esque detail is just
what you'd expect from Bauanne.
This year's show is finally hitting Japan! It's a given
that Japan's top model, Stella, will appear on stage,
but so will the teen hit Amanogawa Kirara!
This rising star is Stella's own daughter, and this show
marks their first time competing on stage together,
hence the buzz. Creative Director Baurollo Bauanne had
this to say: "Japanese fashion has developed and evolved in its
own unique manner. Dreamy Hill in particular is a splendid
city for fashion given its distinct blend of varying styles."
This year's show is finally hitting Japan! It's a given
that Japan's top model, Stella, will appear on stage,
but so will the teen hit Amanogawa Kirara!
This rising star is Stella's own daughter, and this show
marks their first time competing on stage together,
hence the buzz. Creative Director Baurollo Bauanne had
this to say: "Japanese fashion has developed and evolved in its
own unique manner. Dreamy Hill in particular is a splendid
city for fashion given its distinct blend of varying styles."
"It's a given that Japan's top model, Stella, will appear on stage, but so will the teen hit Amanogawa Kirara!"
"It's their first show as mother and daughter!"
That's great for Kirara!
All these mags are buzzing about it, too!
Why are you the one getting excited?
The Bauanne Collection finally premieres tomorrow.
I wonder if they're doing rehearsals right now...
Nah, I'm going on stage cold.
Kirara?!
Should you really be here?
Sure.
I don't have any other work to do, so I've got nothing but time to kill.
You're pretty calm!
If I were up tomorrow, I'd be a nervous wreck!
I've been aiming for this show for ages.
Honestly, I'm so excited I can't sit still!
That's so cool!
I'm not surprised.
I can't wait to see your big show!
Good idea!
Wanna head there now?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
What a huge studio!
The Bauanne Collection will be here!
So, the employee entrance should be...
Mom!
Kirara!
As Bright As the Stars!
The Runway of Kirara's Dreams!
It's been so long! How've you been?
Fine... you came to check the studio?
I sure did!
Wow! It's the real, live Stella!
Oh, Mom, let me introduce you.
B-Bonjour! I'm Haruno Haruka!
Good day, I'm Kaidou Minami. It's an honor to meet you.
This is Perf, the poodle we raise at the dorm.
This is Aroma, who's just kinda there.
They're all my friends.
Friends?
You have friends?!
I'm so glad to meet you!
Thanks for taking care of my daughter!
They're with me to check the studio.
They've got invites to tomorrow's show, too.
I see.
Well, hope you enjoy it.
We will!
All right, it's up!
Raise #3!
Wow, this is cool!
It's splendid.
This is the stage I'll be on...
Oh, Stella!
Hi, Bauanne!
I'm counting on you for le show tomorrow, my Aphrodite.
Hello, Bauanne. I'm Amanogawa Kirara.
Oh, Star Princess!
I'm happy to be part of this.
I expect much from you!
Thanks!
Hey, Bauanne, can I try the runway out?
It's nice!
Bon. C'est la Stella.
The studio's atmosphere changed in an instant.
That's the power of a top model like Stella.
That's who I have to walk alongside.
Safe...
Shoot, I'm totally nervous...
Wait, we're going to your house now?!
Yeah, come and stay the night!
I want to hear about how Kirara's been at school!
Wow, can we really?
But you two have such an important show tomorrow...
Oh yeah...
Yeah, I still need to...
Don't be like that!
It's quicker to stay at our house than go all the way back to the dorm, anyway.
Yeah, but...
We haven't received permission to stay out past curfew...
Hey, Mrs. Shirogane?
It's you-know-who!
I know, it's been ages!
Yeah, yeah, totally.
So just... yeah!
Okay!
Permission granted!
That was fast!
Now let's all go shopping for dinner!
Wait, Mom!
Geez!
I thought we'd go to a fancy supermarket!
I grew up in the city, so this feels closer to home.
Oh!
Let's all take a picture in that!
Huh?
I've never been in one of those...
We've got to take a picture together! Right, Kirara?
Ooh, I like it!
Minami, pick a frame!
Sure...
This is the one we just took.
That's one forced smile. What'll I do about tomorrow?
Hey, Mom!
C'mon, everyone likes silly faces!
Please excuse us.
Wow!
Sorry, let me tidy up!
Someone's been slacking on her chores...
Yeah, 'cause it's total dullsville!
Okay, fine, I'll clean up for you.
You handle dinner!
Yes, dear.
What?!
Kirara, your dad is the famous actor,
Takamagahara Ken?!
Goodness! I heard he's even
starred in Hollywood movies.
Yup. He's filming in Brazil right now.
Wow, you're a family of celebrities!
I'm full.
Already?
Yeah, I've got stuff to do.
Sorry, but make yourselves at home.
One more push...
I know I can do this.
It's just a runway like any other.
Pardon us!
Um, Mrs. Stella...
Kirara, let's look at old photo albums!
I've got your baby pictures!
You looked like a monkey!
Cripes!
Be serious for once!
Why have you been trying to distract me so much today?
Tomorrow's the biggest show I've ever been in!
I'm finally on a global stage!
I can't fail! I need to focus!
Don't you get that?!
Not a bit.
After all, I'm a natural!
G...
Go away!
Huh? Kirara, dear?
Yeah, I get it! You're just so perfect!
Trust me, you're always shoving it in my face!
But did you really need to spell it out?
Maybe not...
You've never had an ounce of tact!
The first time I showed you an outfit I coordinated all by myself...
You look pretty lame.
That hurt!
Did you have to go into supermodel mode there?
And then at the arts festival in elementary school...
She's airing some serious laundry here...
Well, let's give her a listen.
Yes, it might help Kirara calm down.
Hey, are you listening?!
Yes!
Hey, Haruharu, Minamin, what do you think of my mom?
Uh, me?
The Black Key...
If you desire despair, then I shall—
Nay, Princess Twilight, please allow me.
Well, someone got some confidence out of nowhere.
There's naught but one place certain to draw
strong dreams as well as the Princess Precures.
Pigtails!
I spent the whole time complaining to my friends.
I wound up not getting any practice.
Oh well.
Worrying won't do much good at this point.
I can't turn into Stella overnight,
so I'll just have to do things my way!
Kirara.
Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
Thanks for asking.
Your smile is much livelier than yesterday's.
Merde. You'll do great.
Stella, standby on stage right!
Okay!
Did Mom actually...
You're lucky!
I would've liked to see Kirara's house!
Sorry, it was a spur of the moment...
Let's all go together next time!
Twilight!
Shut!
Did they start?
Is she a model?
She's like a princess!
Not "like," I am a princess.
Hey, what are you people doing here?
I've found her!
It's them!
Mom!
Now, show me your dream.
I want Kirara and I to walk on the same runway!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Two of them?
Everyone, please evacuate!
The stronger the dream, the deeper the despair.
How fitting for a Precure's parent.
Mom...
You really were helping.
Everything you did was to relieve the stress I put on myself...
Just you wait, Mom! This time, I'll be the one to help you!
Girls, let's go!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Today is naught but the day you shall lose your Keys!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil.
Dyyyyyspair!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Dys!
Pair!
Dyspaaaaairvil!
Dyyyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Dyspair.
It's fitting for you to be crushed by the
despair born from your mother's dream.
You kidding?
There's no way I'll lose!
Because I saw it!
I saw that Mom's dream was to perform with me!
I've always dreamed of being a model like Mom!
Of walking on the same runway as her!
So I'm not biting the bullet here!
I'll beat you guys in a cinch...
Dys?
And then Mom and I will make our dreams come true!
Dyspair!
Dys?
What?!
What?
That's...
A new Dress Up Key!
W-What?!
It's Twinkle's Miracle Dress Up Key!
It was drawn to the bond between Kirara and Stella!
A Key of dreams that brings Mom and I together!
Shut, steal that Key!
Right!
Dyspairvil!
You won't get this Key!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dyspairvil!
Beautiful...
Princess Twilight, look out!
Dyspair!
Let's finish this!
Come on, girls!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Princess Twilight, are you unharmed?
I'm fine.
Then I shall strike again!
No.
Let us depart.
Right!
Open!
The door to your dream!
The show must go on, Mom.
The Bauanne Collection 2015 is about to begin!
Kirara was amazing!
Indeed.
Good work, Kirara!
You were great.
Thanks. I couldn't have done it without you.
But what now? Your dream's already come true.
Your dream was to perform with me, right?
Maybe, but I have more.
There's always the next dream to chase.
Huh? Which?
For the both of us to be top models!
Okay, you're on!
Just you wait, that'll come true in a flash!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
How splendid! The author of "The Princess of Flowers" is doing a book signing!
They say she left the public eye
right after publishing that book.
She's the one who inspired your dream, huh?
What's she like?
I wonder if she's like a princess.
Oh, I'm so nervous!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Secret Behind the Story!
What is a True Princess?
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Chiba Prefecture - Sakura (Age 6)
Saitama Prefecture - Hiiro (Age 7)