I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Frozen, frozen hard.
Yeah, they're no good.
Ugh, full of toxic dioxins.
I saved these for evidence
a while back, but--
Hey, hold on! I know you're hungry,
but those things are poison!
A confidence man who cons women?
That's who you wanna catch?
I don't have much choice.
Is he a big tough crook?
Smallest of the small fries.
Spike's gonna hate it
when I tell him about it.
Edward wants chocolate!
Guess I'll do it alone then.
You've gotta be kidding!
Cut me some slack...
It stinks!
Really... weren't you taught
to clean up your own poop?
Like, bury it or something?
I've been trying to figure out
who it is you remind me of.
Now I know. It's that guy
with the thin eyebrows.
Whitney Haggis Matsumoto.
I wonder why I suddenly thought
of him out of the blue like that.
Do you wanna know a secret
about my past? Do you?
Ms. Manley, does it look like
the patient is reviving?
Why yes, Doctor. I believe she is.
Ms. Manley, does she look like
an old woman to you?
No, she doesn't, Doctor.
Do you think she's been
successfully unfrozen?
I believe so, Doctor.
Can you hear me? Huh? Yoo-hoo!
I am Doctor Bacchus.
Bacchus, as in the Bacchus that
drowned more humans than Neptune.
Have you ever heard
about that Bacchus? Hmm?
Well, I used to be an
alcoholic back then.
Bacchus was drowning
because of Bacchus!
Hey, that was a good one!
Now open nice and wide. Aah.
You're healing beautifully.
No wounds left, and the cells
are dividing quite nicely.
So you only have one problem left,
and you know what that is? Huh?
Coming up with 30 million
Woolongs for the basic operation.
In addition to 54 years
of interest payments...
Uh, how much is that?
273 million.
Add the hospital fees to that,
and the total is 300,028,000 Woolongs.
Right! So when you've paid that amount,
you'll be free! You understand?
I don't understand...
Good! Then everything's just--
What did you say?
This place... where is it?
Where am I? Who are you?
Ms. Manley?
She is not acting, Doctor.
I'm Whitney Haggis Matsumoto,
your lawyer.
Lawyer?
Tortoise Insurance Company
brought me in on the case.
I've already done some
research on your past.
Miss Faye Valentine.
Is-- is that really my name?
It's an especially lovely name.
I think it suits you very well.
- And so?
- We need to know about your memory.
Hmm... that's a monitor,
a hot water pot,
that's a cellular phone.
So I remember everything, really...
Everything except my own life.
- I see.
- And?
And according to the records
that we have, when you were 20...
Well, in a sense, you still are 20...
You were involved in a serious accident.
Accident?
They couldn't save you with the
medical technology back then.
But I'm totally fine.
You can see that.
I don't have a scratch.
"Back then?" What do you mean?
The accident. It was 54 years ago.
You were put into a cold sleep.
In other words,
cryogenically preserved, until now.
Medical technology has
finally advanced to a point
where you could be fully
cured and reawakened.
You might say you're a modern
version of Sleeping Beauty.
You're kidding me.
I'm very serious, Faye.
Then... I'm dreaming.
Listen to me, the year is 2068.
This is not a monitor...
It's a washing machine.
This isn't a hot water pot,
it's a face cleaner.
And this is not a cell phone,
it's a biothermometer.
- You put the round end in your mouth--
- Liar!
You think I'm gonna believe
a load of rubbish like that?!
Temperature: 94.1. Pulse: 54.
Blood pressure: 40/75.
- It's still low.
- Hold on!
Your memory is trapped in an earlier era
when cell phones had solar antennas.
Then tell me! What kind of accident?
I need to know!
What was I like before?
Calm down. If you get
too excited, you could--
What?! What's gonna happen to me if I--
You'll pass out, Faye.
Oh brother.
Hey there, want a cold one?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Wait, come back here!
Miss Valentine! Hello!
Wait! Please!
Stay away from me!
What do you get by running away?
Listen, Miss Valentine, please...
I can't pay 300 million.
It's not fair... to revive me...
and then expect me
to pay all that money.
I don't even know
anything about myself.
What am I gonna do?
You can deal with the debt
payments little by little.
I'll do everything I can to help you.
And you know, someday your
memory might come back to you.
If you hang in there,
you might meet someone wonderful.
What's this?
It's an ID.
If you should die,
or if you forget yourself,
they know who you are
and where you're from.
I don't even have one.
I don't have an ID at all.
♪ Sometimes I think, oh yes, ♪
♪ I'd move to where all the
shooting stars are gone ♪
♪ With all of our wishes ♪
♪ How could they bear, oh no, ♪
♪ To carry around
the stupid human hopes ♪
♪ So I'm gonna help, I will ♪
♪ Give me a key ♪
♪ To the lock the door
to the secret paradise ♪
♪ There are so many queuing up ♪
♪ And I won't let them in ♪
♪ Look at them, they are cheeky ♪
♪ They are never worthy to be saved ♪
♪ Lay your heart, lay your soul ♪
♪ Upon my magic carpet ♪
- What's that?
- Collection agency.
- The insurance company got impatient.
- What do we do?
♪ Remember, surrender ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do ♪
♪ 'Cause love's such a joke ♪
♪ Like a little jack-in-the-box, you know ♪
If we stay here, we'll both get caught.
- You better jump out and run.
- What about you?
I'll meet you at the
medical clinic. All right?
But why are you helping me like this?
A prince has to protect Sleeping Beauty.
That's the way it works.
We just went through
all of his paperwork.
In the event of an unforeseen accident,
his instructions were to transfer
all of his assets to you.
If you give us a thumbprint here,
everything he owns will be yours.
Oh Whitney...
He really did care...
So press this with your thumb...
Why are all the numbers there in red?
Hmm... those are all his debts,
but they say debt is an asset.
His debts?
You have got to be kidding!
'Course, I can see now how stupid I was.
I mean, if you think about it,
he risked his life to save me.
And his debt... well, it was a drop
in the bucket compared to mine.
All in all, it really wasn't that much.
How long were you
in there listening, Spike?
Too long. Your story needs editing.
You should be ashamed, you know.
I'm sure that guy's
crying in the next world,
since you ran off
without paying his debt.
I can't help that.
It's way more than I could ever pay.
Now she gets huffy about it.
Why shouldn't I? Remember,
I'm a lot older than you.
Your past is always changing.
Last time, you said you were a gypsy.
Maybe you made this story up too.
Think what you like, but it's not a lie.
I just don't know
the whole truth, all right?
There's nothing I can do about it.
Welcome back!
This guy has a rep as a Don Juan.
He's really just a cheap confidence man.
- Girls fall for him?
- Take note.
When others are snoozing,
Jet is on the job.
Whitney... Haggis... Matsumoto!
Uh, yeah... long time no see.
All right, she knows him, but why
does she have to talk to him alone?
Apparently, they were very close.
We talking ex-boyfriend?
Yeah, and they were made for each other.
Looks like you've been living
very well, Mr. "Lawyer."
Why, 'cause I'm a little plump?
Isn't that biased?
I want a full explanation.
Well, I just had a fat implant.
It was right after the accident.
They squeeze it in through
the armpit with a plastic--
Not that!
It's been over three years.
You look... healthy.
Thanks a lot. Were you trying
to create a whole new identity?
I wanted to start all over.
Start from scratch.
By conning women out of their money?
Well, you became a bounty hunter.
I'd say it was destiny.
So everyone was in on it, huh?
I had no choice.
The doctor was protecting me.
I owed too much.
And now he's dead.
Maybe I should've just let
them come and arrest me.
I couldn't ask for more than to have
you hand me over to the police.
You think it's safe to leave them alone?
Worried about him, or her?
I'm afraid she might let
him escape or something.
Well, she'd have to
have a heart to do that.
Don't be fooled 'cause she acts tough.
Babes like her are the first ones to go
soft when it comes to an old boyfriend.
Is that right...
Women are hopeless.
They don't work on reason.
We're here! Welcome, visitors!
So are you the ones that contacted us?
Yeah, I wanna claim a bounty.
Hmm, I see.
- Ms. Manley, prepare for rendezvous.
- Yes, Doctor.
I'm glad I got to see
you one last time...
Sleeping Beauty.
Let's go.
It's all right!
You don't have to do this
for me, it's too risky!
They opened the hatch already?
- He's trying to get out.
- She's helping him...
- Wanna bet?
- Yeah, I'll give you 4 to 1.
- Dammit, hurry up, Spike!
- I'm trying!
Whoa, it's impossible!
We'll never make it!
You can't squeeze two people in here!
Just don't breathe so much!
Exhale or something!
Hey, wait!
Stay back! We're leaving!
She wants the guy instead of the money.
Jet caught him! It's his reward, Faye!
I have some history
to work out with this guy,
so I claim first rights to him and
to the bounty that's on his head!
Is it just me, or did that
not make any sense?
Just like I said.
Women don't work on reason.
Let me outta here!
- Are you gonna set him free or what?
- We'll see!
Oh man!
Visitors, thank you for your attendance.
Where are we going?
What are you gonna do with me?
I wanna know the truth.
Tell me, who am I?
Tell me where the lies end
and the truth begins.
What are you doing?!
If you're not careful,
I'll hit the cockpit.
I'm not going easy on you!
Thought that was my line.
You know, you really are a big pain.
Who am I?
Are you sure you really wanna know?
It's going to be hard to swallow.
Are you prepared for
all the consequences?
- I am.
- Are you sure?
- Spit it out!
- I don't really know myself, I swear!
You're lying.
Who am I? My past? My future?
These are questions every human
asks at least once in their life.
Who are you?
However, puberty is the only time
to worry about things like that.
Only people who are bored think
such thoughts after a certain age.
I've heard that voice before somewhere...
Here I am. Yoo-hoo!
Oh jeez, is that the doctor
from the cryoclinic?
Sure seems that way.
You told me that doctor was dead!
Uh, not dead, I mean, not completely--
How many lies are you gonna
tell me before you're through?
Uh, I, uh...
You were cryogenically
preserved in our labs.
That is a verifiable fact.
I can guarantee it.
- Huh?
- What about my past?
Who in the world am I?
Actually, I gave you
the name Valentine.
Yes, I named you after
my favorite love song.
All the other data on you was lost
when the astral gate exploded.
So you see, no one
knows who you are,
or why you were put
in a cryogenic state.
Is this guy a doctor or a cop?
Pilot of patrol ship 118.
You are in a vehicle which
has been reported stolen.
State your department code now.
I repeat, state your code.
Doctor, this is not good.
We're going to be apprehended here.
Oh, it's very unfortunate, but we'd
better cut our losses and make tracks.
Good call, Doctor.
You're on your own, Whitney.
Take care of yourself.
Bye-bye, Whitney.
Wait-- Wait a minute, Uncle! Don't go!
- He's your uncle?
- Uh-huh...
Hmm...
I'll take my bounty right here and now.
Ah, that's better.
And good riddance.
What a fitting payback for
all the sleazy lies you told me.
Well, there is one part that's true...
That I fell in love with you
while you were sleeping.
I fell in love with Sleeping Beauty.
Uh, no, I-I'm lying!
It's just another lie, you know!
Look who's here.
You must really want me back.
Yeah, nice try.
You were jealous.
In your dreams.
I'm still in the dark.
I may never know
anything about my past.
Doesn't really matter, does it?
Easy for you to say.
At least you have a past.
And you have a future.
That's what counts.
- What's this?
- It's your share of the bounty.
The big 19,800 reward.
You're kidding.
The smallest of the small fries.
So it wasn't 19,800...
I kinda put an extra zero in there.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
So I have to admit, the next
episode of Cowboy Bebop is, well...
It's kind of depressing.
Very depressing, actually.
The only characters who show up
are a bunch of musty old guys.
I hate to say this,
but it's kind of heavy-handed.
Children shouldn't watch it.
Ladies should avoid it too.
And on top of that, it's better if
you young guys don't tune in either.
Next episode:
"Black Dog Serenade."
Oh... All you old guys?
I wouldn't miss this one if I were you.