Ushio?
Shinpei!
What're ya doin' here, Shinpei?
Ya came back?
I-I should be the one askin' ya!
Huh?
That necklace...
It was one-of-a-kind and she left it behind. But how?
Ushio's dead.
W-We held a funeral for her two days ago!
Dead?
Yer not her.
Ya can't be Ushio!
Huh? What're ya sayin'?
Ain't I alive?
Look! I'm right here!
What's it saying?
This thing's a Shadow! No doubt about it!
Y-Ya don't remember what happened to ya?
Huh?
What?
Why...
Why am I here?
I... huh?
That's weird.
Y'don't remember what happened before coming here?
Pain...
There was a lot of pain.
That's all I remember.
I was underwater...
Everything was going dark.
Wait! No, it can't be!
I see. I did die!
Then what the heck am I?
A... ghost?
But don't ghosts float in the air?
Does it really think it's Ushio?
What's going on?
I remember just one thing.
My last thought was that I wished for somethin'.
I wished I could see ya one more time, Shinpei.
Is that why ya came back?
I'm so happy!
That voice. That behavior.
Stop it! What the hell?
It's like Ushio really has come back from the dead!
Hey, Shinpei.
There's one more thing I wanted to tell ya if I ever saw ya again.
I love ya.
Y'know.
I love ya, Shinpei!
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Jamais Vu
Huh?
What did she just say?
She l-loves me?
What's that supposed to mean?
Wh-What're ya sayin'?
Did dyin' make you go crazy?
Maybe.
It's like my head's all fuzzy.
D-Don't be fooled. Take a step back!
Two days ago, Ushio was lying in a casket.
She's ash now. She's no longer of this world.
That thing's pretending to be her.
What the hell is it after?
Why did ya come here?
Well, that's what I'd like to know.
When ya die, ain't ya supposed to go to heaven?
Wh-What's yer goal?
What do y'all want?
What do I want?
Shinpei, those fireworks.
Don't tell me today's the 24th.
It is.
No way! O-Oh my gosh!
There is somethin' I wanna do!
I wanna go to the festival with ya!
H-Hey!
Shinpei, hurry up!
It doesn't think of itself as a Shadow.
Does it really consider itself to be Ushio?
Oh!
Shinpei, I wanna play this game!
Hold on! Why's it still in a swimsuit?!
I-Idiot! Everyone's starin'!
Somethin' smells really yummy.
I wanna eat takoyaki!
This ain't the time!
What if someone we know sees ya?!
How am I even supposed to explain this?!
Come one, come all!
We got the biggest and cheapest octopus in our takoyaki.
Tastes real good!
How 'bout it, sir?
Wanna try it?
Hey, Shinpei!
Why do we hafta hide here?
I'm hungry.
Ain't Mio 'n' the gang comin' too?
I wanna see 'em.
No! Absolutely not!
Think about the situation for a second, will ya?
Look, yer dead!
We held a funeral for ya two days ago!
But—
But nothin'!
Yer a Shadow—
No, maybe yer a ghost. I dunno.
Everyone can see ya, after all.
What even are ya?
So yer sayin' I can't see my friends?
Of course not!
A-Anyway, just hide here until the festival's over.
Shinpei, ya big dummy!
Quit spoutin' nonsense!
Or I'll twist yer mouth off!
So she punches before warning me?
That's just like Ushio.
I ended up talking with Ushio's Shadow for a bit.
About what I'd experienced in my two years off the island,
and memories from when we were younger.
Ushio remembered it all.
Do you remember who my favorite author is?
Ain't it Nagumo Ryuunosuke?
One of his books became a movie, and we went to see it at Garden Park.
But for some reason, she had no memory of anything related to Shadows.
She doesn't even remember how she died.
Don't ya wonder what happened to Shiori?
Huh? Somethin' the matter with her?
And it doesn't seem like she's acting to me.
No, it's nothin'.
Phone call?
Yeah, it's Mio.
Kofune Mio
Hey!
Gimme!
Hello? Mio?
What is it?
Sis?
Hello? It's me!
M-Mio? It's me!
Yes!
I swear I just heard my sister's voice.
That ain't possible!
Y-Ya sure yer okay?
R-Right.
Sorry, I must be hearing things.
Where are ya, Shin?
The fireworks are over already.
We're inside the shrine.
Yeah, they're starting the ceremony.
I'm close.
Yeah.
Got it.
I'll run over.
What'd she say?
Never ya mind! Y'need ta stay hidden!
Hey!
I-I'll come get ya later.
Y'don't even know just how dangerous things are right now.
Hmph!
Ya once told me to protect Mio.
I don't wanna have any regrets anymore.
I don't get it.
I ain't never said anythin' like that.
There ya are, Shin!
Took ya long enough! We were worried.
Mountains!
Sorry, my stomach suddenly started hurtin'.
M-Mesopotamian culture.
See? Told ya he had to poop.
Why do ya look so proud?
On Hitogashima,
there is a long-held belief that says a god dwells inside everything which drifts ashore.
That deity is Hiruko no Mikoto.
We call it Hiruko, the god of fishing.
Any wreckage that gets washed ashore is gathered instead of discarded.
We send the god off in a ceremony called "omiokuri" and burn the items.
A lot of people came to see it.
There are easily a thousand here.
It's been so long since we all watched the ceremony together.
Yeah.
Ushio's watchin' too!
What?!
In heaven.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Right.
Should I have even come to the festival after my sister's passing?
I really hope she's here in spirit.
Yeah.
Well, Sou.
What did ya want to talk about?
Apparently,
my brother is going to confess to Mio today.
What?
I-Is he serious?
He can be so illogical sometimes.
Sometimes magic can happen, though.
Indeed.
But it's not going to happen here.
Huh? Why?
Because Mio
already has someone she's in love with.
Oh, really?
Who?
I shouldn't be the one to say.
Shinpei!
And Tokiko!
Listen closely!
U-Um, hey, Mio...
No, Mio!
I know this probably ain't the time to say this.
But that's exactly why I want you to hear it!
I really do love you, Mio!
W-With that said, Mio.
Let me protect ya!
Whoa!
He really said that!
Whoa! Hold on, Sou!
What're you—
E-Everyone's listening!
What do ya even like about me?
I'm happy ya feel that way.
But I'm sorry.
I just want us to be good friends!
Ah...
What did I tell ya?
Now that sure was somethin'!
Yo, Sou!
Keep yer chin up!
I thought I said to stay hidden!
That idiot!
Summer Time Rendering
Th-That pretty hair...
That voice...
Ushio?
Huh?
Wh—
Th-There's no...
wayghh!
I am not this Ushio of whom ya speak!
I am the warrior of love,
Cure—
Stop.
Shinpei, I got figured out in less than a second.
You idiot. You call that a disguise?
Sh-Shinpei!
It can't be!
Sorry.
I really just wanted to see everyone's faces.
Did Toki help ya get dressed, Mio?
Ya look great in that yukata!
That's not her.
Mio?
What are ya doin', Shin?
Get away from it now!
That's not my sister!
Huh?
It's a monster!
Mio.
I refuse to let her go.
Th-That hurts!
Shinpei?
Mio, wait!
Shinpei! Explain!
What're ya thinkin'?
There's no way ya can trade places with someone who's just had a funeral.
Ya never were planning on switchin', were ya?
Why didn't ya listen to me?
Are ya deaf or somethin'?
Who?
Who are you?!
Everyone, run!
It's too late.
Th-That's—
That's not Shin!
It's time.
About ten minutes ago
Mio, I'm sorry for suddenly running off.
What am I doing, worrying her like this?
I'll explain later.
Hey, Shin.
Got a minute? I've got somethin' I wanna ask ya.
Huh?
I-I didn't even see it move!
And this strength!
No human's this strong!
Shin, I heard ya recorded me.
That should be unthinkable.
Unless you knew beforehand that I was comin'.
How'd ya know?
It knows!
It... It can't be...
Yer kidding me.
Did it kill all of them?
Just how many victims have there been?
Did that traitor tell ya?
Traitor?
I can't let this slide.
The plan's almost complete.
There will be no interference.
Investigate.
How much does he know?
It cuts off and repeats.
My memories are quite strange.
How many times have ya died?
Th-That's...
my Shadow!
I must have been copied there.
Does that mean it has my memories up to that point?
Crap! It's gonna update its memories!
They're gonna find out!
They'll know that we're looking into the Shadows!
And stuff like Mesopotamian culture!
No!
Ushio. Why are these things popping up everywhere now?
What happened to there being safety in busy places?
No, damn it!
Crap, crap, crap!
Dammit! That's not what I should be thinking about right now!
Done?
Wait.
I can get rid of him now, right?
I gotta run...
No!
Run, or they'll kill me!
Everyone will be killed!
I said wait.
Don't kill him, Mio.
Why, Shin?
Take a step back and think.
Didn't Mother tell ya?
If he dies, he can just try again, right?
You mean the looping?
Are those memories for real?
This ain't a video game, y'know.
He can't control it on his own.
But if we assume it's true, then everything makes sense.
We have to consider this issue in four dimensions.
Take a step back and look at our third-dimensional thinking from the fourth dimension.
Even if he doesn't know it now,
he might figure it out in the future.
You read way too many weird books.
If he can return to the 22nd with his memories intact,
then one day he will without a doubt become a hindrance to us.
So don't kill him.
Not until everything's finished.
I'm going up.
Take his phone from his back left pocket.
Send some others down a level to grab Ushio.
She's in the equipment storage behind a tent.
Got it.
Hurry up and go.
If we're late, we'll never hear the end of it.
Right.
Damn it... w-wait.
Pathetic, isn't it?
You weren't able to protect anyone in the end.
Wait!
Wait, dammit!
Don't you dare lay a finger on Mio!
Honestly! Just give it a rest, Shin!
Yer bein' too cool.
But it's too late.
Mother will be waking up soon.
Hey, just stay still.
It's just sad seein' ya struggle so pointlessly, Shin.
Mio!
Should I break yer leg, too?
The word "narezushi" isn't used on Hitogashima, is it?
I've never eaten it before.
Have you?
Huh? Wha?
She's...
from the ferry!
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Maelstrom