Yurika!
Why... Why are you doing this?!
You all are trying to protect
too many things at once.
That's why you can't protect anything.
I won't let you lay one finger on Yurika.
That's if you can win.
Then I will.
I will win!
That white magic again?
Koutarou-sama.
Sakuraba-senpai?!
Even Harumi Sakuraba can use magic?
This is your sword.
I understand.
I wish you luck.
Sakuraba-senpai!
It looks like she's okay.
I'm surprised.
So, that's your true power?
I'm surprised, too.
You're like a monster.
But, I can at least test
that power of yours...
Double Cast, Force Field! Thunderlance!
What?!
What power...
At this rate...
Quick Cast, Fog Cloud!
Modifier, effective area colossal!
Yurika!
How dare you, Koutarou Satomi?
In order to defeat him, I'll have to
get the power residing in room 106.
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
The Sun and a Rainbow
Huh? I...
Are you back with us?
Koutarou-sama...
Satomi-kun!
Oh, yeah.
Is Yurika-san okay?
Yurika-san!
Calm down, Sakuraba-senpai.
She's just unconscious.
But...
It'll be okay.
Just relax.
R-Right.
I'm sorry.
So, what happened?
I don't remember anything
after when Yurika-san fell.
You don't remember?
No, nothing.
I see. I guess that's fine.
Yurika!
Yurika-san!
Satomi-san...
Sakuraba-senpai...
They haven't come back...
Luckily for them, fifth
period was only study hall.
I guess I'll try to contact them.
I tried to call them, but they
were out of the service area.
If you're worried, we
can go looking for them.
I'm not worried at all!
Anyway, I have to go work on the play.
Don't bother me!
The problem is the end.
It's true that the Silver
Princess loved the Blue Knight,
but did the Blue Knight...
They kiss
I imagine if they loved
each other, they'd kiss...
No, no!
The Blue Knight and the
Silver Princess would kiss!
Wh-Why would I imagine kissing someone
as lacking in etiquette as he is?!
B-But...
I have to direct him...
S-So that means I have to...
You know, just like a couple would...
Have one of those breath-taking,
passionate kisses...
Your Highness! What's wrong?
A kiss...
Huh?
Everyone, help!
Sanae?
I see...
Maki-chan...
Yeah, she got away.
I had Sanae run to go get everyone.
Wait for them.
We don't have time for that.
Yurika-san, you can't push yourself...
I'm fine.
I'm a magical girl who
represents love and courage.
But...
Maki-chan is at Apartment
106, no doubt about it.
We need to head there.
You can't fight in your condition.
Wait here a bit longer
until you feel better.
But...
I'll fight with you.
But, we won't be able to win
before you've recovered.
Also, there's something I want to ask.
About your magic.
I understand...
I see.
That sword was created by controlling
some of the magic that's pooled here.
It was so powerful for
only having used a bit of it.
If I read the magic Satomi Koutarou was
using, and control this energy myself,
I'll be able to gain the advantage.
I had the potential to use magic,
and one day, I was attacked by a beast
that sensed that magic within me.
Magical Girl Nana-san saved me.
She saved your life?
Yes.
I wanted to repay Nana-san
for what she had done.
So, I started helping her.
She wouldn't let me join her in any fighting,
but I'd prepare meals,
and help her with research.
Nana-san was a Forsarrian, so
she didn't have any papers here.
There was a lot for me to do.
Forsarrian?
It's the name for the people
from the magical kingdom.
Nana-san was one of the
Archwitches for the
Magical Kingdom Forsarria
Army, Rainbow Heart,
and was a genius mage.
If there's other mages around,
why are you fighting, Yurika?
Well...
Nana-san lost her magic because of me.
Eight months ago, I was held hostage by
Maki-chan's group, Darkness Rainbow.
Nana-san was badly hurt protecting me,
and released all of the magic within herself
to defeat Maki-chan and the others.
Once you do that, you're no
longer able to use magic.
But, Nana-san did it to protect me...
I see...
So, you took her place after that.
Yes.
This costume and this staff...
originally belonged to Nana-san.
I have to do what she
was supposed to do.
Yurika-san...
I'm okay now.
Let me go, Satomi-san,
Sakuraba-senpai.
This is troublesome.
I never would have thought
I'd see old Forsarrian magic here.
Koutarou Satomi... who are you?
He's so warm...
I think I understand how Sanae-chan
feels since she's always back here.
Yurika...
You really are a magical girl, aren't you?
Huh?
I know I said this yesterday,
but you know there's all kinds of
people gathered around me, right?
Yeah.
But, I thought of you as a normal girl.
Just another normal person, like me.
Messing around with everyone
from class, joking around...
I thought we'd go through high school
together without anything special happening.
I know it wasn't fair of me to think that.
I think I just wanted you to
be a normal classmate of mine.
A normal classmate with a hobby
a little different than everyone else.
Fighting doesn't suit you.
Satomi-san...
Yurika.
Yes?
I'm sorry for not believing you.
Pretending to be a cosplayer for
these last six months wasn't so bad.
I see.
Hello?
Koutarou?!
Where are you?!
Why did you leave without saying anything?!
I did it.
I managed to gain control.
This is some serious magic,
even if it's just a small portion.
Now Koutarou Satomi can't
use that crazy magic of his.
I'm going to take him out.
You're here.
You're giving this room back.
You want to fight here?
Wait!
You're pretty good, Koutarou Satomi.
You too, Maki-san!
Mind Flare!
How about this?!
Quick Cast, Force Field!
You're good.
Sonic Impact.
Modifier, Touch Trigger!
Quick Double Cast!
Acceleration, Tiny Memory Flash.
Modifier, Touch Trigger!
Watch out for her staff!
If you touch it, you'll lose
your memories for a few seconds!
What was that?!
I can't get close!
Control Plant.
Modifier, Extend Length Four Times!
Yurika!
Now, Satomi-san!
Leave it to me!
Looks like I have to use this...
Wh-What's going on?
You surprised?
This is your power.
Satomi-san, run!
Maki-chan is controlling
the power from Apartment 106!
You need to hurry!
What?!
It's too late now!
Die, and return to the soil
from whence you came,
Koutarou Satomi!
Lightening Lance! Modifier, Change
Element Darkness and High Concentration!
This is bad!
Take this, Koutarou Satomi!
Quick Cast, Anti-Magic Shield!
Modifier, Maximize!
I didn't expect you to still be alive.
I'm glad.
S-Satomi-san, run away.
Damn it...
Looks like it's time to say goodbye,
Yurika Nijino, and...
Satomi Koutarou.
Karama, Koroma!
Right!
What?!
Expand an etheric field in front of us!
Time to show our stuff!
Let's go, Brother!
Damn...
Kiriha-san... Everyone else...
How did you...
I opened a hole in Maki-chan's barrier.
Give up, Maki-chan.
Hmph.
A bunch of weirdos all together.
You think you won because you
managed to block that one attack?
I agree.
You can't win a battle
without attacking yourself.
Blue Knight. Fire the ships'
high convergence lasers.
Obliterate my enemy.
As you wish, My Princess.
Quick Cast, Force Field!
Modifier, Maximize!
Your Highness, isn't this a bit too much—
I'm punishing her for hurting my knight.
What's going on?
I can only defend against it by
pouring all the room's magic into this...
Hm? So you're still standing,
but this is the end.
Blue Knight, attack with the main cannon.
Your Highness!
Koutarou must be in the play with me.
We'll scream at each other, and laugh.
The play will be great!
But, this girl hurt him!
I won't forgive her!
Yeah, but you can't blow away
Corona House along with her!
Hey, I wanted to ask you all something...
Y-Yes?
Who did that?
U-Um, it was Maki-chan.
I see.
What—
Who are these people?
It's not just Koutarou
Satomi, but all of them...
Now, are you going to persist?
We won't hold back next time.
Take our advice. Surrender.
Thanks for everything, Twilight Wing.
Sacrifice Twilight Wing,
Pre-cast Spell Release!
Maki-chan?!
She got away...
Are you okay, everyone?
Cosplaying again, Yurika?
Huh?
I told you not to go around
the neighborhood like that.
Keep that stuff between you and your club.
Hey Ruth, when did we get back from school?
I don't know.
I feel like we were in class
until just a second ago.
It feels like time just flew by.
That's weird.
Very weird.
That's not possible.
My roof is broken!
Who did it?
I won't forgive them!
I-It wasn't me!
What?
What?!
I see, Rainbow Yurika has allies?
Yes,
but we need to be most
wary of Koutarou Satomi.
Huh, you in love?
Stop with the bad jokes!
At any rate,
we were able to make some progress
on deciphering the spell in that room,
and got information on the enemy.
You did the best you could,
given we can't act yet.
Yeah, but I sacrificed Twilight Wing
in exchange for their memories.
I need to make another staff.
And get more information
without attracting attention.
We're depending on you, Maki.
I know.
Koutarou Satomi...
I'll take you down myself.
What is this, Satomi-kun?
A sea urchin.
It's small.
Don't laugh at me.
Why?
That's not nice, Satomi-kun.
Kou's such a kid.
Yeah.
I'm glad.
Sakuraba-senpai was able to
ask Satomi-san on that date.
It feels a bit different than usual, too.
But...
Yurika, what's with you lately?
You seem unhappy.
You're sighing, too.
I had some people that
I felt finally understood me,
and then now they don't all over again.
I see.
That's too bad.
Satomi-san,
what do you think I'd have to do to
get you to believe I'm a magical girl?
Hm... Well...
I don't think you'd have to do anything.
Huh?
Lately, I've been feeling
like I don't really care if
you're a magical girl or a cosplayer.
What do you mean "don't care"?
I keep telling you to believe me!
I do believe you.
That's precisely the reason.
You protected Sakuraba-senpai
and got hurt over it, right?
I can't really remember when that was.
After I saw that, I stopped caring
whether or not you're really a magical girl.
No matter who you are, you're a good
person who saves other people.
There's not many people who'd throw
away their own life to protect another.
Whether they're a magical
girl or a cosplayer.
That's why if you say you're
magical girl, that's enough for me.
You can do things worthy of that name.
Satomi-san...
That's right.
That's why I looked up to Sakuraba-senpai.
Even if I couldn't be like Nana-san,
if I could be a magical girl
like Sakuraba-senpai...
I am a little worried about
having you use magic, though.
It might be better for you to be a cosplayer.
Sun and rainbows suit you better.
You're so mean, Satomi-san.
So who should I consider you from now on?
I'm Yurika Nijino.
Your classmate, and someone who
stays at your place for free.
No Fear
Hey Kou, let's play a trading card game!
What's that, Matsudaira-sama?
Well, you battle with them!
Rhinoceros Beetle Man
Look at this, I finally got—
Makkenji never learns, does he?
Next Episode: The Earth Empire vs. The Sun Squad