SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
Why can't I do it?
Really.
Noel?
SKY OF THE
RAINY SEASON
QUARTZ RAINBOW
Do you have your wallet?
Yes!
Identification?
Check!
Handkerchief?
Tissue?
Check!
Map?
Compass?
Check!
Instant food?
Helmet?
Check!
Gun?
Huh?
Grenades?
What?!
That was a joke, Kana.
You scared me, jeez.
If you were thinking calmly, you would've caught on.
You're such a bully, Rio.
They've been getting along well lately.
Rio is just like a worried mother.
Here, this is today's list.
Listen up. Today's mission is for you to go downtown and purchase the supplies on that list.
Got it?
Yes ma'am!
Well then, drive safely.
Okay.
Proceeding to depart.
Hurry back!
We're having pot-au-feu for dinner.
She's just like a mother.
Don't take any detours, okay?
This is our first time going into town together, isn't it Noel?
Yes.
But then again,
it's like the first time ever going into town for me.
Amazing!
What's that!
This was completely different during the festival.
Now it's such a calm and quiet town.
Ow-ow-ow...
First was Nue, a roof decoration particular to Trois.
Its purpose is to ward off evil spirits.
Hm?
Next was the fountain.
It's modeled after the Twelfth Archduke of Helvetia,
Akira Arcadia the Second.
We're here.
Ah, from earlier!
Yes.
I drove safely, as I was told.
Ah, thank you! Now I understand.
You know a lot, don't you Noel?
Hey, girls.
You coming in or not? Decide already.
You're messing with business.
You're the granny from the festival.
It's "miss".
Don't be pushy.
You're as stiff as usual, I see.
Well, at least call me Naomi.
Naomi?
So the next shipment is next month?
Yes.
Does she know?
No.
You're all so unusual.
Even though you're soldiers-
E-Excuse me!
W-What is it?
What is that?
You had your eye on it the first time you came here, didn't you?
Do you like it?
Um... M-May I touch it?
Sure.
A-flat.
This is a fish, isn't it? What's it called?
Ah, that's....
It's not a fish.
What? But...
That's a dolphin.
It's more closely related to humans than fish.
It was a marine mammal back when the seas still had life.
The sea? It lived in the sea?
Yes.
It's wonderful.
That old man really does have skill, making stuff like that.
He might not look it, but he's a romanticist.
You know the person who made it?
There's a big factory on the outskirts of town.
All of our glassware comes from there.
I want to see where they made this.
Don't worry.
About what?
We're going there afterwards.
I see, so that glass factory makes a part used in the Takemikazuchi?
Yes. Naomi is also collecting parts from the old era.
But, you really are awesome, Noel.
You can fix that complex machine in a jiffy.
"Jiffy"?
I mean, I have trouble just trying to remember all the trumpet calls.
It's not... a big deal.
Because... machines never betray me.
Noel...
Here you go.
The change is 2,750,000 yen.
Is it really that much?!
Incorrect. It's 2 yen and 75 sen.
Cold as usual, aren't you, Noel.
Your change.
She's right.
Have you been doing the morning calls recently, missy?
Y-Yes, I have.
I'm sorry, I'm still bad at it.
No worries.
I like it. How do I put it...  It's sure to wake me up.
Stare.
It's nothing! I just need to get better soon so I don't bother the townspeople...
That's not fair, Seiya!
Kanata, I-
Catch me if you can!
Ouch...
Ah, I'm sor-
Hah, you ran into someone!
I'm really sorry!
Oh? You girls are...
You're from the festival!
The airhead girl!
I'm glad.
Looks like you're well again.
You murderer!
Seiya! They had nothing to do with your parents.
They're all the same!
I hate all soldiers!
Just get out of here already!
And your crappy bugle irritates me every morning!
Hey, Seiya!
I'm truly sorry.
That was uncalled-for.
I-It's okay.
He's a wartime orphan.
Because of that, he sees all militaries the same way.
Noel....
I'm fine.
It's true that we are soldiers.
That's why...
Noel...
I guess you're right.
We're soldiers, aren't we?
I took the Parador Oath when I enlisted,
and I thought I understood it, but...
Wait, what am I talking about?
It's something I knew from the beginning.
There's no point hesitating about it now, is there?
That's right, I just need to improve in case something happens.
Everyone will be in trouble if there are no trumpet calls.
We're close.
Is that the glass factory?
Yes.
Isn't it amazing, Noel?
I've never seen a building that large before.
So this is also a failure, eh?
Maybe optical aberrations?
I'm pretty sure the refraction is correct.
I-I'm Sorami Kanata, the new recruit!
Nice to meet you!
Sure.
And I'm...
So, how's the timing when the errors occur?
The seek-times don't deviate much.
Closed distortion within the peripherals has decreased somewhat from the last.
Sorry about that.
When the boss talks about work, he thinks of nothing else.
But old man Carl is truly awesome.
He's one of five people in this country who hold the title of Meister.
He's a brilliant artisan.
Once, he won a national competition and got to present his work to the Archduke.
Maria, if you have time to talk, move your hands!
Okay!
Sorry, Boss.
Seriously, I can't take pride in being called a "Meister",
since I can't even get these things to work.
What are those?
The optical sensor lens for the Takemikazuchi.
That is the original.
To repair the Takemikazuchi, I need two identical lenses. So I ordered a reproduction.
But, they don't work.
Even though they're so beautiful?
Other than silicon dioxide as its primary element,
a lens also needs to be infused with additional sodium oxide and magnesium oxide.
This is to correct chromatic and peripheral aberrations.
In other words, it removes distortion in the captured image.
But, we don't know the ratios.
The technology of the past era practically works like magic.
I thought glass was just pretty to look at, but it's quite complicated.
Because Seize has high-quality silica deposits,
several small factories were built to produce glassware.
This was originally one of those small factories.
But, as the war progressed,
demand for glassware with military application increased.
This factory prospered thanks to the war.
Kanata,
I love machines.
Yeah.
But, there are times when machines hurt people.
I'm sure the Takemikazuchi has killed several people in the past.
Do you think machines that have killed people are scary?
Yeah.
But...
I think I fear the people using those machines more than the machines themselves.
Take this trumpet for example, you know how it sounds when I play it.
But when Rio plays it, it sounds so beautiful.
I'm sure tanks are the same way.
Also, Rio let me hear the Takemikazuchi's song the other day.
It could sing such a beautiful song.
I'm sure the Takemikazuchi is a nice tank.
Oh yeah, let's listen to it next-
Noel.
Let her sleep.
She must've pulled an all-nighter again.
She works very hard to fix the Takemikazuchi.
I know.
This girl is a real worker.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have taken the task of making this troublesome part.
Here.
Put this on her.
Thank you very much.
By the way, you two stopped by the Windmill, right?
How's Naomi doing?
Great.
She said the Boss is a wonderful romanticist.
You hear that?
Aren't you glad, Boss?
Sh-Shut up!
Get back to work already!
Ah, he got mad.
Gotta get back to work.
But is the past technology really that awesome?
I guess.
But, the Boss always says this:
"No matter how awesome it is, it was made by a human. There's no way we can't do the same!"
Wouldn't you agree?
Yes.
Well, I want to say yes, but...
I see.
Certainly, your performance is very different from Rio's.
I'm always wondering how I can play just like her.
That's why I'm practicing so hard.
Even my lips are swollen because of it, see?
And yet...
I can't produce the same sound as her no matter how much I try.
I guess I really have no talent.
Missy.
Yessir!
"Talent" is the worst excuse for someone who has given up.
Hand it over.
I may not know much about trumpets,
but newbies do make plenty of mistakes.
Missy, aren't you trying to too hard to produce the sound?
It's not like I'm trying to shape it like this,
the glass is the one that wanted to take this shape.
Thank you very much, old man Carl!
Let the notes resound by themselves...
Morning?
Yeah, it's as if the sun has just come up for that girl.
That girl is a worker too, eh?
It's a good sound.
Sound?
The sound of the glass changes slightly depending on amount and type of impurity.
Though our normal ears may not catch the difference,
one with outstanding hearing should be able to tell them apart.
I will have Kanata check these samples and determine which comes closest in sound.
If I do that, then maybe...
Alright, listen to the voices of these samples, missy!
Yes sir!
Noel has changed a lot since she joined, hasn't she?
You think so?
Yes!
You did it! You did it, Noel!
Thank you.
This is my first time seeing Noel smile.
Pile up the feelings of love and friendship
Performing is also important
I cried happily
I laughed eagerly
But all of them make me alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me why we dance
you just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I want them to echo forever
Speaking endless words touched by love
Our harmony
I can hear our harmony
MOUNTAIN CLIMBING - THE END OF THE WORLD
Next episode: Mountain Climbing - The End of the World
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.