Say...
Something happen?
Not in the least.
If anything, my life's been as boring as watching paint dry.
They say no news is good news,
but I think any news is better than "completely uneventful."
What's the matter, Bro?
Uh, long story short,
nothing happened.
Well, did you know...
What are you, GEICO?
You've always been prone to saying the dumbest things,
but they get even dumber
when you're feeling down.
That so?
Hey...
Did something happen with Yui and Yukino?
Did they say something to you?
Nah, I just thought that might be it.
I see.
So, what did you do?
Isn't it weird to assume
I did something wrong?
Hey, there's always a chance
you messed up unawares.
All right, let's hear it.
You can tell me everything.
Easier said than done.
Nope. Can't think of anything.
Don't be shy, now.
Tell your dear sister all about it.
Drop it already. You're being annoying.
Did you have to say it like that?
How else could I have said it?
I mean, you were being annoying.
Oh? Is that so?
Forget I asked, then.
Sounds good.
I'm leaving. Be sure to
lock up on your way out.
Aight.
See? Something did happen!
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something real
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Mornin'!
Morning.
A world that chose not to change...
A world that wished to maintain the status quo, huh?
Good morning, Hachiman.
Yo. Morning.
What's up?
N-Nothing.
Just surprised that you greeted me like normal.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Situation normal.
So bitter...
Also, did you hear that the crepe place by the station is like, super delish?
Really?
Let's go sometime, Yukinon!
Sure.
The chocolate banana's the best—
So you came.
Guess I did.
By the way, everyone was acting normal, right?
Well, uh...
They all...
Yeah.
There didn't seem to be anything wrong, from what I could see.
Well, that's good to hear.
I was actually, like, nervous about what'd happen,
but I guess I had nothing to worry about, huh?
They were all... the same as ever...
I'm not sure I understand them anymore.
We've never been able to understand their thinking.
Knowing each other is one thing,
but understanding is an altogether different matter.
Well, let's not get too hung up on it.
Carrying on like normal would be the best thing to do, no?
We should act normal, too?
Yeah...
"Normal," huh?
So, that's what you consider normal?
You're saying you won't change, aren't you?
You're...
Um...
Yukinon!
H-Hey...
I'm coming in.
I've got a job for you guys.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
What do you need?
Oh, yeah. Come in.
We'd like your help on something.
Shiromeguri...
Iroha!
Oh, hey, Yui!
Yo, 'sup?
Long time no see!
Candidate for student council president?
Yeah.
I bet you're thinking I don't look the part.
Not really.
I get that a lot, so I can tell.
People call me slow or thickheaded all the time.
Well, is there a problem?
Isshiki here is running for president,
but uh, like,
we'd rather she didn't win.
Er...
Does that mean you don't want to be student council president?
That's right.
Then why run?
The thing is,
I didn't volunteer for the post.
People entered me without asking.
Huh? What is she, an idol?
I stand out in a bad way, I guess?
But yeah, she seems like she'd be hated by the other girls.
I'm the soccer team's manager and
get along with Hayama and the gang,
Reminds me of a certain
someone from junior high.
so I think I built up an image
without realizing it.
A girl with guys in the palm of her hand,
playing with them like a juggler and her props.
I have to say, that would be quite the elaborate prank.
I'm pretty sure you need at least 30
nominations to become a candidate.
That's a lot!
I'm amazed you got that many.
I'll give the culprits a good talking to, of course.
If you don't want the post,
just lose the election.
What else is there?
Well, nothing, but the problem is that Isshiki's the only candidate right now.
That means she'd need a vote of no confidence.
But losing one would make me look super lame!
Oh, do you know who's giving your campaign speech yet?
No.
That makes things simple, then.
Uh, what do you mean?
Basically, we just need a way to make Isshiki lose the election,
or in the worst-case scenario, lose a vote of no confidence, without losing face, right?
In other words, people just need to know that she wasn't the reason she lost.
But is that even possible?
If she loses a vote of no confidence due to an awful campaign speech, nobody'll hold it against her.
And who'll make that speech?
That doesn't sound very nice.
Well...
Anyone who's willing and able should do.
I can't approve of such a method.
And why's that?
That's because...
It's not a sure thing.
Besides, a speech bad enough to cause a vote of no confidence
will cause problems for Isshiki.
And even if she does lose that motion,
do you really think there'd be a re-election?
Also...
People don't care about the student council.
Nobody'd mind if we withheld the vote tallies and just announced the results.
So if we want, there are any number of—
Yukinoshita.
I take it back. That was inappropriate of me.
I think we have no choice but to back a different candidate and have them win.
If someone actually wanted the post,
wouldn't they have announced
their candidacy already?
But hey, we could ask people who seem like they'd do it.
Doesn't look like we're gonna reach a conclusion here.
Let's try again some another day.
Okay.
Ms. Hiratsuka.
Do you have a moment?
Who's winning as of now?
Winning what?
The battle to decide which of us is better equipped to serve others and solve their problems.
The winner can order the loser to do anything they want.
That was a thing?
R-Right!
Well, you've been working together most of the time.
You're all doing very well.
If you want to know where you three stand relative to one another,
I could give you my judgmental and prejudiced evaluation.
That's fine.
If we go by results over all else,
Hikigaya's one step ahead.
If we take the process and
long-term vision into account,
Yukinoshita comes out on top.
All said and done, though,
Yuigahama's contributions also seem vital to keeping this club afloat.
So there's no clear victor yet?
That'd be the implication, yes.
That means it's not a problem if our opinions differ, am I right?
Huh? What do you mean?
That there's no need for him
and I to pick the same methods.
Damn straight.
Forcing ourselves to compromise would be pointless.
What's going to happen to club activities while you sort things out?
Members can participate if they wish.
I guess that's reasonable.
I thought we both hated superficiality more than anything.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
All right.
If you say so.
You're a nice guy,
and there's no shortage of people you've helped.
Why would you say that?
I may not look it, but I'm rather prone to favoritism.
And you call yourself a teacher?
My policy is to praise students to help them grow.
You sure don't act like it.
But that doesn't mean I don't scold them.
And if you stick to your ways,
you won't be able to help somebody
when you most want to.
New message
Komachi
Inbox
Totsuka Saika
Saika here
Thank you very much.
Now, there's a face you don't see often.
Hey, no need to run away.
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
How rude.
Hikigaya.
Yes?
Tell me something interesting.
Love that super-annoyed reaction!
You always deliver!
Is Yukino doing all right?
She's the same as ever.
Good to hear.
So, have you made any progress?
Huh?
Didn't you go on a school trip?
You sure are awfully well-informed.
We got a delivery of souvenirs.
She used a courier?
I guess she didn't want to meet.
And yet she buys you souvenirs?
Talk about dedicated.
You're probably way off the mark.
She hates us, but she doesn't want us to hate her in turn.
Anyway, now that all the major events are done and dusted,
I suppose you'll be focusing on your entrance exams?
Aren't you bored?
Not really.
There's still stuff like the student council election.
Oh, right.
Meguri's finally retiring, huh?
Knowing her, I bet she asked Yukino to succeed her.
Actually, she didn't.
What? That's boring.
So Yukino won't be student council president?
Nope.
Uh, what about it?
Well, it's just that I was never president either.
How lame.
Huh? Hikigaya?
Whoa! It's been ages! Did I just draw an ultra-rare card?
Orimoto?
I always thought junior high classmates would stay buried in the darkest depths of my memories,
but Orimoto Kaori's name came to me all too easily.
Wait, you go to Soubu High?
Y-Yeah.
Smart guy, huh? News to me!
Well, you were practically mute,
so I'm sure it's news to everybody.
Your girlfriend?
Nah.
Figures. I knew she was out of your league.
Why am I forcing a smile?
Gross.
Is she a friend?
Is it just me, or did that question sound more like "Whoa, you had friends"?
Just a classmate from junior high.
I'm Orimoto Kaori.
Oh, I'm Yukinoshita Haruno.
I'm Hikigaya's—
Say...
What exactly am I to you?
Don't ask me.
Calling us friends would be weird, right?
Your big sis?
How about we pick the middle option and say I'm your girlfriend?
Let's just go with high school alumnus.
Aw, you're no fun.
You went to the same junior high as Hikigaya, huh?
Got any interesting stories?
What?
I wanna hear about Hikigaya's love life!
Oh, that reminds me.
He asked me out before!
No way!
Tell me more.
We hadn't talked at all before then,
so it was a real shocker!
We had.
We even texted each other.
Whether it was out of pity or whatever, she gave me her number.
I used all kinds of dumb excuses to text her,
and waited with bated breath for replies that may or not come.
But I'm sure she has no clue
about it, let alone remembers.
You asked a girl out?
It's all in the past now.
Yeah. It was a long time ago,
so who cares now, right?
Oh, yeah!
If you're in Soubu High, do you know a guy named Hayama?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
For real?
Chika, you could get him to introduce you!
I think I'll pass.
Look, we're not friends.
Thought as much. You two are like apples and oranges, anyway.
This could be amusing.
All right!
I'll introduce you.
Oh, Hayato? Can you come see me right now?
Actually, just come.
I'm at the donuts place near the station.
What in the world do you think you're doing?
See you later, Hayama!
I'll text you!
Holy smokes! He's such a cool guy!
Why'd you do this?
It sounded amusing.
That again?
And why was he involved? I would've
thought it had nothing to do with him.
You'd be surprised.
Apparently Hikigaya used to like the girl with the curly hair!
I'd love to see the look on Yukino's face if she ever hears about this.
Well, that was a nice way to kill some time.
I'll be leaving, then.
Thanks for hanging out with me, Hikigaya.
Later.
Haruno must like you.
Are you stupid?
She's just messing with me.
She wouldn't mess with people
she had no interest in.
Instead, she'd just ignore them.
She either smothers the ones she likes,
or destroys the ones she hates.
That's scary as hell.
M-Morning.
'Sup.
Will you come to the clubroom today?
Nah, I'm not planning on it.
Th-Thought so.
So, uh, we decided to discuss things with Iroha
and come up with some kinda strategy,
but I didn't want it to look like we were doing it behind your back...
Well, I guess I could drop by and listen.
It's been so long since Yukinoshita
and I were last in direct opposition,
but nothing's changed since then.
Once again, she'll reject my way of doing things,
but if nothing's changed,
then it's perfectly fine by me.
You came!
Let's begin.
For starters, the best possible outcome would be if someone else runs for president,
and you lose to them fair and square in the election.
I agree.
Oh, but I'd prefer to lose to someone amazing.
We thought up our candidate's election pledge and speech.
The fact that you're coming up with the election pledge
would mean that the candidate would be a total puppet.
Are you okay with that?
Assuming they get elected, what happens to the student council's operations once they do?
Th-That's why we'll look for someone who can handle all that.
That'll make things even harder.
If you consider future complications, this plan seems bad and pointless.
What point is there to your methods, then?
In this scenario, she can avoid the worst possible outcome.
And once she loses the vote of no confidence, she can withdraw from the re-election—
"In this scenario"?
No. That's wrong.
You've always been avoiding the problem at hand.
And? Did it cause any problems?
Weren't you the one who called such superficiality meaningless?
You don't intend to change?
Nope.
H-Hey...
Guys...
I'm going home.
Silently,
Yukinoshita Yukino Makes Her Decision.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
And Yuigahama Yui Makes Her Declaration.
Hey!
Is this gonna work out?
I'd feel much more at ease if a capable person ran against me, but...
I guess you'd need someone like Hayama, then.
No Hayama!
Well, I'll figure something out
if worst comes to worst.
That's a relief!
Nobody's willing to help me out.
You guys are my only hope.
I should get to practice.
I'm counting on you!