Whenever I wish for someone to be happy, someone else has to suffer as much.
That's what it means to be a Puella Magi.
I'm such an idiot.
Sayaka!
What's that? Just what the hell are you?!
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Get back.
Hold on.
What are you...?
Just do it!
She's...
If you let go of me, time will stop for you too.
Be careful.
What's going on?
Where did that witch come from?!
That is Sayaka Miki.
You have seen it yourself, haven't you?
Are we running away?
Drop that useless burden if you want to come along.
Let's kill that witch.
Can you do it?
Are you mental?!
You'll just be a hindrance with that.
Get out of here for now.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 9     I won't allow that
Sayaka!
Sayaka! What's wrong?
Where is her Soul Gem? What happened to her?
Her Soul Gem turned into a Grief Seed. She became a witch and died.
You're kidding... right?
It's the truth.
That's the final secret of the Soul Gems.
When the gem gets tainted and turns black,
we become Grief Seeds
and turn into witches.
That's the unavoidable fate of all who become Puella Magi.
It's not true... Tell me it's not... Please!
That's... Why?!
She wanted to protect people from witches...
She wanted to become a hero of justice...
That's the kind of Puella Magi she wanted to be...
And yet...
She took the burden of the curse equal to that wish.
She will live on now causing suffering just as much as she was helping others earlier.
You! Who the hell are you?!
Are you showing off how you know what's going on?!
How can you talk so cold?!
She's Sayaka's...
She's her best friend!
Do you understand now?
The truth behind what you admired so much.
You carried the body out, but be careful with it.
It can cause us trouble if you get rid of it carelessly.
Are you even human?!
Of course not.
And neither are you.
May I come in? I have something to tell you.
So you're still alive.
Is it true what Homura said?
What she said is not incorrect.
So you try to turn us into Puella Magi so that we'd then mature into witches?
Please don't misunderstand.
It's not like we hold a grudge against humanity or anything.
It is all for the sake of this world we all live in.
Madoka, do you know what the word "entropy" means?
Let me give you a simple example.
The heat you get from a campfire isn't equal to the energy that's needed for that wood to grow.
Some energy is lost when it changes form.
The energy of this universe is slowly diminishing,
so we were looking for energy that wasn't bound by thermodynamics.
And that's when we discovered the magic of the Puella Magi.
Just... What are you...?
Our culture developed the technology
that converts the emotions of conscious life forms into energy.
Unfortunately, our species is incapable of what you call emotions.
So we evaluated many other species in this universe,
and finally found you, humans.
If you consider the population and emotional power of humans,
the emotional energy that one person generates
increases as that person grows.
Your souls are an energy source that counters entropy.
And above all,
the fluctuation of hope and grief in girls in their second growth phase is the most effective.
When your souls burn out in the Soul Gems and turn into Grief Seeds,
they emit immense amounts of energy.
It is our, the Incubators' job to collect that energy.
So we're just... expendables?
Are you saying we should just die for you?
Do you know how many cultures exist in this universe, consuming energy every moment?
Sometime in the future you humans will leave this planet and join us, too.
It wouldn't be nice if the universe was dying by that time, would it?
If you think about it, it's not such a bad trade-off!
Don't say that.
Because of your stupid reason, Mami died and Sayaka ended up like that...
It's... it's too cruel!
But we're making the contract only if you agree to it.
Isn't that kind enough for you?
You've just been tricking us!
We can't understand what it means "to trick" to begin with.
When you regret a wrong decision based on a misunderstanding,
you humans tend to hate the other party for some reason.
I can't keep up with what you're saying.
I can't understand it at all.
It's hard for us to understand the value standards of humans.
Your population is six billion nine hundred million right now,
and it's still growing by ten every four seconds.
So why do you make such a big fuss over the loss of just one of you?
If that's how you think, you really are our enemy.
I came to explain it all to you.
I wanted you to understand what greater good your sacrifices serve.
It's not working out, is it.
Of course not!
Madoka, sometime in the future,
you shall become the strongest Puella Magi...
And then turn into the strongest witch.
When that happens, we'll be able to get immense amounts of energy.
If you feel like dying for this universe, just call us.
We'll be waiting!
What do you plan to achieve by maintaining the heat in that body?
Is there any way to get back her Soul Gem?
None, as far as I know.
So, there might be one that you don't know?
The existence of Puella Magi itself is against reason.
I won't be surprised no matter what improbable actions you take.
So it's possible.
There's no precedent. So I don't know of any way either.
Unfortunately reason doesn't apply to you.
Who needs that.
As if we'd accept your help!
Madoka, you look so pale this morning. Are you all right?
Yeah... It's just that I didn't sleep enough.
And Sayaka is staying home today, too?
Should I go visit her later?
But would it really be all right to go see her?
We aren't on very good terms right now...
Hitomi... You know...
After all that happened yesterday,
how can you go to school as if nothing happened?
Madoka?
We have to talk. Would you come along?
Hitomi, sorry, but I'm skipping school today too!
Huh? But... Madoka! Wait!
What did you want to talk about?
Do you want to save Sayaka Miki?
Can we save her?
Or would you just leave her like that?
Sorry about that...
You might think I'm stupid,
but I don't want to give up until we're sure if we can save her or not.
She turned into a witch, but she might remember her friends' voices...
If we talked to her, she might remember the time she was human...
I think you're the one who could do that.
Do you think it'll work?
How should I know?
That's why I want to try it.
Like, if we cut that witch in half,
maybe Sayaka's Soul Gem would fall out instead of a Grief Seed or something...
It'd be like a story where love and courage win, right?
When I thought about it, I realized that I became a Puella Magi because I love those stories.
Even though I totally forgot about it,
Sayaka reminded me of it.
I won't force you to come along.
What we're going to do is dangerous.
I can't promise that I'll be able to protect you no matter what.
I'll help you. Please let me help!
I'm Madoka Kaname.
Seriously, you're too nice.
I'm Kyoko Sakura. Nice to meet you.
Excuse me! I don't feel well. May I go to the nurse's office?
Who's the health representative in this class?
Kaname hasn't come to school today.
Then the class rep should go with...
Will Homura help too?
I doubt it.
Isn't she your friend?
Not really.
It's more like we joined up to defeat enemies we couldn't take down alone.
A few days from now, a Walpurgis Night will come to this city.
Walpurgis?
It's an insanely powerful witch.
Neither of us would be able to defeat it alone, probably.
That's why... Well, that's the kind of allies we are.
This is it.
Is it really Sayaka? And not some other witch?
It's the same magical pattern as yesterday.
It's her for sure.
Now, I ask you one last time.
Are you sure?
I kinda got used to it...
I was always just following behind... I could never really help...
But please, take me along!
You really are a strange one.
Hey, Kyoko...
Huh?
I never do anything... The others always fight for me. Am I a coward?
Is that why you think you should become a Puella Magi?
I wonder...
Don't underestimate it. This is not a job just anyone could do.
But...
Someone, who spends every day surrounded by a happy family,
who has such a convenient life...
I wouldn't let someone like that to become a Puella Magi just because she thinks she should.
I'd beat her to a pulp.
Only those who have no choice should put their lives on the line.
If someone else does it, it's just a game.
They'll just be screwing around.
I wonder...
There might come a time when you'll have to fight no matter what.
You should save those thoughts for when it happens.
Kyoko, you...
She knows we're here.
Here it comes!
Okay? Do just as we agreed.
Sayaka, it's me! Madoka!
Can you hear me?
Do you recognize my voice?
Don't be afraid. Continue calling out to her!
Sayaka, stop! Please, remember!
This isn't what you wanted!
You wanted to be a hero of justice!
Please, return to your old self, Sayaka!
So you're not listening?
Kyoko!
I'm fine. I'm not even breaking a sweat.
You should continue calling her.
Stop! Please stop!
Sayaka! Hear us!
Are you just returning what you got back then?
I remember... At first we were fighting to kill each other...
I thought you were too soft...
No matter how much I beat you, you always stood up.
You're angry, right?
You feel like you can't forgive?
I understand...
Just wake up after you've had enough of this to satisfy you.
Sayaka...
Please... I beg you.
Sayaka!
You said you believed in it!
That you could use this power to make people happy!
Please, God... If this is how my life ends...
Let me see a happy dream at least once!
Kyoko!
No... You...
Please take care of her.
I was stupid enough to bring her along.
We can't fight and take care of hindrances at the same time, right?
It's all right. That's the answer.
Just protect the one thing you really want to protect, until the very end.
Heh... And here I thought that's what I was doing until now...
Go.
I'll handle this.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
It sucks to be alone...
It's okay. I'll be beside you... Sayaka.
Kyoko...
Akemi Homura
Kyoko Sakura really wished to save Sayaka Miki.
That's foolish! It's obviously impossible!
Then why didn't you stop her?
Of course if it was a needless sacrifice, I would've stopped her.
But her fall had a greater meaning.
Now you're the only Puella Magi left to face the Walpurgis.
And not even you would stand a chance alone.
To protect this city, Madoka must become a Puella Magi.
I won't let that happen.
Akemi Homura
Artist Namaniku ATK (Nitro+)
No one believes in the future.
No one can face the future.
Episode 10     I can't depend on anyone anymore.
I can't depend on anyone anymore.