The Dollars?
That's the angel who shouts, "Pipirupirupiru,"
flying through the sky, panties showing.
Don't use too much.
If she doesn't wake up,
they take it from our pay.
We don't know much about
the Dollars, either.
I'll tell you what we know, though.
Seems they're a color gang,
but no one knows what color, etc.
Dengeki Bunko just released
their latest publishing run.
Ten more for other stuff.
"Other" stuff.
You're not getting away!
Turning right!
A man needs testicular fortitude.
Haven't done something like this since we
joined the Dollars, have we, Kadota-san?
Sit your ass down.
The Dollars aren't an angel who flies
through the air, panties showing,
shouting, "Pipirupirupiru,"
are they, Dotachin?
Don't call me that!
OK. We got rid of them.
That's insane!
Damn it!
Now then, let's have a chat
about those human experiments
you're involved with.
I'm Kadota Kyouhei.
Actually, I don't like being
called Dotachin.
This all began eight hours ago.
Active
Interest
What I'm about to tell you
is the famous Kazutawno incident.
It was a classmate of mine who vanished.
A friend of a friend, to be precise, but...
I'd never met them.
A friend of yours vanished, Tanaka Tarou-san?
Lately, a lot of people have
been disappearing.
Lots of rumored missing persons cases.
You love rumors, Kanra-san.
The rumors I've heard say
that the girls who disappeared
ran away from home to the big city
or were illegal aliens.
In other words, people who wouldn't leave
any traces if they vanished.
A lot of them are going missing
between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
And once they vanish, they're
never found again.
Really?
There are even scarier rumors, too.
The reason they're never found is because
the Dollars are eating the disposed-of bodies.
Digging the rusted sign!
Is this the hunting spot the
information broker mentioned?
Sure looks like you'd see
a lot of illegal aliens here.
OK, let's get to work earning that cash!
Kazutawno!
Oh, teenage girls!
Twenty percent bonus.
Nah, let's stick with the usual today.
If we get greedy,
you-know-who might show up.
The Headless Rider?
For today, let's just go with this one.
What's up?
You don't think he's broken somewhere?
Well, it's human.
Well, the middle-aged man has some wear and tear,
so we should expect a discounted price.
Hey.
Hi there, seeds of life.
I'mma Japanese! Same as you!
But'cha know, people always
says I look foreign!
I'zo sad!
Sometimes they pick on me, ya know?
I don't think we can sell this one.
What the hell does "I'zo sad" mean?
So like, without a younger-brother type
helper-fairy character like Yuuta,
he's just a masochistic wolf
with a hair fetish.
He's just a younger-brother type,
a cross-dresser.
I'd prefer a younger-sister
type helper-fairy.
Or an older sister.
Don't talk about that shit
when we're eating, OK?
Dotachin, let's get some food!
Food, food!
OK.
Man! This is sweet, Kadota-san.
The toilet's bigger than my room.
I'm told the concept is a "quality cabaret
club, offering a quiet evening."
We should get going.
This day only comes once a month.
Yeah.
Who is it?
Kazutawno.
"Sara wareta (I broke a plate.)"
So buy him a new one.
Time to hit the dollar store!
I'm Japanese!
You think maybe it was supposed to be
"sarawareta (kidnapped)"?
No way.
Shut up!
Get him to shut up already!
On it.
It's cheap!
It's fresh!
So you heard that rumor, too, Sonohara-san?
Yes.
It's OK!
The whole thing's BS.
That's right.
Harima-san just disappeared.
We don't know that she was kidnapped.
I'm sure she wasn't kidnapped
and then killed...
Ever heard of a thing called "tact"?
Screwed the pooch there.
Here you go. Nigiri-sushi for three.
It's OK.
Our sushi's made out of fish.
No human, even on half-price day!
However...
We're still talking about this?
Simon!
Your banner outside's broke!
The banner?
Yes, the banner!
Let's go fix it! OK?
Yeah!
Let's fix it!
It's true!
The corner sushi shop uses
human meat on half-price day!
The banner!
Scary!
Togusa-san, wanna turn your car into
an itasha using anime decals?
I love itasha!
You want to die?
Itasha, Italian cars, are expensive,
since they're not domestic.
I'll take mantis shrimp from Setouchi!
I'll have amberjack and
striped horsemackeral.
That was dangerous!
Sure was.
What kind of idiot spills a whole bottle?
And on himself...
It's no good. I'm too tired...
Don't fall asleep till we
drop off the goods.
This is bad. Bad...
M-My eyelids!
Look up front!
Excuse me...
What?
He's why you're sleepy.
Throw him away somewhere,
and you'll get better.
Kazutawno, brought you some sushi!
Hey! Brought you an old plate
from Russian Sushi, too.
Ah! What the hell?
That email wasn't about breaking a plate.
It was about a bowl!
Dotachin.
"Simple kanji converter."
Kazutawno...
He was kidnapped by the Manhunters.
We'll never see him again.
How am I supposed to live without Kazutawno?
How can I live without him?!
We all understood how important
Kazutawno was to Togusa.
No one could replace him.
Not that it didn't make Karisawa,
Yumasaki, or me a little sad.
If he was kidnapped when that
email came, it wasn't that long ago.
We'll find him before they drop him off,
and we'll bring him back.
But how?
I know!
I saw their car!
Hasim!
He's here!
The ultimate younger-brother type
helper-fairy character!
Once, in the town of El Paso, Texas,
there was an alien autopsy facility!
All right, if we find them,
get the inside foreigner out.
Our team of intrepid reporters succeeded
in finding a man who had worked there!
We don't know when they're
gonna hand him over,
In 1995, I first heard about it
from a buddy in the military.
so I want to rescue him
as soon as possible.
OK, black van, right.
You know the plate number?
Yeah, got a pen?
At the time, I was working at a nearby building,
when they hired me for my skills and...
Gimme a sec.
OK, ready.
Thanks, Hasim.
Yeah.
Can you eat sushi?
Yeah!
See you!
This has wasabi?
It's got wasabi, yeah.
Don't worry, Russian wasabi isn't spicy.
Don't lie to the kid.
Let's go.
OK!
Black van, OK?
Here's the number.
Take care!
They're subcontractors for
some evil corporation.
You can call them underlings.
They kidnap people who won't be missed
and then hand them over to their bosses.
The kidnapped people are probably being
used as "materials" for all kinds of things.
It's like cannibalism.
This month, the subcontractors
aren't turning in much.
Yes. Recently, the materials
have gotten cautious-
I don't need any excuses.
Fire the subcontractors who
can't get their numbers up.
But...
Or would you rather be
the material yourself?
You can leave.
Seiji...
Tissues
Light bulb 60w
Coffee
You idiot!
We looked everywhere for the black
van that kidnapped Kazutawno,
certain we would find and save him.
I tried everything I could think of,
but we found nothing.
I was getting nervous.
Would I never hear those
words from him again?
Those words from my childhood,
which I thought I'd never hear
again, after I grew up.
Tickets:
Selling
Buying
Got tickets?
We got tickets!
Yes, Kazutawno was the
last of a dying breed.
And it was through him that
Togusa gained the greatest happiness
of his entire life...
Togusa's eternal goddess: Hijiribe Ruri.
A goddess to whom he offered his
complete and unrequited love.
Kazutawno was his wizard,
who brought him front
row seats for concerts
when even normal tickets
were impossible to get.
I have to save him for Togusa's sake.
Dotachin, what are you talking about?
And with whom?
Nothing...
I was thinking, why don't we call his cell?
We might be able to negotiate with them.
Sushi love!
I love fatty tuna.
Who the hell is this?
Oh, hey! It's Dotachin!
I was just walking along,
and someone was sleeping.
Their phone was ringing, so I answered it.
Where am I?
Near the entrance to the Taishouken
in south Ikebukuro.
But Russian Sushi's running
a promotion today.
Izaya!
Stay the hell out of Ikebukuro!
Whoops. Shizu-chan found me.
See ya!
Izaya!
Wake up!
Wake up, damn it!
Hey, wake up!
Wake up, damn you!
Put those away.
He's not waking up.
But if we don't hurry, Kazutawno's...
That's right.
If they hand him over, he'll be killed!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to have his friends tell us
where they're meeting up.
It's almost time.
The higher-ups will be coming,
so keep an eye out.
I'm Japaneze! You need ta realize!
Are you still going on about that?
So it says "Japanese" on your
birth certificate, right?
That's the thing.
It was lost during the air raids!
How old are you?
Yes?
Hey, it's me.
Oh, Kanasawa. You awake?
Sorry. I'm on my way.
Where was the hand-over place, anyway?
Man, you idiot! OK...
We rock so hard! We did it!
Who are you?
We're the Dollars!
Dollars?
And don't you forget it!
I'm so tired. So tired...
Our entry into the Dollars was
a truly simple matter.
Togusa, Yumasaki and Karisawa just
started hanging out with me.
I don't know what they see in a
guy like me. Weird group...
One day, I got an email on my cell.
"Do you want to join the Dollars?
There aren't rules or restrictions.
Just say you're part of the Dollars."
It was a weird invitation.
People had been talking
about how the Dollars
were a bit odd, for a while now.
But when I agreed to try it,
I was sent a URL and
password the next day.
I logged in, and my nick was displayed
on the Dollars site.
No one, including me,
has ever seen the leader.
There are a number of smaller
organizations within,
each a part of a larger
vertical hierarchy.
But for some reason,
no one knows who's on top.
Since there isn't a top, I don't feel
like I'm working for someone.
But I'd be lying if I said I didn't wonder
who had created this strange system.
Between you and me,
I've got my suspicions.
That asshole who started
calling me "Dotachin."
Fatty tuna for the win.
That's not where you'll find
what you're looking for.
Nerima 502
I'm sorry, Celty...
How much you think we'll get for him?
Probably not much.
Yeah, probably not.
Is that the boss?
Yeah, probably.
What the hell?
Kazutawno!
Kazutawno, we're coming for you!
It won't be that easy!
How presumptuous!
Wow, lame dialogue.
What does "presumptuous" mean, anyway?
Th-The Headless Rider!
But we took an old man,
even though it meant losing money!
We won't do it anymore! We won't!
What?
Kazutawno!
Dotachiwno!
They're escaping!
You're not getting away!
Turning right!
I wonder if I can go home.
Now then, you should probably tell us where
you're dropping off your "goods."
No, it's no fun if we don't
get to torture them.
Pick a book.
We'll torture you the way
the book describes.
"Bludgeoning Angel Dokuro-chan"
"Ladies x Butlers"
Guys, you can have your fun, but don't use
any gasoline inside the car this time.
Gaso-
Tokusawno!
Time for the morning ritual!
Milk
We'll talk!
We will!
Yagiri Pharma, huh?
They're pretty big, huh?
Is this really where they're doing
the human experimentations?
We didn't really believe it,
at least not from looking at its front.
But everything's usually got both
a front and a hidden side.
And there's stuff hidden here in Ikebukuro
that would blow your mind.
OK, let's get some food.
Yeah.
Go for morning breakfast at Russian Sushi!
OK!
Let's go!
All right! Then it's decided!
Use as much money, any way you like.
Thank you, Sis.
Bye, Seiji.
Let's go.
That's the story of the famous
Kazutawno incident.
Well, today we're just glad
our friend's back safely.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Bad-ass
Dude
Shut up, shut up! Damn, you piss me off.
When I can't contain my anger, my body moves on its own,
regardless of what will happen to me.
Next time:
Bad-ass Dude.
But I hate violence!