Every day, I've been secretly doing good deeds
tengoku iku tame mainichi kosotto
so that I will eventually go to heaven
naishou de ii koto shiteta kedo
But right now, my tears are falling
namida hitohira
and my head is spinning
atama kurakura
That girl is a veteran love thief,
anoko hasuppa koidorobou
while I'm just a nice and likable girl
watashi kenage ii hito
My love is unfulfilled
kanawanakatta koigokoro
Why is it so, God?
kamisama dou shite
I've got to forgive that love thief
yurusanakucha koidorobou
because she is probably a nice girl
anoko tabun ii hito
I've got to forget about all of this
wasurenakucha konna koto
because I'm the heaven
watashi wa tengoku
I've got to forgive
yurusanakucha