I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but a sudden situation changed everything.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
Different feelings and words that won't connect...
Is fighting the only thing we can
do to make them connect?
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
I'm sure that meeting was just a coincidence.
But if you layer an endless amount of
coincidences on top of one another...
...I'm sure people pick one at random,
and that becomes the path they travel.
At least, that's how I believe people live.
My life seems to have recently started
with a coincidence like that.
That's why I feel that I want to keep going
like this, believing I've made no mistakes.
Of my own free will... and with my own feelings.
This is Like a Town of Hot Water,
the Uminari Hot Springs!
Now then! In Japan, the whole country celebrates
a long series of consecutive holidays.
Though our coffee shop, Midoriya, is exempt from this.
But during the holidays and stuff, we leave our
shop in the hands of the other employees...
...and go on a big family vacation.
This time, we're going with my best friends.
Onii-chan and his girlfriend,
Tsukimura Shinobu-san, are also going with us.
And the maids who work for the Tsukimura
household are also with us today.
For two days, we'll be relaxing at a hot spring inn
that's said to alleviate the stress of our daily life.
For the Takamachi family, our plans are
always the same for vacations like this.
Look, look! It's so green out here!
Really!
Nanoha.
Nanoha, you have to at least rest and take
things at a nice, slow pace on vacation.
I know.
I'll be fine.
The black mage I met last week...
Having not been able to find even
one Jewel Seed since then...
Because I've been dwelling on things, I've decided
to take a good, long rest from everything for a bit...
...and Yuuno-kun also recommended it...
It's so big!
Yeah!
For the next two days, I'm going to try
to relax and act like a normal kid.
I think I'm going to play as much
as I possibly can while I'm here!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No problem. Shall we go?
Yuuno-kun, have you ever been in a hot spring before?
A-Ah, umm...
If you count a public bathhouse
as a hot spring, then yes, but...
Hot springs are really nice!
R-R-Really...?
N-Nanoha... really, I think I...
Umm... really, I think I'd better go into the guys'
bath with Kyouya-san and Shiro-san...
Huh? It'll be fine! Let's go in together!
Ah! Fantastic!
This is amazing! It's so spacious!
This sure is impressive.
Truly!
Onee-chan, I'll scrub your back for you!
Thank you, Suzuka.
Me too!
Thank you.
Then I get to wash yours!
Don't worry! I'm good at washing.
Vacations like this are so nice, don't you think?
Yeah, they are.
And we can leave our shop to
those kids working there, too.
And our children are clearly full of spirit.
And... so are you.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Quite a bit of time has passed, huh?
Yes.
Well... you and the kids don't need
to worry about me anymore.
From now on, I'll only be the Midoriya's owner.
Yes... thank you, dear...
Here you are.
Thanks.
But you're not supposed to be working today, Noel,
so it's okay to take a rest from all that.
Yes, thank you, I will be sure
to rest myself while I'm here.
Well then, Onee-chan, Shinobu-san,
we'll be leaving now!
Okay!
Nanoha-chan, Alisa and I are
going to go explore the inn.
Okay. See you later.
All right! Here we go, Yuuno!
That felt so good!
Yeah.
Now that we're out of the hot spring,
wanna go play ping pong?
Huh? Ping pong?
I wanted to check out the souvenirs they're selling...
Umm...
Ping-pong...
Hmm, what should we do?
Which should we do first?
Why don't we do rock-paper-scissors to decide?
Hi, little girls!
Was it you? The one she was talking about?
You don't look too smart or too strong...
You look like some normal little runt to me.
Nanoha, do you know this woman?
N-No...
It seems my friend doesn't know
you! Who might you be?
Sorry, sorry!
I think I have the wrong person!
It's because she looks like someone I know.
Oh... so that's it...
That sure is a cute ferret you have!
Yeah.
There, there. Pet, pet...
This is just a simple greeting.
Let me warn you in advance.
Children should be good little kids, and play elsewhere.
If you get in our way too much, I'll swallow you whole.
Now then, I think I'll go take another bath.
Nanoha...
Yeah...
Nanoha-chan...
Y-Yeah...
What the heck was with that woman?!
Umm... she sure was unique, huh?
Was she drunk?! And in the middle of the day, too!
Disgusting!
Alisa-chan...
Now, now... this place is supposed to relax people...
...so there's bound to be lots of different types here.
Even so, there's something known as
moderation, you know! Moderation!
Ah... hello? Fate?
Arf here.
Yeah...
I checked her out. The girl in white you mentioned.
I see... what did you think?
Well...
She didn't look like a big deal to me.
She's not a worthy enemy, Fate.
Is that so?
I've made a bit of progress here, too.
I've been able to pinpoint the general
location of the next Jewel Seed.
I think we'll be able to capture it tonight.
Nice, Fate! I expected nothing less from my master!
Thank you, Arf. Let's meet again this evening.
Okay!
So relaxing...
Oh, they came out.
Oh no!
I wonder if this would be all right?
And they all lived happily ever after.
Oh, Farin-chan. Are the children asleep already?
Yes, Momoko-san. They're all sound asleep.
Thank you so much, Farin-chan.
Not at all, I like doing things like this.
Yuuno-kun. Are you awake?
Y-Yeah.
I wonder if the person we met this afternoon
is related to the girl we met last week...?
Probably.
I wonder if things will turn out like they did last time...
Probably...
Nanoha, I've been doing a lot of thinking since then.
Really, from here on out, I think it'd be best if I...
Stop!
If you say anything else, I'll get mad.
"I think it'd be best if I worked alone. I don't
want you involved in this anymore, Nanoha."
...is what you were planning to say, wasn't it?
Yeah...
Gathering the Jewel Seeds... at first, I was doing
it to help you out, but that's different now.
It's something I'm doing because I want to do it.
If you said you'd leave me behind and go
off to do it on your own, I'd get angry.
Yeah.
Now let's go to sleep.
Something else might happen tonight.
Yeah.
Bingo! Found it, Fate!
Nanoha!
It'll be fine. Let's hurry, Yuuno-kun!
Raising Heart, please!
Stand by, Ready. Set up.
This thing sure is amazing.
So this is the power of a Lost Logia?
Though this one's unstable, so its power is incomplete.
I wonder why your mother wants them so badly?
Who knows? I don't, but that doesn't matter.
I must get them because my mother wants them.
Bardiche! Awaken!
Yes, sir.
Sealing Form, Set up.
I'm going to seal it. Arf, support me.
Sure, sure.
That's...!
This makes two...
My, oh my. My, my, my.
Didn't I tell you earlier that you
should be a good little kid?
That... Jewel Seed! What are you going to do with it?!
It's dangerous!
Who knows? I don't see any reason to tell you.
And I was being pretty nice when
we spoke before, wasn't I?
When I said that if you weren't a
good kid, I'd swallow you whole!
As I thought... that woman... she's a familiar!
Familiar?
That's right. I'm a magical beast created by her.
In return for being allowed to live through her magical
power, I give all of my life and strength to protect her!
Go on ahead. I'll be right behind you.
Okay. Don't be too reckless.
Okay!
Nanoha! Please take care of that girl!
Do you think I'll let you?!
I'll make you let me!
Movement magic...? This is bad!
Trained in magic that manipulates barriers to
suit its needs. You have a strong familiar.
Yuuno-kun isn't a familiar! He's my close friend!
So? What will you do?
Isn't there some way we can talk this over?
I must collect the Lost Logia fragments...
the Jewel Seeds.
And if you have the same goal, it means we'll
be enemies, with the Jewel Seeds on the line.
That's what I mean! I believe
we need to talk this over...
...so we don't make dangerous
decisions like that quickly!
Simply talking... nothing will change
through words alone.
Nothing will be transmitted!
Flier Fin.
But even so...!
Put yourself on the line and make a bet.
One Jewel Seed to the winner.
Photon Lancer, Get set.
Isn't it about time you stopped running?
Why did a mage strong enough to create
her own familiar come to this world?
And what do you know about the
Jewel Seeds... the Lost Logia?!
Shut up!
Thunder Smasher.
Divine Buster.
Raising Heart, please!
All right.
Nanoha... you're so strong!
But she's still too innocent.
Scythe Slash.
Nanoha!
Pull out.
Raising Heart! What are you...?!
I'm sure it was worried about
you and did it to protect you.
Let's go home, Arf.
I expected nothing less from my master!
See you, little girl!
Wait!
Never appear before us again, if you can help it.
If something like this happens again,
I may not be able to stop.
Your name...
What's your name?
Fate. Fate Testarossa.
Umm, I'm...
Bye bye!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Nanoha is keeping
a secret from us...
There's nothing we
can do about it.
Everyone has something
they can't tell their friends.
Past events are
slowly being revealed.
And what is the fate of the two
magical girls who meet again?
Next time on
Magicl Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Six:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Let my Lyrical Magical reach her.