Really?!
I get to perform at the Western Festival?!
You want me to let your third-rate band play back-up for Joe?
Unfortunately, he already has a band.
Isn't it obvious?! We're here to settle the score!
Tell Mario Minakami what's happening!
I'm counting on you, Shigeo...!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Ryuga
Typesetting:
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon, Ryuga
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Shades
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
"Western Festival"
Brother...
"Jazz Club"
--Stop it!
--That's enough!
--Joe!
There goes your pretty face.
Mario...
Mario Minakami...
What a waste.
You're just about to perform, too.
What's going to happen now?
How much do you want?!
I'll pay you! Just stop this at once!
You're sorely mistaken if you
think money can fix everything.
I don't give a damn about the Five Lemons anymore.
I just wanna screw everything up
for your adorable little Joe.
What?!
You had some nerve, disrespecting me like that!
Knock it off, damn it!
Mr. Kawamata...
Joe used to work with you!
Why can't you just be happy for his success?!
You're in the music business too, after all!
Mr. Kawamata!
Dad...
Did you drop this note, kid?
That's...! Give it back! Give it back!
I have to go see someone named Mario Minakami!
I have to help my dad and Joe!
Give it back!
--Isn't that note...?
--Yeah. The one I gave Joe a while back.
This is one adorable messenger pigeon Joe sent...
You did well, kid.
I'm the Mario Minakami you're looking for.
Now let's go help your dad and Joe!
Yeah...
Let's go! Turtle! Cabbage!
Mr. Kawamata...
Damn you!
Mr. Tsubouchi! This is too much...!
You said you were only
going to keep Joe from performing!
Yeah, I said it. And I meant it.
He's never going to perform anything again!
Mr. Tsubouchi...!
All right, playtime is over.
Pay close attention, Ms. Yamauchi...
Bye-bye, Joe...
Mario...?
What the hell do you want?!
Turtle. Get Joe.
Alright!
Cabbage. We'll take out the trash.
Right!
You assholes can't just barge in here and hope to leave--
Quit your blabbering and bring it on, all of you!
What are you doing?! Do something!
Bastard!
--You okay, Joe?!
--Yeah...
Oh, just look at 'em go!
Th-The phone!
Dad!
--Dad!
--Shigeo...
Dad, you're bleeding!
It's okay. It's nothing much...
Sorry to worry you, Shigeo...
I'm gonna kill you...
I'm gonna kill all of you!
Soon...
Soon it'll be my brother's turn...
Mr. Arito! This way!
You boys did this?
Okay! Let's leave the rest to them and get going!
Can you stand, Joe?
Yeah... Thanks...
And just where exactly are you going?!
That's obvious! Isn't it, Joe?
To the... Western Festival...
There's no point now! You'll never make it in time!
Hate to break it to you, ma'am,
but ex-reformatory inmates
are never good at giving up.
Wait.
Use it.
Faster, Cabbage!
I know!
I don't believe in miracles.
But if there's any chance of making it in time...
Please, Anchan!
Make a miracle happen for Joe!
Mario and his friends threw
the blood-covered Joe into a car
and raced to the theater.
"It's always like this for us.
But ex-reformatory inmates never give up so easily."
"Western Festival"
Hurry! Get them to let you sing,
even if you have to beg on your knees!
Yeah!
You go too, Turtle. We're counting on you.
Yeah! I'll be there to see Joe's big moment!
I hope Joe gets to sing...
Misfortune is his only constant.
Although he was used to it, Joe was devastated.
"Did I give myself the ex-reformatory
inmate brand, or was it God?"
The blue-eyed youth stood silently in the bare hall...
Joe...
They said it was unforgivable for a newcomer
to show up late to a show...
Ms. Yamauchi! I'm sorry!
I'll start over from square one!
Please continue to instruct me!
I promise that next time
I'll live up to your expectations-- !
There will be no "next time" for you.
Huh?
For a no-name loser like you, this festival was
your first and only chance for success.
And you screwed it up.
You can forget about making it
anywhere in this business now.
Let's go.
The hell with that!
You're saying this is all Joe's fault?!
--Just what I'd expect from a reformatory loser.
--What?!
I was stupid to think I could transform him.
--Mr. Arito.
--Ms. Yamauchi!
Please! Just give me one more...
Just give me one more chance!
Annoying little brat.
Never show your face around me again.
It's... all over...
Hey Mario, please tell me...
Is it pointless for people like us to try our hardest?
Cabbage...
Does being in a reformatory make you scum forever?
Are we...
...not even allowed to have dreams?!
What the hell are you crying about?!
You're pathetic!
"We can't have dreams because
we were in a reformatory"?!
Do you seriously believe that, Joe?!
Turtle...
It's not over yet!
Sing! We'll listen to you!
Sing...?
This thing means we get to hear you sing.
Got a problem with that?
Yeah! I want to hear you sing, too!
Cabbage...
Yeah...
They don't got tickets, but let 'em hear anyway!
Turtle... I...
What, you can't sing for us?
This might be my very last performance...
Having you as my audience doesn't sound bad.
--It's not just us.
--Huh?
Yeah. I'm sure Anchan is listening, too.
Yeah.
♪ On nights I can't sleep,
I can hear the rain make a melody ♪
♪ Let's slowly go take a look into
the future on our ship in the clouds ♪
♪ A bridge in the dark, starless sky ♪
♪ They say a magical rainbow appears
for a moment on days like this ♪
♪ It's an impossible trail ♪
What's the matter, Joe?
M-Meg...?
You can't stop halfway through...
Meg...
Sing all the way to the end, Brother...
Say, Turtle. How did you find Joe's sister, anyway?
Oh, that?
I tried to go into the theater but then I got into an argument
when the guys told me the show was over.
Then a girl came up and asked,
"Do you know Joe Yokosuka?
"I think he might be my brother..."
So, I promised her I'd get Joe
to sing despite the show being over,
and then I said to come inside if it was her brother.
You're so cool, Turtle!
Really?
--You don't look cool, though!
--You didn't have to say that!
It's a real miracle, though...
It's all thanks to Anchan...
Anchan?
Yeah! I asked him for help!
I asked him to make a miracle happen for Joe!
Whose grave is this?
His name was Anchan.
He was like an older brother to the six of us.
"Sakuragi"
So, what are you going to do now, Joe?
What do you mean?
You wanted to be a singer so you
could find your sister someday.
Now that you're giving up singing, what's next?
Who said I was giving it up?
I'm not giving up…
I have to start all over from scratch again,
but I'll never give up singing!
Thank you, Anchan...
I will become a singer...
"Famous Singer"
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
A manly family business.
With a new dream, Cabbage steps into an unknown world.