Now introduce yourself please!
Umm... I'm... Homura Akemi.
Umm... Well... Nice... to meet you.
Akemi was hospitalized for a long time because of her heart disease.
Since she hasn't been to school for a long while,
she might need your help every now and then.
Please help her if you can!
Akemi, which school did you go before?
Were you in any club?
A sports one? Or an art one?
Your hair is so long! Isn't it tough to comb it every morning?
Well... I... Umm..
Akemi!
You must go to the nurse's office, right?
Do you know where it is?
N-No...
Then let me show you! I'm the health representative for this class!
Sorry girls!
You know, Akemi has to go to the nurse's office in the breaks to take her medicine.
Oh really? Sorry for keeping you then...
Let's talk later then, Akemi!
Sorry about that.
They're nice people, it's just that transfer students are so rare they get carried away.
No, I... Thank you.
You don't have to be so nervous!
We're classmates!
I'm Madoka Kaname. Just call me Madoka.
That's...
It's okay!
Is it okay if I call you Homura?
Umm... People don't usually... call me by my first name.
It feels so strange.
No way! It feels like... dunno, it's so cool!
I'm not really worthy of it...
That's not true!
You have a great name, so you should act cool to match it!
Assume that p is a prime number and n is an arbitrary natural number.
Prove that (1+n)ᵖ - nᵖ - 1 is divisible by p.
Let's give this problem a try.
Ah, you've been absent for a long time, right?
Borrow the notes from your friends.
Seriously, passing out from the warm-up? It must be tough...
Oh well, she had to stay in bed for half a year... It's kinda understandable.
You should act cool to match it!
I can't... I can't do anything.
I only cause trouble to others...
Why?
Will I stay like this forever?
Then it'd be better if you just died now, wouldn't it?
It might be better if I just died...
Yeah! You should just die!
If I just died...
What's this place?
What? What's going on?!
No!
That was a close call.
It's fine now, Homura!
You're...
They are Puella Magi. They hunt witches.
Now you know our secret... But don't tell the others in class!
Mami Tomoe
So Kaname, you're fighting things like that all the time?
Not really all the time...
Mami is the veteran. I just made the contract with Kyubey last week.
But in today's fight you were much better than earlier, Kaname!
Is it okay? Aren't you afraid?
It's never really okay and of course I'm afraid...
But defeating a witch helps a lot of people
so it's kinda worth it, right?
Kaname should become a pro before the Walpurgis Night.
Here I go.
But... Tomoe... just died...
That's why.
Now I'm the only one who can stop the Walpurgis Night.
It's impossible! You can't win alone against that!
You'll die too, Kaname!
Still, I'm a Puella Magi.
I must protect everyone.
Let's run away!
There's nothing we can do!
No one would hold it against you!
Homura, I'm happy we became friends.
When we got there in time when you were attacked by the witch...
I'm still proud of that.
So I really think it was worth becoming a Puella Magi!
Kaname...
Goodbye, Homura.
Take care!
Kana... Kaname!
Why... did you have to die?
You knew it!
Rather than saving me, I wish you...
I wish that you lived on!
Do you really mean that, Homura Akemi?
Would you risk your soul for that wish?
If you're ready to accept a life of fighting for that wish,
I can give you the strength for it.
I can wish for anything if I make a contract with you?
Yes. I feel the power for it within you.
Tell me.
With what wish would your Soul Gem shine?
I...
I want to redo my meeting with Kaname.
Instead of being protected by her,
I want to protect her!
The contract is formed.
Your wish has improved the entropy.
Now, let your new power loose!
Where...?
I'm... still in the hospital?
Mitakihara Junior High School
Admittance Information
So it wasn't a dream?
Now introduce yourself please!
I'm Homura Akemi. Nice to meet you!
Akemi was hospitalized for-
Kaname! I became a Puella Magi too!
Let's work hard together from now on!
All right, here I go!
What do you think, Mami?
She can stop time...
It's really amazing, but she can't use it properly...
Yes.
Mami, now!
Okay!
Akemi, your turn!
Yes!
I did it?
I did it!
You did it!
Congratulations!
Amazing!
You're amazing, Homura!
What's wrong?
Hey, Kaname!
Hang on!
Why?!
What?
Why?
Why is this...?
I must tell her...
Kyubey tricked us all!
And what would Kyubey gain by such a lie?
That's...
Do you want to turn us against each other? Is that why you're spouting that nonsense?
Don't tell me you're conspiring with that Kyoko whoever.
No!
Sayaka... You shouldn't turn against her either.
If I can have a say in this, I'm against teaming up with this girl.
Madoka and Mami have firearms, but
you really should stop with all these sudden explosions.
I'm always afraid I'll get caught in the next one.
Don't you have any other weapons, Akemi?
Let me think about it.
Just what the hell are you?!
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Sayaka, stop it!
Please! Remember!
This isn't what you wanted!
I'm sorry... Miki.
Sayaka... Damn it!
This...
This is so cruel! Too cruel!
Tomoe!
If the Soul Gem turns us into witches,
our only choice is to die!
You too... And me too!
Sto-
No!
I can't take this anymore!
It'll be fine! Let's work hard together!
Let's defeat the Walpurgis Night together!
So this is... the end for us too, right?
The Grief Seeds...
Right...
So how about we become monsters together...
And turn this world upside down?
So that... nothing bad... or sad... would remain.
Destroy, destroy, destroy it all!
Wouldn't that be just fine?
I was lying. I had one.
That's-
Why me?
Because I have something to ask of you...
Something only you can do.
Homura, you can go back to the past, right?
You said you can change history so that it won't end like this, right?
Will you save me from my stupidity... before I get fooled by Kyubey?
I promise! I'll save you for sure!
No matter how many times I'll have to repeat it, I'll protect you!
I'm glad...
Can I... ask you one more thing?
I don't want to become a witch.
There were tough times... and sad times...
But there are lots of things... in this world... that I want to protect.
Madoka!
Homura... Finally you called me by my first name...
I'm happy.
No one believes in the future.
No one can accept the future.
Then I...
Who?
Madoka!
Even if someone shows up promising you miracles in exchange for helping him,
you must not do what he says.
Homu...?
I won't depend on anyone.
No one has to understand it.
I won't let Madoka fight.
I'll take care of all the witches myself.
And even the Walpurgis Night...
So cruel!
That's how it goes.
It's way too strong for her.
That's too cruel! This isn't fair!
Madoka! Don't listen to what he says!
If you give up, that'll be the end.
But you have the power to change fate.
All this destruction and grief. You could reverse it.
You have the power to do that.
Really?
Don't listen to him! He's tricking you!
Even I could do something?
Could I stop all this from happening?
Sure! So make a contract with me and become a Puella Magi!
Don't!
She was really amazing... when she transformed.
I thought she'd become the strongest Puella Magi,
but to defeat the Walpurgis Night in just one hit...
And how will this end? If she's even stronger than you thought.
Either way, her end will be the same.
As the strongest Puella Magi, she defeated her greatest enemy.
Now there's nothing left for her but to become the most evil witch ever.
As Madoka is now it won't take long before she's destroyed this planet.
But well, that's not my problem.
I gathered a lot more energy than our collection quota.
Won't you fight?
No.
This is not my history.
Homura Akemi, you're...
Repeat.
I'll repeat it no matter how many times.
I'll live through the same events again and again.
Until I can find the only way out.
The way to save you from despair.
Madoka...
My only friend...
Homura...
If... If it's for your sake...
I don't mind being locked in this eternal maze!
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 10     I can't depend on anyone anymore
Artist Mura Kuroe
Didn't you feel anything while protecting those girls?
Didn't you try to understand how hard it must've been for them?
Episode 11     The only remaining way
The only remaining way.