Fairy Tale
"Inaba no Shirousagi
("The Hare of Inaba")
Written by Sasami Tsukuyomi
Once upon a time there was a cute and clever hare.
One day the hare found herself at a loss,
unable to cross the river... when a shark appeared.
Hare... Sasami is a hare!
The clever hare came up an idea
when she saw the suspicious-looking shark.
Mr. Shark, Mr. Shark, can I step on you?
What? Was the Hare of Ibana
supposed to be that straightforward?
But if you want to step on me,
I wouldn't ask you a stupid question like that!
Yay!
The hare got on the back of the shark
and managed to cross the river.
Thank you, Mr. Shark!
According to the story of the Hare of Inaba,
the hare gets put on her back on the ground.
In other words...!
If she were a human, she would be
undressed and humiliated!
How dare you get aroused over your blood sister!
Oh? What are you doing, Papa-lin?
Yawn. Tsukuyomi plays a lame role
even in the parallel world...
Hello, Gods, would you please listen
to what I have to say?
As it turns out, I...
Hmph! It's your fault.
Yawn...
It is absolutely absurd for a fish to even think
he could speak to us gods.
Tama wants to do it, too!
Ah, that felt good!
As faithful to the original story, those gods
simply walked away with no remorse.
Shark was dying alone, but then he
found himself enveloped in warm light.
Mr. Shark, Mr. Shark.
I shall give you medicine that you will be grateful for.
At last, a kind god appeared
and healed the shark's wounds.
I've never had anyone be so kind to me before.
To repay your kindness I will-
To repay your kindness,
I will dedicate the rest of my life to you, Sasami,
who are beautiful and kind.
Sasami?
Today you're going to school, okay?
Big Brother, you lech!
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 3                                              Ganbaranai
"YOU WORK, YOU LOSE"
Sasami Report.
Chapter 5, Second Draft.
The power of the Supreme God.
Inside my Big Brother, Kamiomi Tsukuyomi,
resides the power of Great God Amaterasu.
The one who possesses the Power of God
can "alter" the world in any way he wants.
resides the power of Great God Amaterasu.
The one who possesses the Power of God
can "alter" the world in any way he wants.
All he has to do is wish it
and the Yaoyorozu carry out
the Alterations by themselves.
All he has to do is wish it,
and the Yaoyorozu carry out
the Alterations by themselves.
Yes, how can I help you, Sasami?
Food.
Yes! Right away!
However, he hasn't realized that he has the Power within.
That's right. He believes that it's still inside me.
My family, the Tsukuyomi family, was the first
to acquire the Power of the Supreme God.
We're the descendants of Nigigi no Mikoto.
Channel 15
WINDS OF JAPAN
Heritage Landscapes
Winter walks in Kyushu
Round 1: Mysterious and
Beautiful Landscapes
A mysterious family living in Tsukuyomi Shrine,
located deep in the mountains of Kyushu.
Over many generations we've stewarded
the Power of the Supreme God,
Top female athlete and
Popular Supreme God
in spectacular showdown!!
protecting that power and maintaining a world
convenient for humans by use of the Alterations.
Channel 58
Crawling into the outside world
"The mystery unravels...
I grew up in the Tsukuyomi Shrine,
isolated from the outside world,
and trained to become the vessel to
inherit the Power of the Supreme God.
Those days were Hell, filled with
harsh discipline and torturous training.
I used to believe that was normal.
But one day I couldn't take the training anymore,
so I ran away from home.
I came down from the mountains
and saw the city for the first time.
What I thought was normal crumbled
when I first discovered the internet
at a manga café that I infiltrated.
They found me soon afterward and took me back home,
but I started questioning the way of my life.
After that incident I snuck out every now and then,
checking out the internet to see
what's going on in the real world;
I'd found an escape in the virtual reality.
As I longed for the world outside, I took my Big Brother...
What can I do for you, Sasami?
I'm out of Red Blue.
I'll go get some right away.
I took my Big Brother...
Thank you for waiting.
That was fast!
I'll put the rest in the refrigerator.
I took my Big Brother-
What are you writing?
Don't look, you lech!
Were you writing something embarrassing?
It's not nice to keep secrets between siblings.
Now tell your brother everything
that's on this maiden's mind!
Get out!
Let's see, where was I?
Oh, I know.
I took my Big Brother and escaped Tsukuyomi Shrine.
But there's no way the Tsukuyomi family
would do nothing about it.
They may not know our whereabouts for now
thanks to the Alterations,
but the commotions of the Valentine's Day Disaster
and the Yamata no Orochi SNS Incident
might have given them some clues.
I wonder how much longer this peaceful life
where I don't have to work hard would-
What? What? What's going on?
What's the matter, Sasami?
Big Brother, what am I supposed to do? I...!
Oh, finally! My love for you pays off today!
All right. Just let your Big Brother do the rest.
Now go to the bed...
Shut up, you idiot!
Listen to me!
What the heck are you thinking, you lech?
What?
I thought you wanted me to lie next to you
because you had a scary dream.
Huh?! Oh, okay.
I was thinking about something different.
That's not it!
Look at this...
I don't know what happened to me.
It is very strange.
You're already a high school student,
but they don't seem to grow bigger at all.
Big Brother!
I can feel it. It might hurt if I cut it off.
What really happened to you, Sasami?
Big Brother, do you know what this is?
It's an arm. What about it?
"Alteration"
It's an Alteration... Big Brother
hasn't recognized this Alteration.
I decided to call it a sarcoma for now.
Sasami report, chapter 13.
Postscript. My family...
For generations, members of the
Tsukuyomi family are short-lived.
Repeated interbreeding,
in order to preserve bodies that are most
perfectly suited for the Power of God,
resulted in bodies that were completely ruined.
Females of the family are to become
priestesses and train their psychic powers
to channel the Power of the Supreme God.
When the time came I took over the power of
Amaterasu and housed it inside my body.
They clouded my consciousness with drugs
and eliminated all my personal desires
so that I wouldn't wrongly use
the great power for personal reasons.
Males of the family become servants to assist
the priestesses, and protect them with their lives.
They take care of them and at the end
serve them as tools to produce offspring.
My Big Brother hid his face and lived his life
as if he were a ninja or a stagehand.
He never questioned the way of his life.
It's as if he was a robot.
If I ordered him to, he'd gladly bite
through his tongue and kill himself.
For the longest time
I took advantage of his condition.
My Big Brother, of all people,
would never betray me.
would never hurt me.
He would always love me, only me.
No matter how ugly I am,
not even if I'm the worst kind of good-for-nothing girl,
my Big Brother would say yes to me.
He'd support and protect me.
That's why I took my Big Brother
when I ran away from the shrine.
I'd never go back.
What would become of the world was not my concern.
I was already on the verge.
The night I ran away I was trembling
in guilt, regret and fear.
But I had my Big Brother to hold me tight.
Although he barely spoke to me at the Shrine,
he kept talking to me until I fell asleep.
"It's okay, Sasami. Don't be afraid."
"Please don't cry, you're free now."
"I want you to be proud of that and have a happy life."
Even pain...
Even pain,
...pain,
Even pain, regret, guilt... all the negatives...
Just give them all to me. I'll accept that.
That's my job.
That's the meaning of my life.
So he followed through with his duty.
What?
What? Why is it moving on its own?
H...
He...
Hel...
Hell...
Hello...
That's right. You and I are different "characters".
...different "characters"
What are you?
"The people of the shrine have created me
by giving you drugs to split your personality."
"I'm an 'emergency character' which enables
you to act independently just in case."
an emergency character
How could they do such a thing to me?
"Don't worry. My job is to protect you.
"The reason why I'm greeting you like this is
because my job has finished. You're safe now."
"Safe"?
"Your biggest threat are the pursuers
from Tsukuyomi Shrine.
"If they find you this time you'll never
be able to escape again."
"You'll be forever isolated from the rest of the world
by drugs and brainwashing."
"But what they ultimately want is the Power of God.
It's not Sasami Tsukuyomi.
"And currently that Power resides in...
Don't tell me you've...!
"All I did was to show these reports to him
while you were sleeping."
"He reached the conclusion
and made the decision on his own."
"And to protect you, he went to
the shrine instead of you...!
Someone, please help me... Just today...
Just today... please let me...
Big Brother you idiot!
Dammit!
What's up?
Are you okay?
You're a girl so you wouldn't want to
scar your face. Let me see.
Don't cry. You did your best.
I didn't do my best...
I thought I could go on living my life
without doing my best...
I believed that I could be happy
if I escaped and became free.
But all I've ever done is to
make my brother do everything.
All I've ever done is to dump all my burdens on him!
Don't push yourself too hard.
I won't forgive him... He's my Big Brother...
I won't let him take everything in
and go far away from me!
All I do is make him take all the burden...
I still haven't given him anything yet...
Doing your best and straining yourself
are two different things.
You're still just a kid, so it's okay to walk with a little help.
That's not emotional dependence.
That's trust!
You'd better come talk to me if you have issues at home.
I'm your homeroom teacher, you know.
Where am I?
Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Haven't been here in a while...
You've been here before?
Let's talk while we walk.
I could've shut it down if I wanted to.
I used to let them be in charge of those gods for me.
What? So that means...
The Gods of Creation, Izanagi and Izanami,
once assigned me power to govern this land.
You are...
Great God Amaterasu?!
But those gods did whatever they pleased
and never listened to me.
If I'd get upset and lock myself in a rock cave,
they would drag me out of there.
So I entrusted the Power of the Supreme God
to Ninigi no Mikoto and went into hiding.
Ame Nigishi Kuni Nigishi Amatsuhiko Hiko
Ho no Ninigi no Mikoto... My distant descendant.
I was going to go back to work once Ninigi-kun died,
but he exercised an unexpected method
and transferred the Power to his descendants.
Intermarriage among relatives...
He bore offspring with genetics close to his
and let them carry the Power.
But the world humans had made for
themselves was pretty good, too.
So I decided to just sit back and watch.
Just like you.
I observed and made sure that the one with
the Power of God wouldn't do anything stupid.
But I let them handle all the troublesome issues.
I just didn't want to work at all.
Aren't you going to take that Power back?
I'm so tired of it.
But if I'm going to get it back, I'll give it to a successor,
someone younger and newer.
And that successor is her.
Tama?
Thank you for the food!
Thank you!
She's a new god I made
by severing a portion of my existence.
Because she was made from a part of me
I call her my younger sister.
I told her that she was born from the Supreme God.
So that's why she calls my Big Brother,
who possesses the Power of God, "Papa-lin".
Bow to it now. Since it's the shrine.
Kagami...
Make it a bloodbath...
Since it's a shrine.
Kagami is similar too.
Long ago, I discarded a part of myself
after being cursed by the enemy.
Bad guys found that and grew it into her.
They designed her as a spiritual robot
using black magic tools and modern weapons.
She's a robot, modeled after a god...
It'd be wrong to let them use her for criminal purposes,
so I kidnapped her and have been
taking care of her ever since.
Take a good beating!
Since it's the shrine!
(pray)       (take a beating)
That was a pun on "sanpai" and "zanpai"!
So what's happening here?
We're destroying this shrine!
Can you guess why we showed up?
What?
First of all, we gods are so incorporated into the world
you can't sense our existence.
Can you guess why we're here?
Guess why...?
Because you wished it.
You wished for us, the three Yagami Sisters.
As your allies who protect your peaceful life.
That's why we've been protecting
your ordinary everyday life.
Now let's take that idiot Tsukuyomi home
and go back to that chaotic life.
Okay!
Yawn...
Big Sis, we've got a problem.
Mr. Tsukuyomi is nowhere to be found.
His scent is still here, so I think he was here, but...
I can't find him anywhere!
Hey, I want to ask you something!
Lady Sasami, I didn't realize you were back home!
Hey, have you seen my brother?
Kamiomi came home a little while ago,
but Master chased him away.
What?
He was saying something like he has the Power of God
so he wanted to be a priestess in Lady Sasami's stead.
He was talking complete nonsense.
They checked his psychic power and divinity levels
just to be sure, but he's got absolutely none.
Despite the fact that he carried you off
and got kicked out of the family,
he still came home, talking nonsense,
so Master got upset and chased him out.
So that means...
What's going on?
There was a big misunderstanding.
It seems that the Power of God
has been inside me all along, after all.
I've always wished a happy life for my Big Brother.
The gods must've responded to my wish
and made his wishes come true.
I'm not in
right now
Because I'd assumed I'd relinquished the Power
I'm now unable to manifest my real power.
The pain I always felt when I stepped outside
had to be the work of evil gods.
But...
I'm okay now.
From now on, I'm going to live my life
in a world filled with sunshine.
REFLECTING
ON PAST
CONDUCT
Now let's go, Sasami.
All right, let's do my best starting today!
You've got a problem!
I'm here to rescue you! Tsurugi here!
Supporting the unenthusiastic Sasami
is the job of us Yagami sisters!
So that being said, today three of us
are going to sing instead!
I'm not giving the microphone back to Sasami anymore!
Do whatever you want.
Big Sis Tsurugi, Tama wants to do it, too!
I love singing!
All right! Let's do it together!
Sasamisan@Ganbaranai is the only place you can hear
the beautiful voice of Amaterasu-chan,
the Great Goddess of Japanese Myth!
Yeah!
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You look fed up, but you're still smiling
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together!
Way to go!
Kikoeruyo
I can hear it
I'm not going to sing, but you're okay with it right?
It'd be great if you could join them, too, Kagami.
Somehow I've got this feeling that Kagami
is going to be just like Sasami.
Yawn...
Please don't put me in the same category
with that failure of a girl.
I understand, but can you talk to Sasami
and convince her to make more effort?
I'm sure Sasami will listen to you.
What do you mean by that?
Well, you'll understand what I mean as the story unfolds.
Oh? It looks like the song is almost over.
Thank you for your hard work, Ladies!
Can I go home now?
Ganbaranai Cooking
It's time for Ganbaranai Cooking.
Today's menu is authentic beef stroganoff.
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
Make him go get beef, onion, mushroom,
tomato, red wine, butter, bouillon and paprika
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Mushroom 20
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Mushroom 20
Tomato 1 (medium)
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Mushroom 20
Tomato 1 (medium)
Red wine 200 ml
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Mushroom 20
Tomato 1 (medium)
Red wine 200 ml
Butter To taste
Authentic Beef Stroganoff
4 SERVINGS
Beef 280g
Onion 1 (medium)
Mushroom 20
Tomato 1 (medium)
Red wine 200 ml
Butter To taste
Bouillon To taste
then stomp the floor with your heel,
and it'll show up in front of your door.
It's really simple, so give it a try!
Episode 4
Next time, episode 4:
"Parasitizing at Home"