Were you still alive,
Cal Devens?
Did something happen?
I saw a phantom.
I swore to protect her.
I promised to go back.
But I let her die alone...
That's what I thought the whole time.
You thought wrong, right?
The one who shot yesterday was her.
I see.
Cal joined Inferno as a sniper.
Master Huang,
I, Xu Jian Fa, feel greatly honored to be able to become your sworn brother
on such an important date such as your birthday.
Xu... Don't be so humble.
I should've rewarded you for your achievements in expanding us into West Japan.
I believe Kantou will also be ours soon.
I'll be counting on you.
My younger brother, let us toast for our journey ahead.
The Godoh Group's request is to finish off the head of the rival Chinese mafia group - Xu, right?
Is there something wrong?
Is there a need to finish off that Huang geezer?
You do realize that he's helping a group that's opposing Inferno.
If I remember correctly, he helped you out a lot when you were removed from Inferno.
He knows too much.
You don't care about morals?
You can care about that.
But I'm different. That's all.
This is Gregor. Your orders?
Yeah, I'm listening.
Gregor here. We're all in position.
We can go in anytime.
Just stay where you are for now.
What happened to Phantom?
I don't know.
She didn't like this mission from the beginning.
I'm leaving her out of it.
Is that okay?
She certainly might not be suitable for this mission.
She's only giving cover after all.
Gregor, just carry out the mission as originally planned.
First, Parker's group infiltrates from behind and takes out the bodyguards.
Roger that.
It'll take them three minutes to lure out Huang and Xu?
Are you dissatisfied?
No, not at all.
But if she did it, it would only take ten seconds.
Ten seconds?
Dammit!
You fucking bastard!
What's going on?!
That's...
Watch out!
Goddammit!
What the fuck is this?!
I think this is the most effective and rational way of doing it.
This is Japan!
Putting on a big show like this will...
The value of a life is the same whether it's in Japan or America.
This way!
Master Huang.
Who's responsible for this crazy attack?
I think I know.
Are you from Scythe?!
I was the one who saved that man!
Is this how he's going to repay the favor?!
Favor? What does that mean again?
Master Huang!
You've got some guts.
Still not going to admit your defeat?
I like you.
Let's play a game.
Do you like to play games?
We'll shoot when the song ends.
You're taking me lightly...
It doesn't matter which organization you're from.
Don't think you'll get off lightly for doing something like this!
I see...
You're still clueless.
Phantom.
Since you live in the underworld,
you've probably heard of that name, right?
Correct.
That's...
Me.
If you defeat me, the whole world will bow down to you.
Pick your occupation wisely in your next life.
Adios, chink.
I was the one who created this mess.
I taught her how to kill.
I showed her the way to the underworld.
These hands of mine screwed her life up.
The escape preparations will soon be complete.
Until then...
Yeah.
I got it.
Where did you go yesterday?
To see some friends.
Did you come in contact with him?
Zwei, that is.
That's none of your business.
I'll settle things with them my way.
I see.
It's your turn next, Reiji.
Umm...
Good morning.
You went home pretty early yesterday.
Huh?
Well, you see...
You had already left when I went to find Sanae after school.
I had stuff to do.
It's not like I'm trying to pry into your life.
I wasn't thinking that at all.
Okay...
It's snowing.
You're right...
The weather forecast was wrong.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
You really spiced things up, Miss Garland.
Even the police is on it.
I suggest whoever was involved in the shooting yesterday to leave this country immediately.
Don't worry about that.
They left... Most of them.
That's great.
Anyway, I thank you for erasing Xu without leaving any evidence trail back to the Godoh Group.
However, I would appreciate it if you would tell us your plans before the next time you do something in Japan.
Please excuse me.
It's not like it was some insanely hard mission.
Had we stuck to the plan, no one would have had to die.
It was my mistake.
When she... When Phantom didn't appear,
I should've known something like this was going to happen.
Don't blame yourself.
It's true that Drei has problems.
However, it can be understood.
Drei is too impatient.
The current Drei has not fully taken over the name of Phantom.
Because she hasn't fought it out with the previous Phantom.
If Drei truly takes over the name of Phantom,
she will become steady and flexible.
In other words, if she defeats Zwei with her own hands...
Reiji, no boxed lunch today, right?
Yeah... But Motegi, how did you know?
Then let's go to the cafeteria.
That's fine with me, but what about yours?
I ate it after second period.
Since you're the cool kid for today, Motegi,
I'll allow you to sit there.
Yes, thank you.
Do you still remember me?
Of course.
You're the unpopular Motegi-kun.
That's what my brother said.
How did you introduce me?
You used me too, didn't you?
I'm begging you! Just share a little of your happiness with me!
You're so forcible.
Oh come on, Brother.
These things aren't bad once in a while.
I know, right?
I feel honored to have the same train of thought as you, Elen-chan!
I guess we're made for each other, right?
Are you saying that Cal won't dare to try anything in a group of people?
I guess so.
Look after my seat. I'm gonna go buy food.
Okay.
Get me a B set.
Buy it yourself.
Oh? So the reason Reiji had to leave early was because of you?
I had to discuss some family matters with my brother.
I'm sorry... Even though I knew he was on a date with Mio.
It wasn't a date.
What?
If that's the case, just be straight with it.
Well, I thought it would sound kind of lame...
You dense bastard!
A person like that should be punished.
Why are you eating it?
Because you're hogging the happiness all to yourself!
What do you mean?
Are you seriously dense or what?!
There are a lot of people in this world who aren't as lucky as you!
Yeah!
For example, Motegi.
What?!
Someone asked me to give this to you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
You're kidding...
What's wrong?
Some underclassman's request.
A tiny bit of happiness just left...
Didn't you only want a little?
Now then...
Hey, where do you think you're going?
I have to make sure none of the guys bother her.
Elen's pretty popular. You'll get tired soon if you go every single time.
You siscon!
But...
Just go. She's your only sister after all.
I'm sorry. I'll make up for it next time.
What about me?!
Keep dreaming.
Elen...
Are you looking for someone?
Do you want to kill me?
That's right, you're capable of killing me.
Not by being ordered, not by being driven into a corner,
but by your own will.
And that's why you're special, Zwei.
Ein, even though brainwashed,
cannot be compared with you who has a genuine killing intent.
From a certain point of view, you can be branded as a failure.
But you gave me a new line of research.
So I began exploring the theme of "hatred".
You saw it, right? My proud third creation, Drei.
What did you do to Cal?
If you're speaking from a concluding point of view, I didn't do anything.
No brainwashing. No hinting.
No control of her memories or emotions.
I just completely uncovered...
the hatred within her.
I thank you for giving me such a genius.
Scythe, you're the only one I...
Can't forgive? Hate?
But you can't kill me here.
There's too much risk.
Such self-control.
Not only do you have a genuine killing intent, but also a calm sense of judgment.
A perfect balance.
But Drei is awful at that. She can't control herself.
But...
At least she has a way to cover for it.
Don't tell me...
You'd better hurry if you want to help her.
Hurry up and show yourself.
No one will interfere with us here.
Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you the Old Phantom?
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
The only reason I'm still alive...
...is to find and kill that man.
That's all.