[heavy metal music playing]
GREATEST LOSER
[Brünnhilde] Over the course
of his entire life,
Kojiro Sasaki never won a single battle.
ICHIJODANI CASTLE TOWN
AT THE CLOSE OF THE SENGOKU PERIOD
TODA DOJO
[men grunting]
[wood tapping]
[groaning]
How pathetic. You are obviously a slacker.
KAGEKATSU TODA
NEPHEW OF SEIGEN TODA
If you want to stay a student
of our dojo, you'd better shape up.
[yawning]
Huh?
[Brünnhilde] In the dojo of Seigen Toda,
a swordsman renowned throughout Japan,
the boy was seen
as little more than a burden.
Sasaki!
Uh?
Hello. Master Kagekatsu,
good morning to you.
Late again, are you?
You must be pretty brave, you little shit!
[laughing awkwardly]
Aw, I'm hardly worthy of such praise.
That wasn't a compliment!
I'll teach you to focus,
if I have to beat it into you.
Huh?
[growling]
[grunting]
- Did he just...?
- Did he block Master Kagekatsu?
[straining]
Ah! Ooh. Ah. [grunting]
I surrender!
D... Did you say surrender?
I did. Victory is your, Master Kagekatsu.
You little bastard!
You call yourself a warrior?
If you lose your blade,
fight with your fists.
If you lose your fists,
bite with your teeth!
Struggle and fight until the very end.
- Save your breath, Kagekatsu.
- Huh?
Such teachings hold no sway
over young Kojiro.
B... But, Father...
KAGEMASA TODA
- ...did you see what he...?
- [sighing]
Brother, Kojiro is
talentless with a blade.
Why are we wasting
our dojo's time with such a failure?
Hmm. Kojiro, you held your own
at first, so why surrender now?
TODA-RYU FOUNDER
SEIGEN TODA
Uh, well, I couldn't win even if I fought
Master Kagekatsu 100 times.
At my current level, if I gave it my all,
I would only get injured,
- damaging any future prospects I may have.
- Huh?
"Current level," huh?
- [scoffing] "Future prospects"?
- Huh?
[Kagemasa] Now you're sounding just like
a born and bred businessman.
Thank you,
but I'm hardly worthy of such praise.
[both] That wasn't a compliment!
So is it true, then?
Is an aptitude for the sword
what you truly lack, Kojiro?
Indeed. Though it's painful to admit.
- Unbelievable!
- [students laughing]
[Brünnhilde] However,
the dojo's senior disciples
had not yet come to recognize...
Kojiro Sasaki's true nature
as a swordsman.
Now then, how can I defeat
Master Kagekatsu?
Perhaps I should work on
my physical strength?
No, he's so much bigger than me
that my footwork will be more important.
The foundation of swordsmanship
lies in the lower body, after all.
- [leaves rustling]
- Hm?
Whoa!
Ha! This is just what I need.
This movement, it's perfect.
Huh? Hey, wait. Wait for me.
[Brünnhilde] Instead of the dojo,
Kojiro found his lessons in nature.
Huh? [screaming]
[straining] At the dojo, the only thing
they give us to eat is millet.
I need more.
I'll build up my body by eating meat.
This too will be my training.
[hissing]
[shrieking]
Learning the flow of battle
from beasts in the wild...
this too will be my training.
[Brünnhilde] Within each loss,
he sought the path to victory.
Refining his technique alone,
such was the talent Kojiro possessed.
[shouting]
Uh. I... I surrender.
Hello there. Sorry I'm late.
Hmm?
Kojiro, you got nerve, I tell you.
You disappear for six months,
and show up here like nothing happened?
Is Master Seigen here, by any chance?
[all gasping]
[Kagekatsu] He looks like
a completely different person.
What has he been up to all this time?
This could be fun.
Kojiro, let's have a match.
I'll admit, you truly were a mighty foe.
So much so that I had to fight you
146 times in my mind
- before I could defeat you.
- You what?
So I'm afraid
I've no need to fight you again.
No need to fight?
So you're saying you beat me?
[yelling] I don't think so!
Ah.
- Master Kagekatsu just...
- Kojiro didn't even draw.
I think that's enough. Wouldn't you say?
Uh... Uh... I...
- I surrender!
- Uh!
Are you all right, Master?
What's wrong?
Uh, listen, I never intended to...
Hmm.
[laughing] Master Seigen!
There's a request
I'd like to make of you, Master.
If I may, would you do me the honor
of sparring with me?
Very well.
[inhaling deeply]
Well, then...
Here I come!
[roaring]
[exclaiming in awe]
[Brünnhilde] After their match,
Kojiro stopped coming to the dojo.
Though many years later...
[wood splitting]
[grunting]
[sighing]
It's been some time, Kojiro.
[laughing] Master Seigen!
What a surprise.
It has been far too long.
I was curious as to why
you never returned to the dojo,
so I thought I'd check on you myself.
[Brünnhilde] By the time of his visit,
sickness and age had already robbed
Seigen of his sight, and yet...
[gasping]
For a brief moment, Seigen's unseeing eyes
perceived everything.
My word.
Even these old eyes of mine,
I can see it all so clearly.
Kojiro, I can see...
every hard-earned step of your training.
Well, surpassing everyone took a while.
Four years and nine months,
if I'm being precise.
KAGEKATSU TODA
KAGEMASA TODA
KANEMAKI JINSAI
[Seigen] He wasn't trying
to show off to anyone.
Nor was he trying to compete with anyone.
He did all of this
merely to further himself.
You've done well to come so far alone.
Oh, Kojiro.
It seems as though...
SEIGEN TODA
...you've surpassed me too.
Hmm. This tea is miserable.
[laughing] Well, I did use
whatever leaves I could find.
Listen well. I'll ask the Asakura clan
to take you in as their sword instructor.
A fine position that could make you
the lord of your own castle.
Hm.
You honor me, Master.
But the truth is, I've decided
that it's time for me to move on.
I'm afraid there's very little
left here that excites me.
And where do you intend on going to next?
I don't know.
But I hope to keep on losing
over the course of my journey.
[Brünnhilde] As to where Kojiro went
after leaving Seigen Toda's dojo,
no one can say.
No historical records exist
to confirm his whereabouts.
No songs are sung in his honor.
Only one thing is certain...
KAGEHISA ITTOSAI ITO
ITTO-RYU FOUNDER
Huh. Well, you need more training.
[groaning] I surrender.
[Brünnhilde] Kojiro Sasaki continued
to rack up loss after loss,
moving from opponent to opponent,
and growing stronger.
Please grant me a match.
MUNETOSHI SEKISHUSAI YAGYU
YAGYU SHINKAGE-RYU
Ah!
I... I surrender.
[Brünnhilde] And stronger still.
[thunder rumbling]
I implore you, please grant me a match.
Master Kamiizumi!
[chuckling]
Well, I believe that
I can give you a decent fight.
[crashing]
I surrender.
[horse neighing]
[laughing] So that was the Sword Saint.
I didn't stand a chance against him.
[Brünnhilde] Like a parched desert
longing for rain,
Kojiro continued to pursue
and challenge undefeatable foes.
And he continued to lose.
All right, then. So how can I beat him?
[Brünnhilde] Why, you ask,
did Kojiro Sasaki's name vanish
from history until his final,
fateful duel with Ganryujima?
Because the man continued to lose,
as he trod his path towards greatness.
Thanks for the meal.
Mm. That's delicious!
[Brünnhilde] And so,
history's greatest loser was born.
I'm not dying today.
But I suppose, for a battle like this one,
"I surrender" won't cut it.
I implore you.
Grant this old fool a match.
Ah...
All right, you're in it now, Kojiro.
This is one battle
you can't run away from.
For all the pioneers
who paved my path to strength.
For all creation, which nourished me
and became my flesh and blood.
I need to stand...
[wind whooshing]
...with my head held high.
[gasping]
[sighing] Here I come.
[narrator] Kojiro Sasaki's first move
was a technique all his own.
He swung his famed
three-foot-long Bizen Nagamitsu,
a long sword
also known as the drying pole,
down from above with all his might,
in a single, devastating slash.
The drying pole possessed a weight
of 1.5 times the average katana.
After a slash of that strength,
physics dictates that halting its downward
acceleration should be nigh impossible.
And yet...
Kojiro Sasaki's series of defeats
had given rise to an attack
that defied such petty constraints.
A swift strike...
like an arrow racing toward its target
and changing its course mid-flight.
His signature move.
[metallic ringing]
Tsubame Gaeshi!
Did you see that?
[grumbling]
He's quick. He moved before
Poseidon had the chance to skewer him.
Pretty virile for an old man.
Huh? This is a surprise.
I never thought I'd see the great Poseidon
looking a human in the eye.
So you meet my gaze at last, huh, kiddo?
- [groaning]
- You okay, Papa?
Sasaki!
APRIL 13, 1612
FUNASHIMA (LATER KNOWN AS GANRYUJIMA)
[narrator] The first unblockable swing
of the drying pole,
comes down upon his foe
like a giant hatchet.
If they dodge the first swing,
they're finished with the second,
which follows the trajectory of the first,
yet in reverse,
appearing from nowhere.
An attack that is at once unblockable,
and undodgeable.
The Tsubame Gaeshi!
Really brings back
some good memories, Sasaki.
Listen up, sea god.
Even if you are divine, you better not
approach this man unguarded.
[all] Curse your luck, for today you test
your skill against the man we call
Number One Under the Sun.
- [crowd cheering]
-[Göll] We can do this.
We can really do this.
Come on, Hrist. You've got this.
Let's win one for the humans!
Huh. The weight of it, the blade,
not a single fault to speak of.
[narrator] The second
of the 13 Valkyrie sisters,
Hrist, the Trembling One,
Bizen Nagamitsu Sanjaku Yosun, Völundr.
This trusty drying pole of mine,
I can't imagine a weapon
more perfectly suited to my style.
Huh?
- I never thought I'd see the day.
- No way! This can't be happening.
What's going on?
I don't believe my eyes.
The god among gods, Poseidon himself,
is advancing upon his opponent.
[blade ringing]
[inhaling deeply]
AMPHITRITE
[exciting rock music playing]
[Heimdall] Poseidon's jabs are
as relentless as the raging tides,
but Kojiro deftly weaves
through the onslaught!
Kojiro cannot be touched!
Amazing! Poseidon's trident's so fast
but Kojiro can see through every move.
Does that mean his eyes are somehow
just as good as Adam's were?
It's not that he can see the moves,
he can dodge them because
he's already experienced them.
Wait, what do you mean?
They haven't fought before, have they?
How has he experienced anything?
He can experience a battle
before he's even drawn his sword, you see?
Uh...
[Brünnhilde] After challenging countless
powerful opponents,
and suffering defeat after defeat
after defeat,
Kojiro Sasaki would continue
fighting his foes within his head.
Since the moment
Poseidon entered the arena,
Kojiro has been analyzing him,
making note of the most
seemingly insignificant details.
His gait, his breathing,
even the way he blinks.
All this information allows him
to form an image of Poseidon in his mind.
He then takes that image, and then
challenges it an endless number of times,
simulating over 1,000 different attacks,
1,000 different outcomes.
All in advance.
Wait, he did that already? They only
looked at each other for, like, a sec.
Yes.
If Adam can lay claim
to having the fastest counterattacks,
Kojiro has the fastest prediction.
No matter how fast the opponent strikes,
no matter how many times
they cut him down,
Kojiro can simulate their attack
and evade it.
He can predict any move
his opponent might make.
That is Kojiro Sasaki's
thousand-fold defense.
Senju Musou.
[Kojiro] I know that one. And that one.
That one too.
And this one.
I know 'em all!
[panting]
[crowd cheering]
That's the way to do it, old man!
[man] History's greatest loser's
gonna win!
Exactly how many attacks
has that decrepit old man dodged already?
I refuse to believe that Poseidon
hasn't landed a single hit on him yet.
Does this mean he's able to predict
even a god's moves?
- We're supposed to be unknowable.
- Yes, that certainly seems to be the case.
Then that means there has to be something
wrong with all of the people here.
These humans that push themselves
to the heights of perfection.
Why are they all so...
So impossibly...?
Why are they so impossibly,
unbelievably exciting?
Hm.
[whistling tunefully]
He's whistling?
[all murmuring]
[whistling continues]
Well, this should be quite interesting.
[Kojiro] Hmm. What's his next move?
That one!
[gasping]
He's faster than I predicted!
Not good!
[splashing]
[gasping]
Ah!
Something wrong?
[narrator] At long last, the god
finally broke his silence to the human.
You were supposed to be reading my moves,
were you not?
Worthless clown.
[Japanese pop ballad playing]