When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Here you are, Mistress
Kuzuha. Please say, "Ah!"
Butler Economy, Trade and Industry
The futures index of the butlers
at our Hakuou Academy is...
Down 3 points.
They have grown soft.
A butler, for example, can get run over
by a car speeding along at 80kmph
or get trampled by a giant robot...
Pardon. A bit of cream on your mouth.
Only when they can survive such
things as if it were nothing
can they be considered full-fledged butlers.
Am I not right, Sion?
You are.
But even so...
Let me think...
If there were a butler somewhere
with a look of poverty about him
that just makes you want to smack him,
who was in his late teens
and roughly 168cm and 57kg...
If there were?
Well, I would not be against
giving him some special attention.
It sure is autumn.
It certainly is autumn.
Tama, cut it out.
Hey, cut it out.
Rarrr!
Rarrr...
Oh?
I-I feel like someone
is calling to me from somewhere.
I think it's about time we busted out a new.
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
I know! I have just thought
of a good way to stave off boredom!
Wait, so uh... Who might you be?
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Hayate Rising
I've done it! It's finally complete!
Congratulations!
You'll win the new author
award for sure this time!
Y-Yes...
Th-Then make sure to get this manuscript...
Yes, I will send it out to the publisher.
Oh, also...
When you go to school, grab the PSP
from my desk while you're at it.
Oh, did you forget it there?
It's got Crisis Core in it. I'm working
on finishing a hardcore challenge.
I'll be counting on you.
Miss!
Um, please get some good rest.
A normal, peaceful morning!
It's a bit disappointing that
the Miss couldn't make it, though.
Morning, Hayate.
Oh, Hinagiku.
Are you alone? Is Nagi playing hooky again?
Yes, well...
Morning, students of Hakuou Academy.
It is early, but I have some
interesting information for you.
This voice is...!
Wait! Look, Hinagiku!
I will have you know, this is no joke.
I am serious.
Wh-What was that?
That woman's up to no good again!
Wait...!
Wh-What the?!
elzzaD
"D-Dazzle! The First..."
"Hakuou Academy..."
"B-Butler..."
"Battle..."
"Tournament..."
Hinagiku, um, please calm down.
What in the world is this about?
Hayate, you stay back.
Oh-ho, I am surprised
you knew where to find me.
You are not our student body
president for nothing, I see.
Um, who is this woman?
She's our school's Superintendent.
S-Superintendent?!
Indeed.
Hakuou Academy Butler
Battle Tournament to be Held!!
What is this?!
Butler Battle Tournament?!
You're making no sense!
It's exactly what it sounds like.
I want to check up on the level
of the butlers at our school.
I also have a somewhat
personal interest in this.
A strong, tough butler worthy
of some special attention!
That is what I am looking for!
Th-That gave me the chills
for some reason...
But she seems like an awfully
extreme sort of person.
I-In other words,
you're up to your usual thing
and you plan to have fun by treating
the students as your toys, don't you?!
"Have fun"?! How insulting!
The ability to fight is one of the most
important aspects of being a butler!
B-But all the butlers
at this school are serious students!
For example, take Hayate here.
Huh?
I see, then perhaps
I shall ask him directly.
W-Wait, have I been made
the focus of this conversation
before I could even understand
what's going on?
Boy.
By the looks of it, you seem to be
at least some sort of butler yourself.
Answer my question.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
"A battle tournament such as this
"to test the strength
of butlers is pointless."
Now... "Yes" or "no"?
What? Uh...
Beep. Beep. Beep.
W-Well, I wouldn't say
that it was pointless,
b-but I think there might be
more important things than that.
Like one's dedication to one's mistress...
What?!
Boy!
You understand nothing!
Hayate, take this!
You seem to have some skill.
Hold on! Please don't just drag me
into your battle world!
But at this rate, you
still have a long way to go!
Wh-What should I do? This is my fault.
A butler is tasked with
the protection of his mistress,
even if it should cost him his life.
Boy, what would you do
if I were out to kill your mistress?
Would you still be able to
say the same thing then?
That strength is not a particularly
essential quality for a butler...
Th-That is...
You left yourself open!
A lesson for you!
Watch out!
What?!
She ran out of juice.
Not good... My blood sugar level...
S-Sion... a sna... a snack...
Yes, I already have one waiting
for you in your room.
Is it sweet?
Yes, very.
Sion...
Mistress Kuzuha...
O-Oh, my!
What in the world is up with these people?
Allow me to explain.
Hakuou Academy Superintendent,
Kirika Kuzuha,
has triple the combat
ability of a normal person,
but in exchange, if she uses up her energy,
she just drops like a fly.
How dare you do that
to my precious Mistress Kuzuha...
You won't get away with this.
Wait, what? I'm going to
be held solely responsible for that?
What?! This is...!
Could this be the Territory
formed by this person's Aura?
My name is Sion.
Written as "si" as in "poet"
and "on" as in "sound".
Sion.
O-Oh, is that so? I am...
This person is good!
I've been robbed of my
freedom before I knew it!
You're a butler? What
is this world coming to?
When you are so weak...
Why don't you just give up being a butler
and switch to being a maid?
That would suit you better.
If that makes you angry,
try entering the Tournament.
The winner will receive
the privilege of challenging me.
Though, I doubt you could ever manage that.
Uh, um, Hayate, I'm sorry.
For, you know, getting you mixed up in this.
Not at all...
Um!
P-Please pretend you didn't
see that... just now...
A-All right.
Wh-Where's all this leading to?
What in the world is this
Butler Battle Tournament?
Um, I'd like to ask you something.
J-Just what kind of person
is the Superintendent of Hakuou Academy?
And she seems to have some
sort of history with Hinagiku...
Oh, did you run into her today?
What? Yes...
Yeah, that Superintendent's
a fantastically troublesome character.
For example, just to stave off boredom,
she changed our field trip destination
to the non-Internet Amazon
without our consent.
Uh-huh...
Or simply to stave off boredom,
she schemed to open
a pool made solely for Char.
I see.
So, it's kind of been like that,
with Hinagiku trying
to protect the students and Earth
from the evil reach
of the Superintendent's whims.
H-Hold on...
Um, that last part...
Well, here's a bit of friendly advice.
Better not get involved
with that Superintendent or her butler.
But this Butler Battle Tournament
sure came out of the blue.
Let's see...
"The winner will be presented
with a prize of 100 school credits."
That's like a roundabout way of saying
you can skip all the classes you want.
Hayate, if you don't mind,
why don't you enter this tournament?
What?!
Wait... Miss, you don't mean...
No, no, I don't care about the 100 credits.
Whether it's there or not,
I'll skip school when I skip school.
R-Right...
More importantly...
Hayate, I wish to see it for myself
with these very eyes
when you win the tournament.
W-Win, you say?
Yes!
After all, you must be invincible
to be a Sanzenin butler.
In other words, you are...
...invincible!
Invincible!
Which equates to victory!
Miss...
Ooh! I'm starting to get more
and more excited!
Because knowing you...
Things like this...
...and this...
...should be in your arsenal.
And it's not often I get to
see stuff like that.
Wait... So, with the way this is going,
am I pretty much being forced
to enter the tournament, no matter what?
But if the Miss has such
high expectations of me...
Hinagiku Katsura, this is a warning.
Ultimately, you are
a commoner without a butler.
It would be for your own good
to mind your own business
and refrain from interfering
with the Tournament.
I retrieved this tape earlier
from the student council post box.
Incidentally, the packaging was all sticky
with brown sugar syrup.
I see, so her snack today consisted
of Japanese sweets (wagashi).
My Master (wagashi)
None of that matters!
Isn't there some way for us
to intervene in this Tournament?
Having said that, I have no butler...
Oh, what am I going to do?
I've made up my mind!
I'm going to ask Kotetsu!
It must be nice
for those of you with butlers.
The 100 credits are definitely appealing,
but now, what are Miki and I to do?
You, there! Don't be letting
the devil's temptation get to you already!
Mm-hm.
Hina, I have a good idea.
Um, perhaps you should refrain
from anything so dangerous?
No, I've made up my mind.
Maria, I'm going to enter
the Butler Battle Tournament!
I cannot let the Miss down!
Yes! I'm starting to get more
and more fired up!
I will try going with the
flow, in spite of it all!
E-Even with this hot-blooded turn of events,
I guess he's still off in his own world.
What of butler Hayate's fate?
And... the day of the Tournament's
come around in no time!
A warrior is as good as his word.
(Bushi ni nigon wa nai.)
Die once and you cannot die again.
(Ichido shineba nido shinanu.)
A-Are they burning it up over there?
And now, we hereby commence Dazzle!
The First Hakuou Academy
Butler Battle Tournament!
I am the Superintendent
of this academy, Kirika Kuzuha!
All of you, vie against one another!
Compete ruthlessly!
I expect tough fights worthy
of this great stage for butlers!
It's finally time, Hayate!
Y-Yes.
Please wait for me, poem person!
And now, we'll begin the first match!
In the red corner, the butler
of some household, Other 1!
And in the blue corner, butler of
the Segawa household, Kotetsu!
I never knew the committee
chairman had a butler.
But no one's coming out.
After I begged him to come, too!
Thank you!! Urakari Main Line
Farewell, Urakari Main Line!
Th-This roundish shape of the
train carriage is just to die for!
Right?! Right, right?!
R-Red corner wins by default!
Don't be mean!
Next up, the second match.
Yo, Ayasaki! So yer in this, too, eh?
O-One of the members of the
"very generous people" folk?!
How in the world?!
I hired him as an interim butler.
M-Miss Asakaze!
I lost at rock-paper-scissors to Miki, so...
I used my connections to get a pinch hitter.
What kind of connections do you have?
Rock-paper-scissors?
Fight!
Get him!
Beat him to a pulp!
Stick it to him good!
What?
Y-You win!
Um, please, just don't
tell anyone about that!
Allow me to explain.
A butler's necktie is his soul.
Regardless of the amount of damage
or if there is even any damage,
the butler whose necktie
gets taken first loses.
Th-The winner is Kashiwagi,
butler of the Asakaze household!
O-Oh, right, his name is Mr. Kashiwagi.
But...
Kashiwagi! Kashiwagi!
Good work!
Keep it up and get me those 100 credits.
I'll be sure to do the work
I've been paid to do.
Heh Heh Heh
S-So black... There's something
so black about them.
Next up, the third match!
In the red corner, butler of the Azumamiya
household, Kaede Nonohara!
Nonohara, go for the win!
Get the 100 credits!
Fight!
Nonohara...
And... his opponent is...
What?!
Power of Flower
And someday, even that bud
It's me!
Will bloom large right
in the middle of your heart
Interim butler of the Hanabishi
household, Hinagiku Katsura!
Power of Flower
Wh-Why is Hinagiku...
...a-a butler?
That is because I won against
Risa at rock-paper-scissors
and I gained the draft rights.
Hina wants to upset
the Superintendent's plans.
I want the 100 credits.
Well, it's a so-called
aligning of interests.
With this, victory is ours!
Good grief, an interim butler, is it?
People seem to have a lot of contempt
for our profession these days.
If I've offended you, I'm sorry.
But by no means did I enter
this Tournament as a joke.
Then, shall we begin?!
Yes!
I-Incredible!
Oh-ho. You're pretty good.
Nonohara, you seem awfully sure of yourself.
Why haven't you tried
to use your super lethal technique?
Th-That is...
Nonohara, go for the win!
Get the 100 credits!
But don't hit Miss Katsura!
No matter how powerful your technique is,
I, Hinagiku Katsura, will repel all
your attacks with everything I have!
Understood.
Then here I go.
Safety Shutter!
Safety Shutter
Super Explosive Flaming Slash of Darkness
I-I will not be beat!
What's wrong? Is that all you've got?
Safety...!
Nonohara, the build-up to your
technique takes a bit too long.
I win.
Th-The winner is Hinagiku Katsura!
Thank you.
For not going easy on me,
just because I'm a girl.
A butler fights with everything he has,
no matter the opponent.
Besides...
Even my master does not wish
for me to win against you.
Nonohara...
How did you like that?!
I'm one step closer to you two now!
She's great.
Yes, she is.
Hinagiku...
And finally, it was Hayate's turn.
Okay, next match!
In the red corner, butler of the
Sanzenin household, Hayate Ayasaki!
All right, here goes!
Now, who will be my opponent?
In the blue corner! Who the heck
is it under that mask?!
Mystery butler!
Free-style K!
Who could that be?
That air of dignity could only be
that of a true master.
Yes. And he's even got
a strange tiger with him, too.
Who in the world is it?
I don't know.
But don't let your guard down, Hayate.
Who might this mystery butler and tiger be?
Next time, he will fight against
a critically desperate situation.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Sign: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
G'morn! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
With a new warning, opening,
and ending, it's a fresh start.
Yes, it is, Miss.
Looks like we can fight
for another half a year with this.
I had all kinds of worries, but I guess
things have a way of working out.
That's not entirely true. This show has
a lot of people keeping an eye on it.
About the new opening song
we have starting today...
It's on a grand scale that makes
you think of the universe, isn't it?
You think so?
Though, of course,
it's still quite a nice song.
Buh-bye!
Preview
I guess it's been many months since then.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Hayate, you're always doing your best
and I'm grateful to you for that.
Miss...
Hakuou Academy Butler Battle Tournament
finally gets to the championship round.
Will Hayate Ayasaki manage
to remain a contender?
There is something
I absolutely must protect!
Hayate!
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Black Hayate
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Black Hayate".
At crosswalks, even
when you have a green light,
make sure you look around
and cross carefully!