Aoi found my weakness...
What do you mean?
Our team requires Saki methodically controlling the movements of the ball.
Aoi is countering that with a run-and-gun strategy.
The speed of their attacks is a far cry from ours.
I see.
They up the pace and shoot as much as they can?
Their field/goal percentage isn't half bad, either.
Yeah.
Our rhythm is all over the place. We're trapped in their rhythm.
They're playing us perfectly.
What are you gonna do, Coach?
Don't worry, I have a plan.
Good work, everyone.
You're doing well.
Huh? Onii-chan, we're losing.
They've been practicing very hard, too.
This doesn't compare to the last time.
But don't worry. I know how we can win.
That's my Subaru!
So what's the plan?
First of all, Airi, focus more on pressure defense this half.
On offense, don't roll too far to the basket.
Stand near the free throw line and support the others.
When you're on defense, fall back immediately.
Got it?
Y-Yes! I'll do it!
Okay.
Saki, this is what you need to do:
Okay!
Everyone!
Just keep running for the second half!
Oh!
This is a fairly complex strategy.
Can you do it?
It is... But let me try!
All right, then.
What's next, Subaru? What's next?
Oh! I'll do my best at whatever, too!
If there's anything I can do to help, please tell me!
You three will play the same way this half.
Eh? We'll depend only on Airi and Saki?
Well, it'd be great if you played a bit more offensively to help out Airi and Saki.
We'll attack harder to make up for Airi and Saki playing defense, right?
All right!
But, but! We have to work hard on defense, too.
Attack hard, defend hard!
That's my Subaru! I love simple explanations!
Saki, are you alright?
It's a bit tough, but that's what makes it fun, right?
How about you? Are you okay?
What?
Offense.
Don't go completely wild without me there.
I won't.
I'll do my best so you can do what you have to do.
All right. I'm expecting the best from you.
Hii!
Gettan!
Nice pass!
Kagetsu!
Yes!
Nice shot!
Hina-chan!
Take this!
So fast!
Mokkan!
Maho and the others suddenly got faster.
They left the offense to three players, so their attacks got simpler.
Of course their pace went up.
This seems like a simple strategy, but the players are doing it well.
Tsuba!
Masami! Please!
Please!
Again?
Masami! You're moving too far away from the basket!
Shoot at a distance where you know you can make it!
Too far? When did I...
Why isn't Masami shooting from her best spot?
Saki is pressuring her.
Huh?
Saki's defense seems normal at first,
but she's been forcing Masami-chan to shoot from an increasingly long distance every time.
How can you possibly pressure me?
Mind games are important in basketball too, you know.
I see.
You're having the Airi and Saki duo on defense.
If you only had Airi on defense, the other team will blow by her using their speed.
But I think you could have also gone with an all-out attack.
We'd have to watch our pace and it'd be a lot easier to mess up.
I wanted to maintain our usual play style.
I feel it's best to attack methodically.
Masami!
Don't mind me. My job is to shoot.
Dribbling, defense, pace...
I'm the worst in all those categories on this team.
That's why I've got to give it my all!
Not bad.
That's my Masami.
Of course!
This is the reason I'm on this team.
Crap! We won't lose!
It seems the 5th graders are running out of gas.
Are we going to win like this?
Or...
Hiiragi!
Yes!
It'll be a 4 point difference if they score here!
We've got this!
In the end, it all comes down to...
...the power of our aces!
I won't let you pass!
Oh? I won't lose!
A turn-around jumper...
That shouldn't be something a grade schooler is able to do.
Now it's tied.
Okay! Let's go!
Please!
Oh! Here you go!
Make this, Mo!
We all helped to get these points!
I won't let them go to waste!
No! I won't let you shoot!
So far away?!
No, this is...
Mokkan, you're the best!
You finally perfected your floater!
That was an amazing buzzer beater!
Oh! I was so surprised!
Great job, everyone.
Nice playing with you, Subaru.
Nice playing with you, too.
You really pushed us today.
Yes...
Tomoka and her teammates were tough.
First of all, we need to thank you all...
Not happening!
We're not becoming your slaves!
If we have to face such shame, then we'll quit playing basketball!
That's not true, Tsubaki-chan, Hiiragi-chan!
The 6th graders aren't going to...
You shut up, Aoi-oneesan!
You didn't think of a way for us to win!
You liar!
I'm sorry.
Do you two really think it was due to Aoi-oneesan that you lost?
W-We'll never be your underlings!
We're gonna quit playing basketball!
Wait!
Those two are extremely stubborn. I'll go after them.
That wasn't cool at all.
Masami.
You were amazing today. Not just your shot, your movements, too...
Silence.
Your words of encouragement just make me even angrier.
Um...
I'm going, too.
Okay.
Thanks, Aoi.
Selfish as it may be,
I want to say it was a lot of fun.
Do your best in the finals.
Aoi-chan!
Manaka-senpai...
Aoi, we'll go inside first to get seats.
Being a coach is... difficult.
Aoi-chan...
These thoughts just keep popping up in my head.
"If only I had done this, or that..."
Yeah.
Maybe they could have won, too...
Mokkan!
Maho!
Wow!
We should be able to win like this.
Yeah, even though they aren't playing their starters.
They're able to play this well against such a strong school...
They're really something.
Saki-chan!
Airi!
Pass the ball to me!
Okay! Got it!
Airi-san...
Aya, don't lose her!
You're the only one who can stop Airi-chan!
Yes!
Airi wants to show her how to play as a tall player.
Airi-san.
Here I go, Aya-chan!
Okay!
With a final score of 30 to 18, Keishin Academy's 6th grade girls' basketball team wins!
Thank you very much!
So smooth!
One, two!
Yeah! We won!
Let's have a great game next time, with our starters.
Sure, if we can...
No, we will play.
Um...
Thanks to you, Airi-san, I've come to enjoy basketball.
Let's both do our best.
Yes, Onee-sama!
See you!
Bye-bye!
Well, let's head to the party.
Maho's dad took the time to prepare it.
We shouldn't be late.
Okay!
Subaru!
Aoi, good timing.
Want to come with us to the party?
About that...
Wow! I didn't expect a simple party to be this great.
Yeah.
I've already told them I'll miss the party.
I want to go look for Tsubaki-chan and Hiiragi-chan.
Please excuse the interruption.
Would you please focus your attention on the stage?
This is Fuuga-sama's special present.
Is this our uniform?
Yes, we've prepared uniforms for all of you.
Wow! Matching uniforms!
It's like a dream come true!
I want to have them wear that and play in official matches.
Well then, let's get this started!
Beer party!
You can't! No alcohol!
Please don't worry. This is non-alcoholic beer for children.
Non-alcoholic?
Well, just relax for once.
You don't get to experience this often.
Miho-nee, you're getting way too excited.
Take this!
How's that for shot in the face?
Maho...
Here you go, Subaru-sama.
Take this!
Subaru, it's so cold!
Hey, wait!
Go! Double attack!
Wait, my glasses!
Fire!
Hina! Take this!
Onii-chan barrier!
Onii-chan, here I go!
Airi is...
That was pretty fun.
Tomoka? What's the matter?
Subaru-han?
Tomoka?
Subaru-han, where did you go?
I was so lonely!
What's up with you all of sudden?
Don't tell me you got drunk off these?
But they're non-alcoholic...
Subaru-hama...
You must stay at my side forever! Forever and ever!
To-Tomo—!
You smell so nice! I won't let go!
Don't tell me you're regretting it.
We're not regretting anything!
Not playing basketball is a lot more relaxing!
Yes, yes! There's no point if we can't beat Maho!
Basketball wasn't a fit for us from the very beginning.
See? I'm so short.
The two of us are invincible, but we can't show our full potential in a five-person team.
Are you serious?
Hahaha! So funny!
Now that's what losers should act like!
Who're you?
I hope I'm wrong. Are you laughing at us?
No, I'm not.
I'm just here to see how losers cry.
What the hell?
Hmph, we lost the finals and our coach didn't care at all.
I came here because I wanted to see her sorry face.
But seeing your pathetic faces made me feel a lot better.
Watch it, you midget. Let us teach you a lesson!
I'll teach you not to mess with 5th graders!
Sure! Come at me!
Want to settle this with basketball?
Your wild boar powers were pretty scary!
What are you talking about?
You're talking like I'm a wild boar.
That's not what I'm getting at.
I think it's kinda cute.
Huh? Cute?
Like how a wild boar sniffs using his snout.
Its thick fur, too.
Oh, that?