The Shimogamo Shrine is located
in the triangular area surrounded
by the Takano and Kamo rivers.
Although there are mountains of
shrines with noble lineages in Kyoto,
Shimogamo Shrine is one of the foremost
among the ones that existed
prior to the Heian period.
Though scores of visitors
go there throughout the year
to receive matchmaking and all
kinds of other blessings from the gods,
few know that a small ramen cart
appears in the vicinity each and every night.
It's called Neko Ramen.
[neko: cat]
The rumor is it uses
actual cats to makes the broth,
but whether that's true or
not cannot be ascertained.
However, the taste is unmatched.
You are a person of Shimogamo Yuusuisou, yes?
In fact I am a resident of Shimogamo Yuusuisou.
Yes, and...?
I also live there.
Shimogamo Yuusuisou is a boarding
house behind Eizan Demachiyanagi Station,
and it's apparently exactly the same as it
was since it was rebuilt after it disappeared
during the violence of the final
days of the Tokugawa shogunate.
If it weren't for the light leaking out the
windows, it would be no different than ruins,
and when I visited there at the introduction
of the University Co-op at the start of school,
It's no wonder I thought I'd
accidentally stumbled into Kowloon City.
Ah, that's it!
I remembered that I have spotted this queer,
curious fellow quite a number of times.
I am a god of Shimogamo Shrine.
My proper name is Kamotaketsunuminokami.
K-Kamotake?
Kamotaketsunominokamo.
Don't make me say it twice.
But the second time was different...
You didn't know?
I know everything about you.
Your parents' names, how you were always
throwing up and making sour smells as a baby,
your nickname during elementary school,
the middle school cultural festival,
your fleeting first love during high school,
the first time you watched an adult video,
your life as a ronin, and your lazy,
idle days spent after entering college.
You've got to be kidding me!
After suffering romantic disappointment
in the club of your dreams,
unable to open up to people,
before long you started getting
in the way of people's path to love.
And why have you spent these
two years in such a timid state?
That's because Ozu...
I accept that you have had your soul
somewhat dirtied by the influence of Ozu.
But that is not all, is it?
The past two years go rambling through
my brain like swaying paper lanterns.
At the sacred woods of
Shimogamo Shrine, of all places,
my delicate heart was seized
by painful memories, and...
Ahhhh!
...is what I wanted to scream out,
but I restrained myself like a gentlemen.
N-None of your business.
It's got nothing to do with you.
It will soon be Kannazuki.
I must travel to Izumo once again.
It is our job, yes, but it is quite a lot of
work, and don't make light of the train fare.
In this age we just toss everyone's proposals
into the wooden box for
"already inspected" with hardly a look.
And yet as I am a serious fellow,
I can't help but to be deep
in thought, scratching my head
thinking about which two people
would be most suited for each other,
almost like a matrimonial agency.
Woe is me.
Don't you think?
I don't follow in the slightest.
When fall comes we gather at Izumo,
and decide the relationships of man and woman.
Here is the name Akashi-san, whom you know.
And here are you and the name Ozu.
Do you understand?
Understand what?
You're even stupider than I thought.
As a god of matchmaking,
I am preparing to match this woman
you know, Akashi-san, with someone.
In other words, it's between you and Ozu-kun.
If you desire, come to my room.
Shimogamo Yuusuisou, room 210.
This strange fellow is saying he is trying
to tie Akashi-san to either Ozu or me.
The Tatami Galaxy
When I was in high school
I didn't participate in any club activities
and just stayed cooped up with
a bunch of other layabout guys.
But now I was a brand-spanking
new freshman university student
and countless doors to the
mystical treasure that is known as
that "rose-colored
campus life" lay open before me.
I was half-swooned with glee.
And the one I chose was...
Cupip
Among the raven-haired maidens
working up an invigorating sweat,
I would begin the rally of love!
...is what I, a fool
beyond all help, had thought.
The first summer.
My still-as-of-yet rose-colored self was
cut to the quick by that which is called reality.
Making 100 friends wouldn't be
so bad, or so I frivolously thought,
but I was soon made aware of just how difficult
casually getting to know other people could be.
My wish of a rally unfulfilled,
I was not even able to hit back,
and my serves were left unreturned.
I tried training myself to
be sociable and easy-going,
but I wasn't part of the
conversation to begin with.
By the time I realized I had to be sociable
in order to be included in the conversation,
it was already too late. I had
lost my place among the circle.
It was then that an ominous man
stood beside me with a face of ill portent.
Are you some messenger from hell
that only delicate little me can see?
You say some pretty mean things.
There's no need to worry, I am your compatriot!
That was my first contact with
Ozu, as well as worst contact.
Anyway, it's quite a contrast, isn't it?
Maybe I should mix it up over there myself.
The place where the Kamo and Takano rivers join
below the Shimogamo Shrine is
referred to as the "Kamo River Delta,"
Us, Concealed
Party Area
and is widely used as a location for parties
from spring through summer.
Ozu is in the same year I am.
8 in 10 people who saw him in the
dark would mistake him for a youkai,
and the remaining two could be convinced of it.
Eating the unhappiness of
others as a topping on his rice,
he's a man with seriously
not a single point of praise.
My soul would have surely stayed
unblemished were it not for having met him.
Hey, are you gonna turn on me?
I'm just joking with you.
Stop touching me!
But the night breeze is so chilly...
You lonely bastard!
Damn it... Why does it have to be you
next to me instead of a raven-haired maiden?
Oh, look. Akashi-san came, too.
See, over there.
Let me see!
She's in the engineering department, so
maybe she's designing for Birdman or something.
Hey, maybe we should call it off for today...
I don't want to get Akashi-san mixed up in this.
What are you saying? What happened
to your pride as a "Black Cupid"?
Well, sure I have my pride, but to someone
from the outside, this just looks like...
You're going to let your conviction bend because
you're worried about what other people think?
Well I, who have dedicated both my
body and soul, am not a person such as that.
Are you not here today precisely because
you bear this loneliness and isolation?
They are the ones that
have lost sight of reality!
You must bring the hammer down upon those
who have lost themselves among frivolous dreams!
Now, without further ado!
Hear ye, hear ye! For we
are the ones who hinder love!
We will now rain the heavens down upon
you merrymaking ladies and gentlemen!
Id... iot...
Yes, we may be idiots, but
you guys should watch out for us!
Bottle rocket fireworks are for the
purpose of rocketing up into the night sky.
Doing things like holding them in your hand,
aiming them at people, or using
them to bomb people over rivers
having a peaceful, harmonious
party are quite not allowed.
Hold your ground! Counterattack!
Oh?
You damn barbarians!
That's one shallow river!
We're gonna smack you good!
Hey, Ozu, they're not all out!
Hey!
Since I had met Ozu it was just
cutting, cutting, and more cutting
the red threads that stretched
across the circle like at Yasui-konpiragu.
At these activities Ozu was ingenious,
and there were even villainous rumors
that there was no personal information
we did not know and make use of,
and that we would
scatter oil and then light fires,
and whether that was true
or not it was spread around
and it was an environment
where we were set up as guys
who constantly enjoyed blazing scenes
of carnage here and there inside the circle.
Like some incarnation of evil,
a disgrace among all homo sapiens.
Even after we were kicked out of the circle,
we did not let our activities slacken,
we expanded globally,
and cloaked as gods of death the evil name of
the "Black Cupids" roared throughout the land.
If there was a maiden in love in the
east we'd say "Give up on that freak,"
or for a man in the west worried
about one-sided love we'd advise
"Just give up, it's no use."
If the spark of love was sprinkled in the
south, we'd immediately pour water on it,
and it's said love in the
north is impossible to begin with.
Sometimes our victims came close to
drowning us in the canals of Lake Biwa,
surrounded the boarding house, made
me hide in a manga cafe in Kitashirakawa,
or cried at me in the middle of
Konoe Street when I spoke too frankly.
But I didn't lose, I couldn't lose,
even though I was sure that losing would
have let me and everyone else be happier!
Except for Ozu. I could care less if he's happy!
As I was walking, catching my breath
after having run all the way to Kiyamachi,
under the overhang of someone's house
I was caught by an old woman who
emitted a suspiciously ghoulish aura.
This unplaceable aura was
persuasive, and thinking logically,
there was no way that the
fortune-telling of a creature
who emits such an aura
could be anything but spot on.
What do you want to know?
Your face is a face of extreme
impatience... You are unsatisfied.
I can feel that you are
not blessed with a situation
where you can make the most of your talents.
Yes, that's exactly right!
I can sense your fiercely earnest talent.
Quickly I did tip my hat to
the old woman's keen insight.
To perceive my good sense and talents in
an instant and yet be so very unassuming,
like how a master always hides their true
ability, it made even me forget where I was.
Anyway, I sense there is an
opportunity you can't let pass by.
An opportunity?
As in an excellent chance.
Yes, I know what it means...
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
You must grab this opportunity and act on it.
It's still somewhat vague.
Can you be more specific?
And if you do not!
You will walk this life as now, ever unchanging.
That'll be 1000 yen.
But you haven't answered anything yet!
Playing the lost lamb?
A friend of yours, Ozu-kun?
You shameless bastard!
How the hell are you popular all of sudden?
Now that's just uncalled for.
Force feeding me such a bundle of fungi?
What is with these ribbed bits?
She's the dental hygienist
at the dentist I go to.
She looked totally drunk
and asked me out for drinks.
Dentist?
And what about you?
I bet you've never had a young
lady like that stick her fingers
in your mouth your entire life, right?
Don't bring me down to your level.
Oh, yeah?
I know you visited the god of
matchmaking at the Shimogamo Shrine.
I just wanted to do it once for fun!
Speaking of which, what
do you think of Akashi-san?
In other words, it's between you and Ozu-kun.
What do I think?
I had thought I was the
only person unfortunate enough
to actually be able to comprehend a
human being as dumb as yourself, but...
Shush, you.
I think she might go out with you.
This is an opportunity!
Now look here.
I'd much rather have a
beautiful raven-haired maiden
that makes you go "whoa..." than someone who
is able to comprehend a person such as myself.
Why so selfish?
Don't tell me you're still hung up
on being dumped by Kohinata-san
when we were freshman, right?
Say not that name in my presence.
Then I'll become happy in your place.
I'll take this opportunity.
Now see here. Akashi-san
is not interested in you.
Don't give me that depressed look.
I pray for your victory.
Shut up!
Thanks to you I've wasted
my perfectly lovely college life!
Oh? I think you're also to blame for that.
After all, it doesn't
matter which path you took,
you'd keep ending up right where you are now.
At any rate, once I met you I put all
my efforts into making you no good.
Why do you haunt me so?
It's the way I show my love!
We're connected by the black thread of fate, after all.
The Japan Trench
A chill went down my spine as a
fearsome phantom rose into my mind.
Senpai, if you want to
eat any more, please hurry.
Akashi-san, why are you here?
You really are pretty dense, aren't you?
This is the usual place
for the after-party, yes?
The Birdman Circle is camped out over there.
I haven't eaten meat in a
while, so if you don't mind...
Meat after a party? Do they have
no pride as an agricultural people?
Where's Ozu?
He already ran out the back door.
You escape too, Senpai.
That bastard's left me behind again!
I will handle the bill, so out the
back. That's what I came to say.
I'm in your debt!
Forget about the debt, just keep your promise.
Never mind. Hurry and leave, I have to get back.
I met Akashi-san the previous year during a
part time job at the Shimogamo used book fair.
A year younger than I, said to
be in the engineering department,
and meticulously prepared at
anything and everything she does,
it felt like just one stare from her eyes
and even a shoplifter would stay their hand.
Oh, really?
What do you do on vacations, Akashi-san?
Why do I have to tell you something like that?
After that she was not someone
who was asked her weekend plans.
I sent her off with a fiery cheer of
"You just keep doing things your own way!"
Good evening.
What are you doing?
Don't just barge into my room!
How dare you just stroll on in...
It's a Castella.
You can have it, so chill out.
You giving someone something? That's rare...
You can't get any lonelier than
eating a giant Castella all by yourself.
Pining for a taste of a person's love...
Get out! I'm busy!
Is this really necessary?
Leave!
He probably came to visit the person in
this boarding house known as "the master."
This Castella is surely the leftovers.
Nevertheless, just as Ozu said, a Castella
like this is to be eaten together with someone.
Most definitely not Ozu.
Perhaps with Akashi-san...
Even I was surprised that
Akashi-san's name came to mind.
Could that strange man who called himself
a god and said he was heading out to Izumo
to decide the relationships between man
and woman seriously be telling the truth?
Kannazuki. In other words, the 10th lunar month.
The myriad gods gather at Izumo,
leaving vacant the various lands.
This is quite well known. Even I know that.
And among those gods there are sure to be
some of suitable peculiarity. That is not the issue.
The question I have often pondered is for
what reason all those gods would gather at Izumo.
And written right there it says that, at Izumo,
after a boisterous and outspoken argument,
the myriad gods decide the
relationships between man and woman!
Don't they have anything better to do?
Now that I'd ascertained the truth,
it would be best for me to climb
the stairs and see this god face to face.
But if that god from yesterday went...
Ha ha, I got you good!
...or something, I couldn't stand it.
I'd surely end up cursing myself and spending
the second half of my life in a right mess.
Even if that man is really a god,
it's not like I'm burning with passionate love;
it would go against my beliefs
to seek the comfort of a stranger
from this transient loneliness.
Is it not because I scorn
those inexcusable students
who cannot bear the isolation
and greedily seek out others
that I ran to the name of limitless
notoriety as "one who hinders love"?
This guise of a barren,
agonizing, wretched life...
Have not I finally reaped the victory close
at hand from the endless number of defeats?
Would I, the one who hinders love,
forgive myself for changing the way I live?
Or will it end with me
providing entertainment to the gods
as the spider's thread to which I cling snaps?
Then I'll become happy in your place.
Although I don't think Akashi-san would
be fooled by a freaky, finicky youkai like Ozu,
I feel like her compassion may be deep enough
to find a monstrous man like him intriguing.
If this continues and Ozu and
Akashi-san become friendly with each other,
this will no longer be a problem of my own love;
it will become entangled
with Akashi-san's future.
I felt like even my reason was crumbling
to pieces like the Castella before me.
I'm not gonna lose!
I'm not gonna lose to pining for love!
The taste is definitely unmatched,
but unfortunately no one
knows where they'll set up.
It's a ramen stand that
comes and goes as it pleases.
You go there quite often, yes, Senpai?
Well, I have a good nose.
When I'm hungry, if I cock my ear
I can hear Neko Ramen's wind chime.
I would like to try eating there as well.
Let go! Let go, Akashi-san!
I s-s-squished it... I squished it...
Now, now, calm down.
I apologize. I am not fond of moths.
These are called Mochiguman, and they
come in sets of five, but I have lost one.
Worry not! As this earth is round,
you are sure to meet once again!
Or if you'd like, I'll help you search for it.
I'd rather you take me to Neko Ramen.
If that's what you want.
Then it's a promise.
Promise? Ah, that's it.
After careful analysis,
indeed over-analysis of things,
I calmly execute a perfect countermeasure.
Or rather, I'm a man who doesn't
hesitate to analyze to the point
where a perfect countermeasure
becomes out of reach.
Analyzing the number of different
patterns of Akashi-san's life and my life,
I quickly came to a conclusion as to who
should become happy, and who should not.
But the most vexing
question of all was whether I,
who had hindered the path
of love for countless people,
could at this juncture change the way I live.
As a result of the life or death struggle
between love and reason that occurred within me,
I stumbled in my sleep-deprived
state to knock on door 210.
Yeah?
You can't give her to Ozu!
Give Akashi-san to me!
Right. Good, wait here a moment.
Oh? Understood, yes...
Meet me before 8 PM on
the east side of Kamo-oohashi.
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Stopping on top of the bridge is dangerous!
Oh, so today is Gozan.
Now you will cross this Kamo-oohashi.
When you do, Akashi-san will
come walking from the other side.
Strike up a conversation about
something and ask her out on a rendezvous.
No way! I refuse!
Stop your whining.
Something isn't right here!
Weren't you going to
Izumo and being a matchmaker?
This sort of preparation is also important.
This is nothing but a frontal attack!
Stop complaining and get out there.
Everything until now is water under the bridge!
Now's the time to push forward
toward that rose-colored campus life!
Senpai, good evening.
You escaped safely last night?
Thanks to you, yeah...
Here for Gozan?
Yes yes.
Bye!
That went well.
That's enough for today.
I was able to come this far despite
learning not even the slightest
bit about running the path of love!
This was plenty!
Oh, hey!
You just thought something like
"that's enough for today," didn't you?
Don't defy the words of a god,
hurry up and run along the path of love!
Are you saying this was all your plot?
You made a wish to the
god of matchmaking, right?
I don't want your help!
Now's the time to grab this opportunity!
If you don't make a
serious move now, I'm jumping!
Wait a sec!
How do my love life and you jumping
have anything to do with each other?
I'm not too sure myself.
Ozu-san! The river is swollen.
You will die if you jump in.
You damn traitor!
You've got nowhere to run, Ozu!
Revenge for the fireworks? But, this is...
Ozu-senpai, have you done some more mischief?
You evil, good-for-nothing...
Ozu!
You're a friend of his?
Me? I don't know Ozu at all...
Don't!
I can't shake off the feeling of regret
for choosing the tennis circle "Cupid"
in front of that fateful clock tower.
If then I had chosen some other circle, I would
have surely spent quite a different two years.
Perhaps I could have grasped
the mystical treasure that is known
as that "rose-colored campus life."