kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
I wonder why I can't play well.
Really.
Noël-chan?
The Rainy Season Sky
The Glass Rainbow
Do you have your wallet?
Yes, ma'am!
Identification?
Handkerchief?
Yes, ma'am!
Tissues?
Map?
Yes, ma'am!
Compass?
Rations?
Yes, ma'am!
Helmet?
Sidearm?
Eh?
Grenades?
Eh?!
She's joking, Kana-chan.
What's with that? You scared me there...
If you had calmly thought about it, you would've realized.
That was mean, Rio-senpai.
It seems like their relationship has been improving lately.
Rio's almost like an overly fretful mother.
Here. This is today's list.
Listen up.
Your mission today is to head into town to buy the supplies on that list, got it?
Yes, ma'am!
Well, then. Drive safely now, okay?
Proceeding with departure.
Come home soon!
We're having pot-au-feu tonight!
Don't be late!
Just like a mother, eh?
This is the first time isn't it, Noël-chan?
For the two of us to come into town together like this.
Although...
Come to think of it, this is basically my first time going into town.
Amazing!
What's that?
It's totally different from during the festival.
It's a very peaceful and quiet town.
Ow...
The first one was a Nue, a roof ornament that is found only in Trois.
It is used to ward off evil spirits.
The next one was a drinking fountain.
Its carved head was modeled after the twelfth Helvetian Archduke, Akira Arkadia II.
We have arrived.
The things from before...
Orders were to drive safely.
Thank you! I get it now!
Noël-chan, you sure are smart.
Um, girls?
You coming in or not? Could you hurry up and decide?
You're blocking the store.
You're the old lady from the festival!
Young lady.
Splitting hairs. Bad.
You're such an intractable child as always, aren't you?
Then how about calling me Naomi?
Naomi-san?
So the next shipment is next month?
By the way, does she know?
Uh-uh.
As always, you girls are such an unusual bunch.
Even though you're soldiers—
Um... excuse me!
Wh-What is it?
What's that?
You were interested in that when you first arrived, too.
You like it?
Um... C-Can I touch it?
A-flat.
This is a fish, right? What's it called?
Ah... that's...
It's not a fish.
But...
It's a dolphin, which was closer to a human than a fish.
It was a marine mammal that lived when there was still life in the ocean.
Ocean? They lived in the ocean?
How wonderful...
That old guy is quite good at making this type of stuff, isn't he?
As always, his face doesn't look it, but he's quite the romantic.
You know the one who made this?
There's a large workshop on the outskirts of town. All of this glasswork comes from there.
I want to see it — the place where they're made.
No problem.
What is?
We are heading there next.
I see! So Takemikazuchi's parts are also made there, huh?
Correct. Naomi is also collecting parts from the previous age.
But Noël-chan, you sure are amazing! You can fix that complex machine in a jiffy.
In a jiffy?
I can't even memorize all of the bugle's signal codes. My head's at its limit!
It is really... not that difficult...
Eh?
Machines... will not... betray you.
Noël-chan—
Okay!
Your change is 2,750,000 yen!
Eh?! We get that much back?!
Incorrect. Our change should be 2.75 yen.
The same as always, Noël-chan.
Here's your change.
She's right.
The one that's been playing the bugle in the morning recently is you, isn't it?
Y-Yes!
I'm still not that good. Sorry...
It's okay; I like it!
How should I put it... It completely wakes me up.
I was thinking that I need to hurry up and master it, so I don't cause trouble for the people of this town.
Seiya, that's not fair!
Kanata, I...
You'll never catch me!
Ow...
Ah, sorry—
Ha! You ran into someone!
I am really sorry!
Oh? It's you girls.
You're the clueless girl.
You're from the festival.
That's a relief.
Have you fully recovered?
You're a murderer!
Seiya-san, they have nothing to do with your parents.
They're all the same! I hate soldiers!
Get the heck out of town!
Day after day, you play that bugle horridly in the morning!
It's annoying!
Hey, Seiya!
I'm really very sorry for his rudeness!
It's okay...
He's a war orphan, so when he sees a soldier he becomes really angry.
Noël-chan...
I am fine.
We are soldiers, and that is the truth.
So...
Noël-chan...
Yeah, that's right... We're soldiers.
When I enlisted, I also swore the Oath of Paradores.
Although, I had believed I understood...
Just what am I saying?
I knew what was involved from the beginning.
Now's not the time to be unsure!
That's right! The more time I spend, the better I'll become.
If there isn't a signal bugle, everyone will be troubled.
You can see it.
Is that the glass factory?
That's amazing, Noël-chan.
It's the first time I've seen such a large building!
This one's no good either?
Is it a problem with the aberration?
The refraction shouldn't be the issue...
I-I'm the new recruit, Sorami Kanata!
Nice to meet you!
Same.
And, uh... I...
How was it until the error came up?
The seek time was virtually the same.
The distortion around the peripheral was smaller than before.
Sorry!
The boss doesn't see anything else when he starts working.
But he's amazing, that Carl-ojisan.
He holds the title of Meister that only five people in the nation have.
He once won a competition in the capital and even presented his work to the Archduke.
Maria, if you have time to chit chat, why don't you go work?
Got it! Sorry, Boss.
The Meister title is a stupid little thing anyway.
I'm not good enough to make this right yet.
What's that?
It's Takemikazuchi optical sensor lens.
That's the original one.
In order to repair Takemikazuchi, we require two more of them,
so I requested to have them made.
But it is not going well.
Even though they're this pretty?
For the lenses, there is more to them than just silicon dioxide.
Also mixed in are sodium oxide and magnesium oxide.
Furthermore, there are chromatic and peripheral aberrations.
In other words, it corrects the distortion of images.
But we do not know the distribution.
This thing is like some ancient, magic item.
I thought that glass was just pretty.
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
You can collect high quality silicon in Seize,
so there are several small factories that primarily work on hand-made art.
This factory is one of those.
But when the war intensified,
the need for glass increased.
Because of that, this factory became larger.
Kanata, I like machines.
Yeah.
But machines can also hurt people.
Takemikazuchi must have also killed many people in the past.
To tell you the truth, machines for killing people... really are terrifying.
Yeah...
Although, maybe the scary part isn't the machine itself, but rather the people who used it, right?
I mean, take a look at this bugle.
It's like that when I play it, but when Rio-senpai plays it, it sings beautifully.
Tanks must be the same way, right?
And recently, Rio-senpai played the song from inside Takemikazuchi for me.
It sang so beautifully.
I'm sure it was a good tank — the Takemikazuchi.
Oh right, next time let's—
Noël-chan...
Let her sleep for a while.
She usually doesn't sleep at all.
Noël-chan works real hard... to fix up the Takemikazuchi.
I know.
This young lady is a real craftsman.
Or else I wouldn't have taken such a troublesome request.
Here. Cover her with this.
Thank you.
By the way, you girls dropped by Windmill, right?
Is Naomi-san doing well?
Yes! Naomi-san also said that he was a wonderful romantic.
Did you hear that? Isn't that great, Boss?
Shut up. Hurry up and get back to work!
Oh! He's angry. Time to get back to work...
But, is that old technology really that amazing?
Yeah. But the boss always says:
"No matter how amazing it is, as long as humans made it, there's no way we can't do it either!"
You think so too, right?
Yes... or so I'd like to say...
I see.
It's true that Rio-san's playing is very different from yours.
I'm so envious. I don't know if I'll be able to play it like her.
I intend to work as hard as possible.
Even my lips — here, look — they've become this swollen.
But...
Regardless of how much I play and I play, it still doesn't come out the same as senpai's.
I guess I don't have the talent...
Missy.
Y-Yes?
"Talent" is the lamest excuse for those who quit.
Give that to me.
I don't know about playing bugles...
But young people often find failure here.
Missy, are you forcing the sound out?
I'm not trying to make it into this shape.
The glass, you see, wanted to become like this.
Thank you very much, Carl-ojisan!
Let the sound resound the way it wants.
Morning?
Yeah, the sun came out a bit early just for her.
That girl is also a craftsman.
It's a nice sound.
Sound?
Glass will produce different sounds based on the type and amount of impurities it has.
That is, even if our ears cannot differentiate it,
someone who has perfect pitch should be able to discern it.
Kanata can find the one that sounds closest to the original from all the ones made so far.
If she does, then perhaps...
Now then, listen to their voices, missy.
Yes, sir!
Noël-chan's changed a lot since she came here.
You think so?
Yeah!
It worked! It worked, Noël-chan!
Thank you.
This is the first time I've seen Noël smile.
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
Mountain Climbing
The Edge of the World
Next time: Mountain Climbing · The Edge of the World