There are many springs
hidden in the forests around Meirocho.
It's said that the gods, unseen by us,
gather by these waters,
and their presence makes these places holy waters
for Urara to nourish their power.
The water also cleanses your body.
This is a holy training ground
where we offer up our prayers.
That's why...
we certainly did not come here for a dip
because it's been hot lately!
That has ZERO believability!
We're gonna have class outside in the forest!
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose the way to their fate,
or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Girls, you're all quite tired from all the studying
you've been doing lately, right?
So take today to stretch and relax as much as you want!
Yay!
Yay! Let's swim! Let's swim!
Okay, my turn!
Ta-dah! Whaddya think?
It's my special skin-tight swimsuit!
Hey, Koume!
I don't think you should be wearing that...
that lewd outfit to such a sacred place.
What? You look way worse than I do.
O-oh no, what should I do?!
No worries!
I thought this might happen,
so I brought swimsuits for everyone!
See-thru!
My, girls, what wonderful swimsuits!
Chiya's in an energetic red!
Nono's in a cute, light yellow one-piece!
And I knew Kon had to wear this one!
A maid-themed swimsuit!
Why am I the only one with one like this?
It has to be you!
It's my special design for you,
as the brilliant genius designer Koume-chan!
I've got other ones like a kunoichi style,
or a shrine maiden style!
I never asked for these!
Okay, let's all go together!
Line up!
Huh?
One, two, three!
Oh, my.
Chiya, you really did it this time!
What is this?
I'm naked!
Ch-Chiya!
Put this on!
No! It just gets in the way!
This isn't lewd, it's cute and refreshing.
Even MORE
see-thru!
Come on, I'll tie it in the back for you.
Hmph!
Jeez. Nobody can stop Chiya when she's out in nature.
No, there's something that can.
Huh?
There are a lot of them in these kinds of places.
My natural enemy.
Natural enemy?
Sharp claws!
Crabs?
Jeez, you need to stop being so scared of these things.
Their little claws are so small and cute-
Crabs are scary!
Claws are scary!
Padded
HEY!!
Nono, I see you brought Matsuko-san, too.
Y-yeah. I'd feel bad leaving her behind...
Thank you, Nono.
This feels so good!
So scary!
Kon?
POKE
Don't you think you've grown a little too much lately?
Hey!
Right back at you!
SQUISH
Koume, u-um, maybe
you should cut down on the sweets.
Hey... huh?
What's wrong, Nono?
N-no way!
I can't get out?!
Th-that tickles!
Help me!
Nono, you look like a bug
that fell over and can't get up!
A bug?!
Meanwhile,
at another
spring...
Stare...
Nothing wrong with this spring!
Captain Saku's kneecaps are so awe-inspiring!
I didn't see anything wrong, either!
Captain Saku's ankles are so cool!
Are you sure you saw
a suspicious individual around here?
Of course!
Well then, we've got to take a better look.
Wh-why don't we look inside the spring, Captain Saku?
I see. He could be hiding underwater.
Captain Saku'll be so beautiful in the water!
The captain'll be totally soaked!
We'll assist you, Captain!
What're you doing, you harlots?!
Y-you've got it all wrong, Captain!
It's been a really long time
since we've hung out like this!
We've done nothing but study for a while.
We might be Urara, but we're normal girls, too.
We still want to go out and play like other normal girls.
What's this?
Kon's not serious at all today.
I-it's fine!
I'm a delinquent today. A foxy deviant.
Well then, Miss Fox, what should we do next?
Huh?
U-umm, well, there's something I've always wanted to do.
Ooh, ooh, what kinda game is it?
W-well, it's not really a game! It's...
Come on, spit it out already!
I-I want to do something we shouldn't.
I-I didn't mean it like that!
I wanna try the underwater spring technique!
O-oh, is that all?
You scared us.
Underwater spring technique? What's that?
UNDERWATER
SPRING
TECHNIQUE
Um... Well, it's a secret technique done by two Urara,
who use the spring water to dissolve and entwine
their powers with each other,
and it's supposed to temporarily boost
divining power for both.
Really?
I never knew that. Sounds convenient.
Yeah, but it won't work if you
don't get along with the other person,
and there's the risk of one person
absorbing the majority of the power,
so it's a technique that nobody should try.
Oh, that's why you said it's something we shouldn't do.
So it's forbidden play...
That still sounds perverted.
It's not perverted at all!
I've wanted to give it a try ever since
I read it in a book when I was little...
But I can't do it by myself.
I've always dreamed of trying it!
You sure have a lot of those dreams.
Okay, let's do it now!
Let's do all the things you wanted to do
when you were all alone, Kon!
Chiya...
W-well, later, I wanna try jump rope, and blindfold tag,
and shadow tag, and hide-and-seek, and guess who,
and skipping stones, and statues...
and, uhh, oh, we played kokkuri already...
Jeez, how many do you have?
Kon, how do we do the spring water technique?
Um, first, you both get in the water,
and hold each other's hands.
Then you make sure you're breathing in sync
and count to three.
Wow, that sounds easy!
Nono, let's give it a try!
O-okay.
Let's go!
On the count of three, we'll-
A-alright, Nono!
Let's start with putting our heads underwater!
Let's give it a try, Kon!
O-okay.
I know we can do it!
We're really good friends!
You said you have to get along really well, right?
That's right.
We are good friends.
Yay! Friends, friends!
What're those two doing?
No idea.
Okay, let's do it, Chiya.
One, two...
One...
Dissolving and mixing my power with Chiya's.
Is it like melting together and becoming one?
Two...
I feel like the water's getting warmer.
Three...
Four red eyes swaying in the water.
Two bad, bad girls.
Now, who is looking...
...and who is being looked at?
I-is this...
Kon?!
Are you alright, Kon-chan?
Y-yes.
My leg just got caught on something...
And then we couldn't get Nono's butt out of her float!
Stop, Koume-chan!
You sure have grown, Nono.
You too, Sis?!
The float was just small!
Well, your swimsuit got snipped by a crab, Koume-chan!
Chiya?
You saw it.
Huh?
You divined my true form...
You bad girl.
As punishment, I will take something precious from you.
Ch-Chiya?
Give it to me.
N-no!
Give it to me. Give it to me. Give it to me.
No, no! Stop!
Someone...!
A... a dream?
Chiya? You're awake?
Huh? Wh-wh-what?
Hey, cut it out!
Hey, if you can't sleep, can we talk?
Chiya?
Umm, the reason you're feeling down
is because of the spirit we saw in the spring, right?
So you saw it too, that black... ghost.
Yeah, it was just for a second, but I definitely saw it.
But as soon as I saw it, it vanished.
I've been thinking about it ever since.
About what?
You said you saw a spirit out in the field, right?
Yeah.
Maybe the spirit you saw back then
and the one we saw today are the same?
Maybe it's one of the gods of Meirocho.
You think it's a god of Meirocho?!
Yeah, it's just a theory.
I think you have the power
to see spirits... no, to see gods,
and when we shared our powers in the spring,
I could see them, too.
Oh, yeah. Uh-huh?
Sorry, that was a little too complicated.
Umm, well, do you remember
the one thing Urara must never do?
Yeah. Never try to divine anything about the gods.
Yeah.
Urara must never divine
the true nature of the gods of Meirocho.
If you break that rule, you'll lose your powers forever.
I don't know what to do, Chiya.
I may have just broken that rule.
Wh-why would it be just you?
I saw it, too!
You can see the gods even without using
your divining powers, I'm sure of it...
I mean, you suddenly started divining
after what happened on the field, right?
And the underwater spring technique
is a type of divining.
I used divining power to force my way
into looking at the gods.
That's... forbidden.
And if I've really lost all my divining power,
then not only can I never become a Rank 1 Urara,
but I can't be with you guys, either!
Thinking about that has me so scared...
Ch-Chiya?
Um, h-hey, wait! Chiya!
O-okay, wait! Wait!
Sit, Chiya!
Chiya...!
Chiya?
Becoming an Urara was my dream for the longest time.
I don't want it to be taken away from me like this.
I know...
Hey, Kon, do you remember
that night we looked for shooting stars?
We promised we'd both become Rank 1 Urara.
Your dream belongs to you, Kon.
Nobody can take it away from you,
so don't give up on it!
If the gods take away your power,
then I'll give you power.
I'm much, much closer to you than the gods!
And even if the gods say you're no good,
I'll always be with you!
Can you do that?
I can!
How?
That's what we'll figure out now!
Huh? Why are you laughing?
S-sorry, you just sounded so confident.
Huh?
Sorry. You really are amazing, Chiya.
It's like I'm already using a bit of your power.
How odd.
I was so scared until now.
Kon...
You're crying again!
This is different.
Huh? Then you're feeling better now?
Yeah.
Okay, then let's ask the gods!
"Did you really take away Kon's powers?"
"Are you mad?"
Huh? But...
It's okay!
If they're really mad at you, we'll just apologize together!
And ask them to give them back!
Anyone would forgive us
if we showed them both our bellies!
We're going to apologize like normal people!
You can use our bellies, too!
H-how long have you guys been here?!
From the beginning.
From the beginning?!
You guys snuck out in the middle of the night,
how are we not supposed to worry?
And Kon!
If you're so worried about something you're crying
about it, you should've talked to us about it sooner!
That's right, Kon-chan.
S-sorry.
We all want to help you.
So we brought this for you.
What is it?
Eating something sweet will
make you forget all about your worries!
Koume, you just wanted to have a moon-viewing party.
I'm just kidding!
Umm, we actually wanted to give you this.
If you really lost your divining powers, then you
wouldn't be able to do kokkuri fortune-telling, right?
It'll be a quick and easy way to figure out
what's going on, right?
I get it, Koume! You're so smart!
B-but, what if I really can't do fortune-telling anymore?
We'll figure that out if it happens.
It's okay! We'll be right with you!
You guys...
Okay, I'll try it.
I beseech you, O god.
Kokkuri, kokkuri, please come out.
Hear my heartfelt desires as divined.
If my powers have not been taken,
I beseech you to connect with me.
Come on.
Come on!
It...
it worked!
Kon! You did it, you did it!
Shh! Chiya, be quiet!
O... O Fox God, have I not broken your laws?
May I stay an Urara?
YES
Hooray, Kon!
You did it!
That's great, Kon!
Yeah, yeah!
I didn't break the rule!
I can still be an Urara!
That's right.
I bet what you saw wasn't a god, but an actual ghost.
Huh?
They say that spirits gather by the waters,
and if there were really that many there,
then one might end up attached to you.
Eek, a ghost!
Kon-chan!
Koume! Kon was finally feeling better!
Sorry!
If it wasn't a god, then what was it?
I dunno, but I think it's more fun
that something mysterious happened.
And we might know what it is someday!
Huh?
It's like carrying a treasure chest that's closed shut.
It's something to look forward to
tomorrow or the next day!
You really are amazing, Chiya.
Here!
So yummy!
There's a special kind of taste
to sweets secretly eaten at night!
If Nina-sensei finds out about tonight,
I wonder if she'll get mad at us again.
It's our little secret.
S-sorry to drag all of you into it.
Why're you treating us like strangers?
Sharing secrets is how we get to be even better friends!
A moonlit night.
Becoming better friends.
I know what we should do!
What?
Howl!
What's that? It sounds fun!
How do you do it?
Like this!
Kon, you've gotta put more heart into it,
and do it louder!
B-but...
You can do it whatever way you like!
Whatever way I like...
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Mothers and Knowledge are Sometimes for You"!
Let's use the invocation we learned a while back
to divine what kind of episode it'll be!
"Mothers and Knowledge are Sometimes for You"
Kon-chan, could you do it quieter?