This is my second year at high school
and the month of May is almost over.
Edogawa, who asked me to be her friend that day,
still hasn't done anything to suggest
that she's actually my friend,
But
but there was one major reason for it.
It was because Edogawa had a secret
that she couldn't tell anyone about.
a secret
I'm sure she really wanted to be friends with me,
but she must've been afraid
that her secret could be revealed.
But finally I found out what Edogawa's secret was.
It's not what you think!
I'm not a boy! It's like...
I don't know how to explain it, but...
Umm, umm...
My body somehow grows a penis every now and then!
Now that we both share her secret,
I must care for her and protect her as her friend...
as her best friend.
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
Deatta kouya no hana
Kowakute yasashikute
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 10                                             Ganbaranai
"FIGHTING AN ENEMY YOU CANNOT SEE"
Year 2 Class Left
A penis... A penis...
What's the matter, Sasami?
You sound like your brain's gone necrotic.
What? Oh, I'm just dealing with
one of those puberty issues...
But more importantly,
I wonder why I'm not making any more friends
even though I'm already in my second year.
According to my plan, I was supposed to have
a whole bunch of friends
CAN I MAKE A
HUNDRED FRIENDS?
because they just couldn't leave me alone
after I became a more cheerful person.
Ah...
What are you doing?
My hand is tired.
It's absurd that I have to use my own hand
to use chopsticks.
It's a pain in the butt.
Stop talking like me. You acquire food on your own.
STRAWBERRY
MILK
I feel more loved when others feed me.
COFFEE
MILK
There's no love. They do things for you
because they have no other choice.
That's mean!
Can't you tell I love you so much, Kagami?!
Don't scream misleading statements like that!
I love you for not abandoning me, Kagami.
Let me feed you, too.
I thought your hand was tired.
Just this once, okay?
Despite that, sweet Kagami never denies my action
and continues to dig herself into a hole
and eventually starts feeding me from her mouth.
What an evil plot!
That's seriously scary, Sasami!
I guess it's true that they're a couple.
I bet they have no interest in men.
They have no interest in women
who aren't interested in women, either.
Kneel before me, ignorant masses!
Oops, that was not it.
I meant, "Good day, everyone!" Right?
I see all your stupid faces here!
"The 1st Social Gathering for Year 2 Class Left
"2 Night 3 Day Lovey-Dovey Resort in Kuzuryu Shrine"
The 1st Social Gathering for Year 2 Class Left
"2 Nights 3 Day Lovey-Dovey
Resort in Kuzuryu Shrine"
Lovey-Dovey
I know this is out of the blue,
but we're going to enjoy our vacation
on the long holiday weekend!
The 1st Social Gathering for Year 2 Class Left
"2 Nights 3 Day Lovey-Dovey
Resort in Kuzuryu Shrine"
All-you-can-eat-and-drink at a beautiful resort!
It is absolutely free!
The more the merrier, so I'll take you guys with me, too!
I'm taking all of you with me
so that you could taste the joyous luck
of being in the same class with me, Jou Edogawa!
Y-you don't have to come if you don't want,
but I'm sure you have nothing better to do anyway,
so I'm ordering you to come with me!
You'll never have an opportunity like this
in your misfortunate life!
Feel hopeless!
We're feeling hopeless!
Now pick it up, ignorant masses! Be elegant! Be elegant!
You haven't told anyone about it, have you?
N-no.
I will kill you if you ever tell anyone about it.
Hey, Edogawa.
What?
Can I go on the trip with you, too?
Of course. As a matter of fact,
I will kill you if you don't.
You've got a cold.
You can't go to the social gathering.
No way. Edogawa is going to kill me!
You can't travel with this fever.
I don't care how much you hold
a grudge against me for this.
I'm not going to let you go outside today.
If something happens,
you could either press this button or recite a charm of
"I love, love, love my Big Brother".
I don't have that kind of energy.
Get some rest now, Sasami.
You idiot...
Yay! Yay!
Good morning, Mama-lin! How are you?
Tama? What are you doing here?
I didn't go on the trip.
Big Sister Tsurugi told me that
I could stay with you, Mama-lin!
That bitch...
She went on the trip while forcing me to babysit her!
Trip?
I want to go on a trip, too!
I want to go on a trip with you, Mama-lin!
Me, too. I want to go with you, too.
Oh yeah, I've got an idea!
Basically, this will solve all the problems. Got it?
Y-yeah...
Are you sure about that? Anyway, don't move.
It tickles!
Yamato wa kuni no mahoroba
Japan is the most magnificent country of them all
Tatanazuku aogaki yamagomoreru
Mountains spread like blue hedges
Yamatoshi uruwashi
My beloved Japan
Oh? Tama became Mama-lin?
I tied a psychic string to the circuit
inside your forehead with that kiss earlier.
I'll control you like a super robot by using that string.
Tama is a super robot?
From this room, I can sense everything
that you see, hear and feel.
You go attend the social gathering as me.
Okay! I'll do my best!
All right, let's go!
Did you call me, Sasami?
You must need my love. Where should I put my love?
Now show me where in your chest
it's throbbing for me, my sister!
Omohishi kotonoha
I'm putting my feelings into words
Tsuzurite todoke
Hope they reach you
Sasami-san
"Sasami-san" has entered the chat room.
"Tama, can you see this?"
Sasami-san
Tama, can you see this?
Um, Mama-lin. Let's see...
"Tama, can you see this?"
"Tama" has entered the chat room.
dekita?
Were you able to do it?
Sasami-san
Type in Japanese, okay?
"Type in Japanese, okay?"
Sasami-san
Were you able to do it?
"Were you able to do it?"
I see you're using your real name...
Anyway, just do as I tell you.
"Tama, can you see this?"
Anyway,
just do as I tell you.
Okay, I'll do my best!
What's the matter, Sasami?
Sasami-san
Tell him, "Big Brother, I got over the cold."
Tell him, Big Brother, I got over the cold.
What?
Sasami-san
Don't you read the "tell him" part!
Show him that you're feeling better.
Sasami-san
Look how good I'm feeling now!
You seem unnaturally well.
Sasami-san
Beg him to let you go on the trip.
So, Big Brother, can I go on the trip now?
Please, Big Brother!
Mama-lin... no, I mean...
I'VE been looking forward to it.
So let her wish come true,
I mean, let MY wish come true.
But...
Say I can go, please, Big Brother!
I love you so much because you're so sweet, Big Brother!
What's gotten into you, Sasami?!
What made you be so honest with your feelings?
You totally stole my heart with that comment.
Oh, I get it. Marriage, right?
I already have all paperwork ready for marriage,
and all you have to do is to sign your name.
Law is our only enemy, you know.
"Marriage"?
I'll marry you, Big Brother!
What?! Normally I'd be greeted by
a body blow or a choke hold,
but what is this, a dream?!
No, this is my happy ending even if it's a dream!
No, it's my true happy ending! I can die now!
But we won't be able to love each other if you die.
I want to be lovey-dovey with you, Big Brother!
What are you saying?
Just go ahead and go!
I'll do my ultra best!
"I'll do my ultra best!"
All right, Big Brother! Let's go on the trip!
You must be talking about the honeymoon!
Now let's go and write the story of our love!
Yay! Yay!
Now I'm worried...
Here's the travel guide. Be elegant! Be elegant!
Say hello to Edogawa.
Tell her "thank you" for taking you with her.
Okay!
Edogawa? Thank you so much!
Today, I'll do my best to be Sasami Tsukuyomi!
Don't say that!
It may actually be convenient.
What?
Oh, nothing! You're very welcome!
Let's get on the bus once everyone's here.
Just like cattle!
Me, too...
There's no seat for you.
What?
Oh no, Sasami!
The love torn by destiny!
Natsumi:
"It's morning... Big Brother!"
That's Big Sister Tsurugi!
What are you doing here, Tama?
Wait, what...?
Oh, I see.
This sure looks like fun.
Good morning, Tsurugi.
Oh, chat room, eh?
Tsurugi-chan
"Tsurugi-chan" has entered the chat room.
Pretty interesting stuff you came up with, Sasami.
Pretty interesting stuff
you came up with, Sasami.
I thought you'd be wetting your pillow
with your tears by now.
I don't mind you wetting something
other than your pillow, you know!
Why do you have to sexually harass
me every chance you get?
Why do you have to sexually
harass me every chance you get?
I was feeling bad for leaving Tama alone,
so this is actually perfect.
Tsurugi-chan
"But be careful."
But be careful.
Remember you're vulnerable not that you've
Remember you're vulnerable now that you've
entrusted the power of God with your mom.
entrusted the Power of God with your mom.
It'll be fine.
Right now I'm in the safest place in the world.
What?
Kagamin
"Kagamin" has entered the chat room.
Yawn...
Good for you, Kagami.
She was sulking and sad because Sasami didn't come.
I wasn't sulking or sad! I was just sleepy!
Good morning, Big Sister Kagami!
If you're going to pretend to be Sasami,
call me "Kagami," not "Big Sister Kagami".
Right. Good morning, Kagami!
How could you address your older sister like that?
What am I supposed to do?
I think the cold medicine started kicking in.
I can't stay awake much longer.
I really don't want to, but I'm going to take a quick nap.
Good night, Big Brother.
Sasami-san
"Sasami-san" has left the chat room.
Mama-lin disappeared.
Sasami must've fallen asleep.
I wonder if she's going to be okay with her cold,
Big Sister Kagami.
Like I said, you can't call me that.
What am I supposed to do?
If that's the case...
I see!
O...
One...
Onee...
Onee-sa...
Onee-sama!
Wh-wh-what did you call me that for?
I could be your sister or friend
and still call you that, right?
Was that weird, Onee-sama?
Was I wrong again, Onee-sama?
Am I a bad girl, Onee-sama?
S-stop it! I can't take it anymore!
I guess that can't be helped. I'll let you call me that.
I love you, Onee-sama!
She finally started calling her "Onee-sama"!
That's so Yuri! The pitcher and the catcher!
They've gone to a place where we can never reach...
Goodbye, my first love!
You guys just can't stay out of the spotlight, can you?
Umm... I'm sorry, but who are you again?
That's so mean!
Konohana Sakuya Academy,
second year homeroom teacher...
Let's see...
I-I am Youko Kitsunebi.
Note: Written with the kanji characters Kitsune + Hi
(fox fire; will o' wisp) and "You" (ghost)
I'm sorry about that!
I'm horrible when it comes to
remembering people's names!
Let's get acquainted during this trip, Miss Yagami.
Bow before the shrine.
Bow to each other.
Now look at each other!
Now get ready to fight!
Thank you for the food!
Now take whatever you want! Eat whatever you want!
I want you to gain weight and regret it,
my ignorant masses!
I, Jou Edogawa, am the goddess
who guaranteed this freedom to you!
Worship me!
Call me "Marianne"!
Do you want to join us to eat, Edogawa?
You must be lonely by yourself over there.
What? Oh, yeah...
What's the matter, Kagami? It's free, so dig in!
Something about her bothers me.
Could it be love? Are you going to cheat with her?
I like that! Go on and knock yourself out.
I've started to really get into cuckold stories lately.
It's totally hot!
Sasami-san
Sasami-san has entered the chat room.
Good morning. I slept for a while...
Good morning! I slept for a while.
Sasami-san
You're up, Sasami? How are you feeling?
Not too well. I can't seem to get rid of this cold.
Not too well.
Sasami-san
I can't seem to get rid of this cold.
Here you go.
You share the same palate with Sasami, don't you?
Let me know if you see anything you like.
I'll get it for you.
Thanks. you're so sweet to me today, Kagami.
Seriously, I'm an angel at all times.
Are you having fun, Youko?
Let's drink together, have deep conversations,
get really close and get in bed together!
Let me rub your boobs!
Don't we have to do anything about that?
She's the disgrace of the family.
I don't want to be associated with her.
Can I have your attention?
It looks like the bath is ready.
If you're finished eating, go ahead and take a bath!
All right, let's go take a bath!
It starts off as "I'll wash your back"
and leads to "I'll wash your front"
and then we get some action!
And Tsurugi-chan can tell you!
The bath is filled with hopes and dreams!
There's no such reality!
Let's go, Edogawa.
What? Oh, I'm not sure...
Crap. Right now I have IT!
Come with us! I want us to wash each other's backs!
"Wash each other's back"...?
I can't, because...
Come on.
NO!
There's something I need to be doing!
You guys go ahead and do whatever!
Don't associate with me! Stay away from me!
What... What is it?
You're so serious, Edogawa.
You must've thought that you needed
to clean up the plates and other things.
Sasami-san
Be discreet and ask Edogawa
if she's got that thing on her right now.
Sasami-san
You have that thing on you again right now?
Don't worry. I'll cover for you.
Don't try to do that all by yourself. We can all help you
and it'll be done before you know it.
Everyone's on your side, Edogawa.
She's right. I'll help you, too.
Sure thing. We can handle the cleanup ourselves.
BATH
Kuzuryu Hotel
Who's here first? It's Tsurugi!
Are you a toddler or what?
You've got that thing, right?
BATH
"Hide that thing with this if it gets out of control."
What does that mean?
Let's see, "That thing will turn into a weapon
when you look at a naked girl, right?"
Do you know what that means, Edogawa?
I-I guess...
Stay with me. I'll take you to a place with fewer people.
You should be able to hide it here
because the water is white.
It feels nice!
R-right.
I didn't know you were here, Sasami!
*BAD MANNERS.
Can we join you?
You seriously have no boobs, do you, Kagami?
You need to drink more milk.
Mind your own business, will ya?
There's no Tama today and Youko ditched me.
I need more boobs!
Hey, we've got Edogawa!
Your body... It's hard to believe you're
a high school student.
Come on, come closer to me.
This is not good!
What's the matter, Edogawa?
Does it hurt? Do you want me to rub it?
No, don't touch it!
Sorry!
Something's poking me!
I can feel a foreign object poking my butt!
Let me join you!
No! If you want to pass through here
you must defeat Tama first!
I'm not interested in that flat chest right now!
You can touch mine when we go home!
But I want to touch them NOW!
You can't touch Edogawa right now!
You're going to make her big black weapon explode!
Why not? Why not?
Look! Miss Youko, in a place like that!
WHAT?!
That's impressive! They're 10 times bigger than mine!
She's got a really nice body
under those clothes? Where is she?
Miss Youko!
Now we're safe. Big Sister Tsurugi sure is persistent.
You're okay now, Edogawa.
Why?
Why do you care about me?
You covered for me when we were eating, too.
You helped me out so that
no one would find out about my body.
You protected me just now, too.
Why would you do so much for me?
Well...
You might laugh, but I was really glad
with what you did for me.
What?
When we first met, you said, "Let's be friends."
That's all.
Is it so strange that I want to do my best
just because of that?
I think sharing and keeping secrets are what friends do.
I want to be good friends with you, Edogawa!
We can never be good friends.
Because...
I'm going to kill you one day.
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
All right, I see no one around...
Everyone's on the trip right now.
While they're gone, ah, ah, mic check... Just kidding!
Mata ashita ne bye bye shitemo
See you tomorrow!
Nanka sugu ni aitaku naru
I already miss you right after I say goodbye
Densha ni norumade zutto koe wo kiitetai yo
Until I get on the train I want to keep hearing your voice
Actually I was a little curious
about singing the ending song.
I think I'll get in trouble with some big guy
if I don't sing it at least once.
I want to practice first because
I want to sound good if I sing it.
Since people have this "clean" image about me!
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
It's hard to hit the right note.
I can't sing that high because
I don't normally talk that loud.
Hikari sasu koi iro
Light shines on the love color
Zutto te wo tsunagou
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kasanari au shintoatsu
Kanjitainda
For a long time
Mama-lin, good work!
Hey, Tama! Were you listening?!
Yup! We were all listening to it.
Oh, no! Why? NO!
Next Episode
Preview
"Ganbaranai Foreign Film"
was initially scheduled for this slot,
but the programming schedule has changed
due to the prolonged baseball game.
So I thought about bringing you "Ganbaranai Debate"
but that had to change too, due to the guest's illness.
So I figured that I could straighten the situation
by broadcasting the re-run of
"Ganbaranai End-Of-Year Special '99",
but I realized that I overwrote the videotape
with a TV drama, so oh well, I don't care...
Next Time
Next time, episode 11,
"Love Is Nothing But An Urban Myth"
Episode 11