Rider, look.
Are you scared, boy?
Yeah. I'm scared.
Or should I borrow your words and say this is exciting?
Seems like you're starting to understand.
Is the enemy inside?
Berserker?!
Utw
Presents
Will one last miracle come to pass?
あと一度だけ奇跡は起こるだろう
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
優しい声で描く歪んだ未来
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
もう誰も泣かない世界の為に
Mou dare mo nakanai sekai no tame ni
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
紅く汚された空の何処にも
Akaku kegasareta sora no doko ni mo
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
届かず消える叫びと祈り
Todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
慰めは捨てて行ける
Nagusame wa sutete yukeru
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
綺麗な月の光が始まりへと沈み行く
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga hajimari e to shizumiyuku
Into the distance
その彼方へ
Sono kanata e
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
閉ざされてく瞳でまだ遠くへ手を伸ばす
Tozasareteku hitomi de mada tooku e te wo nobasu
I believe in your sorrow
君の嘆きを 信じて
Kimi no nageki wo shinjite
They're going to drink here?
What happened to your beloved chariot?
Well...
It irks me to say this, but I lost it to Saber.
Have you forgotten what I had decided?
I believe I told you I'd defeat you at your full strength.
True, my weapons have been somewhat depleted.
However...
It is because I am not in perfect condition that I am more than perfect tonight.
I see.
Indeed, the aura that you're exuding...
It's more potent than usual.
It appears you've come here with some chance of winning.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
Our banquet's last question.
I shall allow it. Speak.
Now, if my Ionian Hetairoi were armed using your Gate of Babylon,
it would surely create the most powerful army imaginable.
And?
Why don't we become allies?
Together, the two of us could conquer the stars themselves.
You never cease to amuse me.
It's been so long since I've laughed this hard
at the ramblings of someone who isn't a fool.
Unfortunately, there is only one friend that I've had and ever will have.
Also, there is no need for two kings.
The lonely path of kingship.
I shall challenge your unwavering spirit with respect.
Very well.
Show me what you can do, King of Conquerors.
You are a rebel worthy of my judgment.
You guys seem friendly with each other.
I could hardly be unfriendly to him.
He may well be the last opponent I'll face.
Don't be stupid.
You can't possibly be killed.
I won't allow it.
Have you forgotten about my Command Spells?!
You're right.
You're exactly right!
Gather, my comrades!
Tonight, we go down as the greatest legend in history!
Our enemy is the mighty King of Heroes.
A worthy opponent!
My warriors, let us show the eldest
Heroic Spirit our path of conquest!
Come to me, leader of conquering armies.
You will now behold the form of a true king.
Why are you in so much pain?
Because Berserker... must fight...
Why?
Because the priest said so.
The priest?
Yeah.
He promised me that he'd give me the Grail.
Once I have the Grail, I can save you.
You're going to save me?
Yeah, I promised you...
That we'd all play together... like we used to.
Then...
I'll be able to see Mom again, right?
Mom...?
Now!
It barely scratched him?!
He can see it?
He knows the length of this blade.
Could he be a knight I once knew?
I assume from your skill that you are a famous knight, and ask you this.
If you know me to be Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
reveal who you are, as a knight's pride demands!
Attacking with your identity hidden amounts to foul play!
You...
N-No...
A-Arondight?
You can't be...
Arthur...
Sir Lancelot...
Why, my friend?
You were the first of the Knights of the Round Table!
Why would you sink so low as to become Berserker-
Lancelot!
Lancelot...
You saved your subjects, but you never led them.
Because I never led them...
You are bound by the false idol of a king who serves others but not himself...
My ideals...
My kingship...
You are but a little girl.
Have they driven you to this state?!
Arthur!
Lancelot...
To unite dreams beneath a banner of conquest.
I praise your efforts.
But, warriors...
Did you not understand?
That all dreams eventually disappear, when the dreamer wakes.
Therefore...
It was inevitable that I would stand in your way.
King of Conquerors.
You will learn of the conclusion to your endless dream.
I'll personally show you how things are.
Here it comes!
Awaken, Ea!
A stage worthy of you has been set!
Look up and behold!
Enuma Elish!
Hold on tight, boy!
What's this?
Is that sword an anti-world Noble Phantasm capable of destroying all creation?
Rider...
Come to think of it, there's something I wanted to ask you.
Waver Velvet.
Would you like to serve as one of my subjects?
You...
You are my king.
I will serve you with everything that I have.
Please show me the way...
Let me see your dream!
Very well.
As a king, it is my duty to present a dream.
And as one of my subjects, it is your task to see the
dream to the end and speak of it to future generations.
Live on, Waver.
See it all to the end.
Live a long life and speak of it.
Of your king...
Of how Iskandar charged forth!
Now...
Let us go, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon.
Challenge it because it is unreachable.
Speak of conquest and demonstrate it.
For the sake of my subjects who watch behind me!
By the gods, you keep pulling out one oddity after another...
Have you awakened from your dream, King of Conquerors?
Indeed, I have...
This campaign has been...
...very exciting...
Feel free to challenge me as many times as you like, King of Conquerors.
This entire world is my garden until the end of time.
Thus, I can guarantee this.
You will never tire of it.
That's good to hear...
Ah, I see...
The pounding of my heart...
...was the sound of Ôkeanos' waves...
Boy.
Are you Rider's Master?
No.
I am his subject.
I see.
However, boy, if you really are his loyal subject, you have a duty to avenge your fallen king.
If I challenge you, I will die.
Of course.
I can't do that.
I was ordered to live on.
Your loyalty is splendid.
Never tarnish it.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths of righteousness for His Name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for Thou art with me.
Thy rod and Thy staff-they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me in the presence of mine enemies.
Thou anointest my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life.
Episode 23
The Sea at the World's Edge
Doushite sora wa konnani aokute
どうして空はこんなに青くて
Why is the sky so blue?
Nanimo kanashimi wo shiranu you ni
何も悲しみを知らぬように
As if oblivious to sadness
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita e to kuzureochiru
いつも躊躇わず明日へと崩れ落ちる
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuru no ne
命は足りないまま生まれてくるのね
I suppose we are born with our lives short
Kakeochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
かけおちた心にあなたが触れて
You have touched my torn heart
Futari de yuku mirai wa kegare no nai tsuyosa de
二人で行く未来は穢れのない強さで
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
空は高く 風は歌う
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Yume wo miteta yorokobi e to
夢を見てた喜びへと
Men will one day come to realize
Hito wa itsuka tadoritsukeru
人はいつか辿り着ける
The joy of chasing after a dream
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
子供の瞳であなたは信じた
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
Soba ni iru yo
そばにいるよ
I'll be right beside you
Kooritsuita mori wo nukete
凍りついた森を抜けて
As we pass through the frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni mayowanu you ni
その瞳が世界の嘆きに迷わぬように
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
You'd take the Grail from me?!
What are you doing, Saber?!
How helpless you are...
That's ridiculous!
It longs for its own life, its own birth!
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
I knew you'd come.
Next Episode
The Last Command Spell