Eichi...
This is where you were?
Mitsuki!
Answer us!
Where are you?!
Eichi, please hurry and get me.
I'm here. I'll be right here.
I'm begging you!
Please be safe!
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki! Mitsuki!
You idiot!
This plane will be landing
at Narita Airport shortly.
- Mitsuki...
- Please check your seatbelts once again
to make sure they
are securely fastened.
I would've never imagined that our trip
to America would be so painful.
Yes.
Grandma!
She came to the airport
to meet us?
I contacted her before
we left America.
Mitsuki.
Grandma...
Mi...Mitsuki?
Mrs. Koyama,
this was all my—
Dr. Wakaoji!
You told me that going to America
would be good for Mitsuki, did you not?
Yes.
And this is the result?
I was opposed to
the trip to America.
But I persuaded myself that
since it would be with the doctor
who Mitsuki trusted, it would be okay.
I'm sorry.
Umm...
Right now, Mitsuki needs
all the support she can get.
So...please...please...
support Mitsuki!
I don't need you to tell me
something I already know.
Let's go, Mitsuki.
I'll take you to the car!
That will not be necessary!
In that case...
I'll deliver her luggage later.
Dr. Wakaoji, I cannot entrust
her to you any longer.
From now on, please stay
out of our family's affairs.
Of course,
I will switch hospitals as well!
Hey, wait! I'll let you know
if something happens!
Takuto!
Listen carefully, Mitsuki.
When you—
Grandma.
I'll never sing again.
I'll give up my dream
of becoming a singer.
From now on, I will always do
exactly what you tell me to do.
I-I see. You finally understand.
I've been telling you
all along, haven't I?
That music only
creates unhappiness.
You've finally come to
understand that, haven't you?
It was exactly as I told you,
wasn't it?
Yes, it really was.
I can't watch her any longer.
I...
Did she really mean it when
she said she'd never sing again?
And also, Takuto...
Those backward letters
won't go away.
If things continue this way,
Mitsuki will really—
That's right, she'll leave this world
before she's able to live out her lifespan.
Hello!
How are you,
Mero and Takuto?
You seem to be worrying about
unimportant things as usual.
Unimportant?!
What do you know?!
Takuto!
Izumi, don't stick your nose into this.
This is Green Onion Ramen's work.
It has nothing to
do with you, Izumi!
Work, huh?
But, to be blunt, it's more
than just work for you
when it comes to that girl,
isn't it?
That's why I, as a Death Spirit
with more experience,
have come to give you
some advice.
Advice?
That's right. I promise not to tell
the Division Chief of Death Spirits,
but you should just reap her life
and store it somewhere.
What did you say?!
You jerk, stop saying
whatever you want!
Yeah! That goes against
the duties of a Death Spirit!
As a general rule, yes.
But, in Mitsuki's current state,
she's just like a corpse waiting to die.
If she were to continue
living until spring,
don't you think it would
be just too pitiful?
How pitiful.
Well, see you.
If there's anything I can do to help,
just let me know.
Bye, Mero.
See you around.
You jerk.
Stop messing with us!
But Takuto...
With Mitsuki as she is now...
it may be just as Izumi says.
I don't know what to do anymore.
What can we do at this point?
How is she?
Hmm... Well...
I really can't say
anything conclusive
until I have seen the results
of the extensive tests.
I see.
Mitsuki, I need to speak with the doctor,
so please wait outside.
All right.
She's a very
sweet granddaughter,
listening to what
her grandmother tells her.
You're too kind.
I'm really sorry!
You really did it this time!
I don't intend to
make any excuses.
This is make or break time
for Full Moon!
What in the world
are you thinking,
giving her time off
on your own authority!
Can you really call yourself
a professional manager?
You can go home for today.
I will contact you later.
What?!
Full Moon cancelled?
That's right.
She was supposed
to be today's guest,
but she cancelled
because of health issues.
That's unfortunate!
I hope she comes back
to work soon!
Yes.
The other guests are...
Madoka Wakamatsu,
Shonen Drill...
Dr. Wakaoji...
Welcome home.
It makes me sad that
you didn't consult me.
I'm sorry.
It's true that the only
option right now is for
Mitsuki to take some time off because
she isn't healthy enough to work.
But you could have at least
said something to me.
No. I think it was better that
I made that decision alone.
My office may fire me,
since I gave our number one idol
time off without permission.
Hopefully it will end with me being fired
and not turn into a liability issue.
That's why it's better that you're
not involved in this, Dr. Wakaoji.
It would make me very angry if you
really meant what you just said.
Huh?
I am Mitsuki's main doctor
as well as Full Moon's producer.
So you, as her manager,
and I share a common destiny.
Dr. Wakaoji...
Don't try to shoulder
all the responsibilities.
Please depend on me more.
I wasn't able to do anything.
Even though I had
decided to support Mitsuki
not only as a singer
but also as a girl.
Not just as a manager who is
in charge of her schedule,
but as someone who truly cares about
what is going on in Mitsuki's heart.
But I...
I wasn't able to do anything.
Even now when Mitsuki is in
such distress, I can't do anything.
I thought I understood Mitsuki well.
But I'm not even able to help at all.
Don't say anymore.
Don't blame yourself like that.
Thank you for the meal.
Huh? You're already done?
Mitsuki, finish what's
on your plate.
I'm sorry.
Umm... Mitsuki?
I wonder if I didn't
season it well.
Wait a second!
Why?!
Because I said so!
But Mitsuki said she
was giving up singing!
She's getting
weaker and weaker.
We need to report this
to those two!
I can't believe that she meant it
when she said that.
There's no way she would
be able to give up singing!
Takuto...
If we tell her manager
and Wakaoji right now,
it would just
worry them more.
Let's monitor the situation
a little bit longer. Please!
All right.
But...I wonder if the day will really
come when Mitsuki sings again.
Mitsuki, are you cold?
No.
You should lie down a little
when we get home.
Okay.
Is there anything you want?
No, nothing in particular.
I see.
Full Moon wasn't on TV
the other day.
Maybe she's taking time off
from work again?
No, it might be a new kind
of promotion tactic.
There's no way
it's a promotion tactic!
There's no way that girl would
take a break from singing
to use such a feeble tactic!
What's up with her?
How weird.
Hey, let's go.
That's right!
There's no way that dumb Full Moon
would stop singing for no reason!
It's Full Moon who's always
singing with carefree abandon!
I know!
Something happened!
What is that?
Oh... Ma'am.
Is that for Mitsuki?
Yes.
Mitsuki doesn't have
any appetite these days!
I thought maybe she would eat
her favorite taiyaki from Shunpudo.
I'll do it.
Huh?
I will bring them to her.
Huh?!
Umm... Ma'am...
Madam has changed.
I wonder if there's going to be
a natural disaster of some sort.
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki.
Grandma...
Ms. Tanaka bought
these for you.
She's worried about you because you
haven't been eating much these days.
Thank you very much.
But I'm not hungry.
I see.
How is she?
The test results are in, aren't they?
It's a very difficult
situation after all.
I believe that we should
go ahead and operate.
Huh?
Operate?
Umm... Will that affect
the vocal cords?
Yes, I have to tell you that
there is definitely a possibility
that she will lose her voice.
Doctor, if she has the operation,
she will be saved, right?
I won't do it.
I absolutely won't do it.
I won't have the operation.
I don't want to lose my voice.
M-Mitsuki! Do you understand
what you're saying?!
If you don't have the operation,
you will...
I don't care what
happens to me.
Huh?
I don't care anymore.
Hey! Do you really mean
what you just said?!
H-Hey, Takuto!
Until just recently,
you were saying that
you would live the short life
you were given to the fullest!
But now you're saying
you will never sing again
and that you don't care!
That's not like you, Mitsuki!
Takuto, calm down!
Damn this!
Why?! Why won't you sing?
You loved singing so much!
I'll transform you as many
times as you want!
She's not transforming!
No way!
Why?
Unless Mitsuki has the desire,
we won't be able to transform her
with our Death Spirit powers.
Mitsuki!
I was able contact a different hospital.
Let's hurry over there.
Wait!
She's not herself right now.
The real Mitsuki could
never give up singing.
For people who sing,
singing is a testimony of life itself.
I will make her like singing again.
Giving up on singing is not something
that you can do so easily.
I know that best.
Ow...
What was that just now?
I agree.
This is definitely a condition
that requires surgery.
That is your opinion too?
We've gotten the same opinion
from various hospitals.
It would be great if one could operate
without injuring the vocal cords,
but that is extremely difficult.
I understand that Dr. Lon Herberd
is developing
a new operating technique in America,
but it's still unavailable in Japan.
In America? With that technique,
the vocal cords wouldn't be injured?
No, though it is
not 100% certain yet.
But in Japan, we just don't
have the facilities or the surgeons.
Of those that I know of,
I believe Dr. Wakaoji
at Tanemura General Hospital
is knowledgeable about this.
Dr. Wakaoji?
That's right. There is no better
doctor practicing in that field.
If you'd like, I'd be happy to
write a letter of introduction.
Jeez, where did that Takuto go?
I just assumed he was behind us.
My throat...
I don't want to lose my voice.
Because...
Because if I don't continue to call
out to him, Eichi won't turn around.
Takuto, just what do we do?
She's...
That can't be! There's no way
she'll stay like this!
But her appetite
is even affected
now that she knows she'll
never see Eichi again.
Wait a second!
Was that Madoka Wakamatsu
that I saw going in to the house?
What is going on?!
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Sympathetic Heart."
- Look forward to it!