Good morning, Run-chan.
Good morning.
Have you got your panties on?
Of course! I'm not as drowsy as last time.
There! Let's go!
Run-chan...
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Carbonated drinks really help to wake you up, don't they?
Wouldn't coffee be better?
Really?
It's refreshing, and it tickles my eyes, so it really wakes me up.
Is that so?
Nice shot!
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Tooru yet today.
She has morning duty today, so she said she's going to be busy.
Oh, I see.
It's lonely without her, seeing as we're always together.
Yeah, isn't it?
Well, if she's on morning duty, then it can't be helped.
That's right...
What's wrong, Nagi?
Wanna go see...?
See what?
That first year student, Tooru.
Classmates
Oh, look at that scribble on the wall!
It's still there, huh?
It's carved in, so it can't be erased.
More importantly, let's get going.
Hey! Wait a sec!
The homeroom from when we were freshmen brings back memories, right?
That was a while back, right?
Ah! Is that it? Tooru's homeroom?
I wonder how Tooru acts in her homeroom?
Do you think she seems intimidating to others?
You wouldn't expect it, but she's actually a model student!
No way! Even though she has such a violent image?
Yeah. I was certain that she would swing her b-bat around,
and fill the classroom with blood!
No, I don't think she does.
Sensei, I'm finished.
Thank you, as always.
The figure that shows the number of boys was wrong, so I've corrected it.
Is that okay?
Oh, really?
That was my mistake.
Thanks, you're a big help!
Don't mention it.
TO-O-RU!
Don't mention it, huh?
What a good girl!
You're a big help, huh?
Why are they here...?
Umm...
I've forgotten my textbook.
May I look at yours?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, but I also forgot my contact lenses today.
I see...
Ah...
I can't see...
She's close...
Thank you very much!
You really helped me out!
Don't mention it.
I'm Yutaka.
I've always wanted to talk to you, but I never got the chance.
I see.
Please be my friend from now on!
Toorun!
I'll treat you to a drink to show my thanks!
Wait!
What was that just now?
Huh, Tooru?
What's wrong?
Well, that's new.
You're crushing me! Ouch!
What happened to Tooru?
Who knows?
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Toorun!
I've bought seconds!
Huh? Toorun, where did you go?
Toorun?
Wait a sec.
Yes?
Your forehead is really pretty.
Run is talking to some weird guy...
It's very nice.
Thank you.
By the way, where's the infirmary?
And what's up with that weird looking shirt?...
That way.
I see. Thank you.
Well then, goodbye.
Nagi-chan.
Hey, who was that just now?
He said he's the new school nurse.
Apparently, he got lost.
Really?
He looks very suspicious...
He then praised me, saying that I have a very nice forehead.
Isn't that weird...?
A new school nurse, huh?
He was kind of shady, though...
School Nurse Saitou-sensei
But that type seems to be popular among women...
Him again!
Thanks for what you did back then.
You really helped me out.
You're welcome!
That's right! Come by the infirmary next time.
I'll save a bed for you to use.
Sensei, you're a fun guy!
Come by any time.
Is there something moving around?
You're...
You're getting a bit too friendly with Run-chan.
Eh, so Run-chan's her name?
May I call you that as well?
Yes!
Really?
Run-chan.
Cute, huh?
You look a bit like a sea urchin, so... Uni-chan, right?
She's gotten down, huh?
Well, she gave help to an enemy.
You're really cute, Run-chan.
As is your forehead.
Thank you very much!
It really, really is...
Get away from Run-chan!
I apologize.
It's time for my medicine.
Ah, he's sick.
Oh yeah! Look at this!
Ta-da!
No music, no life!
Oh, you got one of the limited edition colours?
Eh, is it really?
How nice.
I really want one myself.
It looks really high-tech, right?
What songs do you listen to, Run?
Well...
I still have 'no music life'.
You haven't added anything yet?
I thought it was broken because even though I tried various things, I couldn't put any music on it.
Like this...
MD Stereo
It won't connect...
Or this...
Cassette
It won't connect.
Or that...
Like a TV
Hit on a 45° angle
But it didn't work, no matter what.
That last part! What was the last thing you said you did?!
You took it apart?!
Well, I thought it was broken...
You thought an amateur like yourself could fix it?!
There are other ways of fixing it, such as sending it back to the manufacturers!
Calm down! This isn't your problem!
If you'd done that to mine, I'd take YOU apart!
Don't worry.
I'm not broken, so there's no need for that.
That's not what I meant!
Oh! It turned on!
Ah. Thank goodness.
Run, you can't put songs on it unless you connect it to your computer.
I don't have a computer.
Why did you even buy this?!
Um...
Where do you always go during the break?
I won't let you go until you tell me!
I was just kidding! Toorun, wait!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
It's really stretched out...
I told you it's okay. It will shrink when it gets washed.
No. You can use it like this.
Well, where shall we go?
Yutaka will be your escort, no matter where you go!
Run-chan.
Ah, that's right.
She has P.E. next, doesn't she...
todokisou nanoni todokanai kankei
届きそうなのに届かない関係
In a "near yet far" relationship,
nani ga hitsuyou? nani ga tarinai?
何が必要？何が足りない？
what is essential? What is lacking?
sagasanakutemo honto wa shitteru
探さなくてもホントは知ってる
Even if you don't look for it, you will know the truth.
hon no sukoshi no yuuki to tsuyogari
ほんの少しの勇気とつよがり
It's a little bit of courage and bluffing.
keetai nara ima sugu ni
ケータイなら今すぐに
If it's over the phone, even right now,
koe no kimi ni wa aeru kedo
声のキミには会えるけど
I can meet you by your voice.
boku ga kowarechau kurai
ボクが壊れちゃうくらい
But to the point where I break down,
gyutto shite hoshiinda
ぎゅっとして欲しいんだ
I want you to hold me.
Sign: Please be quiet
ima sugu ni demo aitai
今すぐにでも会いたい
I want to meet you right now,
koi to wa dokoka chigau kedo
恋とはどこか違うけど
and though it's not quite romantic,
koko ni itekurenakya imi ga nai yo
ここに居てくれなきゃ意味が無いよ
it means nothing if you're not here.
dakara gyutto shite hoshiinda
だからぎゅっとして欲しいんだ
That's why I want you to hold me.
Run-chan.
In the end, it was
Tooru's job to put music on.
Currently in use
But still...
Isn't it strange to be wearing bloomers in this day and age?
You're right about that.
They wear shorts at other schools.
Bloomers are just like panties.
Wearing panties under this is just...
Panties under panties.
Nagi?
Attending class in panties is strange!
"It's not embarrassing because they aren't actually panties"?!
It is!
Nagi, you're way more embarrassing than bloomers!
When you talk like that, it seems like you like them.
Let's start the warm-up exercises!
Hey.
What is it, Yuuko-chan?
Do we pull?
Don't we push?
I see.
On 'heave-ho' then.
Let's do this!
Heave-ho!
What are those two up to?
I guess we should have pulled on that one.
You're right, Yuuko-chan.
This is working!
You look like you're really enjoying yourselves.
If you fool around too much, you'll hurt yourselves.
It's all right.
Huh?
What is it, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing at all!
There.
Now, on to the next problem.
Toorun, are you looking at me?
No doubt about it!
Do you need something from me?
You're in the way.
There.
Can anybody solve this?
Well, aren't we motivated?
Ah! You're talking to me?
Yes. Come forward please.
Toorun!
Currently in use
Yuuko-chan.
Instead of tucking it in, try leaving it out!
My P.E. uniform?
It looks like you're not wearing any.
Nagi-chan, look here! Yuuko-chan isn't wearing anything, nothing at all!
Run, you're too loud!
...is what happened.
Tooru, you're wearing your P.E. clothes right now!
You're saying I should pull it out?
I don't think it'll be what you think.
Hey, this looks like a normal dress!
You're good at hiding how big that is!
She praised me!
Toorun...
Isn't that...
Listen up!
Let's begin with P.E.
For warm-up, please form pairs.
Toorun!
Please pair up with me!
Woah! Mipo-rin.
You're going to pair up with me, right?
I really want to pair up with Tooru.
We'll pair up, right?
Come this way.
Mipo-rin!
Hey, Yuuko, do you have a plaster with you?
Why?
Are you injured?
Nah, I just scraped my knee when I fell during P.E. earlier.
That's terrible!
We have to hurry and disinfect it!
Let's go to the infirmary.
What?
For a scrape like this,
washing it out and sticking on a plaster is enough.
That's no good.
It'll be bad if it gets infected!
It's all right.
Besides, the next class is starting.
Never mind that. Let's hurry!
Wait a minute.
I'm telling you it's okay!
And I'm telling you it's not!
I wonder if something happened.
Excuse me!
Wha-
Yuuko-chan?
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I didn't expect somebody to be laying there!
I tripped because of a spasm.
Thank you.
Yuuko-chan!
What happen-ed?
Sensei, I'm sorry!
I didn't realize...
No, quite the opposite.
It was an honour to have you step on me, Run-chan.
Um...
Satou-sensei, you seem to be quite fond of Run-chan.
What do you like about her?
How she can talk without hesitation...
...and how she is open and seems to have no hidden nature.
You're right.
Also, her natural sadism and her beautiful forehead.
The size of her forehead is unparalleled.
Ah, her forehead...
T-This teacher...
Excuse me.
Come by any time.
Class has started already.
Sorry for dragging you along with us.
You shouldn't underestimate scratches.
I know. I'll be careful.
But really, is this teacher all right?
What about him?
He collapsed, right?
Should he be left alone?
I might be a little worried.
You're right!
That teacher is dangerous!
What's dangerous about him?
That teacher...
...has some strange inclinations...
Ah, you're talking about that.
He praised my forehead, saying it was beautiful!
That is dangerous indeed.
Right?
Well, whatever.
Toorun, please teach me this.
Sure thing. What don't you understand?
All of it!
Then I'll explain from the beginning.
Sure!
Tooru-san is really nice.
Yeah.
How could you not understand this?
I keep explaining it over and over!
I'm sorry! This goes like this...
No! I'm telling you, it goes like that!
I'd just give up on her.
Yeah.
You get it?
Not at all.
Yutaka.
Ah, Mipo-rin.
Yutaka, you've been bothering Tooru-san too much lately.
Sorry Tooru-san, you don't have to put up with her.
She's getting on your nerves, right?
We're leaving now.
Stop pestering Tooru-chan!
If you really don't understand something, ask me first!
I don't feel sad that she's gone.
I don't at all!
Not at all!
Tooru?
Tooru, wait a sec!
This hurts, it hurts!
Do you think something happened to her?
Who knows?
I give up, I give up!
I'm not lonely at all.
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
As you see, Yutaka and Mipo-rin had major appearances this time.
By the way, it's already summer, isn't it?
Already? Isn't it a bit soon for that?
It's that, you know, there are all kinds of things that need to get done.
Such as a bathing suit episode, and a hot springs episode.
Well, I don't think there'll be a hot springs one.
But before you can change into your bathing suit, there is a barrier to overcome!
Next Time!
Kilogram
Next time on A Channel: "Kilogram."
Dieting, huh?
A word which means nothing to Yutaka and her nice body!