I need you to do one more operation in Las Vegas soon.
I was under the impression that our focus was to be shifted to the west coast.
This plan wasn't conceived by McGuire or the others.
Well, this is kind of my way to score points.
Make an unexpected contribution and have your superior indebted to you?
Yes. That is the reason why we need to keep this between us.
I cannot bring myself to hate such a scheme.
I suppose so.
Very well.
I will carry it out in absolute secrecy.
This is the perfect chance to show the usefulness of Phantom.
That concludes our weekly weather forecast.
Coming up is the recent news.
The topic of a large shopping mall in Santa Monica has garnered local attention.
Although throughout the year tourists do come to the west coast,
most of them come due to the sports-related activities.
Who was it?
My part-time job's shift changed.
They asked me if I can come over right now.
For alleviation the residents have devised a large shopping mall to draw tourists back in.
Is that so....
I'll take you there.
I was planning on doing a little driving practice anyway.
No need.
A couple living together would do that, wouldn't they?
You're right.
Moving on to the next point.
Although the drug market on the west coast has long been the monopoly of the Chinese mafia...
...Japanese organizations have been comparatively active recently.
Frequent clashes in Chinatown are the result.
According to our sources there is a major danger this might escalate into a larger conflict.
The cooperative legal body consisting of FBI and local police has assured us
they will ward off any hazards to national security.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I won't mess up and get dragged into it.
That's not what I meant.
I wouldn't want people to find this place just
because you caused a commotion with a fire.
Y-Yeah.
Are you going out?
Miss McCunnen.
If it's okay with you, do you want to come along?
Unfortunately I have to go practice my driving skills.
Then you can use my car.
I'll walk.
How is the car?
Do you like it?
Don't you feel you can go anywhere with it?
Don't you feel like a world champion?
Of course not.
All it does is fool me.
Good job stopping the car.
We were almost done for.
The end....
There is no such thing as the end.
Even if I die....
...that only means there would be one less assassin.
You can't!
You can't die a pointless death.
I will decide the place of your death.
You earned that right as the man whom I trust.
Drive!
Keep driving, Zwei!
This is a mission I wasn't expecting, but...
Well, consider it a part-time job if you wish.
Understood.
It seems that Claudia has been quite intimate towards Zwei.
Make sure she doesn't steal him away from you.
Even if that was the case, there wouldn't be a problem.
Zwei's existence isn't crucial to the mission's success.
That's true....
Your pairing with Zwei was just random chance originally.
Go play around for a bit.
Come back here in an hour.
What do you mean?
Get used to handling this thing.
Fly, Zwei!
That's quite a flamboyant car you have there.
Are you sure about meeting us so openly?
Rest assured.
I've taken measures to ensure our privacy.
There should not be a problem with speaking your mind.
That's good.
About that plan of yours,
I have thought about it thoroughly.
In other words, guns and organization will be on your end,
while the men carrying it out will be on our end.
Those are the conditions you proposed?
Correct.
And we get the 500 kilograms of cocaine worth 200 million dollars, huh?
That would take care of our budgetary problems for a while. Isn't that right?
Yes.
You think I'm lying?
We just couldn't fathom it, Miss McCunnen.
What profit could you make by proposing such favorable terms to us?
I want to be indebted to by the Godou clan.
I want a clan with strict principles, like you, to owe me.
Is that so?
You want someone to cover your back?
Correct.
I will give you 200 million dollars.
But I will be able to gain something more valuable than that.
Indeed, you can call that a proper deal.
Well, whatever. We have made our decision either way.
We accept.
Your pairing with Zwei was just random chance originally.
I'm a reporter from INN.
There is something I have to ask of you.
Take this....
What is it?
Just give it to the police.
I'm counting on you.
Ah! Wai-
Why is this happening?
I've had enough.
I'm hungry...
What day is it?
I want to go home... to Japan.
It's quiet.
I might be able to run for it now...
I can't.
If I go out, I'll be found out right away.
And get killed by her.
Giving Phantom this much trouble.
And still alive...
What a guy.
He chose to stay hidden here suppressing fear and hunger.
He decided that would be the only way to survive,
while his instincts kept suppressing his impulse.
Interesting.
What an interesting subject.
Zwei...
Zwei, get up!
We're leaving.
Get ready!
Okay.
It's a mission.
It is to be carried out tonight.
We need to survey the site while there's still light outside.
Tonight at 22:00, 500 kilograms of cocaine will be delivered here.
Inferno is planning on taking them.
Our mission is to back up the attack.
Can we trust them?
The assault team, I mean.
It seems that Claudia has been quite intimate towards Zwei.
Make sure she doesn't steal him away from you.
I haven't been told about it.
So it's a mission only Phantom can do, huh?
Let's go back.
We need to ready our weapons.
Ein,
have you ever dreamt?
Dream?
Visions of things you've never seen before....
...or meeting someone you don't know.
Such dreams... are they... my memories?
Who knows.
You never see them?
Things like them...
Sometimes... I dream about colors.
Colors?
Yes, colors.
And also...
...the wind.
Blue, white and green.
That's all that's left. The rest is a place of emptiness.
But it's so bright and dazzling...
The wind blows...
A really strong wind.
Those visions might be of your homeland.
I don't know.
But....
So what?
Know your homeland, then what?
Don't you want to see it with your own eyes?
The place that remains in your memory.
That is... not a place for us.
The place for murderers is...
...nowhere but here.
There is no other place.
There's nothing.
Dreams are just a mirage.
They will only become a hindrance for reality.
Hey, it's me.
Lizzie.
A message from Clau.
Zwei, you are to go to Clau's house at 8 o'clock.
Why so suddenly?
What's the matter?
Change of positions. I need to look after a big deal tonight.
You will be Clau's replacement bodyguard.
No, please wait...
We received a different set of orders for tonight.
What? I never heard of that.
Whose orders?
Scythe Master's.
It must be Scythe's own volition.
Don't mind him.
Your superior is Clau, after all.
But....
8 o'clock. Don't forget.
You can go, Zwei.
Ein....
I will do the mission from Master on my own.
You follow Miss McCunnen's orders.
That's too dangerous.
It's okay.
Doing it by yourself...
The ones deciding that....
...are not us.
Yes, it seems he set some things in motion when I wasn't keeping an eye on him.
Scythe Master is not stupid, so he probably paves the way for us.
Yes.
Allow him to sate his ambition under your watchful eye.
Use the car we hid on fifth avenue.
I understand.
Let him do as he wishes so long as it's money or drugs.
However, if he crosses the line...
Understood. When that happens, I will assume responsibility.
Both he and his puppet will rest peacefully for all eternity.
Ein.
Be careful.
You too.
Once I know my past...
Once I know about myself...
I'm not sure I can be myself any more.