You deceived us, didn't you?
I merely asked if you wanted to be a magical girl.
I just didn't explain some aspects of being one.
Why didn't you tell us?!
You didn't ask.
If you never found out, it wouldn't have bothered you a bit.
Mami, for example, never did.
Besides, you humans don't even realise you have souls in the first place.
Your body's nothing more than a collection of neurons and a centralised cardiovascular system.
So when a human body can no longer maintain life, its soul vanishes along with it.
I gave your soul a physical form to prevent that from happening,
a form you can pick up with your own hands and protect.
That way you can battle witches a little more safely.
Nobody asked you to do that!
You're taking combat far too lightly.
For example, how much do you think it would stimulate your...
...pain receptors if your stomach were to be impaled by a spear?
This is how it would actually feel.
You can't even move, and that's how it would feel with only one strike.
The only reason you were able to remain standing during...
...your fight with Kyouko was that anything too painful was limited.
It was only possible because your
consciousness isn't directly linked with your body.
You survived your fight because of it.
If you got used to it, you could learn to completely cut off all pain,
but since your reaction times would slow, I don't suggest it.
Why...
Why did you do this to us?
You had a wish so important that you
agreed to a fate of combat, am I correct?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 7     Can you come to terms with how you really feel?
Stand.
Bow.
Homura-chan, did you know about that?
Why didn't you tell us?
No one has believed me thus far,
even when I warned them in advance.
Why does Kyubey do something so cruel?
He doesn't think it's cruel.
He's a creature that doesn't understand human values.
He'll just say it was an appropriate
payment for bringing about a miracle.
That's not fair at all!
He did that to her, and all Sayaka-chan
wanted to do was heal someone she loved!
It was still a miracle.
He made the impossible possible.
Even if Miki Sayaka spent her entire life tending to him,
he would never have been able to play the violin again.
Normally a miracle costs far more than a human life,
but Kyubey goes around selling them for that price.
Sayaka-chan won't be able to go back to her normal life?
I've said this already, have I not? Give up on Miki Sayaka.
Sayaka-chan saved me!
If Sayaka-chan wasn't a magical girl at the time, Hitomi-chan and I would have died!
You mustn't confuse gratitude and responsibility.
There is no way for you to save her.
You want to repay her so you don't feel inferior,
but it's not your place and you need to stop thinking that way.
Homura-chan, why are you always so cold?
I suppose I am. It might be because I'm no longer human.
How can I visit Kyousuke after being turned into this thing?
Just how long are you going to lay there and mope, dummy?
Come out for a bit.
We need to talk.
You're beginning to regret what was done to your body, aren't you?
I'm kind of just going with it.
I mean, I can do whatever I want with the power I got out of the deal.
It's not really something to regret at the end of the day.
You just got what you deserved.
That's a good idea. You can think of it that way.
If you live only for yourself, everything you do is your own fault.
You have no reason to resent others, and there's no way you'll have any regrets.
You can get through just about anything if you think that way.
Why did you bring me all the way out here?
It'll be kind of a long talk.
Want one?
Don't waste food.
I'll kill you.
This was my dad's church.
He was extremely honest and way too kind.
Every day when he read the newspaper in the morning,
he'd start to tear up and seriously worry about things. He was that type of guy.
My dad always said that in order to save a new era, you'd need a new type of religion.
That's why sometimes he'd preach things that weren't part of the doctrine.
As a result, everyone stopped coming.
He was even excommunicated.
No one would listen to what he had to say.
I mean, it makes sense.
It would seem like some sort of sketchy cult if you knew nothing about it.
But it wouldn't matter if he was talking about doing what was right,
or what was obvious, he was an outcast in the eyes of society.
Our whole family was left with nothing, not even food to eat.
I couldn't accept it.
My dad wasn't saying anything wrong.
He was just saying things that differed from the norm.
If anyone would lend him their ear for just five minutes,
they'd realise that what he was saying was right.
But no one listened to him in the end.
I couldn't stand it.
I couldn't forgive what was happening.
I couldn't bear the fact that no one understood what he was saying.
That's why I asked Kyubey to make it so people would seriously listen to what he was saying.
The next morning, my dad's church was filled with people.
The number of believers multiplied at a frightening rate each day,
and I became yet another magical girl.
No matter how good my dad's sermons were, it wouldn't help in killing any of the witches.
I thought that was where I came in, so I got all hyped up about it like an idiot.
I thought that my dad and I would save the world. He publicly, and I from the shadows.
But one day my dad found out what was going on.
My dad completely flipped out once he found out most of his...
...followers were there not because of his sermons, but because of magic.
He called me, his daughter, a witch that swayed people's hearts.
Pretty funny, huh? I had been fighting real witches every night and that's what he had to say.
And then my dad snapped.
He was pitiful in the end.
He drowned himself in alcohol and went crazy.
Eventually he took his whole family with him and killed himself,
leaving me behind.
My wish destroyed my family.
Everyone ended up worse off just because I made a...
...selfish wish without knowing what anyone else would think.
That's when I swore to myself that I'd never use magic for others again.
I'd use my powers only for myself.
Miracles aren't free.
If you wish for hope, an equal amount of despair scatters across the world.
It all cancels out to zero. That's how the balance of the world is maintained.
Why are you telling me this?
You just need to stop worrying about everything and do whatever you want.
You know, since you got what you deserve becoming a magical girl and all.
Isn't there something wrong with that?
If you're trying to live only for yourself, why did you even worry about me?
We both started from the same mistake.
You shouldn't continue regretting things.
You've already paid too much for what you got.
You should start thinking about how to get some change back.
Just like you?
That's right.
I've come to realise that, but you keep making mistakes.
That's just hard to watch.
I had the wrong idea about you.
I'm sorry for that. I apologise.
But I don't regret the fact that I used my wish for someone else's benefit.
I've decided to never regret my actions,
so I don't cheapen the feelings I had when I first made the wish. Not now, not ever.
Why are you...
I don't believe that I've paid too much.
I can do plenty of wonderful things with this power, depending on how I use it.
And what about you? How did you get those apples?
How did you get the money to buy them?
Can't say anything, can you?
I can't eat one of those apples, then.
I wouldn't even want one.
You dumbass!
We're magical girls!
There's no one else like us!
I will continue to fight in my own way.
If that happens to conflict with you in some way,
you can just try to kill me again.
I won't lose, and I won't hate you for it.
Good morning, Sayaka-chan!
Good morning, Sayaka-san.
Good morning.
What happened yesterday?
I felt a little sick.
Sayaka-chan...
It's OK. I'm fine now.
Don't worry about me.
Anyway, let's get...
My, Kamijou-kun was released from the hospital?
Kamijou, are you OK now?
Yeah. If I sit at home all day, my rehabilitation won't go anywhere.
I'm aiming for being able to walk without crutches by next week.
I'm glad Kamijou-kun's doing well.
Yeah...
Sayaka-chan, go say hi.
You haven't said anything to him yet, right?
I'm... good.
So, what did you want to talk about?
I want to ask you about someone I like.
I've been keeping something from you and Madoka-san for a while now.
Huh?
O-OK...
I've...
...been attracted to Kamijou Kyousuke-kun for a while now.
I-I see.
I never would have expected that from you, Hitomi.
Kyousuke's pretty suave.
You've known him for a long time, right?
Yeah, but we just kinda hang out because we've known each other for a while, I guess.
Is that really all?
I've decided that I won't lie to myself any more.
What about you?
Sayaka-san, can you come to terms with your own feelings?
W-What are you talking about?
You're an important friend to me.
So I don't want to try and go after him if you're already with him, or try to steal him from you.
You've spent far more time with him than I have.
That's why you should have the right to go after him first.
Hitomi...
I will tell Kamijou-kun after school tomorrow that I like him.
I will wait one day exactly.
Please decide on a course of action that you won't regret.
It's up to you whether or not you think you should tell him how you feel.
I-I...
Madoka...
Can I go with you?
I don't want you to be alone, so...
Why are you...
Why are you so kind to me?
I'm not worth it.
That's not true...
Today, I almost started to regret what I did.
I thought, just for one second, about what would have happened if I didn't save Hitomi.
I'm a failure of a hero.
I couldn't look Mami-san in the face.
Hitomi is going to take Kyousuke!
But I can't do anything about it!
I'm already dead!
I'm a zombie!
I couldn't ask him to hold me when I've become this thing.
I couldn't ask him to kiss me.
Thank you. I'm sorry...
Sayaka-chan...
I'm fine now.
I feel better.
Anyway, let's go. We have to get us a witch tonight.
Right.
I'm surprised you're just sitting here watching.
She's fighting a witch today, not a familiar.
It'll drop a Grief Seed. It's not a pointless hunt.
And you'd let her take your prey for that, huh?
Damn, that idiot.
She's having trouble.
Sayaka-chan!
God damn, I couldn't just sit there any longer.
Anyway, just get back.
I'll show you the basics.
Hey!
Don't get in my way.
I can do it myself.
Sayaka-chan!
Are you...
It's true!
If you want, you really don't...
...have to feel pain any more!
Stop... Please stop...
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Illustrator Tensugi Takashi
I'm going to become a different type of magical girl than all of you.
I've decided that.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own good.
Episode 8     I'm really stupid
I'm really stupid.