Armin, I'm glad I could be a good person for you.
You've won your bet.
But this is where my gamble begins!
We've identified the person likely to be the female-form Titan.
Her name is...
Annie!
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
muimi na shi de atta to iwasenai
until I am the last one standing
saigo no hitori ni naru made
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
ryoute ni wa Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
utau no wa Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
senaka ni wa Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
nigirishimeta ketsui wo hidarimune ni
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
kirisaku no wa Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
soukyuu wo mau
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit
Mercy
Raid on Stohess District (pt 2)
A few days earlier
They're late.
Erwin and his damn folk are making me wait.
Our Military Police escorts are gonna arrive first.
Maybe he's constipated again.
You're quite talkative today, Captain.
Cut me some slack.
Talkativeness is in my personality.
I'm sorry.
It was all my fault. If only I'd made the right decision...
I told you. No one could have foreseen the outcome.
Sorry for being late.
Not at all.
You guys...
Excuse me...
We've identified the person likely to be the female-form Titan.
This time we will catch her.
The operation will begin the day after tomorrow.
The location is Stohess, where we'll be passing en route to the royal court.
This is our one and only chance.
If we can't escape there, you'll inevitably fall into the hands of the authorities.
Then it'll be even harder to pursue those who scheme to destroy the Walls.
Mankind's annihilation will become even more imminent.
We must bet everything we have on this operation.
The plan is at follows:
While we're passing through Stohess,
Eren, you'll act as bait to lure the target to this tunnel.
If you can bring her into its depths,
then even if she transforms, she won't have the space to utilize her power.
But if by any chance she transforms before then,
we'll have to rely on you, Eren.
Yes, sir. Are we certain our target is in Stohess?
Yes. She's in the Military Police.
The Military Police?
Armin figured it all out.
She's also suspected of killing those two captive Titans.
She might be your former fellow cadet from the 104th.
Hold on now! The 104th?!
The name of the woman suspected to be the female-form is...
Wait...
Annie Leonhart.
Shit!
Damn! The way she was acting...
She must've seen through me right away!
She knew we were gonna ambush her underground!
There must've been some other way!
You'll have time to think about that later.
What should we do now?
First of all, we need to rendezvous with Team 3 on the surface
then according to the backup plan, fight Annie... the female-form Titan.
Eren, you'll have to transform and assist with her capture.
That okay?
Yeah.
Hey!
It's Team 3!
Did your capture attempt fail?
It did!
Move on to the next sta—
She kicked it in?!
We have to help them!
Eren! Back!
Hey, Mikasa!
That bitch wouldn't mind killing Eren?
She risked it...
She smashed open the tunnel hoping she wouldn't kill you.
It's crazy, but that just makes her even scarier!
Annie will be trying as hard as she can to catch you!
What should we do? She cut off our escape.
Even if we jumped out using our gear,
she'd ambush us the instant we surfaced.
On the other hand,
if we stay here it's just a matter of time until we're crushed.
I'll handle this!
Like that time with the cannonball!
Come here!
Let's do this!
Stay close to me!
Not again! Why now?!
Why now?!
It hurts!
So you can't transform unless it's for a specific, concrete reason?
Clear your mind! Focus on it again!
I'm trying!
Aren't you really
just hesitating to fight Annie?
Eren?
Don't tell me that you still
refuse to accept that she's the female-form Titan?
What just happened right before your eyes?
That bitch killed your comrades! You still refuse to accept that?
Shut up! You're not helping!
Annie's the female-form Titan?
Why? Why would you say that, Armin?
She knew your face from the beginning.
Not to mention, she reacted when I referred to how you "sought to die so soon,"
which nobody outside the 104th would understand.
And mostly because I'm pretty sure she killed Sawney and Bean, the two experimental subjects.
But why?
One would need quite the skill to kill those two.
The culprit would've used their own 3D Maneuver Gear, since they'd be accustomed to it.
So that's why we had a gear check? But Annie wasn't caught.
Because she brought Marco's to the check.
That's how she passed.
What? What does Marco have to do with this?
I don't know.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
No, I'm pretty certain.
I got that, kid. Do you have any other evidence?
I don't.
In my opinion, the female-form resembles Annie.
What? What are you even saying?!
Is that all you—
So we've got no proof, but we'll still do it.
No proof?
What? Then why?
What if it isn't Annie?
If it's not Annie, then she'll be cleared of suspicion.
True, we'll have put her through a terrible ordeal.
But if we do nothing, you'll be sacrificed to Central's whims.
It's just not right to doubt Annie.
Eren, after hearing that it might be Annie, has anything come to mind?
You fought the female-form in hand-to-hand combat.
Did she use any of Annie's typical moves?
You know it too.
Annie is the female-form Titan.
So why aren't you fighting?
Are other feelings holding you back?
What?!
I've got a plan!
Mikasa and I will exit that hole and the entrance at the same time.
Annie will have to follow one of us.
That should buy you time to run the other way!
Wait!
That means one of you is going to die!
If we keep sitting here, it'll be all three of us!
Mikasa! On my mark!
Okay!
I'll go that way!
Mikasa!
Armin!
How?
How can you fight?!
How?!
We've got no choice.
It's a cruel world out there.
Currently Disclosable Information
Wall Sina (pt 1)
About 200,000 people live within the capital, inside Wall Sina.
It's primarily reserved for the royal court and their associates,
so living there requires special citizenship.
Currently Disclosable Information
Wall Sina (pt 2)
Such citizenship can be earned by excelling in the Garrison or the Recon Corps.
This is considered the only way for the poor to live in safety.
Eren!
Annie! I'm not letting you have Eren!
Eren! I'm going for you!
Eren! Wake up!
Don't let the female-form get away!
We can't let her out of here!
What's going on?!
Backup team! Leave this to us! Go check it out!
Yes, sir!
This is weird.
That explosion and—
Nile!
Dispatch all of your soldiers.
It's probably a Titan.
What are you saying?
This is Wall Sina! There can't possibly be Titans in here!
Stop! Don't move, Jaeger!
I've tired of playing dress-up!
Never call me that again, asshole!
Commander, I'll go as well.
Get your gear from Team 4.
Yes, sir.
Having a fiery spirit is good, but don't forget how to stay alive.
Erwin, what—
Commander, here!
Thank you.
Hey, Erwin—
All that can move, mobilize!
We must assist with the capture of the female-form!
Erwin, stop!
What you're doing is a clear rebellion against the King!
No.
Is your head as hollow as that gun barrel?
You haven't a clue what's going on, by the looks of it.
Dismantle your gear, Erwin!
A Titan! There's a Titan!
How did it get here?!
Dude... That's a Titan.
But how?
Outta my way!
Just stay standing, dammit!
I wanted to be one of them.
What about now?
Shit!
Don't even try taking it down!
It'll be enough if we can just hold it back!
It's hopeless! It can see right through the movements of the 3D Maneuver Gear!
You won't get rid of me so easily!
Eren! Answer me! Eren!
What are you doing?!
Jean! Eren's under here!
What?! Wasn't he supposed to transform into a Titan?
He couldn't!
Probably because the female-form was actually Annie.
What?!
We have to get him out!
Help, Jean!
He couldn't?!
What the fuck were you thinking, Eren?!
I told you we'd all be counting on you!
Is this our payback for placing mankind's future and our very survival in your hands?!
Marco... Marco...
Eren?
Shit! We've gotta get rid of her first.
Eren, remember what you told Jean before?
You can't change anything unless you can discard part of yourself too.
To surpass monsters, you must be willing to abandon your humanity.
Annie can do that, I bet.
I don't know what her goal is, though.
But whoever can pull it off, wins!
Annie!
If you don't kill me now,
next time you won't have time to place your bet!
Armin, this way!
Roger!
Coming... She's coming...
Squad Leader, your eyes are glowing maniacally.
Okay! I didn't think we'd need another backup plan, but you're just insane.
Commander Erwin is quite the guy.
Now then...
Be a good girl for me, will you?
You can't summon other Titans to eat you either this time.
But don't worry... I'm going to devour you instead.
I'll make sure to digest every bit of intel I get from you.
She broke free?!
There weren't enough traps?!
Don't let her escape!
You can't change anything unless you can discard part of yourself too.
I know.
My friends are out there. I can't fail them now.
Remember...
I'll annihilate her.
No... I'll kill her!
I don't have time to worry if it's right or wrong.
You can't hope for a horror story with a happy ending!
Yeah!
Mikasa!
It's a cruel world out there.
What is it this time?!
Eren!
Eren?
tatoeba ore ga ore ja nai to shite
If we suppose that I am not me
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitai da
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
I broke out of the deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We used to feel like living corpses
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
But now we're breaking out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
"I'll exterminate them all. Every single fucking one."
The same wrath that made the young Eren take this vow,
now urges him on once again...
Onward to destroy this entire world.
Wall
Raid on Stohess District (pt 3)