When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Where am I?
You're finally up!
It's after nine already.
Go wash your face.
Breakfast is ready.
That's right. I slept over at the Hamster's last night.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't go back to sleep!
Hey, what are you doing?!
If you don't get up already, you'll suffer.
Is this where you like it?
Stop it!
Get up!
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
Hey, Hayate, it's me.
Yeah, I'll be heading home now.
WHAT?!?!
What's the matter, Milady?
Huh?
Hayate!
Yes!
What type of girl do you like?
Huh?
I-It's not that I'm doubting your feelings.
But, how do I put it...
I wanted to double check just in case.
Love fortune for Sagittarius...
What are you thinking, reading over my shoulders?
"A sense of crisis between couples."
"Your partner might be getting tired of your selfishness."
"Listen to his preferences, too."
Is that what caught your attention?
Maria!
Geez!
Answer me, Hayate!
What kind of girl is your type?!
Let's see...
What is the picture of your ideal married life?
Between food, bath, and me, which comes first?
How many kids do you want?
Please don't bombard me with questions.
Why can't you answer?!
I won't forgive you if you hide anything from me!
Oh, please don't!
You'll get tired if she speaks like that, right, Hayate-kun?
No, that's not true.
Let's see...
My ideal type would be...
Would be?
I guess a normal girl.
Eh? Normal?
Yes.
I think being normal is very important.
I wish I could be married to a normal person and have a normal family,
without worrying about a 150 million yen debt from parents or getting involved with the very kind people.
That's my little dream.
Normal?
I think your life until now was way beyond what could be called normal, Hayate-kun.
Normal...
I'm sure it's something you wouldn't understand, Milady.
What did you just say?
I said, "It's something you wouldn't understa-"
You fool!
Nagi!
Did I say something to upset her?
Yes. But I'm sure you wouldn't understand.
Don't make fun of me!
Is he saying that I can't become his ideal figure?
All right, then...
Eh?!
Milady left the house again?
Yes. The SPs called in a few minutes ago.
That's no good. What could the reason be this time?
The reason is always you, though, Hayate-kun.
Welcome.
Come on over.
Will I get to acquire "normal" if I hang around here?
But, this is a little...
No, get your act together, Sanzenin Nagi!
I must master the art of normalcy and match Hayate's ideal figure!
Until then, I will not return home!
Now, bring it on, normal!
Your opponent is me!
Wow, the normal appeared!
Huh?
It's here!
Normal is here!
What are you doing here, Sanzenin-chan?
Nishizawa Ayumu.
The one and only normal life form in Hayate no Gotoku who exudes normalcy in any kind of condition.
What's that supposed to mean?!
I'm sorry for being normal!
Yeah, really.
It's a problem for you, of all people, to be normal.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Besides, what are you doing here, Hamster?
Where I am is none of your business.
And will you stop calling me Hamster?
Oh yeah. If I observe her, I might be able to learn normal.
God, that girl.
*stare*
Hey, why are you following me?
Is there a problem if someone follows you?
Yes! Since I'm about to go shopping!
Perfect! I wanted to see what normal shopping is like.
Wh-Why does it turn out like that?
So this is a station.
I know. This is where you get on and off trains, right?
I've seen them in mangas, but I never knew they really existed.
Oh boy. Is she really going to follow me?
Here we go!
It's bullying me!
I'm being bullied by the station!
I'm against bullying!
Just because I'm not normal!
I'm against racism.
You can go through if you pay.
Geez, why do I have to buy your ticket?
So now I finally get to ride a train!
You pervert!
It's impossible.
Eh?
I can't get on that.
Do normal people always jump on when it's moving at that speed?
Huh?
That one is called a limited express.
Local lines will come, too.
What? So that one wasn't normal?
Oh, okay.
Wow!
Look! The outside view is flying away sideways.
Hey, where's the driver's seat?
I want to drive this, too.
Eh?
You can't do that!
It's not a video game.
Oh, you can't?
I'm good at train simulators.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Everyone's sitting on my seat without permission.
Huh?
Of course they are! This isn't reserved for us.
Eh?! It isn't?
No way! You didn't even know that?
Oh my god. It's normally common sense.
Stop bragging about being normal!
You know, it's been bugging me,
but why are you so hung up on normal?
It's none of your business!
You say that after following me?
Hurry!
What? We're going to walk that much?
Yup. It's a shop about 500 meters in.
Why didn't you go all the way there on the train?
Don't be ridiculous!
What is this?
Lots of people are waiting.
I'll take three.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Can I still buy Koyuki's Special Seafood Cake?
Yes, you can.
Yay, I'm so lucky!
Is this the famous "line"?
One that appears whenever new games or limited goods for an anime are released?
Yup. It's a really popular cake and only fifty are sold per day.
Today, my parents and little brother are away on a trip, so I'll have it all to myself.
I won't give any to you.
I don't need it.
Normal people want really boring things, don't they?
I won't give it to you even if you beg!
Hey, it isn't moving at all.
Patience, patience.
Things taste so much better if you go through the process of waiting.
What?
Where did she go?
Hey, Hamster!
Come over here.
What are you doing now?!
Be happy! I was able to buy this shop's limited stuff without lining up.
Huh?
Thank you for your business.
XPS 360 made of 18 karat gold. Limited production of three.
It'll be five million yen.
W-We don't need it!
Zenbu kure!
Zenbu kure! = Give me everything!
Rerere no Oji-san da.
Rerere no Oji-san da = I'm the rerere Oji-san.
What?
H-Hayate-kun. Do you want to take a photo sticker with me?
She finally said it.
Ayumu, fight!
But I have a job to go to right now.
It'll be over in a second. As a memory. Okay?
Memory of what?
Um...
Of going to your job?
Huh?
Anyways, let's go! Just once!
Nishizawa-san!
There goes the limited cake.
Don't be so disappointed.
Whose fault was it?
I was only able to get the leftover cream puffs.
That's what you get for trying to do things differently from usual.
I tried to learn what normal is,
and you're not being a good reference at all.
Why do you only say such nasty comments?
I've had enough. I'll have people from your place come get you.
Tell me your phone number.
What is that?!
Hey! Don't look at other people's photo stickers!
I won't forgive you!
When did you take such a thing with Hayate?
*smirk*
Are you envious?
This is a keepsake photo sticker between Hayate-kun and me.
I have something, too...
Look! I have Hayate registered as 001 in my phone book!
What, you have your own cell phone?
I won't tell you his number.
Jealous, aren't you?
I'm a little jealous.
Let me take the opportunity to make this clear.
Hayate belongs to me!
Eh?!
Even if you might be a world record holder of super normal, this will never change.
Yeah? I bet he'll get tired of selfish girls and leave your side soon enough.
I won't follow you anymore!
So disappear already!
Wh-Who do you think you are?
You were only bothering me from the beginning.
Come on.
I'll walk you home.
Leave me alone!
Listen to what I say a little.
Ow.
You're covered in blisters.
It's because you walked a lot when you're not used to it.
I told you to forget about me.
It'd be best for you to call and have someone from your home come pick you up.
I'm not going home until I master normal!
Then do you want to come to my place?
My home is around here.
Like I said earlier, there's no one home right now, so I don't mind you coming over.
Fine. If you insist so much, then I will.
Good grief, you're so stubborn.
Here they are.
Here's yours.
Th-Thank you.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm sorry about earlier.
You couldn't buy the cake because of me.
This is little unexpected.
So you can say "thank you" and "I'm sorry".
D-Don't make fun of me.
Of course I can.
Hey, this is good.
Isn't it?
It costs 200 yen per puff, you know?
Oh, it's that cheap?
And how do you live in this small room?
I now understand what figurines feel like when they're placed in showcases.
I-Is that what you should be saying after eating someone else's cream puffs?
Okay, I want you to serve me dinner next.
Keep serving me normally.
She hasn't learned anything.
So this is what a normal dinner is like.
It's frozen food.
Watch out!
I get it.
Normal is just an extremely
scaled down version of what I usually do.
I see.
If you weren't super-rich, you'd be a normal girl.
I would?
A normal girl?
Yeah. Since you're stubborn and a sore loser.
What did you call me?
How you get worked up when it's about the person you like.
But that's what's cute.
You're a normal girl.
That's right! I'm a normal girl!
That Hayate doesn't understand anything!
Hayate-kun doesn't?
So that's why you were so hung up on normal.
Exactly.
I see. So Hayate-kun likes normal girls.
I won't lose, do you hear?
Eh?
No matter what kind of history you may have with Hayate,
that single picture won't do anything against our bond!
Picture? You mean the photo sticker?
Oh, come on. There isn't any deep meaning behind it.
Oh. That was an episode without any surprise or drama.
You don't stand on the pinnacle of normalcy for nothing.
The way you say it really hurts.
It's a compliment, so be happy.
This is my room.
Go ahead and use that bed. I'll be sleeping in the living room.
Good night.
H-H-Hey!
Um, ah...
I don't mind sleeping with you, you know?
I thought you might be scared sleeping alone.
I really don't mind, you know?
Then let's sleep together, shall we?
Yeah!
And...
Tell Hayate that I'll be sleeping over here tonight.
Just this once, got it?
O-Okay.
H-Hayate-kun?
It's me, Nishizawa Ayumu.
Um, ah...
Yeah, it's been a while.
Wait!
D-D-Don't turn it off.
Okay. Good night, Sanzenin-chan.
Just call me Nagi.
Goodnight, Nagi-chan.
Goodnight, Hamster.
This is how the girls' night quietly ended.
Next week will be the climax of the butler battles.
We'll fight and fight and fight and fight to the ends of the Earth!
Really?
Okay. Then please take care of Milady, Nishizawa-san.
Why is Hayate here almost in the middle of nowhere when he's had almost no screen time this week?
Actually, he was around.
See here?
And here, too.
And even here.
Can you get a move on?
I'm sorry.
He stalks Lady Nagi to make sure she's safe.
I take that back. He was following her.
Looks like I don't have to go help them out.
Hayate-sama!
Over here, Hayate-sama!
Isumi-san?
How did you end up there?
I got lost while taking a walk in my garden,
and I found myself up here before I noticed.
Please hang in there. I'll be there right away.
Please hurry, Hayate-sama.
Don't panic, Isumi-san.
Hang in there, Isumi!
Wataru-kun?
Sir! It's dangerous to climb up such a place!
I'm coming up to save you.
I'm almost there, Isumi!
Wataru-kun.
Isumi!
You pervert debt-ridden butler.
Hey, why did I have to fall, too?!
And where's your jab at me asking where I came from?!
Are you all right, Isumi?
Hayate-sama really is so dependable.
And so, it was the debt-ridden butler that was doing the most work behind the scenes.
And that concludes the time-filler using minor characters.
Why is this happening?
Wataru and,
Saki's...
Butler Network!
Hey. I'm Tachibana Wataru.
I'm Kijima Saki.
Sir, the sales promotion goods we were talking about last time...
How do signed photographs of the tiny store manager sound?
Saki! When did you take a picture like this?!
It's my payback for last week.
And so, Rental Video Tachibana is a fun store filled with smiles.
Please stop by if you happen to be nearby.
Aye! Mystery!
Looks like it's not snowing this year.
So it's been a whole year since that day.
Yes. Time flies.
I'm the butler who has been reborn to fight you!
Take this!
You're...
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Preview of the final episode, part one.
Hayate in Danger! Complete Shut Down!!
Right now, you have lost your powers as a butler.
Because of the curse cast by
the Superintendent of Hakuou Academy.
Did you know? "Cyborg" is
a shortening of "cybernetic organism".