When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
I'm not giving Hayate-kun to you!
He's... He's...
My important butler!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Would you like to become my butler?
Gladly, Milady.
Who are you?
The story traces back to this morning.
Ayasaki Hayate, returns!
Wake up, Make up!
No!
Yes, these are the right clothes.
Last episode, Hayate was taken in by Isumi's house,
but now, he's back at the Sanzenins'.
I must devote myself to Milady.
Was I summoned?
Um, Milady?
Hey, Hayate.
Yes?
I have a question. Have you ever had amnesia?
Amnesia?
No, I don't remember experiencing it.
Apparently she's going to submit something to a manga contest.
Yes. I want to try one of the over-used settings;
amnesia this time.
Like running out of the house from the shock of getting the sheep sold and getting run over by a horse carriage.
Or like cold-sleep.
Indeed, there are countless precedents for this setting.
But I will say this.
That's exactly why it's worth the challenge.
And, she's thinking of a situation using amnesia, but...
Nothing's coming to mind...
How about I go to Wataru-kun's place and borrow several movies with an amnesia theme?
I see. Y-Yeah, that would...
Order me anything!
I am your obedient butler!
Hayate.
I'll be on my way now!
Maria.
Hayate is the most reliable man in the universe, isn't he?
Well, yes...
I hope he won't get in any danger.
Because of what he said last episode,
Hayate's life was constantly in danger.
Pass this on to the other candidates, as well.
Anyone who wants the Sanzenin estate will have to defeat her butler, Ayasaki Hayate, first!
Hey, Ayasaki Hayate.
I owe you one from last time!
That voice! Is it Gilbert-san?
I will take the Sanzenin estate.
Seriously...
You don't learn, do you?!
How foolish of you to put yourself in a mobile coffin!
Wh-Why you!
Let's see.
Today's lucky item.
Pizza.
Lucky Point: Park.
An encounter with a prince
on a white horse could be waiting for you.
Maybe...
I'll get to meet Hayate-kun?
But, as if something like that would happen.
Hayate-kun?
No way!
Nishizawa-san?
Get off of me, dang it!
H-Hayate-kun...
It really is you, right, Hayate-kun?
B-But, what are you doing?
Why are you fighting against that thing?
Well...
Ayasaki Hayate.
Prepare to die!
I'll explain later!
We need to get out of here!
Y-Yes.
No, this kind of idea won't do.
Forget fax.
I can't even expect to get fifty of these done with this special paper's tone.
Nagi, you have a call from Sakuya-san.
You're not getting any signal. Bye.
Hold on!
Hey, is my stupid Aniki over there?
Stupid Aniki?
You talking about Gilbert?
That jerk rented some super-weapon under my name.
W-Weapon?
Yeah, yeah.
Man, the heiki's not getting better at all.
Note: Heiki = Weapon; Keiki = Economy
You mean keiki!
Went off on a tangent, but I bet he's off to make the debt-ridden butler cry.
If he shows up, can you give him a light spanking?
Nagi?
It's Hayate, so I don't think we'll have to worry much, but...
Call the SPs!
We'll search for Hayate.
There it is!
Nishizawa-san, can you be on your own feet for a second?
Y-Yes!
A little something that Maria-san gave me in case of times like this.
What's this?
I see. So this is how it works.
Thank you, Maria-san.
This is a great help.
Hayate-kun, it's back.
I'm getting sick.
This mecha makes me 3D sick.
Set, on hand!
Hayate-kun!
What's going on?
Hayate-kun.
You'd better remember this!
Hayate-kun, get a hold of yourself.
Hayate-kun!
Tens of thousands of years later,
Hayate, who had lost his memory,
was floating through space alone.
Nu... Nunna... lly...
Welcome back.
Oh, it was a dream.
That's right, I have to return with
an amnesia plot quickly for Milady.
Ah... What am I doing?
H-Hayate-kun, I-I'll call an ambulance right away!
You can't die!
Um...
Thank goodness!
Are you all right?
Does your head hurt at all?
No, not really.
And ah... Your leg...
Why am I giving him a lap pillow?
Ow.
That hurt.
I-It's been a while since we've seen each other alone.
Yes.
Um, I always wanted to ask.
You shied away that time but...
I'm...
...only interested in 2D.
SFX: Gahhh!!
Gahhh!!
So, to be honest with yourself, what do you think of me?
So?
Um...
So? So?
My head!
Hayate-kun?
Where is this?
Who am I?
Crap! I came up with something based off the setting, again!
This can't possibly work.
A-Amnesia?
Hayate-kun has amnesia!
You're going to believe it?
What should I do? I've never dealt with real amnesia before!
Oh, Winter ******! ****** Sonata!
I should have watched ****** ******!
Sorry for the wait.
Thanks for your order!
Oh right, I had ordered it since I was hungry.
I totally forgot about it.
Hey, could you possibly be a butler?
Hey, you are, right?
Wow, this is my first time seeing one.
Then she must be your lady.
So, I should get the money from the butler?
Um, the bill.
M-My butler, Hayate-kun.
Wh-What are you spacing out?
Hurry and pay him the bill.
Y-Yes, right away, Milady.
Yes, that! I always wanted to see that once!
Here's your tea, Milady.
Thank you.
So I was your butler?
That's right, Ayasaki Hayate-kun.
You... You're Nishizawa Ayumu's butler.
I've done it...
I'm trapped. I can't find the timing to quit this at all.
What should I do? Hayate-kun seems to believe me.
Oh well! Things will turn out as they should.
This is good!
Could the taste be different from one side to the other?
Yes, this is called "half-and-half".
Butler Hayate-kun, why not eat this side, too?
Yes, thank you.
This is so good.
I've never tasted something like this before.
That's anchovy.
You've never had anchovies before?
Ah... No...
I've seen them when I was doing a part-time job, but...
This tastes great, Lady Ayumu!
Could this possibly be a present from God himself?
Hayate!
And... Could you be...
The Burglar Hamster!
Milady...
Hey, Hayate, what is this about?
Stop this ridiculous joke.
Um...
I'm not giving Hayate-kun to you!
He's... He's...
My important butler!
What?!
Crap! Now I'll have to end this even if it's forcefully.
Hayate-kun?
My head hurts...
Hayate!
Okay, now's my chance.
What...
Hayate!
Hayate's experiencing amnesia?
That's ridiculous!
Rest assured, Hayate.
I will get your memory back.
I lost my chance again.
Um, how long should I pretend that I'm asleep?
Indo kare ha karezo
Indo kare ha karezo = Curry from India is hot.
Zou ha okkiin dazo.
Zou ha okkiin dazo. Sabu. = Elephants are large, you know. So dumb.
Sabu.
We will now start Project Ayasaki Hayate's Memory Restoration.
Conveniently, I was in the midst of thinking about what amnesia is today.
I have several missions prepared,
so I'd like to ask for help from everyone.
I-I'm starting to feel like I'm in danger.
But Milady was working so hard over an idea for her manga.
If this could trigger a spark in her...
All right!
What? Where is this?
I'm...
Oh, Hayate, you're awake!
A-Are you all right?
Yes...
Hayate!
Yes?
I hear that you have amnesia and believe you're this Hamster's butler, am I right?
Ah, yes, I'm Lady Ayumu's-
No!
Hayate! You're my, Sanzenin Nagi's, butler!
She's right!
Ayasaki Hayate, how pathetic.
I will bring this guy's memory back no matter what it takes.
Klaus, are you saying that I won't be able to restore his memory?
I'm sorry, but yes I am.
Interesting. I'll take the challenge.
We'll fight to see who can restore Hayate's memory!
I know I'll be the winner.
Um, fight?
So Hayate, do you remember something now?
It's your favorite clothes.
Favorite?
That prettiness!
I sort of remember seeing it in episode eight.
No... I never knew Hayate-kun had such tastes.
And so Project Memory Restoration began.
Come now! Defeat him in one blow!
But I can't turn into his food.
All right, I'll use this as my chance!
Enough!
No... I never knew Hayate-kun could kill tigers.
My memory's-
Looks like it's not back yet.
That's not what you used before.
Looks like we need to put off the decision.
Why...
Lady Nagi and Klaus fought on.
They fought on and on to get Hayate's memory back.
He still doesn't have his memory back?
All that's left now is applying shock.
Wait! Please stop!
Stop!
Go!
A parachute?
Klaus-san!!!
That yell! Maybe Hayate-kun got his memory back?
Or, maybe he didn't lose it to begin with?
Great observation.
No, not yet!
Hayate's memory can't possibly be restored with what Klaus could come up with.
I-I see.
But, Hayate isn't coming up.
Maria, minimum throttle. Let's search for him just in case.
I think this is going over the top.
Um...
Please forgive her.
Nagi means all of this to be for Hayate-kun.
In her own way.
Hey, Hayate! Are you all right?
If you are, answer me!
Hey!
It's a little frustrating.
A lot has happened without me knowing.
Between Hayate-kun and her...
What?
Was there an island like this
when we came here fishing the other day?
I'm not sure.
Let's land there.
Maria, dock on the shore.
Yes!
Me too!
What the?
Could this be from Lake Sanzenin's strange ecosystem?
Oh no!
What? The engine stalls at a time like this?!
Those voices are...
Milady and Nishizawa-san!
Wh-What is this guy?
Could you be...
The turtle of the island? Are you?
L-Let's run. Hurry.
W-Well, that landing wrenched my waist.
Ow!
Hayate-kun would...
At times like this, Hayate-kun would...
Hey!
That way!
Hey you, stop it!
She's an important person to Hayate-kun.
If you touch her...
I won't forgive you!
Do you hear?
Nishizawa-san.
Hey, Hamster! I like your intentions, but don't sound so weak at the end.
Stop it, you reptile!
Hayate.
Hayate-kun?
I won't stay calm if you do anything to these two!
Milady! Nishizawa-san!
Are you two all right? Are you hurt anywhere?
Hayate-kun...
You...
I'm sorry for putting you in danger.
I'm a failure as a Sanzenin butler.
Hayate! Your memory's back!
Thank goodness, Hayate-kun.
But... I'm...
It's fine as long as you're back to who you've always been.
Yup.
Yes!
Thank you very much!
All right, that's the end of Project Hayate Memory Restore!
Are you sure you don't have to send her off?
Much to my regret, I was saved by her this time.
So I'll let her have a chance to be alone with him
Owie.
I'm glad I was able to see what your new life is like.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I caused.
Hayate-kun, do you remember what I asked you at the park?
No, what was it?
My head is little foggy today.
I knew it.
That lady is very important to you, right?
But... you're very important to me, too.
Nishizawa-san.
Hayate-kun, next time...
Let's go to a pizza place sometime.
You've never had anchovy pizza, right?
But you'll love it!
I just know you will.
I just do.
As if, right?
I'll see you again, somewhere out there.
Nishizawa-san...
Leaving a bitter memory in Hayate's heart,
Nishizawa-san leaves the Sanzenin mansion.
And Klaus was...
A little to the right...
As you see.
He's off to oblivion on autopilot.
Next week, we'll fight against a new development.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Magical Change into Sanzenin Nagi.
And I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
It's almost half a year since this anime started.
Yes, we made it here, but the path ahead is still long.
I'm still counting on you, Hayate.
Yes, Milady.
And starting next week, we'll have a new opening.
The plot will be a battle of butlers over the legendary butler uniform.
Hayate no Gotoku Casa**na Saga.
What? Really?
I bet it's something like that.
Bye bye.
What is this Butler Battle Tournament?
It doesn't make any sense!
It's as you see.
I wanted to find out the levels of
the butlers we have at this school.
She's the superintendent?!
She is my dear Kuzuha-sama.
I won't forgive you.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Hayate Rises Upon the Earth.
Hayate, I want to see you win the tournament.
Will you be able to live through it?