Hey, Kawai.
Are you heading back now?
Yeah.
What a coincidence.
A lie
I had day duty today, so I got held up too.
Really?
Real lie
Do you have a flat tire?
I think she's implying I should've told her that first.
But I refuse to take the hint!
Kawai Complex isn't all that far away, so I
figured it'd be nice to take a walk for once.
Plus, the view from this bridge is really pretty.
Hey, we live together. Show me some love, please.
Just kidding.
Kawai, of all people, stopped reading her book!
Though I don't know what to make of how happy I am right now.
Ricchan's always by herself, and I think she's actually really lonely.
So please be there for her.
I mean, you've gotten so close already.
I'm sure you can do it.
You can do it.
Will I actually be able to pull it off, like Sayaka said?
Maybe it'd do me good to be a bit more pushy!
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Four
For the Time Being
Sumiko...
Where'd those come from?
My friend gave them to me.
Would you like some?
We would!
Oh, the high schoolers will have to settle for soft drinks.
Figures.
Thanks for the offer, but I'll have to pass.
Sorry.
Come on. It's not that shocking.
Did you hook up with some new loser?
Why are you assuming he'd be a loser?
I've been overeating and overdrinking lately, so I'm trying to exercise some self-control.
I mean, it's not good for the skin and all.
Come to think of it, you have been eating less rice.
You used to be such a hungry hungry hippo, too.
What?
But your belly feels so good to fondle right now.
My belly is not for fondling!
Then I'll have to fondle your boobs instead.
Why are you acting like you're duty-bound to fondle?!
Don't tell me... Another ex?
Nah. It's just a friend.
Hello?
Yeah, should be fine.
You mean the one next week, right?
O-Oh...
I don't know what to say.
A-Are you okay?
Okay.
Just relax for today.
Talk to you later.
This is so good.
What's wrong, Mayumi?
Thanks
Tremble
So my friend has this high-society boyfriend, right?
Thanks
Tremble
She got all condescending on me, like, "I'll set up a
mixer with my beau's friends," and actually made plans.
Tremble
She even gave me advice like,
"You'd better lose some weight!"
lel
Tremble
Sounds like a wonderful friend you have there.
But she just called and said that she broke up with her boyfriend, so the mixer's down the drain!
Should I be disappointed, feel sorry for her, or delight in her suffering?
It'd be terrible if I reacted the wrong way!
Relax. You were certified terrible the
moment you even had to think about it!
Also, all I'm getting from you
is disappointment and delight!
I don't wanna be the kind of woman who delights in a friend's suffering!
It's fine if they're strangers, though!
No, it's not.
But, Mayumi, didn't you hate that friend of yours?
Yeah.
So she might as well be a stranger, right?
Now that I think about it, there was
no need at all to hit Shiro, was there?
Once more... Once more...
Don't sweat it. I mean, this is Shiro we're talking about.
I guess.
Well, how do I say this?
We girls can only be friends with so many people.
And we can only be really good friends with a select few.
The rest we just tolerate out of habit.
And there are all kinds of weird rules. All in all, it's a total pain.
I feel ya!
Right, Ricchan?
Don't ask me to confirm your stereotypes, please.
What am I, chopped liver?
And I could do without the support of a
rule-breaking enemy of womankind like you.
While we're on the topic of rule-breaking, Ricchan refuses to make friends too.
Hey, Sayaka!
It's not like I'm alone because I want to be.
Yeah, yeah!
How could you say that?
Being drunk's no excuse!
Nobody in my high school freshman class went to the same junior high as me.
In the first place, not many people from our junior high join that high school.
Or at least, not many girls do.
I never really had the chance to approach my classmates,
and before I knew it, I was all alone.
And, well, it's easier on me this way, so I don't really mind.
Sure sounds like you're alone because you want to be.
Come on.
You have me, Mayumi.
Since when are we friends?
You only want me for my body!
Let's wrap this party up, shall we?
The three of them are drunk as skunks.
"Easier"?
She's totally lying, isn't she?
Is that what it looks like to you?
W-Well, I'm just wondering if she's actually lonely.
I don't know about that.
It seems to me like one needs to keep up with the
trends if they wanna be friends with high school girls.
Sounds rough.
Trends?
Come to think of it...
Actually, that's probably irrelevant.
What is it?
Please tell me.
Remember when baggy socks were all the rage?
Yeah.
I think the next big trend could follow on from the "baggy" part, only this time it'd be baggy panties!
This sucks.
They're coming off again!
And the girls would keep holding
them in place from above their skirts.
Wow, it really was irrelevant.
Good night, jerk!
"Easier"?
She's gotta be lying.
Though...
it doesn't look like she's lying at all!
She really seems to be enjoying herself.
But even though I've seen her laugh and get flustered like anyone else,
she just sits and reads books
in a corner of the living room.
Hey.
Another coincidence, huh?
I'm walking home today.
Don't take the hint!
Uh, Usa...
Are you trying to look out for me
because of what I said yesterday?
If so, then don't let it bother you.
It really is easier on me this way.
I don't have to worry about missing TV shows because I'm reading,
replying to texts too late,
being distracted when I'm trying to read cellphone novels,
or awkwardly suggesting trips to the bookstore.
I don't have to worry about any of that when I'm alone.
She bases everything around books?
If she feels she needs to say all this,
she must actually be lonely deep down.
Is there anything at all I can do to help?
...is what he's thinking. I can see it in his eyes.
Um...
What is it?
Doesn't it wear you out?
What do you mean?
It must be hard adapting to so many different people.
Like Shiro, Mayumi, and Sayaka, for example.
Is she worried about me?
Wear me out? Please.
I just act like I always do.
What? It doesn't wear him out?
I see. You're pretty amazing.
Sh-She just complimented me, right?
Oh, it's really not that big a deal.
He doesn't need to adapt to the others.
He just fits in naturally with them.
He looked like a decent guy,
but he's a weirdo too.
So she thinks highly of me after all!
That means I was right!
It would do me good to be a bit pushy!
All right!
Oh, my.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
I'm home...
I'm gonna do my best!
Without taking any hints!
Kawai.
Kawai!
I'm off to school.
Already?
I'll come with you.
Later!
Looking at him lately reminds me of the hamster we have back home.
She's not showing up at all.
Guess I'll kill some time at the bookstore.
Oh, so this is where she was.
Kawa—
Hey, isn't that Ritsu?
You're right!
Friends of hers?
Ritsu!
That is one exaggerated reaction.
Long time no see!
Th-These friends seem rather violent.
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
We haven't seen you in ages!
Not since we graduated junior high, I don't think.
Still a sucker for books, I see.
Yeah, you still go off into your own little world.
Not many people from our junior high go to your school, so we never hear anything about you.
We were worried you'd turned into a loner.
Yeah.
You've always got your head in the clouds and all.
What?
That's not true.
Really?
Really!
Would you look at that?
She actually does enjoy being with friends.
Let's exchange numbers again. Mine changed.
Okay.
What say we get our junior high gang back together soon?
Oh, that sounds good.
That's a relief.
Well, catch you later!
Yeah, see you.
What's with that "Crap, the wrong guy
saw me at the wrong time" expression?
Hey—
Why...
Why is she running from me?
Hey...
Kawai?
Uh...
I shouldn't take the hint... right?
Aren't you glad... about what happened earlier?
You got to meet your friends from junior high again.
Knock it off!
Quit jumping to conclusions
and getting worried about me.
Give it a rest already!
Just kidding.
Sorry.
Hey.
If you keep lying there, I might step on you.
Feel free.
Corpse
What, did you get infected by Shiro's masochism?
Oh, you wound up making Ricchan mad, right?
If you knew this was gonna happen, you should've stopped me!
But it was so amusi—
It looked amusing.
What was the point of that correction?
I had a hard time too, you know? You made me feel homesick!
I wanted to see Hamjirou so badly.
I have absolutely no idea how that's related!
How many times did I tell you not to take Sayaka seriously?
But she said I'd gotten so close to Kawai already.
That made me so happy!
Of course I'd believe her.
So please be there for her.
I'm sure you can do it.
Well, she wasn't exactly lying there.
Though I wouldn't go as far as calling you two "close."
R-Really?
Then...
I should've just maintained the status quo!
Instead, I went and dug my own grave with everything I had!
Exactly.
Good work.
This is why I keep saying she's horrible.
She's evil incarnate!
Think of it as training to be eaten by a spider.
Feed
Who the hell trains for that in tenth grade?!
And why would I even want to?
Teen spirit can kiss my ass!
You're plenty evil yourself!
Ricchan?
What are you doing there?
Weeding.
Depressed?
Not really.
You're like an open book.
Did something happen with Usa?
Why do you ask?
Because he's been down in the dumps since yesterday too.
Not just Usa...
That's not it!
I just want us to be friends.
I mean, we're both residents here, and we go to the same school.
Also, she seems fun to talk to.
And I'm a little worried because she's always by herself.
Is that last point important?
I don't like his chances.
I knew it.
Shiro and... Kawai?
Do I really look that lonely?
Trying to get on the same page when you both know that'll never happen,
or exchanging numbers when you know you're not gonna call...
I'd rather be alone than do stuff like that.
I don't hate them, but I just wanted the
conversation to end as soon as possible.
And yet, I smiled and played along with them.
And even though I don't mind being alone,
I don't want others to think I'm lonely.
Give it a rest already!
I keep contradicting myself,
and then I went and took it out on Usa.
Are you going through one of those self-loathing phases?
I don't really
get it, but...
What's that supposed to be? Don't be stupid.
It's your standard teenage angst.
Spare me. It sounds like a pain.
Though, well, I don't think I'm ever gonna come to like myself, either.
I-It's not what you think!
Yeah, youngsters do tend to be obsessed with perfection.
I used to be like that too.
Man, I was totally off the mark.
But somewhere down the line, you'll start to believe that you're fine just the way you are.
Just like I did.
So relax, and have all the angst you want.
I never thought I'd hear Kawai say things like that.
Does she actually like...
Don't you hate the way you are right now?
I knew that was coming.
Good. I was just imagining things.
But didn't it sound like I was saying something cool?
Not at all.
Wow, you've inherited Sumiko's sharp tongue!
No, you're not fine at all.
For the time being,
I should take the hint.
And I should stop calling out to her.
Still wants to
stand next to her
Even when I stand right next
to her, she seems so far away.
Came back
Number of green signals: four.
Signs that she's going to move: zero!
Can she even get home by herself?
There are cars and all kinds of
other dangers on the way home.
Now that I think about it, she
comes home late pretty often.
Just look at her. She's acting like a child.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Hey.
It's green.
Usa?
You don't have to close it.
It's interesting, right?
Uh, so...
It's not like I wanted to walk home with you or anything,
but we're going to the same place anyway,
and it felt like you'd stand there forever if I left you to it.
You don't have to worry about talking to me or anything.
Er, it's kinda like those traffic-safety ladies.
What I'm doing is much like flag-assisted guidance.
Though I don't have any flags.
What the heck?
That's so weird.
You really are weird, Usa.
For the time being,
this will do.
You're plenty weird yourself!
Whoa, she's already engrossed!
Currently
guiding traffic
Hey, look!
A rainbow!
Sorry I disturbed you.
Thank... you.
Did you say something just now?
I couldn't catch it.
Not really.
In that case...
you're welcome.
You caught it loud and clear!
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
All the singles out there can't stand how beautiful I am
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little panic in the air
So we try to help each other out
One for all, and all for one
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
Um, Kawai...
Could you lend me a book you recommend?
That's amazing, Usa.
Your all-powerful virginity allows you to use anything Ricchan touched as rocket fuel!
Teenagers can fantasize about anything, huh?
Uh, this goes without saying, but I
wasn't planning on using it that way!
Will you use it to press pickles?
Oh, I know! You'll pump books to make up for the exercise you miss by never going outside!
Don't put me in the same boat as you!
Then what will you do with it?
Isn't that obvious? The same thing Kawai does!
The same as Ricchan?
Oh, you're gonna use it as a weapon?
The fatter ones have more attack points, and the corners are where they're most effective.
Episode Five
I Knew It
Not you too!