I'm gonna go look.
What?
I'm gonna look for my woman.
You can look for that other woman.
Are you dating Julia behind my back?
I feel like I'm in a confessional...
Have you ever had
experience as a minister?
You were always the one
leaving others out of the loop.
We still haven't settled
the score from earlier.
Any time.
Lin!
Hey, out of the way, Lin!
Lin...
I was in the same unit as Vicious on Titan.
You said that you didn't need comrades...
...but I'm attracted to that word.
To the point of tears...
On Titan, we were all comrades...
What song is that?
Julia...
That's a good tune.
Would you mind if I played that tune
on my sax when I go home after all this?
After I came home from
the war, I was imprisoned.
They suspected that I was a spy.
I heard that Vicious testified against me.
In prison, I went insane from insomnia.
As a result, I became a drug addict.
There were side effects...
My hormonal balance went out of whack,
and this is what happened.
You're the second person to
know Vicious since I arrived here.
And the second that
I've talked about this to...
Why are you going to see Vicious?
Didn't you just say that he framed you?
I want to see if he really did.
You're going to die.
I'm not afraid to die.
You're lying.
Either way, I won't last much longer.
Why did you bring me here?
Perhaps I wanted to be with someone...
You selfishly help people,
and bring them along...
...and then you go off to die?
Are you sure it was this woman?
Yeah... It's been 6 months since
I last saw a woman in the flesh...
...and 2 years since I saw
someone that good-looking.
Of course I wouldn't make a mistake!
I never wanna live in this town...
She sat there, and was talking to Gren.
Julia always sat in that seat, too.
Julia...?
She suddenly wandered in 2 years ago,
and disappeared before a month passed.
What kinda woman was she?
She was a real babe.
I'm the only one that can keep you alive...
And I'm the only one that can kill you...
I'm only watching a dream
that I never awakened from.
It's like I am watching a dream...
Be careful when you're with that woman.
Women are all liars...
When this is over,
I'm getting out of all this.
And then... will you come with me?
Are you going to betray me?
They're going to kill you...
Oh, you're finally up.
You've slept too much.
It's been three days.
Your left eye and right eye
are different colors...
My left eye sees the past...
Then what about your right eye...?
I'm not dead...
Which way is west?
Thanks.
Tranquilizer, huh? They're mocking me...
Sorry, but can I ask ya something?
Where is a blue apartment
building called Orlando?
Don't ask me! I don't know anything!
Um, come on...
I want nothing to do with
foreigners from now on...
I'm just asking!
I'm gonna go find an honest job...
What the hell?
It's here...
Hey!
Hey, get it together!
Jet?
What the hell are you doing?
What's all this about?
He was one of those kinds of guys?
What are you saying?
Gren... isn't like that.
Gren?
"Mangan," with "ura-dora"...
He's using an ancient code...
Julia was here... in this town.
Yo.
Yeah?
Got anything?
None.
I got something good.
Catch 'em yourself.
I know about the guy
from that code name "Julia."
It's a guy named Gren.
He's an escaped convict,
and has a hefty bounty on his head.
If you catch him, I'll let you back on.
Hello?
I'm overhead.
Come to the roof of the
building closest to the sky.
I'll send a woman over.
I don't care...
Although I would have
liked to see you as well...
You broke the Bebop, but kept the
Swordfish and Hammerhead mobile.
Did you leave that message
so that we'd come find you?
You've got to be kidding.
Were you just testing us?
Why did you come here?
I want my money back.
The safe...
...only had 20,000 in it.
Is that so?
Dummy.
Hey... Who is Julia?
Dunno... but she has
something to do with Spike.
That's all I know.
Souvenir, souvenir, is it here yet?
It has an EX+ ranking. It's real.
Hand it over.
This is the Titan Opal that you requested.
Give Gren my regards.
You saved me from
that scorpion back then...
Yet you sold me out...
Gren?
Long time no see.
What are you up to?
You gave me that music box because
you never thought I'd take
it apart and examine it?
You found the transmitter...
Julia was the one who found it.
She realized as soon as she
heard it was a gift from you.
And what about it?
Are you trying to kill me again?
We fought in the war together...
We were comrades...
We fought together...
on that desert battlefield...
I looked up to you...
I believed in you...
There is nothing there to believe.
Nor is there a need to believe...
Sir Vicious!
In this world, there is
nothing to believe in...
Vicious!
Lin's soul won't be saved since he lost
his life protecting someone like you!
I'm not what he was protecting!
He protected the rules!
You're in the way!
Hey! Come on, get a grip! Hey!
Where is Julia? Where did she go?!
Do you know her?
Where is she now?
He hit some vital organs.
Shit, would an ambulance
come to a place like this?
Can you lift me up into the pod again?
I want to go to Titan...
You can't possibly last in your condition!
It would take too long!
I won't last long anyway...
Dying during the voyage
would be a good way to go...
I want to return there... one more time.
I want to be as close as I can... Please...
I see.
You are Spike.
Julia was always talking about you...
That your two eyes
were of different colors...
That's what she said...
That you get a strange feeling
when you look into his eyes...
What was she doing?
In the corner seat of the bar...
She always sat there while
I wasn't paying attention...
She always requested the same song...
...and smiled.
Sadly... smiled.
What do you have?
Nothing.
Hurry up and get in. We're taking off.
Julia...
What?
Mm... nothing.
Just an adult's idle muttering.
Where did all of you guys go?
Someplace good.
Ed's the only one left out!
I'll tell you someday.
Nah, it's okay, really.
You're not being cute.
The star fell, Bull.
That is no ordinary star.
That is the tear of a warrior.
What is a warrior?
One who has finished his battle
somewhere on this planet...
A pitiful soul that could not
believe in the Great Spirit...
"What is going on with this world?"
"In life, darkness looms
one inch away from you."
"This world is truly full of mistakes."
"In that case, we'll step away
from the mainstream...
...and lead the life of a dropout."
A psychedelic rhapsody
for someone just like you.
Next episode: "Bohemian Rhapsody."
Now...
Won't you waste away your life with us?
"Bohemian Rhapsody"