Why'd you ask me to come out?
Did you need something?
Thought we could compare answers
like I said the other day.
Did you figure out Yukino's future plans?
Well, I do know,
but it wouldn't be nice for me to say.
My, how responsible.
But I'm glad to hear she told you.
It would appear she trusts you a fair bit.
Trusts me?
Please. I'm not the trustworthy type.
Oh, so you're aware.
Yeah, it's actually not trust,
but something far more sinister.
She hasn't changed one bit,
and I bet she thinks that's fine.
While it's part of what makes her so adorable,
I hate that about her.
If it isn't trust, then what is it?
Beats me.
But at the very least,
you can't call it genuine.
Isn't that what you said before?
Is anything
truly genuine?
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Man...
I wanna eat something sweet.
Though sweets and me
go together like chalk and lettuce.
Get it? Chalk and let.
Oh, right. It's coming up soon.
You've got it good, Hayato.
We got no chance.
But dude,
Hayato makes it a point
not to accept V-Day chocolate.
Seriously?
What a waste!
But I get it. It's gotta be kinda scary to get them from someone you don't know too well.
Well, handmade stuff would seem clingy,
so I can see why he wouldn't accept those.
Clingy?
Yeah, you're right...
But hey, it ain't too late for us.
Don't chalk it off just yet.
Handmade, huh?
Why'd you ditch me?
I never said I'd go with you.
I thought you were waiting for me.
You stayed in the classroom rather long.
I was just checking how
Hayama and Miura were doing.
Oh, it's all good now.
And like, you gotta love that.
They're living in the moment and cherishing it.
Yeah.
These might be the best days of our life.
Whoa, you sound unusually positive.
The past makes you wanna
die out of regret,
and the future makes you
depressed out of anxiety,
so by elimination, the present is likely the happiest time.
I take it back!
It was negative after all!
There you go again...
Hey.
Are you free someday soon?
W-Well, probably.
I'm mostly free, but...
L-Let me think about it.
O-Okay.
Yo, 'sup!
You're late!
Seriously, what are you even doing here?
By the way...
Not that I care, but do you like sweets?
I think Hayama would eat anything happily.
But Hayato was saying
he wouldn't accept any chocolate.
What? Why?!
D-Dunno...
Because it'd lead to conflict, obviously.
Back in grade school, the classroom usually
had a strained atmosphere the next day.
Then I'll make do with you.
Do you like sweets?
What's with the bizarre questioning?
Hikki, like,
loves sweets!
Indeed.
I'm not sure why you two
answered for him,
but that's perfect.
What is?
I was unsure how sweet I should make it.
Everyone has different tastes, right?
"How sweet"?
You're planning on making some yourself?
That's a surprise.
Why?!
I'm really good at making sweets, you know?
Anyway, I just wanted your input on the chocolate I'm making for courtesy.
Courtesy, eh?
What, do you never get chocolate?
He'll...
get some for sure.
Right?
Wait, are you saying...
That's right.
I've got Komachi, after all.
Coma cheese?
What, eating your loneliness away?
I'm not.
Oh, Komachi's Hikki's little sister.
Into your sister?
Hell no, idiot.
I don't know if I can deny that.
So you really are into younger girls, huh?
That's not true.
Besides, your birthday's in April, which means
there's less than a year's difference,
so you don't feel like
a "younger girl" at all.
What?
Nothing.
I was just surprised.
Scary!
Why do you know her birthday?
You're creepy, Hikki!
Seriously creepy.
Aren't you well informed.
Weren't you there when she brought it up herself
and pointlessly showed off her foxy side?
Say what? It wasn't pointless!
And I'm not foxy!
If anything, you're the foxy one here!
Y'know,
I'd like to try makin' some chocolate.
I mean, we'll be busy with
entrance exams next year,
so I thought I could
at least try it out once.
Didn't you say handmade chocolate makes you look clingy?
W-Well...
Now, now. I don't think it's a bad idea.
Hikitani, you should give Hayato some bromance chocolate too.
Dream on.
Not like he'd accept any.
I'm sure he would if it was from a guy.
Why would a guy give
chocolate on V-Day?
Yeah...
If he's saying he won't accept any,
that makes things difficult.
Seriously.
Please, no.
How scary.
So, did you need something?
Oh, uh...
Hey, I'm not done talking here.
All you're doing is drinking tea.
There, there.
I'm sure SakiSaki came here for a reason, too.
Let's hear it.
Uh, it's about chocolate.
My sides. You're giving someone chocolate?
Look, girl. Get it through your thick skull that I ain't like you.
Stop it!
Play nice!
So, what about chocolate?
My little sister wants to try making some.
Is there anything even a kid can make?
Even a kid?
But SakiSaki, aren't you good at housework?
I can cook, but the stuff I make is so plain.
I don't think it's what a kid would want.
What can you make, by the way?
R...
Ri...
Rice krispies treats.
Man, that is plain.
Nothing wrong with that!
I can't cook at all,
so I think you're amazing!
Right, Yukinon?
Yes.
And krispies sounds kind of
like kitties, so it's cute.
That's the best you got?!
What do cats have to do with anything?
This is quite the problem.
Yeah, Miura's pulling all the stops and it's starting to worry me.
I was talking about the
number of requests, though.
But, y'know, I kinda get how Hayato feels.
I mean, he must be looking
out for a lot of things.
Oh, that kinda sounds like you.
You think?
Like me, huh?
Well, all we need is a pretext.
A reason Hayama can accept.
A situation where he has to take it—
or, well, one where taking it would be the obvious course of action.
So you're saying we have to
prepare an excuse?
For example,
instead of Valentine's or whatever,
if someone just asked him to taste test the chocolate, he'd eat it.
Am I right?
I dunno.
Oh, so we could all just make it together.
Sounds good to me!
Gather all the people who asked for help and hold an event.
And Yukinoshita could teach
all of them at once.
Y-Yes. I wouldn't mind that.
Hello, vice president?
I order you to draw up
and submit a proposal!
What about me?
You can...
work with me.
No faith in me?!
What about Hikki, then?
I can't cook to save my life, you know.
That's fine.
You need only taste them
and give us your thoughts.
Then you've come to the right person.
I happen to be an expert.
Okay, take care of it.
So, yeah, we'll handle
all the formalities,
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
so please put on a great cooking class!
Chiba Mihama Takasu Community Center
Takasu Community Festival
Pre-Valentine's Day
Cooking Class
Our last event was very well-received and generated a lot of buzz,
so long may our alliance last.
Indeed.
Y-You guys came too?
Didn't I mention it?
I don't recall seeing it in our email logs...
Tee-hee!
What the heck? You're adorable!
Prez, we'd like to get started.
Okay.
Catch you later.
This is also a business opportunity.
We could use crowdfunding to source a budget...
What are they doing here?
We can get funds from them by making this event a collab. Isn't that for the best?
And I'd consider myself lucky
if I didn't have to spend out of pocket.
R-Right...
That thought process aside,
you're surprisingly capable, Isshiki.
Yo, 'sup!
Sis...
Sorry I'm late!
Here we have Miss Harunon,
today's special instructor.
Hello, I'm Miss Harunon.
Why'd you have to go and call her?
But she seems super experienced!
I could've done this by myself, you know.
Chop up the chocolate and boil it in water.
And once it cools down, pour it into a mold.
That it?
Yes, pretty much.
Sounds like a piece of cake.
You're too naive, Yumiko!
There's more to boiling it
than just putting it in water!
It's all, like, bam!
Wham!
Was bringing her along really okay?
I don't see why not.
Thanks.
Keika, what would you like to eat?
Eel!
O-Oh, I see.
Sorry.
W-We had it for dinner the other day,
and she's been in love with it ever since.
Overseas, it's more common for men to give gifts on Valentine's day,
so we should keep such
globalization in mind for this event.
Great idea.
This way, everyone can act natural.
And Tobe's on cloud nine, too.
Chocolate!
I couldn't care less about chocolate or Tobe.
Especially Tobe.
So mean.
Hayato!
You really are a good cook, huh?
What, are you hitting on me?
Assuming whispering sweet nothings to me would work just because I'm making sweets is sweet, but naive.
I'm sorry. Better luck next time.
Is that too sweet for you?
There's a vast difference between Japanese and overseas mindsets.
A culture gap, one could say.
Hikigaya, do you have any
extra chocolate molds?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Come to think of it,
didn't I give you chocolate before?
No, never.
I see.
Then I'll give you some this year.
U-Uh, okay.
That reminds me.
You got some from Yukino before, didn't you?
Oh yeah, that happened.
It was before we started grade school.
You and I both got some.
And who are you planning
to give chocolate to?
I don't see how that's
any of your business.
Oh? You're not gonna say "nobody"?
So somebody is gonna get some.
Well, there are very few guys
you'd consider giving chocolate to.
Ridiculous.
Say what you want—
S-Sorry!
Nah...
Why are you getting flustered?
Looking at you like that just
makes me flustered as well.
Don't... get... flustered...
You've still got a ways to go, Yukinon.
My handling of bowls and other kitchen utensils is top-notch!
Yeah, but you're rock-bottom
at everything else.
This turned out to be a great event.
I guess.
Though it was pretty nonsensical.
That's fine.
You were always a nonsensical guy.
Everyone around you is nonsensical, too.
It's only natural it'd end up like this.
Don't you think you're being a little mean?
But well, I do understand you
a little better now.
People's perception of others
gets clearer by the day.
If you continue to spend time and grow
with someone, you'll gradually understand them.
I don't feel like we've grown any, though.
We're always running around in circles.
People usually don't look back to see how far they've come while they're still walking.
Of course, when they come to a standstill,
the more progress they've made, the more betrayed they feel by their expectations.
However, I'm glad to have been able to see this up close and in person,
because I can't watch over you guys forever.
Hikki, try these!
Okay, I'll give them a shot.
You seem to be ready for the worst,
but it'll be all right.
I worked on those too.
Oh, that's a relief.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Well, uh...
Thanks.
Sure thing!
Oh?
Is that what you call "genuine"?
Is spending time like this
what it means to you?
I couldn't say.
Is this really it?
I thought you were better than that.
Are you really that boring?
I'd be the popular guy in class
if I were interesting.
I like that about you.
But right now, you guys
are kinda lame.
I much prefer the Yukino of old.
Because it was all new to me, and because I'd never experienced anything like it,
I thought that I just wasn't used to it.
That I'd gradually learn to live with it.
But she still saw right through us.
The student council can take it from here.
Oh, but we'll stay and help 'til the end.
Yes. There's no need to hold back with us.
Really?
In that case, I'll take you up on that offer.
Yukinoshita Haruno threw in my face
something I was trying not to think about.
She said it wasn't trust
but rather something far more sinister.
Mother? Why are you here?
Because I heard about your
future plans from Haruno.
Yukino, what on Earth
were you doing out so late?
I didn't expect this from you.
I placed my trust in you and
let you do as you please, but...
No, this is my responsibility.
My error in judgment.
Was it my fault?
Um,
there was a student council event today.
We were helping out...
I see. You walked her home?
Thank you.
But if you stay out too late,
your family will worry too.
Understand?
I want you to stay true
to yourself and live freely,
but I'm worried you'll go
down the wrong path.
I can explain.
So please leave for tonight.
"True to herself."
"True to myself."
We all have our own personal image that's dictated by others—
one that's always off the mark.
We wish to remain true to ourselves,
but who gets to decide
who we are as people?
I-I'll be leaving, then.
I'll walk you.
Nah, it's okay.
I feel like that'd be unfair of me.
I see.
When our image never goes
hand-in-hand with reality,
where can we find
something genuine?
Where can we find
With the Answer He Seeks Still Out of Reach,
the Genuine Article He Craves
Keeps Going Wrong.
our true selves?
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
Spring Always Comes to Life Buried Underneath a Pile of Snow.
There's something I want,
but I'm not the sharpest tool in the shed,
and I don't play fair,
so I can only come up with one answer.
But I'm sure that's not the answer expected of me.
Why is it that what I want and
what's expected of me are so similar,
yet so different?
In truth, a lie would be good enough.