Dollars?
I don't know much about them either,
but they have lots of crazy members. A shitload of 'em.
You can't skip school on the first day.
Leave me alone!
Anyway, don't go near Heiwajima Shizuo.
Orihara Izaya?
Anyway, he's trouble, so don't get involved with him.
Oh, Simon.
He's supposed to get customers for that Russkie sushi shop.
Very good! Very good!
This is Russian sushi!
It's yummy! It's cheap!
Mister, don't run away.
We have Russian sushi!
Excuse me.
Do you speak... Russian?
Yes, I do.
Ah, great.
Uh... Could you tell us how to get there from here?
You just have to follow that road.
Are you tourists?
Yes.
This is a charming city.
I'm sure you'll enjoy your time here.
Thanks for the help.
If you feel like it, stop by for some sushi.
Ikebukuro... This city that never sleeps stretches from east to west.
To the north, there's a large pleasure quarter.
A sprawling city where a million people gather everyday...
That's Ikebukuro.
This city is full of foreigners.
Like him...
And her.
They came here searching for something, seeking something.
They're here to change something.
We haven't chosen class representatives yet.
Do we have any candidates?
A new city.
No one who knows your past.
An opportunity to become someone new.
However...
Sonohara...
Sonohara Anri, right?
Any other candidates?
All right, you'll be the female class representative.
Take care of the rest, Sonohara.
U-Um...
Is there a boy willing to be class representative?
I kinda want to do it,
but it'd be a pain...
But I don't want any other guy to be paired up with her...
You should do it.
Me? Are you serious?
Man, that would be a pain.
But you'll get to pair up with her.
I'll do it.
U-Uh...
Ryuugamine... Mikado.
See ya.
Sonohara-san.
U-Uh, about the meeting with the other classes tomorrow...
I-I've never done anything like it before—
I'm sorry!
I have urgent business to take care of. Bye!
Dude, I better not underestimate you.
To think that you used to whine when someone spread rumors in
elementary school about you being in love with your childhood friend.
Now you're a pretty active romancer, eh?
Yeah, whatever.
However, your finish was weak.
With that level of engagement, your happy-go-lucky love-comedy school life will stay a dream even though you finally made it here.
I never had that intention in the first place.
With that being said,
let's go hit on some chicks.
Me? Now?
Right now?
It's my time to be popular with the ladies!
I doubt they're interested in high schoolers.
They came here seeking change.
But changes don't happen that easily.
Even if you're standing on a different stage,
it's still the same old you standing there.
What? No way.
I already have a boyfriend.
That doesn't matter.
Even if a guy hits on you and invites you for a drink, it doesn't count as cheating.
Did you guys hear?
Yumi's new boyfriend is in the Dollars.
Are you serious?
Isn't she scared?
Hey, that's interesting.
Why don't we continue this in a café?
Aren't the Dollars like, a biker gang or something?
In this city, there are groups that commit violent acts from time to time.
Each group has its own color.
Thus, they're called "Color Gangs."
But the group that exercises its influence the most
doesn't have a specific color.
Simply put, they're transparent.
That's the "color" of the Dollars.
It's said that they're a special group that recruits members through their private website.
It's rumored that the recent hack-n-slash incidents are also the work of the Dollars.
Really?
Like I said, why don't you tell me the details in a café?
Dollars?
Yeah.
What kind of people are they?
They're awesome!
I heard they made a deal with the Triad recently.
Oh, and apparently it was one of the
Dollars who stabbed that yakuza.
Man, this sucks.
They all ran away because of that gloomy look on your face.
Kida-kun!
Hey.
Uh...
Your name was like a character's from a comic...
Mikado-kun, right?
We're going to Toranoana. Wanna tag along?
Susie Yasuda-sensei's signing her works today!
Dude, don't shout so loudly about that sort of stuff!
Why not?
What's wrong with talking about it?
Dollars?
Yeah, I've heard of them.
My friend told me a rumor today...
Well, I've never really seen them before.
Do they even exist?
You think they're just a fictional group made up on the Net?
Uh... I'm not really sure.
But if they really do exist, it's best
not to get involved with them.
Dollars?
They always fight against the Flame Haze that's sealed under the Sunshine 60, right?
You're wrong, Yumacchi.
They're angels that fly in the sky, show their panties, and shout, "Pipiru Pirupiru."
Why are you asking about them?
Uh, well...
Did the stories scare you?
I've heard a lot of rumors too.
They're very dangerous.
Really?
You shouldn't get too curious and go near them.
You know the deal about curiosity and the cat.
Kadota-san, you're so cool!
You're like the mature older brother of the protagonist.
Totally the dream man of girls into "dandy daddies."
No, no...
Shut up!
There are places you shouldn't go to in this city.
Tsundere hero spotted!
Your tummy won't be funny!
You should give it a shot.
One time won't kill you.
Man, I'm starving.
Yeah, me too.
Want to have something before we—
It's the Headless Rider!
No way!
Come on, why all this occult stuff in broad daylight?
Such a hard worker.
Sometimes, there are people who are swallowed by the city.
And there are people who look for them desperately...
I'll find her.
I'm sure I can find her.
My love will summon her.
Harima-san?
Harima-san!
I-I'm sorry! I thought you were someone else!
And the city is full of danger.
Hey.
Like here...
Hey, wanna have a drink?
And here.
He was supposed to be seeking change.
You serious?
He thought that something would change,
that something would happen in this new city.
However,
a deep darkness lurking in the shadows of the seemingly glamorous city was awaiting him.
His legs felt cramped.
He was losing his nerves from the anxiety of his inability to live in this city.
I understand how you feel!
On the train, you get treated as a molester.
On the street, you get shady invitations.
At home, you get in arguments with your neighbors.
And if that weren't enough, there's the Headless Rider and the Dollars.
That's Tokyo, the concrete jungle!
However!
Get over it!
If you pledge to be a bona fide Ikebukuronian,
you will overcome this ordeal, Mikado!
Yes, you! Ryuugamine Mikado!
Well, I'm with you, so no worries.
Kida-kun...
Oh, and when hitting on chicks, be sure to smile.
Got it?
I don't think hitting on MILFs is a good idea though.
What're you talking about?
I'm just talking to them.
Hey, haven't you gotten a bit cocky ever since Harima Mika disappeared?
I heard you became the class rep.
Aw, she's being bullied.
And the bullies are so awfully clichéd.
With that much makeup, even I'm not scared of them.
Youko's boyfriend is in the Dollars.
Hiroshi.
Yo! You!
Imma call my Dollars bros, so let's get this shit rollin'!
Eh, man?
People like this can be found anywhere in the world.
Having so many clichés is actually refreshing.
Uh, I better go help her.
But how would I do that?
Hey! Cut it out!
No... I'll get my ass kicked.
Then...
Wow, what a coincidence, Sonohara-san.
Let's go.
Whoa, he's so cool!
That's it!
That's the only way.
Bullies?
You're planning to stop them?
And in this city, unfathomable events occur frequently.
U-U-Um...
H-Huh?
H-Hey... Wha—
Huh?
H-Hey... Wai—
What is it?
E-Er...
You bullies are lame.
It's a terrible thing.
That's none of your business, old fart.
Yes, it's certainly none of my business if you get punched or die in a corner.
Even if I punch you, and you call me an "old fart" despite me still being twenty three,
it doesn't change the fact that we're absolutely not related.
Huh?
Humans are so weak...
Well, I'm not into punching girls.
So,
I'll make stomping on a girl's cell phone my hobby.
What's with him?!
I got bored.
I'm done with that hobby.
Hi-Hiroshi!
Yo! Yo!
Yo!
Hey man!
You wanna fight?
Aw, I'm scared!
Y-You fucker!
I surrender!
Wait! Wait!
You'll pay for this!
Kamaitachi cometh.
But hey, it's really admirable to save a bullied girl.
It's been a while, Kida Masaomi-kun.
Yeah...
Hello.
That's Raira Academy's uniform, right?
Grats on being admitted.
Thanks.
It's unusual to see you in Ikebukuro, Izaya-san.
So this is the Orihara Izaya I shouldn't piss off?
Oh, he's just a friend of mine.
I'm Orihara Izaya.
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
Sounds like an A/C unit.
What brings you to Ikebukuro?
I just came here to see someone.
But I'm done with that already.
No way!
Was that the trash can from the convenience store?
It literally flew...
How?
Oh shit...
Izaya-kun.
A bartender?
Didn't I tell you never to come back to Ikebukuro?
I can't hear you, Izaya-kun.
Shizu-chan.
Weren't you working at the West Gate?
I got fired a long time ago.
And didn't I tell you to stop calling me that?
My name is Heiwajima Shizuo!
Heiwajima Shizuo?!
Another one of the people I shouldn't piss off?!
Oh, come on, Shizu-chan.
You're still pissed because I pinned that crime on you?
I'm not pissed.
I just want to beat the crap out of you.
Jeez, when you get violent, no logic or reason reaches you, Shizu-chan.
Oh boy, what should I do now?
Let me off the hook already.
Hey! That's him!
You got some balls to fuck with me!
We'll show you what it means to make fun of the Dollars—
A bartender outfit?
No way! He wasn't here a moment ago!
H-Heiwajima Shizuo?!
Who the hell are you?!
People lose the ability to think rationally when they're scared.
You just hit my head, eh?
You know that hitting a vital spot can kill someone, right?
You hit me there knowing that it could be fatal, right?
That means you have no complaints about what I do, right?
Those who wield a great power
will awaken instinctive fears in others.
He's like the embodiment of the word "violence."
He's like someone who lives off of violence.
No, he  is violence.
You cowards! Don't run away!
See ya!
You won't get away!
Why?
How?
He jumped from above?!
Let me answer the question in your head, even though it's not the one you should be asking.
I was just making a delivery to a regular customer living at the top of that building.
Simon, you bastard.
Shizuo, it's not good to fight.
Shut up!
Get lost!
H-Hey, Mikado!
Let's get outta here!
What? You serious?!
Mikado!
Hey! Wait!
S-Sorry!
The city also gives presents.
A very tiny, yet great miracle.
The adventure he has been desiring.
A possibility for the start of a new story.
And...
U-Um...
Thank you very much.
Please excuse me.
...there's also the possibility of nothing starting.
I found...
my love!
I heard the Dollars did it again.
Yeah! Same here!
They fought with a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo in broad daylight.
I heard the Dollars picked a fight.
A fight between Shizuo and the Dollars.
Looks like it.
No, that's wrong.
I happened to see it.
They were just impostors.
That's not all.
Recently, people who called themselves the
Dollars attacked and robbed a pedestrian.
What?
The Dollars are so scary and merciless.
You better watch your ass.
'Kay. Thanks.
They're really scary...
The Dollars.
Izaya came to Ikebukuro.
Just when I was going to kill him, Simon got in my way.
But... why did he come here?
This city is full of foreigners.
They came here searching for something, seeking something...
They're here to change something.
Welcome! Welcome!
Me too.
Eat some sushi.
Hey, listen to my story till the end.
The very unique story about me and her.
Next time: Alone With Just Your Shadow For Comfort.
I'm sure you'll be non compos mentis and trembling in fear.