[LULU] From the beginning,
we hated you,
but also, we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you,
so we had to cross the wall.
[gavel thunks]
[LIFE SEXY] Defendant bear
Lulu Yurigasaki, I ask you this.
Will you give up on love?
Or, will you give up on kisses?
I will never give up
on love, Your Honor.
So, I'll give up on kisses.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[LULU]
Growl.
Please, oh, please,
make me a human girl!
I've just gotta go to
the other side of the wall.
I can't let Ginko go alone!
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
Welcome, everyone. This is
known as the Severance Court.
The door has opened,
so enter what we consider
the land of enlightenment
for all living things.
Yes, even human and bear.
I'm the Judge, Life Sexy.
[LIFE COOL]
I'm Prosecutor, Life Cool.
I'm Defense Counsel,
Life Beauty.
Sparkle, sparkle!
[LIFE SEXY] All right, since
court is not in session today.
I thought I would tell
you all a sexy story
that might clear some of
this craziness up a bit.
[LIFE COOL]
Your Honor!
We aren't spending today
looking like this, are we?
Why not? I couldn't possibly
be more adorable right now!
Sparkle, sparkle!
The problem is I'm
not feeling very cool.
[LIFE BEAUTY]
But you look so cute, Cool!
Well, not as cute
as me, of course.
[LIFE COOL]
Hey!
[LIFE SEXY]
Order in the court!
"The Princess Who
Gave Up on Kisses"?
She gave up on Kisses?
[LIFE SEXY] Let us begin
the story, for that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.
[LIFE SEXY]
Once upon a time,
long before the Wall
of Severance was built
to separate people from bears,
there was a lovely bear kingdom
in a lovely bear forest.
In that kingdom, there lived
a very beautiful princess.
She was called Lulu,
for that was her name.
Princess Lulu was
heir to the throne.
The future Queen Lulu.
Princess Lulu was special from
the very moment she was born.
In fact, not a day went by
without the bears of the castle
praising her vast
charm and beauty.
[ATTENDANT ONE]
How adorable you are!
Princess Lulu, you are our
kingdom's greatest treasure.
[ATTENDANT TWO]
No pearl or gem of any sort
could ever outshine
Your Highness!
[ATTENDANT THREE]
We are so fortunate
to serve such a smart,
kind, and beautiful princess!
[ATTENDANTS]
We are truly blessed!
Yes, Princess Lulu
was by far the favorite
of all the bears
in all the kingdom.
Desire!
[LIFE SEXY]
And then, one day.
More shooting stars
fell to earth
than anyone had
ever seen before!
They were fragments of
the former planet Kumaria,
and they came from
the far reaches of space.
[ATTENDANT ONE]
Princess, rejoice!
Her Majesty, your mother,
has just given birth
to a beautiful and
healthy little boy!
You have a baby brother
now, Your Highness.
That must be so exciting!
The king and queen
are both practically
beside themselves with joy.
Yes, the long-awaited prince.
Our beloved kingdom
is finally secure.
[LULU]
Wait, who's the heir?
[ALL]
The prince, of course!
[LULU]
Whaaa--?
[LIFE SEXY]
♪ Shaba-da. Shaba-daba-daba. ♪
From that day forward, Princess
Lulu was no longer the favorite.
[ATTENDANTS laughing]
My, Prince Milne,
you're so cute!
Oh yes, how adorable
you are, your highness!
The whole kingdom is fortunate
to serve such a kind
and beautiful prince!
[MILNE laughing]
[LIFE SEXY] From the very
moment her brother was born,
the entire castle, nay,
the entire kingdom,
was wild about their new
favorite, the little prince.
Princess Lulu was
left alone, sadly.
Yes, she became unwanted.
Oh, my!
[ATTENDANTS, MILNE laughing]
Oh! Hey, Big Sis Lulu!
I love you, Big Sis!
Oh, shut up.
That kid is in the way,
like big time.
Hey, Big Sis,
I have a question.
Is it true what they say?
That real love turns into stars?
See, Mommy reads me a book,
and the pictures say it's so.
I guess the words do, too!
Tell me, Sis, does love
really turn into stars?
Does love really
turn into stars?
Does it? Does it? Does it?
[LULU]
Yes, it does.
Real love climbs all
the way up to heaven
and then turns into the
stars in the night sky.
[MILNE gasps] A shooting star!
[LULU] Did your book
talk about what happens
with shooting stars, too?
When they fall to earth,
it turns into a Promise Kiss.
Yeah, right!
Love turning into a kiss?
Talk about a stupid fairy tale.
Grody growlll.
Then, Promise Kisses
must look like stars.
I bet they're all
really sparkly,
with different kinds of colors!
Yeah, maybe so.
Ohh.
Okay! You know
what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna go get a Promise
Kiss for you, Lulu!
Huh?
That shooting star
was my love for you!
I mean, I love you
with all of my heart,
so it just has to
be my love, right?
Yay! Bet it's on the ground
out there somewhere.
That was the fateful moment.
Princess Lulu thought of a way
out of her pesky situation.
She knew how to get rid
of her little brother.
Desire.
[FEMALE VOICE]
Kuma shock!
[LULU]
Hey, Milne.
Do you honestly love
your big sister Lulu?
Yep, I do! So, can you
give me a big ol' kiss?
I will as long as you
bring me a Promise Kiss.
Think you can do that?
[MILNE]
Mm.
[LULU]
All right, better get in here.
[MILNE]
Okay!
[LULU]
Die!
Die! Die!
Desire, growl.
Now, I can finally be
the favorite one again!
Without Milne,
the world is surely going to
start wanting me once more.
But just then--
[MILNE]
I'm back, Sis! I'm back home!
[LULU]
Huh?!
[LIFE SEXY] Prince Milne, who
she assumed was dead, came back.
And what's more--
[MILNE]
Here, I got your Promise Kiss!
Look how sparkly! And it's
the same color as a star, too!
Huh?
This isn't a Promise Kiss,
it's just boring old honey.
C'mon, gimme a kiss!
You promised you would,
don't you remember?
Kiss me! Kiss me, please!
You promised! You promised!
C'mon, Sis, kiss me,
kiss me, kiss me...
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up!
Ah!
[LIFE SEXY] Princess Lulu
threw the Promise Kiss
that Prince Milne had
brought her far, far away.
She got rid of it
because it wasn't what
she had wanted at all.
She wasn't one
to give up, though.
[LULU]
Hey, Milne.
Do you honestly love
your big sister?
Yep, I do! I love you, so can
you please give me a big kiss?
I will as long as you
bring me a Promise Kiss.
Think you can do that?
[MILNE]
Mm.
[LULU]
All right, better get in here!
[MILNE]
Okay!
[LULU]
Die!
I'm getting my
desire this time.
There's no way I won't!
[MILNE]
I'm back, Sis!
You promised me a kiss! Come on!
Kiss me, Sis, kiss me!
[LULU]
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Hey, Milne.
[MILNE]
Yep! I do!
I love you! Give me a kiss!
[LULU]
Die!
[LULU] For real this
time, desire max!
[MILNE] You just gotta give me
a kiss, now. You promised!
Kiss me, Sis. You promised...
[LIFE SEXY] Surprisingly,
no matter how many times
she sent him plummeting
to his death,
Prince Milne returned
to Princess Lulu
over and over and over again.
In his hands, he would have the
Promise Kiss, a pot of honey.
And with a smile, he would
pester her for a kiss.
[LULU]
Shut up, shut up!
[LIFE SEXY]
Until one day--
[door opens]
[ATTENDANT ONE]
Uh! I have terrible news!
It's Prince Milne.
He's passed away!
I saw the whole
thing happen!
It was a tragic, tragic
accident! An accidental death.
Well, all right, then.
Everything's worked
out perfectly.
[LIFE SEXY]
And so, once again,
Princess Lulu became the
kingdom's favorite bear.
[gasps]
That dream. I had it again.
[LULU]
♪ Simmer, simmer, porridge, ♪
♪ simmer, simmer softly! ♪
Growl, growl!
[giggles] And for my
special finishing touch.
[KUREHA]
That wasn't a dream.
I killed Mitsuko. I killed her
with my own two hands!
A bear turned human?
But, why? How?
[LULU]
Oh, you're awake?
[KUREHA]
It's you, why are you here?
[LULU]
It's Lulu, remember? Kure-pie.
"Kure-pie"?
Growl! Like cutie pie
but with Kureha!
Adorable, right?
Lulu is so clever!
[KUREHA]
N-Never mind that.
How did you get into my house?
Mm. The open window? Well, the
broken window, but it's fixed!
What do you want with me?
I mean, you basically
broke into my house,
and then you start cooking?
Why are you even here?
Growl, we, uh, we just wanted
to come to see if you were okay.
You haven't been to
school in a long time,
so we were starting to get
really worried about you.
[KUREHA]
Why not ask Miss Yuriika?
She knows where I am.
[LULU] Dunno. Probably
because we were so worried.
[KUREHA]
Worried? Drop the act.
I'm sure you're invisible
like the others by now.
Invisible? No, not at all.
We're trying to be
good friends, Kureha.
You're my friends?
Mh-hm! For you!
It's a Lulu special!
I call it honey porridge.
It's so tasty, it'll make you
all growly-gooey inside!
Oh, Sumika.
[SUMIKA]
Here.
We can each take half, okay?
I think food tastes better
when we're together.
[KUREHA]
No, Sumika is my only friend.
Uh!
[gasps]
[LIFE SEXY] Several years had
passed since Prince Milne died,
and since Princess Lulu
became the kingdom's favorite.
She had grown into
a beautiful lady,
and prince after prince visited
from surrounding kingdoms.
However, every time...
[LIFE SEXY]
Princess Lulu,
won't you please give me
a Promise Kiss?
I want to share a
passionate romance with you
that will burn hotter
than the sun.
For that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.
Oh, my!
[LIFE COOL] Your Highness,
you mustn't be taken in
by play-bears like him!
Were I to be the lucky one
who receives your
precious Promise Kiss,
I would double your
kingdom's economy.
No, wait! I would
increase it tenfold!
[chuckles]
I'm so cool.
Oh, my!
You're both silly
little fools, aren't you?
Haven't you been told what
really matters in a man?
It's how cute they are!
A-sparkle!
I'll stay by your side
forever, Princess Lulu!
We'll be beautiful!
You'll give me a
Promise Kiss, won't you?
Oh, my!
[LIFE SEXY. LIFE BEAUTY,
LIFE COOL] Oh, my!
We could keep at this, but
I'm sure you get the picture.
[LIFE SEXY grunts]
[LIFE SEXY] Authority,
the attention of her people,
words of love. Princess
Lulu had gotten everything
she had ever hoped to have.
And it was all thanks to
Prince Milne's convenient death.
However, even after she had all
she ever thought she desired,
Lulu never felt truly happy.
On the contrary,
she felt rather--
[LIFE SEXY yelps]
[LIFE SEXY screaming]
[LIFE ESEXY] Rather plagued by
an awful feeling of emptiness,
as though she had misplaced
something deeply precious.
[sighs]
[LIFE SEXY]
And then, one day.
[knocking]
What is it?
If it's more princes or
new dresses, I don't want any.
[door opens]
[LULU]
Milne!
I'm back home, Sis,
and look what I have!
Here you go. I brought
you a Promise Kiss.
How far did you have
to travel to find that?
Oh, Milne.
Everyone thinks that you died!
Yeah, I know.
I had to go super far away,
it was real, real hard,
but I still made it back okay!
I can't take that from you.
I know I'll just
throw it away again.
Oh, don't worry!
I'll find as many of
these as you want me to!
So kiss me, Sis, please?!
You promised you would.
Don't you remember?
[knocking]
[LULU]
Milne?
Who are you?
[STRANGER] Here, is this
your little brother's?
[gasps] Yes, it is.
[STRANGER] I found it across the
valley, so I came to deliver it.
Did you throw this away?
[LULU]
Yeah.
[STRANGER]
It still belongs to you.
If you forget about
the thing you've lost,
then you really will
lose it, eventually.
[gasps]
[clunk]
Good talk.
[LULU gasps]
[ATTENDANT ONE] It was a
tragic, tragic accident!
The way Prince Milne died
was awful. As always,
the darling little prince said
he wanted to go get some honey
to bring back for his
beloved sister, Princess Lulu.
He went up to the
bees' nest, and was stung.
That's what killed him.
It all happened so quickly.
[MILNE]
You promised you would!
Kiss me, Sis! Kiss me!
[LULU]
From the beginning,
Lulu hated you.
But also, Lulu must have loved
you from the beginning, as well.
[GINKO]
Well, that sucks.
Your honey porridge is good.
Shame to waste it.
[LULU]
It's because Lulu made her mad.
The only thing Lulu
figures she did wrong
was say we were trying
to be good friends.
Lulu just wanted to be nice.
Lulu.
Thanks, Ginko.
My love is about making
sure your love is fulfilled.
Lulu feels like
if she can do that,
if she can help you, Lulu might
be able to see him again.
One more time.
And that's why... why Lulu.
[GINKO] Well, I have
someplace to be, so see ya.
[LULU]
Wait! Where are you going?
[GINKO]
Beyond the Wall of Severance.
To the human world?
But, if you do that, you're
for sure gonna get killed.
Oh, no, I'll be fine.
That's because
I got love from her.
[LULU]
You "got love"?
Yeah, so I'm gonna
go return it.
I'll see her and
deliver my love.
I made her a promise.
We would meet again,
and I would kiss her.
Kiss her?
Yes. It's a Promise Kiss.
[MILNE]
You promised!
Kiss me, Sis! Kiss me!
[LULU] So, this girl is on
the other side of the wall?
[GINKO] Yeah, I know
she's waiting for me.
[LULU]
But she's human, right?
If you meet her,
she might try to kill you.
[gunshot]
Yes, I know.
That doesn't bother you?
No way.
Because I am a criminal bear.
I refuse to back
down on my love.
[gasps]
Take me with you.
What?
Take me with you
across the wall!
Oh, please, let me go along!
If you take me,
I can help you.
We can work side by side.
Get you that Promise Kiss!
Why would you do that?
Because, like you,
I'm a criminal bear!
[LULU]
You're me... before I lost mine.
No, that's wrong.
I think you've already
lost yours once.
But if there's someone out there
still alive for you
to meet, we'll go.
Even if that girl
is across the wall!
[LIFE SEXY] Defendant bear
Lulu Yurigasaki, I ask you this.
Will you give up on love?
Or, will you give up on kisses?
I'll never give up on love,
so I'll give up on kisses.
[BOTH grunt]
[LULU]
Growl.
Please, oh, please,
make me a human girl!
I've just gotta go to
the other side of the wall.
I can't let Ginko go alone!
First, I need you to understand
that if you make this choice,
you will lose
all kisses forever.
[LULU] They're already lost,
and I'll never see them again.
But not for Ginko.
I know she'll still
be able to see hers!
So, since I can't have mine,
I'll help complete
her Promise Kiss.
[LIFE SEXY]
In other words,
you're entrusting
Ginko Yurishiro
with the wish you failed
to fulfill yourself?
Trying to achieve
self-actualization that way
is mere self-satisfaction.
It is pride. And that,
dear, is a crime.
Great. I'm okay with it
since I'm a criminal bear.
[LIFE SEXY] I see. I shall
now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
[LULU]
Growly-growl, growl!
[LIFE SEXY] And thus,
Princess Lulu. Correction.
And thus Lulu Yurigasaki,
set out with Ginko
Yurishiro as human girls
to cross the Wall of Severance.
Now, the question remains,
will the Promise
Kiss come to pass?
For that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.