"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
On your mark, get set...
Nothing less from Kona-chan! Amazing!
You're so good at sports.
Why don't you join any
of the athletic teams?
Because if I join any of the teams,
I won't be able to watch any of
the prime-time anime shows.
"The Girl Who Dashes Off"
Hey, Tsukasa, which end of
a choco-cornet do you eat first?
From the head end first, right?
I see...
By the way, which end is the head?
The fatter end, or the thinner end?
I think this end,
the thin side, is the head.
I see... I thought that
the fatter end was the head.
So, why is the thinner end the head?
I mean, doesn't this look
like a type of seashell?
Why do you think it's
the fatter end, Kona-chan?
'Cause it looks like a caterpillar.
A caterpillar?
Well, but when you think about it,
the seashell gives a better image.
Um...
You can also tear the thin end off,
and dip it in the extra chocolate
cream on the fatter end.
I get it!
Nothing less from Miyuki-san!
You're so smart!
No... Each person has their
own way of eating, so...
How do you eat a cream puff?
A cream puff?
Let's see... I start off by
splitting it into two, taking the lid,
and dipping it into
the cream in the pot area.
Then, after that, I start
eating the pot area.
That way, no cream spurts out,
and I can eat both the pastry and
the cream in a balanced way.
There are some that have both
custard and whipped cream, right?
How do you eat those?
Do you mix them?
No, I don't go out of my way
to mix the two.
Wait, how exactly would you
mix them together?
No, I was just asking.
When do you eat the strawberry
on top of a strawberry shortcake,
or the chestnut on top
of a Mont Blanc?
Let's see...
That depends on the amount
of strawberries
that are sandwiched between
the two layers of sponge cake.
I try to think about the pace
at which I eat the strawberries,
the whipped cream,
and the sponge cake.
So the timing in which I eat the
strawberry on top always differs.
That's well thought out.
I always save it for last,
but sometimes, I get so full
that I can't eat it after all,
or someone in my family
takes it away from me.
You have to eat your favorite
food at the beginning, after all.
Come to think of it,
I don't think I've ever seen
my big sister having her
strawberry taken from her.
That's Kagami for you.
Doesn't leave herself open.
Can you eat the last bite
on a popsicle without dropping it?
Does it drop?
When you don't eat it right...
It drops off, doesn't it?
Yes.
How do you go about it, Kona-chan?
I lick it up to the end.
Wow...
Why not keep turning it around
while you eat, like this?
Oh, that sounds like a good idea.
I'm not really one for
soft-serve ice cream.
Why not?
I dislike being left with
just the cone in the end.
Right, right! You always have
just the cone left in the end!
I always try to push the ice cream
further and further
into the cone as I eat.
How do you push it down?
As I eat, like, with a push and shove.
A push and shove, is it...
Yuki-chan, you're always concerned
about balance, aren't you?
I suppose so.
Then how do you eat curried rice?
Do you mix the curry roux
with the rice when you eat?
No, I don't mix the two,
but I always try to have
an equal amount left.
I mix them up.
What about you, Kona-chan?
It depends on the curry.
When I pour on some sauce,
or drop a raw egg on it,
I tend to mix it up, I guess.
Sauce? On curry?
Yeah. It's tasty.
Do you use sauce on fried eggs too?
No, it's soy sauce for fried eggs.
I see... I use mayonnaise.
On fried eggs? Not hard-boiled eggs?
Yeah. Mayonnaise goes well
with basically every egg dish.
You put it on curry too?
Yeah.
Of course, I do on plain white rice too,
but also on beef bowls.
It goes well with that sweet broth.
It's also good on
chicken and egg bowls.
You know how egg and chicken
are child and parent, right?
So, I put some mayonnaise
that's made from eggs on it,
and call it the Relative Bowl.
That, and I used to hate natto beans,
but I can eat them when
I put mayonnaise on them.
Ew, I can't even imagine that.
Oh, but the tastiest thing must be
when you put mayonnaise
on soft-boiled eggs.
In our house, even
the fried eggs are half cooked.
That's how my dad likes it.
I guess he likes sucking on the yolk.
So if you fry the yolk too much,
he can't suck it out anymore.
How do you eat chicken skewers?
What do you mean, how?
Do you eat it right off the skewer?
Or do you take the meat off
the skewer with chopsticks?
Let's see.
When I eat the entire
skewer by myself,
I'll eat it as is,
but when I'm eating in a crowd,
I separate it from the skewer.
Oh, yeah, don't you feel awkward
when one last morsel is left?
Yes. The very last piece is very
difficult to put your hands on.
And with nobody eating it,
time passes,
and it gets all dry and obviously
not so tasty looking,
and nobody really wants it anymore.
But when the server tries
to take the plate away,
you say, "Oh, we're still
eating that," and stuff.
And yet, we sometimes go home
without eating it after all.
It's such a waste.
I feel sorry for it...
Oh, you know, I also feel sorry for
that one piece of meat
that's left on the grill
and turns into charcoal when
you go for Korean barbecue.
Well, with Korean barbecue,
you're always eating and
chatting at the same time,
so you end up pretty busy.
Salted beef tongue with green
onions roasts really quickly,
so it's especially hurried.
You're right. It's already done
by the time you flip it over once.
You flip it over?
Salted tongue with green onions?
Yeah.
You shouldn't flip those over!
Is that so?
I mean, when you flip it over,
all the green onions on top
fall into the grill!
Oh, you're right.
You don't need to flip it over.
You just roast one side,
and enough heat is distributed
over the meat naturally.
I see. I'll do that from now on.
You absolutely, positively
shouldn't flip it over.
Is that so?
Yeah.
No kidding...
Anyway, the fatter end
and the thinner end,
which end is the head
of a choco-cornet?
A mega bad boy!
There sure are a lot of
confinement crimes lately.
Like, having a girl call you
"Master" and stuff.
You know, isn't that more
because of guys playing
too many dating sims and erotic games,
rather than just moral degeneration?
That's a really common situation.
You're really talking about yourself!
Wait a second. Why do you know
what goes on in those adult games?
You're in eleventh grade, right?
Lucky Star!
"First Trimester Midterm Results"
"3rd: Miyuki Takara"
You're amazing, always
at the top of your class.
Miyuki-san, do you have
any faults at all?
I am embarrassed to say,
but sometimes,
I tend to think things out too much,
or just plain space out.
--Sometimes I slice my finger
using a vegetable slicer,
--Ouch!
or trip over my own feet and fall down,
or get one end of my tote bag
caught in the train door.
Miyuki-san, you don't call those faults.
You call them "moe points."
Moe?
Clumsiness is your element?
What kind of images are running in
your head right now, Kona-chan?!
Miyuki-san, you're attractive enough.
Why do you wear glasses?
You can only target a certain breed
of people like that, you know?
Target?
Putting aside whether
she's popular with guys,
why don't you switch to contacts?
I hear that eyeglasses tend
to make your vision worse.
Well, it's embarrasing to say now
that we're in high school and all,
but, well, I...
I'm afraid of contact lenses!
Or rather, I'm scared of
putting anything into my eyes.
I can't even open
my eyes underwater.
Damn, she's really cute.
A natural airhead...
Oh, isn't that Miyuki-san?
"Yoshimizu Optometrist"
Maybe she came to get
an eye exam for contacts?
Maybe Miyuki-san is better
off like that forever.
That looks painful...
She's a living national monument.
Kagami's sick at home
with a cold today?
Yeah. At least it doesn't seem
like she's got the flu.
I'm an idiot, so I have no worries
about catching the flu and stuff.
I hear that about a cold often enough,
but that works for the flu too?
Colds and the flu are different things?
I thought the flu was just
the deluxe version of a cold.
I think it's different...
But when you ask me like that,
I'm not really so sure myself anymore.
The difference between
influenza and a cold?
Yup, yup.
Well, let's see.
Influenza is viral,
and has many full-body symptoms
such as fever and muscle aches,
and furthermore can
have complications.
On the other hand, a cold is mainly
inflammation of the throat
and a runny nose,
and your fever doesn't
end up that high.
The detailed symptoms
are different as well.
Hmm...
So these two are different illnesses.
Really...
B-But...
Well, there are a lot of
common aspects as well,
so you could still say the flu
is a scaled-up model of a cold.
I see!
Kona-chan, what's with that
serious look on your face?
Well, it's nothing big,
but something's been on my mind
about this morning's conversation.
You mean about the cold and the flu?
Tsukasa, you didn't deny it even once
when I said I was an idiot.
It's not like that!
That's not what I meant...
Oh, welcome, Konata.
She came by to visit Sis.
Oh, thank you for
coming all the way out.
No problem. Excuse me!
Heh, Kagami's face is unexpectedly
cute when she's asleep.
--What?! What are you doing here?! Go home!
--Oh, she's up, she's awake.
A visit? You? All the way
out here just for me?
That's right.
But I'd feel bad if you
caught what I have,
so I'll just take the sentiments.
What's with this? It makes me happy.
A new type of virus is going around,
so she's worried about me?
I thought that the only things she
thinks about were games and anime.
I'm kind of touched now.
Well, I'd like to copy that
homework we got the other day.
That, and you showed me
a really cute sleeping face,
so don't worry about it.
Go home!
Kagami, Miyuki is here to visit you!
Okay...
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry to trouble you
on a holiday.
Is it all right for you to be up?
--I brought this as a get-well gift.
--Thanks!
I'm almost completely well.
I took some medicine,
so my fever is down too.
Here.
Flowers and fruit! I'm so happy!
Oh, do sit down.
Thank you so much.
I had thought of visiting
right away with Izumi-san,
but I couldn't find the time
to do so yesterday...
It's all right, it's fine.
I was entrusted with the
committee meeting minutes.
Oh, thank you!
If you can take a look at it,
though not so much as to
worsen your condition...
Sure.
That, and these are the budget
requests for each club...
And what else did I have... Let's see...
Oh, if you're not feeling well
right now, I'll go home now.
This is what a visit
really should be like!
Had something happened?
Actually, Konata came by yesterday...
Oh, brother.
Perhaps that was Izumi-san's way
of caring for you?
About the homework, perhaps
she was goofing around
in an effort to cheer
you up, Kagami-san.
And your sleeping face might
have been an inevitable result
of trying not to make noise.
Is this girl a saint or something?!
I can't think of it that way at all!
Come to think of it,
is Tsukasa-san out today?
Morning...
Sis, are you feeling any better?
See for yourself. She lives
a more relaxed life than the ill.
Well, I'm not always like this.
Today, it's like that "One sleeps
late in the spring" thing.
Oh, it's a little late to
say this, but welcome.
I know how that is.
I have trouble waking up
in the morning myself lately.
Isn't that it? I'm so sleepy lately...
That's true. It's especially
warm out today.
Yeah, yeah. Like that.
You can't help it.
The holiday we had the other day
was really warm too, right?
Yes.
When I woke up, it was already dusk.
I spent most of the day asleep.
It's better to rest when you can.
In the end, I spent that
entire day in my pajamas.
Oh, I guess the same goes for today.
Is what you have on
right now your pajamas?
Yeah, it is.
That is very cute! They don't
look like pajamas at all!
Really?
Yes.
Is it all right for me
to stay in this outfit?
Yes. I think you could walk
around outside like that.
--Maybe I can head to the
convenience store like this?
--Man, it's an endless
wait for the punch line...
--Yes, I think it would
probably be all right...
"Nurse's Office"
A slight increase...
No, that's not it!
The bra I'm wearing today has
underwires and a large pad in it,
so I'm heavier by that much!
Right, that's it. I wonder
how much it is in grams.
If I can subtract that much...
It's over...
I screwed up!
I forgot that the
physical exam was today,
so I wore character-print
underwear today!
I'm so embarrassed!
"Nurse's Office"
I haven't grown!
Dammit! Why are you
the only one looking confident?!
S'up? I'm here.
Oh, Sis.
Just a thought...
Kagami, you come here
to hang out a lot.
Don't you have friends in your class?
Don't put me in the same boat as you.
Are you picking a fight with me?
What, I thought that you were
shunned by your classmates.
Before you worry about others,
why don't you worry about yourself?
You have zero social skills!
I have no worries about that.
I may look like this, but I have
about a hundred friends,
and my social and bargaining
skills are pretty high,
and I join a party every night.
With my allies, I work to bring
back the glimmer in crystals
to prevent the world
from falling to ruin,
and rescue the kidnapped princess--
Wait, you're talking about a game!
I haven't seen that guy
around for a while...
Who?
She's talking about one of
her game buddies, I'm sure.
Yeah. He was
a soldier-type character,
but he wanted to raise
his combat skills,
and he left saying
he was going to train
in an area with a lot of monsters...
And he hasn't come back since.
I heard he's camping out
in the underground nest.
But I wonder if he's all right,
acting all hermit-like.
Everyone's getting pretty worried.
A hermit inside a game?
I don't know the details,
but from the login info,
it looks like he's been
playing the game nonstop.
A hermit, both in real life
and in virtual life!
Well, it's the same guy doing it, so...
By the way, how did you two get to
know each other, Tsukasa, Konata?
Tsukasa was about to be taken away
by some suspicious big foreign guy,
and just then I arrived on the scene
in the nick of time!
And I used my strong moves, the
front punch and the whirlwind kick,
ever so gracefully to rescue her!
Why does she end up talking about
games in every conversation?
Well, actually, I just showed
my skills as a martial artist.
I don't approve of
starting off with violence,
but that's one of your
good points, I guess.
Actually, the foreigner was
just asking for directions,
but I didn't understand
what he was saying at all,
and was troubled when
Kona-chan came by...
Wait, that's no good at all!
Why are you acting like
you won the battle?!
The time has finally come again...
Is something going on?
Well, pro baseball season has started.
Kona-chan, you don't like
watching sports and stuff?
You seem to be good
with anything athletic.
I thought you'd be the type that
would like watching that stuff.
But when extra innings delay
all the following programs,
it throws off the recording times
for all the late-night anime,
and at worst, the broadcast
itself gets cancelled.
It sucks to have something
you like disappear.
Kagami, when do you
eat the strawberry
on top of a strawberry shortcake?
Why?
I was wondering if you were the type
that saves your favorites
until the end.
It's true that I eat
my favorite stuff last,
but when it comes to
strawberries, it depends.
Then do you roast both sides of
salted tongue with green onions?
Salted tongue with green onions?
They roast very quickly to begin with,
but when you roast both sides,
it gets done even faster.
You shouldn't!
The green onions will fall off.
I thought you put the green onions
on top after the meat's all roasted!
If you do that, the green onions
don't get roasted at all.
Aren't the green onions acting
as a condiment in the first place?
You don't get it at all...
Well, maybe both ways are all right.
Which side of a choco-cornet
do you think is the head,
the fatter end, or the thinner end?
The fatter end?
You're agreeing with me.
Seriously?
Then which end do you eat first?
Aren't you supposed to
tear off the thinner end,
and dip it in the leftover chocolate
cream in the fatter end?
Really...
Yeah.
Have you ever made friends
in real life other than us?
I used to have a really good friend
back in junior high.
Oh, you actually had one.
I haven't contacted her in a while...
I wonder what she's
been up to lately.
She had written in the junior
high graduation literature book
that her dream was
to become a Mage...
In the end, birds of a feather
are flocking together?!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Now Lucky Channel has finally begun!
We're on TV now! All right!
Hello to all the people seeing me
for the first time on TV!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
Oh... and I'm Shiraishi.
Who?
A joke! Just kidding!
This is Minoru Shiraishi-san, who
will be helping me out from now on!
Ta-da-da-da!
Oh, well, I am Minoru Shiraishi,
and I will be the assistant
for Akira-sama...
Nice to see you.
Oh? You're a bit tense, Shiraishi-san?
Come on, you're finally on TV now,
loosen up a bit more! Just kidding!
I'm sorry, I'm just not used to this.
Now, I know this is early,
but we already have
letters of congratulation
from our viewers!
Oh, yes... well...
A letter from "I Love Berry-Kou" in Osaka.
Congratulations on the TV
debut of Lucky Channel!
That's a thank you!
By the way, I have
a question for Akira.
Akira, you're recognized as
a super-idol by yourself and others,
but how much money
does an idol earn?
Please tell me.
How much money?
Yes.
Kind of a personal question here.
You know... What's the point of
asking me something like that?
Akira-sama?
Well, if you want to know, I'll tell you.
Honestly, it really depends.
There are some events
that are really cheap,
but since I'm still getting a set
amount from my production company,
I don't know how much they're
deducting for company profit at all.
On top of that, I've been in this
business since I was three,
so all my earnings still get deposited
into my parents' bank account.
I only get a small allowance
from them. And it's really small.
Hey, come to think of it,
Mama's been buying pricey
brand-name bags left and right lately.
Maybe that was the money
I earned from this TV show?
You're freakin' kidding me!
--Am I Cinderella or something?!
--Wait a minute!
--Just because Dad stopped sending living
expenses ever since they got separated,
--Well, uh, you really don't need
to go that far in describing...
--she shouldn't be totally
relying on me for money!
Oh, no, it's time for us
to say goodbye!
Akira's so lonely!
And so, in this segment,
please send all sorts of
questions and praise to me,
as well as opinions you have
about the show as a whole!
A word from you as well,
Shiraishi-san, please!
Oh... then, I hope you will see us
again in the next episode.
See ya!
That's right... Are you serious about
getting a part in the main show?
Oh, where did you hear about that?
Going to karaoke with
four people is unusual.
I hardly ever come to places like this.
Come on, we only have two hours,
so all of you, sing up a ton!
You don't have to be so enthusiastic.
We have plenty of time!
You know, this makes my heart race.
It's so much fun.
And when you sing, you end up
with such a clear conscience...
Hey, where's the catalog?
Catalog?
Yeah, the catalog.
The catalog?
You know, the one that
lists all the song numbers.
Oh, you mean this? Here.
Then I'll go first!
That was fast... Wait, you already
entered three songs?!
It's such a waste of time if you
don't put in tons of songs!
Test, test, test.
What song is this?
Space Iron-Men Kyoudain!
You just have to start off
with this one!
I don't know this one...
Go for it, Kona-chan!
Konata, that's too loud!
I'm telling you, turn down the volume!
How the hell does she know a song like this?
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Konata here! Sleepy!
Why is it that on the nights
that you slept so much,
you're especially sleepy
in the morning?
It kinda defeats the purpose
of getting a good night's sleep.
Next episode: Efforts and Results.
"Efforts and Results"
Look forward to it!