Dollars?
They're angels that fly in the sky, show their panties, and shout, "Pipiru Pirupiru."
Don't fuck up the dose, 'kay?
They'll pay less if she doesn't wake up.
We don't know that much about them either,
but we'll tell you everything we know.
Apparently, they're part of a color gang,
but no one knows which.
The new publication of Dengeki Bunko came out today,
...and ten... for other things.
Yep, for other things.
Don't think you can get away!
Right turn!
A man needs strong abdominal muscles.
This is the first time we've gone all out since we joined the Dollars, right, Kadota-san?
Stay in your seats.
The Dollars aren't angels that fly in the sky, show their panties, and shout, "Pipiru Pirupiru," right?
Dotachin!
Stop calling me that!
All right, we shook 'em off.
Are they insane?!
Shit!
Well then, start talking.
Let's hear about the human experiments you're helping with.
I'm Kadota Kyouhei.
I don't like to be called "Dotachin."
This adventure started eight hours ago.
I'll be talking about the infamous Kaztano incident.
The person who disappeared is one of my classmates.
Well, to be precise, a friend of a friend.
I've never met that person before.
So, someone you know went missing...
Oh, speaking of which, a lot of people have disappeared lately.
There are a lot of rumors about these incidents.
Kanra-san, you really like rumors, huh?
From what I've heard, it's either kids who ran away from home,
or illegal immigrants.
Basically, people who don't have any
impact on their surroundings.
Quite a few people fitting that profile seem to
disappear between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
On top of that, when someone goes missing,
that person is never seen again.
Really?
Some rumors are even scarier.
The reason they're never seen again is because
the Dollars dispose of their bodies.
Nice, a rusty sign.
This is the place.
So this is where the informant said there'd be a good supply.
Yeah, this looks like a ghetto that illegal immigrants would live in.
All right, let's get in, get this stuff done, and then get some money.
Kaztano!
Shut up!
Whoa! Teens!
Extra 20%, here we come!
Nah dude, let's play it safe this time.
If we don't, that thing  might come again.
The headless guy?
Let's just make do with that tonight.
'Sup?
Is he a beer short of a six pack or something?
Well, he is human.
So we should be prepared to get paid less for bringing in some geezer.
Hey.
Yo, my cash cow.
I'm Japanese! Just like you!
But many people say I act like a foreigner.
I'm un poco sad.
I get bullied sometimes.
This geezer isn't even worth a cent.
Besides, what the hell does "un poco sad" mean?
So, if there isn't a brother-type fairy-helper character like Yuuta,
it's just like a maso with a hair fetish.
It's more of a trap than a brother-type character though.
I want a little sister-type chara that comes to help like a fairy.
But I wouldn't mind a big sis-type either.
Just don't talk about that during dinner.
Dotachin!
Let's go grab some dinner!
Dinner! Dinner!
Okay.
Man, your craftsmanship is as excellent as ever, Kadota-san.
This bathroom is bigger than my room.
They wanted it to feel like a high-class cabaret inviting you to relax.
Oh, we'd better hurry up.
Today's the important day that only comes once a month.
Yeah.
Who is it?
Kaztano.
"Bin is borked."
Then he should buy a new one.
He should go to a dollar store.
I am Japanese!
Maybe he meant "I've been abducted"?
You're thinking too much.
Shut the hell up!
Make him sleep already!
Aye!
It's cheap!
You heard the rumor too, Sonohara-san?
Yes.
Don't worry.
It's just a silly rumor.
Yeah.
Harima-san just disappeared.
That doesn't mean she was kidnapped.
It's unfathomable that she would be kidnapped and dispo—
Good job going into detail.
Did I just dig my own grave?
Here's your sushi.
No worries, our sushi is made of fish.
Even when they're half off, they're not made from humans.
But you know...
Shit, is he gonna continue?!
Simon!
The banner out front is broken.
The banner?
Yes!
Let's go and fix it.
Okay? Okay?
Let's go and get it fixed.
Really.
The sushi shop around the corner serves human meat on "50% Off" days.
Humans! Humans, I say!
Scary, isn't it?
Hey Togusa-san, why don't you decorate your car with anime charas? {ok the pun is terribly hard to explain. itasha = those cars with anime figures on it etc though itasha could mean italian car too - dont leave it as itasha}
They're awesome.
I'll kill you.
Well duh. Italian cars are expensive since they're foreign.
A Setouchi-style shrimp please!
I want yellow tail and white trevally!
That was dangerous!
Yeah.
Dude, why'd you empty the whole bottle?
You even got some on us.
I can't drive.
I'm too sleepy.
Don't fall asleep until we've delivered him.
Fuck, man!
M-My eyelids!
Watch where you're going!
Ah, 'scuse moi.
What?
This guy's the cause of everything.
We can rejuvenate ourselves by throwing him out.
What?
Kaztano! We've got your sushi.
We even got you another old bin from Russia Sushi.
What the hell?!
He wasn't saying, "Bin is borked," after all.
Yeah.
A porcelain bowl!
Dotachin.
Kanji conversion for dummies.
Kaztano...
He must have been kidnapped by those human hunters!
We'll never see him again!
What am I going to do without him?
Who's gonna support me now?!
We all knew how much Kaztano meant to Togusa.
No one can replace him.
Not even us three.
That kinda makes me feel lonely.
If he was being abducted when he sent that mail, it couldn't have been that long ago.
We've got to get him back before they deliver him to their client.
How?
I know!
I saw their car.
Hashim.
Yays!
The ultimate supporting fairy, "Little Brother Character"!
Okay, got it.
We just have to save the foreigner when we find them, right?
Yes.
We don't know where or when the exchange will take place.
But we want to free him as soon as possible.
Okay. A black van, right?
You have the license plate?
Yeah. Got something to write on?
Wait a moment.
Go on.
Thanks, Hashim.
No need.
Can you eat sushi?
Yes.
Bye.
Does it have wasabi?
Yes.
Don't worry. Russian wasabi isn't spicy.
Don't lie to him.
Let's go.
'Kay.
It's a black van. Here's the license plate number.
Be careful.
The perpetrators are just hired goons for some corrupt corporation.
Well, they're like peanuts.
Apparently, they kidnap people who go unnoticed in society and hand them over to their superiors.
I guess humans are used as raw materials for various things.
It's almost like cannibalism.
We haven't been getting much from the "subcontractors" this month.
Right.
We have been careful with the—
Spare me your excuses.
Dismiss the groups that can't supply enough.
But...
Or will you be the "raw material"?
You may leave.
Seiji.
Shinra, you idiot!
Spa~rkling...
Da~ncing...
We frantically searched for the black van that abducted Kaztano.
We were determined to save him.
We tried many things, but we still couldn't find his whereabouts.
A feeling of anxiety encompassed my heart.
Will we never hear that classic phrase from him again?
That nostalgic phrase I heard so many times as a kid.
That very phrase that I never thought I'd hear as an adult.
You need tickets?
I've got tickets!
Kaztano's kind isn't one you see much nowadays.
And Togusa relied on him for the greatest happiness in his life.
Togusa's eternal goddess, Hijiribe Ruri.
A goddess that Togusa worshipped, even though his love was one-sided.
Kaztano was his magician, so to speak, as he never failed to snag Togusa a hard-to-get stage-side seat to his goddess.
We have to save him for Togusa.
Dotachin, what are you talking about?
And who're you talking to?
Well...
I've been thinking...
Why don't we try calling his cellphone?
Maybe we can negotiate with them.
Sushi love.
I like fatty tuna.
Who the hell are you?
Oh my, if it isn't Dotachin.
You know,
I was just passing by and saw some guy sleeping.
So his cellphone rang and I—
What? Where I am?
I'm in front of Taishouken in South Ikebukuro.
Ya know...
Today, Russia Sushi is half off.
Izaya!
Don't ever come back to Ikebukuro!
Whoops, Shizu-chan found me.
See ya.
Izaya!
Wake up!
Hey! Wake up!
Wake up, dammit!
Don't do that.
You'll put him to eternal sleep.
But if we don't hurry, Kaztano will—
Yeah! When he's delivered, he'll be disposed of!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to make his friends tell me where the exchange will take place.
It's almost time for the exchange.
You better watch out. The higher-ups are coming.
Yeah.
I'm Japanese!
You guys should notice your mistake already!
You still keep saying that?
That means you're listed as Japanese in your family register.
Listen, that's the important part.
My family register burned in the air raid.
How old are you, for crying out loud?!
Yeah?
'Sup, it's me.
Oh, Kanazawa?
You awake?
Sorry, I'm coming over there.
Hold on, where was the meeting point?
Dude, I can't believe you.
We are so awesome!
We got it!
Wh-Who the hell are you guys?
We're the Dollars!
Dollar...
Plus "s"!
You better remember it!
I'm sleepy... So sleepy.
Let's go.
We joined the Dollars for a simple reason.
These three were hanging out with me before I noticed.
I have no idea what redeeming quality they saw in me.
Seriously, what a praiseworthy bunch.
One day, I got a text message.
"Do you want to join the Dollars?
There are no rules or restrictions.
You just need to say that you're a part of the Dollars."
A very weird invitation.
Rumors were spreading about how "different" the Dollars were before I got this text message.
At first, I thought it was a prank,
but when I agreed just to see how it'd turn out,
I received a URL and password the next day.
When I logged in,
my nick was displayed on the Dollars' site.
None of the members, including me, have seen the leader before.
The Dollars is comprised of many smaller groups,
and they all form a hierarchic society.
However, the one on the throne is nowhere to be seen.
As long as there's no leader, I don't feel like I'm working under somebody.
But I cannot deny my curiosity about the person that created this organizational structure.
This is between us,
but there's a person that I think could be the leader.
That rude guy who started calling me "Dotachin."
Fatty tuna, yummy.
What you're looking for isn't that way.
Sorry, Selty.
How much do you think this guy will bring in?
Well, some beer money, I'd say.
Guess so.
Is that them?
Probably.
What the fuck?!
Kaztano!
Kaztano! I'll save you now!
You think it's gonna be that easy?
En garde!
Whoa, that's retro!
"En garde"?
Th-The headless one!
Even though we went for some geezer that won't net much money?!
Sorry! We are so sorry!
What the hell?
Kaztano!
Dotachino!
Ah, they're running away!
Don't think you can get away!
Right turn!
Can I go home now?
You better tell us who you were delivering him to.
No, no. Stop. It wouldn't be any fun if people talked without being tortured.
Please pick a book.
We'll torture you in accordance with the plot.
Hey, I don't care what you do, but don't use gasoline in the car like last time, got it?!
Togusano!
Gasoline?!
Let's perform the morning ritual!
I'll talk! I'll talk!
Please! Let me out!
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, eh?
Pretty nice place, actually.
Do they really perform human experiments here?
We doubted it.
At least, that's what the exterior made us think.
But a coin has two sides.
There's a lot of darkness, especially in Ikebukuro.
Anyway, let's go grab something to eat.
Yeah.
Breakfast at Russia Sushi!
Sounds great! Let's go!
All right, it's settled.
Spend as much money as you want.
Thank you, sis.
Bye, Seiji.
Let's go.
Those are the details of the Kaztano incident.
Well, we're happy that our friend is back safe and sound.
Shut up.
You're annoying.
You're pissing me off.
I can't hold my rage any longer.
My body moves on its own.
I don't care what happens to me.
Next time: The Strongest.
But I hate violence!