Where... am I?
This is the infirmary.
Infirmary?
Why are you all still here?
Don't push yourself.
I'm fine, Kanade-chan.
Well, it looks like it was a challenge even for Yurippe.
I'm amazed how you managed to be the leader for all this time.
Even you two?
What are all of you doing here still?
Aren't all the Shadows gone?
There shouldn't be anything in your way now.
Yeah, we know.
Then why?
You're still here.
We still need to take care of you.
M-Me?!
Right...
W-What should I say to that...?
What?
I have a feeling the internal struggle Yuri had has been relieved.
It has, Yuri?
Um, well that's...
Fine then, I'll use my hypnosis to make her sp-
Don't you dare!
How she rejects it so quickly... looks like that's the case.
Huh?  No!  Th-That's not true.
I-I mean, I'm the leader, so if I were relieved so easily,
I'd be a total laughingstock.  You know?
Then I'll use my hypnosis to-
Fine, it's true!  You got a problem with that?!
Ah.  She admitted it.
You're so mean, Kanade-chan.
No, you're just obstinate, Yuri.
Thanks...
But that strangely makes me happy.
What does?
To hear you call me "Yuri."
Why?
Well, it sounds like we're friends, right?
Friends...
You're right.
Which means the preparations won't go to waste.
Yeah.
What preparations?  Is something happening?
There's something we want to do as a last event.
Apparently Kanade's never experienced it.
Huh?  Experienced what?
Where are the others?
They all left.
I see.  That's great.
This is possible thanks to everyone helping out.
It was one heck of a job.
Only God could accomplish such deeds.
But you know, despite what everyone said,
they all enjoyed their lives here.
I realized that.
I think it was all thanks to you.
Yeah?
You know, Takamatsu ended up being obliterated, too.
He was able to come back to his senses, even after becoming an NPC.
Oh, really now?
You don't sound too surprised.
Wasn't it you who said there would be no turning back after you became an NPC?
I guess the program allows one to return to normal depending on the will of the programmer.
What was that song from?
You were humming it back when we were setting the stuff up, too.
What was it...?
I know.
It's the last song Iwasawa-san sang.
"My Song".
Ah, that song.
The one that played on the school's PA system, right?  Of all things...
It's a nice song, isn't it?
Yes!
The gym?
Yeah.
We made it ourselves.
Kanade did the words.
I see.
So Kanade-chan never participated in a graduation ceremony?
I wanted to know if it's fun.
It's not fun.
But she looked like she was enjoying it when she was writing the sign.
Most girls cry, you know.
That's why girls are pathetic.
Well, should we get started?
Now?!
Why do you think you got changed?
Well, I was wondering if I really will be obliterated or not.
And I need to prepare myself a bit, too.
And you're really calling yourself our former leader?
W-What was that?!
Yeah, you don't seem like a leader at all now that everyone's gone.
Oh?  R-Really?
Yeah, something is different.
Huh?  How?
Let's see...
I know.  You seem more feminine.
Am I supposed to be happy about that? Or angry about that?
Now that the battles are over, you've changed back to a pure girl who doesn't even know how to respond to that.
Yurippe's got a bit of a cute side to her.
Yuri's funny.
Okay, let's start this!
Opening statement!
We will now commence the graduation ceremony
for the members of the Afterlife Battlefront who have been fighting after their deaths!
First, the battle anthem!
"Battle anthem"?  What's that?
A song for the Afterlife Battlefront.  Instead of a school anthem.
I don't remember making anyone come up with that!
Kanade came up with it.
You made one?!
Wait, besides, you're not even part of the Battlefront!
What's the big deal?
There, pass the lyrics down!
What's the melody?
All school anthems are similar, right?
I think we'll be in harmony even if we wing it.
Ready?
And sing!
"From the world where the sky is dead,"
"We present to you, our happy-go-lucky selves."
"Before you die, be sure to eat some mapo tofu."
"Ah, mapo tofu."
"Mapo tofu."
What is with these lyrics?!
Somebody should run a check beforehand!  I ended up singing it!
Look, Kanade-chan put some serious thought into it when she wrote it, so you don't have to talk about it like that.
Right?
"Serious thought"?
I see "happy-go-lucky" written right here.
Still, how should I put this...
It's packed with Kanade's feelings.
Where exactly are they, though?
They're from the top, down to the bottom.
I guess you're right.
There you have it, Kanade-chan.
What's next?
Next...
Diploma presentation ceremony!
We have those?
We made some.
Mostly by Kanade, again.
Okay, so where's the headmaster to give them to us?
Me!
Gross...
Hey now, I lost in janken!  You got something to say?!
Why am I always the one stuck with these things?!
It's a perfect role for you.
All right... let's begin!
Diploma presentation ceremony!
First, Tachibana Kanade!
Yes!
Next, Nakamura Yuri!
You look great in that.
Leave me alone.
This is silly.
Next, Naoi Ayato!
Yes!
Praise me.
What the?  You da-
Good work!
Otonashi Yuzuru!
Yes!
Take that off.
Okay.
Hinata Hideki!
Y-Yes!
Oh, geez...
Thanks.
Same here.  You took good care of me.
Representative of the graduating class, your final message!
Ah...
Looking back, there were so many things.
The first person I met at this school was Nakamura Yuri-san.
And the first thing she explained to me was that I was dead.
Also, I learned that everyone here couldn't accept the life
they'd been given and was fighting against God.
I fought alongside them as a member.
However, after regaining the memories I had lost, I was able to accept the life I'd had.
It was a wonderful feeling.
At that point, I wished that everyone could feel that.
They had been fighting all this time.
It was a hard thing to do.
But they were able to help and trust each other.
The Battlefront that formed around Nakamura Yuri-san had become a group of such great people.
People started to accept their lives,
changing the group's strength into courage.
In the end, everyone was able to look ahead and leave this place.
The remaining five will graduate from here today, as well.
Even if I forget the faces of those I spent my time together with,
I will not forget the bonds that have been etched on to my soul.
I'm so glad I was able to spend time with you all.
Thank you so much.
Graduation class speaker, Otonashi Yuzuru!
All, rise!
Sing, "Precious Days."
"We are thankful for all that our teachers have done for us."
"We've stayed on this campus for many years."
"Looking back, they've all been very precious days."
"Now is the time for our paths to part ways."
"So-"
You're a beat late!
What?  It was definitely just you who was going too fast!
No, you were too slow!
We were in harmony, right?
Your attitude is so different with Otonashi!
Ready and-
"So this is farewell."
Closing words!
With this, we will close the Afterlife Battlefront's graduation ceremony.
Graduating class, dismissed!
I don't want to see the girls cry.
I'll be heading out first.
You're the one crying.
Otonashi-san.
If I hadn't met you...
I would never... have been free from my struggle...
But, I'm...
I won't get lost anymore.
Thank you very much!
Yeah.  Get going now.
Thank you very much.
There he went.
So, who's the next one to cry?
No one will.
Kanade-chan.
I'm sorry all we did was fight.
I really wonder why we couldn't have become friends sooner.
I'm really sorry.
I was the oldest girl in the house, so I looked after
my mischievous siblings like I was their parent.
So I could have taught you many things.
You looked very unfamiliar with the rest of this world, so I would've taken extra care of you.
We could have done so many things...
We could have had fun doing so many things...
If...  If only we had more time...
I...  I guess this is goodbye.
Yes.
Be well, Kanade-chan.
I will...
See you.
Yeah.  And thanks, Yuri.  I'm in your debt.
Good work, Leader.
We'll meet again somewhere.
Well, I'd say it's my turn, considering the order here.
No, I can go.
What are you talking about?!
Don't leave before Kanade-chan.
I'll go.
Okay.
Yeah.  I'll go.
Thanks for everything.
Without you, nothing would have started.  We never could have had closure like this.
I'm really grateful.
I was lucky.
If you think about it, I had no reason to be here.
What do you mean?
In the end, my life was a fulfilled one.
I found myself in this world because I had forgotten that fact.
And because I was able to remember, I was able to realize happiness from feeling fulfilled.
So that's how it went.
You really were a special one, then.
It was all a chain of luck that I was able to be of help to everyone.
I see.
Well, enough chit-chat.
I'll get going.
Yeah.
If you happen to see Yui, say hi for me.
Yeah.  I know I saved up my luck, so I'll use everything I've got.
Okay!
See ya, buddy!
So...  How was the graduation ceremony?
Did you enjoy it?
Yes.  Very much.
But it's pretty sad at the end.
But it's the start of a new life.
Everyone's off to their new lives.  Isn't that a good thing?
I suppose.
Hey, why don't we step outside?
I want to feel the wind a little.
You know, Kanade.
Would you... like to stay behind?
I thought of it just now, suddenly.
I mean, there will be people who will come to this world like Hinata and Yuri after having unfulfilled lives, right?
You're right.
They could end up sticking around here like Yuri and the others did.
And continue to suffer and resist the opportunities they've been given here.
You're right.
But if we stayed behind, we could tell them the good part of being here and guide them to graduation.
I may have come here to play that role.
So...
Would you like to stay behind with me?
If you stay with me, I wouldn't be lonely, even in a world like this.
I may have said this before, but...
I want to be with you.
I want to continue to be with you.
Because I...
I just... I love you.  So much.
I love you.
Why won't you say anything?
I don't want to answer.
Why not?
Because I would be obliterated if I say what's on my mind right now.
Why?
Because I came to say "thank you" to you.
What do you mean?
I'm the girl whose life you saved, with your heart.
In my chest right now, your heart is beating.
My only regret in life was how I couldn't say
"thank you" to the person who gave time back to me.
That's what I wanted to say...  That was the only thing that kept me from fulfillment and made me come to this world.
You mean...
But how do you know it was me?
I've realized it since the time I first stabbed you.
You have no heart.
But that's not enough to...
The reason why you were able to regain your memory is because you had that dream while lying on my chest.
You were listening to your own heartbeat.
That's...
Yuzuru.  Please.
Can you say those words... just once more?
I-I can't...
If I did... you'd be obliterated!
Yuzuru!  Please!
Saying it again...  I can't!
Yuzuru!
Please let me believe what you believe in, too.
Let me believe that life is wonderful.
Yuzuru.
Kanade.
I love you.
Let's always be together.
Yes...  Thank you, Yuzuru.
We'll always... always be together!
Yes... thank you!
I love you.
Kanade.
Yes.  Thank you so much.
Kanade...
Thank you for loving me.
Don't obliterate on me.
Kanade...
Kanade!
Thank you... so very much... for giving me life.
KANADE!!!