Why is the new song a ballad?
It shouldn't be?
It's not fit for diversion.
Hey...
What's this "diversion" about?
Were you not listening during Tornado?
She's a part of the school rock band that gains the students' approval.
We don't hurt them, but at times we make use of them, and should they get in our way,
we have to get them out of the area.
At times like that, she and her girls act as a diversion.
What lowbrow NPCs.
More like her band has that much skill and charisma.
So?
It's a no-go?
A ballad is a bit...
If they listen so quietly and attentively, we couldn't do anything wild.
I see.  Then I guess I'll need to trash it.
On a different note, the next announcement is for everyone.
Otonashi-kun.
Close the curtain, will you?
The next operation will focus on retribution: Operation Tenshi Domain Infiltration.
We'll be rolling out in 3 days.
So we're going with that strategy?
Oh yeah.
However, last time—
This time, he will be coming with us.
Greetings.
He just popped out from behind the chair?!
He has glasses, too.
Yurippe, what kinda joke is this?
What good is that shrimp gonna do us?
Come now, don't be like that.
Fine!  In that case!
I'll test him!
I bet you don't have any friends, huh?
3.1415926535...
Stop!  Stop it!!
What?!  Pi?!
He has glasses, too.
Please stop!  He's a moron!
Exactly.  Our weakness is that we're all morons.
That's not something a leader should say.
During the last operation, we brought our lack of intelligence to the forefront.
However!
This time, we have him, the one called a prodigy hacker.
He will be added to our team, alias Takeyama-kun.
We will have him perform thorough research regarding the domain.
You mean that wasn't his real name?
Call me Christ.
See there?  You ruined his cool alias.
Way to go, Yurippe.
So, what's this "Tenshi Domain"?
It's where Tenshi lives.
"Where Tenshi lives"?
W-What could it be like?
Wait.  A hacker is necessary for a place like that?
A computer is what controls the core of her hideout.
So it's all mechanical?
There should be a lead to God in there somewhere.
This is an incredible operation!
Since it's our second attempt, Tenshi is likely to be on higher alert.
We'll need a big show out of GDM.
You got it.
Good chance and luck!
Okay.  Looking good.
Hey, aren't I getting way too used to this?
Well, in actuality, they aren't as bad as I first thought they were.
So this is part of the grand diversion.
Oh, sorry.  Did I surprise you?
Oh, it's you.
You know me?
Yeah!
The upperclassman who always walks around with a big axe said something like,
"Watch out for him, he only brings bad luck."
That bastard.
Hey, is it really okay to take up the whole gym like that?
It's not all right at all!  Completely unheard-of before.
It's not a live where we're acting as a guerilla force, but a regular announced live concert, too.
The teachers won't overlook this, so who knows what kind of interference might happen.
But for this mission, I've been told that we need to gather people up even if it means going this far.
Girls Dead Monster, eh?
By the way, you're...
I'm Yui!
I'm only a flunky in the Diversion Division.
But I'm perfectly fine with that!  I mean, I get to help GDM!
You know!  Girls Dead Monster, GDM for short, is really amazing!
They can play that well with only girls.
And above all, the presence that Iwasawa-san, the vocalist and lead guitarist, holds...!
She even writes the lyrics and composes the music!
My favorite is "Crow Song."
The tempo of the chorus section is totally awesome!
The lyrics, too.  They're talking about herself.
Another great high-tempo song is "Alchemy."  "Alchemy" is—
I'm not done talking yet!
"Alchemy" is—
You really have time to waste?
Go get working for your favorite GDM, why don't you?!
Ah, that's right!
'Scuse me, then!
Whoops...
Sorry, I'll restring it right away.
Okay, we'll take five.
That was some heat in there.
I can understand why the NPCs get all excited over you guys.
I found myself tuning in.
Thank you.
I heard you don't have any memories, right?
Yeah.
Lucky you.
Are your memories... well...
Have you heard anyone else's yet?
Yeah, Yuri's.
Oh, Yuri's?
She has the worst ones.
Mine aren't as bad as her's.
"Not as"?
It's really nothing special.
I couldn't sing the song I like...
That's all.
My parents were always fighting.
I didn't even have my own room.
I would shrink myself into a small ball in the corner of the room and cover my ears.
All I could do was to close myself into a protective shell.
There wasn't anywhere I could relax.
That's when I came across the band called Sad Machine.
The vocalist was also from an unfortunate family.
During the hard times, he would plug his ears with headphones and escape into the world of music.
I started doing the same.
I felt like everything was being blasted away.
Like the vocalist was screaming for me.  That he was singing for me.
I began to believe that those who spoke rationally were wrong, and those crying out were right.
It made me realize that we lonely people were the ones who were truly human-like.
That music screamed, tore apart, and destroyed the unfairness that existed.
It... saved me.
I met this thing on a rainy day by a trash bin.
So I started singing.
I thought I had nothing left in life, but I had found song.
Are you serious?
You could go anywhere with your grades.
Hey.
I don't want to rely on my parents anymore.
I worked part-time to make money and went from one audition to another.
I was determined that after graduating, I would leave the house, go to Tokyo,
and make a living out of music.
I was determined to...
What?
Am I tired?
I can't play guitar like this...
I should skip playing on the street tonight and get some rest...
When I awoke, I had lost my power over words.
I had anepia... due to a cerebral infarction as a result of head trauma.
The cause... was a blow during one of my parents' fights.
I cursed my fate.
I had nowhere I could escape to.
My life ended there.
Iwasawa!
Ah, Hisako.  Okay!
We're all tired of waiting.
Hey, amnesia boy.
Keep it.
Her eyes...
Those eyes were cursing life.
She had a ghastly time, too.
It isn't that people are afraid of turning into water fleas.
People here are all trying to fight against God.
They're all trying to fight...
against their unfair lives.
Why don't you let it slip by, Prez?!
He's right!  GDM's live concerts are our only entertainment here!
Don't take that fun away from us!
Yeah!  Yeah!
Right?
Huh?
Where did she go?
So I'm the bad guy?
Listen up.  This time, we'll be going in with a minimal number of people.
Operation starts at 1900 today.
Operation, start!
The crowd's small.
You get a box seat.
It's time!
All right.
Let's rock the roof off!
Clear!
Good.  We made it in fine.
We're in Tenshi's Domain.
Close the door already!
Takeyama-kun, you take care of the computer.
Call me Christ.
Hey, isn't this...
This is just scavenging a girl's room!  It's a crime!
What do you think you're doing?
This is the girls' dormitory!  Turn the lights out!
You said it was computer-controlled, didn't you?!
It's just one laptop!
Password...
Nobody could guess it last time.
I see.  So this is where I get to show my skills.
Starting analysis.
Oh?  Guess he's somewhat useful, after all.
Hey, come on...  You're violating someone's privacy!
Shut your mouth.  If you dare keep talking, I'll slice your throat open!
Screw you all!  I was just starting to think better of you guys!
Why?  There should be more coming...
"Alchemy"?!  So early in the concert...
Go!
It's "Alchemy"!
Hey, you guys!
What do you think you're doing?!
Return to the dorms at once!
Forget it!  We wanna hear this!
Yeah!  You guys get out of here!
Yeah!  Yeah!
She's here...
Dear fans, rock out even harder!
No, it's not they themselves...
It's our skill that incites them!
Tenshi has arrived.
Roger.
Takeyama-kun?
I'm running the program that cracks passwords right now.
It'll be finished in no time.
Also, please call me Christ.
We're in.
Well done, Takeyama-kun!
Copy all the data!
That would take too much time.
It would take at least an hour to do that.
Also, please call me Ch—
Why not take the hard disk back?
She'll know we were here.
Then what should we do?
Just show us some critical-looking data, Takeyama-kun!
It's Christ.
Student roster?
NPCs...  No, we're in the list, too.
It's only a roster, isn't it?!
There's no suspicious data!  This really is just a crime!
Shut up!
The Diversion Division has been detained.
Tenshi will be returning.
I guess this is it.
Nothing gained this time, either.
We'll retreat.
Damn you!  This is bullshit!
Stop this!
They're doing this for us!
Let go of them!
Their music is our life!  Please!
We were only letting it slide until now!
Don't be so full of yourselves!
We're confiscating all the instruments.
You won't be using these, not even in the school festival!
You don't mind if this is thrown away, do you?
Don't touch that...
Don't...
Don't touch that!
Stop it!
Wait!
Hand it over.
A new song?
Takeyama-kun!
I'm on it.  And please just call me Christ!
That's my life.
To keep singing on like this.
That's the meaning behind my life.
Just like how I was saved, I will save others the same way.
I finally... finally found it.
Iwasawa?
Summarize the findings for us, Yurippe.
Tenshi was creating her skills on her own.
And irritatingly enough, it was done exactly the same way as how we make weapons.
What do you mean by that?
I don't have an exact answer, yet.  I can't say.
How come?  Don't give us the cold shoulder like that, Yurippe.
It means there's a reason why she must use the same methods that we do.
The logical conclusion from that is we're in the worst possible setup.
There is no God.
Why doesn't she receive her skills from God if she's an angel?
Why does she have to make them herself?
Then, here's the other issue we have.
Where has Iwasawa-san gone to?
Wasn't she obliterated by Tenshi?
In the middle of the concert?
Then what do you say happened?
Who could have done this to Iwasawa-san...
No one did.
She accepted it.
That's all there is to it.
The condition for being obliterated is obeying Tenshi and acting out a proper school life.
I guess that isn't the only way it happens.
Play ball!
I'm sure to add strength to your team.
It's baseball.
Don't stop dancing!
I challenge you, kid.
She'll be filling in for Iwasawa?
I'll form the best team.
It really is a total mystery what you were doing until you died!
I'm Yui-nyan!
Who are we fighting against...?
I'd say so, also.
Your team has not enrolled in the event.
will face a penalty game more painful than death.
Are you shivering?
That... would be the best feeling ever...