Hello, gentlemen.
I have come to take your lives.
Hello, boy.
Your partner sure is unlucky, Jet.
Well, he wasn't all that lucky
to begin with.
This case is especially bad.
It would be better
to not get involved in this.
I don't care. Just answer me. Now.
I'm telling you this for your own sake,
and if you get too involved in this,
I'm gonna get in trouble, too.
You know, Bob...
you're the only person
I can rely on right now.
I'll make sure
it won't be bad for you. So...
Don't you say that every time?
Really... you always have been a guy
that likes to get into trouble.
All right, this is only a rumor, but...
Have you heard the name Mad Pierrot?
There he is... the rumored mummy.
So, I heard you got beaten up
by some weird guy?
I recall you sleeping like this
once before.
You really haven't shown any improvement.
Oh, well,
it doesn't have anything to do with me.
Don't you end up in situations
like that because you never behave?
Well, I have nothing to do with it.
So, since I have nothing to do with it,
if you'll excuse me...
Take care.
The victim was a high-ranking guy
from the ISSP.
He was the seventh victim.
What did you say?
Can't blame you. This is top secret.
Apparently, those higher-ups don't want
the world to find out about this.
Why?
Your partner is in deep trouble.
The guy is a perfect killing machine.
They say that nobody who has seen his face
has made it out alive.
Even those lucky enough to escape
will be tracked to the ends of the world.
And they always wind up dead.
They say he appears with a smile
and he leaves with a smile.
Yeah, he is the mysterious assassin
known as Mad Pierrot.
Tongpu.
Faye-Faye!
Puff, puff! Faye-Faye!
Hey, you, can you stop saying my name
twice like that?
Faye-Faye, some weird mail came-came.
Hey, hey, hey!
And I would've been done
if I had a little more time.
I can't read it.
"Hello, boy.
I'll invite you to a wonderful party..."
Wait, this is...
Listen, keep the fact that this mail came
a secret from Spike.
Secret?
Why? Why a secret?
If we don't, that idiot--
Will run out to meet him?
It's secret, secret mail.
Space Land?
Pretty considerate of him
to hold the party there.
You're gonna go like that?
Well, it would be perfect
if it was a masquerade.
Maybe this one
really will be the end of me.
Just kidding.
Would you come rescue me if I said that?
Idiot.
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Hey.
Oh, it's you, Ed. Where's Spike?
He went somewhere.
What?
Not that this is anything new. That idiot.
Idiot, idiot?
Ed, I have a favor to ask.
What, what?
Hello! Welcome!
Yo.
Let's party!
You can't enter here.
It's dangerous in here.
Let's play outside.
Shut up.
It's dangerous in here.
Let's play outside.
Hi!
All right, Ed.
First enter the ISSP's main computer
and look for section 13.
Aye, aye.
That's the section
that doesn't exist to the general public.
It's a pretty tall order. Can you do it?
Yup.
Hello.
Found it.
After you open it,
find the file with the code name Tongpu.
Yup.
Peekaboo!
ISSP Assassination Ability,
Improvement Experiment.
Experiment sample chart number 46.
Code name Tongpu.
Confirmed a strong regression
of the mind during the experiment.
Experiment was canceled.
Sample to be permanently kept
in a quarantine facility.
In the beginning, he escaped
from the facilities to seek revenge.
But now he seems to be enjoying
the actual act of killing.
His mind must be continuing to regress.
So, he's like a child
with superhuman fighting abilities.
Really.
There is nothing as pure and cruel
as children.
It's showtime!
That was unnecessary.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
That hurts.
It hurts!
Hurts!
Mommy, it hurts!
Mommy!
It hurts! Mommy!
Spike. All right,
we figured out what he is. He's--
No. I don't need it anymore.
It all ended just now.
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
I knew there was something fishy
going on lately.
So, that's what it was.
What are you guys talking about?
You really can't judge people
by their looks.
Honestly disgusting.
Hey, what are you guys talking about?
I never thought
it would be a teenage girl.
It makes me despise him.
Who are you talking about?
Next episode: "Boogie Woogie Feng Shui."
I didn't do anything.