So that's the plan!
All right.
Okay.
Here we go...
Oh, Madame Towa! Is it really vous, Madame Towa?
I must have worried you, Siamour.
Oh, vous have not only returned safe,
but as such a belle dame!
And what's more,
seeing vous have become a Princess Precure is nothing short of le miracle!
It seems I must ponder deeply...
upon the meaning of this miracle...
and how I shall atone.
Bonjou—oooah!
You okay, Haruharu?
Oh, Towa! Do you want to go to town?
T-Town?
Yeah!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
What is the meaning of this?
Getting some fresh air!
Fresh air?
You've been holed up in your room ever since you arrived, right?
So today...
we're gonna make sure you have loads of fun!
Fun? But I...
We're calling it...
"The All-Smiles Dreamy Shore Tour"!
Let's go!
W-Wait!
Together Forever!
The Four of Us Are Princess Precures!
Ta-dah!
What do you think of this elegant princess ensemble?
It's cuteness in full bloom!
You're the best, Kirara!
Aren't I?
That settles that.
We'll take this.
All right!
What is this?
It's our present to you!
Yeah!
Present?
You can't wear that old dress out on the town, can you?
You'll need to blend in with our world for a while.
Thank you...
Hey, we're just getting started!
But wait—
I buy flower seeds here all the time!
They hold plenty of exhibits here, so I stop by every week.
It was only recently that I first used one of these.
What is this?
It's a doughnut!
Yummy!
Hey, Perf, you've got some stuck on your cheek!
Aroma, you've got some too!
As do you, Haruka.
H-How embarrassing...
Hey, you smiled!
Thank goodness!
I was worried you weren't having fun!
You should smile when you're enjoying yourself.
Yeah! Don't hold back on our account.
I mustn't.
Towa?
Until I save Hope Kingdom...
I cannot afford myself the luxury of "fun."
But...
My transformation into Cure Scarlet was a miracle granted by the heavens so that I may redeem myself.
I'm different from you girls!
You're not different! We're all—
Just leave me be!
I mustn't be with you any longer...
Hey, wait!
Towa...
From here on out, I must live on
my own without relying on others.
What is that rucku—
Hey, lady, would ya move it?!
What're you doing? Don't you know how traffic rules work?!
Huh?
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
These conventions are complex indeed...
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
Let's learn
the rules of
the road!
Easy to Understand Traffic Rules
I must be cautious among the castle grounds.
But first, I must remain calm and procure lodging.
Welcome! We have plenty of splendid houses on display!
Dreamy Shore Model House Exhibition
Ah!
Pardon.
Yes?
Do you have a castle?
Huh? A castle?!
I'm in no position to demand luxury...
so a mere three maids will do!
So... what's your budget?
Budget?
Come to think of it, I came to
this world without my wealth.
Thanks for shopping!
Welcome! What would you like, dear?
Money.
Huh?!
Uh, so you'd like to work here?
I can receive money if I work, correct?
How old are you again, dear?
Catch me if you can!
Wait up!
So, children can't even work?
I never thought I could be so powerless...
How can I save Hope Kingdom if I can't even survive on my own?
How pitiful...
Child...
It's her again!
If you'd like, could you help me with something?
Huh?
Curse you...
Twilight!
Dyspear, where are you going?
For now, I will return to the Forest of Despair.
I must heal my body.
For me?
Fill it with human despair.
It shall be my energy.
I see.
Lock, I leave matters to you.
Understood.
But Lady Dyspear, I—
Lady Dyspear...
So, fill it with despair, huh?
Pineapple Ponytail!
How scrumptious...
Good to hear.
You can have mine too, if you'd like.
Sure...
Thanks for tagging along.
Huh?
I wanted to try both, but it's a bit much for me alone.
I only wanted half of each.
I should be the one to thank you.
I feel my strength has returned.
I knew it!
You are cuter when you smile.
T-That won't do.
Why is everyone in this world so kind?
I didn't think Princess Towa was putting so much pressure on herself.
We tried to cheer her up, but I guess it backfired.
It's her sense of responsibility that
drives her to bear her burden alone.
Should we leave her alone until she cools off?
We can't leave her.
Towa was in despair this whole time.
She hasn't been able to laugh with friends, have fun, or eat good food ever since!
Leaving her alone at a time like this is something I just can't do!
Haruka!
I figured she'd say that.
So, which human's gonna give me the most despair?
Isn't she...
That was quite delicious.
Indeed...
We can't do anything on an empty stomach, correct?
Huh? I suppose...
But filling it with a meal gives us strength once again.
Just like it did for you.
So it is with the heart.
We can't do anything on an empty heart.
The heart?
Yes. And when the heart is filled with warmth, it gains the strength to act once more.
Warmth, you say?
Twilight.
Look who's all gussied up.
Lock!
A friend of yours?
Sure am! We go way back, 'kay?
As for you...
Seems you've got a strong dream, 'kay?
Please, run!
Show me your dream, 'kay?
I want to build a bright future for our youth!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
It's my fault... again!
Go ahead and transform.
Don't leave me hangin', 'kay?
I will save her!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
Oh, snazzy!
Dyspairvil!
Fireworks!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
Towa!
Wait, girls!
Isn't that a Dyspairvil?
You're right!
It's a Dyspairvil!
Towa must be over there!
Fireworks!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Spark!
Dyspair...
Viiil!
Not bad.
I see how you chased off Lady Dyspear, 'kay?
As only the Princess of Despair could!
I am not—
That human wouldn't have had her
dream sealed if she'd never met you.
Everyone around you ends up miserable...
First Hope Kingdom, then Prince Kanata...
I think this world's up next.
You're a fool. You would've saved yourself the hurt if you'd just stayed as Twilight.
Now let's kick things up a notch.
Viiiiil...
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairviiiiiil!
Its strength suddenly increased!
Lock, when did you get such power?!
Wouldn't you like to know?
If you make everyone miserable,
then why bother sticking around?
Dyspairvil!
Bye bye, Princess of Despair.
Are you okay, Scarlet?
Flora...
Dyspairvil...
Oh no you don't!
Don't forget about us!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Tch, the gang's all here.
Mrs. Mochizuki!
Why?
A friend of yours?
Poor lady. She wouldn't be in
there if it weren't for Twilight.
Everyone around her just ends up miserable.
That's not true!
You girls love raining on my parade, huh?
Flora!
Smile, Scarlet!
Huh?
Happiness, joy...
hopes, dreams, and all those other warm, fuzzy feelings...
are best shared together!
So let's share them until we can laugh off anything they say!
And then we can grow strong,
okay?
Warmth...
It truly is filling me with strength.
Mermaid!
Twinkle!
And Flora!
I apologize for everything I've done!
I know an apology now could never erase my crimes,
but still!
I want to save her and everyone else Dyspear has made suffer!
So I beg of you,
please, lend me your strength!
Sure!
With that out of the way...
Let's do this together!
Right!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
'Kay, I'm ticked off! Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Not happenin'!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Dys...
Scarlet!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Burning!
Adieu.
I'll call it a day, 'kay?
Open!
The door to your dream!
My apologies for getting you involved.
But I'm glad we could save you!
'Kay, it's gettin' fun now.
I think it's about time...
for me to get serious, 'kay?
We're getting called by the principal!
My apologies... It's all because you girls had to cover for me.
Don't worry, we figured they'd find out eventually.
But who is the principal?
Even I've never seen her in person.
Wait, not even you?!
This is sounding worse by the second...
Pardon us.
Welcome.
Sorry for the wait.
Aren't you...
Mrs. Mochizuki Yume?!
Wh-Why are you here?
Oh my.
It's been a while. I am the principal of Noble Academy.
Wha?!
So you're the one I've been told about.
Yes...
Quite the curious twist of fate, Towa.
Hearing about you gave me an idea...
Would you like to become a student here at Noble Academy?
How about it?
Towa!
Let's go to school together!
Yeah, we'd all be together!
I'm sure it'll be tons of fun.
Girls...
Certainly!
I'll find plenty of warmth here!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Towa, your uniform?
My maid dresses me.
It's time for lunch.
But where is the waiter?
Geez, you can't do anything on your own!
Oh, is that a challenge?
Things are getting tense between those two!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Forced Smile?
My Roommate's a Princess!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Yamanashi Prefecture - Mako (Age 7)
Aichi Prefecture - Akane (Age 5)