You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
Killed?!
Impossible...
Why would they kill the priest?
It defies belief.
This cannot be allowed!
Why did you not tell Tokiomi?
Tell him what?
How I pity your father...
He died believing his son to be a man of God.
No...
Might that perhaps have been his salvation?
Does your father's death leave you indifferent?
He was killed, after all.
You might look a little sad.
Yes... It bothers me to no end.
Does it, now?
Is that because you were unable to kill him yourself?
Saber...
Irisviel, how are you feeling?
It appears I've made you worry.
I'm sorry...
No, as long as you truly are all right, that's fine.
But...
It's okay...
This presence is Maiya.
From Tohsaka?
Yes.
Tohsaka Tokiomi requests an alliance.
An alliance? Now?
Tohsaka is surely uneasy at the thought
of dealing with Rider and Berserker.
So he invited us to meet, assuming we are the most likely to favor a collaboration.
Meaning that he believes we are the weakest of the lot.
Tohsaka said he wishes to meet tonight, at the Fuyuki City church.
From the start, Tohsaka Tokiomi has made elaborate preparations for this Grail War.
Furthermore, it's also likely that he controlled Assassin's Master, Kotomine Kirei.
If Tohsaka holds some power over Kotomine Kirei,
then we cannot ignore this offer.
That's right.
Kotomine Kirei...
Keep this in mind, Saber.
If there is anyone who can defeat Kiritsugu to win the Holy Grail War,
it is Kotomine Kirei.
We shall accept.
Father?
Father!
Rin.
Your father would like to speak with you.
As you grow up, try to keep the Church in your debt.
Beyond that, I leave the rest up to your judgment.
You'll be fine on your own.
One day, the Holy Grail will appear.
It is the responsibility of the Tohsakas to attain it.
Above all,
if you wish to be a magus, that is the path you must follow.
Rin. Take this.
Well, I'll be going then.
You know what to do now, right?
Yes.
Goodbye, Father.
First, allow me to thank you for coming at my behest.
Let me introduce you.
This is Kotomine Kirei, my student.
While we were once competitors for the Grail,
all that is now in the past.
He has lost his Servant,
and has yielded his rights as a Master.
The Grail War is heading toward its conclusion.
The ones remaining are,
as anticipated, the Masters of the three houses,
along with one outsider.
Now, how would you appraise this war?
The Grail must not be allowed to fall into outside hands.
We two should at least be able to agree on that much.
Any alliance is out of the question.
However, if you wish to discuss the order in which we approach our enemies,
we may be able to come to some agreement.
Elaborate.
We can settle things with the Tohsakas after we have defeated the other Masters.
We are prepared to agree to such a proposal.
So a temporary, conditional ceasefire?
A fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
First, that you share any information you have concerning Rider and his Master.
Very well.
Our second request is to remove
Kotomine Kirei from the Holy Grail War.
Would you explain your reasons?
There is bad blood between
the Einzberns and the Executor.
If the Tohsakas continue to protect him,
we will find ourselves unable to trust you regardless of circumstances.
What does she refer to?
Kirei.
Well?
How do you like Kiritsugu's present?
It's more like a horse than a car.
It seems to suit me better.
Then, I shall go ahead,
and ensure that the route is safe.
Let us go as well.
M-Madam..
What's wrong?
Go ahead, Maiya.
But...
Tohsaka will realize something is amiss...
This isn't unexpected...
It was inevitable.
Honestly, the fact that I've been able to function as a human for this long is a miracle.
I was a homunculus created for the Holy Grail War.
You know that, right?
Yes.
Grandfather Acht gave the vessel an instinct for self-preservation
so that it would avoid all danger and
safeguard the Grail to its completion.
He disguised the vessel, and called it Irisviel.
That is who I am.
But how is that...
Then you are...
Very soon,
I will return to being as I was.
Next time,
I won't even be able to talk to you like this.
That's why Kiritsugu gave me Saber's scabbard.
Avalon..
Are you familiar with what it does?
Halts aging, alongside an infinite healing power.
That's what I've been told.
Its effects are what has stopped the shell that is me from collapsing.
Of course, when Saber isn't nearby,
it does not work as well.
Why tell me this?
Hisau Maiya...
You would never pity me.
You'd accept me.
That's why.
Madam, I...
I have always thought of you as a more distant figure.
That's not true...
Do you understand?
Yes.
Even at the cost of my own life,
Irisviel,
I will see you to the end.
So please,
die for Emiya Kiritsugu.
To make his dream a reality.
Thank you.
I would have preferred to have known
of your relationship with the Einzberns.
Unfortunately, I have no choice.
You must withdraw from the Grail War,
Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Who are you?
Will I leave this place,
never even knowing that?
Still thinking, even now?
Could you truly be so slow, Kirei?
The Grail beckons you still...
...and you still long to fight.
As long as I can remember,
I have spent my life in search of a single thing.
I've invested all my time into it. Endured great pain.
But all of that has come to naught.
And yet, I want the answer now,
more than I ever did before.
All that self-examination,
so why do you hesitate?
I have a premonition...
That when I've learned all the answers,
I shall destroy myself.
I understand. Very well.
Surely, that was quite an exciting revelation.
We've learned the location of the Einzberns' hideout.
What, Kirei? You honestly amaze me...
All this time, were you not planning to continue?
I did hesitate.
I was prepared to stop.
But in the end, it is as you say, King of Heroes.
I know no other way than to keep asking the question.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
JN424.
The Gospel of John.
God is spirit,
and those who worship him must worship in spirit and in truth.
However, Kirei...
A very serious problem remains.
If you choose to participate in the Grail War,
Tohsaka Tokiomi will become your enemy.
In other words, you are standing unprepared
in the same room as an enemy Servant.
Is this not a dire situation?
No.
I'm prepared to beg for my life.
Gilgamesh...
Let me tell you the truth behind the Holy Grail War.
What?
The ritual here in Fuyuki is an attempt to open a passage to Akasha
through the sacrifice of seven Heroic Spirits' souls.
By killing all seven Servants,
one may activate the Great Grail.
Yes, all seven.
You understand?
That's the reason my master has worked so hard
to avoid using his Command Seals.
Because when all the battles end, he requires it to force his own Servant to commit suicide.
Then the loyalty Tokiomi has shown me was all a lie, you claim?
Put another way, my master is a magus to the very end.
He may worship a Heroic Spirit,
but he harbors no illusions about his idols.
Tokiomi...
Finally, you have proven your worth.
That boring little man will be able to entertain me at last.
Now then, what will you do, King of Heroes?
Will you remain loyal to my master and ask me my true intent?
Indeed, I hardly know...
Despite his disloyalty,
Tokiomi still supplies me with prana.
Were I to abandon my Master, it would hinder my ability to remain materialized...
Oh... Come to think of it,
there is one with a Command Seal, but no partner.
One searching for a Servant unbound by contract.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
But is that man worthy of being a Master in the eyes of the King of Heroes...
He will suffice.
He is, perhaps, a bit stiff,
but he has great potential for growth.
He may yet prove a fine source of entertainment for me.
I've been waiting, Kirei.
I came to have a word before departing Fuyuki.
I'm still proud to have had you as my student.
I hope you will maintain good relations with the Tohsakas, as your father did...
What do you say?
Your words honor me.
Once this Grail War has ended,
I'd like for you to help train Rin, Kirei.
It's simple, but in essence, it's a will.
I thought it wise to prepare for the worst.
It leaves the Tohsaka family wealth to Rin,
and names you as her guardian until she comes of age.
Leave it to me.
I shall do all I can to look after your daughter.
Thank you,
Kirei.
What is this?
It's for you.
A gift from me.
Open it.
An Azoth dagger.
It symbolizes your mastery of the Tohsaka family magics,
and marks the end of your apprenticeship.
You are far too kind to me, sir.
I cannot begin to express my gratitude,
my master.
It is I who must thank you,
Kotomine Kirei.
Now I can prepare for the final battle.
Look at the time.
I'm sorry to have kept you.
I hope you will make it in time for your flight...
No.
You needn't worry,
my master.
I never bought a ticket.
Master...
You are like my father.
You never did understand me until the very end.
Such a boring ending.
Look at that.
Look at that idiotic face.
He did have a dematerialized Servant at hand.
It was hardly illogical for him to lower his guard.
You've already learned to jest.
You are a quick learner.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel a little better about not having had the chance to kill your father?
You really have no qualms,
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh?
Not so long as you continue to amuse me.
Once things change, Kirei...
Well, you ought to question your own resolve.
My will creates your body,
and your sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call
and obey my will and reason...
I hereby swear.
Your offering will be my flesh,
Kotomine Kirei.
My new Master.
Now, Kirei.
Let us begin.
Put an end to this farce,
howsoever you see fit.
As a reward, I shall hand you the Grail.
Very well,
King of Heroes.
May you have your fill of amusement.
Until I find the answer I seek,
I shall gladly play the fool.
Episode 17
The Eighth Contract
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
Kerry, what do you want to be when you grow up?
Don't go to that mansion.
What is this?
Decide the rest for yourself.
It's still too early for you.
Someday, you'll have the power to change the world.
Next Time:
Distant Memories