The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Well then, good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
I'll be holding on to this as a member of the Dollars.
I heard you're acting all conceited even though Harima Mika went missing.
How the hell can one kill her?
You heard about it, right?
There's been another slashing incident in Ikebukuro.
I'll just have to start a war that only I can fight in.
Ain't that right?
I've come to my senses!
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Welcome, welcome!
Russia Sushi!
Very tasty!
Cheap, too!
Eat sushi!
The Slasher?
Again?
How many victims is that so far?
This is the scene of the slashing crime that happened last night.
A huge meeting took place abruptly in the
downtown area of Ikebukuro six months ago.
It's actually around this time that the Slasher began to appear.
Also, a certain 'Headless Rider' seems to be a popular topic of discussion among the youth in Ikebukuro.
America has already come in contact with the Headless Rider, and-
"The Slasher"?
The Headless Rider.
So scary!
Something is born in the city every day, and at the same time, something also disappears.
Even then, nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's her daily life.
Suddenly and Precipitately
Our love is anything but real.
Even so, it's more powerful than real love.
I'm in love with the scar on your neck.
And through that scar, it leads to true love.
I'm in love with you.
I'll love everything about you with all my might.
I get jealous every time I see them.
Then don't look at them.
If there's a pretty girl, I look at her!
Then I proceed to talk to her!
Isn't that the fate that's carved into the DNA of all existing males?
Don't group me in with them.
But rest at ease.
My body belongs to everyone, but my heart belongs to you only, Anri.
Huh?
I always wonder,
"Why is Anri so sexually attractive?"
What?
The first part...
The "sexually" was uncalled for, Masaomi!
Gotcha.
So putting that part aside, you do acknowledge her attractiveness.
Huh?
Well, so...
Oh? So you're going to say that she's not attractive?
S-She is!
She is, but-
Oh, okay. So you do acknowledge the fact that she's cute.
However, I also acknowledge her sexual attractiveness.
Which means, in a sense, I understand her and love her more than you do.
That means... I win!
What's with that self-centered decision?!
You lose!
After the Dollars!!
The Slasher!!
There was a little incident six months ago.
Everyone was talking about it in both the city and at school for a while.
However, it has nothing to do with her.
In fact, she's hardly interested.
You okay?
Y-Yeah. Thanks.
Nothing happens. Nothing changes.
That's her daily life.
Man, I'm so glad I had a lot of points racked up!
Hurry up.
What are you going to do with that poster, Yumacchi?
She must be in a hurry.
Don't you think she's been riding
around pretty forthrightly these days?
I suppose...
I wish beings like that could be a bit more secretive.
It'd be just right if we were the only ones who knew about it, sort of like a certain wealthy girl's secret.
You're talking about Nogizaka Haruka, aren't you.
Jesus Christ...
Guys, don't be like that.
She probably has her own reasons.
Hey, look!
The Headless Rider!
This is how Celty Sturluson's day usually goes.
It's something she was used to.
People who are dragged into the unordinary cause a panic.
And that's when she calmly escapes.
That was how Celty Sturluson did things.
However...
I often think about how people like us always tend to be the weak foils in fiction that star people like you.
Whenever the psychic protagonist appeared, we'd always be lying in a puddle of blood,
just to emphasize the strength of the opponent.
That's fine.
That just goes to show how powerful people think we are.
It's staged, so there's not much we can do.
But I've always wanted to say one thing.
If a monster or an evil psychic or an android or a ninja really appears...
Then there's one... just one thing...
that I'd like to say.
Don't underestimate the Traffic Police Force, monster.
I'll say it once more.
A mere monster shouldn't underestimate the TPF.
Celty!
Welcome ba-
What's wrong?
What happened?
It's the greatest honor for you to embrace me like this.
Maybe 'honor' isn't the best term here...
Hey...
You're trembling.
Seriously, what happened?
Celty?
I-I-It was scary.
Frightening, Shinra.
C-Cops these days are like monsters!
Cops?
About a dozen police motorcycles and police cars kept chasing me as if they were part of one organism...
Oh yeah, I heard a famous motor officer was
employed from outside the city in order to oppose you.
I think his name was Kuzuhara Kinnosuke.
A problem officer who chases his opponents too far and even causes them to get into accidents occasionally.
He...
He was really scary.
I was bloated with pride.
I'll live frugally from now on, so please forgive me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Just who are you apologizing to?
It's not like you to be so faint-hearted.
You only have to act frail like that in bed-
Could your timing be any worse to say something embarrassing like that?
Yes... that's more like it.
W-Well, sorry to ask you this when you're still in shock,
but could you pick someone up for me?
No, it's not work.
Yeah... he came home.
My dad, that is.
Geez... he could have taken a cab or something.
He used to always mess with me, but...
Hey, hey, hey!
Say something!
You're all white.
Too white.
Could that be...
What's with this old man?
Don't you think he looks pretty cool, Horoda-san?
Gentlemen, the air in Tokyo is very filthy.
Wouldn't you agree?
What?
Well, it looks like that dirty face of yours is protectively colored.
Within this filthy air.
I think this guy's fucked in the head.
Well, who cares?
Seems like it's time to teach you
youngsters the power of an adult.
I'm sure you all think that because you're protected by the Juvenile Law, you can kill people as you please.
Just remember.
When you're trying to kill someone,
you must be prepared to be killed by them as well-
You really are crazy, aren't you, old man.
I'm past twenty already!
Hang on a second.
This really hurts, and I can't run because you're stepping on my shoes.
Your finger's going to go through!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
What are you doing, Celty?!
What?
Hurry up and save me!
I wish I didn't have to...
Don't you realize that I acted all tough simply because your presence reassured me?
Whoa, Horada-san, that's the black motorcyclist!
What?!
Are you serious, Higa?!
Dead serious.
Saw her on TV.
I heard you were at the Dollars meeting six months ago, too.
I'm tired of everyone acting all big in our territory.
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna say something?!
Yeah?
Something wrong?
What the hell is this?!
Hey!
W-Wait!
Yeah, this is how people usually respond.
Great, it's not broken.
It's something precious Shinra gave me.
They sure got told!
This is the true power of an adult!
I can't take a liking to him at all...
Yagiri Namie
Secretary
Is there really a point to this?
Geez, what rules does he play by?
Russia Sushi!
Sir!
Oh, Izaya!
Yo, you're hard-working as ever.
I've seen you in Ikebukuro a lot these days.
Since you're here, stop by the restaurant.
The canned fish were just opened this morning.
Very fresh!
Sorry.
I'm actually pretty busy, despite how I look.
I'll stop by sometime in the future.
Hey.
You won't be able to keep something a secret forever.
Please don't talk about it in a city where she could hear you.
All right?
Okay, so to decide which one of us understands Anri better,
let's talk about her qualities.
I'll start.
The fact that she's sexy!
That right off the bat?
Let's move away from that topic.
Those who laugh at sexuality cry from the lack of it.
I don't even get what you're trying to say.
It was my first time making friends that were boys.
Your turn now.
List one of her qualities.
Well...
Actually, to be precise, it was probably my first time having friends.
You know...
Are you trying to say she doesn't have any qualities?
When did I say that?!
Then say it.
Now.
I mean now!
Well...
She used to only serve as a foil for a girl named Harima Mika.
But that was fine.
That gave her a place to belong to.
Friends forever
But now that she lost that place...
She couldn't find her standing ground.
Okay!
In order to prove Anri's sexual attractiveness,
we're going to go pick up chicks!
What's with that logic?
P-Pick up...?
Don't worry.
You're essentially coming as a snare so we can trick them into thinking,
"They've got a girl with them, so it'll be all right to go along."
You don't have to do anything!
Hang on, Masaomi!
Okay, let's go!
Follow me!
Off we...
go!
Let's go!
K-Kida-kun?
Masaomi!
Was it really okay...?
It's fine.
Even if we don't go with him, he'll do it alone anyway.
Geez...
You're so needy.
Since you're so inexperienced and naïve, I need to give you this much of a handicap.
Man, I'm such a bro.
Geez...
Let's have fun.
Yeah.
Umm...
She had realized that the two boys had taken a liking to her.
But...
Hey, the sunset is really pretty!
Huh?
Oh, but I see a strange cloud over there...
It may rain later, so let's be careful.
Yeah.
Umm...
Huh?
What is it?!
I'm going to be heading home now...
Huh?
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Ah... yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Not much of a smooth-talker, am I.
Even if one of them confesses to her, she
probably won't be able to give them an answer.
Even now, she likes Harima Mika.
And she likes the two about as much as she likes her.
She still doesn't know the difference between friendship and love.
For her, Harima Mika,
Ryugamine Mikado and Kida Masaomi are all...
Even if we insist?
We still really need you...
Stop making me repeat myself.
I have nothing to do with you guys anymore.
This isn't a place for me to be.
I don't plan on coming back.
To this side, that is.
Seriously?
That's hilarious.
What is the identity
of the Slasher?
Eight incidents so far this month!
None of the victims have anything in common. Could the culprit be a psychopath attacking randomly?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
He probably can't cut through jelly.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
A friend of mine was attacked by the Slasher yesterday!
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Was he killed?!
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
Idiot, the Slasher doesn't kill people.
He just hacks at them with a Japanese sword.
Was he killed?!
So he doesn't actually kill them? That's boring.
The Dollars is behind the slashing incidents!
They're planning on having Ikebukuro under their thumbs!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
Isn't Russhia Sushi doing it to obtain meat for their sushi?
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
It's gotta be the Headless Rider.
She's got a huge scythe, doesn't she?
I saw the Headless Rider attacking humans!
A lot of people wearing yellow have started to appear in the city.
Yellow?
I've noticed that, too.
Since you can actually notice by seeing them, they even stand out more than the Dollars.
Ah, the Yellow Scarves?
You know about them too, Setton-san?
Well, a bit...
They've been around for a while.
The Yellow Scarves...?
A team that used to be active in Ikebukuro.
But they actually disappeared due to a dispute with another team...
Oh, I've actually heard of that before.
So you mean, they've resurrected?
Ikebukuro's gotten pretty dangerous.
Yeah...
Even the cops are scary.
No, seriously!
Don't underestimate them!
The cops?
Wow, she fell.
How lame!
I only kicked her lightly.
She's so slow.
Well, she's a pinworm, after all.
What's with that look?!
And it doesn't seem like the slashing incidents will go away anytime soon.
Oh yeah, have you heard?
People are saying that the Slasher is actually in the Dollars.
Some people are even rumoring that it could be the Headless Rider.
What?! Who started that rumor?!
I don't think that's true.
Jokes aside...
You should really watch out for the Yellow Scarves.
Some of them aren't too happy about the Dollars,
since they really spread their influence
while the Yellow Scarves were inactive.
I see...
Thanks, I'll be careful.
Seriously...
First Harima, and now Ryugamine, Kida,
and on top of that, Nasujima?
Just how many people do you have to sell your body to for you to be satisfied,
you whore?!
You can't even survive unless you feed on somebody.
You pinworm!
Pinworm!
Pinworm...
The girl knew...
that what they were saying was true.
She was depending on Harima Mika.
And even now...
Why aren't you saying anything?!
Say something!
Do pinworms not have mouths?
She may be depending on those two boys.
To find a place within them where she could belong.
You smell, pinworm!
Quit coming to school!
We've lost two boyfriends because of you!
What are you staring off into space for?!
She had been protecting herself and her soul like this.
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That was her daily life.
Don't you live around here?
Let us come over.
We'll dig up some evidence!
Hurry up and lead the way!
Saika-san has entered the chat.
Here she is!
Whoa.
Huh?
Cut
I cut
We're the ones that want to cut you, geez!
Cut
I cut
Wrong
The one that's been trolling BBS' and chat rooms related to Ikebukuro since six months ago, right?
Weak, wrong,
I cannot conquer
You still hadn't banned him?
Weak, wrong,
I cannot conquer
Wish, I want
I did!
But no matter how many times I do it, it's pointless!
Wish, I want
Love. I don't have enough love.
Oh, I see.
I, want to love, humans
I, want to love, humans.
I've banned his remote host, but he enters immediately via a different host.
I, long, for, a, stronger, love
Oh, a proxy?
Wish, I, mother, mother
Well, it doesn't really seem like he's on a proxy.
I, long, for, a, stronger, love
Wish, I, mother, mother
He's kind of giving me the creeps.
Mother
Help-
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's...
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Unrest Prevailing
The Slasher exists somewhere in this city.
The terror that arises in the hearts of the people every time the incident occurs
causes millions of rumors to fly about within the heavy, stagnant night air.
However...
Next time: Unrest Prevailing.