U-Um, that's not it.
Things like flexible work hours exist, right?
As someone aiming to become part of the elite, I'd like from now on—
I thought you wanted to be a stay-at-home husband?
I believe you said that to work was to lose.
It's just that it's wrong to label lateness as evil.
I'll hear what you have to say before I hit you.
The police start moving after an incident occurs,
and it's common knowledge that the hero always arrives late.
But do you still condemn the hero for being late?
Paradoxically, I'd say lateness is justic—
Hold on. Hitting is not—
Jeez.
There are so many problem children in this class.
Flexible hours for you as well, Kawasaki Saki?
Black lace?
You're retarded.
In this room filled with light,
I'll be waiting for you
If you'd realize you're floating and gazing upon a box,
You'd notice it doesn't return your gaze
The reflected heart is pure white
Just like the light from the falling snow
This shivering rain that blankets me
Isn't going to dispel until the spring breeze returns
So let's search for some azalea
Bring me with you to a comforting garden
Is not something I can ask
That fairy tale-like happiness isn't real
I know that much already
But still
I want to go there
I guess it's Yukinon's turn to ask a question.
Then we'll start with Japanese.
Finish the following idiom, "If a butterfly flaps its wings..."
The Tokyo-Chiba train line will stop?
Is this some kind of quiz about Chiba?
Yuigahama, recently they keep it going at reduced speeds actually.
The answer is, "It might cause a hurricane somewhere."
Next question relates to geography.
What are Chiba's two local specialties?
Miso peas and boiled peas?
Do you think all Chiba has is peas?
Whoa! Oh, it's just Hikki.
I thought some creeper was randomly talking to me.
So you were also invited to the study group, Hachiman?
What's with that look as if someone you didn't invite just showed up?
We didn't invite you to the study group, so what do you want?
Quit saying such spiteful things as if you were simply stating facts.
What's that?
Documents for summer courses.
Wow, you're already studying for exams?
Haven't most people aiming for college already started?
Besides, I'm aiming for a prep school scholarship.
Scrap?
Scholarship.
Prep schools these days give tuition breaks for students with good grades.
Furthermore, if I get tuition from my parents, all that money will become mine.
That's swindling.
His ill nature is at fault.
It's fine if no one's disadvantaged.
Oh, Brother?
Komachi? What're you doing here?
My friend here asked me for some advice.
Hello there.
I'm Hikigaya Komachi.
Thanks for always being kind to my brother.
Nice to meet you. I'm his classmate, Totsuka Saika.
Well aren't you cute.
Right, Brother?
Yeah, but he's a guy.
There you go, joking again.
Wait, really?
Well yeah, I'm a guy.
Nice to meet ya. I'm Hikki's classmate, Yuigahama Yui.
Nice to meet—
Can I go now?
Nice to meet you. I'm Yukinoshita Yukino.
I'm not really his classmate or his friend...
Quite regrettably, his acquaintance, I guess?
"Regrettably?" And a question, even?
Um, I'm Kawasaki Taishi.
I'm in the same cram school as Hikigaya.
My sister is a second year at Sobu High too.
Her name is Kawasaki Saki.
Black lace?
Oh, Kawasaki?
She's a bit scary.
Isn't she a friend of yours?
Well, I've talked to her before.
But don't ask a girl stuff like that. It's hard to answer.
But I don't think I've seen her get along with anyone.
I heard that Taishi's older sister turned into a delinquent recently.
She even comes home late now.
So he asked me how to get her to become her old self again.
About when did this all start?
Just recently.
Ever since she started going to Sobu High.
She was really diligent in middle school, and kind too.
In other words, she changed after joining the same class as Hikigaya, right?
Why do you have to say it like it's my fault?
Am I some kind of virus?
I didn't say you were.
Isn't your imagination just running wild, Hikigerma?
You said it. You definitely said germ.
I stuttered.
It's Hikigaya germs! Touch!
I had a barrier up just now.
Barriers aren't effective against Hikigaya germs.
"Barriers aren't effective"?
How freaking strong are Hikigaya germs?
So like, what time does she come home?
I get home pretty late too.
After 5 AM or so.
Isn't that more like morning?
Don't your parents say anything?
They both work, and we have a younger brother and sister,
so they don't really fuss about her that much.
Familial circumstances, huh?
Everyone's got them.
Okay.
What're you going to do?
Taishi is the younger brother of Kawasaki Saki, a student at our school.
Considering that he asked for advice about her,
I think this falls under the Volunteers Club's jurisdiction.
I was just thinking about it,
but it would be best for her to solve the problem herself,
rather than us solving it for her.
Yeah, I guess.
So what exactly did you have in mind?
Do you know about animal therapy?
So what are you going to do with my cat?
By letting her play with the cat, we'll draw out the kindness in her heart.
She'll definitely pick it up if she's moved by it.
She's not some old-school delinquent leader, you know?
I've decided on everyone's role.
Everyone get into position.
What're you doing?
What do you mean?
Well, you were just talking to my cat, Kamakura.
I believe you were ordered to be on standby.
Can't you even do something so simple?
I had assumed your mental capabilities to be low,
but I honestly didn't think they were this low.
If I say anything more, she'll kill me. It's in her eyes.
Even grade schoolers can do what you tell them.
What's up, Komachi?
Oh, Brother? It's Taishi. I just heard from Hikigaya—
You don't have the right to call me Brother.
Why'd you hang up?
I'm busy at the moment.
Waiting for your sister.
It's about the plan.
My sister is allergic to cats.
It's true that there are things you just can't talk about with your parents,
but couldn't you talk to other adults instead?
Kawasaki.
Do you want something?
I hear you've been going home late recently.
What are you doing and where?
Who'd you hear that from?
I can't divulge the identity of my client.
Regardless, answer the question.
Does it really matter where?
It's not like I'm causing anyone trouble.
You might later.
You're a high school student.
Haven't you considered your parents' feelings at all?
Actually, there's no way you could have experience with things such as a parent's feelings.
Being single and all.
You should really worry about your own future instead of mine.
Like marriage, for example.
I feel bad for her.
I'm going home...
Seriously, someone marry her already.
If she changed for the worse, how about trying to change her one more time?
It'll definitely go better this time.
And how can we change her, I wonder?
There's only one reason a girl will change.
Love.
Afternoon. You seem tired.
Is it 'cause of a part time job?
Everything in moderation.
Thanks for your concern.
Hey.
You don't have to act so strong.
Oh, I don't need your consolation.
It seems like I was rejected.
Well, nice work.
It's mean to laugh.
It's cool. I'm not worrying about it.
I'm not your Brother.
What're you talking about?
Anyway, it looks like Taishi's sister got a phone call from some weird shop.
She got a phone call from the shop manager of some Angel something or another, right?
Yup.
After doing a little searching,
I found out that it's a shop called Angel in Chiba.
There are only two shops that stay open until early morning.
And this place here is one of them?
I don't know that much about them.
What kind of shop is a maid café?
I don't really know either, so I called someone who does.
So it's finally my turn?
Why are you making that face when you were the ones who called me here?
I just thought responding would be a pain.
Then be silent and follow me.
Let's go have the maids pamper us.
Pamper?
What?
I don't like this.
I mean, isn't this place for guys?
What would we do here?
It looks like girls are welcome too.
Welcome home, Master. Woof.
Sorry for the wait, Master.
Does it look good on me?
Wow, you look so cute, Yuigahama.
Right, Hachiman?
Y-Yeah.
Really? Thanks.
Hmph. You're merely cosplaying a maid!
There's no heart in it!
I'd rather have...
Huh? What?
Master.
Whoa! Yukinon, you're amazing!
You look great! So pretty!
Thank you.
Anyway, it seems like Kawasaki isn't here.
Did you check?
Her name wasn't on the shift schedule.
They called her home, so if you think about it, it's unlikely she used an alias.
Quite strange.
What is?
A haughty girl is working secretly.
"Meow, meow. Welcome home, Master."
"Wait! What are you doing here?"
That was fated to happen!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
We're going to the second place.
On the top floor of Hotel Royal Okura,
is Angel's Ladder, the stairway to heaven.
Sorry for the wait.
Where are the others?
They don't have any clothes to get past the dress code requirement.
I see.
Still, these clothes came from Yukinon's place.
She's got a ton just like these.
She even lives alone too.
Seriously, who are you, Yukinon?
You're exaggerating.
I have them only because I sometimes get the chance to dress like this.
Normally, people don't get such chances, though.
Is this for real?
Quit glancing around like that.
Straighten up, and stick your chest out.
Lower your chin.
Kawasaki?
I am terribly sorry.
Who might you be again?
You're in the same class, yet she doesn't remember you. Forgettable as always, Hikigaya.
Yukinoshita?
H-Hello.
Yuigahama.
So he's from Sobu High too?
Yeah.
So what did you come here for?
It wasn't for a date or anything, right?
Of course not.
Haven't you looked at this thing next to me? The mere suggestion is insulting.
I get that you're bickering with her, but could you not poke fun at me?
I hear you're going home late.
Your little brother is worried about you.
So it's your fault everyone around me is being so fussy?
I don't know what Taishi said to you guys, but don't worry about it.
Leave me alone.
Cinderella's magic is broken at midnight,
so yours will be broken here.
Once the magic is broken, won't the happy end be waiting for me?
I wonder if it will, Mermaid Princess.
I think you ought to watch out for the bad end, though.
Hey, what are these two talking about?
We aren't supposed to work late at night at our age.
In other words, Yukinoshita is suggesting that Kawasaki is falsifying her age.
I see. Why don't they just say that then?
Do you have any intention to quit?
Nope.
Y'know, I also work part time whenever I don't have any money,
but I've never lied about my age to work.
I just need the money.
Well, I can understand that.
How can someone who thinks working is losing understand?
So you heard that?
You're underestimating life.
I'm not working because I want money to fool around or anything.
Don't lump me in with that fool over there.
You guys talk big, but can you provide money for my sake?
Are you guys going to shoulder the costs that my parents couldn't?
Well...
That's about enough.
Any further barking—
Hey, isn't your father a member of the Diet prefectural assembly?
There's no way someone who lives so comfortably would understand.
Hey! Yukinon's family has nothing to do with this!
Then mine doesn't, either.
I guess that's true, but Yukinon...
I just knocked my glass over.
It's nothing, really. Don't worry.
Let's just go home for today.
I've got to talk to you about Taishi.
Hear me out tomorrow morning.
Five thirty at the WcD's on main street.
What?
I'll tell you what it's about then.
Later.
Hey!
This isn't enough money.
She didn't pay for mine?
Taishi?
What are you doing, being out this late?
That's what I want to know.
What are you doing, being out until so late?
It's got nothing to do with you.
Kawasaki, why is it you're working?
Why did you need the money? Let me guess.
Taishi, has anything changed since you entered your third year?
I started going to a cram school, I guess.
I get it. It's to pay for his tuition.
Nope.
He's been attending cram school since April.
That means that the problem of his tuition is already sorted out.
That's how it is.
The little brother isn't the only one who needs tuition paid.
Our school is for college-bound students,
so most people are consciously preparing for college.
They begin seriously thinking about summer classes and such.
Sis!
That's why I said it's fine if you didn't know.
I plan to go to college.
I didn't want to bother you or our parents about it.
Um, can I say something?
Well, both our parents work too.
When I was little, I hated it when I came home to an empty house,
so I ran away from home.
And it wasn't my parents who came for me, but my brother.
Ever since then, he started coming home before me.
I really feel grateful towards him.
Wasn't he coming home early because he had no friends?
How do you know that?
From Yukipedia or something?
I totally agree, but my version made me sound smart.
What were you trying to say with that?
Just as how you don't want to be a bother to your family,
Taishi doesn't want to be a bother to you, either.
If only you'd understand that, the younger sibling would then be happy.
Well, I feel the same way.
Kawasaki, do you know about scholarships?
Are all siblings like that, I wonder?
Doesn't it depend on the person?
You could also say they're the closest stranger to you.
I suppose.
That's something I understand quite well.
Oh, that's right.
You actually did end up meeting.
What're you talking about?
You know, the sweets person.
Aren't you glad?
Thanks to that little bit of pain, you got to meet someone as cute as Yui.
What did she just say?
Yuigahama is the sweets person?
The owner of the dog I saved on the day of the entrance ceremony?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Want to buy bread on the way home?
Sure.
That's all, and that ends the workplace field trip. Dismissed.
Hikki!
What took you? Everyone's already left for the family restaurant.
Aren't you going?
I was waiting for you.
I'd feel bad leaving you behind.
You really are kind, Yuigahama.
You don't need to worry about me, you know?
It was just a coincidence that I saved your dog.
I'd probably still be alone even if the accident never happened.
There's no reason at all for you to fret over it.
Sorry.
You really didn't have to mind me.
But you don't have to worry about me from now on.
If you're being kind because you're worried,
then stop it.
Well, I wonder why it is.
It's not really like that...
The ever kind Yuigahama will probably be kind to the very end.
Jerk!
I hate those types of kind girls.
You can't get them off your mind if they merely say hi to you.
Just a single text from them can make your heart flutter.
Then if you get a call from them, you'll just keep happily looking at the call history like an idiot.
But I know better.
About that thing called "kindness."
If someone is kind to me, they're also kind to others.
I almost forget that sometimes.
If the truth is that cruel,
then I'm sure lies are truly kind.
That's why kindness is a farce.
I always get my hopes up and end up misunderstanding every time...
At some point I just gave up hope.
I'm an experienced loner. I'll never again fall for it.
I'm a veteran warrior.
I'm the absolute best at losing.
So I will forever hate kind girls.
He once again returns the way he came.
Laughter resounds in the distance,
And then it can't be heard anymore
I'd rather not force myself to laugh and try to forget
I'd rather drown and freeze it in silence
I don't mind getting hurt
Before the setting sun disappears beyond the ocean's horizon,
If I could tell you it was all a lie
Maybe we could get back to our shining days
Just the two of us alone again
Hello! Hello! Alone!
Darn, and here I had some expectations for her.
It's not like Yuigahama has quit—
If she doesn't come, it's the same thing.
I didn't know what sort of things she liked, or what her hobbies were.
Sorry. I guess I got a bit carried away.
I want to talk this through with you properly.
You don't have to trouble yourself with me anymore.
So that's why it's over with this, okay?
Idiot...
At last, his and her beginning will come to an end.
Next time: