We now begin the 57th expedition!
Advance!
After departing on an expedition
to find a route to Shiganshina,
the Survey Corps encountered a female
Titan thought to be human, like Eren.
That's not an Abnormal.
It's a human controlling the body of a Titan!
As soldiers fell one after another,
the survivors ran into a forest of giant trees,
with not a clue as to why they were doing so.
If we, the Levi Squad, don't
stop it, who's going to?!
Decide.
Either you believe in yourself
or the soldiers of the Survey
Corps, myself included.
I'll keep going!
Fire!
Oh, right.
There's something I want to ask.
Is it all right if I sever your hands and feet?
They'll grow right back, won't they?
I'm talking about your real body.
It'll be a problem if you die, after all.
This shows the enemy was prepared
to abandon everything.
To think they'd have themselves devoured
to avoid leaking information...
All soldiers, retreat!
Assume the formation.
Return to Karanese District!
Erwin.
Why'd you have Levi resupply?
We don't have time.
The female Titan was devoured.
But... did you see the person inside get eaten?
I didn't.
Don't tell me...
Exactly.
Just as you deduced before,
if they're a type that can move to some
extent even after transforming...
Furthermore,
assuming they had a three-dimensional
maneuver device equipped...
Wearing the same uniform as us, the one
controlling the female Titan could...
Lance Corporal Levi?
No, that's not him!
Who're you?!
Huh?!
Gunther!
...have slipped into our ranks.
Wohlan, Freund!
Woh
lan,
Freund!
Well, friend!
lan,
Freund!
Jetzt hier ist ein Sieg.
Jetzt
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Victory stands before us.
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Dies ist die erste Glorie.
Dies
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
Our legend begins now.
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
O, mein Freund!
O,
mein
Freund!
O, my friend!
mein
Freund!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
ern
wir
die
sen
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
battle!
I won't let you say, "My death is meaningless."
Not until but a single arrow remains.
≪一矢≫
The enemy is cruel... But we'll prevail.
Der
Feind
ist
grau
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
ma
de
Der
Feind
ist
grau
de
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
The enemy is titanic... So we'll jump.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Bearing steel blades of glory, we sing an anthem of victory.
Sieg
≪鋼刃≫
Sieg
≪凱歌≫
On our backs are the Wings of Liberty.
Sieg
Frei
heit
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
On our chests are our fists, tightly clenched with determination.
The screw of folly rips through.
heit
≪愚行の螺旋≫
gen
der
Tor
heit
Wings of Liberty dance in the blue sky.
sou
kyuu
Frei
heit
sou
kyuu
wo
ma
u
Flü
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
The Decisive Blow
————— The 57th Expedition Part    —————
⑤
When the Colossus Titan disappeared,
a pre-equipped three-dimensional
maneuver device ensured that
the human inside could swiftly
escape through the steam.
Don't you think the same
can be said about this case?
But then...
Considering Eren's condition
after reverting back,
we can conclude that it
isn't too likely, right?
His equipment was damaged,
and part of his uniform was gone.
Most notably, he was so exhausted
that he couldn't even stand on his own.
The female Titan had the
ability to call in other Titans.
Because we didn't predict that, the plan failed.
If powers as a Titan are
commensurate with one's skill,
then considering a novice like Eren
as the norm has been a mistake.
In order to outwit the enemy,
we need to think outside the box.
Are we withdrawing because
the plan was a success?
If it was, we may have already identified the
one who was controlling the female Titan.
I'd like to see them.
But what made the commander so sure they
would chase after Eren once he left the walls?
I think it had to do with why the Titans suddenly
stopped attacking during the last incident.
Huh?
Despite managing to break
through Trost District's gate,
they didn't attempt to continue any farther
and stayed back when Eren sealed the gate.
Could it have been because they
had more pressing concerns?
Meaning?
Something even more important
than destroying the walls.
Remember the unexpected
event that happened next.
You mean Eren's transformation?
That's the only thing I can think of.
Which means...
Uh, so...
Someone who was there, who saw
Eren transform into a Titan,
is the one inside the Titan.
Gunther!
Eren, don't stop!
Keep moving!
Gunther is...
Who is it?!
Protect Eren!
Damn, what now?!
Eld, which way should we go?!
There's no time to mount the horses!
Head to HQ as quickly as possible!
Is it the female Titan?
Or were there others?
Damn, how dare you...
Bring it on!
I'll kill you at any cost!
The female Titan?
No way... How?!
Didn't we capture them?!
If the enemy is able to conserve their strength,
they may also be able to
transform a second time.
Bingo, huh?
Here it comes!
It's the female Titan!
Damn, why you...
I'll do it this time!
I'll kill it!
Don't!
The three of us will take
down the female Titan.
You continue heading to HQ at full speed!
This is something I noticed
after facing the enemy.
Limiting ourselves to the best course of action
will never give us the edge over the enemy.
We must take necessary and costly risks,
facing them with the resolution to lose everything.
Let me fight with you!
No!
This is for the best!
Your power poses far too great of a risk!
What's with you?!
You doubting our skills?!
Is that so, Eren?
Are we really that unreliable?
Unless we fight like that,
mankind cannot prevail.
I believe my squad will be victorious!
Good luck!
We blinded it.
It won't be able to see for at least a minute!
We'll finish it before that!
To hell with capturing it!
We'll kill it now!
Die a dog's death here!
Down with this damn Titan!
As if we'd let you recover your vision!
We'll slice all of the muscles around your shoulders
so you won't be able to hold up your arms!
Slice them apart...
And those arms...
Will drop!
They're down!
Now the neck!
Once the muscles supporting its neck are cut...
we can get its nape!
They're amazing.
The female Titan is cornered...
And how they can coordinate their
attacks without saying a word...
It must only be possible because
they trust one another.
That's how they've overcome hardships.
And that's why they're so strong
despite having just lost Gunther.
I'll keep going.
If I keep going and believe in them,
never looking back, then...
I'll have made the right choice!
I finally understand!
I don't know the right answer.
I never have.
Even if I believed in myself
and the decisions of the comrades
who've earned my trust,
the result was always a complete mystery.
Your nape is mi—
Eld!
How?
It can't possibly see already!
Not even thirty seconds have...
Just one eye?
It prioritized one eye to heal faster?
How is that possible...
Petra!
Right yourself already!
Petra, hurry up!
Hey...
Die!
Why?
My blade won't go through.
I'll...
kill it!
Eren?
Hey, wha—
Mikasa!
This voice...
Don't tell me...
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Survey Corps Horse Part ①
The horses given to the Survey Corps were selectively
bred for their exclusive use. They measure about 160 cm tall
and weigh from 450 ~ 500 kg.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Survey Corps Horse Part ②
Their top speed ranges from 75 ~ 80 km/h, and they can maintain speeds of about 35 km/h.
These horses are just about the only way to outrun the Titans.
Because I made the wrong decision...
Because I wanted to believe in my comrades...
everyone died!
If only I had believed in myself
from the start and fought...
If only I had killed her from the start!
Back then...
if I'd transformed into a Titan...
No...
If I'd fought...
even before that time...
Lance Corporal Levi was there too.
We'd definitely have won.
Maybe we could've even captured it.
You're not in the wrong.
Feel free to do it.
I...
I made my decision.
And everyone died because of it.
Because of me, they all...
But...
in the end...
you're still responsible!
I'll rip you apart.
Once this hand heals...
I'll split you wide open...
Tear you to bloody shreds...
Mangle every last chunk...
And devour it all!
Eren!
Wait... Eren...
Don't go...
Give Eren...
Give Eren... back!
Give him back!
Why won't the blade go through?
I know... he's alive.
I know that Eren's alive!
Wherever she goes,
I'll be sure to kill her,
slice her apart,
and get you out from that filthy place.
Sorry, Eren.
Wait just a little longer.
Stop!
Wh-What're you...
Fall back for now.
Maintain this distance.
She must be exhausted.
Her pace seems to be slowing.
It looked like he was bitten out nape and all,
so is Eren dead?
If we were to assume that I'm not me,
tatoeba ore ga ore janai toshite
then could you be sure that you are you?
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
I shattered a vessel of sand, spilling its contents.
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Could you retrieve your heart and gather it all?
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
The sound of others calling my name
dareka no yobu koe ga
is now all but noise to me.
miminari ni kawatta
It's as if time is standing still.
toki ga tomatta mitai da
Now, open your eyes.
saa me wo samase
I slipped out of the vast darkness,
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
and fled from it as swiftly as a gale.
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
It's as if I was a living corpse.
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We now head beyond the walls.
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
Let us meet again in those uncharted lands.
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
"Eren is alive."
"Give Eren back."
Mikasa, who watched the female Titan
take Eren from right before her eyes,
joins forces with humanity's
most powerful soldier, Levi,
to challenge the female Titan to battle.
The Defeated
————— The 57th Expedition Part    —————
⑥