Can ye greenhorns strike me?
Crooked magistrate!
Prepare thyself!
I am next.
Make your peace.
Face judgment!
What did you just hide?
Huh? Wh-What're you talking about?
What is this?
"Grow-Me-Big"?
Gimme that!
I need that medicine to go on a date with Master—
A date with Master?
A date?
A date, you say?
N-No, it's just...
that's what the rumors are...
So just give it back!
Stop right there!
You will tell us everything you know!
Stubborn!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
One Day, Somewhere
Hm?
What was I doing?
My parts aren't separated!
Are these ears?
I don't have screw holes!
Nothing to report!
Wait, Kurara!
It's me, Ann!
Hey, you're gonna break me!
Oh, I'm sorry.
What the heck...
So when you woke up, your body blew up in size.
Hm. Well,
when a girl your age reaches puberty,
it's perfectly natural for your body to change in unexpected—
It's not that! I'm not a human!
I'm a Shinki!
I see!
They must have built extremely detailed life-sized Shinki!
And your consciousness must have been installed in one...
Or, probably not.
But...
I really am...
Cramming for tests is tough, huh?
But you can't give up!
If you keep trying, I know you'll make the grade!
I suggest seeing a shrink.
I'll be off!
Wha?
Please wait!
It won't open...
Who's she?
She's super fishy.
Potchi, Tamami!
You know her?
I've never seen her in all my nine lives.
It's me, Ann!
I'm the Shinki that belongs to the master who lives here!
It's true, trust me!
I woke up all of a sudden and found myself in a human-sized body...
That sounds fuzzy to me.
You're fishy!
We'll chase you out!
Go, Meowchines!
W-Wait!
Please stop!
She ran!
Let's tail her!
She can't have gone far on those human legs of hers!
We're gonna skin her when we find her!
Skin?
It's raining!
We left Master's laundry outside!
That's a cat-astrophe!
Let's go home, quick!
What's happening?
Wait!
That's my umbrella!
M-Master!
Maste—
That sounds fuzzy to me.
You should see a shrink.
What should I do?
Um, you don't have an umbrella, do you?
You can use this umbrella if you want.
No, I don't want to bother you...
But you'll get wet.
But you'll get wet if I use it...
Don't worry, I'm close to my home.
W-Well, I am too!
Something wrong?
I...
Hm?
I'm lost!
Oh, well—
wait, lost?
Since you're wearing that uniform,
you go to the same school as me, right?
Y-Yeah, I do.
Then you should live around here.
What's your address?
Well, it's...
I was at the bus stop before I knew it,
so I kind of don't know...
I see.
When you move to a new place, you forget where you live a lot.
Something like that.
The streets here are complicated, so it's easy to get lost.
I moved here in the spring,
but I got lost a lot at first,
and I was late all the time.
That's right.
And even then, you always sleep in just before you need to leave.
You run out the door every morning.
Huh?
I-I was talking about myself.
I'm pretty bad with mornings, too.
My Shinkis always wake me up at the right time,
but I always fall back asleep.
I'm a handful every morning.
No, you're not a handful at all.
Hm?
I mean, I think the Shinkis feel that way...
That's fine too. Thanks.
Th-Thank you too...
Oh yeah.
Are there any distinctive buildings around your home?
If we go somewhere high up,
you might see something you remember.
Wanna try it?
Y-You're right.
Let's do that.
It's a dead end.
Hm?
There was a way to get up there the last time I was here.
Whoah, wait!
H-Huh?
Normally, I could handle this...
You're not going to get anywhere by jumping on—
Wai—
I'm not looking, I swear!
S-Sorry.
M-Me too...
Stairs?
Oh, we can use that to get up.
The rain's lightened up.
Yeah.
It's so pretty.
It really is.
Anyway...
R-Right!
Do you recognize anything?
Well, um...
Don't worry.
We'll definitely find it if we search together.
Right!
Thank you so much!
Welcome!
What would you like?
Huh?
You're probably thirsty, so pick whatever you like.
Then, grapefruit...
Grapefruit, huh?
This is it.
Sorry.
I-I'm sorry.
We might get some info if we go to the shopping district.
Oh, right!
If you've lived in this town at all,
you've probably shopped here at least once.
Found something?
Oh, no...
Would you like to try it on?
Oh, no, I'm...
I think it suits you perfectly, ma'am!
You and your boyfriend are welcome here!
B-Boyfriend?
It looks wonderful on you, ma'am!
Doesn't it?
Y-Yeah.
It looks great on you.
N-No way...
No, really...
It seems that your boyfriend likes it too!
Thank you for your purchase!
W-We're in a hurry today, so maybe later!
Boyfriend, huh?
Is she still sleeping?
We were up late last night playing Pop Up Samurai,
so she's probably still tired.
She's sleepin' too much for that.
It's past noon already.
But she sure looks happy.
I'm sure she's having a sweet dream.
I'm back.
Here you go.
Oh no, you shouldn't have!
Don't worry.
The gelato here is great.
It's yummy!
Isn't it?
Give me a second.
Gimme that!
I need that medicine to go on a date with Master—
No way...
You liar!
You're wrong!
I was just scared of earning your scorn, so I never told you!
I can't believe you masked your true form and deceived me this whole time...
Wait! Forgive me!
Farewell. This is the end for us.
Why?
You liar!
Something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Nothing...
Oh, I'm great at those!
Wanna try it?
Okay, here we go.
Sure, go for it.
Is this right?
Just a little... there!
Oh, stop there!
Thank you very much!
No problem.
If I ever start feeling down,
he cheers me back up...
She's still not up?
There's no reason for her to sleep this long.
Ann!
Wake up already!
Hey.
Come here.
Virus news?
A virus that imitates update software is currently spreading...
What does this mean?
Read the list of symptoms.
When the virus activates,
the afflicted Shinki is left unable to exit Sleep mode,
and it can end in Shinki functionality ceasing permanently!
So you're saying that Ann's caught this virus?
It has already encroached upon her AI partition.
Wh-What should we do?
Good question...
But right now, we've gotta call Master!
Guess we couldn't find it.
Where to next?
Um...
Um, I...
The truth is, I'm—
Sorry, give me a sec.
Hello?
Master!
Um, Ann's in trouble!
We installed an anti virus,
but the symptoms...
Oh no, her AI partition!
Huh? An external memory module?
Oh, Master can get one from the Shinki shop!
Hina!
I can reach Master sooner through flight!
I see. I'll be right there.
Um...
I'm...
I'm Ann.
Don't worry.
Huh?
I'm sorry for lying.
Thank you for today.
It was like a dream come true.
Walking side by side under an umbrella,
running together hand in hand,
Seeing the beautiful scenery from up high...
It's strange.
Even though I've flown higher plenty of times before,
it looked completely different.
But you really are a nice person, Master.
I'm so happy to be your Shinki.
I feel this way all over again.
I love you, Master!
Huh? I'm...
Master...
Ann!
Ines!
Ann.
You've revived!
We're so happy!
Why are you all...
Don't be like that!
We were worried to death over you!
Master was up all night...
Huh? It's morning?
Ann!
Master!
Ann! Thank goodness!
I'm so happy!
Master, that hurts a little!
Can ye recovered cripples truly strike me?
Crooked magistrate!
Prepare thyself!
I am next.
Make your peace.
Accept judgment!
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
I wonder if Master and I had the same dream?
Oh yeah, Master was talking in his sleep!
Ooh, what'd he say?
The meat's too hard, so don't lay the noodles sideways...
Meat? Noodles?
He was dreaming about beef.
Master...
Next time, our Master's lunch is in big trouble!
Busou Shinki!
Next time
"Lene's Underground Empire Wars"
Lene's Underground Empire Wars!
I shall enjoy this.