Enjoy yourselves.
Something wrong?
Oh, no.
When you said "tea," I didn't
think you actually meant "tea."
Relax. I'm picking up the tab.
Uh-huh...
Nakajo didn't pan out?
Nor Haba?
That's right.
Nor Sawakiguchi, either?
I don't think so.
I see.
I hate to say it, but...
You don't have to worry about being polite.
I would like you to tell me, then,
what about them was so wrong?
First, let's start with
Nakajo-senpai's theory.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Tea Room Hifumi
which is why I couldn't adopt
Sawakiguchi-senpai's idea, either.
I see.
Blind Spot to All
Who was it that turned down Nakajo's idea?
That was me.
And was it the same for
Haba and Sawakiguchi?
That's correct.
When I first asked you
to solve this problem,
you said you didn't want
me to expect too much.
But then you went and put to rest
every last one of their ideas.
Just as I secretly thought you would.
You thought I would?
It turns out that they weren't
up to the challenge.
I knew from the start that they didn't have
the necessary skill to solve this problem.
That was just a charade? Then...
Of course, I'm not saying
that they are incapable.
They possess skill that
is hard to come by.
But even so, that doesn't make
them of any use in this situation.
Then why did...
If you weren't...
If you weren't around, we would
have used one of their ideas,
and the production would likely
have ended up a failure.
That's pretty cold. Not to mention cruel.
If we must, that's what we'll do.
But there is one other person
that we can turn to.
I have heard from three different
people about this person's ability.
One is Chitanda Eru. One is
someone outside the school.
The last one is Togaito Masashi.
This person might be able to
serve as the video's detective.
That's what I thought.
I was after you from the beginning,
not the Classic Lit Club.
Oreki-kun...
Given all that has happened, I consider
you to have proven your skill.
You...
are special.
You are special.
So I would like to ask you one more time...
Oreki-kun, please, help out Class 2-F.
I'd like you to find a
solution to this video.
I don't have any skills.
I just happened to get lucky.
How disappointing.
Then allow me to say something else.
Consider it an amusing anecdote.
A certain athletic club had a benchwarmer.
The benchwarmer tried extremely
hard to become a regular,
but she just couldn't make it.
This was because the club had other, far
more capable members than the benchwarmer.
Among them was someone who
was born with natural ability.
Her talent was, of course, the difference between
night and day when compared to the benchwarmer.
At one competition, she
performed extremely well,
Prize
and was even chosen as the MVP.
An interviewer asked her,
"That was quite a feat.
What is your secret?"
She answered him,
"I just happened to get lucky."
I think that her answer sounded
fairly caustic to the benchwarmer.
How about you?
Everyone ought to recognize who they are.
Otherwise, it makes fools
of those watching them.
Am I special?
Do I truly give myself enough
credit for who I am?
Is it right for me to believe it?
Irisu-senpai,
I...
This is unusual... you going to the school
on your own during vacation.
Do you have some business there?
Can I not go to school without
having any business there?
No, it just goes against the grain.
I received a personal
request from Irisu-senpai.
I'm going to identify the
culprit that killed Kaito.
Oh, yeah? No kidding. You, Hotaro?
Oreki Hotaro is both dutiful and devoted.
I'm not sure I heard that. One more time?
Hmph.
Still, this is quite a
change of heart, huh?
Was Chitanda-san the reason
behind it this time, too?
No.
Then, what was the reason?
"If I don't have to do
something, I don't do it."
That's your motto, isn't it?
Satoshi...
Hm?
Do you think that there's anything
that only you can accomplish?
Nope.
No?
Haven't I told you? I
don't have any talents.
For example, I fancy myself a Sherlockian.
But I could never be one.
I lack the basic nerve necessary
to forge my way headlong
into the deep and rarefied
labyrinth of knowledge.
If Mayaka were to turn her interest
toward Holmes, I guarantee you,
she'd pass me up in three months.
I go around peeking into the
doorways of various genres,
and getting my pamphlet stamped.
That's the most that I can do.
I couldn't ever be an
authority on anything.
I get it. Irisu-senpai roped you into this.
Nonetheless, you're still having
misgivings about your own aptitude.
And you never have doubts about yourself?
Not really. I'm going on ahead.
Mayaka should already be at school,
so I'm going to say hello.
Satoshi!
Hm?
I'm not sure what you think,
but I give you more value than that.
If you wanted to, someday,
I think you could be one of the
finest Sherlockians in all of Japan.
There are any number of things
that are more appealing
than being a Sherlockian.
Though I have to admit...
I couldn't be more envious,
at all.
Earth Science Prep Room
I-It's summer vacation, and Oreki
voluntarily came to school?!
Something wrong with me being here?
It's wrong, all right.
It's creepy, like the prelude
to an apocalyptic disaster.
I decided to help solve the mystery.
You? Why?
Aha! I'll bet Irisu-senpai seduced
you with something, huh?
Mayaka, you're sharp, huh?
Okay, whatever. Never mind me,
how did it go after you left yesterday?
You mean Chi-chan? She seemed
to get home all right.
I called her this morning, and she
was sick in bed with a hangover.
Now that's a rare case, huh?
Ahem. Well, anyway,
let's watch that movie again.
Kaito!
I-I-It's blood!
H-Hey, what's that?
Kaito-senpai's arm there
really is nicely done.
It looks just like a real arm.
The prop makers might be the most
capable ones of all of them.
Oh, no...
It sure doesn't look like
there's a fancy setup, huh?
Yeah. Something so difficult
is being made to look simple.
No it's not.
The reason it looks simple isn't because
it was set up to look that way.
What, then?
Here's what I think. This video
just makes for a dull movie,
and it has no appeal to the viewer,
which is why the mystery doesn't pop.
Ho...
The volunteers of Class 2-F,
having decided to participate
in the Kanyasai...
That's true. Seeing it for the first time,
I didn't even realize that it was
a locked-room murder movie.
The production is awfully weak, after all.
Such as?
The camerawork is poor.
Yeah, there's that.
Then Ibara, how would you shoot it?
If it were me? Okay...
For example, let's see here...
Right here.
Wouldn't it be more effective
to shoot this from farther away,
to show the characters together
with the room's interior?
True enough.
Also...
right here.
Hey, Sugimura! How about you?!
I-It's fairly clean in here.
We might be able to use it.
I think it would be better to shoot
this from Sugimura-senpai's view
to make it easier to tell that the lobby
is in full view from up there.
When the camera looks up
at him from the lobby,
that point doesn't get conveyed
to the viewer, right?
Let's see, what else...?
Sorry, but that's enough.
How come?
You'll go on forever.
Hmph.
Criticizing how bad the video is
won't get us anywhere.
Now, now, it might be good
to study it a little.
I found you, Fukube!
So this is where you've
been goofing around!
Hey, Yamauchi-kun, welcome!
H-Hey, no need to get violent!
I'm doing this for your own good!
But I have lots of other things to do!
You idiot! Omichi isn't messing around!
Don't you care if you fail
to pass the class?!
Satoshi, you should go take
those remedial lessons.
B-But Hongo-senpai's mystery
is important, too!
Hotaro, go ahead and pull the solution
out of thin air right now!
What kind of nonsense
are you going on about?!
Oh, well, you see...
No! I want to know the secret! The secret!
And he's gone.
What is he, an idiot?
He's back.
I'm sorry, Hotaro. The constraints
of the world are beyond my control.
Having come to this...
Fukube!
Think of this notebook as being me.
Come on, let's go!
Okay! I'm coming!
For Pete's sake.
Well then, I have to go, too.
Oh?
What are you looking at me like that for?
Irisu-senpai may be one thing,
but I am not planning to help you.
'Zat so?
I have library duty. If I had
known we'd be doing this,
I would have left my schedule
open ahead of time.
It's your own fault for
springing this on us. Still...
Sorry, Oreki.
Okay then...
Let's split up and look around inside!
Eh...
Damn it! Who did this?!
I-I-It's blood!
It's okay. I'm sure there are keys.
Eh?!
That's it.
No unauthorized personnel
That...
is what Hongo intended.
Shosho ('Heat's End')
For the sunshine easeth,
and blue skies begin their withdrawl
Hyouka
Come in.
First, I'd like to ask,
did you reach a conclusion?
Okay then, let's hear it.
Right.
It goes without saying
that the locked room is
the key to this mystery.
The room that Kaito...
I mean, Kaito-senpai died in
could not have been entered
by any of the other members,
nor could they leave it.
You can forgo the "senpai."
Stage left wing is a locked room.
Damn it! Who did this?!
The only other exit, this window,
was in the condition you see here.
Which makes it inconceivable that the killer
came or left by any means except for the door.
So how did they do it?
It's unclear from the video whether
or not the door is rigged.
Which means it's most reasonable to assume
that the killer used the
master key to let themselves in.
However, the lobby was under
Sugimura's observation.
As a result, the killer couldn't have
even entered the right hallway.
This creates a second locked room.
None of our six characters could have gotten
the master key from out of the office,
and then gone down the right hallway.
So what does that leave us with?
If none of the six are the killer,
there can be only one conclusion...
There was a seventh character there.
A seventh character?
Like Sawakiguchi was saying?
Yes. When she first came up with it,
I thought it was pretty absurd,
but according to Sawakiguchi,
Hongo was looking for someone
to play a seventh character.
Remembering that, I became convinced.
However, Hongo wrote the script
to play it straight with the viewer.
It's unimaginable that a phantom
character would suddenly appear.
Incidentally, there were a number
of odd occurrences in the video.
Satoshi wrote about these.
"Konosu finds the floorplan.
It is illuminated.
I believe it to be a flashlight.
Another spot, when they
go searching for Kaito.
The hall is dark. Not enough light.
A flashlight is used."
A flashlight, huh?
That's right.
And none of the featured characters
are carrying a flashlight.
Looking at the scene right after
where the flashlight is shown,
such as immediately following
their entry into the crime scene,
this can clearly be seen.
There was enough time
to hide the flashlight,
but there isn't any
legitimate reason to do so.
I know, you want to say that
it's simply scene lighting, right?
But please, keep this in mind for later.
There's another thing... and please don't take
offense, as this is coming from a film lover.
"This movie is dull. It
was poorly produced.
The camerawork in particular
had no innovation at all."
But what if there was a reason for that?
This movie was shot with the cameraman
always in the same place as the other six.
I think you might have
figured it out by now.
Are you trying to tell me...
that the cameraman is
the seventh character?
There were seven of them from the start.
The six of them in the picture,
and the cameraman shooting them,
for a total of seven.
Please watch closely.
There are some scenes where the
actors pay attention to the camera.
They were aware that the
cameraman was there.
Calling him the cameraman is misleading.
How about we call him the seventh man?
As for the flashlight illumination,
it wouldn't be out of place to
think that he was carrying one.
The poor quality of the camerawork,
and the fact that he couldn't shoot the scene
from multiple angles at the same time,
becomes more convincing if you
think of him as a character.
Also... and this is important...
When the others departed
the interior of the scene,
the camera was still in the lobby
after everyone was gone.
The scene then fades out.
In other words, after the
camera stops temporarily,
it was waiting there in the lobby
for the others to return.
As such, the crime is simple.
The seventh character waited for
the others to leave the stage,
and after stopping the
camera he was holding,
he moved quickly to obtain
the master key from the office.
After killing Kaito, he uses it
to lock up the room.
Then he waited in the lobby
for the others to return.
That is my conclusion.
If Hongo had not chosen
a seventh actor yet,
I recommend that you find one
as soon as possible.
Two things...
First, if that were true,
the fact that the seventh
person never says anything,
nor does anyone ever speak to him,
comes off as awkward, doesn't it?
Hongo may have been
using that as a motive.
The seventh character was one
that the other six ignored.
As a result, he was unable
to speak up, himself.
Second, if that were true,
the characters in the movie would reach
the same conclusion before long.
They would all suspect the seventh man,
who remained in the lobby.
Also, the "second locked room"
that you speak of is still intact.
We can assume that the seventh man's
movements were in public view.
In which case, they would know
who the culprit was right away.
If I may borrow an expression
from Sawakiguchi,
"What does it really matter?"
Who really cares if the cast
of characters know who it is?
As long as the viewers are puzzled
by the mystery, isn't that enough?
That may be why there's no
detective character in the script.
There's no need for the folks in
the show to reach a deduction
because it's obvious to
them who the killer is.
Congratulations.
Huh?
It looks like you solved Hongo's mystery.
It's a surprisingly bold
approach, to be sure,
but since it corresponds
to all of the facts,
there can be no doubt that you are right.
Also, thank you.
Now we can finish the movie.
It looks like my estimation
of you was right.
You do have the skill.
A power that no one else has.
Er, well, I'm... most grateful.
How about it? Would you like to be
the one to give the movie a title?
A title?
Just off the top of your head.
As long as you're the one who thinks of it,
I'm sure everyone will approve.
Huh...
Well, let's see... in keeping
with the content...
What do you think about
"Blind Spot to All"?
Hm...
That's a good title. Let's settle on that.
Home run.
Good morning!
For all of you 3rd-years...
October brings with it
the culture festival...
There's a screening of the movie in the
AV room. We are already there.... Chitanda
I just don't think anyone could
have gotten near that room.
That's true. With the exception
of one person... you.
Did you do this?
You're the one who did this?
How could you?!
How could you do something like this?!
Yeah?!
Surprised, huh?
Hey, hold on!
Are you running away?!
Give yourself up!
He pulled it off, all right.
Man, that really was a great ending!
It's the real Kaito.
Yeah, really. Who'd
have guessed it was the cameraman?
Hey, I heard!
It turns out that you're the one
who thought this up, huh?
Yeah, well...
Man, that was a surprise ending!
No complaints!
Hey! It's the great detective!
Great detective?
Way to go!
Although, it's too bad that when
the seventh character is revealed,
they turn violent, and all gang up on him.
Yeah...
Well, anyhow, thanks.
See you!
Right.
You know, Nakajo...
What?
Your pit sweat is out of control.
You'll never get a girl that way. That arm
was worth all the work we put into it.
Tch!
It looks like it wasn't to Haba's liking.
Hotaro!
We saw it.
Okay, now let's submit
it to the executive committee.
What did you think?
Mm, not bad.
It was interesting. Who'd have
guessed the cameraman did it?
Had you thought about this last time?
No, at the time, I hadn't come up with it.
Oh.
What? She doesn't seem very surprised.
That's our Hotaro for you, huh?
Yeah, right. I hate to admit it, though.
Well, what do I expect?
Oreki-san...
Yeah?
I...
Um... I'll tell you later.
Well, anyhow, well done, Hotaro.
The "Empress" is satisfied,
and the movie is finished.
The viewers will enjoy the
element of surprise, too.
Oreki...
There's something I have to ask you.
What is it?
Hey, come on...
Oreki, you're the one who came up
with that solution, right?
That's right.
All of it?
Mostly.
Then what do you think about
what Haba-senpai said?
Haba?
They...
They didn't use the rope
anywhere in that movie.
Ah...
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Credit Roll of Fools."
Credit Roll of Fools