No way-
What cup size is that?!
She's still a freshman, right?
They're huge!
This year's got another great crop of freshmen, eh?
No kidding!
Have you heard about Shiraishi?
Shiraishi?
You know, with this-
"Best in School / Giant Breasts Rankings!!"
1st Place Shiraishi
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Yako-chan, Yako-chan!
I have a great idea on how to get Underwear Club members!
Really? I'll help if there's anything I can do.
We do need ten people to start it.
Yeah! Thanks!
So, if you don't mind,
I was hoping you could come over to my house today.
Eh?! Now she's after Jinguuji-san?!
Haruka-chan, good morning.
Good morning...
Something wrong? Did you catch a cold or something?
You look a little down...
N-Nope! It's nothing.
Oh.
That's the bell.
Quickly head to your seats.
To Each Their Own Figure
Hey! Nice to see you two.
Well, come on in.
R-Right!
Thanks for always looking after my sister.
Ah!
Help yourself to an afternoon snack.
Thank...
Thank you very much.
Whoops. We'll need some milk.
Hmm, Nayu's got friends home!
He's the person we saw after the entrance ceremony!
Yeah-
I can't believe he's her brother!
Thanks for the food!
Delicious!
For someone interested in schoolgirls,
he's got some real cooking talent.
Come on! We're over that misunderstanding, right?!
Keigo-san, don't you have to go to a meeting?
Oh no, you're right!
Your brother has to work at this time?
Yup! Keigo-san's an underwear designer.
Underwear?
Yup! Here are some samples of his work.
He's male, but this is amazing.
That design's cute, isn't it?
This looks like it would fit you perfectly!
The size...
"AA-cup?"
Would this bra fit me?
That has a wire, so I think this would be better.
This bra's double-layered,
and since your chest is sensitive, it should be perfect.
I see.
Choosing underwear isn't really something I can do by myself...
And sometimes they don't look the way they feel.
T-That's true!
Um, I've got a request for you two!
Underwear Club Advertising
Fitting Plan
"Underwear Club Advertising-"
"Fitting Plan"?
Yes!
Girls our age, like we saw just now, probably have a lot of questions about which underwear is best for them.
That's why if we help them develop an interest in underwear after fitting them, they should-
Wait a moment.
What is a "fitting"?
Um... It's finding underwear that fits someone properly,
and giving advice on how to wear it comfortably for a long time, I guess.
Yeah, I think we've got it.
Then what did you want us to do?
Y-Yeah...
I'd like you to become models...
Eh?!
Wha- That'd mean-
Stripping down to our underwear in front of everyone?
Yes, but of course boys won't be allowed in.
That's obvious, but...
I thought I'd do it alone at first,
but if I could get you to help me, then
I thought I'd be able to help people with large or petite breasts...
Large | Petite
Who's "petite" now?!
I'm sorry!
Why you! Why you! Why you-
But if they can learn how important fitting is,
I think they might be interested in the Underwear Club.
No matter what,
I want everyone to know how fluffy and cute underwear is,
and how comfortable it is to wear underwear that fits perfectly.
Well, disregarding "petite", it sounds like a decent idea.
Normally, in PE, we all undress anyway.
Then you'll...?
I'll help you out.
Really?
Warriors do not stray from their words.
Thank you, Yako-chan!
Hey, don't jump at me!
Haruka, you'll do it too, right?
Don't worry about it so much.
Do you think that girls like us need a fitting?
Yeah. While our breasts are developing,
it's definitely best to find the perfect size.
If we could help even in the slightest...
I might be saying strange stuff again...
No, it's not strange.
What's strange is my...
Huh?! This is bad! It's almost my curfew!
Thanks so much for today.
Next time, let's just have fun.
Keigo-san would be pleased, too!
Nayu, you really look up to your brother, huh?
Eh?
You're always adding "san" after his name.
For you, someone who makes underwear is definitely an important person, huh?
That's partly right,
but it's also because he became my
brother after my mother remarried.
My mum and dad died in an accident.
Now I live with Keigo-san.
But you know, we can talk about anything.
I'm truly glad that Keigo-san's my brother.
Seems like she's got a lot going on, too.
Yeah...
Um...
I'd like you to see this.
"Giant Breasts Rankings"?!
What's with this?!
This morning, some boys dropped it and I picked it up.
That's why you've been looking ill all this time!
People I don't know have been pointing at me...
It kind of makes me wonder if I'm at fault for having breasts like these...
The ones at fault are the boys.
They really don't have any subtlety, do they?
I'll say this now: you aren't in the wrong at all.
So don't worry about it anymore.
Got it?
Thank you.
Um, actually, I felt a bit shaky,
when I was listening to Nayu-chan talk.
When she was talking about her parents and Keigo-san?
Nayu-chan never says anything about it, right?
And yet she's so lively and... always so cheerful...
And yet I'm worried over an insignificant bit of paper.
To be honest, I'm scared and embarrassed to be seen by others just wearing my underwear.
But I want to do something for Nayu-chan!
Haruka...
Not out of pity or anything!
Yeah, I understand.
But don't force yourself if you can't do it.
Yeah...
Class Representative Meeting
Well then, if there are no questions,
that's it for today's representative meeting.
So that girl's a class representative too?
Hmph! Using her position as an honour student.
Hmm? Hamachi-kun?
It's Ko-machi.
Remember it, will you?!
K-Komachi-kun, what are you doing here?
I'm Class E's representative!
More importantly, what's that scribble there?!
Ah! This is, um-
Ah, that's it!
Thank you! I've been meaning to thank you for a while.
T-Thank me?
Oh...
Thanks to you, I have an idea to get more members to join the Underwear Club.
So first off, I think I'll have an explanatory meeting.
Don't get more friendly than necessary with me!
Sorry.
I wonder if people will come?
You've posted notices about the meeting, right?
I finally finished weeding the back of the school.
Basically, you're asking for permission to use an empty classroom, right?
That's right.
I understand.
On that note, what are you going to do as a "demonstration"?
A fitting.
Eh? A fitting...?
Ah, it's a bit difficult to explain with words. Actually...
You! What were you looking at?!
But sensei's got such a great figure, but she's not taking care of it-
Huh?!
Perhaps my classroom would work?
...Yes!
Hayama-san, what are you doing this time?
Sensei, one moment...
Hayama-san?!
Keep it together, Tamaki!
The proper reaction to this would be...
Stop this at once, Hayama-san!
You and I are teacher and student-
This is unacceptable for our relationship, or better put...
Agh, this is bad, Sensei!
Your valuable F-cups are turning into two-stepped breasts!
Since your bra doesn't fit properly,
your breasts are being squeezed too much!
Look, the top's being separated!
Just as I thought!
The bodice line has a wire mark!
"Bodise?"
It's the contour below the breasts.
Sensei, haven't you ever thought your bra seemed tight?
Ah, I suppose so.
Occasionally, I think the lower part of my chest hurts-
That's just it!
Letting the wire dig into your chest is dangerous!
In extreme cases, the ribs could be deformed.
Sensei! You've got to choose underwear that fits you!
If you do, your breasts will look better,
and most importantly, it will protect your body!
Underwear can protect my body?
Yes! So, I think you need to learn more about underwear.
This is why I want to do a fitting,
and have everyone learn about underwear.
Hayama-san...
Oi... That's all fine, but...
There is a male here!
I forgot about that-
Have some sense, you moron!
I'm sorry, Sensei...
I just really love underwear, and, um...
Hayama-san.
Y-Yes?
I'll be there that day!
As long as I'm there, I'll allow the fitting!
Sensei!
Hayama-san... You really are a bit odd,
but you're a good girl, working hard for the sake of your passion!
The day has come at least!
Anyway,
please change into these!
You're looking extremely excited today too, huh?
Hmm? Yako-chan, your chest...
Hasn't it got bigger?
Ah, um- It's growing, after all.
Tissue?
Why the tissues?
Because...
If I wear underwear in front of everyone,
they'll find out I'm flat-chested, won't they?
But, I really did want to help you, so...
Yako-chan...
I see...
Those tissues are your courage.
Thank you, Yako-chan.
Instead of tissues, should we try a thin pad?
Is that okay?
Yes! Here you go.
Thank you for coming along with us too, Haruka-chan.
It's fine... It's to help you, Nayu-chan.
Also, it's something that I've decided to do.
They're already gathering.
They're an hour early!
Are you people from the Underwear Club?
It's not a club yet, but...
Hey, what's a push-up bra?
What kind of bra would be good for my chest?
They said Underwear Club would be naughty and yet,
they are really interested.
It's about their own bodies; of course they'd have some questions.
Shouldn't you have started by now?
There's a lot of things we'd like to ask...
I-I understand. It's a little too soon, but...
Let us begin!
Mizuno-sensei's not here yet, is that all right?
It's no problem, no problem! Absolutely no problem!
Choosing a Bra
IMPORTANT
...and for people with larger breasts,
the way you put on a bra is important...
Haruka-chan, can I ask you to show them?
Ah... yes...
What should I do? I'm scared.
What if I get weird looks again?
Haruka.
That's right...
Everyone has problems, but they're not running from them.
No, I'm fine.
Wow, how beautiful!
They look fantastic!
I'm jealous!
You could wear any mature bra you want.
Ah, um...
Um, now then, Haruka-chan.
Er... yes!
I'm going to put my hands inside the bra, is that all right?
Your hands?
I just want to confirm that your breasts aren't being pressed into your armpits.
Y-Yes...
Doing this, if your breasts start to move out to the back,
you can place them back in with your hands.
There wasn't anything scary about that.
Nayu-chan's soft touch...
somehow, it felt good.
Thank you, Haruka-chan.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Why is... my face getting hot...?
So that's how you place them in the cup!
Underwear's quite important, isn't it?
I've got a great feeling about this.
With this, I might even get some members!
Stop pushing, I can't see!
Idiot, your voice is too loud!
What are you two doing?!
Oh no, peeping toms?!
Haruka-chan, put on some clothes.
Mhm. Still ten minutes before it begins.
I made it with time left over!
What are you all doing?!
I don't know! This guy suddenly...
Don't lie! You red-handed peeping tom.
Let's go already...
Wait!
Come on, stop this!
That's enough! Stop this at once!
And what sort of commotion is this?!
Honestly. We've got two class representatives here,
and this still happens?
I'm very sorry...
I went ahead and...
I see.
Gathering members for the Underwear Club?
And where are these prospective members?
T-They...
Pay attention!
You couldn't have actually gathered them, correct?
Everyone knew this was a ploy to attract the attention of the boys.
That's not it. Not at all!
If so, then how do you explain Nozoki's presence?
That...
From now on,
to prevent more commotions like this,
I will not allow any activities relating to this Underwear Club.
Cheer up, Nayu-chan.
We could do things other than forming a club.
We'll think about it together. Okay?
Thank you.
Sorry.
We finally got to collaborate and now...
It's my fault that...
Nayu...
There's some amazing underwear!
If you wear this, you'd probably catch a cold, you know!
You're definitely right.
Why's it got this shape?
It's called an open-back girdle,
it's a sort of correctional underwear that pulls the bottom together.
Of course Nayu-chan would know this!
T-Then, what's this?!
Hole
I have never seen panties like these!
Are you supposed to put your crotch through this or something?
Even you don't know, Nayu-chan?
What a bunch of virgins.
That underwear is used for sex, right?
You didn't even know this,
and you wanted to form an Underwear Club.
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
I hope that I can grow as big as Mizuno-sensei!
But then you'd have a lot of problems.
Your shoulders get sore, your chest sweats,
and you can't wash your belly button, it's really troublesome!
I was talking about my height, though...
Between
an
Adult
and
Child
Eh?
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra!