Are ya making curry fer dinner? Shinpei's curry?
Ushio?!
Again?
Quit acting like ya saw a ghost.
Yer only supposed to appear on the 24th!
What?
Why do ya know that?
Listen, Shinpei.
Ya might not believe this,
but something terrible happens on the 24th.
Everyone gets swallowed up by some
black shadow monster and disappears.
Wait... Are ya saying...
that ya came from that festival too?
What?
Ya did too?
I washed my eyes, so I feel a bit better now.
Wh-What?
That smell! Are ya making curry?
Y-Yes.
Dang, I wish I thought of that.
Wow, yer stomach growled so loud!
Just like Sis.
Thank goodness.
That means yer feeling better.
I guess so...
I gotta calm down.
Dice onions
Grate garlic and ginger
Take a bird's-eye view of the curry recipe and relax.
Roughly chop tomatoes
Julienne the peppers
Cut chicken thighs into small pieces, salt
Add 1 tbsp veg. oil, 3 tbsp butter to pan,
saute onions, garlic, ginger
Add tomatoes
Th-This situation isn't good.
Simmer
Add 3 tbsp weak wheat flour
Add 2 tbsp curry powder, 1 tbsp salt,
and keep simmering (roux complete)
Move finished roux to a pot
Fry chicken in separate pan
Ms. Nagumo, this is way beyond "unexpected"!
Sorry I took so long to get back, Shinpei.
That Mr. Karikiri sure can talk.
Welcome back, Alain.
It's almost finished.
Mio, why ain'tcha helping?
My job's eating!
Smells great. Ushio used to love that.
In five minutes, Alain goes to the washroom, and Mio goes to the bathroom.
Go to my room then.
Don't be seen.
Does she even understand this situation?!
Lie on the phone to Totsumura
Tell Sou I'll call him tomorrow
O-Okay, all done!
Lastly, add the peppers and salt to taste
Huh? Where are ya going?
Oh, uh... I'm gonna eat in my room.
With two plates?
W-Well, I'm super hungry.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Curry! Curry! Curry!
Th-This is... the curry chant!
Memento
Shinpei's curry!
Damn it. Why is this happening?
Don't let the words and the
appearance of shadows affect you.
Wow!
Can I eat?
Sure.
Yay! Thanks fer this meal!
Somehow, this shadow Ushio looped back with me.
Yum!
That has to be it.
How'd ya get here?
What?
I walked.
I woke up on Omoto Beach fer some reason.
Don't worry.
No one saw me.
It's a monster!
I'm like a monster.
I'll make sure no one sees me again.
Monster?
N-No, I wouldn't...
I wouldn't say that.
Wh-What was that?!
It really tickled!
Did ya do something?
Oh, uh, no.
Sorry.
Jeez, I got goosebumps.
I can kill it.
Just stab its shadow.
It's so good!
Look, it's not even a bit on guard.
But it did save me that time.
It...
Tokyo?
Alain's friend is in Tokyo.
I'm gonna stay there and go to culinary school.
I won't go to a high school in Wakayama.
What?
I made up my mind.
Ya never told me.
It's not like I need to tell ya.
How can ya make such an important decision by yerself?
Why can't I decide for myself?!
I'm not a Kofune.
I need to start earning my own living.
I hate constantly being a burden on y'all!
A burden?
Do you hate it here?
What? Why're ya asking that?!
No, Ushio.
Enough! I didn't even need to tell ya!
I'm...
I'm the one who's had enough!
in love with you!
I don't want us to become family like this.
Hey, Shinpei.
Today's yer last day.
I want yer curry fer dinner.
What?
I need to pack.
I'll make it fer ya next time.
Ya dummy.
There was no "next time."
At one point, that's what I thought.
Ya finally made it fer me.
I'm glad.
I got to eat yer curry again.
I'm glad I'm alive.
Is it good?
I want seconds!
It's not as good when Dad makes it.
I really like yers the best.
This is Ushio.
She's Ushio.
I see.
I'm glad.
Hey, Shinpei.
Will the same thing happen on the 24th?
Yes.
I'm trying to stop that.
I'll help too.
I can't stand that monster ruining Hitogashima's summer festival.
And I definitely can't let Mio and the others disappear!
Right. Me too.
Let's stop it together!
Okay!
Can ya copy humans?
I guess not.
It's currently 8:45 p.m.
Shadow Mio should appear in ten minutes.
How does your location look, Nezu?
No issues.
Just a little breeze.
There's enough light in town.
Any contact from Shinpei?
None.
Don't rely on his foresight too much, Ryuunosuke.
Prey never moves the way we expect it to.
Hunters always need to adapt.
Roger that.
Hizuru
Any issues?
It's from Ms. Nagumo.
Should I mention Ushio, or lie to her?
Hizuru
Any issues?
Either way...
Shinpei?
Oh, yeah.
Why're ya still dressed like that?
I-It's weird to wear a swimsuit in the house.
Huh?
Oh yeah.
Why...
Why didn't it bother me until now?
H-Hey!
Wh-What the hell did ya do?!
It wasn't me!
My swimsuit disappeared! Why?!
I-Is it 'cause ya copied the swimsuit?
Whatever! Just gimme something to wear!
What? Mio's shadow is coming?
Did ya lock up?
We're fine.
Although, locking up probably won't help much.
It only takes a tiny gap fer a shadow to slip through.
Really? Lemme try!
Don't worry.
It hasn't come in here.
Not once.
Shin?
It's Mio! Hide!
Are ya finished eating?
I wanna wash the dishes.
Oh, the dishes. Sure.
Yeah. Ya all done?
What? Ya used two spoons?
Two glasses too.
Is that so strange?
Nope, that isn't strange at all!
Why'd ya suddenly drop yer accent?
Sis ain't here, is she?
Ya made this bowl fer her, didn't ya?
I'm sure she's here.
On Hitogashima, souls return home as guardian spirits.
Mr. Karikiri always said that.
O-Oh...
Ya can leave the bowls.
I'll wash them later.
Okay.
The food was great, Shin.
Yikes.
That was a close one.
Mio does have good instincts.
Ah! Whoa!
Wh-What is it?
Forgot something?
What the...
It's not...
Ushio!
That hurt, dammit!
I can't beat it in a fight.
But if I'm going to die anyway, I'll try everything I can do!
Come on then, Mio.
I'll take ya on!
Sh-Shinpei.
Sis, why are ya on his side?
He's with Nezu and Minakata, who kill shadows.
Guess the fake doesn't have the same instincts.
I love Shinpei.
What's wrong with helping someone I love?!
But yer dead.
Ya died, Sis.
Yer dead and turned to ashes!
Shin—
What'd I tell ya?
It hurts...
Why?
Shin...
I also...
Ushio.
Hey, stay with me, Ushio!
Coming in.
M-Ms. Nagumo.
Why get in my way?
I'm glad you're safe, Shinpei.
But look at that.
It's a shadow.
I'm going to kill it, so get out of my way.
I-I won't!
Did that shadow get into your head?
I told you they can trick you if you keep talking to them.
I know you begrudge shadows and want to kill them all!
But this one protected me twice, sacrificing itself!
It doesn't think before it acts.
Doesn't consider the consequences.
It's that idiot Ushio, through and through!
So please heal its injury!
Like you did to me!
I'm begging you!
Unbelievable.
Letting it go is one thing, but actually healing it?
If you side with shadows, I'll kill you too.
That's fine!
I'll just loop back and persuade you next time!
Shinpei.
Where's Mio?
Is the real Mio okay?
Sh-She's...
The real one is in the bath.
I checked.
Really?
I see.
Great.
It's the same voice.
Ms. Nagu... Can ya... hear...
The voice that brought me to this island.
Adapt?
Fine.
Show me your injury.
Kofune Ushio sent me that message.
Summer Time Rendering
No way!
Wait, what?!
My arm disappeared!
U-Ushio?
Huh? It doesn't hurt.
That injury is a projection of the
damage felt by the actual shadow.
A normal method won't heal it.
So be careful of—
If it doesn't hurt, it ain't a big deal.
Ya got over that too quick.
You're so big now.
I'm Minakata Hizuru.
You probably don't remember me.
I used to come to Bistro Kofune a lot.
Really?
Sorry. I don't remember that.
Listen to this.
Summer festival...
Everybody was killed by shadows...
Only Ajiro Shinpei... can stop...
We need yer...
Please help. Please.
Do you recall this message?
What is that?
It's my voice.
This is the reason I came here.
So you don't remember?
I see.
Fine, forget it.
There's a bigger problem.
Why'd the shadow Mio go inside the Kofune home?
The shadow Mio knew that Shiori was defeated.
Apparently, they're sharing information.
Perhaps Mio was aware of us and decided to eliminate us.
It was after Nezu and me before,
but now it knew that Ajiro Shinpei was also with us.
So Mio entered your house to kill Ajiro Shinpei.
Is it because I went with you to Koba Mart?
But how did it find out?
We destroyed all of the shadows that were there.
In any case, I can't work with you anymore.
As long as you stay with Ushio's shadow, at least.
She may have saved you and doesn't seem a threat to us.
However, if she's broken,
we don't know when she might get fixed.
That's the most we can do.
Ms. Nagumo!
At three o'clock tomorrow, Mio's shadow killed you in the forest near the shrine!
We killed Mio, but there may be others.
Please don't die!
Your fate isn't set in stone.
This is a rare opportunity to prove that.
Bistro Kofune
July 23rd
Shinpei.
Good morning.
Yer awake?
I'm hungry. And thirsty.
I'll bring you something.
Thanks!
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Thanks, Tokiko.
I feel better.
No, I'm sorry I kept ya up.
Right.
Bye.
Good morning, Shin.
I'm up already, so ya don't have to come wake me, okay?
J-Just wanted ya to know.
Uh... okay.
She can't come wake me if I'm already up.
Wait, Shin!
Mio gave ya this?
Yes, this is the original.
The original...
Does it make ya remember anything?
Like before ya died?
Bistro Kofune
Will ya think about it?
Where are ya going?
Bistro Kofune
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
We're opening the restaurant today.
I see.
That sounds like Dad.
Yes, a restaurant is always there.
It has to stay the same.
Alain always said that.
I need to protect this simple everyday life.
Hey, Shinpei.
Sorry. Am I early?
Sorry fer the wait.
Hey.
Here.
An umbrella? It's super sunny today.
Just take it.
What's with ya? Such a weirdo.
I'll get straight to the point.
I need to tell ya something about Ushio's death.
Okay.
Ligature marks, right?
Someone mighta killed me.
Right.
Actually—
Wait, who the hell?!
Ushio, ya don't need the disguise anymore.
Huh? Ushio?
Wait... No... It can't be...
Ushio!
Yo.
He's frozen.
We told Sou everything.
He quietly listened to everything we said.
Sorry.
If only I'd done more to save her.
If only...
I know being sorry won't bring her back!
But please...
hit me!
If not, I—
What a kick!
Stand up, Sou!
Feel better now?
We're relying on ya here.
Quit yer whining!
The private beach behind the elementary school.
So this is where I died.
She really doesn't remember.
No.
Oh, that's my phone.
I wanna see inside, but it's locked.
Huh?
The password was changed.
Oh, it opened.
Huh?
With the fingerprint scanner.
Open yer email, memos, photos... Anything could help.
Friday was the 20th, right?
There's a video file from the morning of the day before I died.
Friday
That's it!
Wait a sec.
I'll play it.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Fall, My Tears