What?!  A huge Roman force has appeared at Seize's border, in No-Man's Land?!
Aisha!
What was that gunshot just now?
We've secured the Roman soldier!
Is she dead?
No, she's still breathing.
Well done!
We will now link up with the 1st and 3rd Divisions at the border—
What are you doing—
Don't move!
Move and I'll shoot.
Captain!
Colonel, please have your men fall back to outside the bastion perimeter.
What exactly is going on here?
Mutiny!
They've barricaded themselves in the bastion,
and taken our own commander hostage!
What did you say?
Luckily, it missed her internal organs.
Then...
For the moment, she should be fine.
Thank you, Yumina-san!
Well done.
That woman will become a scapegoat to start a war.
She's not worth as much if she's dead.
What's the meaning of this?!
For this past month,
we've been tracking movements of the Roman army along our country's rearward borders.
It's most likely just posturing meant to influence the peace talks.
They see us as fools.
But the Archduke passed down these pussyfooted orders that we absolutely could not become the aggressors.
That's why we need something that will push them to attack us first.
Something like a crying, screaming prisoner of war executed before their very eyes.
You can't possibly—
The peace talks are a farce!
Rome must be destroyed!
Isn't that right, Kannagi Noel?
Or should I say, my dear ally, Witch of Helvetia.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
Stop!
Noel was just used by you people!
Noel-san, you really do have something to do with the Invisible Death Reaper?
"Invisible Death Reaper"?
Named as one of the greatest geniuses ever in academy history,
the one who revived a former-era bio-weapons plant, the Invisible Death Reaper,
is that little girl sitting right over there.
Your talent is invaluable.
Return under my control—
Kureha-chan, throw that man into the underground distillery.
My comrades are already in the process of confronting the Roman army.
One small spark will set the entire thing off.
Back to the battlefield again, huh?
And I thought it was finally over, too...
We've got terrible luck, the both of us.
The Colonel has been confined in the distillery.
Good work, Kureha-chan.
Why don't you have something to eat?
These are some baked goods I picked up at Treize.
They're tasty!
Naomi-san, you're still here?
I'll leave if it really gets dangerous.
This is really such a mess!
The fire maidens are supposed to protect the city...
But we're the ones getting the city involved in the fight!
Actually, about that...
When we were hiding, I asked Aisha about the legend of the fire maidens.
And she said that in Roman literature, a completely different story has been passed down.
What kind?
Fire maidens protect lives.
W-What?!
It's time to switch.
I'm fine!
I'd only worry if you were the one out here.
And anyway, can you even fire a gun at someone?
If I really believed that it was the right
thing to do, I think I could.
Really?
I'm a bastion maiden, too, after all.
Like our great predecessors, the fire maidens...
What?
Did you believe that?  That arbitrary Roman fairy tale?
Yeah.
It somehow sits right with me.
Fire maidens protect lives.
I really think that might be the case.
What's the matter?
I can hear it...
Huh?
Hear what?
Kanata!
No matter how good her ears are, there's no way she's going to be able to hear you from here.
The ceasefire signal?
Yes!  I heard it!
Are you sure?
Hundred-percent!
It's too early for celebration!
She might've misheard it,
and even if she didn't, there's still no way to know whether it means the peace talks were completed or not.
At any rate, we should relay this to Colonel Hopkins—
We have a huge problem!
When I went to take food to the Colonel, he wasn't there!
What?
I'm grateful you're safe, sir!
We will commence the attack in ten minutes.
Colonel, sir!
Do you really think they'll listen?
There's no harm in trying, is there?
Understood.
Pointless.
The Colonel... was laughing.
When he saw that the Death Reaper I had revived had killed so many people,
he was laughing so hard...
He... will kill... will fight until no one's left.
But I helped him do that.
It's my fault.
If you feel that way, then you'll just need to save more lives than you've taken,
Noel-san.
Aisha!
A ceasefire, you say?
Don't make me laugh!
But you really can trust that girl's hearing!
That's right!
We'll vouch for her!
She's a little happy-go-lucky, forgetful, and childish,
and isn't sexy at all, but we will!
She wouldn't lie!
Restrain everyone here!
Do you really want to go to war that badly?!
War drives forward civilization and science.
I want to bring back the glory humanity once held within its grasp!
What did you say?!
The Roman army is going to begin its attack tomorrow morning!
Then there's no way to prevent this war anymore, is there?
Naomi-san was detained.
Let's go.
That's ridiculous!
Our opponent is the Demon of Vingt!
But I want the sound I was entrusted with to transcend!
You're just doing as you please!
That's selfish!
What do you think will happen if you make selfish decisions and act for yourself like that?
We're soldiers!
It's been said that the world is already at its end.
But I like this world.
I like this city.
I love all the people here.
To give up like that... I just can't.
Kanata...
Please.
Stop the war.
Aisha-san said the same thing.
But I...
I also killed people as a soldier like you, Noel.
I... you... the same.
You have suffered enough.
That's why I forgive you,
even if nobody else will forgive you.
That's why I...
You'll... forgive me?
Thank you, Aisha.
If we go, there's no way we can turn back.
Even so, you're fine with this, right?
Yeah.
Then I... have nothing more to say.
Do as you like.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
You've been offering objections all along just for our sakes, haven't you?
I just...
Of course I'm against having a girl the same age as me tortured!
But Rio-senpai's gone and...
And Noel and Kanata are both so lax...
So I thought I had no choice but to be tough and...
I'm sorry I'm such an unreliable captain...
Kureha-chan.
Let's go, everyone.
Let's.
May all of the gods bring blessings upon the fire maidens.
Main converter reactor, output rising.
FAP, FAC, DMR, ECP — all normal.
Superconductor circuit functioning within stable parameters.
Firing control systems are also a go.
Primary and secondary cannons are up and running!
Release all joint locks!
W-Weight reduction system in operation.
Coefficient is about minus five.
Dispatch preparations complete.
If we do it just like in training, we'll be fine.
Let's go, my little ones!
Right!
Prepare to fire the main cannon!
Prepare high-explosive projectiles!
High-explosive projectiles, loaded!
Alignment set!
Kana-chan, the signal!
Right!
"Commencing attack"?!
Fire!
It's Kanata-neechan!
The Takemikazuchi...
They've restored that hunk of former-era technology by so much...
Notify all tanks!
Use all of your power to stop them!
Begin the attack!
We won't let you through!
We don't want any more war!
Don't get in those girls' way!
If you want to get through, you'll have to get past us first!
That's right!
Now what will you do, Mister Demon of Vingt?
Move out!
We'll join up with our forces at the rear!
Fire maidens protect lives.
We will leave it to you, Kanata-san.
A long time ago...
Long before the world became what it is today...
An angel whom God sent to punish the world
was injured, and rested his wings in a town on the western border.
The ones who saved that angel were the maidens who lived in that city's bastion.
Though the angel had been sent to destroy them, seeing his injured form evoked compassion in the maidens,
and, borrowing the power of a giant spider, they sheltered him at the bottom of the valley.
In order to hold back the blood, one by one the maidens embraced his neck.
And as thanks, the angel granted unto the maidens a golden horn.
But before long, the citizens learned of the angel's existence,
and set fire to the valley.
The maidens were also caught up in the fire, and thus the angel lost his head, and so passed on.
At that moment, armies of angels suddenly appeared, taking over the skies.
But then a miraculous thing occurred.
Suddenly, a sonorous sound resonated through the sky,
and the angels departed.
What saved the people's lives
had been the sound of the golden horn, bestowed in trade for the last maiden's final breath.
Hey, do you remember that girl?
The one you gave the caramels to?
She's gonna get caught up in this too, isn't she?
All hands, prepare to charge!
There's nothing we can do about it.
That's what being a soldier means.
Charge!
What?
What is that?
It's being operated by allied forces!
It's from the...
1121st Platoon!
It's the ceasefire signal!
Yes...
It's the Roman military!
Commander, sir!
We can't quit here!
Prepare the main cannon!
No good.  They're not stopping.
Captain!
Kana-chan!
That girl...
What are you doing?!
What happened to the attack?!
Fire!  Open fire!
Both sides, lower your arms!
I am the second heir to the royal line of Helvetia and the fiancée to the Holy Roman Emperor,
Rio Kazumiya Arcadia!
In the name of my father, the Archduke of Helvetia,
and in the name of the Roman Emperor,
I declare that the peace talks have reached their conclusion,
and there shall be no more fighting!
Both sides are to disband posthaste!
This is an Imperial command!
Those who disobey will be punished in the name of both leaders!
Impossible...
Then, we...
Don't need to fight anymore, do we?!
Hooray!
Missy!
Sergeant!
Wow, it's really springtime now, isn't it?
Oh yeah, Noel, that letter Aisha sent you before...
What'd it say?
"My wounds have healed well and I'm now practicing my trumpet on a daily basis."
Translate it!
She's doing well and practicing the trumpet now.
Is that so?  How nice!
Man, we get letters from Rome, but not from the capital.
I'm sure she's busy.
She's a princess, after all!
But you know, even on the battlefield,
she was so quickly surrounded by everyone
that we weren't even able to talk to her.
Oh!  I can hear Krause-san's bike!
She's here, she's here!
I'm so looking forward to meeting our little newbie!
I'm gonna work her really—
As of today, I have been transferred to the 1121st platoon.
I am Second Lieutenant Rio Kazumiya Arcadia.
Captain Phylicia Heideman,
I request permission to take up this post.
Granted.
Though we don't use rank or class here, Rio.
Um...
That Roman Emperor is actually a pretty understanding guy.
H-He said that as a reward for stopping the war,
he'd grant me any wish.
So I...
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Senpai!
Welcome back, Rio!