Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home
Let's say goodbye
Night falls to draw me in
This wild world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Master, how are you?
I'm sorry I just disappeared.
Are you worried about me?
Are you nuts?!
Die in a fire!
I'm in the Mirror Capital now.
Welcome, Little Sister
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
I have to get going.
Okay.
Sure is a gloomy face there!
What a moody little brat!
Shut it.
Central Axis
General Agency
Shrine
It won't be long.
Okay.
Thanks.
Take care of the cottage.
Okay.
If something is wrong, just tell the priests.
Also...
Count your tears, crybaby!
Inari won't be around to save the day, coward!
That's enough, you two.
The familiars don't mean it like that.
Don't mind them.
You have to stand your ground now that you're part of Shrine.
Planetary General
Agency Shrine
Don't let it get to you, whatever they say.
Okay, Master.
I can't believe the kid the fox took in is one of us now.
He's sort of a free spirit, you know?
How impudent.
What's the fox thinking?
Is she human or spirit to begin with?
Just look at her red eyes.
Don't skip practice.
Toughen up and pay them back.
I'm sure your mother wants that too, Koto.
Do your best, kiddo!
Next time we meet we'll play with you.
Take care!
It's Koto!
You're not gonna stop Koto?
Koto!
If you're going to beat him up, pay attention to your stance!
Okay!
Those two are abnormal!
The bearer of the fox mask should know how to behave!
I demand that the chief priest hear about this!
Inari, Koto!
You heard the man.
I think it's his fault because he was messing around during practice!
I also think he should have apologized!
And he shouldn't be so weak!
You seem a little stressed out to me.
You should take a few days off.
I can take care of your students in the meantime.
No! No! I don't want that, Master!
But he feels he is at an impasse with his educational ideals.
No, no, no, no!
Someone should help him.
Mind your own business!
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Good morning, Koto.
Good morning!
I have a secret.
You're sleeping with your mask on again.
You're so weird.
Koto...
Morning!
Morning, you tomboy.
This place is so big, Master.
Isn't it nice to have so many rooms?
So bitter!
Horrible...
Should we look up all the harmful stuff in burned bread?
Don't waste your day.
What's your problem, guys?
Master, you're pretty useless outside your job, huh?
You wound me.
Wonder if I should start cooking again.
Not a chance.
Just put some sugar on if you think it's too bitter.
Over my dead body!
Where are you going today?
To assist the observers.
Just assist?
What's wrong with that?
When are you changing plane?
Nine o'clock, I think...
Time to stay in school
Don't rush me, Koto!
Might have to work all night!
Hurry up, fox!
Take... care...
Koto!
I knew you'd be here.
I was looking for you.
Katsura?
I can tell you've forgotten.
A checkup!
Bingo.
I forgot! Sorry!
Sorry! I forgot!
Sorry!
Koto...
I have a secret.
Inari's on bodyguard duty all day?
Such a waste.
You could put a special unit to much better uses.
Even the head priest watches his step when he deals with the old families.
I heard you got into a fight with some noble kids.
I didn't.
Nobody'd call that a real fight.
Hey!
I like that, Koto!
That's the spirit! Beat your way through!
He must be stupid.
He must be.
That hurt, dammit!
You messed up my vision just now!
You trying to kill me?
You can't die, Kichijouji.
That's not the issue!
Out of my face!
What if you damaged the data?!
You worry about that now?
What do you mean?!
She's got a point.
What?!
You should have it checked out.
Katsura...
Koto!
You always get along so well.
Head Priest!
I recommend Koto for an early combat assignment.
I have been amply assured of her willingness!
Kichijouji's just weak.
Damn you!
Is that so?
I expect much of you, disciple of the fox.
Sure!
Your prowess delights me.
However, you shouldn't neglect your studies.
And you! Don't spoil her!
Nothing of the sort.
It's too late anyway.
I get the complaints if she skips class.
Geez, you just can't get used to school, can you?
Shrine is trusted with protecting the order of this world,
and has done so since ancient times with pride and skill.
23         Sakaki Yuuta
24      Hinohara Enishi
25               Koto
Koto! Koto!
Fang!
Grand!
Dung!
G again?!
Get ready for the last fight of your life!
I thought you fled from me, Koto!
Hachiman...
Today I shall defeat you!
You said that yesterday too.
Silence!
Fight me!
Come at me!
Are you making fun of me?!
I don't have anything else with me.
You think you can defeat me using that?!
Yeah.
Fine!
Once more!
Once more...
Once... more...
Just give up.
A valiant effort.
Let me die a man's death!
Nope.
Damn it!
Deal with it.
Shut up!
A man of the Hachiman family won't accept defeat!
This brings shame to our name!
Living the tough life of a noble.
Shut up!
Don't cry.
You used to cry so much!
Then one day you just toughened up.
The hell are you?
Come on, Hachiman.
Everyone knows.
I'm the foundling of the fox.
Hey!
Good luck fighting for your family!
That's not what I meant!
And tomorrow you're eating dust!
Yeah, sure.
Welcome home, Koto!
Good to be back home!
There it is!
Koto
Mom...
Master...
Master?
Koto
Koto...
Koto?
I have a secret.
Welcome back!
I'm home.
When did you arrive?
Just now.
And you?
Just now!
What is it?
I thought you were asleep.
I was awake!
What?
Koto?
Did you cry today, Dad?
Huh?
We have a secret.
Still she haunts me, phantomwise,
Alice moving under skies
Never seen by waking eyes.
Children yet, the tale to hear,
Eager eye and willing ear,
Lovingly shall nestle near.
In a Wonderland they lie,
Dreaming as the days go by...
Good morning!
You're mumbling to yourself again.
Mumbling?
You were thinking about the Mirror Capital again, weren't you?
I wonder.
You're always lying!
I know it!
Ouch!
You put your whole weight into that kick, didn't you?
I guess I should praise you for taking practice so seriously.
Of course!
I'll be the strongest one Shrine has!
And you used to cry so much...
All teachers delight at seeing their students improve.
I might be stronger than you one day.
That'd make you the new master.
I wanna go and look for my mom.
I want to meet her and talk to her.
It'd be nice if she was pretty.
She'd be surprised, right?
I wanna ask about you too.
But you know the truth, don't you?
Yeah.
Koto, I'm sure you'll make it there one day.
Where summer dies and is born anew.
Paradise lost.
The place beyond the mirror, where the
gravestones of memories stand in neat rows.
I'm sure.
Chapter Six
Present (2) / Council of Three
You don't turn up here very often.
Try to look happier when you do.
They seem a happy bunch to me.
I had to deal with rampaging devils.
I'm tired.
Hate to hear it...
Is what a more sympathetic man would say.
I think he does a good job.
They like him.
I'm somewhat jealous.
I'll graciously relinquish custody.
No, thanks.
Don't be like that.
Decisions made here are absolute.
Right?
Right.
I know.
Dealing with her is a little like playing with fire.
I've gotten burned plenty.
She's such a cute tomboy.
I'm expecting great things.
She has the same name and the same red eyes.
Are you telling me she's her?
I wonder.
Are you scared of the idea?
You've always been a crybaby.
Unlike you, I've changed out of my diapers.
Your clothes have the same function.
Rest easy.
You are both little boys.
There is no arguing either way that she is special.
Let us welcome our first unlikely guest since they left us.
Well then, let us pledge upon the one who came first, my siblings.
The three of us who followed...
Shall treat the others with honor...
And have no secrets.
By our great mother's name and our own,
let us follow the Ten Flawless Commandments!
I'm there, Dad.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
When Mother and Father disappeared, I didn't cry.
My brother and sister cried quite a lot,
but I was determined to hold my ground in the wide world.
That's how I could prove my worth.
The Firstborn and His
Cheerful and Nerdy Team
Next time: "The Firstborn and
His Cheerful and Nerdy Team".
That was the day the story began.