Attention!
I will now elaborate on the plan
to recapture Trost District!
First, allow me to introduce someone.
Belonging to the Training Corps,
this is Eren Jaeger!
He is the product of successful top-secret
Titan transformation research.
In his Titan form, he'll lift the large boulder,
carry it to the destroyed gate, and seal it!
Your duty is...
to protect him from other Titans
while he is carrying the boulder!
When this plan succeeds,
mankind will recapture territory from
the Titans for the first time in history!
Compared to all that mankind has lost thus far,
this may be overwhelmingly insignificant.
However, despite that, to mankind
it will be a great advance.
Eren, don't you recognize me?!
It's Mikasa!
Your family!
Dodge, Ackerman!
What's with him?!
He's just another stupid Titan, huh?
We'll modify the plan.
Until we can recover Jaeger,
we'll protect him from the Titans.
He holds valuable potential for mankind.
We can't give up on him that easily.
Where am I?
I'm at home?
Jean!
Why isn't he using his
three-dimensional maneuver device?
Don't tell me...
Is his equipment acting up?!
I'll figure something out!
Mikasa!
What's going on with the plan?
It failed.
We can't just leave Eren, so everyone's fighting.
But at this rate...
the Titans will overwhelm us with numbers!
From the back of the head to the nape...
One meter long and ten centimeters wide...
Eren, answer me.
Why do you want to see
the outside world so badly,
knowing that with even a step beyond the walls,
a living hell and cruel death might
be the only things that await?
"Why?"
It's because I was born into this world!
Eren!
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Primitive Desire
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑨
Damn.
How can I afford to be dead weight?
Will this work out somehow?
Squad Leader, this is it!
There's no one left but us!
Withdraw to the boulder for now!
Status?
Five Titans approaching from the gate!
As if I'm gonna wait until the Titans are gone!
Jean!
So it was his gear.
What's wrong?
Dammit. What the hell?
You're kidding me!
Why now?!
Jean, calm down!
Marco?
What are you doing?!
Sheesh, quit pulling our legs!
Damn, why is the trigger so stiff?
Jean!
What the hell was that?!
Right back at you!
Hurry and go!
You're all insane!
You're one to talk!
Can't believe we made it.
Look over there.
Eren...
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren's in control!
He's trying to fulfill his duty.
Now, if we can just escort him to the gate,
victory will be ours!
Defend him!
Even if we have to die in the process,
protect Eren until he reaches the gate!
Keep the Titans away at all costs!
Don't let them stop him!
We'll back Eren up!
You two, head over to Eren.
That's an order!
Understand?
Yes, sir!
Mitabi's squad?
What're they...
The Titans aren't paying attention to us!
We'll have to get closer until they do!
Turn this way, damn it!
If you don't, we'll kill you by
sticking blades up your asses!
Here they come!
We got two!
Hurry! Run to a building!
No way...
It's suicidal to stay on the ground.
They can't fight without horses or buildings.
No, we have... no other choice.
Follow Mitabi's squad!
Armin, us too.
This way!
Follow me!
My body... feels like it's gonna be crushed.
Mikasa? Armin?
What are you doing?
If you're down there, the Titans will...
Come on! Hurry up, you blockhead!
This way!
H-Hey!
No, Mitabi!
Why do you want to see
the outside world so badly?
We're all free from the moment we're born.
It doesn't matter how strong the opposition is.
There doesn't need to be flaming
water or land made of ice.
Those who witness the outside
are free like no other.
Fight.
My life is second to that desire.
It doesn't matter how fearsome the world is.
It doesn't matter how cruel the world is.
Fight.
Fight!
There's one more left!
Leave it to me!
Out of the way!
Go for it, Eren!
Fight!
Everyone...
Your deaths... weren't in vain.
Today, for the first time, mankind has...
defeated the Titans!
Yellow signal confirmed.
It appears the plan was a success!
Send in reinforcements!
Rescue the elite squad!
Currently
Disclosable
Information
History of the Battle Against the Titans Part ①
According to the oldest confirmed record,
the Titans first appeared 107 years ago.
The majority of mankind was devoured.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
History of the Battle Against the Titans Part ②
Mankind tried to oppose the Titans using cannons,
but due to the Titans' amazing vitality,
there was nothing they could do to stop them.
The remaining Titans are coming!
Let's climb the wall!
I will once we recover Eren.
Armin, how's Eren doing?
He's practically burning up!
We have to hurry over the wall.
A part of his body won't separate.
It won't come off!
We'll have to cut it.
P-Please wait!
Eren! Armin!
Mikasa?
That's...
The Wings of Liberty...
Hey, you brats.
What's going on here?
Afterwards,
thanks to the Survey Corps and the
Garrison engineers' quick response,
Wall Rose had once again
repelled the Titans' advance.
An entire day was required to eradicate
the Titans from Trost District,
with the wall's fixed cannons
firing around the clock.
High-explosive shells annihilated the
majority of the Titans swarming the wall,
and the Survey Corps eliminated
the few that remained.
Furthermore, a 4-meter-class and
7-meter-class Titan were captured alive.
On the other hand, 207 soldiers
were killed or missing in action,
and another 897 were injured.
Repelling the Titans for the first time
in history was a noteworthy feat,
but simply far too many lives had
been lost to allow for celebration.
Hey...
Is that you... Marco?
Recruit,
do you know his name?
I haven't seen him around...
But...
Not him.
I don't believe it.
Marco, what happened?
S-Someone...
Did someone see his last moments?
What's his name?
If you know, answer already.
Don't you understand, Recruit?
It's already been two days
since the gate was sealed,
but we're still not done
collecting the corpses yet.
If we delay any longer,
an epidemic could break out.
We must prevent a second disaster.
There's no time to mourn just yet.
Understand?
Belonging to the 104th Training Corps,
Leader of the 19th Squad, Marco Bott.
Marco, huh?
I'm glad you knew.
Let's move on.
What... is this?
A Titan threw it up.
They don't have a digestive system,
so after eating their fill of humans,
they throw them back up.
That's...
Damn, we won't be able to
identify anyone like this.
I'm sorry.
Apologizing won't help.
We need to put them to rest.
Do you have any questions?
The head of the Survey Corps, Commander Erwin,
and Lance Corporal Levi...
Um...
Where... am I?
As you can see, it's a dungeon.
You're currently in the
Military Police Brigade's custody.
We've only just received permission to see you.
That key is...
Yes, it's yours.
I'll return it later.
Your home—
Dr. Jaeger's basement in Shiganshina
is where the secret of the Titans lies.
Correct?
Yes, probably.
That's what my father said.
You have amnesia, and your father is missing, huh?
Sounds awfully convenient.
Levi,
I believe we've already concluded
that he has no reason to lie.
We're still very much in the dark,
but I think what's best for us now
is to question your intentions.
My... intentions?
In order to investigate your home,
we must recapture Shiganshina
District and Wall Maria.
Drastic measures are necessary
to quickly seal the gate.
Your Titan power will be crucial.
It seems our fate is controlled
by the Titans, after all.
Whether it's the Colossus Titan
or the Armored Titan,
they're likely to be the same as you.
Your intentions are the key here.
The key to freeing mankind from this despair.
I...
I'll exterminate them...
from this world...
I won't spare a single one!
Hey, answer already, scum.
What is it you want to do?
I want to join the Survey Corps
and slaughter some Titans!
Oh? Not bad.
Erwin, I'll take responsibility for him.
Tell that to the top brass.
It's not that I trust him.
If he betrays us or goes berserk,
I'll kill him on the spot.
I doubt anyone will object.
There's no one better suited for this, after all.
I'll accept your enlistment
into the Survey Corps.
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba
The special court-martial.
Eren, who was detained in the dungeon,
has been dragged to the courthouse to
appear before the top officers of each corp.
They shall decide whether he lives or die.
Eyes Yet to Be Seen
————— Eve of the Retaliation Part    —————
①