Come on. We're going to be late.
Okay!
Man, I'm so freakin' sleepy... Vision... blurring...
Geez, Katsu!
My traditional wake-up grope, just for you.
Didn't you feel the sleepiness just drain away, Asuka?
What kind of a tradition is that?!
And I thought you were the one who was sleepy, Katsu!
Sure is nice weather today, huh?
Kaminarimon
Yanagikoji Alley
Puppets?
Puppets...
Mm-hmm.
Puppets—which is to say, dolls controlled by another person.
They're also known as "marionettes" or "dummies."
Puppetry is the ninja art of manipulating such dolls
in order to mislead and disorient your opponent.
Based on what you've told me,
it sounds like the ninja who attacked you is a master puppeteer.
Puppeteer?
Puppeteer...
Yeah...
Why don't we just have one person ask the questions from now on?
So what is this puppeteer after?
Why target us?
It's too soon to tell that yet.
Hanayashiki Street
What's the matter, Ikaruga?
I just hope...
nothing bad comes from all this.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't truly smile
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Light does not coil around us like a spiral
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Go past the present and put the shadows in your crosshair
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
The Legendary Ninja Revealed
Secret Ninja Art: Phoenix Flash!
One!
Two!
Come to me, my dragon!
Secret Ninja Art: Tornado Spindel!
Secret Ninja Art: Leg Sweeper!
Secret Ninja Arts,
also known as Summoning Ninja Arts,
are special techniques known only to ninjas
that miraculously call forth a creature envisioned within the user's mind.
Ikaruga and Katsuragi, your
performance was outstanding.
Yagyu, as calamariffic as ever.
Calamariffic?
What's "calamariffic"?
Mr. Kiriya has a real way with compliments.
Ikaruga, complimenting me won't get you anywhere.
Now then...
Asuka! Hibari!
Y-Yes?!
What do you think?
Ready to show me what you're made of?
W-We'll do our best.
Um, Mr. Kiriya...
What is it, Hibari?
When we summon, it can be anything, right?
It doesn't matter if it's a real or imaginary creature.
However, the efficacy of the summon is greatly affected by the summoner's characteristics,
or in other words, "compatibility."
I thought about it for ages,
but I finally made up my mind!
I've chosen someone who
I think will fit me just great!
Oh? Then would you like to give it a try?
Okay!
I've never seen Hibari look so serious.
What on Earth is she trying to summon?
Something that fits her, eh?
It better be something sexy.
I don't understand what you mean.
Good luck, Hibari.
Please... Come to me...
Ah! It's here!
A rabbit?!
A pink rabbit?!
Alley-oop!
Boom! Boom!
Awesome...
It does a lot more damage than you'd think.
I did it! I did it!
Mm-hmm. Hibari...
That was most rabbitastic.
Thank you very much!
He really does have a way with compliments.
You did it, Hibari.
A pink bunny, huh?
And bunnies mean bunny girls!
We all gotta dress up as bunny girls now, okay?
Where did you pull that from?
Being prepared is one of
.the basics of being a ninja.
That was amazing, Hibari!
Thank you! It's your turn next, Asuka.
Ah, y-you're right...
Okay!
You're up next, Asuka.
I-I'll try my best.
Man, havin' a little bath after training is just the best!
Did you have to bring those toys in again?
Join in the fun, Ikaruga! It's great!
No, thank you. We have a shower room for a reason.
Why won't it work?
No need to rush. Take your time.
Ikaruga...
If you try to force it, you'll just stress yourself out.
I've been thinking about all the animals I like,
but it just doesn't seem to work.
Um, Ikaruga, how did you make up your mind?
How did you choose that fried-chicken-like—
It's a phoenix!
Oh, sorry about that.
And it chose me.
It chose you?
Yes. I think that's how it works with everyone.
So I'm sure one will choose you too, Asuka.
A summoned beast that fits you perfectly.
Thanks!
It's all right.
You are the great Hanzo's granddaughter.
Believe in yourself.
Yeah, you're right.
Grandpa would laugh at me if he saw me all depressed over something like this.
That's the spirit.
So I say, but still...
Grandpa...
Those short swords before you are the very pair I used until I retired.
Make use of them, and live to your full potential!
Asuka's grandfather, Hanzo, is a master famous throughout the world of ninjas.
He was also the founder of the Cabinet's
Special Intelligence Bureau Section One's
top-secret intelligence officers—
also known as the Ninja Squad.
Special Intelligence Section One
In honor of his achievements, and to provide students with a goal to strive toward,
this school also bears his name—
that of the legendary ninja Hanzo.
I need to try my very hardest, so that I
don't bring shame to Grandpa's name.
Asuka, come play with us!
Katsu!
C'mon, it's fun!
Aw, I just got changed!
You can always change again, right?
C'mon, take it all off!
I can undress myself!
Where's the harm in a little helping hand?
Abusing your seniority, huh?
Huh?
What are you girls up to?
Ah... Well, you see, we were just washing up after our training...
Mr. Kiriya? I thought today's training was over.
There is one thing I forgot to mention.
I forbid you to make contact with anyone outside the school until further notice.
Outside the school?
Is this to do with the puppets?
That is correct.
Ha! I don't care how many of them there are! I'll take 'em all on!
No!
This is an order, Katsuragi.
Right.
What got up Mr. Kiriya's butt?!
I bet he's just pissin' himself over those puppets, right, Asuka?
Uh... I wasn't there at the time, so I dunno...
Oh, right.
"Homura," was it?
But I probably won't see her again...
The way Mr. Kiriya was acting...
He seemed to know more about the attack on us than he let on.
That's the feeling I get, anyway.
Something more?
What do you mean, Ikaruga?
I'm not sure.
It doesn't matter.
We are ninjas.
All we have to do is carry out the orders we are given without fail.
But if those scary guys show up again, I don't know what I'll do.
Don't worry. I'll protect you, Hibari.
Sure!
Then leave Asuka's breasts to me!
Senran Kagura
Frog!
Frog?
There's a frog down my shirt!
H-Help me!
Geez, it's just a frog.
Well, I'll be. It's a tree frog.
The tree frog,
also known as the rain frog, is an amphibian of the family Hylidae.
These frogs are able to change their color from yellow to grayish-brown, depending on their surroundings,
and are associated with rain due to the loud chirping they make
when the temperature drops
before an evening shower.
If you're that shaken up over a mere frog,
how will you cope with the
perils of being a ninja, Asuka?
They're so small and cute.
I've never been good with frogs.
Their legs and their webbed feet just freak me out!
That's oddly specific, huh?
They'll choose me, huh?
That's what Ikaruga said, but unless I
...imagine some specific kind of animal...
Komodo Dragon
Is this... a lunch counter?
Like in a sushi restaurant?
Yeah.
Huh? It couldn't be...
So you're here.
That voice!
Grandpa!
"Grandpa"?!
Come now, Asuka.
We just saw each other not
too long ago, didn't we?
Asuka...
Is this gentleman... by any chance...
Thank you for looking after my granddaughter.
The great Hanzo!
Th-The legendary ninja?
Hey, I was just thinking of treating you all to some lunch.
Hooray! Sushi! Sushi!
You even went and set up a store front?
I wanted it to be a surprise for you.
Living up to your name as
.the legendary ninja, I see.
Beautifully done.
Doing all of this by myself was quite a strain, though.
Oh, but what about your family business?
Grandpa's more or less retired,
so the business is run by my mom and dad.
I see. Your parents...
Ikaruga?
Oh, nothing.
It sure is nice to have a family, huh?
Yeah! That's what I think too!
Here. Thanks for waiting.
My legendary specially made sushi rolls.
Sure is nice to see those fine young ladies chowin' down on my sushi rolls.
Does the soul good, I say.
I hear you're havin' some summoning trouble.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
I'm afraid that with the way things are going,
I'll be an embarrassment to you and the rest of the family.
Now, now, don't you worry 'bout that.
But I guess it ended up comin' to this after all, huh?
Sometimes, your family line also affects the manner of beast you can summon.
Family line?
It happens especially often in families like ours that have been ninjas since way back.
Then, Grandpa, what did you summon?
Something rather traditional for a ninja.
Rather traditional? What kind of creature does our family summon?
Well, you see...
T-Toads?!
With the legs... and the webbed feet...
I guess I should've gotten you more accustomed to them when you were little, Asuka.
Never thought I'd raise a girl who was scared of frogs, of all things.
This is a trial you must face as a ninja!
I'll do my best.
Good. Oh, by the way, where's Kiriya?
Long time no see, Master Hanzo.
Haven't changed one bit, eh?
Not a single one to be found, is there?
Let's look over by the pond again.
Mr. Frog!
Um, I appreciate the help, but this is my problem. I can't get you all mixed up in it.
The shortest path to a successful summon is to be as close to the subject as possible.
Kind of like this.
I'm not putting a frog in my mouth!
I'd rather go my whole life
without summoning anything!
I give up.
What are you so up in arms about? I was speaking figuratively.
She's right.
Asuka, we're all here looking for frogs so that you can become more accustomed to them, right?
Stick with it.
You're right, Ikaruga.
I don't wanna let you guys down, so I'll keep trying.
So she's terrified of the very creature she's destined to summon.
No wonder she could never do it, no matter how much she tried.
Yeah.
There are none here.
We might not be able to find any unless we go to a rice paddy.
I hear frogs!
I can do at least this much to help her, right?
After all, I came all this way just to check up on her.
Is that the only reason you came back to this school?
I heard they were attacked by puppets.
Oh, so you heard about that after all?
I'm sure you too have realized just what this means.
They have already made their move.
Having made contact, what then is your assessment?
Ma'am, the girl Asuka, who carries the blood of the legendary ninja,
was one I took particular interest in, but I found nothing notable.
Same with the others.
They seemed to have enough trouble dealing with my adorable marionettes alone.
Then there is little to fear?
Affirmative.
We must take care not to underestimate them based on a mere one encounter.
Carelessness invites death.
That is something you should know well.
Of course.
It is inevitable that those girls will get in our way again one day.
However, bear in mind that patience is a virtue.
Carry yourselves as ninjas should, tread deeply and quietly,
and eliminate them.
Affirmative.
Yomi...
You are next.
As you wish.
Hang in there, Asuka.
You want me to hang what where?!
You'll be fine. Those frogs don't bite, you know.
This is no laughing matter!
You're like a frog that's been cornered by a snake.
Serpentine Academy for Girls? You mean...
Indeed. The truth is revealed at last.
It is a secret training organization for dark ninjas.
So they are behind this after all.
Where there is light, there is shadow.
While there are ninjas that strive to
maintain national stability and peace,
there are others who work behind the scenes as pawns for those who seek only their own dark desires.
The history of ninjas is one that is rife with battle between the forces of light and darkness.
They may still be in training, but
.these girls are ninjas all the same.
Now that the others have made their move,
we must be prepared to put our lives on the line.
Though their purpose remains
shrouded in mystery,
we must be prepared for
.whatever comes our way.
Right.
I just can't do it!
Nice, Ikaruga! Showing Asuka how it's done?
N-No, that's not it!
Look how much fun Ikaruga's having. Don't you want to try?
She's having fun?
I don't think she'd agree.
Get them off me, get them off me, get them off me!
Gratitude and Service
Yonpei Store
Each
A welcoming party for Grandpa?
You don't have to go to so much trouble.
Potatoes
70￥ Each
Onions
Oh, but we do.
After all, Master Hanzo is a legend among ninjas.
We need to show him the hospitality he deserves.
Asuka?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Grandpa's such an amazing person, but I—
I told you to take your time, did I not?
But I'm causing so much trouble for all of you.
You always try your very hardest.
Everyone knows that.
And we know that one day all your hard work will be rewarded.
Oh, Ikaruga...
And you know, I had some trouble with those frogs before as well.
Sorry about that.
These bean sprouts certainly are expensive.
Don't you think so?
S-Sure... W-Wait, Ikaruga!
We were ordered not to make contact with any outsiders—
Today's Specials!
Bean sprouts are peasant food.
I'm sure you two have no interest in them whatsoever, do you?
That's exactly why I despise spoiled kids like you.
I decided on this path
and now I won't hesitate anymore
I have the passion to go forward
and courage to match it
The feelings I accepted
might all be the result of fate
And yet now I stand perplexed
With courage
With pride
And with beauty we will go forth
Let's go according to our dreams
Let's take it all on
They're my guiding light, honest as I am
Every day a kiss
Just like lovers
You looked forward to a real fight, right?
I decided I would believe
Now I try to make it real
Let's go according to our dreams
Next Episode Preview
You're really on top of things, Ikaruga. How can I get it together like you?
To put it bluntly, you need
to pull yourself together.
All right! I'll pull myself together!
Hold on, Ikaruga! That's the same thing!
Moonlight Intruder
Next time, "Moonlight Intruder."
Come get it like your life depends on it.