[HAWKEYE]
Colonel... Please.
You don't have to do this...
Don't sacrifice everything...
for my sake...
[GOLD-TOOTH]]
But you will do it...
Won't you... Mustang?
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Well?
[ROY]
All right.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Good...
I knew you'd see reason.
[ROY]
All right, Lieutenant...
I won't perform
the transmutation.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
You'd forsake her...
How very cold of you.
[ROY]
You should talk...
You seem to
have no problem
treating these men as
your sacrificial pawns.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
These men are more than happy
to lay down their
lives for me...
They were abandoned...
Left by their parents,
they would have all
died without my care...
I saw to their education...
I gave them a reason
to keep on living...
I infused their very
existence with purpose.
For the kindness
I showed them,
they remain grateful to me.
[ROY] And that's just
the sort of overconfidence
that could get you in trouble.
[GOLD-TOOTH] Hmmm?
What do you--?
[SCAR]
He vanished.
[GERSO] Oh yeah,
we're grateful alright...
let me show you just
how grateful we are.
[GOLD-TOOTH]
No! Let me go!
[GERSO] Let every one down
there loose right now...
or that's the end of you.
[GOLD-TOOTH] No, wait!
Just listen to me...!
I'm the only
doctor here right now
who can use alchemy...
Without me you can
never save the woman...
Don't you understand?!
[GERSO] Hah...!
Yeah, nice try, doctor...
But I won't fall for that.
[MAY CHANG]
A Philosopher's Stone!
[ROY]
Outta my way!
Lieutenant!
[ROY]
Come on--stay with me!
Lieutenant, open your eyes!
[ROY] Lieutenant!
Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
[DARIUS]
You all right?
[MAY CHANG]
I have to get that stone!
Grrrrrrr!
[MAY CHANG]
She comes first.
Let me help!
[ROY]
Lieutenant!
[MAY CHANG] I've stopped
the bleeding for now...
but she still needs
to see a doctor.
[ROY] Thank you...
I owe you one.
[HAWKEYE] Colonel...
I'm so sorry.
[ROY] No, don't speak...
Just rest now.
[HAWKEYE]
You understood my signal...
I'm not sure how,
but I'm glad.
[ROY] We've been
together long enough...
And besides...
I know that glare. It means
"use human transmutation
and I'll shoot you."
[DARIUS] That's
the last one of 'em.
[ROY] Everyone, thank
you for all of your help.
[DARIUS] Sure...
It was no problem at all.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, right! The Stone!
[footsteps]
[ROY]
King Bradley...
[ROY] His wounds
aren't regenerating.
[BRADLEY] It's been
quite some time...
eh, Colonel Mustang?
[ROY]
Indeed it has, sir.
I'm afraid I'd be lying
if I said you were
looking as good as ever.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
Here, King Bradley!
Take this!
Ow!!
Arrgh!
[splash]
[BRADLEY] Knowing that
weakling's heart of yours,
I thought if someone
dear to you fell...
you would do
anything to save her,
even if it meant
human transmutation.
[ROY] There was a
time when I might have...
but that time
is behind me.
Luckily... I have
people by my side now
who will stop me
from being reckless,
and keep me headed
down the right path.
[BRADLEY] Hmph! And here
I was under the impression
you were all
pathetic creatures
who could never
learn a lesson properly...
but apparently there are
those like you who can learn--
who can change...
That's one more reason why
I can't stand you humans...
[BRADLEY]
It infuriates me
when I can't predict
how you'll behave.
Huh?!
[SCAR]
What's wrong?
[MAY CHANG]
He's under us...
Their leader's still
down there somewhere...
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Noo...!
I won't let you
interfere with him!
[GERSO]
Oh, give it up, doctor...
You're not going anywhere!
[ZAMPANO]
Gerso!
Get up!
[GERSO]
Run... get outta here!
[DARIUS]
This is bad.
[MAY CHANG] He's right...
something's coming...
something awful.
[ROY] Please...
Look after her for now.
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel!
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Hehehehe!
[GOLD-TOOTH] Very good.
Job well done, Bradley.
That's the kind of man
I brought you up to be--
[schling]
[gagging]
[PRIDE] Well,
Colonel Mustang...
looks like
you're our fifth.
[BRADLEY]
That's right...
The last one.
[barking]
[YOUNGSTER]
Not again...
What's with all the noise
and smoke around here today?
[YOUNGSTER]
Oh...
it looks like the
eclipse has begun.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[PRIDE]
I was really hoping
that I wouldn't have
to resort to this...
but there is no choice...
We have run
out of time now.
[BRADLEY]
Whether you like it or not,
we're going to force
you to open the portal...
Prepare yourself.
[ROY]
No. I won't do it.
[BRADLEY] As I said, it doesn't
matter if you want to...
Pride has just
assimilated an alchemist
who possesses knowledge
of human transmutation.
[BRADLEY] He has
the necessary formula.
[PRIDE]
He's safely pinned...
Move back, Wrath... Now.
[coughs]
[BRADLEY]
I wonder...
What will be taken from
you in exchange, Mustang...
Ahhhh!!
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel!
[MAY CHANG] No! You'll
get caught up in it, too!
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel!
[BRADLEY]
The transmutation's complete.
[ZAMPANO] That's the
old guy with the glasses?
[HAWKEYE]
The colonel?
[BRADLEY] Oh,
Mustang's still alive...
Right about now,
the good Colonel should
be joining our Father.
[BRADLEY]
Although...
I can't vouch for his
physical well-being.
[BRADLEY]
Take a good look...
See what kind of
shape I'm in right now?
[BRADLEY] Who among
you would care for
the illustrious honor of taking
down the Fuhrer of Amestris?
A Chimera?
The outsider?
Mustang's dog?
Or perhaps...
You'd all like to
come at me at once?
I don't think we can beat him
even when he's in this shape.
[GERSO]
Right there...
beneath the hole in the ceiling.
[GERSO] When May
said their leader
was right below us,
that crazy doctor guy said
that he wouldn't let us
interfere with him, right...?
So I'm guessing
Bradley doesn't want us
to go down there either.
[SCAR] Ah...
so that's the center.
[MAY CHANG]
It must be.
That's where the chi
felt the strongest.
[SCAR]
Well then...
[ED]
Colonel!
[PRIDE]
I've brought him to you...
He's our fifth.
[FATHER] Hmm... I wish
we could say that makes
all five of the
required sacrifices...
but Alphonse Elric
has not arrived yet.
[ED]
Colonel, are you okay?!
Say something!
[ROY]
Fullmetal?
Where... where are we?
[ED] The bearded
guy's hideout...
Now what happened?
What did they do to you?
[ROY] I was flung
into a strange place,
into a gateway of some sort.
[ED]
The portal?!
That means... something
was taken from you...
But, your arms and
legs are still here...
[ROY]
Fullmetal...
I don't know
how you can expect
to see my condition when
it's this dark in here.
[ED]
What do you mea--?
[ROY]
It's all dark... pitch black...
The lights...
Where are the lights?
[ED] No...!
It can't be...
[PRIDE] Ah,
so you can't see, then?
That's good...
We've found your abilities
to be quite problematic
in the past...
You're by far the
most troublesome
of the State Alchemists
we've dealt with.
[PRIDE]
I think it's fair to say,
you've had this coming.
[ED] Colonel...
you performed it...?
Human transmutation?
[ROY] Of course not...
You think I would
willingly do such a thing?
[PRIDE]
That's true, he didn't...
We had to force him
to open the portal.
[PRIDE] It all
worked out in the end...
Now Colonel Mustang's meddling
and his troublesome flame
alchemy will present...
no more problems for us...
[FATHER] The truth can
be such a cruel thing...
The two brothers
who wanted to feel
their mother's
warmth once more...
their attempt to bring
the dead back to life
cost one of them the
leg on which he stood,
as well as the only
family he had left...
[FATHER] The other
lost his entire body,
to have it replaced
by a suit of armor
that could feel nothing.
The woman who
sought to bring back
her only baby
was given a body
and then...
the man who looked
to change his nation
had his eyesight
taken from him...
and now he can no
longer see his future.
[FATHER] Humans who
would dare to play god
must pay a steep price
for their arrogance...
That is the way
of the universe,
the natural
order imposed
by the very thing
you claim to worship...
That is Truth.
[ED]
I don't think so!
[ED] If he'd done it of
his own volition like we did,
that would be one thing.
But...
to force someone
to participate
in human transmutation
against his will
and then steal
his eyesight?!
You think that's justified?!
That isn't a truth that
I'm willing to accept!
[BRADLEY] You plan to
interfere with Father's plans?
[BRADLEY] Tell me...
You go by Scar.
What's your real name?
[SCAR]
I have none.
I left it.
[BRADLEY]
You don't say...
What a coincidence...
I don't know what my
real name is either.
[BRADLEY]
It's almost poetic...
two nameless men
fighting to the death.
[ED]
May Chang!
[MAY CHANG]
There he is!
[FATHER] And now
my lovely home
has a gaping hole in it...
How dare you, girl.
[MAY CHANG]
He may look different now,
but there's no
mistaking it...
he's the one who's
behind all of this!
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, Alphonse!
What happened to you?
[ED]
I don't know...
I can't get him to wake up.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, no!
Please wake up,
Alphonse...!
Come on you have to!
Come on, Alphonse, get up!
[AL]
My body...
That's... my body.
[AL (human)]
I've waited a long time.
Welcome home, Al.
[AL]
Your arms...
You've grown so thin...
Nothing but skin and bones.
It's all you can do just
to stand up... I can't...
I can't...
[AL] I can't fight
in a body like this...
but everyone
else is fighting!
[AL (human)] You don't want
to become one with me again?
[AL]
No, it's not that!
For a long... long time
all I've thought about
is getting my body
back... and yet...
I can't come back to you...
I just can't right now...
That body isn't
strong enough.
[AL (human)]
You want to go back there.
You want to go
back in that body?
[AL (human)]
Then I won't stop you.
[AL]
I'm sorry...! I'll be back...!
Just wait a little longer!
I swear I'll be back...!
I promise...! I promise!
[ED]
Al!
Al! Are you all right?
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse!
[IZUMI]
Al!
[AL]
Teacher... Brother...
May... Then we're--?
[AL (human)] He left behind
the body he had searched for
for so long to go
and help his friends.
My valiant, noble soul...
as your vessel,
I am very proud of you... but...
With your selfless return...
the world may be plunged
into darkness and despair.
My Alphonse.
[FATHER]
And now... all five are here.
[NARRATOR]
Courage can be brought
to its knees by
unremitting force...
And happiness can easily
be shattered into pieces.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode 60: "Eye of Heaven,
Gateway of Earth."
And before long...
the world is
shrouded in darkness.