Hurry and get up. You stayed up late again, right?
I've checked. and the lights were still on at 2:30 AM.
Isn't that right?
Ryuuji... Inside your ears...
Grain... Grain... Guru guru...
Sparkling white rice... Just done....
If you want breakfast, it's right here.
I'll heat it up, you go and wash your face.
Breakfast...
Okay!
Now I just have to wash the dishes and do the laundry...
This is a really dreary room.
A cardboard box?
What's this?
An album?
This is...
What are you looking at?
Oh, Taiga! This is...
That's right, they're photographs of Kitamura-kun. Do you have a problem with that?
By the way, I won't listen to any complaints.
So this is... Kitamura?
I-It can't be helped!
I don't know how it happened, but they just got blurry.
Somehow, it happens whenever I take pictures of Kitamura-kun.
I'll help you take one.
Eh?
Photograph.
I'll do it.
Although I'm not really good at it, it'll still be much better than these.
Wait a moment!
H-How many can you take?
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
That Moment's Face
What kind of picture would be best?
His thoughtful face during a test...
Or during softball practice...
Ah, his expression while he's eating lunch too.
Didn't I say I'd take however many you want?
Even if you say 'however many', there has to be some conditions, right?
Then take tons of pictures for free, got it?
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
You're late today.
Yeah. I had to make a trip to the Student Council room first today.
Ohha!
Outdated... That's too outdated, Taiga.
N-No... That's not...
Well, that...
Aisaka.
Ohha!
I'll be going then.
O-Ohha?
Hey, hey. Did you catch it?
Catch what?
Of course it's when he did the "Ohha", right?
It was too sudden, how could I have caught that?
Useless mongrel.
Look here...
Maruo, take a look at this.
Hey, hey. This magazine model looks just like Maruo!
Look here, you two. The morning assembly is about to start.
Stop chatting and hurry to the school yard.
Maruo is so cold.
Even if he's the vice president, he's still too serious.
There's got to be at least some reaction, right?
Right?
Kitamura is surprisingly popular among the girls, huh?
What Maruo...
Shall I use this hand to roll you up?
Everyone, line up with the front!
Hey, you guys.
The number of people forgetting their student handbook seems to be increasing.
The evidence was already brought forward.
During last week's special item check, according to discipline committee member Fuuki's report...
How many was it?
59.
There were a total of 56 students in the school who forgot their student handbooks.
Oops, I made a mistake. It's 59.
Well, the trivial matters are unimportant.
Anyway, forgetting your student handbook is tantamount to forgetting being a student of Ohaji High School.
Have you got it?
Yes!
Do you have the right to talk about others?
Don't you forget things yourself?
Ai-Aisaka...
That little fellow over there, what did you say?
You forgot "look straight ahead".
Look straight ahead!
Oh, sorry.
Everyone, look straight ahead!
Geez, why do high school students have to align to the front in the first place?
Maintaining this totally stupid position and listening to your totally long-winded nonsense.
Is it really as tough as you say?
You're just sticking your hands on your waist, right?
What did you say?!
Hey, Aisaka.
Not bad. Getting some exercise in the morning, huh?
President, you should calm down too.
What do you know?
We don't have back pain or body pain, so why do we have to stick our hands on our waists?
This stupid embarrassment...
Aisaka!
Ai-Aisaka... Please get a hold of yourself.
Sorry, President. Please carry on with the morning assembly.
Y-Yeah.
What? What?
I heard that the palm-sized tiger bit the President.
That girl...
The cool does this dos...
She's clearly depressed.
No, she's being happy.
...man not's himself to...
Okay, okay. Haruta-kun, that's enough.
Well, next is...
A-Aisaka-san?
Feeling good today, aren't you...
Then, how about you read for us?
I guess if you don't want to read it...
Haruta-kun!
Yuri-chan, that's unbelievable!
Please do your best!
Listen to what I have to say...
Here, lunch box.
No need. I've got no appetite.
Quarrelling with the President of the Student Council, and bringing trouble to Kitamura-kun...
But my arms were held back.
Waki-waki carnival...
T-Taiga?
But, I still want to apologise to him!
If it's that, don't mind it.
The President of the Student Council isn't someone who would worry about trivial things.
Oh?
A lunch box, huh? Can I join in?
Whoa, not bad, not bad.
Count me in too!
This isn't bad once in a while too.
Right?
I'm hungry.
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
The sides today, what are the sides today?
W-Why did it turn out like this?
Ah, it's fried chicken today!
One, two, fried chicken~
Taiga is about to faint!
Whoa, Taiga's lunch box looks appetizing!
Crap! Speaking of which, our lunch boxes are...
Aisaka, you've been bringing a lunch box recently... Are you making them yourself?
That... is....
Takasu?
Um... That's not...
Look, wasn't Kushieda doing it too? The job of styling cellphones.
I made these lunch boxes for some extra pocket money too...
Oh, is that so?
Eh?
I want to taste a lunch box made by Takasu someday.
Me too. And make sure that it's a brown and sober lunch box,
which increases one's appetite.
T-Then, I'll make everyone a share next time.
Kitamura-senpai, Kushieda-senpai.
Um, it's about time...
It's the manager from the softball club.
A meeting, huh?
Sorry, please carry on eating, the two of you.
Y-Yeah...
It wasn't pleasant just now. Very bad.
With Kitamura-kun... Kitamura-kun...
Huh? Taiga?
Look here.
How can you let Kitamura know that your lunch box was made by me?
It wasn't easy for us to get everyone to understand that there's nothing between us.
What should I do? What should I do? What should I do?
Calm down!
Geez. Why do you always get nervous whenever Kitamura is mentioned?
Listen, you've got to be more careful from now on...
What is it? Swallow first if you've something to say.
Hey, there's no meat in the lunch box today.
If you love meat so much, why don't you go become the child of a meat-loving family?
As expected of mold in the public toilet.
However, your luck ends here when you're discovered by me.
Taka-chan, it's about to end.
Yeah. Leave the rest to me, you can go first.
Lucky. I'm counting on you then.
Come on, come on, you damned black devil.
What's wrong? Are you surrendering already?
Good. I'll finish you off with one of the Takasu family's 48 household chore techniques, the Takasu Mold Buster.
Ryuuji.
What are you muttering over there?
Hurry up and come here, you lazy dog.
What... Taiga?
You... This is the men's toilet...
Enough already, hurry up!
Hey!
What is it, Taiga?
What are you doing...
Ah, it's Kitamura.
Here, hurry up. Hurry up and take it.
This fellow...
Here, now, now! Hurry up!
I got it. The shutter seems to be...
Now, now!
Wait a moment. Setting it now...
Ah, fine then. Give it to me!
I see. This is how those silly photographs were taken.
Amazing, Kitamura-kun. There, there.
Go!
Hey, he's waving wildly.
Shut up.
Stupid.
Welcome to Sudoh-Bucks.
Shop manager, one serving of Neapolitan please.
Neapolitan, right?
How is this place not receiving any complaints?
Speaking of which, you didn't really need to print them out, right?
Hey, you. You're drooling all over the place.
So many Kitamura-kuns... Kitamura carnival...
What are you doing? There's a limit to young people's antics, right?
I'm helping you, mongrel.
Eh?
Because you helped to take those photographs.
There's no need to. I still want to dry the futons tomorrow.
I'll kill you if you say anything more.
Kill... You...
Moreover, you have to bring lunch boxes along next time, right?
For Minorin and... Kitamura-kun...
Well then, do you know how to peel the potatoes?
D-Don't treat me like an idiot!
Something that trivial... It's just the removal of the skin, right? Geez.
Personally cooking for Kitamura, huh?
That's right. It's not often that I can cook for Minori, I better work hard...
What are you doing...
What is it? Isn't this properly removing the skin?
Furthermore, I definitely won't cut my finger this way.
No, well...
It's rice balls for dinner, just like a picnic.
And also, this tiny rice ball is so cute!
That was made by me.
Taiga-chan's a genius?
Well, it doesn't matter how you train if you're doing this.
There isn't a need to remove the skin either.
Like I've said, finish it before you talk.
Delicious!
The taste of Taiga-chan's hands!
Here. I made some tea.
If you don't put it into the album properly, it'll get torn.
Shut up, troublesome.
What is it? And here I am, about to offer to laminate the one that you like.
Can you do something like that?
Well, yeah.
Then, wait a minute. Um...
If you process it that way,
nothing will happen even if you tear it or drop it into water.
Taiga, what's wrong?
N-Nothing.
If not, a few more is fine too.
Two is fine, three too...
Shut up!
Wait a minute! I'm choosing it now, aren't I?
What is it, suddenly...
I'm...
I'm going back.
What is it, all of a sudden...
I can't quieten my heart here, so I'll choose it when I get back to my house.
Hey, Taiga! Wait up!
What is she doing?
I want the pictures too.
Of Kushieda.
Look, look at this!
T-This is...
A light yellow-coloured squid? No, a slime?
It's awesome, isn't it?
Using a bucket, I made the pudding!
T-This?
How do I put it... It's like a browser crasher...
Making pudding with a bucket, that's a forbidden desire of women!
However, it wasn't done well because everything was too large.
It's sticky, soft, and became mixed up altogether...
That's really...
The ladies over there!
Look here, look here! My latest bucket: Yu-Gi-Oh edition!
This is...
Kushieda's photograph.
Look here, look here! My latest bucket: Yu-Gi-Oh edition!
How do I put it, it's really troublesome and hard to make...
Although it's different from what I had imagined...
Well, forget it.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oh? It's you, Ryuuji.
Are you still choosing it?
Shut up, geez.
What's with that?
You went back suddenly yesterday too.
Didn't I say any number is fine if you can't make a choice?
What are you doing?
If that's the case, then you choose it instead.
Huh?
I'm leaving it to you then.
Something like this, how do I make a choice?
That Taiga.
Does that belong to Aisaka?
Yeah, you can say so.
Those are my photographs.
No, this is that...
How do I put it... That...
Speaking of which, I've nearly forgotten about it.
I've always left it inside.
Huh?
What...
How nostalgic.
Why do you have a photograph like this?
The photography club used to sell them often.
I bought one of them...
It's not that! Why do you have Taiga's photograph?
I liked Aisaka so I put it in.
Just that.
Eh?
I confessed to her once, but she completely refused.
Ah, I let it out. You've got to keep it a secret from everyone, okay?
What... What...
Takasu, what's wrong?
Hey, Takasu?
What the hell?!
What a waste.
It can't be helped.
He said he liked me, I was dumbfounded and it gave me a shock.
Although I rejected him,
I became conscious of him after that.
So... Somehow...
Somehow, I seemed to like him!
It was right here.
Aisaka!
You've never hidden your anger!
I like your outspoken attitude.
I'm crazy about you!
Kitamura...
It's a weird confession, right?
Is he praising me or making fun of me?
However, I was happy.
Because he liked me
for the way I was,
and accepted that I am who I am.
Why? This moment somehow surfaced in the room where Taiga lives.
I have so many photographs...
But there are none that I like.
Eh?
I want that expression back.
That moment when Kitamura-kun confessed to me.
Once more...
What embarrassing things have you made me say, you perverted dog!
How was it my fault?!
Who else is here but you?
Being needed by somebody.
What meaning does it have for Taiga?
Speaking of which, it's stupid indeed.
Coming to like him after that, isn't it better to not answer right away instead?
Right, Inko-chan?
Kitamura is Kitamura too.
Since he liked her once, he should have gone out with her, really.
I... In...
Oh, Inko-chan thinks so too?
In... In...
Whoa, say it, Inko-chan.
I...
Isn't it good?
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
Kawashima Ami
The naturally elegant girl who appeared suddenly, Kawashima Ami.
What I wanted to say was...
Women are really scary!
Huh? What's that?
Ami-chan, you won't understand.