People hide their faces behind big fat clouds
hitobito wa atsui kumo de kao wo kakushite
They can't find a vent for their sadness,
and it grinds inside them every day
ikiba no nai omoi wo zutto motte toide iru
In this ordinary town, they will be buried, and yet they remain
nanimo nai machi ni umorete mo, sore demo, ima demo
Mannequins displayed in a string of windows,
tsuranaru windou ni
it's a nightmare
narabi tatsu ningyou no warui yume
Or, hiding in the back with their sadness,
soretomo souko ni kakurete fusaide itatte
where no one can find them in piles of dust
hokori dake kabutte mitsukaranai
And they can't feel the touch of someone's hand
dare no te ni datte furerarenai
Our time is now. Even if nothing else changes,
boku tachi no genzai wo kurikaesu koto darake demo,
we will come across each other someday
sou itsuka kimi to deaou
Think about that day, and let's go on one day at a time
sonna hi wo omotte, hibi wo yukou
One day at a time
yukou