Now, the time is ripe.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
keep your room brightly lit, sit
as far from the TV as you can,
and wait for the fated moment.
Well, well, well. Everyone,
it's time at last.
The day has finally come
to attempt the legendary great
maneuver with Miss Layla.
After all those nights I cried by myself.
After the many times I almost gave up.
But I'm fine now.
The tears I want now are
the tears of victory.
If I want to cry, I should cry after I win.
After I win! After I win!
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
We're not going to die.
We'll make sure to succeed.
The time is ripe.
You who were chosen by the stage,
who overcame many ordeals.
Now indeed is the time to tell you
everything about the legendary great maneuver.
You must tackle the maneuver
with unshakable confidence.
The legendary great maneuver is...
"An Amazing Comeback."
Wha... What?
Maybe that spirit of the stage
is there in front of them.
What?
I bet he is.
In order to perform the
legendary great maneuver,
the players must have absolute confidence.
After they answer that they would never die,
they are acknowledged by
the spirit of the stage.
If those two hadn't said that they
would never be afraid of dying...
They would have been abandoned
by the spirit of the stage.
Either we would have to
cancel tomorrow's show,
or they'd attempt the
maneuver recklessly, and...
So that's the legendary great maneuver.
It's amazing.
It's more than I imagined.
Miss Layla,
please make sure to rest your shoulder
well in preparation for tomorrow.
I will practice a little more.
All right.
Mia...
Yes.
I have some suggestions concerning
the stage construction for tomorrow.
Would you mind discussing my suggestions
with the Directing Department?
Sure.
So it has been set in motion.
Tomorrow, at last, the legendary
great maneuver will be revived
by Layla Hamilton and Sora Naegino.
Good. Keep that height and rhythm.
According to Miss Layla's plan,
they're going to switch to
a trampoline after this.
Please wait at the gate
until your cue to appear.
Anna!
So all of you came.
Of course.
I can't stay still.
Is the legendary great maneuver amazing?
I just built the device which
Arlon told me to build.
One, two... Jump!
Yeah!
Higher, higher!
Amazing, amazing.
Marion! Jonathan!
Sora, everyone's back!
What?
Everyone who was in Freedom Lights is here.
I heard that even the people who
quit Kaleido Stage came back.
Everyone?
Kaleido Stage is back the way it was!
We did it!
I've not seen you in a while.
The last place we met was at
the Vancouver Festival, right?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow, I'll be on an
extended business trip to Asia.
I don't have much time.
Can you make it short and
tell me what you want to say?
No matter what, please come to
see Layla's performance tomorrow.
Hmm? Oh, I see.
If it's about selling Kaleido
Stage, I already know.
But if you want me to do something about it,
unfortunately, I have to tell
you that you should give up.
You and I are alike.
I tried to re-create the Kaleido
Stage my father envisioned.
In the end, I had no clue
what he was thinking at all.
No, I wasn't even trying to understand him.
You too, are trying to avoid
understanding Layla's thoughts.
Avoiding? Me?
I'm a fool who could not bring
himself to leave the nest
even after his parents had left.
And you...
You are a fool who can't acknowledge
that your daughter has already
left the protection of your wing.
Layla is already able to fly high
and strong even without your help.
And she wants you to see it.
But you've been trying not to look at that.
Father...
How was my performance today?
Your seat is already reserved.
Mother? Good morning.
Yes, it's tomorrow night.
Sorry for letting you
know at the last moment.
Really? How is Yume?
Seats are fine.
I already got you reserved seats.
How is it?
Has the pain abated?
Yes.
If it stays like this, I think
I'll be all right tomorrow too.
It's strange.
What?
I'm always nervous before I go onstage,
but I'm calm and I just
can't wait until tomorrow.
As a doctor, I couldn't possibly
approve of you appearing onstage,
but as a fan, I'll do
whatever I can to help you.
Thank you, Kate.
Sora, are you working hard?
I can't believe this.
Using only one arm, she can do that much.
Oh, Rosetta!
Amazing.
You're amazing, Sora!
Sora...
We're all set too.
Okay.
Miss Layla...
Then after that, the entire
cast will move away at once.
Then they will start the
legendary great maneuver.
Your special stage is there.
I finally understand how you felt
when you sent my father off to the stage.
The players who were chosen by the stage
cannot help but attempt the
legendary great maneuver.
Nobody can stop it.
I know.
I planned, by any means necessary,
to create a Kaleido Stage that
doesn't produce any injuries.
But, in the end, I wound
up losing everything.
It's not finished yet.
What will be will be.
You should run it the way you like.
Originally, I planned to let Arlon
handle all management-related matters.
No...
As I see it, I think Kaleido
Stage should belong to you.
Your reckless method made
Sora who she is now.
I did nothing.
She just dashed headlong into this herself.
So it finally happens tomorrow.
Yes. It should be around this time tomorrow.
The legendary great maneuver...
I will perfect it with
Miss Layla by any means.
The swing is longer than the
one we used for practice.
So watch your timing.
Yes.
With our power,
we're going to turn the
legend into a reality.
Yes.
Excuse me,
may I ask you one question?
What?
If Fool hadn't qualified us yesterday,
what were you going to do?
I never considered that.
What? You didn't?
No.
Naturally, I thought that we
would be qualified by Fool.
But, come to think of it, it's
usually what everyone thinks.
How about you, Sora?
Well...
To tell you the truth, I'm the same.
Both of them are laughing.
Sora!
Yes.
You have guests.
Sora.
Mother, Father...
Yume! Have you been a good girl?
Thank you for inviting us, Sora.
It's not a big deal.
I'm the one who's supposed to thank
you for coming all the way here.
We're just happy because if this
were the old you, you would say,
"I don't want to ask them
to come all the way here."
You used to be so reserved. Remember?
Oh, that's true.
You were the girl who was concerned
about the hotel expenses
and picked the flight which departed
on the same day of the audition.
Yes, I remember that.
It made me worry more.
Well, I thought it would be all right, so...
Sora, you seem so lively somehow.
I think it means you're confident.
Yes.
That's why I want both of you to
see my performance by all means.
Of course, you too, Yume.
You have two more people
you want to show. Right?
You have four parents.
We'll all be watching over you.
Yes.
Really, you're so pushy.
Please don't say something
like that and just watch.
Please reconsider selling Kaleido Stage.
It's already a done deal.
Mr. Kenneth...
Then maybe I should buy it back.
What? All by yourself? Ridiculous!
Those who are afraid to take risks
have no choice but to walk behind.
You greenhorn.
Please keep holding it tight, Sora.
Yes.
If we perfect the legendary great maneuver,
the audience will come back again.
Yes.
If they do, let's create
a wonderful show again.
A real show which both children
and adults can enjoy.
Oh, Kate, how are Sora and everybody doing?
They're fine.
Good.
The last card.
The potential for unlimited possibilities.
The upright Fool.
The door to the future will open
to those fools who are not afraid.
It looks like they don't have any lifelines.
Really? Then if they drop...
That would be bad...
I'm going to create the
best show with Miss Layla.
Sora...
Somehow, I'm getting chills.
It's so far, but it looks
like it's so close to me.
It's like magic.
Let's start, Sora.
Yes.
I need to focus only on Miss Layla.
Come, Sora!
Jump toward Miss Layla...
Amazing!
They did it.
They're flying. Really...
Both of you have wings on your back.
Is this really happening?
They finally made the legend reality.
I'm not scared at all.
I'm with Miss Layla.
I'm so happy.
I feel like crying.
I wish I could keep performing
like this forever.
The brilliance of life that
doesn't flinch at anything.
That is indeed the legendary great maneuver.
Now, I know.
Not only is the legendary great
maneuver a dangerous maneuver,
but it is also an expression of a strong
life that keeps even death at bay.
Arlon...
The maneuver which even gives the
audience the strength to live...
That's what the legendary great maneuver was.
Amazing.
No wonder someone like me was
unable to get in their way.
Sora, let's go back.
Yes.
The swing is farther than it's
supposed to be because of the wind.
Let's do it with all our might.
Okay.
One!
Two!
Three!
It's done.
Hey, dim the lighting.
What? But...
No buts. Hurry.
Yes.
Miss Layla...
Amazing! Sora, you're the best!
Amazing. It was amazing!
I've never seen anything like that before.
Sora, you did it.
I feel like I'm still flying.
Layla...
Father...
It was a wonderful show.
Did you see it?
Yes.
Now I understand what Yuri said.
Yuri?
You can fly anywhere with your own
wings without my help anymore.
Father...
Did you hurt your shoulder?
Yes.
Is it bad?
At least,
I know I won't be able to appear
on Kaleido Stage anymore.
What?
It's not true, is it?
It is true.
I can't believe it.
But...
Kate already told me.
But still, I didn't want to miss this chance.
I staged the best performance with you.
And received the best applause.
I can't ask anything more
for my last performance.
But... but... I...
Sora!
Sora...
Sora, be strong.
I can't do it!
It's impossible.
In order to perfect the legendary
great maneuver with you,
I prepared myself to pay any price.
Sora,
didn't you tell me that you
would challenge fate with me?
If what you told me is really true,
stand up, Sora!
Sora, from now on,
I want you to be my dream.
Please be my dream, Sora.
I'm going to be Miss Layla's dream?
That's right.
I know you can become a true Kaleido Star.
A true Kaleido Star...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing
Sora...
Sora, hurry!
Hey, Sora!
Yes!
Miss Layla, I will become a true
Kaleido Star no matter what!
I will! I will!
Ouch!
I will work harder and harder!
Hi, everyone! I am Sora Naegino.
How was the legendary great maneuver
which I did with Miss Layla?
It was so tough. I worked so
hard. And I cried so much.
But I am Miss Layla's dream,
and Miss Layla's dream is me.
I'll definitely become a true Kaleido
Star, for Miss Layla's sake as well!
I will! I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star, "Amazing
Prologue To Stardom, part 1."
My wings are my dream and on towards the sky.