There's more of them than before.
The river's waters flow without end,
yet the water is never the same.
In still pools, foam floats, dissolving and coming forth,
never remaining for long,
just as man and his dwellings in this world.
Oh, Mii-kun!
What's up?
Yuki-senpai, you got kept late again?
Yeah, I'm terrible at classical Japanese.
I kind of like it. Want me to help?
Oh, really?
I can't believe you understand this hard stuff!
It's the "Hojoki."
My friend liked it.
Isn't this amazing, Mii-kun?
What's amazing?
This is a letter from someone long ago!
From about 800 years ago, yeah.
It's more of an essay than a letter, though.
800 years!
Someone from that long ago
can tell us their feelings today!
Aren't letters amazing?!
I can see that you really get excited.
Okay then,
shall we begin?
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
Letters
Brrr!
The wind's really awful at night.
Yes.
We're fine now, but we've got to think of
how to deal with the cold before winter comes.
Winter, huh.
Doesn't even feel like it's coming.
Did Yuki go to bed already?
Yes, she was studying until late,
so she's out like a light.
Alright.
We should go to sleep soon, too.
Hey, Prez.
Have you ever imagined that this was a dream,
and you were just gonna wake up
and be at school as usual?
I dream of it every night.
Yuki-chan,
Yuri-san and I have decided.
Ri-san?
Yes, we're going to do something fun.
How can this be fun?
We're going to start a club, all together.
A... club?
That's right.
We're all going to start the School Living Club.
Yuki-senpai!
Senpai, it's time to wake up.
Morning, Mii-kun.
I had a nightmare.
What happened in it?
I forget.
What, really?
Breakfast is ready.
The others are already there.
I see, I see.
Huh? Where's Megu-nee?
Umm...
Oh, Megu-nee, good morning!
This should be good.
The School Living Club is gonna
do its best today, Megu-nee.
It looks so good!
Let's eat!
Wow, this is so good!
They are green onions grown by
the Gardening Club, after all!
I'm glad they shared them with us.
Yeah!
This udon is really great, too.
Huh?
As always, she's scarfing it down,
not listening to a word you say.
Hey, slow down, you're not a dog like Taromaru.
Oh, I think Taromaru has better manners than that.
It's amazing how you've managed to
keep the room temperature up lately!
The udon's so springy!
The miracle of modern technology, I say.
I'd say so, yes. It lets us have warm udon as well.
It's all thanks to the solar panels
and storage batteries here.
Most schools don't have those kinds of things, huh.
That was great!
Ri-san, seconds, please!
Sorry, Yuki-chan, we don't have any more.
We went for variety over quantity on the field trip.
I see.
But wasn't the field trip fun?
We got to make friends with Mii-kun, too!
Th-thank you.
It was quite the ordeal.
Yes, a terrible ordeal...
And on the way back, we had to cram
all four of us and Taromaru into that little car.
I fell asleep right away,
so I don't remember much of it.
That's right, I was driving,
and Ri-san was in the passenger seat,
and Taromaru was jumping all over the back seat.
I'm surprised you guys managed to sleep through that.
Huh?
There were only two in the back?
That's weird.
That car...
had space for four, right?
That's right.
Me, and Ri-san and Kurumi-chan,
Mii-kun and Megu-nee.
And that's four?
Huh?
Senpai?
Where was Megu-nee?
O-oh, back then, remember, you were
sleeping so you probably didn't know,
but Megu-nee said her house was really close,
so she got out and walked back, yeah.
That's right.
She did?
Uh-huh, right?
Huh?
That's right.
Yuki-chan!
I'm gonna go ask Megu-nee!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's nobody's fault.
Yuki-senpai...
It's not good for her to go on like this...
Miki-san?
I know that Senpai's smile
really makes everyone feel better.
But that doesn't mean...
Yeah...
I'm sure Megu-nee feels the same way.
Megu-nee?
You're really here, right, Megu-nee?
It's okay.
Even if I don't have much of a presence,
I won't leave you.
But sometimes I get really scared.
Sometimes I can't remember things, and...
Everyone has fuzzy memories.
That's why you have to talk to
other people or keep a diary.
Then those memories won't be so fuzzy anymore.
That's what I believe.
Even if the person you remember...
...isn't here anymore.
I'll work hard.
I'll work really hard, Megu-nee.
I'm back!
Hey, you're back!
Welcome back.
Mii-kun!
I told you not to touch me so much!
Mii-kun, I just kinda missed you!
I don't care, jeez!
Mii-kun, Mii-kun, something smells weird!
Hey!
I don't mean you, I mean Taromaru, Taromaru!
Hey there, boy, what's going on with you?
Taromaru doesn't want to get in the bath.
I see!
I'll put him in the bath, then!
Hey, wait!
Now that I think of it, the world as we see it
must look so different to dogs.
Yeah.
I hear that dogs can't see colors like we do,
so they see the world in sepia tones.
But because of that,
they have really good night vision,
and can even see some ultraviolet light.
And dogs can smell things that we can't.
All the flowers we see,
dogs have no idea what color they are.
Huh, really.
Gimme back my hat!
Don't you get the feeling the two of them
see the same world?
Yes.
Right?
Even the four of us see the world in different ways.
Hey, Taromaru! Jeez!
Wait!
Yuki-chan!
Are you okay?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Please don't overdo it, Senpai.
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Huh?
What's this?
Looks like they belong to Megu-nee.
What a mess...
I'll help.
Thank you.
You're a club member now,
so you don't have to thank me so politely.
Oh, I see.
Oh, look!
Hey guys, look at this!
Wanna write a letter?
I think it's a good idea to write a letter,
but how are we gonna send them?
Oh, you're right!
The post office is outside school!
You hadn't even realized that?
Then, why don't we send them from the school?
Writing a letter makes me think of carrier pigeons!
Where are we supposed to find a carrier pigeon?
We'll go catch one!
But how are we going to catch one?
With this!
You're going to beat it?!
Nah, I'm just gonna hit it with the back.
Like this!
Whaaa...?
And this!
That's not going to work...
You don't even need to hit them in the first place.
And this!
Expands to 20 times
their size!
Balloons
Why don't we use these?
Oh, aren't those the ones you
picked up in the test of courage?
If we blow them up, they won't fly.
Oh, my.
I wish we had helium.
Oh, I think the Scuba Club
might've been using some.
You had a Scuba Club?
Way back when, yes.
Okay, I'm gonna go check it out.
Wait.
You can't carry the tank on your own.
I'll come help.
Huh?
Ri-san
But...
Mii-kun
I'm a club member, after all.
Alright, if you could.
Right!
I'll go too!
Why don't you stay and write a letter, Yuki-chan?
Oh, that's right!
I'll write one, a really good one!
I wonder if anyone will find our letters.
I think someone will.
It's not like all of mankind has disappeared.
Y-yeah.
It's a really small chance, though.
I hope they do.
Right!
Hmmm.
What's wrong?
It's kinda embarrassing to write really formally.
And my handwriting sucks.
It's alright.
Let me borrow this.
What're you doing?
Oh, you're making a paper doll?
It's so cute!
Yuki-chan, how would you feel
if you were walking along
and found a letter attached to a balloon?
Hmm...
I'd be really surprised! And happy!
Would you think about their handwriting?
Nope!
I'd just be happy to get a letter!
Right?
I get it!
We're back!
We're back. We found a helium tank!
Helium
And we brought a trap, too!
You're still thinking about catching a pigeon?
Hell yes!
Hey, hey, Mii-kun, you should write a letter, too!
Here, here!
Alright, alright.
Hey, Yuki, look at this.
What is it?
With this trap, we can kill a pigeon in a second!
But it can't carry the letter if it's dead.
Staff #2
Then I'll go catch one!
Have fun!
Let's move the tank towards the wall.
Staff #2
Okay!
Sakura
Mii-kun!
Y-yeah?
What're you gonna write?
Hmmm,
I dunno...
KYAA!
Stop!
I wonder what I should write in my letter.
Anything would be fine, don't you think?
You could write about yourself,
or what you want to do in the future.
Anything you like.
My future, huh?
I gotta figure out if I'm gonna
go to college or get a job,
or Megu-nee's gonna get mad at me.
I think everyone would get mad if you didn't figure it out.
Yeah, huh.
We have to leave this school eventually.
Yeah.
Graduation, right?
That's right!
Why don't we write about our dreams
for after graduation!
Our dreams for the future?
Yeah, and then we can write,
"We're doing well and working hard
to achieve our dreams!"
MY DREAM
I want to do so many things.
There's not enough space in this letter.
I want to graduate school and...
Having trouble sleeping?
There's a lot of them by the front door.
Looks like they don't like getting wet,
even now that they're like this.
I found this earlier.
Sakura
It says "Sakura" on it.
Megu-nee...
Is it alright if I hold on to this?
It might be helpful in some way.
Sure, here.
Thank you.
I'm sure that one day, we'll be able to leave here.
Yes.
I wonder when the rain will stop.
I'm sure it'll all be alright.
Alright!
It's time.
Good luck, little Pidgey!
Wait, who the hell is Pidgey?
This little guy, Pidgey Hatonishiki!
No, his name is Arnold!
Aww, I wanna name him, too!
I'm the one who caught him!
"Pidgey" is cuter!
He looks way more like an "Arnold" though!
C'mon, you two, please stop.
But he looks like a "Pidgey"!
Why don't you use both and name him
Arnold Hatonishiki the Second?
It's Arnold!
Why don't you use both and name him
Arnold Hatonishiki the Second?
Fine.
Okay, his name is Arnold Hatonishiki the Second!
Name:
Arnold Hatonishiki
the Second
Where did "the second" come from?
Okay, Arnold Hatonishiki the Second.
Fly well!
On the count of three, okay?
Ready?
One!
Two!
Three!
To Kei.
Kei, how are you?
I'm living somewhere new and
made some new friends.
I'm doing well.
Taromaru is doing well, too.
It's all thanks to everyone here.
Are you fine with just being alive?
Yes.
Living is such a wonderful thing.
The dew may fall and the flower remain,
or the flower wilt and the dew remain.
What's that about?
Words my friend liked.
Huh.
I hope someone finds them.
I hope one day our paths cross again.
We're doing fine.
Bathed in the crimson light
What were you thinking of?
I thought you were beautiful as you tried to brush it off
Tears welling in your eyelashes
I always thought
That these days would go on forever
Without a doubt
The sky we looked up at
Looks upon us from so far away
We just gripped each other’s lost hands
Quietly, without ever changing
I’m not lonely anymore
I just keep moving towards the other side of the ending world
I can see our sunrise
I can see it
So smile
Next Time!
I wonder where Arnold is now?
He's a second generation Japanese man,
so maybe he went to America?
Wow, Arnold!
He is Arnold Hatonishiki's son.
How do you know all this?!
Future
Next time on School-Live, episode 8:
"Future"