Hey, Mop-Top!
Sir!
What do they call you, maggot?
Armin Arlelt, from Shinganshina, sir!
Wow, seriously? Why would your
parents curse you with such a dumb name?
It was my grandfather, sir!
Cadet Arlelt! Why is a runt like you here?
To help humanity overcome the Titans!
That is delightful to hear!
You're gonna be a great light snack for him!
Row Three, About Face, runt!
What do you call yourself?
Sir. My name is Thomas Wagner,
I'm from the Trost district!
I can't hear you!
I'm from Trost, sir, my name...
Look at him go.
The man is a master when it comes to fresh-faced recruits.
That takes me back.
Is a pathetic worm like you
the best Karaness has to offer?
Sir! I'm afraid that's the case, sir!
Tell your backwoods...
But what's the point of all the intimidation?
It's a Rite of Passage. Through stress and
denigration we revert them into blank slates.
From there, we can mold them
bit by bit into proper soldiers.
He is the first step in that process.
We seem to really excel at that back home, sir!
Row Four, About Face!
There are some he's passing by.
A drill instructor is nothing compared
to what those recruits have seen.
They were there. Witnesses to the
hell of the Titan attack two years ago.
You can read it in their faces.
C'mon. Let's go.
What do we have over here?
Jean Kirschtein, sir. From the Trost District!
And why're you here, cadet?
To join the Military Police, sir. The best of the best.
That's nice. You want to live in the interior, do you?
Yes!
No one told you to sit, Recruit!
If you can't handle this, Kirschtein,
then forget about joining the Military Police!
What the hell is wrong with your face, you smiling idiot?
Marco Bodt at your service, sir, from Jinae.
South side of Wall Rose. I aim to join the Military
Police and give life and limb in service to the king!
Well then. That makes you an idealistic fool. And a rube.
You want the truth?
The only use the king has for your
life and limbs are as Titan fodder.
Hey, Cue-ball. You're up next!
Oh, me? Sir! Conny Springer, from Ragako village, sir!
You have it backwards, Conny Springer.
That was the first thing you were taught.
This salute represents the resolve
in your heart to fight those bent on
the systematic destruction of our people!
Is your heart on your right side?
Hey, you there. What do you think you're doing?
You are officially on my shit list.
Just who in the hell are you?
Sasha Braus from Dauper village, at your service.
Reporting for duty, sir!
Sasha Braus, huh?
And what is that you're clutching in your right hand?
A steamed potato!
It sat there in the mess hall begging to be eaten. Sir!
The theft, I understand.
But here? Why eat it here of all places?
It looked quite delicious. And it was getting cold.
So I gave it shelter in my stomach, sir.
Why? I can't comprehend. Why would you eat that potato?
Are you asking me why people eat potatoes?
I'm surprised you don't know, sir.
Here sir. Have half.
"Have half?" Really?
Man, I thought Sadies was gonna kill Potato Girl.
I know. What a helluva first day.
It's funny.
Being told to run 'til the sun sets
didn't seem to bother her nearly as much as
losing meal privileges for the next five days.
I think she said that she's from Dauper.
If I remember right, that's a small
hunting village up in the mountains.
Hey, what's that?
They're dropouts. They'd prefer to work in the fields.
But. It's only the first day.
That's the way it is.
If you can't handle the pressure, you've gotta leave.
I can't believe anyone would
rather pull plants than fight.
I know about some of us, but you never
mentioned where you were from, Eren.
The same as Armin. From Shinganshina.
Oh, wow. That means.
You saw it. You were there that day.
Huh? Quiet!
The Colossal one? Did you see him?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
Yeah, okay? I saw the big guy.
Whoa, seriously?
Okay, exactly how tall was he?
He stuck his head over the outer wall.
Whoa, wait! I heard he stepped over the wall completely.
So did I!
That was the rumor in my village, too!
Nah. He was big, but not that big.
So what did it look like?
It had a mouth like a corpse. And no skin, just muscles.
And the Armored Titan? The one
that broke through Wall Maria?
Is that what they're calling it? In all
the panic, it was just another Titan to me.
No way. So, what were they like?
C'mon. That's enough questions, alright?
I'm sure he'd rather not relive
everything he went through.
Sorry. We didn't mean to...
It's not like that!
Those stupid Titans. They're
really not that big of a deal.
If we focus on mastering the
Omni-Directional Mobility Gear
they give us, then it's Titan payback time!
I've waited years to be trained as a soldier.
All of a sudden, the reality is sinking in.
I'm joining the Scout Regiment.
Then I'm sending the Titans back
to hell. I'm gonna butcher them all.
Hey, are you crazy or something?
Not that it's my business, but signing up
for reconnaissance is like a death sentence.
I guess we'll see. Or at least I will.
You seem content hiding in the interior with the MPs.
Look, I'm just speaking honestly here, kid.
I think it's better than being some loud
mouthed braggart tough-guy wannabe pretending
he's not as piss-scared as the rest of us.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Stop it you guys!
Alright, sure. Makes no difference to me.
Huh?
Hey. I apologize. Sorry for calling you
names and dismissing your choice of career.
Put 'er there, kid. Whaddaya say?
Right. Yeah, I'm sorry as well.
Umm. Excuse me?
I... Uh. I just wanted... I mean.
I've never seen anyone like you before. I mean, uh.
I'm... I'm sorry. You have really beautiful black hair.
Thank you.
Would you lay off? It's no big deal!
It's just that you get so worked
up you don't think things through.
Again with this?
If you insist on worrying,
worry about how long your hair is.
It's gonna catch up with you in a
bad way when we start on the ODMs.
Okay, fine. I'll cut it.
How short should I go, do you think?
What the hell? Leave my clothes alone, dammit!
What did you wipe on me?
Don't worry. Just my trust.
I'm... finished.
Could it be? It's bread!
I'm sorry there isn't more. It's all I could take.
Hey, hang on. You really should
drink a little water first.
You... You're a Goddess, aren't you? Glory unto you!
Hey. Just what are you two girls up to?
Well, uh. She's been running
all day. Without any food or water.
I see. So you're trying to be "nice," huh?
Eh?
What's the point of breakin' the rules for Potato Girl?
That mindless act of kindness gets you absolutely nowhere.
Whatever.
Let's just get her to bed already.
I'm confused. Are you being nice?
I'm helping her so that she'll owe me one in the future.
I intend to make use of her stupidity.
It's aptitude test time, so listen up!
There is no place for you here if you cannot perform!
Fail, and be shipped to the fields.
We're just drilling the fundamentals here.
You can still determine a Cadet's
knack for it just by watching.
Like her. Completely steady.
She inherently knows what to
do, and how to make it happen.
That's what aptitude is all about.
I'd say we have several capable cadets this year.
And what about this guy?
That's precisely why we run these tests.
He proves that drive and dedication
do not always translate into capability.
What is your major malfunction, Jaeger?
Straighten yourself up!
Why am I... How do I work this thing?
This can't be happening!
Just remember the basics and you should be fine.
No need to try any fancy maneuvers.
Just focus on your balance.
Then distribute your weight evenly
between the belts on your waist and your legs.
Loosen up your stance a little bit.
If I could do it, I know that you can!
Okay. A loose stance, but balanced.
Let's give it a shot, Armin.
Hey, Daz. He was talking big
about butchering all the Titans,
but he got real quiet after ODM training, didn't he?
I guess it's the fields for him tomorrow.
Can't keep wasting food on the useless.
Eren.
Worrying won't solve a thing.
There's still time to get some practice in come morning.
How pathetic. How am I supposed to kill
'em if I can't even stand up straight?
It might be time to let that dream die.
Whaddaya mean?
I think you should give up this attempt to be a soldier.
There's a lot more to fighting and combat
than just throwing your life away in vain.
What're you saying? After everything we
saw that day, after what happened to my mom.
You're crazy if you think I'm just going to walk away.
I get it. But it doesn't matter how determined you are.
It... Wait, what do you mean?
Because whether or not you're
fit to be a soldier isn't up to you.
You misunderstand. I'm not saying you
should return to the fields by yourself.
I wouldn't dream of it.
Because wherever you go. I'm gonna go with you...
So. Uh. Are you saying...
that you're not going to finish that?
What's the trick to posture control? Hard to say.
Guess I got the "gift". You've just gotta feel it, y'know?
I'm trying to figure out your trick.
You've screwed upevery way imaginable, short
of an accidental equipment-related asphyxiation.
Please guys. You gotta help me, I'm begging you!
That's funny. Wasn't it just yesterday you said
"if you can't handle the pressure, you gotta leave?"
No, wait. Or was it "if you're a
complete idiot, you gotta leave?"
Something like that.
Oh, come on. I heard from everyone
you're both really good at it!
Bertholdt! Reiner!
Sorry kid. But there isn't any
special trick to just hanging there.
Not to be harsh, but if it's advice
you want, I'm not really the guy.
Alright.
Let's just hope it comes to you tomorrow.
Hold on. Aren't the two of
you originally from Shiganshina?
Yeah, that's right.
Then you know first-hand how terrifying they are.
Why on earth would you want to be soldiers?
I didn't see the things. Eren did.
He saw their bloodlust first hand,
before anyone realized how bad it was.
And I... I knew I couldn't sit idly by as the
royal government forced the citizenry into the failed
territory retrieval operation.
I see.
So where are the two of you from?
Oh, Reiner and I? We were both from a
mountain village just Southeast of Wall Maria.
But. Then that means.
Yeah. Unlike the more prosperous river towns,
our village didn't receive word right away.
The Titans were on us before
we even knew what was going on.
It happened at dawn. All the livestock were so restless.
Soon after, we heard these strange
rumblings that just became louder and louder.
Eventually, I realized those rumblings were
the sound of death getting closer. I, uh...
I looked out my window, and...
After that, well, uh. Everything is just a blur.
I think we all just panicked.
Hey. Easy now.
You're just getting yourself worked up again.
Sorry. Basically, what I've been trying to say is this.
The four of us aren't like the rest of... of them.
"Them" who?
The others here who've never
been witness to the Titan's horror.
Hey.
Most of them are here for show.
To do just what society expects.
In a world where you're labeled a coward if
you choose fieldwork by the time you turn twelve,
propriety demands our service.
With that said, I'm really no different from the others.
I joined the ranks hoping for assignment to
the Military Police. Tucked away in the Interior.
If that doesn't work out, I'll give up entirely.
I don't really have the fortitude for anything else.
There's no shame in caring about
your life, Bertholdt. We all do.
Do we?
I'm going to return to the home that was
taken from me. That's all I care about now.
I will do it. No matter what.
What about you? Why did you sign up?
Why'd I join?
I decided I have to kill them.
I won't stop 'til every single Titan is dead and rotting.
Dead. Every last one.
You saw what those monsters are capable of,
and you still want to take them on?
Damn right. It's just, after screwing up the training,
I don't know if I'm cut out to be a soldier.
We'll take it from step one: Belt Adjustment.
By tomorrow, you'll be an expert.
I know you've got what it takes. I can see it in you.
Am I wrong here?
No! I won't fail. Thank you, Reiner. Thank you.
Eren Jaeger. Are you ready?
Yes sir! I'm going to do it. I have to!
I may not be as talented as the rest.
But nobody, nobody, has more guts!
Proceed!
The moment of truth. I won't fail again.
To hell with working the damn fields! I'm not giving up.
Not without a fight!
I did it? No, I'm doing it!
No! Not yet!
Once more! I can do it!
Lower him.
I... I'm finished.
Wagner! Please exchange belts with Mr. Jaeger.
Huh? Yes sir!
Your equipment was defective.
If given a piece of functional gear,
you might not be worthless after all.
Quartermaster didn't notice this broken clasp.
Might have to visit the Supply
Depot and crack a couple skulls.
He... He still did it. Even
while wearing that busted gear.
Amazing.
So, you mean I... I didn't wash out?
You made the cut. Now keep training, cadet!
I did it. I really did it!
Check it out, Mikasa! I'm doing it!
I can fight the Titans!
You don't have to worry about me!
Not anymore!
It seems like things worked out for him.
Look, his eyes are saying "check me out!"
They're not.
His eyes are saying he doesn't
have to leave me. Not anymore.
Grisha. Today should bring you pride.
Your son is a soldier!
After graduating from the Cadets,
Eren sees mankind begin to restore its dignity.
"We can beat the Titans."
The moment he feels certain of this,
humanity is given a grim reminder.