♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THE STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK. 3, 2, 1,
LET'S JAM. ♪
WHAT IS A PHYSICAL BODY?
THE BODY IS MERELY AN OBJECT.
IT IS A FORM OF EXISTENCE
FAR TOO IMPURE
TO STORE THE GODS
WITHIN OUR SCORED SOULS.
NOW YOU WILL REMEMBER
BLOODSTAINED HISTORY,
MATERIAL GREED, HUNGER,
SEXUAL DESIRE,
DESIRE TO DOMINATE,
DESIRE FOR FAME,
HUMANITY.
FROM THE PHYSICAL BODY,
ALL THE DESIRES ARE BORN,
AND THE HUMAN EGO
WILL NEVER DISAPPEAR
AS LONG AS DESIRE
REMAINS PRESENT.
HUMANS WILL CONTINUE TO FIGHT
TO FULFILL THEIR BODY'S DESIRES,
AND IT WILL NEVER END.
THERE'S NO FUTURE.
YOU MUST AWAKEN
AWAKEN YOUR SOUL.
RID YOURSELF OF THAT
FILTHY HUMAN BODY NOW.
WE ARE SCRATCH,
THE MIGRATE TO
ELECTRONICS MOVEMENT.
WE ARE DISCIPLES OF GOD,
SENT HERE TO FREE
YOUR SOUL FROM YOUR BODY
AND LEAD YOU TO
THE INFINITE SEA OF ELECTRONS.
♪ COWBOY ♪
♪ BEBOP ♪
GOOD EVENING.
THIS IS CBC ACTION NEWS.
OUR TOP STORY,
THE MIGRATE TO ELECTRONICS
GROUP SCRATCH.
RECEIVING SUBPOENAS FOR THEIR
LEADER, LONDES, LAST WEEK,
THE I.S.S.P. AND THE SOLAR
SYSTEM POLICE BEGAN SEARCHING
THE HOMES OF SCRATCH'S
HIGHEST-RANKING MEMBERS.
[SIREN]
YET ANOTHER TRAGEDY.
EASY CONTACT
AND SALVATION OF SOULS,
THAT HAS BEEN THE MAIN CAUSE
OF THE PHENOMENAL
GROWTH OF SCRATCH.
HOWEVER, ONE MORE SUICIDE HAS--
THE FOLLOWERS OF SCRATCH USE
THE BRAINWAVE CONTROL DEVICE
ON THIS NEW GAME CONSOLE TO
SCAN THEIR OWN BRAIN WAVES
USING A PROGRAM CREATED
BY THEIR LEADER, LONDES.
A PROGRAM THAT IS SAID
TO COPY THEIR SPIRIT
WHICH IS TRANSFORMED
FROM BRAIN WAVES
INTO DIGITAL DATA
AND RELAYED ONTO
THE UNIVERSAL NETWORK
WHERE IT TAKES ON
A TRANSCENDED LEVEL OF BEING.
THUS ALLOWING THEM TO EXIST
AS SOULS WITHOUT BODIES.
NOW, PROFESSOR,
THEY SAY THAT LONDES THE LEADER
WAS ONCE A REPUTABLE DOCTOR.
COULD A DOCTOR DEVISE
THIS KIND OF METHODOLOGY?
THAT'S ABSURD.
IT'S PURE SCIENCE FICTION.
SOME OF IT IS
THEORETICALLY POSSIBLE,
BUT IT'S A THEORY
ONLY A THEORY.
AFTER ALL--
[CRYING]
AND HE HASN'T RETURNED
IN TWO WEEKS.
MADAM, YOU NEED TO TALK
THIS OUT WITH YOUR HUSBAND.
I MEAN, IT'S HIS SON,
TOO, ISN'T IT?
YEAH, BUT HE ISN'T THE TYPE
TO JUST RUN AWAY FROM HOME.
WHAT IF HE KIDNAPPED MY BOY?
WHOA, MADAM, ARE YOU
EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
THAT MUST BE IT!
IT'S LIKE YOUR CULT THING,
YOU KNOW THAT
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
TAKE A SHORT BREAK.
HEY, ARE YOU READY
FOR THE POWER C.D.J.?
THEN LET'S START THE GROOVING!
OUR NEW EXERCISER
RELEASES YOUR INNER D.J.
ADJUST THE BPM USING THIS LEVER!
AND BINGO, YOU CAN BE A D.J.
WHILE YOU WORK OUT!
AND CAN YOU
TELL US THE REASON
YOU DECIDED TO SIGN UP?
YES, I...
I GOT TIRED OF ALWAYS
BEING IN DEBT.
AND THEN, BY SOME MIRACLE,
I FOUND MY WAY HERE.
YOU SEE, IF I GET
RID OF MY BODY,
I WON'T NEED MONEY.
EW.
HEY, JEFF.
HANG ON.
IT'S ALMOST READY.
FORGET THAT.
GET OVER HERE QUICK.
HUH?
BY RELEASING THE SPIRIT
FROM THE PHYSICAL BODY,
WE ARE ABLE TO
ELIMINATE ALL DESIRE.
OH.
I WAS WONDERING WHERE SHE WAS.
THIS MUST BE SOME KIND
OF A SCAM, RIGHT?
BRAIN DREAM!
THE NEW GAME CONSOLE
BRAIN DREAM
CATCHES YOUR BRAIN WAVES
AND PUTS THEM INTO ACTION
SO YOU CONTROL THE GAME
THE WAY YOU WANT IT.
PROBLEMS IN GAME LAND?
TANGLED CORDS? THROW THEM AWAY
AND DREAM WITH US!
LET'S DREAM!
ORDER NOW AND GET
A FREE BAMBOO STEAMER.
THAT IS WHY OUR STATION
HAS THE STRICTEST
BROADCASTING POLICIES
PROHIBITING PROGRAMS SUCH
AS THE ONE YOU'RE WATCHING.
OH, THERE IT IS.
CHOW TIME!
DR. LONDES,
HE'S WANTED FOR
FIRST-DEGREE MURDER.
THE BOUNTY IS 38 MILLION.
I SEE.
WELL, THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY
SHE FLAKED, WOULDN'T IT?
LOOKS LIKE WAY BACK WHEN
HE WAS AN R&D GUY
IN NEUROBIOLOGY.
ONE DAY HE GETS A CALL FROM GOD
AND START A NEW
RESEARCH PROJECT
HOW TO STORE THE HUMAN SPIRIT.
IN OTHER WORDS, THE ACTIVITIES
OF THE BRAIN AS DIGITAL DATA.
SHORTLY THEREAFTER
HE TURNS UP MISSING
FOR HALF A CENTURY.
FASTFORWARD TO TWO YEARS AGO.
THE GUY SUDDENLY SHOWS BACK UP
AND STARTS THIS MIGRATE
TO ELECTRONICS MOVEMENT
SCRATCH.
WHICH IS WHAT?
A RELIGIOUS GROUP OR A CULT.
WHATEVER!
ANYWAY, ACCORDING TO LONDES,
THE HUMAN MIND IS ESSENTIALLY
A WEAK STREAM
OF ELECTRONIC PULSES.
SO IF YOU CAPTURE THOSE
PULSES AS DATA
AND DOWNLOAD THEM ONTO
THE UNIVERSAL NETWORK
AS AN INTEGRATED PROGRAM,
THE PERSON CAN MIGRATE
TO A NEW EXISTENCE
AS A PURE SOUL WITHOUT A BODY.
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
HEY, UP TO YOU IF YOU
BELIEVE IN THAT STUFF.
20,000 PEOPLE DO BELIEVE IT
OF WHICH ABOUT 100 HAVE
COMMITTED SUICIDE
OR OTHERWISE DISAPPEARED,
WHICH IS WHY
THE COPS ARE FINALLY
GETTING THEIR
LAZY BUTTS IN GEAR.
TASTELESS BASE.
SECONDS!
THAT'S ALL THERE IS.
OH.
LET'S GET 'EM.
WE ARE SCRATCH,
THE MIGRATE TO
ELECTRONICS MOVEMENT.
WE ARE DISCIPLES OF GOD
SENT HERE TO FREE YOUR
SOUL FROM YOUR BODY
AND LEAD YOU TO
THE INFINITE SEA OF ELECTRONS.
[GRUNTS]
ECCH.
SEARCHING, SEARCHING!
WHERE ARE YOU?
HI. SO, YOU WANT TO JOIN OUR
GROUP AND RENOUNCE YOUR BODY?
UH... YEAH.
OF COURSE, WE'LL NEED
TO CLEANSE YOUR SOUL
AS A FIRST STEP.
WE CAN START IMMEDIATELY.
UH, RIGHT. BUT BEFORE THAT,
I REALLY WANT TO
MEET MR. LONDES.
UH, WHERE IS HE?
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
HA HA, REALLY?
HE'S UP IN HEAVEN.
LONDES, HMM.
WAS THERE A FELLOW
GOING BY THAT HANDLE?
YOU GOT TO HELP ME, OLD MAN.
ALL HIS COLLEAGUES ARE GONE.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
STILL ALIVE, SO THINK.
UH...
CAN YOU REMEMBER
ANYTHING AT ALL?
MAYBE HE EXISTED,
AND MAYBE HE DIDN'T.
OH.
WELL, WHICH IS IT?
[SNORING]
OH, SO YOU WANT TO
JOIN OUR MIGRATION?
UH, YEAH.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
TO CLEANSE YOUR SOUL.
THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
WE CAN START RIGHT AWAY.
UH...
WELL, CAN I ASK SOMETHING
BEFORE WE DO ALL THAT?
YOU SEE, I WANT TO
MEET MR. LONDES.
WELL, HIM OR HIS SOUL
OR WHATEVER, YOU KNOW.
ANYWAY, WHERE CAN
I FIND THIS GUY?
EXCUSE ME?
YOU REALLY WANT TO
JOIN THIS MIGRATION?
[MAKING AIRPLANE NOISES]
AND THAT IS WHY ALL
OF THE ATTENTION
IS FOCUSED THIS WEEK
ON DR. LONDES.
THE FIRST BIG BOUNTY
IN MONTHS!
SAD TO SAY, WE HAVE NO INFO.
NOTHING, NADA, ZILCH!
HUH?
EVERYONE'S HUNTING
HIGH AND LOW,
BUT NO ONE CAN FIND
HIDE NOR HAIR OF THIS GUY.
HIS FACE IS ON TV EVERY DAY
FOR THE SCRATCH TELECAST,
BUT TRY TO TRACK HIM DOWN
AND IT'S LIKE HE DOES NOT EXIST.
OH, DO YOU REALLY THINK
HE IS A SOUL WITHOUT A BODY?
I HAVE SOMETHING ELSE
TO TELL YOU, JUDY,
AND IT'S KIND OF IMPORTANT.
REALLY?! WHAT IS IT, PONCH?!
WELL...
OH, BOY! I CAN'T WAIT!
THIS HERE IS THE VERY LAST
BROADCAST OF "BIG SHOT."
WE'RE CANCELLED, SHUCKS! HOWDY!
HAPPY TRAILS AND ALL THAT!
WHAT?!
OUR RATINGS SUCK SO THEY'RE
TAKING US OFF THE AIR.
YEAH!? MY AGENT WILL HAVE
SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT THIS!
NO LUCK?
NO LUCK.
I DIDN'T GET ANYTHING EITHER.
AW, NO WAY!
NO WAY, NO WAY,
NO WAY, NO WAY!
I WENT AFTER HIS COLLEAGUES
FROM THE RESEARCH LAB,
BUT IT WAS A DEAD END.
YEAH, I GOT THE SAME THING
WITH THE MEMBERS OF HIS CULT.
[BEEPS]
HUH?!
IT'S FAYEFAYE.
HUH?
IT'S A LITTLE TOUGH RIGHT NOW,
BUT... UGH!
ARE YOU LISTENING?
I THINK I CAN REALLY
GET RID OF MY DEBTS NOW.
[PANTING]
YOU DEAL WITH FAYE.
I'M TRUSTING YOU ON THAT.
GREAT.
I GO SOLO WHILE YOU HANG OUT
IN KIDDIE LAND ALL DAY.
LIKE I SAID
UH, BRAIN DREAM IS A HOT ITEM.
I'VE GOT TO LINE UP HERE
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
IF I WANT ONE.
YOU STILL THINK YOU CAN
HACK INTO HIS WEB PAGE
THROUGH A VIDEO GAME, HUH?
LOOK, IT'S THE ONLY
LEAD WE'VE GOT LEFT,
SO I'M GONNA FOLLOW IT UP.
IF FAYE HAS SOMETHING,
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN USE IT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M ON IT.
UH...
YEAH, FIRE IT UP.
EEYYUP!
WELCOME TO SCRATCH,
THE MIGRATE TO
ELECTRONICS MOVEMENT.
SELECT LINE ONE IF YOU WOULD
LIKE TO JOIN OUR MIGRATION.
SELECT LINE TWO FOR
MORE INFORMATION,
FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS,
AND SITE MAP.
SO, IT WON'T COPY MY
SPIRIT AUTOMATICALLY.
WELL, LET'S JUMP RIGHT IN.
YOU'VE CHOSEN TO JOIN US.
PLEASE INPUT YOUR PERSONAL DATA
BY FOLLOWING THE PROMPTS.
DATA, DATA,
BOGUS DATA.
HMM.
BLOOD AND MUSCLE AND BONE.
WHEN THESE ARE LOST,
EACH HUMAN BEING
CONFRONTS HIS OWN DEATH.
[GROWLS]
HUH?
AND WHAT LIES BEYOND?
HEAVEN, HELL, REINCARNATION?
THESE ARE FANTASIES WHICH
CANNOT POSSIBLY EXIST.
THEY ARE MERE EXCUSES.
[BARKS]
EIN, WHAT'S UP?
HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
HUH?
NO PATH TO SALVATION
HAS HAD THE CLEAR VISION
OF REALITY WE NOW HAVE.
[SIGHING]
[STAMMERING]
AWAKEN YOUR SPIRIT.
SHED THE FILTH OF
YOUR PHYSICAL BODY...
NOW.
[SCREAMS]
[SNARLING]
- HIGH FREQUENCY?
- YEAH.
I'M NOT SURE HOW, BUT IT ACTS
ON THE CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM
PARALYZING THE SYMPATHETIC NERVES.
OH! IT'S ALL VERY FAST,
WITHIN SECONDS.
EVERYTHING GOES BLANK
AND YOU PASS OUT.
EIN SENSED THERE WAS SOMETHING
WRONG AND FANGED ME.
IF HE HADN'T DONE THAT, I'D
BE A MEMBER OF
SCRATCH RIGHT NOW.
ANYWAY, WE NEED TO FIND
A WAY TO COUNTERACT IT, SO...
I THINK I'LL TRY
MIGRATING MYSELF.
HEY, SPIKE, WAIT!
HEY!
WELL, DOGS HAVE BRAIN WAVES.
OH, ED WANTS TO DO IT, TOO!
IF YOUR BRAIN MIGRATES,
WHO'S GONNA SEARCH
THE NET FOR LONDES, HUH?
AWW!
QUIT WHINING.
ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO SCRATCH,
THE MIGRATE TO
ELECTRONICS MOVEMENT.
SELECT LINE ONE
ED, THAT'S ABSOLUTE PERFECTION.
OH, YEAH.
AH.
HMM? OH, MY!
IT CAN'T BE.
THE PERSON KNOWN AS
LONDES NEVER EXISTED.
HIS PAST, ALL THE RECORDS,
THEY'RE ALL COUNTERFEIT.
AN ELABORATE CONSTRUCTION.
AND ALL THE PROGRAMMING LEADS
TO THIS LOCATION RIGHT HERE...
ALLES VALLEY HOSPICE.
COME ON, ED.
I GOT AN IDEA.
OH.
PAPA!
[GROANS]
NOT YET.
PAPA!
NOBODY HERE WANTS VISITORS,
AND APPOINTMENTS ARE
REQUIRED IN ANY CASE.
THE POLICY IS STRICTLY ENFORCED.
WHAT DID YOU COME HERE FOR,
AN INHERITANCE OR SOMETHING?
NOT AT ALL.
YOU SEE, HER TWIN
BROTHER IS HERE,
AND SHE'S SUFFERED SO MUCH.
PAPA!
SHE'S AN
UNUSUAL-LOOKING CHILD.
IS SHE A GIRL?
MY PAPA!
ACTUALLY...
IT'S A LONG, VERY
DRAMATIC STORY.
I JUST PUT HER INTO
A STATE OF DEEP SLEEP.
OF COURSE, AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE OTHER BOUNTY HUNTERS
SLEPT TO DEATH.
AND SO WE FINALLY TRACKED
HER LONG-LOST BROTHER
TO THIS HOSPICE.
[WHIMPERS]
PAPA!
IT WAS SUCH A SHOCK
TO MY DAUGHTER.
SHE'S BEEN SO TRAUMATIZED.
I THOUGHT IF SHE COULD JUST
SEE HER BROTHER ONCE MORE.
GO ON IN.
- THANKS SO MUCH.
- UHHUH.
WHY DO YOU KILL OFF
THE MEMBERS OF YOUR OWN GROUP?
WHAT'S THE POINT OF THAT?
I AM NOT FORCING
ANYTHING ON ANYONE.
THEY ARE MERELY
PRACTICING A FAITH
THAT THEY DECIDED TO BELIEVE IN
OF THEIR OWN FREE WILL.
TELL ME, WHY DO YOU THINK
PEOPLE BELIEVE IN GOD?
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO.
IT'S NOT EASY LIVING IN SUCH
AN UGLY, CORRUPT WORLD.
THERE IS NO CERTAINTY
AND NOTHING TO HOPE FOR.
PEOPLE ARE LOST,
SO THEY REACH OUT.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
GOD DIDN'T CREATE HUMANS.
NO, IT'S HUMANS WHO CREATED GOD.
[MAKING AIRPLANE NOISES]
UH.
HUH?
LONDES?
I'M SICK OF THIS
LITTLE ACT OF YOURS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
COME ON OUT HERE.
ILLUSIONS AREN'T ENOUGH.
I NEED MORE.
YOU ARE CORRECT.
THIS IS AN ILLUSION.
LONDES DOESN'T EXIST AT ALL.
HE'S AN IMAGINARY CHARACTER
THAT I INVENTED.
AN ILLUSORY IMAGE CREATED
BY SCANNING DIGITAL LINES.
I WONDER, IS THIS
A BRAIN WAVE CONTROL SYSTEM
LIKE THAT BRAIN DREAM?
- HEY, EDWARD?
- YEAH?
CAN YOU DISCONNECT
A BRAIN WAVE CONTROLLER
FROM THE NETWORK?
- UHHUH!
- DO IT.
BUT DON'T TURN OFF
THE LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THE GREATEST
AND ALSO THE WORST DEVICE
THAT HUMANS EVER INVENTED?
IT'S TELEVISION.
TELEVISION CONTROLS PEOPLE
BY BOMBARDING THEM
WITH INFORMATION UNTIL THEY
LOSE THEIR SENSE OF REALITY.
NOW TELEVISION ITSELF HAS
BECOME THE NEW RELIGION.
UH!
TELEVISION HAS CREATED
A PEOPLE WHO BELIEVE INSTANTLY
IN DRAMATIC FANTASIES,
WHO CAN BE CONTROLLED
BY TINY DOTS OF LIGHT.
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE LIKE A KID WITH A TOY.
WHAT?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT CAN'T
TELL FANTASY FROM REALITY.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT LIVES
IN THE LITTLE DOTS OF LIGHT.
IF YOU WANT TO DREAM,
JUST DO IT BY YOURSELF.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANYTHING?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT YOU
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT ME?
[GRUNTS]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP THAT!
CUT IT OUT!
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
NO, STOP.
NO! STOP IT!
STOP IT!
DON'T TURN IT OFF.
WHAT?
WHAT DID I DO?
NO!
THIS ISN'T FAIR.
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE LIKE THIS?
EVERYONE SHOULD HAVE...
THE SAME BODY AS I HAVE.
EVERYONE...
NO...
I DON'T...
I DON'T WANT TO DISAPPEAR!
I DON'T WANT TO...
RONNIE SPANGER.
USED TO BE A HACKER.
THE BOY WHO BECAME
A SOCALLED VEGETABLE
WHEN HE HAD A MEDICAL ACCIDENT
TWO YEARS AGO AT AGE 13.
THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE SURE NOT
A BOY ANY LONGER.
YOU ARE QUITE A CON ARTIST.
[GROANS]
OH, IT'S YOU.
LONG TIME NO SEE.
WHERE ARE WE?
[CHUCKLES]
IT WAS ALL A KID'S DREAM.
I GUESS ALL HE COULD
DO WAS DREAM,
SO THE DREAMS TURNED DARK.
AND THIS TIME, I HOPE
YOU HAVE SWEET DREAMS.
THE SOULS THAT GOD
HAS GIVEN US
OUR SPIRITS,
WHICH FOUND A WAY
TO SWIM THROUGH
THE IMMENSE NETWORK
AND LIVE IN
THE INFINITY OF SPACE
IS NOT THE HUMAN BODY
A MERE SHELL,
A FORM OF EXISTENCE ALL TOO
SMALL AND WEAK FOR CONSCIOUSNESS
WITH SUCH VAST REACH
AND POTENTIAL?
[GIRL HUMMING]
NEXT EPISODE,
HARD LUCK WOMAN.