Everyone, that was a nice practice.
Yeah!
I can just feel my skill level rising!
Summer vacation is about to end,
but I want to work even harder on my basketball.
Oh!
Gotta work hard!
Hehehe!
Everyone's so pumped up!
Is everyone ready for the summer festival?
Of course!
I have my yukata ready!
I asked my mom already.
Oh! I'll have a goldfish sash!
It's the last event during the summer vacation!
Everyone at my shopping district is hyped up!
It'll be lots of fun!
I want to eat candied apricots!
Oh!
I want to eat some, too!
I want to catch some goldfish!
Let's create some wonderful memories!
Yeah!
Okose! Big Halation
Let it happen! Big halation!
Ano hi no chikai o hatasu tame
The vow we made that day! We'll make it happen!
Hirake! New Formation
Open up! New formation!
Shisen no aizu yobi au
We signal to each other.
Kibou o nosete hanate Arch
Release the arch that carries our dreams.
Itsumo no toori ne Shinjiteru (makasete)
Same as usual, right? We believe. (Leave it to me.)
Mune ni te o atate te hikioseta heijoushin
I put my hand to my chest to calm my nerves.
Kanaete kita koto Sorezore ga oboeteru
I remember the things that I wanted to make happen.
Ano hi hisoka ni naita koto mo
Like that day when I cried secretly to myself.
Onaji yume miteru no wa Watashitachi dake jainain da yo ne
We weren't the only ones who saw that dream.
Me no mae ni arawareta
It happened in front of our eyes.
Yuru ga nai hitomi hibana chirashite
Unwavering eyes which released fireworks.
Okose! Big Halation
Let it happen! Big Halation!
Hiraku SPACE e hashirikome
Cut into that open space!
Wazuka na Sensation
That little bit of sensation!
Senobishiteita kinou e
Stand tall and stretch! To yesterday!
Wakare o tsugetara
If you tell me that you are leaving,
Egao o tsunagete
then I'll connect your smile with mine.
Yume mita basho he hanate Arch
Release the arch which will carry us to the place we saw in our dreams.
Translator: Ladholyman | Timer/Encoder/QC: Maceart | Raw: SOFCJ-Raws
Presented by Doremi-fansubs | #doremi@irc.rizon.net | www.doremi-fansubs.com
Elementary School Students - Wo~rld!
I've been a coach for these five kids at Keishin Girls' Academy for the last three months.
We've accomplished a lot during this period of time.
The five of them taught me a lot, too.
This period of time has been extremly precious.
Here!
Shooting Guard - Minato Tomoka.
Point Guard - Nagatsuka Saki.
Center - Kashii Airi.
Small Forward - Hakamada Hinata.
Here! Maho!
Power Forward - Misawa Maho.
They have been maturing every single day.
Everyone!
I brought some refreshments!
Here we go!
So good!
Delicious!
Eat up, everyone.
Okay!
Yep. Now it seems like you're a good guy now, Miho.
I'm the advisor, so doing this is natural.
You aren't a student here, so you have no right to be eating that!
Nevermind. You're just terrible.
Airi's not afraid anymore.
Thank you very much.
Saki and Tomoka pair up with each other quite well.
You both have gotten much better.
Saki, you went a bit easy on Airi, right?
Yes, I found myself in front of Airi,
but I wanted to see Saki and Airi go at it.
R-Really?
You're right. 1v1 sounds like fun.
Let's have a go at it next time, Airi.
Okay! I won't lose!
You're quite perceptive as usual, Aoi.
Well, there are things only girls can understand with each other.
You're really a great help.
I'm not really doing this for you...
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Your father has something to tell you.
I'm home.
Tomoka, take a seat right there.
Okay.
You have been really into basketball lately.
Schoolwork, art of tea, and Japanese traditional dancing.
I don't like it when you let go of everything for the sake of basketball.
Two misses in a row?
Did something happen?
Well, my father got angry at me yesterday.
Huh!? You made your father angry!?
It's a common occurrence.
I-I see.
I've been told not to go out too much during summer vacation.
There's a summer festival this Saturday, but he doesn't want me to go.
No way... Why?
Father was against me playing basketball.
I've been very focused on it lately.
He's not happy, I think.
I feel sorry for everyone else,
but this can't be helped.
Eh!?
Mokkan isn't coming?
How boring!
You idiot! Tomo wants to come, of course.
I'm sorry.
We all have things going on at home,
but aren't you working hard at school and at your dance lessons?
Oh! You work really hard, Tomoka.
I don't know if this will help, but we'll all go and ask your dad.
That's okay. I appreciate the thought, but it's okay.
Please enjoy the festival, okay?
Is this okay, Sis?
Oh!
Don't tighten it too much!
Yanbaru!
Is this too short?
So Tomo really isn't coming?
This is too sad for Tomoka.
I shouldn't meddle in things, but...
Did Tomoka contact you?
No, but I'll go to her place and see what I can do.
Thank you very much.
Okay!
Subaru! There's a phone call for you! From Tomoka's mom!
Name: Minato Tomoka
Birthday: 9/9
Blood Type: A
Class: 6-C
Height: 142 cm (4' 8")
Bust: Tiny (She's very concerned about this.)
Words to Subaru: I respect you from the bottom of my heart!
Tomoka!
Subaru!
It's nice being young.
Good afternoon, Subaru.
Um... Thank you very much.
I feel sad leaving Tomoka alone at home.
I'm relieved knowing that you're here with her.
Thank you, Mom! I'm off!
I didn't think she'd let me go. I was surprised.
Yep. That's great.
I can see you too, Subaru.
That yukata fits you really nicely.
Were we here too early?
Where are we supposed to meet?
In front of the candied apricot stall, but my cell phone's not connecting.
Don't worry.
We'll meet up with them soon.
Let's take this chance to have a look around.
Oh? What's that?
Free Throw Game
Free throw, huh?
Want to try it out?
I don't know if I can do it well with my yukata on.
Okay, how about this?
If you can make two out of three, then I'll do anything for you.
A-Anything?
Yep. Anything.
How about it?
You got it! Three out of three! Perfect!
Free Throw GAME Perfect Award - Suzuran Item Certificate
You're amazing, Tomoka.
It's all thanks to you cheering me on.
Um, Subaru...
Please...
What?
Well...
Your promise!
Oh yeah, your reward.
Y-Yes.
Actually, um...
Please come see the fireworks with me!
Oh? The ones during this festival?
I want to be close to you... Even closer.
Okay, let's go see the fireworks together.
Lick, lick, lick...
Ah, it's from Tomoka.
Oh! Is Tomoka here already?
Yes. She went to the free throw game with Hasegawa.
Okay! Let's go meet up with them!
No! They're finally alone together.
Let's go do what we want to do first, then!
I want to catch some goldfish!
Oh! Me, too!
I want to eat choco bananas, too!
Let's split up and meet up later.
Okay!
I want to eat cotton candy!
Yeah, yeah.
Huh? Weren't we supposed to meet up here?
Are they not here yet?
Tomoka?
What's the matter?
Um...
Do you need to use the restroom?
Yes... I've been holding it in... Um...
You can't walk?
No...
Okay! I get it!
Um... Well then!
Let's go.
Thank goodness we made it.
Out of my way, old man.
Um, are you okay?
Yes... But I dropped my glasses.
That's not good.
Excuse me!
He dropped his glasses! Can you help us look for them?
There!
Is this it?
Yes, it is. Thank you very much.
It's fine. Thank goodness we found it.
I'm here to see my daughter, but I guess I'm not used to the crowd.
I understand. I'm not good with crowds, either.
Thank you. You've been a great help.
Go for it, Big Bro!
Stop distracting me.
Huh? Isn't that Natsuhi?
What are you doing? Shooting range?
Oh! Looks like fun!
Let me try! Hand that over!
Huh?
What's with you? Dumb Maho! Stop bothering Big Bro!
Huh? Why not?
No reason! Shoo, Maho!
Tsubaki, Hiiragi.
Here you go. Have at it.
You won't get anything, though.
Let's go.
Wait, Big Bro!
Tsubaki and Hiiragi are so hard to get along wtih.
Don't mind, don't mind.
Here I go!
You'll fall if you keep on leaning like that!
Ah! Maho! Saki!
Oh? Shooting range?
Maho!
Your underwear!
Don't look, Subaru!
Congratulations!
You're so mean, Subaru!
S-Sorry.
It's your own fault for leaning so close!
You try too, Saki.
If he doesn't see your underwear, then I'll forgive you.
He's not going to see them!
How did this happen?
You should tighten up your elbow a bit.
Okay!
So close!
That was close.
Yes, but thanks for the tip.
Lick, lick.
Oh! Delicious!
Yep.
Hey!
Wow! What a nice view!
This place is unexpectedly nice.
The fireworks are about to happen.
Yes!
Tomoka.
Father!
I told you to stop going out so much.
I'm sorry, but...
We're going home.
Please wait!
You're...
I'm the coach for the Keishin Girls' Academy's basketball team, Hasegawa Subaru.
I'm sorry for taking Tomoka here.
No... He's wrong! I asked Mom...
No, I broke her promise in the end.
I'm sorry.
But Tomoka isn't a bad girl!
She has good manners and she's serious towards basketball.
Subaru...
Oh, it seems like you understand her quite well.
I didn't bring her here because I wanted to break her promise with you.
I just want her to be with her friends.
They're her precious friends.
Friends, you say?
Tomoka does not need friends who play basketball.
Father! That's too much!
Oh?
You're that guy...
You're Tomoka's coach?
Yes, I coach these kids.
We need Tomoka!
Yeah!
I wouldn't have realized how cool and fun basketball is without Mokkan!
I love Tomoka, too! I love being with everyone!
Thanks to Tomoka, we can play basketball together!
I'm sorry for going out, but please don't bring everyone else into this!
I was able to enjoy playing basketball again because of Subaru and everyone else!
That's why...
Please don't separate Tomoka with all of her friends!
Please!
I understand. Do what you want.
Father...
Hey!
I think you know already.
Basketball had left Tomoka a terrible memory before.
But it seems like she found some great friends through basketball this time.
This is unbefitting of me to say.
But please take care of my daughter.
Yes!
It's all right.
Let's continue with our promise.
Okay!
You look good today.
Really?
Did something good happen?
Father told me to do well in basketball!
I see.
Très bien.
Who are you?
I challenge you to a game.
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah~
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah!
Rolling! Rolling! Hazumi tsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! Keep on dribbling!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show guts! Say what! Saikou daze! Yeah!
Show your guts! Say what! The very best! Yeah!
Karada mo kokoro mo SS dakedo
Our bodies and hearts are in top shape!
Yume wa LL datte ii jan! Iijan!
But our dreams are super low! It's fine! Just fine!
Seishun miman no onayami ippai
We're full of youthful worries.
Hitori ja nai kara norikoerareru yo
But we're not alone! We can get through them!
Motto (motto) umaku (umaku) naritai na!
We want to get even better and better!
Anata no (Oh!) odoroku (Sugoi) Kao ga mitai no
We want to see (Oh!) your surprised face! (Amazing)
Mawase mawase mawase mawase
Spin, spin, spin, spin.
Chikyuu wa okki na Basketball
The world is a giant basketball!
Ashita o shinjite iku yo (Hai! I Ku Yo)
Let's believe in tomorrow! (Yes! Let's go!)
Mawase mawase mawase mawase
Spin, spin, spin, spin.
Uchuu wa okki na Basket Court
The universe is a huge basketball court!
Anata ni todoketai na (Se~no)
I hope my feelings can reach you! (One, two!)
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Pass! Pass! Pass! Pass!
Uke tomete kudasai!
Please accept it!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah~
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah!
Rolling! Rolling! Hazumi tsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! Keep on dribbling!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show guts! Say what! Saikou daze! Yeah!
Show your guts! Say what! The very best! Yeah!
It's starting!
Finally it's starting!
Calm down, Maho!
Oh!
We only have a very short time for a preview again!
Woof! Woof!
Um, Subaru and I had morning practice, and then...
Wait! Don't spoil everything, Tomo!
Let's end with a greeting!
One, two...
Flying Battle!
Please tune in next time!