I have to take care of something very important to me.
It's like I'm forgetting my own face!
Uh...
Get away!
H-Hey!
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, eh?
Do they really
perform human experiments here?
That's not Harima Mika.
Spend as much money as you want.
We have all the time in the world.
I love you, Selty.
People are fake.
This world is full of fakes.
They say stuff like "I love you," or "I adore you," and rob others of their freedom.
"Look only at me. Stay by my side and desire me."
Such spoiled kids.
My love isn't like that.
It's more perfect, and has no boundaries.
I know, Sis.
Thanks for the money.
Bye.
Want me to buy you something to drink?
Look, the vending machine is right over there.
I'll be right back.
You're so cute.
You still haven't found him?
No. I'm very sorry.
What the hell were the guards doing?
According to the guard on duty last night,
Seiji had stayed at the same hotel for a while,
but suddenly changed locations in the middle of the night.
He answered his phone around seven.
If something were to happen to him...
He promised not to leave Ikebukuro, so they'll find him soon.
Listen.
What do you think will happen to us if the cops see that thing?
Well...
Whatever.
I don't have the patience for you people.
Chief.
I will be back soon.
To me, that thing was just a doll.
It was like one of those pretty, expensive, imported dolls my uncle bought for me as a child.
I've never liked dolls.
I don't think he sent them because he wanted to please me,
but because he liked them.
Hey, Seiji, look at this.
Pretty, isn't it?
Let's see what we've got here.
What is it?
The house was always tranquil,
and Seiji and I were always alone.
Before Seiji was born, I often spent my time in my uncle's care.
I even had free access to his study.
That thing was sitting there.
My uncle would stare at that thing, apparently smuggled in from a foreign county, as though it fascinated him.
He would even talk to it from time to time.
It truly was beautiful.
More beautiful than any doll he ever sent me.
Without feeling a sliver of cruelty or curiosity,
I perceived the head itself as a living entity.
It was nothing more to me.
That's why I secretly let my brother into the study to play.
Maybe I just wanted to share that secret.
Pretty, isn't it?
That's when it all started.
It's the one regret I still have to contend with.
This is the first time we've met, right?
Did the list of illegal immigrants help you, Yagiri Namie-san?
Ah, I'm so overjoyed and honored that the chief of Yagiri Pharmaceuticals' Sixth Research Lab has personally come to such an unworthy place.
Please have a seat.
This is an emergency.
Find out where my brother is.
I don't care how much it costs.
I haven't gotten hold of him since last night.
He must be somewhere in Ikebukuro.
Oh, it hasn't been that long.
Why are you so worried?
He's with a woman.
A girl with scars around her neck.
A girl?
Oh, he's at that age.
Get your ass moving!
Hey, hold on.
Aren't there a lot of other important things I should investigate?
There's a rumor that the foreign Nebula Inc. will take over your company, right?
Then, you'll—
Orihara Izaya-san.
There's no time for that.
Oh, that's unexpected.
I never would have imagined that a woman as successful as you would be in love with her brother.
What do you think you know about me?
The Yagiri Namie-san I know is an excellent woman.
I mean, even though the company's run by your family,
your father was fired because of his mistakes.
And I heard the current president, your uncle, is a rather laid-back person.
In other words, you joined the company and didn't let your youth stop you from rising to the position of chief.
Not to mention your beauty.
I see you did your research.
It shouldn't be a problem for you to find my brother.
Your brother, huh?
I don't think it's a good idea to interfere with his affairs so much.
That's not true!
No one else can protect him but me!
You know, stalkers don't realize what they're doing.
They think they're protecting—
Never group me with stalkers!
Wow, scary!
I'm just kidding.
All right, I'll help you.
However, I'll do it my way.
You know, informants aren't the same as cops.
What rules are you playing with?
Just one question:
Are you jealous of that girl with the scar around her neck?
Why do you ask?
There's no way I'd be jealous of her.
This crimson, rusty jealousy burning in my heart is...
Sis, there's someone I love.
I realized that Seiji was acting stranger with every passing day.
He would recklessly ask to enter our uncle's study,
and the first thing he'd do after sneaking in was gaze at that thing.
He didn't fall in love with a person,
but something without feelings, let alone a body.
I wanted to get that thing as far away as I could from Seiji,
so the moment I joined the company, I asked my uncle to let me use it as a research subject.
Since then, Nebula Inc. started staying in contact with us,
and I was desperate to keep our research from leaking.
That was when my security card was stolen.
Only I had that card.
Sis...
I've killed someone.
What do I do now?
The feeling I had back then was neither fear nor anger.
It was an indescribable feeling of bliss and joy.
Seiji needed me.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
Leave everything to me.
Okay?
I'm not talking about the body. I mean that girl.
So you're the one who took her.
Don't worry.
Leave that to me as well.
It'll be all right.
I promise.
I didn't know that a stupid girl named Harima Mika was stalking him.
When she let herself into his room and saw that thing, Seiji...
I'll protect you no matter what.
Ah, there we go.
Looks like there's no need for you to panic.
The cops will take him into custody and call you soon, I guess.
Well, don't worry when I say, "the cops."
It's not a biggie.
I think.
Are you kidding me?!
Hello.
Yes, that's me.
Huh? What's wrong?
We're leaving?
But we just got here...
Hey, wait.
I'm really glad that you love me so much.
I love you too.
Forever and ever.
I'm scared!
About what?
Please, take me somewhere far away!
I want to be alone with you too.
But where do you want to go?
What's that?
A lover's quarrel?
Help!
Help! Stop!
Please calm down.
We're not suspicious.
No! Stop it!
Listen to—
Let go of her!
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt.
Just go.
I don't know why, but you need to chase after her, don't you?
I've always wanted to say this:
"Go on and leave this to me!"
Wait!
S-Sorry.
Are you okay?
You're...
Wait!
No, you  should wait!
Let go of me!
Let go dammit!
Is she your girlfriend?
Yeah!
She's my soul mate!
Why is she like that?
The hell if I know!
What the hell?!
You don't know anything about the person you love?
Quite irresponsible, aren't we?
That doesn't matter when you're in love.
What?
Then how can you call her your soul mate?
Because I love her.
I need no other reason!
You cannot put love into words!
That's why...
I'll show it through my actions!
I will protect her!
That's all!
I like you more than Izaya.
That's why I'll let you off the hook for this.
Fuck, it's gonna bleed when I pull it out...
Should I buy a band-aid first?
Or should I buy some super glue?
In other words,
your head's attached to a body and walking around?
When you caught her, a high schooler got in your way,
and when you were chasing her, another high schooler popped up and ran away with your head?
Do you honestly expect me to believe that?
I won't force you.
I believe you.
But why was Shizuo-kun there?
Ah, I completely forgot to mention that.
I was waiting in the park because of the job Izaya gave me.
Then Shizuo passed by and we started talking.
W-Well everything's okay, since he called and said the job was canceled.
Orihara-kun, huh?
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you.
Looks like you're still perplexed.
You're always welcome to talk to me.
And besides! Why the heck is my head on another body?!
Well, as I haven't seen it, I can't say anything for sure.
But if you want to hear my theory...
Hmm...
He found a girl whose body matched your head,
and replaced her head with yours.
That's creepy!
Or maybe it's a fresh corpse.
Stop that!
But...
That... That's just...
I don't believe I did anything wrong.
After that incident, I created her for Seiji.
I have to go.
It's okay.
Everything is all right.
I have to go.
You must have been scared.
She...
But nothing happened to you.
Even after she ran away from here and spent time together with Seiji,
my love didn't waver at all.
His love exists because he can use my love as a stepping stone.
He knows that.
And I know that he knows that.
It's quite perverted.
Yet, I still...
Damn...
That bastard was wearing Raira Academy's uniform.
Who is he?
I got it.
Leave it to me.
Anyway I have to find that kid from Raira Academy.
Then, I'll have a talk with my head.
You mean the head didn't scream until it saw you?
What do you want from that "head" that's living as a human, as a whole entity?
Are you telling me that you'll sever the head just because you want it?
Selty.
I don't want to admit...
that my head and memories are lost...
I don't want to admit that everything I've done in the past twenty years was for nothing!
It wasn't.
I'll definitely get her back.
Just wait here.
Oh.
What happened to your cellphone?
Did you lose it?
I don't know.
It was gone.
Even though I put it in my bag.
Huh?
She...
She needs me.
We have to be alone.
I see.
It's okay. Leave everything to me.
That rascal.
That doll should have done what a doll does: nothing.
And quit interfering with my love.
I've made up my mind.
I don't want to regret anything anymore.
Never again.
Understood?
Call all the subcontractors.
I don't care if it's dead or alive.
If you have no other choice, destroy it on the spot.
Looks like everyone's pretty busy.
This is gonna be fun!
So fun! So fun!
There are so many things in this city even I, The Informant, don't know!
Things appear and vanish!
That's exactly why I can't leave a city where people gather!
I love humans!
I love them!
I've got butterflies!
That's why...
humans should love me too.
Thank you.
Have you calmed down?
Can you answer my questions?
You said you don't remember anything.
In other words... Amnesia?
Uh... Well, I'll be repeating myself...
but maybe you should go to a hospital or the police.
Sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
It's okay.
No need to apologize.
I have to go.
Before that person meddles again.
Forever and ever.
I have to go...
Seiji...
Seiji-san...
I love you.
Uh...
The headless rider, Orihara Izaya, and the girl with a scar around her neck appeared again.
Not only that, the guy in the adjacent class is a member of the Dollars!
Next time: The First and Probably the Last.
I've dreamed of a not-so-casual life, but...