Hm? Where am I?
"Construction" "We apologize for the inconvenience"
"We appreciate your understanding"
"Class A River 'River Styx' (Hades)"
Could this be... the River Styx?
Come here... Come to this side...
This side is nice.
Everything's a blast here.
You don't have to be scared, Akihisa.
This side is nice in its own way.
Yuuji, why are you on that side?!
Don't be frightened, Akihisa.
As you can see, I'm just fine.
You don't have to
worry about anything, so...
Come to this side!
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"Episode 2
Me, Yukata, and Festivities!"
Wh-Where are we?
I don't remember much, but
I feel like I went through hell, literally.
When your delirious
ramblings became a conversation,
I thought that you
were goners, to be honest.
I'm surprised... that we're still alive.
Akihisa and Yuuji made
a challenge to hit on girls.
The girls found that out and
gave them punishment. Teehee.
At any rate, what a
horrible punishment that was.
To think that they did not only that,
but they also used something like that...
But this is rather unexpected.
Yeah, we did something pretty terrible.
It was extremely rude of you to go
hit on other girls when you're with girls.
But considering what
we did, we got off easy.
People don't call having a
near-death experience getting off easy.
It's hard to think that they'd
let us off the hook this easily.
There may be more to come.
What do we do, Yuuji? Should we run?
What's this about "running"?!
Tada!
Oh, you guys went and
changed into yukata, huh?
Yes, they're holding a festival, so...
What do you think, Akihisa?
Y-Yeah, that looks good on you.
This might be my
first time wearing yukata.
Oh, that's right. You grew up overseas.
Wh-What, Aki?
Ah, no, nothing.
You were admiring
Minami just now, weren't you?
She's especially cute in a yukata, isn't she?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Kimonos are nice since
they make you look good
even if you have small breasts.
I-I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Geez... If you have no idea,
then I'll show you. Just watch.
Here's a peep.
See? His reaction was
quicker than usual, right?
What's wrong?! Hang in there, Muttsulini!
This may look bad, but it isn't, really.
Yuuji...
What do you think of me in a yukata?
Well, I suppose you look good in it.
Then do you wanna marry me?
Not at all.
Then do you wanna get engaged to me?
Not even a bit.
Then, Yuuji...
No way, Jose!
Do you wanna keep breathing?
Ahh! You're really cute, Shouko!
You shouldn't fight your feelings, Yuuji.
You threatened me.
My mom told me to do whatever it
takes when it comes to relationships.
What's going on with
Himeji and the others...
I thought they were all upset.
Well then, everyone!
Let's go to the festival now!
Yeah, Akira. We don't want to be late.
This is only my second time
going to a festival in Japan,
so I'm looking forward to it!
We can't be late.
Let's go already!
Y-Yeah...
Wow, it's lively, isn't it?
Yeah, it seems fun!
Oh? Döner kebab?
They look delicious.
Yeah? Then let's try some.
What?!
This is your punishment
for earlier. You go buy some.
I shouldn't have said that.
Would you like to eat them,
too, Aki? I'll go buy some.
Yes, I have no objection...
Wait... What?! You'll buy them?
Is something the matter?
No, nothing!
Why...? It couldn't be
that she forgave me, could it?
Well then, let's share it.
I'd like to try many other things, too, so...
O-Okay. You go ahead.
Really? Then...
I guess they don't use lamb in
Japan, huh? Here, you have some, too.
Whoa! This is good!
Oh? Aki, you got sauce on your face.
Th-Thanks, Sis.
Akihisa! I bought some octopus
dumplings. Would you like some?
Thanks, Mizuki. Then, I'll have one piece.
Here you go. Say ahh.
Huh?
Is something wrong, Akihisa?
Ah, no... nothing.
Well then, say ahh.
Ahh...
Hmm... The pancake part is hot
and creamy and the octopus is chewy.
I-It's not like that, Sis!
This isn't illicit sexual activity!
What's wrong, Aki?
--Huh?
--It wasn't good?
What?
What did you screw up this time, Aki?
Getting worked up over a festival?
You're really childish.
Me? It's you who's really getting worked up.
Th-They said they'd give
these to me for free, so...!
You lived in Germany so long,
so you couldn't help it, right?
Oh yeah, would you like
some cotton candy? It's good.
What?
O-Okay then...
Here you go, say ahh.
Do you like it?
Y-Yeah, it tastes good.
Good.
Yuuji... would you like
some yakisoba noodles?
Y-Yeah, I guess I'll have some.
I got okonomiyaki, too.
Th-That's considerate of you.
Here's some ramune soda.
Th-Thank you...
Good, Yuuji was forgiven, too.
--This is a festival after all. They'd want
to enjoy it rather than be upset, right?
Akihisa! I saw some color
baby chickens over there!
I thought they went extinct.
Well... they just paint the baby chickens.
What?! Then it wasn't
because of their breed?
That's not possible! Right, Muttsulini?
"Color Baby Chickens"
"Cheep, cheep, cheep..."
"Grab!"
"Grab!" "Cheeeeep?!"
"Rumble, rumble, rumble..."
"Sneer"
I'll color you however I like!
Th-That's common sense.
Aki, are you enjoying the festival?
Yep!
Yuuji, are you having fun?
Y... Yeah.
Oh, Akihisa, there's a fun
event going on here, too.
"The First Summer 'Miss Yukata'
Beauty Contest"... huh?
A beauty contest, huh?
That sounds fun.
Good photo opportunities.
Why don't we all go?
Or better yet, why not have
everyone compete in the event?
Ah, well, I'm not saying
you must or anything...
I thought that might be
a nice summer memory.
That sounds good.
What? Really?
Yeah, let's participate, shall we?
I'm sure it'll stay in our hearts.
Yes, let's compete in the event...
...let's have everyone here compete.
Scatter!
Where are you going, Aki?
We're all participating in the contest.
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
Right, you guys aren't making any sense.
Hitting on girls earlier...
Surely you didn't think...
that you were off the hook after
that little punishment you got earlier?
Don't worry. I have a makeup kit on me.
What?!
Wait! With my frame, there's no
way I could dress up as a woman!
Please satisfy your anger by
dressing Akihisa up as a woman!
Are you trying to weasel out of
this by yourself?! You frickin' traitor!
You both don't know when to give up.
Why don't you follow the example
of Tsuchiya who gave up like a man?!
Huh?!
Cruel... This is so cruel, Hideyoshi.
I'm sorry. It's not in my nature to go easy...
...since makeup is one of
the techniques for theater.
"Akiko Yoshii"
Why did you guys have
to put your all into this?
"Koumi Tsuchiya"
How humiliating...
Koumi Tsuchiya...? What on earth...
"Hong Xiong Li"
You've got it easy, Muttsulini.
I'm dressed up as a woman, and on top
of that, I'm supposed to be a foreigner!
It's true that people could see a
female foreign athlete having your frame.
All three of you look good with makeup on.
Yeah, you look very cute!
Aki, your sister is happy
that you grew up to be pretty.
That's not something that
you should say to your brother.
Your sex appeal needs work, Yuuji.
You guys forced me to
wear this! Don't complain!
Come to think of it... why am
I being forced to compete, too?
Well, that's the default for this show.
Idiot Test!
"The First Summer..."
Let's start the First Summer
"Miss Yukata" Beauty Contest.
"First Summer 'Miss Yukata' Beauty Contest"
As a commentator, we have
Mr. Obata who's also wearing yukata.
He's a sponsor of the event and
will be the judge for the contest.
I'm looking forward to
seeing pretty women in yukata.
"Akiko Yoshii"
Well then, good luck.
Don't worry! They won't figure it out.
Yuuji, if you believe
in yourself, you can win.
Are you nuts?!
I'll be sure to record your cute side.
Damn you!
What do we do, Yuuji?
Our only option is to lose
quickly and get out of this.
Oh yeah! If we tell them we're guys...
We can't do that.
There might be school affiliates
or acquaintances in the audience.
If someone finds out, not only will
they think we like dressing up as women,
but they'll also think that we're so
confident we participated in a contest
and we have a habit of showing off,
which means we'll appear
incredibly pathetic in their eyes!
If that happens,
my social credibility will...!
I don't think you have any
social credibility to start with.
Listen up! The only strategy
for us to get out of this crisis is
to get eliminated in the preliminary
round without revealing that we're guys.
This is our battle for manhood!
"Thank you very much for your support."
"Part 1. The End."
Now, contestant No. 1,
please step out onto the stage.
Now... what should I do?
Please tell us your name.
I'll have my face down.
I'll answer as softly as I can, too.
Y-Yes, I'm Akiko Yoshii.
Oh? Sounds like you're
a shy person, Miss Akiko.
I find that pure nature of
hers cute. She gets a high score.
Why?!
Do you have any special talents?
If I tell a total lie, it's possible
they'll find it out if they question me...
If I must say, it'd be cooking.
I make things like paella
and spaghetti carbonara.
So you cook at home, too?
Yes, more or less every day.
It's rare to see a young
woman like you these days.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't!
This is good news for guys.
What do you think, Mr. Obata?
If you give me your cell number,
I'll give you some spending money.
Well, if he wasn't our sponsor,
I would've decked him good.
Now, Miss Akiko,
what were you careful about
when you put on a yukata today?
I tried to avoid showing my body lines...
I see.
Mr. Obata, do you have any questions
about her manner of wearing a yukata?
I'd like to know if she's wearing underwear!
Underwear?! Does he mean women's underwear?!
I'm not wearing that stuff!
Thank you for answering
a surprisingly crude question.
Nice high score!
Damn you!
Please tell us your name.
My name is Koumi Tsuchiya.
Did you come here to swim today?
Yes.
Do you often wear yukata?
No.
Did you come with your friends?
Yes.
Are they here in the audience?
No.
Hmm...
Well then, besides yukata,
what kind of clothes do you like?
Silk Chinese dresses, kimono,
and outfits for race car girls,
cheerleaders, nurses, flight attendants,
waitresses at family restaurants, and
policewomen. Also leotards, lady's suits,
sailor school uniforms, school blazers,
shrine maiden outfits,
maid uniforms and tennis outfits.
I think they're wonderf-- Err, nothing...
That was surprising.
Despite your coolheaded attitude,
Miss Koumi, you seem to like cosplay.
P-Please forget it.
Koumi! Koumi! Koumi! Koumi! Koumi!
Y-You can't do that!
What a reaction... She's definitely
going to make it to the final round.
Uhm... Really, you can't do that...
Nice own goal!
How did this happen?
I'm Hong Xiong Li. Nice to meet you.
She's quite tall, isn't she?
What do you think, Mr. Obata?
Wonderful! I love tall women.
What?!
She's got a high mark from the judge!
Do you have any other questi-- Huh?
How does Cambodia
sound for our honeymoon?
We're from different countries!
I can't do that!
With love, all things are possible, my honey.
There's no love!
I'm confident that love will emerge!
I hate you!
We can start off as friends. I'll take
good care of you the rest of your life!
Enough, already! I'm gonna
beat you up, old geezer!
You can do anything you like to me!
I will not permit an affair.
Shouko?! Why is this considered an affair?!
I've got a scar in my heart.
This summer has become
unforgettable in many ways, hasn't it?
I can no longer get married.
It was good that the contest got suspended.
It was a disaster to the sponsor, though.
We went overboard, didn't we?
Shall we let them off the hook now?
Extenuating circumstances...
Looks like they're sorry.
Let's make an exception and forgive them.
But I wonder who would've
won if the contest went on.
Well, wouldn't Hideyoshi
be the most appropriate?
Don't you think the word "appropriate"
is wrong, considering that I'm a guy?
My heart went pitter-patter when
I saw Muttsulini in women's clothes.
How about you, Akira?
Well, since I'm used to
seeing Aki in women's clothes,
I liked the other two. It was refreshing.
Hey, wait, Sis! I don't
wear women's clothes!
What're you saying, Aki?
You wore a skirt again last night,
right...? While you were asleep.
Hey! What'd you do to
me while I was asleep?!
Don't worry. That's half a lie.
A lie? How can you make
what you just said half a lie?!
I only made you wear it up to your knees.
Then you made me wear it half way?!
No. The industry
terminology would be "halfway-off."
Halfway-off?!
Okay, guys! They're pretty much done!
Let's eat!
This is delicious!
Sakamoto really is skilled
in these things, isn't he?
My proud husband.
I wanted to cook, too,
but Akihisa didn't let me help them.
I wouldn't hurt myself with
a kitchen knife or anything.
That's not the problem, Himeji.
The problem is, you could kill people
even without using a kitchen knife.
We'll die if we eat what she makes.
Killer food...
We can't let her make such dangerous food.
Then, how about this time we have
a cooking competition among us girls?
We'll ask the guys to be the judges.
Why'd you go and say that?!
But how can a cooking winner be decided?
I think either a knockout
or a technical knockout.
Yeah, we did eat a lot, didn't we?
Hmm... Somehow I still feel a little hungry.
But we have no food left to cook.
It can't be helped. I guess we'll get it locally.
Get it locally?
There's an ocean in front of us.
Fresh clams taste good when grilled.
You're right!
Come to think of it...
I baked madeleines at home and...
Let's go, Yuuji! Let's find clams!
Yeah! Let's gather so many that
we won't be able to eat anything else!
Beaches at night are refined
and nice too, right, Muttsulini?
I love clams!
I wonder what happened to them.
Beats me.
So, what about the madeleines?
Yeah, I did bake them,
but I left them on the table.
Oh, that's a bummer.
I'm not gonna die!!
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Geez, they're sleeping like kids.
Guys never grow up, so...
Their sleeping faces
look innocent, don't they?
They look cute.
They must be tired after getting carried away.
I'm glad that they enjoyed the trip.
At any rate, they fell asleep
really in no time, didn't they?
They were stumbling around
even before they got in the car.
I thought they ate breakfast quite
vigorously, then the next moment,
they already looked sleepy.
They must've been really hungry.
Yeah. They ate all our food, too.
It's really a bummer, isn't it, Mizuki?
Yes...
Since they fell asleep
right away, I couldn't ask them
how they liked the breakfast
I put so much effort into making.
"Goners" "Class A River 'Riv0er Styx' (Hades)"
"Still Breathing"
Come to this side.
This side is nice.
Question 3.
Name what you're not
supposed to bring to school.
Do bananas count as snacks?
You must've gone bananas...
Is that a good comeback?
Next episode!
"Me, That Girl, and a Stuffed Toy!"
This will be on the test.