Kaleido Stage.
It's neither a circus, nor a musical.
It's not a magic show either.
It is the best entertainment
show in the world.
And there was a girl who aspired to join
this Kaleido Stage and got the leading role.
She is Sora Naegino, 16 years old.
However, the stage she dreamed of
was taken away by a certain person.
Would Sora and her friends be
able to get Kaleido Stage back?
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
My name is Fool.
I am the spirit of the stage who
can only be seen by chosen ones.
Sora Naegino is the only one who can see me.
With her efforts and inborn spirit,
she steadily climbed the ladder to be a star.
And finally, she realized a
co-performance with Layla, the top star.
While Kaleido Stage was
enjoying its big surge in popularity,
Sora and her friends experienced ordeals
which they'd never encountered before.
The treacherous Yuri Killian.
The current Kaleido Stage will
be dissolved after today's show.
What?!
Kaleido Stage will be dissolved?
They could not believe
their ears, but it was fact.
The Kaleido Stage was to be
bought out and immediately disbanded.
And the mastermind
behind it all was Yuri Killian.
Yuri was a star at Kaleido Stage,
sharing the popularity with Layla.
And he had been secretly planning a takeover.
I won. I defeated Kalos.
With the last show near at hand,
Sora tried to tell Kalos, the owner,
how she felt about this performance, but...
Although today is our last show...
No... Because it's the last show,
let's make it the best show.
Boss, do you have anything
you want me to tell everybody?
There is one thing I want to say.
If you're going to prepare yourself for
the stage like that, it's better not to do it.
What?
Sora could not hide her agitation
after the way Kalos brushed her off.
Then, shortly afterwards,
she even lost the ability to see me.
Hey, Fool!
I have something I want you to listen to!
Fool!
Please answer me!
I can't believe this.
I lost the ability to see Fool.
Listen, if you can see me,
it means that you were chosen for the stage.
Once, there was a man who was able to see me.
The man I was talking about
gradually lost the ability to see me.
--Sora lost everything,
--Everything is gone all at once.
--and she didn't know what to do.
I don't know what I should do at all.
The words which cleared up her confusion
came unexpectedly from Layla.
No matter how hard you guys try,
your Kaleido Stage will be over after today.
I'm not thinking that today is the last day.
What?
Hey, look at the reality, Layla.
Even if Kaleido Stage closes its doors,
it can't close the door to my future.
It will not be my last
show, unless I wish it.
At least, if I couldn't believe that,
I couldn't appear on this stage.
Sora!
So, today is not the end of the show, is it?
I want to appear on the stage
many more times with you.
Sora, hurry.
The curtain will be raised as scheduled.
Yes.
Maybe, I don't want to lose...
I don't want to lose the partner
who motivates me so much...
Miss Layla!
Where is Sora?
She messed up her makeup right now, and...
She is fixing it.
Sora...
Oh, Miss Layla.
Oh... I'm doing my best to hurry, but...
Give it to me.
I will do it for you.
What?
Oh... Miss Layla...
Don't talk. I can't do my work.
I enjoyed co-starring on stage with you.
Miss Layla...
Why would you say something like that?
This is not the end, right?
Now it looks good.
Let's go, Sora.
Yes.
Fool...
Can you see me again?
Yes, unfortunately.
The Sun.
This card represents a hope for tomorrow.
A hope for tomorrow.
That's nice.
That's right!
Starting tomorrow, our
performance will start!
And so, the curtain was
dropped on the last show
while everyone's hearts were
filled with mixed emotions.
Then, each member
started walking their own path.
It's amazing how time passes by so quickly.
--And yet, not only are we far from
creating our own Kaleido Stage,
--To shine on that brilliant
stage once again:
--but also we have no jobs.
--with that wish firmly in their minds,
they trained on their own every day
and worked hard at part-time jobs.
There, there, there!
Meanwhile, Layla appeared in a
movie, influenced in part by her father.
Cut!
Each of them was living a new life.
One day, Sora and her friends got a chance.
I found you a job.
What?!
Look at this.
"Wanted: performers to perform
on the open stage at Marine Park"?
The scale of the stage was small,
but they'd be able to appear on stage again.
We got some e-mail responses.
Really?
Everyone's coming!
We're coming in!
Wow!
Sora!
And so, all the old friends gathered,
and they formed a new group, Freedom Lights.
And then came the date that they performed.
Sora and her friends put
on a wonderful performance
as if they were trying to
vent all their frustrations.
Their performance was a great success.
But somehow,
Sora felt something was missing.
If Miss Layla were here with us...
Just as she thought that...
Hey, Sora.
What's that?
A mysterious Masked Star appeared
and flew freely through the sky.
She showed off an amazing performance.
What's that?
She's amazing.
She nailed everyone's
attention in an instant.
Thanks to this mysterious
Masked Star's performance,
Marine Park was packed day after day.
--We have plenty of time until
the Masked Star's show starts.
--Sora's group's performance was
also garnering favorable reviews.
And then one day, an incident happened.
Hey, don't miss that photo op.
Yes.
The Masked Star!
Finally!
A young brother and sister
climbed up on a steel tower
--in order to have a better look at the Masked Star's performance.
--Be a big girl.
Those kids!
Call a rescue team quick!
Yes!
Melissa, go!
Okay.
"The way she moves... She must be..."
Sora was convinced.
You're okay now.
She's going to crash!
Hold on tight.
Shoot...
Good.
Sora avoided a disaster working
in combination with the Masked Star.
I believe that the Masked Star is Miss Layla.
If Miss Layla is with us,
I think creating our own
Kaleido Stage is possible.
However,
Yuri's never-ending evil schemes
struck at Sora and her friends once more.
And finally, the Masked
Star's identity was disclosed.
After Yuri's interference forced Sora
and her friends out of Marine Park,
as their final hope, they decided to enter
the world performance festival in Vancouver.
Oh, I know.
If we get a good reputation, Marine
Park's owner may reconsider firing us.
Meanwhile, Layla was working her way through
playing the lead role of the movie in London.
Don't worry.
It's nice to hear the movie
shoot is going smoothly.
The success of this movie will
decide your future. It's very important.
Yes, I know.
By the end of next week,
we'll finally shoot the big climax scene.
I wish you success.
Thank you.
And then came the date for the festival.
What's this?
"Z"?
Waiting for Sora and her Freedom Lights
was the local amateur group "Z",
who gave a similar performance
to Sora's group's.
This is...
It's the same as ours.
Did they copy us?
That's right.
This was also Yuri's scheme.
Then their lives will be over.
They're getting wonderful cheers...
We can't afford to be beat by those guys!
Just before they were ready to
perform, Freedom Lights was cornered.
Now what are we gonna do?
All right, I understand.
I will postpone the shoot until next week.
In return, I expect the
best performance out of you.
The person who appeared
was that mysterious Masked Star.
And, Sora and her
friends' performance started.
The Masked Star...
Do you know what you're doing?
Just when everyone was convinced
of Freedom Lights' victory...
Don't get in my way!
Layla!
Why are you here?
Today is supposed to be
the day for the climax shoot.
I asked them to postpone the shoot.
What?
I'm aware that I'm selfish.
But I couldn't just stand by and do nothing.
I want to perform a perfect...
a perfect performance
that makes me fully satisfied.
I want to receive applause that
makes my whole body tremble.
And right now, I have a
partner who can make it possible.
Miss Layla!
I've not finished my last show.
In any case, make sure
to finish the movie shoot.
After that, do whatever you want.
--Miss Layla...
--Layla decided to appear on stage
again with Sora and the others.
--That was when the miracle happened.
--What?
--What? What?
What?!
Can you see me?
That's right.
Having resolved to live for the stage,
she also became able to see me!
Layla was chosen for the stage just now.
It is proof that you can attempt
the legendary great maneuver.
The legendary great maneuver?
It was tried once, a long time ago.
After that, no one has
successfully performed that maneuver.
One person was frightened.
Another tried it recklessly
and lost his life.
If you're going to attempt that maneuver,
you will be the second
pair to try from Kaleido Stage.
It needs two stars.
What happened to the two
who tried before and failed?
They died.
But... I think I can do it
if it's with you, Miss Layla!
The two had made up their minds and headed
to the Grand Canyon for special training.
Waiting there was the one and only person
who knew the legendary great maneuver.
Welcome. It's been awhile.
Boss...
Are you ready?
And so began Sora and
Layla's excruciating ordeal.
The training they endured every day was hard
beyond anything the two had ever imagined.
Contrary to Layla, who steadily managed
to finish the assignments she was given,
it took all Sora had just to keep up.
And then...
Miss Layla, why won't you say anything?
Please say something. Say anything!
I have nothing to say.
Brushed aside by Layla,
the partner she put so much trust in,
Sora's confidence was shaken.
It's a nuisance if you're going to
prepare yourself with a half-baked attitude.
If quitting is better for Miss Layla, I...
After Sora lost her confidence,
she headed to Layla's room
with her mind set on quitting.
Miss Layla, I want to talk about something.
Miss Layla...
Ken...
Miss Layla is not here right now.
She's out running.
Running? At a time like this?
Yes. She's trying to lose weight.
Losing weight?
That's right.
The greater the weight difference
between the two performers,
the lower the chance of success
of the legendary great maneuver.
Miss Layla is doing all
of this because of me...
Partners are supposed to be equal.
Thank you, Ken.
Miss Layla!
Sora!
I'm sorry!
I tried to run away.
Because the special
training is hard and painful,
I made excuses and told myself that
I don't have the skills to be your partner!
I tried to run away by myself!
I'm sorry!
I'll never doubt myself again!
I'll work much harder and catch up to you!
And I'm going to perfect the
legendary great maneuver by any means!
We came all this way to do just that.
Yes.
Both Sora and Layla
restored their trust in each other.
However, God imposed new ordeals on them.
Miss Layla!
--What's wrong?
--Due to her drastic weight loss,
Layla grew dizzy.
It's nothing.
Good. She seems to be doing okay.
Layla was injured.
What cruel fate awaited them?
At last, the time came to show
the results of the special training.
However, after Layla smashed
her right shoulder into the cliff,
her condition worsened.
And it came to a point that
her doctor told her not to perform.
Still, her determination was not shaken.
Sora and Layla's performance.
Finally, the time was ripe.
After they overcame cruel ordeals,
the time came at last for Sora and Layla
to attempt the legendary great maneuver.
It looks like they don't have any lifelines.
Somehow, I'm getting chills.
Let's start, Sora.
Yes.
I need to focus only on Miss Layla.
Come, Sora!
Jump toward Miss Layla...
Both of you have wings on your back.
I'm not scared at all.
I'm with Miss Layla.
I'm so happy. I feel like crying.
I wish I could keep
performing like this forever.
The brilliance of life that
doesn't flinch at anything.
That is indeed the legendary great maneuver.
Not only is the legendary great
maneuver a dangerous maneuver,
but it is also an expression of a
strong life that keeps even death at bay.
Arlon...
The maneuver which even gives
the audience the strength to live...
That's what the legendary great maneuver was.
Let's do it with all our might.
Okay.
One! Two! Three!
The applause that Layla had wished for;
the grand applause that
made her whole body tremble.
However, the price for getting
that applause was just too high.
At the least, I know I won't be able
to appear on Kaleido Stage anymore.
What?
It's not true, is it?
It is true.
Kaleido Stage had lost Layla.
What will the fate of Sora and the others be?
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U