All right, that's all for today.
Yeah.
Huh?
What's the matter, Akihisa?
This thing hasn't been functioning properly since the last midterm!
There we go.
You probably don't know how to use it correctly.
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Did you read the manual?
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Iron Bracelet
Startup Manual
Startup Code
"Awaken"
Let's see...
Don't touch it with wet hands.
Don't sit on it.
Don't hang around on it.
Don't give it to your girlfriend.
Don't pawn it.
Keep it out of reach of children.
Nothing important here.
What about that?
Ages 13 and up.
That's it!
I'm over 13!
Not mentally.
Yes, mentally! I'll have you know that I've read quite a few 18+ books!
You had better give us every detail about that...
Then we'll see if you're screwed or not...
Out of the mouth comes evil.
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Twelfth Period
Love and Courage and Our Fight Has Just Begun! (temp)
Good morning, Aki.
It's time to wake up.
Morning, Sis...
Breakfast is ready.
Since you have an ESB with class A today,
I prepared some food with
names that will help you win.
TEKI
Going by the phrase "defeat the enemy,"
KATSU
I got you some steak and porkchop...
Really?
...pictures and put them under your pillow.
Only pictures?
So? Do you think you can win?
This joke is so screwed up that I think it
actually reduced my chances of winning.
Oh, right.
Pictures aren't enough to satisfy a growing body.
That's why I prepared real-
Really!?
...footage of eating them.
Why footage!?
Wait, you ate the steak all by yourself!?
I had a rough time with it.
I had to force it down even though I was already full.
Then let me eat that!
You're so daring...
No! I don't want to eat that!
Akira
I want to eat that!
Meat
First things first, Aki...
Why didn't you give me your thoughts on my bikini?
This shit is so damn retarded...
complimenting your bikini is the last of my concerns!
Wait, why were you eating in a bikini?
The cinematographer said that'd make you happier.
Cinematographer?
Cinematographer
:
Voyeur
Editing
:
Voyeur
Production
:
Silver Link
Oh.
Fumizuki Academy runs on a system of pragmatism.
Even if you have the skills,
you're not worth crap unless
Academic Ability
...you can prove it through testing.
Isn't that why you're in class F?
They even told me that staying healthy was a component of the examination.
We'll just have to show them our brand of pragmatism.
What do you mean?
Our battle begins long before the bell rings.
Hideyoshi.
These belong to my sister.
They're her uniform and favorite books.
These should help us deal with her...
This is more than enough.
We'll figure something out.
Wow, this is class A material.
How do you even compute this?
May I see it?
I'm good at math.
Shinji
Yuuichi
Holding you under the legendary tree
Th...
TL Note: Kinoshita can be read as "under the tree."
Holding you under the legendary tree
This is...
I don't think that's solvable.
This question is way out of my league.
Wow, a question that even Himeji and Minami don't know how to solve...
She must be a genius.
There are others as well.
They cost so much even though they're so thin.
I'm confiscating this!
Akihisa, you're not old enough for this.
Akihisa, bring these with you to declare war on class A.
I'm tired of getting the shit beaten out of me.
You'll be fine.
Holding you under the legendary tree
Pretend you picked up her favorite book and decided the right thing to do was to return it to her.
I see.
Then she'll be grateful and listen to what I have to say.
Kinoshita, you dropped this!
No!
I can't trust anyone.
Aren't you guys made out of flesh and blood as well!?
Sis...
What the hell were you doing!?
I'll make you pay for this!
Here to check out your new desks?
You've got to be kidding!
There's no freakin' way that
class A will lose against class F!
You guys need to take a break from spouting this crap.
Idiot...
I don't think she meant "take a break" literally.
Know your place! You guys need to stay
where you belong, in this piece of crap class.
Stop bothering us.
You're wrong!
It's true that class F has bad grades.
But we're definitely not garbage!
That doesn't change the fact you're class F.
Himeji, you don't belong in this class.
Or maybe you do?
Have you stayed in this class for so long that you were infected by their idiocy?
Take that back!
There's no way Himeji belongs to this crappy class!
Akihisa, you're admitting that we're the worst class.
After the ESB's over, you can take my cardboard box.
Take good care of it.
I'll make you regret this.
Get ready to have your ass whipped.
Part one of our plan is complete.
So how are we going to fight against class A?
I don't think we'd be able to win if we went against them head-on...
We've already exploited Kirishima's weakness once...
I don't think we can use that again.
Yeah, she isn't stupid enough to make the same mistake twice.
Want to know why I haven't exchanged
classroom facilities after all these victories?
The seeds we planted have borne fruit.
Now we harvest it!
Mock-ESB?
We'd like to have a real ESB with your class,
but that's impossible within three months of defeat.
Wouldn't it be a nice practice match?
We have a match with class F in the afternoon.
We don't have time for you guys.
You guys want to take advantage of class F because they just fought?
I didn't know class A was so shameless.
Well, it's true that they're
exhausted from fighting us earlier...
is a pretty shameless way of putting it too.
Are you saying that we'll lose to class F?
Very well, then.
We'll play with you as a warm-up.
Is that all right, Rep?
I don't care.
Warm-up? You sure are taking us lightly.
Seriously...
Do you think we'd lose to a cross-dressing fag?
The mock-ESB between class A and class B will now begin.
Go!
We'll finish you off in no time.
Summon!
Looks like it's started.
Hideyoshi, it's your turn.
Roger that.
How do I look? Do I look like a girl?
That was quick...
I thought girls only needed to worry about other girls...
Why do I have this complicated feeling?
You're awesome, Hideyoshi!
I knew you were a hottie all along!
I told you, I'm a guy!
You finished changing already?
We learned how to get
changed fast in the drama club.
This is a piece of cake.
What the hell are you doing, Voyeur?
Why didn't you tell me about your plan earlier!?
He feels defeated because he couldn't take your picture.
All right, time for some fine-tuning.
Hello, I'm Kinoshita.
I'm Kino...
My name's Kinoshita.
My Kinoshita.
I'm Yuuko Kinoshita.
You filthy pigs!
W-What are you-
Don't talk to me.
You smell like pigshit.
What?
I'm class A's Yuuko Kinoshita.
I'm here to tell you pieces of shit how much you suck.
Pieces of shit...
I really can't stand sharing the same
space with you unhygienic neckbeards!
Animals like you should go work at a circus or something.
Are you saying that we should be in class F?
We're not that worthless.
Say that again!
Anyway, we can't have an ESB with you today because we're busy having one with class F.
But we'll be sure to demolish you soon.
Look forward to your defeat.
What the hell was that!?
Stop!
Finally.
What a pain in the ass. Let's go.
You guys started it.
I'm class C's rep, Yuuka Koyama.
I want to request an ESB with class A.
Huh?
I'll make you eat those words.
What?
Y-Yuuka, why are you here?
I-I never knew you had that sort of fetish...
N-No, Yuuka... This isn't...
Yuuka!
And so, their relationship ended on the spot.
All hands, sortie!
Take them down!
What's wrong with them?
Aren't they afraid of losing?
Here we go!
Yeah!
Sissy, please look at my
gallant figure on the battlefield!
We owe class F a big one!
Class A is being gradually worn down.
Even we can damage them now, and we're class E!
I don't want to continue owing class F a favor.
Let's do the best we can.
We're class A, bitches...
Class E's rep, Hiromi Nakabayashi, is requesting a mock-ESB.
You're not going to refuse, are you?
Wow! Class E's giving class A a hard time!
Mock-ESBs require endurance as well.
Class E's full of athletes,
but class A focuses their time on studying, so there aren't many physically fit people in it.
Once they get tired, they won't be able to concentrate on their attacks.
Moreover, they don't have the time or the opportunity to replenish their points in a mock-ESB.
So that's why you turned down all the classroom exchanges...
You did so in order to have
other classes owe us a favor.
Small things can make a big difference.
We're not trying to win instantly.
We're just taking advantage of favorable conditions.
This is what you call a true battle!
What a lame trick.
What are you talking about?
You used the other classes to diminish our points...
But attacks of that level won't even scratch us!
Don't underestimate us.
You guys are still standing... Not bad.
I'll make sure you regret it later.
Get ready for a beating.
Also, get ready for you-know-what.
We'll show them who's boss!
We'll teach those idiots from class F a lesson they'll never forget.
Guys, the true battle begins now.
Rep?
We'll beat them with everything we have.
Good luck, comrades.
Summon!
What's our plan?
The staircase is right behind their classroom.
Our main forces will attack them from the front,
and our secondary forces will come
around the staircases and surround them.
Rush them!
They're not here.
Where are they?
Did they run away?
Yo, we're here!
They're over there!
You guys should exercise more often. Wouldn't want mold to start growing on you, would you?
Damn, those bastards...
When did they...
Demolish them on the schoolyard!
They're coming, Akihisa.
Okay.
All right, let's go out.
What the hell is this?
Dammit...
Follow him!
They can't run away-
...from us.
Welcome.
Detention!
No!
Those who were KIA must receive supplementary lessons!
Wow, class A...
They even changed their shoes
before coming out. What polite kids.
The split enemy groups have joined back up.
If we all gang up on one person...
Even class A doesn't stand a chance.
All right, it's time for the next phase, Akihisa.
Okay.
Retreat!
You're not running away!
Why did you take your pants off?
Now's our chance!
Kill them all while they're distracted by the pants!
I frickin' love your Being, Akihisa.
No one can match him in terms of speed.
Oh, I have a request!
What's the matter, Voyeur?
Please...
Take off some bras this time!
I knew you'd say that.
You guys aren't bad.
Let me be your opponent this time.
All right, Voyeur... Leave it to me!
What? What? What?
You're wasting your efforts.
I'm not wearing a bra today.
I can still fight...
It's finally time for us to settle things, Voyeur.
Settle things...
The kanji for that is 'female' and 'male'...
Voyeur!
I-I'm fine.
I'll defeat her with my own strength!
Yoshii, I'll be your opponent.
Kubo! All right, let's go!
Weak, Yoshii.
If you so desire...
I will feel no shame no matter how I am dressed!
Prepare yourself for a hard, throbbing impact!
And your counterattack will be a love tap!
Wait, Yoshii! Why can't we "settle things" too-
Now's our chance!
No you won't!
That's enough.
Where's their rep, Sakamoto?
Your opponent is us!
We've taken out a lot of enemies already.
Guys!
Akihisa...
Aki!
All's going well.
The surprise factor works well on these nerds.
There you are.
You guys sure have lots of tricks up your sleeves.
Impressed, aren't ya?
But this is the end.
Yuuji, I'm going to defeat you.
Don't take my line.
Let's do this!
Permission granted.
Summoning Being... Summon!
Summon!
My attacks missed!?
We trained quite a bit.
With my Iron Bracelet, we can perform
summons without the permission of a teacher.
And from that, we were able to learn how to control our Beings effectively.
First off, you aren't experience in the art of controlling...
And then you're exhausted from all the
mock-ESBs, sapping your concentration.
Dodging your attacks is a piece of cake!
Don't give me that attitude!
One hit and you're done for!
That doesn't matter as long as I don't get hit!
Take this!
Our attacks might not do much damage, but they'll chip away at you eventually!
Why? They're in class F!
We've been studying too.
We're still nowhere near your level, of course.
You're kidding...
There they are!
Rep!
They're all from class A!
Reinforcements got here faster than I thought...
Akihisa!
Awaken!
You're not passing through until we're done!
Damn you!
Push!
Your reinforcements are no help now.
Don't worry.
I can handle you guys by myself.
You talk big!
Here I come!
Yuuji...
Prepare yourself!
Bring it!
How can they...
Why?
We're not talking about theory here.
We're talking pragmatics!
Go!
This is it!
What's going on?
My bracelet...
Dammit! Is it at its limit?
It was working fine when it was malfunctioning...
Why is this happening?
It hit its limit because you studied!
What?
That thing can only be used by an idiot!
Kinoshita!
Himeji!
Shouko!
Yuuji...
Shouko...
Akihisa...
Himeji...
Aki!
What's going on!?
Akihisa!
Are you okay, Yoshii?
Thank god...
I thought you were going...
I was so scared, Akihisa!
I was really, really scared!
Akihisa! Akihisa!
I was scared to death too!
Thank you.
That scared the shit out of me.
Well, I only saved you because...
Wh... Wha...
Yeah!
What?
Class A wins.
WHAT!?
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Question 13: What's the name of
Fumizuki Academy's special system
that uses testing as a means of war?
Testing battles!
Please remember what this show was about.
Next episode: Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings.
This will be on your test.