For now, you need to practice with the mouthpiece only.
Dissatisfied?
No! Well...
Anyway, I really want to play as well as Rio-senpai...
I am a Spartan, you know.
Yes, please teach me!
Now it's time for breakfast.
The mess hall is over there. Go in first!
Yes!
Knock, knock, sah, sah...
Let's work hard from today onwards.
Good morning!
Very Shitty!
First Battle
The Story of the Chair
Actually, this was prepared for your arrival last night.
I tried my best to make it.
Thank you very much!
Here, Rio.
Did you help me collect the dried seafood upstairs?
No, I don't know anything about it.
That's weird.
Try your best, Noël!
If you wanna sleep, please do it after you eat.
I'm trying my best. Yes.
You are not at all!
I'm trying...
There... was Rio-senpai's...
Be quick. The meal is getting cold.
Then, let me introduce the personnel of the Platoon 1121 again.
Let's start with the platoon leader.
I am Felicia Heideman, Second Lieutenant. I'm the tank commander.
Let's have fun!
Nice to meet you!
This is...
Come on, Noël.
I'm Kannagi Noë...
She's Kannagi, Corporal. She's the driver.
Also, the mechanic.
Nice to meet you!
Then, the last one.
I am Suminoya Kureha, Private. I'm the gunner.
Listen. Though I am younger in terms of age, I am still a senior to you, so you must do as I say...
She probably ran out of strength.
Thanks for your hard work, Noël-chan.
Then, shall we eat?
Eh?
But...
Enough!
Then, let's eat!
Let's eat!
I'm so happy!
I made this bacon by myself. Please eat a lot.
Yes.
Whether you do military missions or blow the horn, your body comes first.
Eat a lot and let your body grow!
I will try.
Kureha.
Yes!
After breakfast, please take her for a walk around the base.
Yes, ma'am.
Attention!
Actually, I'm busy and I don't want to do it at all, but since it's a command, I HAVE TO take you to walk around!
Y-Yes!
Thank you very much, Kureha-san.
Don't address me as if you are a friend of mine, Private Sorami!
Sorry!
Umm. Private Suminoya-dono!
Good.
Then, first, let's salute the national flag and the platoon flag!
Salute!
Tank Platoon 1121 now has five soldiers.
Including one Second Lieutenant, one Sergeant Major, one Corporal and two Privates. Altogether five!
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono!
Even though this is the smallest formation, this is after all...
An elite platoon!
Yes, madam!
Our platoon is deployed with one tank, one heavy machine gun...
...two light machine guns, four rifles and five handguns.
With this war potential, we are ordered to protect the border around Seize and Trois!
Excuse me...
Private S-Suminoya-dono, I have a question!
Good! You are permitted to speak! Private Sorami.
If I remem... If my memory is correct, isn't the other side of Seize...?
The other side of the mountain is indeed no man's land.
But our country, Helvetia, extends there anyway, so here is the border! The frontier!
It is an important strongpoint.
For this reason, we take turns every night.
No absences allowed for two years!
This is the only hotline in the town that connects to other people.
In other words,
if it rings, we have to take it as the most important thing of all!
In that situation, you need to wake up everybody, entering the first category of alarm condition immediately!
You understand?
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono!
The second floor contains the Captain's quarters and the briefing room.
Usually, trespassing is...
free.
But you need to knock properly!
This is the bathroom.
Boiling the water for the bath is also a part of the cleaning duties!
And then...
The order of taking a bath also depends on ranking, right?
No.
Because it is enjoyable to take baths together, isn't it?
Platoon Leader! What are you doing!
I am cleaning the bathroom.
Noël is on duty today!
But she looked so tired.
As the Platoon Leader, you're setting a bad example to the recruit by doing it yourself.
I will do it later! A Platoon Leader needs to act as a Platoon Leader! Please get out of here immediately!
Now, take a GOOD look at it!
This is the main battle tank deployed to Platoon 1121, Vector 0 series self-walking tank, Takemicaduchi!
It's a lot bigger than the one on the training field!
This is the so-called tank of the zeroth generation!
One of the only ten remainders from the old time in this country.
I've heard that they are really powerful tanks.
But, its feet...
It is being repaired.
We don't have enough parts.
E-Even though the deployment manual is lost and we can't find the parts,
Noël will do something anyway, so no problem!
I won't let you say it's a decoration!
This tank will stand, at some time, stand... for sure...
Don't take me for a fool.
It's slow.
Our platoon is slow.
People are calling us "The Burden Troop of Seize" or "Decoration."
We are the pink queens, but we don't even have a working tank.
But...!
Kureha-chan.
The walk around is over. Dismissed!
They've become friends instantly, haven't they?
Are you sure?
It's exactly like when us two first met.
Right.
But I am a little bit bothered.
Last night, after you sent Kana-chan to bed...
Platoon Leader! Why is that girl a communicator!
Didn't you tell me that we were only recruiting for gun loaders and drivers?
We have to do this. It was Headquarters that sent the girl here.
It's usual that we don't get what we want.
But...!
OK, OK. Everything is fine.
Rio will still love you.
Just like what we have now.
Of course I am the same.
That girl is pretty perceptive. Maybe she's discovered something?
Maybe.
I have to do something.
It appeared.
What?
A ghost?
Yeah.
That's nonsense!
You must be half asleep, Noël!
As expected.
What do you mean by saying "as expected!"
I also saw the ghost.
It was from the direction of our lodging, right?
Yes.
What are you saying arbitrarily!
But generally speaking, ghosts exist, right?
I've said "STOP", OK?
Noël, you too?
As a mechanic, you should completely investigate it in a scientific way before reporting it!
I won't.
Why?
It's scary.
What are you talking about!?
There's no way that ghosts exist!
No way! No way! Completely no way!
I have the same opinion as you.
For sure.
Yes. There can't be ghosts.
No ghosts!
Definitely not!
Definitely definitely not!
Right!
Go and investigate carefully!
In case of an emergency, sound your horn!
Reinforcements shall be sent immediately!
Why...?
Excuse me, Private-dono.
What? Kana... Private!
I feel...
kind of nervous!
The thunder is like an advancing march.
This is a mission, not a game!
Listen, Kana...Private Sorami!
You go first. I will back you up.
Yes!
Then, penetrate!
The area around here is the same as it was before it was transformed into a fortress.
What was it before that?
How would I know that?
Just go now!
Umm.
It is written in idea. What does it say?
Idea is the fictional name they use for japanese in Sora no Woto.
You can't even read it, don't look at it any more.
It might be a beautiful story! If only I could read it...
It doesn't matter. It can only be some girl's nonsense.
Time for us to go!
You're not scared?
No.
Clumsy...
Because ghosts are protecting us, right?
What?
In the village where I was born, we welcome ghosts every year, and we have a Thanksgiving festival for them.
Where the hell is that village.
Ghosts possess people, suck their blood, make the corpse move, etc. They do a lot of bad things.
That was almost dangerous.
Rats spread bad diseases, and...
What? How come you're afraid too...
It looked as if...
It was there.
Kureha? Private-dono?
I guess... Could it be that this place used to be a school?
What? Such a large school wouldn't exist, even in the capital.
But there must have been a lot more people before.
So in the past, the building must have been filled with kids our age studying together.
Ahh!
W-What? What? What!?
Music must have been taught here.
It wasn't even a military place?
Look at this!
It won't change.
Even though I can't read the text...
D sharp.
Sound, won't change.
What are you daydreaming by yourself for?
W-What!?
Kureha-chan! So beautiful!
What!?
Everything!
The town of Seize, the fortress, and everybody in this platoon.
We are just a tiny platoon from the countryside that no one cares about.
The tank can't even move. Supply is almost forgotten.
Now, we barely look like a platoon.
We are about to disappear.
But you like it very much, don't you?
What!? What!? What!?
It's there!! It's there!
Wait, Kureha!
Kanata!
Amazing...
Of course!
Because I am the gunner of the beautiful, beautiful and deeply-loved Platoon 1121!
You saw the true ghost?
Is there any way that this is a ghost?
Hey, you. You look a lot like the thief from yesterday.
This damn prat! I will eat you!
Don't do that, Rio.
Don't threaten someone who's injured.
But...
She doesn't have any other place to go.
And have you forgotten our platoon's coat of arms?
If you make her into a roasted bird, you are opposing your badge.
Right, Shuko-chan?
You don't even have to name her...
But I think she is beautiful.
Don't forget you almost died because of this prat yesterday!
But because of that, we had a big adventure today!
Right, Kureha-chan?
W-What are you talking about!?
You can't categorize that as an adventure!
Good grief. Let's decide by majority.
No. This is an order from the Platoon Leader.
If anybody eats her in secret, there will punishment, all right?
Everybody got it?
Wow!
It was Rio this morning!
If we let Kanata do it everyday, the people in town will complain.
Sorry.
Kana-chan's seat is there.
Kureha-chan?
We found the same chairs by chance.
It's not custom made for you...
Thank you!
Come on! Release me!
What are you girls doing? That's dangerous.
Breakfast...
A Day in the Platoon - Rio Runs!
Next time: A Day in the Platoon - Rio Runs!