Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
I'll dispense you with the face of mask
kamen no kao de tebanasu no da
We meet only to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume nomama tabitatou
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru utakanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
Your Majesty, there is a matter I must bring to your attention...
Speak.
Yes... Um...
What? Speak clearly.
We've received a letter from the Alliance of the Six Nations
requesting an explanation as to why we are gathering soldiers.
What of it?
Perhaps we should cancel the martial arts tournament after all...
Dear me! Is that what you wanted to say?
Why?
I feel that having participants kill one another exceeds the boundaries of a tournament...
Furthermore, the prize offered to the winner...
Do you mean Emperor Gaz's remains?
Yes.
I do not need to take anyone's orders regarding the tournament,
or offering the reward I received for subjugating the emperor as a prize.
But...
There's no other festival
as wonderful as this to be found in all of Verbist. And yet you speak of canceling it...
What a terrible shame, Father.
What do you intend to do, Father?
Arina, Irina, don't worry.
I will not cancel the tournament.
The Castle of Madness
Hmm...
Gathered so few...
Chaika!
Start a fire!
Surprised! Big catch!
Whirl, flames!
The Burner!
Many blessings of the sea!
Okay, it's done.
It's ready?
Want?
Want.
Give.
Accept.
You eat?
It doesn't have to be magic fuel?
Biological organs. Nutrition necessary.
She's not a machine?
Niva's body, likely used Fayla organs, parts.
You again?
So it was you all who got her.
You know her?
Who can say?
Even if I did, I'm not obligated to explain anything to you.
Have question! Want answer!
Oh?
What am I?
You know that now, don't you?
Still have doubt.
Can't understand details.
Am I tool? To gather remains?
If that's what you believe, then it's probably true.
Stop being cryptic and tell us why you're here.
I bring information on remains.
King Stephan Hartgen of the Principality of Hartgen possesses remains.
Unfortunately for you, we already knew that.
We intend to head there tomorrow.
Is that so?
But this time, it will take more than ordinary means to claim them.
What do you mean?
I suppose it's about a day from here by vehicle...
I hope the other Chaika doesn't beat you there.
I don't like him... I don't like him.
Who is he working for?
The way he spoke suggests
that he gave the red Chaika this information, too.
Should we let the red Chaika steal the remains?
That's one way...
Why does Guy know about Niva?
Want shellfish.
Shellfish?
Hey, you!
You're eating too much! How much have you had?!
Huh?
You eat them whole?
This stuff makes great material for my armor.
Want shellfish. Quickly.
Cooking now. Wait a bit.
What a horrible sight.
This doesn't look like the result of an ordinary battle.
A magic attack, huh?
And one by either an extremely powerful wizard,
or a very powerful Gundo.
It looks like this tower was built using magic, too.
What on earth happened here?
The documents that Curren-san found in the library...
The lab they mentioned, where the emperor's fortune was hidden,
may have been here.
Where is this fortune, then?
Who's there? Come out quietly!
What have you come here for?
We're the Gillette Squad, employed by the Kliemann Organization
under the Alliance of the Six Nations.
The Alliance of the Six Nations?
Are you from the Gaz Empire?
What if we are?
Very well. That's enough.
The war is over.
There is no reason we should fight here.
We haven't come to apprehend you.
What happened here? Will you tell us?
Two girls in white and red, calling themselves Chaika, were here.
They had the same hair and eyes as you...
Don't liken me to them!
And what happened to those girls?
When the white Chaika came close,
the doll that Izhmash had made turned into a Gundo.
So this island really was Emperor Gaz's secret lab.
Mass production of demi-human soldiers and Fayla,
and the technology to control them...
What use would one have for that outside of war?
Why did Izhmash continue this research, even after Emperor Gaz died?
The emperor told him to do so.
He said it would become necessary even after his death.
Chaika...
In other words, Chaika Gaz may be the calamity that brings war again
to this peaceful world that we finally obtained.
We must not let Chaika gather his remains.
You're saying Chaika took that Gundo away, correct?
Yes. The doll followed her voluntarily.
Is that enough?
Do you intend to stay here?
We're not going back.
There's no place for us on the mainland.
Don't concern yourselves with us any further.
We can infer that the Gundo that Chaika took was the emperor's fortune.
So if Chaika, his daughter, has it now...
The Gundo could use his remains to become a powerful weapon
and plunge the world into war again, huh?
Yes...
But I will not let that happen.
Fuchan...
"The Gillette Squad is to head
for the Principality of Hartgen at once.
One of the eight heroes,
King Hartgen, is suspected of gathering soldiers for a military expansion.
Requesting immediate investigation", it says.
If he's one of the eight heroes, Chaika would head there for the remains.
Yeah.
We're heading to the Principality of Hartgen.
Toru...
Uh-huh?
Gathering remains, purpose... for father's funeral.
But I am orphan.
Not Emperor Gaz's daughter.
Understand well.
But still have desire to collect remains.
Yeah.
I understand why you'd wonder what you could gain by gathering his remains now.
But I don't care. I'm resolved to this.
Huh?
I don't know what will happen after we gather them all.
But we just have to keep going until you're satisfied.
I've made my decision to stay
by your side until the end.
Toru...
I am back, Brother.
I've brought back a great haul of mollusks.
I can't guess how they taste, but that is no problem.
We should cut them into chunks and season them with something sour.
They're the mollusks you asked for, Brother.
I didn't ask for those.
Why'd you put it on my head?!
You don't realize that you look manlier with that on your head?!
Cut it out!
Hey!
Chaika!
Are you kidding me?
It's starting already?
So the entire ground inside these walls is a battlefield?
Defeat quickly!
Sadica, asdic, rimazo...
Come forth, that which protects and defends!
You've passed the qualifying round.
The tournament may be fought in groups of two to three.
You may use any weapon you can hold in your hands.
Use any armor or defensive gear you like.
Of course, Gundos are also permitted.
Will you three participate as a group?
Yeah.
Then tie those cloths around your arms.
They identify you as participants.
Then proceed to the barracks inside the second wall.
King Hartgen adheres to true martial arts.
In other words, while we call this a tournament,
it is a battle in which your lives are at stake.
Know that.
It's like a war.
Oh? Want to withdraw?
No.
He said it starts in two days, right?
So we have to wait in the barracks until then?
Does your wound hurt?
It's nothing serious.
David, must not overdo.
Hey, come on, Chaika.
Hearing kind words like that from you just makes me worried.
Forget about me. Just think about your own goal.
You're going to get the prize of the remains
and then take all the ones the white girl has, right?
Obvious. No point asking now.
Then let's get in there and do this!
Remains white Chaika has, tournament prize...
Take all.
I'll get rid of you before the tournament!
Just try it!
You two, stop it!
If you keep this up, you'll be disqualified!
Clean this up.
Who is he?
You don't know?
The king realized he had talent and hired him as a bodyguard.
He didn't have to kill them...
They call it a martial arts tournament,
but it's just a killing match.
Killing match?
Yep.
But is there some reason for the participants to risk their lives?
Well, the winner receives money and high status.
They say the winner will be employed as a knight in the castle,
and the king will give him the treasure he earned for subjugating the emperor.
Treasure?
Take my advice.
You don't want to go near that town until the tournament's over.
Guy was right. Ordinary means won't be enough here.
The Principality of Hartgen
has always encouraged citizens to learn martial arts,
but after the king returned from the war, the tournament changed.
Participants are now entering the castle in droves.
Why fight to the death?
It's hard to believe they're sane.
Yeah...
All right, Matheus and Zita, seek an audience with King Hartgen
and try to get a feel for him.
Vivi and I will sneak into the tournament disguised as participants.
Leonardo, find out who the participants are.
Aida, fual, alluel...
Come forth, to surround and hide!
The Concealer!
Okay! Perfect cover!
Goeranson Castle walls, extremely high.
Infiltrate, difficult?
Yeah. We'll have to go in through the front.
Does that mean we'll participate in the tournament?
I can participate, too, right?
Yes. Need your help, Fredrica.
Just leave it to me! I finally get to go nuts again!
Go nuts! Welcome!
Hey...
Brother, it may be a good idea to accept a dragoon's help.
You're right.
Infiltrate castle walls, then search for remains.
Search needed?
Yes. Search, then take remains.
Take remains, mission complete?
Yes. Then, with luck, escape.
Must search for remains immediately.
Yes. Niva, wise.
Wise? Unexpected.
Niva, modest.
Modest. Word used by people of skill.
That means modest!
Niva, fun! Good person!
Not person. I am Gundo.
No difference. Niva, have personality!
King Hartgen, it is an honor to meet you.
I am Matheus Callaway, a vice captain of the Kliemann Organization.
I have a favor to ask of you...
I will not cancel the martial arts tournament.
Nor will I return the emperor's remains.
Would you two care to participate, as well?
Hey, these guys are serious!
You're going too easy, Nikolai!
Die!
What's going on?
They're not in their right mind.
You pass.
It's already begun.
Yes.
Let us in! We wish to participate in the tournament!
Where'd they go?
Come forth, to strike and crush!
The Slugger!
Defeat, success!
It's over already? I didn't get to do anything!
Fredrica, strongest. Save for now.
Aw, what the heck?!
You've passed the qualifying round.
Tie these on your arms.
They identify you as participants.
Is that girl a spectator?
Uh... She's a reserve fighter.
Hi there. Nice to see you're well.
Who are you?
That's your greeting? And after I saved you...
What are you talking about?
Oh, that's right. You don't remember.
I saw the hatred within your heart.
That's why I saved your life.
I think you've realized
that even as you lived in a world without war,
you always felt that something wasn't right.
The doubt and uncertainty toward this world that swirl in your heart
are proof that you are incapable of living in this peaceful world.
That is why you drew your sword, yes?
Against the deceptive justice that was willing to sacrifice your precious subordinates.
And so you attempted to kill your opponent.
I...
You should work for the king.
What do you mean?
Who are you?
You'll know soon enough.
White Chaika will come.
This time...
I know Chaika will come here.
I know it.
Captain Nikolai and Vivi are among the participants as planned.
I told them about the black Chaikas, as well.
They have also seen the white and red Chaikas on the grounds.
It appears they intend to participate in the tournament.
They do?
Then the red and white Chaikas aren't working for Hartgen?
They must have found out that the grand prize was the emperor's remains.
That must mean the black Chaikas we saw with King Hartgen are...
Matheus-san?
Yeah...
Leo, they haven't seen your face yet.
Run from here.
King Hartgen has ordered us to entertain his guests.
Please accompany us.
Efun... Heluste... Ru... Belguil... Fai... Sev...
Come forth, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Remains, inside castle. Deep place.
Beneath the castle, then?
Let's just go as far as we can.
If it looks like we can steal them, we will.
Then we won't have to be in this stupid tournament.
Uh-huh.
Chaika, you wait in the barracks.
Toru, Akari. Caution, very important.
Don't worry. We won't do anything crazy.
We'll be back.
Right.
Shall we go?
Niva! Unknown person!
Your work is done.
Explain!
Bringing this girl here was part of your mission.
You've completed that.
Don't understand...
No need to worry.
Niva, agreed to go with Guy?
Voluntarily agreed.
It's as she says.
You don't need to worry about a thing.
The sky is overcast
The bell rings to signal the beginning
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
noroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
The time has come to break a curse
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
kono inochi kono ai mo
This life and this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
Principality of Hartgen, inside Goeranson Castle, many violent men!
Muscles everywhere!
Full of bloodlust!
I am frightened...
Black Agenda
Next time: "Black Agenda".