When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Everyone, thank you for watching Hayate no Gotoku again.
Now, let's sing the opening song together!
I wonder what Nishizawa-san is doing right now.
One family.
Five or six customers.
Two couples.
One old man.
Crowded.
No one's here.
Welcome.
Let's see...
Anmitsu with cream, egg stew, tokoroten, kuzu mochi, abekawa mochi, isobe yaki, inaka zenzai, and a cream soda.
Note: These are all sweets.
All of those, please.
Y-Yes.
I wonder what Hayate-kun's doing right now.
Come to think of it, what did Nishizawa-san come here for the other day?
I shall...
Lick her all over!
Hayate-kun!
Ina**ma Kick!
Eh, Nishizawa-san?
Thank goodness you're here.
And then there was the quarrel with Milady.
Milady and Nishizawa-san.
Delivery.
Thank you very much.
I feel bad for Nishizawa-san.
I love you, Hayate-kun!
I don't want to say goodbye like this.
So please go out with me!
But right now, I don't have the right to date any girls.
Um...
I'm sorry.
I'm...
...only interested in 2-D girls.
Gahhh!!!
I should have said no in a better manner.
You jerk!!!
But I don't know what I'm supposed to do in times like that.
And, why did Milady's face come to mind then?
Is that you, Hayate?
Yes.
A delivery for you, Milady.
Thanks. Will you open it for me?
Milady.
You are a girl, so please don't read books in that manner.
O-Okay.
I bet an older brother worrying about his little sister must feel like this.
I won't find a girlfriend for a while at this rate.
My hands are full with Milady.
By the way, what is this?
It looks like a document from Hakuou Academy.
It's a transfer form.
For you.
So it's for me.
What do you mean, for me?!
Like I said, it's a transfer form so you can enroll into Hakuou.
I haven't heard anything about that! Anything!
I haven't told you anything about it before, either.
But I dropped out of my other school.
I knew of that a long time ago.
I have that school's documents in hand, too.
See? Right here.
But what am I going to do about tuition?
I don't have the economical backing to afford it.
What are you talking about? Of course, I'll pay.
B-But.
What?
You don't want to go to school with me?
And this is like a thank you to you.
So don't worry about it.
I can go to school again...
Thank you, Milady.
Why are you crying?
Because... Because...
What did you do to make him cry?
No, I didn't make him cry.
He started crying on his own.
After reading this, it appears he has to take a transfer exam.
If you're going to claim to be a Sanzenin butler,
then you'll have to pass Hakuou's transfer exam.
Oh my, Klaus-san.
You're still alive?
Please don't go killing people.
So, if he can't pass the exam, he'll also be fired as a butler.
Hey, what now?
That's fine by me.
After having so much done for me, if I can't pass it,
I'll be too ashamed to be a butler... much less a man!
So observe everyone! What I can do when I'm serious!
For your information, Hakuou's standard score is just over 65.
It's fine. It'll be fine.
By the way, the exam is tomorrow.
Thank you for the useful information.
But will Hayate-kun really be okay?
Seeing his grades from his last school, he's right on the cutoff line.
What's Hayate doing?
He's studying.
I see.
Come in.
How is it going?
Slowly coming along.
Please don't stress over it so much.
Yes.
Just as Maria-san said, I'll call it a night.
Ch-Chief Butler!
Wake up! Please wake up! This is my bed!
Good morning.
It's not morning, yet.
Please get out.
Ayasaki Hayate-kun, you misunderstand me.
I want you to enter Hakuou Academy, as well.
I want you to pass tomorrow's transfer exam!
Do you really?
Do my eyes look like they're lying?
You're scary.
Sorry.
If you're thinking of my welfare,
then please leave and let me sleep.
I'm here to tell you my application process story because I care about you!
I humbly reject your offer.
Accept it!
Stop being nonsensical!
I said I don't want to hear it!
It was when I applied to a prestigious private kindergarten.
Ahh... He started.
There was a problem I couldn't solve no matter what.
The time limit was approaching.
Yet, I couldn't solve it.
And right when the time was about to run out...
Klaus-kun, you pass.
So the lesson is to never give up?
Chief Butler!
Klaus-san!
Get out!
Teretemasu, hisabisa no deban de = I'm blushing because I got some screentime
Teretemasu, hisabisa no deban de
Deluxe animation, Tama no otaku!
Deluxe animation, Tama no otaku! = Deluxe animation, Tama's house!
Sine, cosine, tangent.
I bet they'll come up.
That voice!
Tama! Where did you come in from?
I'll tell you what Hakuou's exam style and questions are like.
I don't want to be taught by you!
Get out!
Ow.
This should do it.
Hayate, Hayate.
You don't have to worry. Sleep tight.
Roar!!!
Are you all right?
I'm only lacking a bit of sleep.
A train?
It's because the campus is so large.
I've done the best I could.
I wonder what kind of questions I'll get.
I think it'll be English and such, like any other place.
But I don't think you'll pass using Moe-tan.
You think Hakuou Academy's transfer exam is something ordinary?
Nagi-chan?
Welcome, former intruder.
And Nagi-chan!
I'm today's proctor, the beautiful world history teacher,
Katsura Yukiji.
"B-Beautiful?"
Don't question that word!!!
Not ordinary? But I took an ordinary exam when I entered here.
If you rely on the past, you won't gain anything in the future, Nagi-chan.
I'm not sure about only looking forward.
Anyway, we'll start the transfer exam, so follow me!
The topic is... the Redmond-style interview exam!
The Redmond-style interview exam is...
...a popular exam style during job interviews...
...to see the candidate's true intelligence through logic questions.
"Why is a manhole cover round?"
It's an exam that doesn't rely on memorization...
...and tests only the intelligence by asking....
...and answering peculiar questions and so on, as logically as possible.
I see. This sure is the famous Hakuou Academy.
The exam style is unique on its own.
By the way, why is a manhole cover round?
Because if it's square, a slight tilt will make it fall.
The length of a diagonal in a square is longer than its sides.
Whereas a circle doesn't have that problem.
You're so smart!
Obviously. I don't go to Hakuou for nothing.
Okay, let's start the exam.
It'll be inside this classroom.
The test begins the moment you step in.
Everything you do or say in here affects your score.
Get ready.
Question one is...
This!
SFX: SNAP
SFX: RATATATATATATA
Are you making fun of Hayate?
Or are teachers forgiven no matter what they do?
Nagi-chan, your jabs are brutal.
But! This is Hakuou Academy!
And, this is a Redmond-style interview exam that tests true intelligence!
If you want to, go ahead and answer the question as you imagined.
But I wonder if that's the answer.
She's right.
At a glance, this is an intelligence test where
a monkey has to get the banana using tools.
But in Redmond-style interview exams,
usually the first thing that comes to your mind is incorrect.
Then...
I got it.
The point to this question is the height at which the banana is hung.
The banana is actually at a height low enough to reach by hand.
Therefore all the tools around it are just to fool you,
and the answer is to take it without using any of the tools.
This is the answer.
SFX: Growl~~
The one and only food for the monkeys that couldn't get the food and are starving.
Oh damn it, so that's how you play it, eh?
I get it. So I get to become red all over after these long, peaceful days?
But listen.
If I don't beat this,
I can't go to school!
Here I go!
So he fights rather than running away.
This is animal abuse.
But, wow, your butler puts up a good fight.
Well, his life depends on this exam.
I see.
Then let's end the joke here and get the real exam started.
What?! This was a joke?!
Of course! If you can test for intelligence with an exam like this, then where's the effort?
Then what was all of this for?
As a token of my thanks, I thought I'd let you loosen up.
I don't need this kind of thanks.
And so Hayate takes the exam
physically and mentally beaten up.
Calm down. Calm down first.
How did it go?
I managed to answer all the questions.
But if I didn't pass it after all you've done for me, what should I do?
Why are you being so pessimistic now?
I'm sure you passed.
You're the person I have faith in,
so let's go to school together.
You're right, Milady.
Heh, Superindendent...
You want me to send this to Sanzenin?
But... Superindendent...
Is it correct to assume you made a typo?
He was a point away from the passing line.
He almost made it.
I... I see...
If he had answered more calmly, he might have passed.
He was really close.
Therefore,
I leave you to your task, Katsura-sensei.
Meanwhile, at the Sanzenin's,
where they don't know what's to come...
It's little early, but let's start the celebration party.
What? Really?
I'm so happy!
...they're already in a party mode.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Hayate, was studying for the test fun?
Yes, I was able to enjoy the mood of a student.
Thank you very much, Milady.
No need for that, Hayate.
We'll be able to go to school together every day from now on.
Well, I guess so.
It'll be goodbye to your all-night online gaming life.
I don't like that idea.
Eh?
I know! You can skip school with me from now on!
Ehhh?!?!
Bye bye!
I meant it as a prank! I meant it as a simple joke!
I never thought he'd fail by just one point!
So you want me to go apologize with you?
Yes, exactly.
Today's party will be a blast.
It's all for he who was admitted to Hakuou.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Wait a Moment! I Have to Go to the Party. Make It Fast.
This situation makes it harder to bring the issue up than I'd thought.
Apocalyptic destiny.