I finally found her.
What did she do at that summer festival?
No, what will she do?
If I can find that out, I can stop her!
Hiruko appears in the form of Haine, the first human she ever copied.
She prefers being called by that name.
She is the god of Hitogashima.
Hiruko-no-Mikoto, mother of the shadows.
This kid... is a god?
Recently, due to poor nutrition, her legs have weakened.
She needed another body.
How many times have we met like this?
Well, Ajiro Shinpei?
Yer still alive?
Ya did it.
You killed Ushio.
You killed Mio.
You're the monster who swallowed up the island.
That's the god of this island?
You were right there from the beginning...
Ya were right in front of me all along!
Shinpei, step back!
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
No, Haine!
Bloody Night
But his loud voice echoes in my head and irritates me.
I almost killed ya by accident.
I like my meals in silence.
Don't speak to me again.
Tokiko.
Ms. Negoro?
What?
She's a nurse at our clinic.
An average of four people die each year on Hitogashima...
by illness or accident.
You already know where I'm going with this, right?
We've always given those dead people to her.
My father also did this.
As did my grandfather, great-grandfather, and so on.
What's with the coffins?
Don't tell me ya feed people to her!
I was waiting fer this.
Quite a feast today!
Tomorrow shall be even bigger.
I said you weren't capable of killing.
But I'm prepared to die by your hands.
W-Wait.
Toki, ya can't be...
Come closer and take a look-see, Ushio.
This is yer original that I missed out on eating.
N-No way!
Ushio!
Is it Ushio?
But we cremated her yesterday.
We gathered her bones!
Dad switched out her body.
Haine printed those bones from someone.
Why?
Why go that far?
Why take care of her?
Toki, ya knew everything?!
That Shiori was being targeted?!
And that Ushio was gonna be killed?!
I didn't know about Ushio.
I had no idea she and her shadow were working together to save Shiori.
She died because she got involved in something that she shouldn't have.
What?
This was all for Haine.
Screw that!
I can't forgive this!
Where's our old man?!
Ya don't know shit! Shut yer goddamn mouth, idiot!
It's yer fault I got stuck having to deal with this!
I didn't have a choice.
I didn't.
If Haine dies, so would our mother.
What?
Mom isn't still alive because her sickness is gone!
Dad begged Haine to turn her into a shadow to keep her alive!
What?
No... Huh? What do ya mean?
I don't get this.
Mom is...
What?
Both ya and Shinpei...
treat Ushio like the real Ushio, don't ya?!
Toki.
No.
I can't let Ushio be eaten by her and disappear!
Shadows freeze for a few seconds during a scan.
Haine's no exception!
Now, Ushio!
Print!
I was waiting fer ya to say that!
Take this!
Ushio!
Are you hurt?
No fair!
They stole my dinner!
Thanks, Ushio.
Are ya okay?
The right time's upon us.
Before it's too late, I should...
Why?
Why fight against shadows?
Are you stupid?
You'll just die.
You can't win.
There's no way.
The Toki I know wouldn't do this willingly.
It's just using ya.
Taking advantage of yer weaknesses.
It's playing with yer emotions to feed its hunger.
Can ya just accept that?
Because I never would!
Don't be messing with my sister's best friend.
I don't care if yer a god or Hiruko or whatever.
Don't underestimate humans!
Ushio...
Boring.
What?
Do they not need to disguise themselves as humans anymore?
I wanna eat Ushio's memories.
Make sure not to kill her.
The best option now...
is for Ushio to break my neck and for me to loop back.
That was actually my plan.
I need to avoid exposing Ushio to any more danger.
But...
I should stop Ushio, but I can't.
I know why.
It's because Ushio and I...
There it is!
...share the same feeling!
Don't underestimate humans!
If I'm gonna die anyway,
I might as well go down fighting.
Shin—
Stop, Haine.
That's enough.
You just tried to eat Shinpei, didn't you?
But they took my food!
That's not a good reason.
But...
How?
Don't worry, Haine.
I'll get Kofune Ushio's body back.
You can't eat this one.
She's an important hostage.
Mio!
Give it a rest.
I know already.
Don't worry.
Mio is alive.
However, if you take even one step,
I'll crush her head like an egg.
Hey. What's going on?
Ya said ya wouldn't touch Mio!
Don't get so upset.
Everyone will die tomorrow, anyway.
What are ya saying?
The last meal at the summer festival tomorrow will heal Haine's body...
and Mom will live again.
Everything will go back to normal.
Just how Dad planned it.
Ain't that right?!
We appreciate the Hishigatas' support.
However, that shall end soon.
Ya betrayed us.
What will ya do to us?!
Tokiko!
Wow!
Brother...
Your father already knows all of this.
Summer Time Rendering
Crap.
I can't stay conscious.
Sis...
Hey, are ya okay?
Yer all bloody!
Totsumura.
Thank goodness.
He's human.
I'm done for.
I'm sorry, Sis.
Ryuunosuke.
Ya were at Ushio's funeral... The lady with the H-cup boobs!
They're a G-cup, dummy!
Where is Kofune Mio?
She was with you.
A-A monster took her.
These baby monsters showed up.
Where's your gun?
I dropped it somewhere.
I took it out and shot at them, but it didn't...
I fell, then I ran.
I don't remember anything after that.
Running was the right choice.
What?
I need your help.
I can't walk anymore, so I need you to carry me.
R-Right! I'll take ya to a hospital—
No.
Take me to the deepest part of this cave!
I can't let this be real.
Ushio.
Come here.
Nice and slow.
I won't forgive y'all!
Who cares if you won't?
Do you want Mio to die?
Come.
St-Stop.
Don't touch her.
If ya wanna eat humans, eat me!
No point in dying in style.
I was wrong to call ya a dud.
Ya couldn't defeat Negoro if ya were.
Yer not broken.
In fact, you've evolved.
It's a waste to erase ya.
Instead, I'll fix yer head and use ya.
I need labor fer tomorrow.
No!
Shinpei!
Please stop!
Guess I can't erase his power.
Which came first, the chicken or the egg?
It's all a loop.
Not fair!
Your right eye can take a bird's-eye view and
see the flow of time from a higher dimension.
It observes multiple parallel worlds.
With it, you can make the world you observe into reality.
You're rendering this world.
Truly the terrifying power of a god.
However, you aren't skilled in using that power.
You can't activate it unless you lose self-awareness by dying.
In other words, we just need to not kill you.
How simple.
Just keep breathing here until tomorrow ends...
drowning in despair.
Mio...
It's hopeless.
If I can't loop, I can't redo anything.
I'm breaking that promise again.
I'm not protecting anyone.
I'm sorry, Mio. I'm sorry, Ushio.
A-Am I interrupting?!
Totsumu—
Ms. Nagumo!
This is my last shot!
That was close!
I almost let her kill you, Shinpei.
Totsumura, Ms. Nagumo...
Nothing can get in our way now.
Thank you...
What?
Thanks to them... I was able to drink it.
You...
Shinpei.
Listen to me.
If one of us dies or gets fatally hurt,
I'll immediately loop back.
What?
Y-Yer gonna kill yerself?
How?
I'll use this.
Wait... ya brought the mercury dichloride with?
How much of this is fatal?
Even a drop would do the trick.
Then drinking the whole bottle will do it fer sure.
Yeah, but it'll be painful.
Yeah.
Let's hope I never use it.
Is this poison?
You know how to die.
Don't tell me you've come this far many times?
Once is enough to deal with you assholes.
Wow, I didn't think you'd have the guts.
Listen...
I'll redo this as many times as it takes.
In the end, I'll defeat y'all!
Ya can count on that!
Hey!
There's nothing I can do now.
I'm sorry, Haine.
Forget him.
Look at her.
She's been repairing the damage I inflicted on her!
Shinpei's risking his life...
so I can't just give up...
without a fight!
She's actually eroding me now!
It can't be! Are ya the egg?!
Kill her!
Don't worry about me!
She disappeared?
That bastard...
He took her.
Ushio!
Shinpei!
You'll be okay.
I won't let go!
I'm sorry, Shinpei.
It's all my fault. Everyone died... Even Mio...
No!
Don't look back.
Just look at the present.
We'll defeat them.
Even if it costs me my life.
I'll go anywhere ya want,
no matter how many times it takes.
As long as we're together.
In other words, you're a time traveler.
Yes.
Yes?
We just returned from the future.
July 22nd
(Fifth loop)
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Friend