Ebisuzawa Kurumi from
Class 3-B, ready to go!
C'mon, what's the problem?
You won't get this pool clean
all hunched over like that!
But Kurumi-chan, the floor's really slippery...
Fool! You will call me "Sergeant"!
You're really on a weird kick today, Kurumi-chan.
That's "Sergeant"!
Follow my lead, Private Takeya!
Yes'm...
C'mon, bust those buns!
Roger!
More, more!
Be careful not to slip, you two!
Roger that!
Whoa! Stop, stop!
Hey, are you okay?
W-We're fine...
Ow... Watch where you're going.
I told you it was slippery.
Be more careful!
They sure are fired up today.
It's really a good thing Yuki-chan
had an extra swimsuit.
It looks good on you.
That doesn't make me happy...
Why did you bring these back
from the mall, anyway?
There must've been things you needed more.
Well...
We're girls, you know.
Still...
SCHOOL ONLY
Staff Emergency Evacuation Manual
After what happened just last night...
Should we really be doing this now?
Wow! Taroumaru leaves it sparkling
clean just by sliding around!
I understand that you're concerned,
but let's not think about it for now.
All right! I'm promoting him two ranks!
It's pool weather today, after all!
Uh...
This is a water tank, not a pool, right?
School Living Club
#9
Holiday
That Morning
SCHOOL ONLY
Staff Emergency Evacuation Manual
Did you get any sleep?
As if I could.
I suppose not.
Hey, that key had Megu-nee's
name written on it, right?
Yes.
So then, from the start, Megu-nee knew...
She knew something would happen,
and kept it secret from us.
Is that what you're saying?
I-I don't know. I don't, but...
I'm not sure, but I doubt it.
This has instructions not to
open it unless ordered to.
They might've given it to her a long time
ago, but even if she had read it...
It would've been after all this happened.
Jeez, all this stuff about
infections and bio-weapons
is so confusing, I can't think straight!
There's something interesting
written in here, though.
An emergency evacuation plan?
There's a second basement level?
Since you didn't know about it, I assume
you've never gone there yourselves.
No.
Is there... something down there?
C'mon, everyone, let's clean!
O-Oh, Yuki-chan, I thought you
were taking Taroumaru for a walk.
Why do you want to clean all of a sudden?
Look at him.
I let Taroumaru loose on the roof,
and he jumped into the lake.
What, again?
Yuki-chan...
Senpai, please be more careful.
Let's all graduate together!!
Write 100 pages each
I can't write that many
Sorry.
You see? It's really filthy!
And there are fish in there.
I feel bad making them live in that.
That's true. Well, it's warm out today,
so maybe we should make cleaning
the tank our job for today.
You're just going to play
in the water, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah! That'd be nice, too!
Yuki-senpai, did you do that to Taroumaru
on purpose so you could play around?!
N-No! Taroumaru was really enjoying his swim!
And it made you want to join in?
A little. A teeny bit.
Senpai, this is no time to be doing things like...
That's a good idea, Yuki-chan.
Yes. Let's spend today cleaning the water tank.
Really, Rii-san?
Sure. We just bought new swimsuits, didn't we?
Yippee!
Isn't that great, Taroumaru?
We should get that scum off first.
Roger!
I meant you too, Yuki-senpai. It's all over you.
Are you sure?
I think we all need a little time
to collect our thoughts.
Sorry. But let's all play
after we clean! I can't wait!
About the future, and about Megu-nee, too.
Kurumi-chan, you actually look
thinner when fully dressed, huh?
Don't say it like that.
Y-Yuuri-senpai.
What is it?
N-Nothing! Never mind...
The sky's so blue!
Yes. The weather's lovely.
It sure is.
The algae really took over the tank,
since no one's been taking care of it.
There's a lot of sand and grit in there, too.
What the heck is that? Gross.
What is this lake supposed to be, anyway?
It's a biotope.
This water tank is a man-made reconstruction
of a natural aquatic habitat.
We use it a lot for biology study.
Wow.
Hey, what kind of fish are in there?
I think they put rainbow trout and carp in it.
Anyway, let's get the fish into
buckets and start cleaning!
Yeah!
All right!
The pool's open!
Not exactly...
This is unlined concrete,
unlike an actual pool, so you...
shouldn't jump in.
I'm first in!
Kurumi-chan, no fair!
As I was saying, you shouldn't...
I'm... I'm drowning!
Hey. What are you doing?
Oh, yeah! My feet touch the bottom!
Hey, this doesn't smell like pool water.
Idiot. Pools smell like chlorine.
Really? Can fish live in that stuff?
People don't keep fish in their pools.
It'd be nice if you could
keep fish in a pool, though.
So you could swim with them?
Yeah, and when I got hungry...
You'd eat them live?!
Rumble
You've done it now! Take that!
That's cold!
Looking at it now, the tank's pretty big.
Look at that belly.
Hey, Rii-san, what're those things?
Oh, those are solar panels.
What's a solar panel?
A sun-powered battery.
It's thanks to them that we're
able to live a normal life.
For now, that is.
And there's a water purifier, too.
It filters water from the river and groundwater.
You know so much.
The gardening club does all its work up here.
If Megurigaoka High School were a town,
and the students its citizens,
they would be able to do all the
tasks needed to be self-sufficient.
That's from the school brochure, isn't it?
I've read it so many times, I've got it memorized.
There are only four of us now, though.
I wonder how many people they
intended for the school to support...
They certainly didn't leave anything out.
As if...
As if they expected something to happen.
That's enough of that.
We decided we'd have fun today.
You're right.
Yes.
Taroumaru, you look awesome!
What are you doing?
So cold.
Miki, heads up!
Here!
Nice receive!
That was a set! This is a receive!
And I'm gonna...
Hey!
Don't hit it too hard!
Attack!
Or so you think, then set.
You don't need to feint.
Here!
Whoa!
Got it!
Too hard!
I'll get it!
Nice job, underclassman!
If I'm going to play, I play seriously, Senpai.
Okay, here it comes!
Here!
Okay!
This feels so nice!
Yuuri-senpai, it's coming your way!
No problem!
Easy hit!
Sorry.
Sheesh, Yuki-senpai...
Still nothing coming in.
Taroumaru?
Rii-san.
What? Is something wrong?
Look, Rii-san.
Oh, I forgot we had those.
Are they water guns?
What're those doing here?
Someone brought them up here.
Interested?
Hey, tell me one last thing.
What would that be?
I can tell you're a veteran gunman.
Got any aliases?
Oh, perhaps.
What is this mood around them?
Like hell they're just toys
someone "brought up here"!
I bet you brought most of them up yourself!
Bingo.
As a reward, I'll give you two useful tips.
One: you were quite joyfully shooting rapid-fire,
but that dual-wielding style should have
you uneasy about your remaining ammo.
Two: I'll tell you my nickname.
The Balloon Bomb Sorceress.
What?
Gotcha!
Nice try!
She deflected the water balloon
without breaking it?!
Uh-oh!
Final round!
Bring it on!
Rii-san! Kurumi-chan!
I'm not done yet!
You're both getting carried away!
Sorry.
I got too worked up.
Rii-san, you were so cool.
I wanna be a sorceress, too!
How do I become one?
Well... I suppose you have to sign
a contract with a demon first.
Okay, fetch!
You won't beat me!
Wait up!
Huh? Yuuri-senpai, is that...
Oh, yes. This is your CD player, isn't it?
I'm sorry. I saw it had a built-in
radio, so I tried it out.
It's okay. Did anything come in?
I thought I could get a signal up here, but no...
Taroumaru?
I still can't get a single station to come in.
Hey, Kei...
Kei!
You'll damage your hearing if you
keep your earbuds in all the time.
Don't worry about me.
You can listen through the speaker.
But...
It's fine.
What's so funny?
Look at him.
Does it smell like Kei?
I think he wants you to play with him.
Right!
Wait for me!
The wind is getting chilly.
Th-Thanks...
Time to wrap things up, you two!
Okay!
The tank's all clean now.
Now Taroumaru will be okay when he falls in.
Don't drop him in!
It's soaking right to my bones!
Kurumi-chan, you sound like an old man.
Hey, if it's tasty, it's tasty.
I wish I could take a bath.
But of course, the school doesn't have bathtubs.
I seem to remember the sports teams
having a tub in the athletics building.
I'm not sure I want to go all
that way just for a bath...
Didn't you have fun today?
Oh, I had a great time.
It was fun, but...
What's wrong, Mii-kun?
Something on your mind?
Not really...
'Cause if it is, you can always come to me.
I'm your senpai, after all!
You don't seem all that reliable, Yuki-senpai.
I-I am reliable! Rely on me!
That hurts, you know.
The problem with you, Mii-kun, is that
you don't give your senpai any "cake."
Do you mean "keii (respect)"?
Respect
Fine. You can be the senpai, Mii-kun.
I'm sorry, I went too far!
Please don't sulk, Yuki-senpai.
You won't be mean anymore?
I won't.
You'll ask for my advice?
All right.
I have this friend.
A friend?
She was my classmate.
She was always bright and cheerful,
and we were always together.
But I haven't seen her in a while...
She refuses to go to school?
That... may be it.
Then you need to have more fun, Mii-kun!
Me?
Do you hate school?
No.
Right? I love school, too.
You're here, and so is Rii-san,
and Kurumi-chan, and Megu-nee.
I love my school!
Oh, and Taroumaru's here, too.
If we have more fun, the school will
become a more fun place to be.
And then...
Then?
Then your friend will come back!
So don't look so sad, okay?
I agree.
You're right.
What are you guys talking about?
About what a fun day we had.
It sure was.
I hope tomorrow, and the next day,
and the next, are just as good.
Okay, we'll play in the pool again tomorrow!
Senpai, you really are childish.
What was that?
Let's go to the basement tomorrow.
Oh, the emergency evacuation place?
Hopefully we'll find something good.
Basement?
I'll tell you later.
I feel like I could just fall asleep right now.
Oh? You don't want dinner?
Dinner! I forgot about dinner.
We're all tired, so why don't we
make something simple?
We've still got canned ginger soy beef, right?
Ooh! I want some, too!
Not a problem. We've got plenty.
And canned salmon and mackerel, too.
Canned yakitori is good, too.
Mii-kun, you're so refined.
Next time!!
So, Rii-san, you're a sorceress?
It's a nickname.
Lucky! I want a nickname, too.
Let's see. What about Hellraiser Girl?
Hellraiser Girl
Hellraiser Girl?
Next time on Episode 10 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Rainy Day."
#10
Rainy Day