[Narrator] Alchemy--the
science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter.
However, it is not an
all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange...
the basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation is
strictly forbidden.
For what could equal the
value of a human soul?
[train whistle]
[Al] Brother...
[Al] The stories about
this priest in Liore...
you think they're true?
The ones about his "miracles"?
[Ed] They say he can transmute
flowers out of thin air, right?
Could just be sleight of hand,
some cheap trick like that...
[Al] But, what if it's not?
Right... If it's not, then
I suppose all that leaves
is the real thing, huh?
[Ed, Age 11] The celestial stone
that destroyed the city of
Xerxes in one night. The grand
elixir, sealed away by the
Eastern Sage.. It goes by
different names, but it's
always the same thing-
some kind of object that
amplifies alchemy.
And that's the
Philosopher's Stone.
If we could just get our
hands on it somehow,
I might be able to get
your body back.
Damn books!
They tell us everything
but how to find it!
Al...
[Al] Yeah?
I think I have a good
feeling about this one.
[Al] Mm. Me too.
[Trisha] Ed? Al? Where are you?
Oh, you boys...
[Trisha] Are you in here messing
up your dad's study again?
And Ed, you know better than
to scribble on the floor.
Yeah...
but, it's not scribbling.
[Ed] Here, watch!
[electric shocks]
Oh, my...
that's alchemy, isn't it...
[Trisha] Did your dad
teach you that?
How can he teach
us anything if he's not here?
Right, we read about
it in these books.
I can't believe
you've done this.
I'm sorry, did
we mess up?
[Trisha] No, no!
It's great! You definitely
take after your father...
My little geniuses.
You make me so proud!
[Ed] And that was it--
Mom had given us all
the encouragement we needed.
From that moment,
we were obsessed with
learning alchemy.
[Ed] But then, in the summer of
that same year, an epidemic
swept the country. The sickness
came, and it took her.
Hey, brother...
I'm hungry, aren't you?
And it's cold here...
Let's go home, please?
Once dad comes back,
everything'll be--
[Ed] Don't even
talk about him!
That bastard doesn't care
about us. He's not our dad.
He didn't even come
for Mom's funeral.
[sad sigh]
You know there might be a way
we can bring mom back...
But I thought it said in
all the books that using
alchemy to make
people is something
you're not supposed
to do, ever.
That's right.. That's why
it'll be our secret.
[Winry] I thought
I'd find you here.
[Ed] What do want, Winry?
[Winry] You know what
my Grandma says...?
She says you shouldn't
cry for loved ones
who've passed away,
because when you do,
it makes them feel sad in
the next world, too.
[Ed] We're not crying!
[gasp]
And, who are you
to talk, anyway?
Every time your parents
go away somewhere,
you cry like a little baby!
I-I do not! I don't!
[Ed] Are you sure, baby?
[Winry] I'm so stupid for
worrying about you...
I'm going home to tell grandma
not to make you any dinner!
[Ed] Hey, what'cha gonna do
that for? Hold up!
[Al] Y-Yeah! Wait for us!
[All] Thanks for dinner!
[gulping]
[Granny] Come on, Ed.
Drink your milk, too.
[Ed] No. I hate milk.
If you don't drink it
you'll stay short forever.
[Ed] Y'mean like you,
you sawed-off old hag?!
What was that, you little
half-pint midget!
Shrunk down mini-witch!
Micro pee-wee!
Baby ant baby!
Sub-atomic shrimp!
[school bells]
ding ding... dong
[Winry] You were reading those
weird books in the middle
of class again. You need to pay
attention to the lessons.
[Ed] Leave us
alone, will ya'?
[Winry] So-- what kind'a
books are they anyway?
It's a secret.
In other words, it's none'a
your damn business, Winry.
C'mon. No fair, you guys're
always keeping secrets.
[Al laughs]
[Al] Bye Winry!
[gasp] Hey! I forgot!
Grandma wanted me to tell you
she's making stew tonight!
Yay! Stew!
Right! We'll be there!
[Ed] Y'know, whoever invented
stew must've been a genius.
It's even got milk in it,
and it still tastes good!
So that makes it genius?
Someone came up with the idea to
pour milk into vegetable soup
for the first time, right?
That's a leap of imagination--
the kind a scientist needs
to be able to make, too.
I dunno, I guess that's true...
Sure it is! Just one leap,
that's all it takes!
And it's what we need to figure
out human transmutation.
[Ed] And so, we began searching
for the key that would unlock
the secrets of human
transmutation and
bring Mom back to life...
We trained with an alchemy
teacher, to prepare our
bodies as well as our minds.
It took years of constant
effort, but we wanted to see
Mom's smile again. We wanted to
go back to our lives with her
the way they used to be. That's
what drove us, day and night.
[optimistic, yet ominous
music playing]
...and we're ready.
[cawing]
[Ed] Water, 35 liters;
carbon, 20 kilograms;
ammonia, 4 liters; lime,
1.5 kilograms;
phosphorus, 800 grams;
salt, 250 grams;
saltpeter, 100 grams;
sulfur, 80 grams;
fluorine, 7.5 grams; iron, 5
grams; silicon, 3 grams...
[water pouring]
Right. Now the
contstructional formula...
[chalk scraping]
And finally... we need
some soul data.
OK, this is it, Al.
[magical eagle screech]
[electrical shock bolts]
Ed, something doesn't
feel right...
[screams]
Al!
NO!
[ugh]
It can't be... A rebound?!
[Al] Brother!!
Ed...! Help...! Ed!
[gasp]
Brother...!
[Ed] Al...!
Al? Wait... what was
I doing? I just...
[Truth] Hello.
Who are you?
Oh, I am so glad
you asked...
[Truth] I am called by many
names. I am the world.
I am the universe. I am God...
I am Truth... I am all...
I am one...
And I am also... You.
[gasp]
[Truth ]
You have dared
to knock on the door.
Now, the door is open.
[screams]
Quiet, child. This is what
you wanted, isn't it?
[screams]
I will show you... the truth.
[door slams]
slam
[screams]
[gasps]
[Ed] It was like all of the
information in the world
was being poured into
my brain at once.
It's too much...!
It's too much! Make it stop!
[screams]
[Ed] What's happening to me?
Stop it! Make it stop!
Make it stop!
[Ed] My head felt like it was
about to burst, but for an
instant, it all became clear.
The truth. Of everything.
Mom... Mom, please!
[fumbly breath]
[Truth] How was it?
I see...
My theory of human
transmutation wasn't wrong...
It can be done.
It's possible...
It's still just
missing something...
[Ed] All of the answers
I need are right here!
The truth about human
transmutation!
[Ed] Please! You have to
show it to me again!
I can't do that.
[Truth] I've already
shown you all
I can for the toll you've paid.
Toll? What toll?
This... Surely you knew?
[gasp]
[Truth] It's the law of
equivalent exchange
Right...? Young alchemist...?
[screaming]
[Ed] Dammit! This can't be
happening! It can't be!
This wasn't... This wasn't
supposed to... NO!
He's gone! What have I done?!
Somebody help me... Somebody...
Please, Mom... Mom, please...
[gasps]
[exhausted breathing]
[syrupy breath]
No... this... this is
wrong... this isn't...
this isn't what we wanted!
Al... Alphonse...
Alphonse! Alphonse!
This is all my fault...!
Al-phonse-No!
No, dammit! You won't
take him, too!
Give him back...
He's my brother!
Take my leg! Take my arm!
Take my heart! Anything!
You can have it!
Just give him back!
He's my little brother!
He's all I have left!
[electric eagle screech]
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Hughes] Roy!
Hey, you're still in Central?
For now, anyway.
They're shipping me back to
Eastern Command this afternoon.
Well now, aren't you the lucky
one. Next time you come here,
I expect you to have made
Brigadier General.
You got that?
[Roy] Easy for you to say.
[Hughes laughs]
Oh... by the way...
if you're leaving,
I'll go ahead and
give this to you.
What is it?
Something you might
find interesting.
The final report on
Isaac McDougal.
[Hughes] I'm guessing it hasn't
reached your office yet.
No.
[surprised choke]
"Xingese Alkahestry",
what's that?
[Hughes] Apparently, that's
something they have...
To be honest, no idea.
You don't know it?
No, it's the first
I've heard of it.
So, how are the
Elrics doing?
You keepin' those
boys out of trouble?
I'm their commanding officer,
not their father.
Hmm.
Hey... tell me somethin', Roy.
Why did you decide to make Ed
a State Alchemist anyway?
He's just a kid...
I mean, military life isn't easy
you know. That boy's gonna
have to go through hell someday.
You and I have certainly
seen our share.
[Roy, thinking] Hell, huh?
Oh, they've seen hell...
Both of them...
and plenty of it.
[epic strings]
[Hawkeye] Lieutenant Colonel...
They're not in back, either.
What is this...?
Where are they?
Where are the Elric brothers?
I want them found!
[Granny] Oh, hush, Den. Don't
bark at our guests... Yes...?
[Granny] Hey,
what is this?!
You have no reason to
come barging in here!
We went to your house! We saw
the floor! What was that?!
[Roy] What did you do?!
[shaky breath]
[Al] We're sorry...
We didn't mean it...
We're sorry... We're sorry...
Wait-- are you...?
[Roy] This is a surprise,
to say the least...
[Roy] I'd heard reports
that there was a brilliant
alchemist living in this town,
so I came to check them out...
The last thing I expected
to find was a boy skilled
enough to attempt human transmutation...
Or advanced enough to bond
a soul to a suit of armor.
[Roy] I'd say he's more
than qualified to
become a State Alchemist.
Should he choose to accept the
position... he will be required
to serve the military in times
of national emergency.
In return, he'll receive
privileges and access
to otherwise restricted
research materials...
Given time, they may be
able to find a way
to get their bodies back...
or even more...
Right after he came stumbling to
my door, half-dead and covered
in blood... I went over to
their house to see for myself
what had happened...
What was there...
Whatever that thing was,
it wasn't human!
[Granny] Alchemy that
created that abomination.
It nearly killed them!
And you want to throw those
boys headlong into it?!
Would you really have
them go through
that kind of hell again?
[Winry] Some tea?
Yes... Thanks.
Say, um... Lieutenant?
Just "Riza", please... It's Riza
Hawkeye. Nice to meet you.
[Winry] Lieutenant Riza... have
you ever had to shoot anyone?
Yes, I have.
I hate what you soldiers do...
Soldiers like you are the
reason my mom and dad
left during the war,
and soldiers are
the reason they're dead.
And now you-- now you're here to
take Ed and Al away, too...
[Hawkeye] If they go,
that decision will be theirs,
and theirs alone.
Yes... It's entirely
up to them now.
[Roy] I'm not forcing you.
I'm merely offering
you the possibility.
Whether to move forward
or stay still...
Will you sit in that chair
wallowing in self-pity?
Or will you stand up
and seize the chance
the military can give you?
[Hawkeye] ...it's their choice.
They choose their own path.
[Roy] If you believe the
possibility exists for
getting your bodies back,
you should seek it out.
Keep moving, whatever
it takes...
Even if the way ahead...
lies through a river of mud.
[Winry] Miss Riza...
Why did you become a soldier?
[sigh]
[Hawkeye] Because there's
someone I have to protect.
[gasp]
[door creaking open]
[footsteps]
We're leaving.
[Hawkeye] Yes, sir.
[Hawkeye] Well, I guess
this is goodbye, young lady.
It's Winry.
Right... Bye, Winry.
[hands clasping]
[Hawkeye] I hope we
meet again someday.
[Hawkeye] Will they be coming?
[Roy] They'll come.
[Hawkeye] That boy. I've never
seen anyone look so defeated...
That's what you saw?
[Roy] No... There was
fire in those eyes.
[train whistle]
chugga chugga chooooo
[Granny] You're sure you
won't regret this?
[Ed] Hmm... My mind's made up.
How long will the surgery
and rehabilitation take?
I'd say about three years,
more or less...
I'll do it in one.
[gasps]
You'll have yourself spitting
blood, you know that?
Al... just hang in there a
little longer, okay?
Then we're gonna get you your
body back, I promise.
Right. And while we're at it,
we'll get yours back, too.
[inspiring chamber music]
[fight sounds]
[Al] Seems like
you're in perfect shape.
Yeah... Now I need to
try some alchemy...
I guess it's been a while since
the last time I used it...
I know...
Not since the night we tried
to bring mom back, right?
[slow inhale]
[hands clapping]
[electrical magic shimmer]
Brother...!
Yeah... I'd say that's
right on the money...
[Al] No, it's amazing!
You didn't even use a
transmutation circle!
You perform alchemy
the same way that
Teacher does!
You can do it
too, can't you?
[Al] Me? No.
No way!
So you didn't see
it, did you.
[Al] See what?
Uhh... nevermind.
[wham]
Hey! You...! Don't mess
up my automail!
You know how hard
I worked on that?!
[Ed] Hell, if it's half
as hard as you
throw a wrench I'd
be surprised.
[groan]
For real... you could try
acting more like a girl
and less like a gearhead...
You think I'm a
gearhead, that's fine!
But you had better
get used to it!
'Cause, as long as you're
wearing my automail,
you're stuck with this gearhead
whether you like it or not!
Huh...?
[Subordinate]
It's unusual for you
to observe the
examinations, sir.
[Bradley] That's true. But
I hear we have a 12-year-old
boy taking the test... I thought
I would come out and see
what all the
excitement was about.
Ah... Would that be a
steel prosthetic?
Happened during the
Eastern Conflict.
[Bradley] I see. So you had a
rough time of it in Ishval, hm?
Who's he?
You idiot. That's
His Excellency,
Fuhrer King Bradley.
Hmm...
[Bradley] Thank you. You may
proceed with the examination.
Do you need something to draw
transmutation circles with?
[Ed] No, that's ok.
I've got it.
[hands clapping]
[chugging adventure strings]
He's not even using a
transmutation circle.
[electric shocks]
[surprised gasps]
My, that's quite
something, isn't it?
[running footsteps]
[Officer] The Fuhrer!
You know, there are some people
who would see this as a good
way to assassinate a VIP...
In the future, you might
want to rethink the way you
conduct these examinations.
That's good... You clearly have
nerves of steel young man.
But, I'd say you still have much
to learn about the world.
Huh?
[metal breaking]
[gasp]
[screaming]
[Bradley] You put on quite
a show, my naiÃ ̄ve young
alchemist. Good luck with
the rest of your exam.
When did he draw his sword?
[wind blowing]
[Al] I wonder if Ed's doing
alright on his exam...
[Winry] Say, Al...?
[Al] Yeah? What is it?
[Winry] If Ed does become
a State Alchemist...
does that mean you'll
be going away?
[Al] Yeah...
[Roy] This silver pocket
watch will serve
as proof of your state certification.
[Roy] This envelope contains
your certificate of appointment.
Heh... And it would
seem our Fuhrer is
not without a certain
sense of irony.
Why's that?
[Roy] Nothing. Congratulations.
You've just officially
become a Dog of the Military.
[Ed] By order of Fuhrer King
Bradley, this document
[Ed & Bradley] ...certifies
that Edward Elric has been
appointed to the post
of State Alchemist,
[Bradley] ...and that he is
hereby granted the title of
"Fullmetal".
Fullmetal?
That's right... Along
with their commission,
State Alchemists also
receive a code name...
Officially, you will
now be known as...
[Roy] ..."The Fullmetal
Alchemist"
I like that... It's nice
and intimidating...
I think that'll suit
me just fine.
[thundering train sounds]
chugga chugga
[Al] Hey... Wake up.
We're almost there.
[waking sighs]
[Ed] So that's Liore...
[ thinking ] Could it really be
there? The key to finally
getting Al his body back...
The Philosopher's Stone!
[Narrator] Having arrived in
Liore, Ed and Al encounter
Father Cornello, a priest
who claims he can perform
miracles. Blinded by false
promises of eternal life
and resurrection for the dead,
Cornello's followers fail
to see the blood-red stone
that gleams on his finger,
or realize what it means.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 3. City of Heresy.
What happiness
can possibly be gained
by looking away from the truth?