This is the first time I've worn such light and smooth clothing.
Shit!
Cal.
This concludes the report on Claudia McCunnen's conspiracy.
She plotted my downfall and lured me into a trap using Zwei, the current Phantom...
...and obtained Wisemel's position.
I can hardly express my admiration.
Lizzy Garland has informed us that Claudia McCunnen's whereabouts are unknown.
It should be impossible for her to restore her position.
It might be a far-fetched story, Scythe Master,
but the basic facts seem to match up.
At your suggestion,
the Godou clan who assisted Claudia...
...should still be cooperated with, correct?
It's true that the cocaine heist one year ago was very painful for Inferno,
however, the profit made on markets by the Godou clan is worth far more.
If you look at it sentimentally,
and seeing how he purged his relatives after knowing the truth,
I recommend that you accept Mr. Shiga's decision.
Well, that is definitely an interesting suggestion, but...
Of course, the Godou clan's profit margin...
...will be cut back as penalty.
Is that acceptable?
Excellent.
Mr. Shiga, for tempting your companions...
...I promise a cruel punishment for Claudia McCunnen.
My deepest gratitude, Mr. McGwire.
We are still trying to locate Claudia.
The real problem is Phantom.
What will he do?
If it doesn't pose a problem, Mr. McGwire, could Ein be given that assignment?
The old and new Phantom confront.
Fascinating.
Are you fine working under the Bloodies?
You gotta be kidding me.
Romero was killed by Isaac!
The Bloodies are being backed by a new and bigger organization.
Yeah, so?
Someday Inferno's age will come without fail.
Are you that desperate to climb the ranks?
You've even given up on taking revenge for your brother's death.
I will go to the place Romero failed to reach.
I believe that is a worthy requiem.
I don't want to surrender here.
Come with me, Lizzy Garland!
I need you by my side.
I may be mafia, but I won't become a fiend.
There is a moral code...
...that needs to be prioritized over loss and gain.
If you promise to adhere to that...
...then fine, Clau.
I'll follow you.
I vow.
Moron.
Acting ahead of me...
You stupid idiot.
No good, we can't find her.
Damn!
Report to Lizzie this is a dead end.
Hey, I found the car key.
It sure is a gorgeous car.
I want to ride the owner as well.
Sure enough.
Reiji, thank goodness.
I'm glad you're safe.
I think you pretty much understand what's going on.
Claudia, you...
I won't be making excuses to you.
All I did was try to survive in the organization.
I rewarded you with all I had, didn't I?
I don't plan on giving up just yet.
I can still turn the table, Reiji,
if I have your help.
I want to leave L.A. and meet up with the organization's East Coast branch,
but to be safe from Inferno's agents, Reiji,
your shield is necessary.
I'll wait for you at the 39th Drive Inn.
This time my life is in your hands.
Cal.
I could erase that scar any time.
But I haven't forgiven you.
Do you know why?
Yes, Master.
What's the meaning of that scar?
Disgrace and decay.
Correct.
Ein, although once my finest creation,
you were marred by him twice.
Now, far from perfect, you are nothing more than trash.
Nonetheless, I have the trash heap called Ein with me.
That's because I believe the time for resurrection will come someday.
Kill Zwei.
Exact vengeance with your own hands.
If you do that and regain the light within you,
I will erase those scars.
I will love you as my creation once again.
My gratitude, Master.
Can Ein beat Azuma Reiji?
If necessary, she will defeat Zwei at the cost of her life.
She won't hesitate to throw her life away.
Oh, so she is disposable?
After losing my creation called Ein,
my art will be even closer to perfection.
As my first creation she warrants commemoration,
but I don't highly value memorials.
Still, there must be a better way than assigning mass numbers.
Sometimes a sketch can be better than what was expected.
We can't know beforehand.
The muse's twisted prank...
...astonishes both artist and audience.
Will the final act be a tragedy?
A comedy?
To entrust the falling curtain to fate...
...should excite and thrill us.
Won't it be a problem for you to dispose of her, Lizzy Garland?
Don't underestimate me, who do you think I am?
You and Claudia are old friends.
You might not be able to pull the trigger.
Shut up, you damn prick.
Someone who looses track of time will be disliked,
Reiji.
This is where everything began.
Zwei!
I am...
My name is not Zwei.
I...
What have I done until today?
I've always wanted to drive like this.
With unequaled speed, leaving everything behind.
One day you will even fly throughout the sky.
That true freedom would be wonderful.
After coming this far, what do you plan to do?
I have no goal.
I just go as far as I can.
You sure are an idiot.
Someday you will tire and stop.
When that happens and you lose your footing, what will you do?
There are things you shouldn't have left behind, aren't there?
You're right.
It's ok, though. Some scenery can only be seen if we move at this speed.
I wanted to chase that down.
Until the end...
You idiot.
I'm sorry.
Won't you do anything before death?
With you as my opponent,
I can't escape.
That's trouble.
I was ordered to fight and win a proper battle.
Ascertain who is the strongest Phantom.
I see.
If so, I will keep you company until the end.
Strong.
Even now, you are still given reasons to fight this viciously...
...by that Scythe.
Elen!
Why?
I can't win this,
because I don't want to win.
I don't want this.
Killing you and escaping from here...
But what would I do next?
What would change?
Being deceived and manipulated,
unable to protect what's precious...
There's no way out.
I hate this repetition.
That's why, please...
Let it end by your hands this time.
I see.
I won't condemn you, it's only natural.
I couldn't bear it either.
But you still fight to survive.
Even now, you still fight for Scythe.
No.
My life's meaning is... this scar.
You told me to stay alive.
I vowed to fight of my own will.
This is a mark which you carved.
I yearned for you.
Even though it was a short while,
the strength you showed that day...
...and the oath you carved into my body...
...are the reasons I couldn't throw my life away.
That's...
You are my other half.
As my substitute,
walking the path I abandoned,
you fought and resisted while you moved ahead.
That's why I was able to live by seeing a dream of you,
believing my other half to be living freely out there.
This scar has always reminded me of that.
But I can't endure this pain forever.
If you want to give up, nobody will blame you.
So...
If you want to rip the seam of the oath we made that day...
...kill me first.
Let everything end.
I can't do that...
It's okay.
I am a failure for Master.
I'm a doll waiting to be thrown away.
Elen.
If this world isn't endless hell,
it's only because you're alive.
That's why, please...
Kill me.
I don't want to be left in a world where you're gone.
I couldn't keep any of the promises I made so far.
I thought I had lost everything.
Reiji.
But... If our promise has subsisted to this point...
...I want to keep it no matter what.
Because that is...
...all I have left.
I will take you away from Scythe.
The fall of the curtain seems to have been disappointing.
Well, I wonder about that.
Maybe this is just another intermission.
Brother.
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll cherish it.
I'll cherish it forever.
Cal.
I won't be coming to where you are for a while.
I still have things I need to do.
Reiji?
Let's go!
You liar!
You said you would never leave.
You said we would be together.