Ryu-chan...
Ryu-chan!
Takasu
Y-Yo...
Wh-Why?
Ryu-chan, you're okay?
Your life was in...
L...Liar.
Yasuko...
You've done a wonderful
job of raising Ryuji-kun.
Yeah...
I did...
I raised him!
I was in a life-threatening accident.
U-Um, Ya-chan!
R-Ryuji was just...
Yasuko was completely fooled
by a fake message Taiga left.
There was a lot of sobbing, and she
got an earful from Grandpa.
But it's like...
It's like Ya-chan's a little girl.
Families sure are amazing.
It's been well over ten years since they
last saw each other, but they're still...
Thanks, Mom!
This is your fault for always spoiling her!
Aw, please. Why shouldn't I?
Because you...
They're still family.
Family...
Ryuji-kun.
Take a bath before the water gets cold.
Oh, sure!
You were never married?
They told you?
Yeah.
Your daddy ran off with another woman
when I was pregnant with you.
Everyone told me I shouldn't keep you.
But you see...
I wanted to protect you,
no matter what it took.
But...I failed in the end.
Everything's fallen apart...
That's not true.
Didn't you hear Grandma?
You did a good job of raising me.
Look, I'm bigger than you now.
You should be proud.
You've really grown up.
You looked so big as I
watched you running away...
I hardly recognized you...
It scared me...
And it made me kind of
happy at the same time...
But I was scared of you leaving me...
So you left me first?
Silly.
Not that I'm in any position to talk, but
running away won't accomplish anything.
Ryu-chan...
I'm going to be more mature.
And I won't do it somewhere far away.
I'm going to grow up right in front of you.
So watch me.
The entire time.
Could you stop crying?
But...
Wha—
What is this?
Grandma said we might as well sleep in the
same room, since we're getting married.
She really must be to blame
for how Yasuko turned out...
Ya-chan's laughing.
Yeah.
Hey, turn off the lights.
Huh? Why?
Just do it.
What is it?
Wow...
There are so many stars...
Uh-huh.
To be honest, I was worried.
I knew running off and getting
married would never work.
But I wanted to dream a little.
Because everything would fall apart
again if I didn't do something.
Man...
You and Yasuko...
Nothing's fallen apart.
And we can start from here.
No need to elope if we have
permission to get married.
Wouldn't it be best to have
everyone's support?
Like who?
Grandpa and Grandma.
And your parents.
That could take a while...
Fine by me.
If we're going to be happy,
we should share that happiness
with the people around us.
Uh-huh.
But let's give it a test run.
There.
A veil.
Taiga...
Uh...
I, Takasu Ryuji...
Well...
What do I say?
Doesn't matter. Whatever comes to mind.
I-I can't just make something up!
Uh...
Take you, Aisaka Taiga—
Forget the vows.
What!?
You're the one who wanted to...
Remember what you told me
back when we first met?
What?
We are tiger and dragon.
Said to stand together as
equals since ancient times.
We don't need vows.
Because we'll always be together, right?
Right.
Tai—
Your eyes are bloodshot.
You're breathing hard.
Sh-Shut up!
Your lips are chapped.
It'll hurt if we kiss.
So I fail...
If we kiss, it'll probably hurt...a lot.
How was that?
Exactly what I expected...
Rough and dry as barren earth...
But also...burning hot.
Hey...
It's pretty cold. Let's try again...
Again...
Takasu
This feels kinda weird...
It was just the two of us on the way here,
but there's three of us, plus one, going home.
You were convinced, weren't you?
That Ya-chan would come
swooping in if we lied.
That she'd make up with your grandparents.
I wouldn't say I was convinced.
But at the same time, I didn't
think it was impossible.
Wonder why.
Maybe that's just how it is.
Because that's what it means to be a family.
Ooh, I'm starving!
Taiga-chan, you'll come over for dinner, yes?
I-I'm...
C'mon, don't be shy!
You're a member of our family!
Right?
Uh-huh.
- Aw, I didn't forget you!
- Taiga...?
- Inko-chan, you're a family member too!
- Go ahead. I need to get changed.
But isn't your mom in your...?
I'm coming with you.
Fine.
Make it quick.
I'm making your favorite,
pork cutlets, tonight.
Okay.
Huh...?
Mom?
Missed Calls: 47    Voicemail: 5    Inbox: 28
Taiga!
What are you think—
Do you understand the conse—
Stop thi—
Taiga...
Taiga, do you truly hate me this mu—
Forget it!
I don't give a damn what
you do or where you go!
I'm leaving!
Have it your way!
Bye-bye, kid!
Man, she's so childish...
Ryuji, you know...
I always believed that no one
would ever love me.
Smells good!
There's more to come.
Grandma gave me a great
recipe for stewed taro.
Yay!
Thank you, Ryu-chan.
But I was probably just running away.
Can't see any stars...
It's tiny.
Useless and helpless, just like me...
I blamed my parents and circumstances
for my lack of confidence.
But Ryuji, you loved me for who I am.
That's why...
I won't run away anymore.
I'll change.
I'll accept who I am...
and learn to be proud of myself...
so that I can give you my love.
Taiga didn't show up for dinner that night.
Takasu, we won't know what's
going on if you refuse to talk.
What actually happened?
Why isn't Taiga—?
All right, class! Take your seats!
Unfortunately, I have some bad news.
Due to family reasons, Aisaka-san
will be leaving our school.
I was just formally contacted by her mother.
Aisaka-san will be going to live with her—
Wait!
It's a lie! A ruse! A sham!
But she didn't tell us...
As you go through life, you will all find
yourselves at various crossroads.
You may wish to stop where you are,
or turn back, but you'll
have to make a decision.
Aisaka-san's decision...means
that she had to leave you all.
But I'm sure she tried to find
the best possible solution.
We should support her.
Right?
H-Huh!?
Kids today terrify me!
You're calling Aisaka-san already!?
Texting her!?
I don't believe this!
- But...reflect on life! Savor each moment!
- Takasu?
Back to your seats!
Takasu-kun!
- Kushie—
- Better brace yourself.
Why did you come back alone!?
Why is Taiga transferring!?
Explain!
Tell me, Taka—!
Kushieda, stop!
Kitamura-kun?
I didn't...
I didn't want to let her go...
If I could bring her back, I would.
I don't know why she would
decide this without me.
But...
She trusts me.
So for now...all I can do is accept it.
Takasu...
Jeez...
She finally learned to
clean up after herself...
What...is this?
Whoa! A lone sock!
Unacceptable!
Where's your partner!?
I'm going to find it!
Er...
That klutz...
She was supposed to take these with her...
Student Handbook
You really are a klutz...
New Message
From: Taiga
Hey, you never said you love me.
Huh? I didn't?
Pretty sure that after I fell in the river...
Oh yeah! Crap!
We were interrupted...
Man... I even said it to
Kawashima a bunch of times...
Klutz.
Yeah...
I'm one to talk...
Downloading
Tomiie-kun, are you busy today?
N-Nope.
I want to stop somewhere on the way home.
Wanna come?
Hey, isn't this...?
Ami-chan!
Taiga...
Sorry about yesterday.
Except I'm not.
Then don't say you are.
I think I get what you were saying, though.
Hey, hey!
A message from Taiga!
I got one!
Me too.
You mean this?
That's it!
Looks like Taiga replied to
everyone who texted her.
But why did she only send a picture?
I don't get it...
Yeah, what does this mean?
Hmm, seaweed?
It's the night sky.
Kushieda?
Oh, you're right.
So this tiny light is a star?
Really?
You sure about that?
Yup, I'm sure it's a star.
But why send a picture of the night sky?
To let us know that she's always
watching over us from above.
Don't say that! She's not dead!
I think she's trying to say...
that she won't give up.
Even when the sky's so dark
you can't see a thing,
there are still stars shining out there.
So if she can learn to shine brighter,
then we'll be able to see her.
I'd say Taiga's being pretty selfish.
But having said that, we all
live under the same sky.
If each of us learns to shine, it won't
matter how far apart we are.
We'll be able to see each other.
That's so cheesy, I'm gonna hurl...
Sent a chill down my spine...
Wh-What's that!?
I like the sound of that.
Uh-huh.
Is this what it means to be young?
I agree!
I hope she's right!
Indeed.
Speaking of stars,
remember how a certain someone
made a huge mess a while back?
Oh, yeah...
That's right...
It'd probably make her happy
if we sent her a reply.
Y-Yeah!
Be careful.
Can't find it...
Where did we put it?
I remember putting it away
with Ami-chan's tree...
Whoa!
Thanks.
When it comes to making others happy...
You're...really good at it, I guess.
More or less.
My very existence is a surprise in itself.
I used to be jealous
of how she was adored
when she was simply being herself.
But...
I guess that wasn't the case.
That little girl with a big attitude had a
heart as tiny and timid as her body.
She worried so much about
what other people thought...
that she never let anyone see the real her.
Reminds me of someone else I know.
Yep, a certain someone who saw through
her facade from the very beginning.
You said that I was just a child, right?
You see, I hated having to act like an adult.
And it annoyed me when everyone
assumed that I was mature.
But after seeing Taiga...
I realized that it didn't matter, as long as
one person out there understood me.
Even if they didn't love me...
- Kawashima...
- Hey!
I found the treasure!
U-Um...
I just press this button, right?
Teach!
Hurry it up!
Before I lose my power as a Patron Saint!
Aisaka—Do your best!
TIGER!!
Come on, Takasu-kun.
Smile!
Smile.
I am smiling!
Amin.
Okay.
Here goes!
I am a dragon.
You are a tiger.
And tigers and dragons have been
considered equals since ancient times.
So it doesn't matter...that you
aren't here with me now.
I'll transcend space and time...
to always be by your side.
My feelings...
will never change.
It's similar but different.
nitetemo chigauyo
mandarin orenji
Mandarines and oranges.
Friends and lovers.
tomodachi koibito
The hearts of the two.
futari no kokoromo
I didn't want to be hurt, so I ran away.
kizutsuki takunai watashi wa nigeteta
And now the light
soshitara hikarimo
Hey, Inko-chan.
Is this lip gloss a bit too flashy?
I am a mom...
I should use a more natural color...
But I don't have anything like that!
Inko-chan!
I-Inko-chan said her name!?
Graduation Ceremony Notice
Ohashi High School 78th
Graduation Ceremony
Man, I'm going to miss those
guys after graduation...
They were a fun bunch.
47th Diploma Presentation
Did you hear about Kitamura-senpai,
the student council president?
He's going to study abroad
in America next year.
Wow...
The president and his class helped make the
culture and athletic festivals so much fun!
Got that right!
But I heard that last year's
Culture Festival was the best ever!
Ooh, I heard that too.
The legendary festival where
2-C swept the contests?
Yeah, that!
It was all thanks to someone
called Palm-top-something.
Palm-top-something?
You mean the Palm-top Tiger?
The one that brings happiness?
Wait, that's a real person!?
Yep, the Palm-top Tiger!
She was a student here until last year!
And she's Takasu-senpai's girlfriend!
What!?
There exists in this world something
no one has ever seen.
It's gentle, and so very sweet...
...That a glimpse is all it takes
to make a person crave it.
That's why it's never been seen.
That's why this world has kept it hidden.
Making it difficult to obtain.
But one day, it will be found.
By the one person who is meant to find it.
What?
I wanted to surprise you.
Have you grown?
Not a single millimeter.
So sue me.
Guess what?
I love you.
Tai—
H-How can you say something so
embarrassing in broad daylight!?
You're supposed to wait for the
right m-mood or s-situation...
Because that's how it works.