Alright, all done.
Looks a bit cleaner now.
What's the occasion? Are you expecting someone?
I'm not expecting anyone, but someone might come!
Someone like Mr. Moriaki...
Oh yeah?
But it's hopeless. Still haven't given up?
Well, I was watching the horoscopes on TV this morning,
and on the weekly love forecast,
it said that my true love will soon come by!
On channel 6.
Channel 6?
I was channel surfing and looking at various horoscopes.
And the last one I saw was my true fortune!
Just the other day,
I saw my first fortune, but it was kinda lame...
so I checked out another channel,
and it kept scrolling down till it got to the very last one, the 13th zodiac sign.
The 13th zodiac sign is still around?
This "Ophiuchus" sign is kinda sketchy, you know?
As a Sagittarius, I'd be a romantic and a reliable hard worker.
But as an Ophiuchi, I'd have the energy to do things,
but then I'd also say a lot of rude things.
She's an Ophiuchi!
Jeez, you always look so happy every day.
Is that what I look like?
Maybe this whole deal about meeting the one I'm destined to be with is about Mr. Moriaki?
Couldn't your destined person be anybody?
Like a sworn enemy, or a rival, or a natural born enemy...
Why would a love fortune talk about my natural born enemy?!
Oh, you're gonna be close to Mr. Moriaki!
Extra lessons?!
Isn't it great?
The fortune was right.
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
七色の黄昏おりてきて
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
The wind is kinda refreshing
風はなんだか涼しげ
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
Saturday night is lively
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
Everyone can't wait
みんなウキウキ
Minna ukiuki
Can't wait.
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Can't wait!
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
Equations.
Just by giving variables specific values, the value of each side can be determined.
These specific values are the keys to the equation.
Right now, before my eyes...
lies my second natural born enemy.
Now that I think about it, my first natural born enemy was in 2nd grade,
the homeroom teacher.
When people read a book,
each person has a different impression of it.
Literature is interesting because there are as many opinions as there are people.
On the other hand,
every math problem has only one right answer.
That's what makes math interesting.
I get it! So I guess I like math.
Huh?
We were just in the middle of dividing,
but now we can't divide any further.
What are we going to do now?
She's right! What's gonna happen now?
We can't do anything about the remainder,
so we write the remaining 5 over here.
Teacher!
What is it, Moriaki?
Umm, I mean... stopping in the middle like that...
is that really ok?
Well... it's annoying, isn't it?
However, there's nothing we can do.
What would you do, Moriaki?
I don't know.
But teacher,
you said that we shouldn't leave leftovers at lunch,
so why should we leave leftovers while dividing?
Yeah.
Moriaki's right.
Yes. It was hard to say, but everyone agrees with me!
You're right that stopping before we've finished is bad,
but when you get a persimmon for lunch, don't you leave the seeds?
The remainder from dividing is just like those seeds.
Sit down already!
You're so stupid. Do you eat persimmon seeds?
Who's the idiot here?
This incident left a huge impression on the rest of my life.
As a result...
I became a math teacher.
That homeroom teacher was my very first natural born enemy.
And now,
before me,
sits my second natural born enemy.
Umm, I'm not sure,
but am I the only one getting extra lessons?
The only one who got zeros on both the main exam,
and the retake was you, Arashiyama Hotori.
Oh yeah? Oh yeah.
Well, whatever!
Since it's just the two of us, I'll just think of it as a date!
My stomach is starting to hurt even sooner than I expected.
Arashiyama Hotori,
as a teacher, I think it's important to have morals.
I like to have some level of
consideration toward my students,
so instead of saying what I'd like to say to you now...
I will be very grateful if you could guess what I want to say.
For some reason, I just made a pretty good guess.
Very well. Please listen then.
This is about when I was grading these tests.
And next up is...
Arashiyama?!
It happens every time.
When it's Arashiyama's turn, I get a sinking feeling in my stomach.
She blatantly gives up while answering the question,
and just writes some answer without the work.
Naturally, the answer is wrong.
Every time I see it, I get sharp pains in my stomach.
But then when I saw all the mistakes that the answers were derived from, my head started pounding.
And then...
If you don't get it just leave the space blank!
Finally, on the answer sheet, just when I thought I found something marked correct...
it turned out to be the zero.
Arashiyama's answer sheet was, without a doubt, an attempt on my life.
This was clearly a plan to commit murder!
No!
You love dramatic things like this, don't you?
What's most unforgivable, is that your grades in other subjects haven't changed.
Given that, you must have an ulterior motive.
That's because math has nothing to do with detectives, right?
Detectives?
I'm just an ordinary high school girl right now,
but one day,
I'll be a high school detective girl!
One day? How long do you intend on being a high schooler?
More importantly,
at this rate you're going to be held back,
so your dream might just come true.
There's no reason why we couldn't have a 20+ year old high school detective girl.
Let's have some lessons to avoid that.
Now, solve the problem.
Good.
Teacher!
What? That was quick.
What's this?
Do you know how this iron ball got into the house?
This has all the necessary information, right?
Absolutely!
The diameter of the ball is fixed at all angles.
Next to it, the sides of the rectangle are also all fixed in length.
Given this, the ball shouldn't be able to pass through the narrow door.
This is impossible.
You see, the answer is...
the ball wasn't put through the door,
but rather the house was built around the iron ball!
It's important to think outside of the box like this in real life.
It lets you find the answer faster than math...
Corn is delicious, poko~
What's going on, Hotori? You're reading your textbook.
How rare. It'd be more believable if you got struck by lightning.
I've already been struck by lightning.
At this rate, I'm gonna be a high school girl for the rest of my life.
I'm jealous.
Moriaki got pissed at me.
Of course he'd be pissed if you showed him this brain teaser.
He's super square.
If you want to know how square he is,
I heard a story about him from another teacher.
Once, there was a high school girl who loved Mr. Moriaki.
She was said to be pure, innocent maiden.
That girl sounds just like me!
Every bit about pure and innocent!
What?
One day she put everything she felt into a love letter,
and handed it to Mr. Moriaki.
The next day, she received a reply letter.
W-What did it say?
I want to know! Ahh, but I'm scared too.
My maiden heart is shaking nervously. Trembling.
There was just one equation written.
It was an equation that meant love cannot happen...
given the moral values between teacher and student.
The high school girl was so heartbroken,
that the principal came to know about it.
Now that sounds like you.
However, the principal...
We've had nothing but shameless teachers till yesterday...
Mr. Moriaki is a true model of a teacher!
He was so moved that the letter still hangs in the principal's office to this day.
And everyone lived happily ever after.
That wasn't happy at all!
The laws are very strict about this.
If you don't study properly you're really gonna be held back.
She's just like her.
My two natural born enemies have the same personalities.
They deceive me by talking about things unrelated to math.
And for some reason, I think they had the same face.
Could it be? Did a grown up Hotori
timeslip into the past and become my homeroom teacher?
No.
No way.
I don't believe in Sci-Fi or the occult.
I'm a math teacher.
Hmm... Oh,
I got it!
Show me. I'll check your answers.
What the heck?
It disproves the other equation.
I'll use it at the next after-school lesson.
You're really going to stay back a year.
Equations.
The variables in these equalities are the keys to finding the answer.
But sometimes, the right answer is to say there is no answer.
Mr. Moriaki, here's your coffee.
Thank you very much.
One for you too, Mr. Kameda.
Thanks for the coffee.
A long time ago, it was said that if you put milk in your coffee,
you'd see the initials of the person you're thinking of on the surface.
You're more of a romantic than you look, Mr. Kameda.
More than I look?
Hmmm, if I try, I think I can see "N. M."
"N. M." in Natsuhiko Moriaki, that is.
I see.
I can see Pi in mine.
Whoa. He ignored what I said about "N. M."
That's not an initial at all.
Maybe it means I love Pi.
Well, I do like it.
What do you see, Mr. Kameda?
If I don't get God's initials, things are going to be pretty bad.
Curse?!
What? The chair just abruptly fell.
The height adjustment lever is broken.
Oh well.
It sinks if I put my weight into it.
The desk next to me is unused.
Why don't you swap with this chair?
Let me do that.
Been unlucky all morning, huh?
Guess that "curse" initial was...
Don't say that, Ms. Nishi.
It's not even an initial.
Hey honey, something's wrong.
Hotori is putting something on her face!
The weather's getting dry, so I told her to put some lotion on.
Oh? She's getting a bit more feminine.
I don't know about that.
She doesn't put on any lipstick. Not quite feminine yet.
What! What's wrong?!
My eyes... my eyes... my face burns.
And now it's chilly.
What did you put on?
The bottle shapes look similar, so you used the wrong one...
You're a jerk, Dad!
Why do we have hair growth tonic when you're not even bald?
Fool! I'm not bald because I have hair growth tonic!
It stings... I can't go to school today since I can't open my eyes.
Don't say stupid things like that!
...and that's why I'm here so late.
Very well.
But you just have one reason after another for being late.
The truth is stranger than fiction, as they say.
Having to put stinging stuff on their heads...
must be rough for men, you know?
Teacher, is your hair doing alright?
Yes, but no thanks to you.
If I start losing my hair to stress though, it'll be your fault.
Blaming someone else?!
You don't look sorry at all.
Class is starting so take a seat.
We'll continue this conversation later.
Please stay after school.
Hmm... well, I've done something like that.
I've tried brushing my teeth with face wash cream before.
Nehehe! You're such a ditz!
Who are you to say that?!
She snapped.
I was just continuing the conversation. Why would you call me a ditz?
Well, once you put something that nasty in your mouth, you won't make the same mistake again.
So you've made that mistake before.
What the heck?
Being summoned for being late? Are you a middle schooler?
So he was serious about me staying after school.
Because, Moriaki is a strict math teacher, you know.
If you want to know how square he is...
The story about the love letter?
I heard it from Tatsun before.
Love can't happen given the moral values between teacher and student.
I know how that story continues.
There's more?
About five or six years passed, and that high school girl
managed to become a teacher at this school.
However, it seems like they didn't fall in love.
You have to know when to give up, poko~
Wow, the weather's great today.
Let's get home before it gets dark. Go, go.
I was going to act all natural and escape,
but I couldn't fool you...
I remembered because that was completely unnatural.
I have to go to work, so make it quick please.
That's your problem.
As a teacher,
I just thought of something unbecoming of me.
I can get some refreshing revenge on Arashiyama for stressing me out all day.
If I can get her to sit on the broken chair...
it'll startle her a bit.
What am I talking about?
I didn't know I had such a sense of humor.
What's going on, Ms. Nishi?
Sorry, I spilled some coffee.
But it's all cleaned up now.
Oh, I see.
I don't know which chair is the broken one!
Regrettably, I'll have to give up on my plan to scare Arashiyama.
Wait, but that means...
I don't know which chair I should sit on!
Light offense style.
Moderate offense style.
Severe offense style.
No matter what style,
I have to sit on a chair.
If the chair breaks while Arashiyama is looking...
Undoubtedly, my dignity will break too.
Which chair is the broken one?
Pushing down them with my hands won't be enough.
If I had known, I would've marked the chair this morning.
Give up on lecturing her today!
Are you going to run from teaching her?
Okay, I'm going to sit.
Right. Go ahead.
Damn! She doesn't get what I'm feeling.
But I just realized, Pi "π" looks like Death "死"...
How ominous.
Get a hold of yourself! There's no such thing as an omen or destiny.
The only certainty is the 33.3333 percent chance that the chair will sink.
What are you doing?
N-Nothing.
Okay, Arashiyama. I'm going to sit.
So you're going to sit too.
Uh, okay.
No hard feelings.
Huh?
Teacher, you're acting weird.
You're mumbling stuff like 33 percent or something.
Ah, uhh...
I mean, within the span of a month,
you've been late 33 percent of the time.
Yeah.
That's not true! It's been twice per week, at most.
So Arashiyama is bad at both math and arithmetic.
Huh? So there's six days of school per week...
and I'm late on two of them, so...
Jeez, weren't we talking about being late?
Why are we talking about math problems now?
She's putting my class on the same level as basic arithmetic.
No! I managed to escape the sinking chair,
so I can't sink into depression now.
For Arashiyama's sake too, I'll say it clearly.
As a teacher, I'm going to sternly...
After this, preserving the teacher's dignity...
will be 100% impossible.
It's not pasta, it's spaghetti, poko~
Sis, you still look at fortunes?
Quiet!
Watch out for love troubles.
Lame.
Today's Taurus fortune: Your academic luck is low.
Don't fall asleep during the exam!
Also lame.
Today's 13 fortunes!
Today's Aries fortune: Terrible financial luck.
No, no, this is no good.
...and that's why I'm late.
Incomprehensible...
ひ、
1,
Hi,
ふ、
2,
Fu,
ひ、ふ、み、よ
1, 2, 3, 4
Hi, fu, mi, yo
退屈や
Living alone is boring,
Taikutsu ya
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
My pufferfish cheeks
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Pulls the town into chaos.
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
I didn't confess to him today.
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
I play the drums to train
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
My body for ping pong.
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
But this band isn't a fake!
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
The members aren't playing rock!
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
We're not trying to lead the song!
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
We're not looking for Nirvana!
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
We're maids! Yea!
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
メイド姿で参上！参上！
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチョー！
acho-!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
They're maids! Yea!
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチャ～
acha~
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
かんちょぉぉお！
enemaaA!
kanchoooO!
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Hey, don't you think Tatsun is odd?
She's definitely a bit odd.
I don't know how to put it, but... isn't it odd?
Whether she's odd or odd isn't that odd,
but oddly, she has odd things about her.
They're all odd, aren't they?
What's odd about me?!
You can't put it into words?
Not really.
Next time: Street number 5 "Tatsuno Toshiko is really odd"
We're all over sometimes, poko~