I'm starting to see more yellow people recently.
The Yellow Napkins?
Have you heard that The Slasher is actually the act of Dollars?
We're really not the same without you.
How's he doing?
He visits me from time to time.
He was just out there.
Tokyo's air is ugly.
Don't you agree?
Parasite! Parasite! Parasite!
Did you hear?
Some students from Raira Academy were just attacked by The Slasher.
Seriously?
That's scary.
I'm totally, frickin' serious.
Female freshmen, apparently.
Sorry.
I'm gonna idle while I make some calls.
Don't worry.
It wasn't your girlfriend.
Thanks.
But I'm still concerned.
Do you know where it happened?
Well,
it's just a little past Higashi Ikebukuro station, along the Metro Highway.
You won't have any problems finding it, since there are police cruisers and such there.
I see...
Sorry, I'm going AFK for a while.
Setton-san, are you going over there to gawk?
Aw, darn.
Sorry, I'm gonna sign off too.
Did you get a hold of her?
She said she's at the police station now...
I guess she witnessed it.
I'm gonna go.
Oh...
Then, me too.
The Slasher.
At that point, I was completely unaware that this bloody incident
had a strong tie to a girl's destiny, and to my past.
I'm home!
I'm home.
Hello, hello.
I'm home, Celty!
Welcome home, dear.
What's wrong?
I witnessed a horrifying sight.
A horrifying sight?
Don't make me say it!
I want to forget about it.
Man, that felt good.
You should at least take that white thing off when you're in the shower.
No.
Tokyo's air is dirty, so I can't ever take it off.
By the way, Celty-kun, thank you for last night.
Anyway, what's up with those rude guys wearing yellow?
That must be the Yellow Napkins.
They formed around the time you left for America.
I thought they were laying low after that fight with the Blue Squares.
They can all die in the sewer after fighting each other.
Stop asking the impossible.
Anyway, Celty brought you home safely, so pay her.
I'll keep a tab with you.
I absolutely refuse.
Then I'll just ignore it.
I was just testing you, Celty-kun.
If you free me right now...
Ouch! Ouch!
It's poking me!
The tip of the shadow is poking me!
Shinra!
I'm in a real crisis!
I certainly expect my son to know how to act in such a situation!
Of course I do.
Thank you for your business.
I will not be leaving any inheritance to you.
I don't need any.
You've been tricked by that monster.
If Celty's tricked me and stolen my soul, that's what I really want anyway.
Oh?
Oh wow, wow, wow, what, Celty-kun?
Have you fallen in love with Shinra?
I knew my son was weird enough to develop feelings for you,
but now you love Shinra too?
Yes.
Celty!
It's great that you admit your feelings for me!
Our relationship used to be so vague and opaque,
but now we're super close to each other and ready to go public with the news!
This progress makes me want to jump up and down in joy!
You're embarrassing me!
Shut up already!
Now I'm overjoyed that I confessed my love to you.
Did you think I'd allow this relationship?
What?
Are you aware that you are an uninvited member of human society, better known as a "monster"?
Of course.
"Of course"? Wait...
What's wrong with that?
Seems like my plan to get control of the situation by pointing out my opponent's anti-social status failed.
That's not convincing at all, coming from you.
Besides...
Shinra told me that he likes me just the way I am now!
Fine, I'll allow this relationship.
But, from now on, you are...
to address me as "Father."
Shut up!
By the way, Celty-kun,
you can't regain your memories if you don't regain your head.
That is, the memories of your time as a Dullahan with a head in Ireland, your homeland.
That... can't be helped.
Let's make many new memories together to make up for your lost ones.
Shinra...
To start, let's have a wedding.
I want to get your measurements for the wedding dress, so take off that shadow suit.
This reminds me: he's always been a strange kid. Always happy whenever there's a dissection.
It's clearly because of you!
Call me "Father"!
I told you not minutes ago.
How careless of you.
This is why you didn't even notice when I stole your head.
Oh crap!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What did you just say?
What do I do now?
I accidentally let slip a very important secret.
But it'll be okay.
Celty is a klutz, so you'll never catch on.
Klutzy Celty!
Shut up!
And don't repeat it!
I can easily predict the attacks of an angry klutz!
Even you won't get away if you make fun of Celty.
All right! All right!
I'll explain everything.
I guess there's no use hiding it anymore.
Yes, the one who stole your head and gave it to a pharmaceutical company was me!
Don't be shameless about it!
Fine.
Then come with me.
There's something I want to show you.
What? He ran away?!
That fucking bastard!
I won't let him!
Is she gone?
Looks like my trick of only pressing the elevator's button succeeded.
I'll come get my bags later.
See ya.
Damn it, where'd he go?
Celty-san.
Is something wrong?
You're totally spaced out.
I was thinking about things.
Tell me.
What's on your mind?
You look gloomy.
It's about The Slasher.
There's this strange rumor spreading on the Net.
Strange rumor?
Yeah, saying that The Slasher is the work of the Dollars.
No way.
Do you really believe that?
I don't, of course.
But if the rumor takes off, something dangerous might happen.
There's already a lot of tension between the Dollars and the Yellow Napkins.
It's true that the town's balance is fragile right now.
Mikado, I'll check around about The Slasher too.
Celty-san...
So get going.
People like you are easy targets if you space out in a place like this.
That's true.
Thank you.
The Slasher, huh...
Sorry, but I don't have a clue.
I see.
You don't have to go so far for the Dollars.
It's not just for the Dollars.
I have some history with her.
I'd be dead if I had a head.
You dumbass...
I know the one who says, "Dumbass," is the dumbass, but I'm fine being a dumbass, so I'll say it.
You dumbass!
You should've told me that first!
I'll kill her!
Totally kill her!
Surely kill her!
Fucking seriously kill her!
But you know, I'm a headless rider.
I'm totally fine.
Oh, no, no.
That's not the issue here anymore.
Attacking you deserves a million deaths.
Killkillkillkillkill...
What about work?
Aren't you on break right now?
I don't care.
I won't allow you to get fired on my account.
Besides, I need more information before I look for The Slasher.
I'll go get ready, so wait!
Fine.
But do it ASAP.
Killkillkillkillkillkill...
There was a reason I needed to be away from Shizuo.
I'm so glad you came to see me.
By the way, did you find your head yet?
Forget about the head.
Let me get straight to the point.
I want info about The Slasher.
Three big ones will do.
So your clothes and wallet are both made of shadows.
So, if a really bright light shone on you, would you be buck naked?
Are you interested?
Nah.
Unlike the weirdo quack and student, I don't get aroused by the headless or a head.
I'm fine, but if you insult Shinra again, I won't forgive you.
You're so in love.
But if another Dullahan comes and tempts him, he might easily fall for her.
I want to believe that he wouldn't...
But even if that happens...
Would you kill Shinra, then kill yourself?
No.
I just won't let any other headless woman come near him.
Because I love him right now.
You've grown so similar to a human!
But you should be careful.
The closer you come to being human, the bigger the shock you'll get when you regain your head.
I'll worry about that after I get my head back.
Actually, I'm starting to think that I might not need the head.
Putting that topic aside,
tell me about The Slasher.
I paid you, so don't tell me you don't have anything.
Don't you worry.
I have some killer info that I haven't leaked to the police, media, or Internet yet.
I was actually waiting to tell you first.
Why?
Because this case involves supernatural evil spirits.
Have you heard about a sword named "Saika"?
"Saika"?
This might sound unbelievable, but Saika is a cursed sword that actually existed in Shinjuku.
A cursed sword?
Like Muramasa?
Yes, it's a sword with a mysterious power.
What's on your mind?
I heard a story about a cursed sword named Saika.
Apparently, there's a legend that says Saika has a mind of its own, and that it can take control of humans.
And each victim of The Slasher testified that The Slasher had red eyes.
And you think that's because of Saika?
Yes.
Every night there was a slasher incident, someone with the username "Saika" logged onto the Internet.
But when I got attacked by her before, I didn't notice her presence coming toward me.
If Saika isn't human, I would've sensed her presence.
Saika only takes over the mind of a person.
And that person is actually moving around.
So it's possible that there isn't a presence that you can detect.
You know a lot about Saika...
Oh, you know, you asked me to check on it before.
Anyway, come to bed soon.
That made me think that Shinra was hiding something from me...
Hey, welcome back!
Ever since Nebula took over Yagiri Pharmaceutical, I've been researching Miss Namie's whereabouts.
Then I found her frequenting your room.
So I threatened her with this toy gun to get in.
A toy gun?!
Didn't I tell you?
Shouldn't we turn this guy over to the police?
But wouldn't you be the one who gets in trouble?
If they search the way I tell them to, they'll find a young woman's head in the room!
You know, that might become the new headline that replaces The Slasher.
So Shinra's twisted character comes from you.
Praising me won't get you anything.
But seriously, I don't need to have the head right now.
My corporation is quite surprised from seeing Celty-kun's manner on TV.
So they came to the conclusion that they should study the body before the head.
So now I'm the one who's supposed to be searching for the head.
It seems you have a very interesting plan for the head.
You assume that a Valkyrie is a Dullahan, and thus are trying to wake the head up by placing it within a conflict.
That's a very unique idea.
Well, I'm trying different things.
In the worst case scenario, I might have to take it somewhere that has an armed conflict.
I'd appreciate it if we can cooperate.
Very well.
I've had eyes on you for a while too.
There's no one around me who's willing to run an experiment based on a mythical legend.
Including me.
Thanks.
Now...
Let me give you some advice.
If you're trying to provoke Celty-kun's head or soul by causing a pseudo-conflict here in Tokyo,
don't get her involved in someone else's conflict.
Instead, getting everyone else involved...
in a disaster with her in the middle would be the way to go.
That's my intent.
Actually, things are progressing faster than I anticipated.
Anri!
You're able to help with the sports festival preparations already?
Y-Yes.
I was so worried about you.
Why were you with those slashed students?
Were they picking on you again?
I'm worried.
I'm very worried.
The Slasher might come after you again.
It's not safe to walk alone.
Harassing her again?
Tsk, tsk, Sensei.
I was concerned about Anri.
Wow, you call her by her given name.
How risqué!
If you pay too much attention to her, she might transfer schools like Niekawa-senpai.
You were her homeroom teacher last year, right?
Of Niekawa Haruna-san?
What's this?
Do you know Niekawa?
Yeah, but just her name.
Anyway, us students should leave.
Who is Niekawa Haruna-san?
Hey Anri,
Mikado hasn't confessed his love to you yet, has he?
What?
Just as I thought.
But you are aware that he's fallen head-over-heels for you, aren't you?
Ryugamine-kun is a good friend of mine, so...
It seems my best friend is seriously in love with you,
so I'll watch from the sidelines for now.
Besides, I need be on good terms with all the fair ladies of the world.
Masaomi!
Sonohara-san!
Here comes The Timid.
Sorry, did you wait long?
The wait was so long, I thought I was turning into a fossil.
Uh... Square root of three points.
"Square root"?
Why square root?
Give me an easier score to understand, like -20 points!
Bye!
See you tomorrow.
See you.
You finally came.
Celty.
It's about Saika.
My father owned it for a while.
But he sold it to an antique dealer a few years ago.
Shingen did?
For what?
Saika is known as a sword that cuts the soul.
Does that mean...
Yes.
He used Saika to steal your head.
To cut the soul that ties the head and the body.
And you've known about this the whole time?
Yes.
I learned later that he used it to steal your head.
I thought I could tell you this now, since you're trying to forget about your head.
But...
Let me think about this alone for a while.
Just as I thought.
Love creates confusion.
That same night, the cursed sword Saika was trying to love a certain girl.
The girl who couldn't discover her place in this world.
Sonohara Anri.
Ikebukuro...
I was only looking...
For the energy source of this town packed with junk.
For the truth behind the town of ever-increasing desire.
Next time - A Fool's Good Advice.