I don't dislike running.
Kurumi, Kurumi! Senpai's here!
But I had an ulterior motive
for joining the team.
Being a manager didn't really suit me.
I thought those beautiful days
would go on forever...
School Living Club
#2
"Memories"
It's time to get up, Senpai.
Senpai!
Senpai, wake up!
It's time for breakfast!
Bring it here...
Mii-kun, that's not what ladles are for.
I'm aware.
Everyone's waiting, so let's hurry it up.
Sorry.
Th-That smell...
This again?
This is no time to drag our
feet, Mii-kun! Let's go!
School Living Club
Ta-da
I was right! It's curry!
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
So you finally sniffed it out, huh?
Morning! I see we're starting
the day on a good note.
Lately we've been eating nothing
but emergency rations.
Oh, but make sure to take your vitamin.
Mmm
This is a little heavy for breakfast, though.
I'll probably gain weight if I eat this...
Oh, dear.
We're all still growing.
One meal like this won't hurt.
Still growing
Exactly. We're still young!
Still young
Oh, yeah!
Well, shall we dig in?
Yeah!
Let's eat!
Let's eat...
Taroumaru
Thanks for breakfast!
Sure.
Okay, I'm off to class.
That's right.
Let's have a good one-on-one study session.
One-on-one with Megu-nee...
What're you so excited about?
Because it'll be just the two of us.
It sounds like fun!
Something tells me you don't plan to study.
Eep...
That's not true at all.
School Living Club
Okay, see you later!
Bye.
Take care.
Come on, Megu-nee, let's go already!
Yesterday, Yuki-senpai
was talking in the classroom again...
Alone.
I see...
I really think we should
do something about this.
Remember how she said she
almost left to go home by herself?
It's too dangerous.
She's in no danger.
Megu-nee is with Yuki-chan right now.
Besides, if she can somehow live
a happy, normal life in this situation,
what could be better than that?
But...
We're not experts.
Why don't we just keep an eye
on her for a bit longer?
All right...
Ebisuzawa Kurumi is going
out on morning patrol!
Take care.
Don't try to do too much.
I know, I know.
Well, let's do this.
Now, Yuki— Takeya-san.
Murasame
Can you solve this one?
Yes!
Then will you come up here and write it?
Don't be so openly reluctant...
Just kidding!
This one's easy, Megu-nee.
Sakura-sensei, please.
Hardtack
Snack and Emergency Ration
Rock sugar added
Keep a stockpile, and you'll be set!
We've got ten cans of hardtack left.
Thanks.
We're running low on supplies...
I'm worried about our power reserves, too.
We need to cut back.
Yeah, it's been cloudy all the time lately.
Still, we have not only a rooftop farm,
but solar-powered batteries, too.
This school really is amazing.
Indeed...
But you know, Miki-san, I think
you're pretty amazing yourself.
H-Huh?
I mean, you fought so hard
all by yourself in that mall.
No, I couldn't have done it on my...
All clear.
Drizzle (Sometimes rain)
Summer rain (May shower)
Monsoon (Plum rain)
Murasame (Village rain)
That's impressive, Takeya-san...
Every single one is wrong.
Urk
Thank you.
How far do you think this whole thing goes?
I hope it's isolated to just this city...
It could be... nationwide.
I'm sure it's not happening worldwide, though.
Help will come eventually.
I can handle one of them.
One...
No.
That's not what they are anymore.
Goodnight.
I'm exhausted.
Hang in there just a bit longer.
Once our tutoring session's over...
Summer vacation starts!
Is there anything you'd
like to do, Takeya-san?
Let's see... I wanna go to the beach,
and to the mountains,
and I wanna light fireworks!
And... What else, what else...
Where else should I go?
It's my last high school summer vacation.
I want to go everywhere
and do everything I want!
Hey, Megu-nee!
What do you wanna do for
our last summer vacation?
Let me think...
A test of courage, maybe?
Yeah, it's not summer without those!
You got another one?
I told you just patrolling was enough.
She was in just the right spot.
It's too dangerous to go alone.
You worry too much.
I'm the club president!
Ahem!
Yeah, yeah.
They're playing soccer again.
I think they're just reacting to the sound.
Maybe somewhere deep down,
they still remember their old lives.
What's wrong?
I was just wondering if anyone's
running on the track...
Maybe.
Attention, School Living Club members!
We're having a test of courage!
A test of... courage?
Mii-kun, your panties...
Don't look!
Sorry.
It's okay.
Okay, let's get this test of courage started!
Should we be doing this?
We're all on the wrong side
of the barricade at once...
I know... But we were running
low on supplies, anyway.
I've been thinking we
needed to come out here,
and I'd be more worried about
leaving Yuki-chan by herself.
Come on, we should get going, too.
Kurumi?
Oh... Yeah, let's go.
Hey, you guys!
You're not going to send me off
alone and ditch me, are you?!
No, no.
Test your courage!
Everyone together, test your courage!
I don't really see them come out at night.
No... They might have all
gone to their homes.
Memories of their old lives again?
Hey!
Act a little more scared.
Kurumi-chan, don't tell me
you're scared of ghosts!
I may just ditch her, after all.
No ghosts here.
Looks like we're okay for now.
But ghosts can jump out at any time,
so keep your voice down.
It's Megu-nee!
Now, now. You need to keep quiet.
Didn't you hear Rii-san?
Yes, ma'am.
You're here too, Megu-nee?
Thanks for helping, Megu-nee.
Y-Yes, thank you.
Now, let me explain how—
Let me explain how this test works.
This test of courage will be held in
the school store and the library.
If anyone should get separated,
remain completely silent and return here.
Okay.
Okay, let's do this.
C'mon, Megu-nee!
I'm... the faculty advisor...
Is it safe to turn the lights on?
This room doesn't have any
windows visible from outside,
so they shouldn't be able to see the light.
As long as we keep an eye on the door here...
I haven't been in here in ages!
Hey, can I buy whatever I want?
The club will cover the cost, so that's fine.
Yay!
Of course she's going for the candy.
Yup.
As we thought.
Now let's get the other items we need.
Hmm, what should I get?
There's chocolate, potato chips...
Oh, this is...
Nummy Stick
A Nummy Stick!
Hey, everyone!
What happened?!
Yuki-chan!
Check these out! They inflate
to 20 times their size!
Isn't that awesome? Not twice, 20 times!
This is a huge victory for science!
That's why you called us over?
Yup, that's right.
Don't freak us out during a test of courage!
S-Sorry...
What would you even use these for?
A Nummy Stick?!
Good question...
You could make balloon animals.
We could make anything we want with those.
We don't know how to make those...
And why are you two eating?!
Are we done shopping?
Yes.
Then let's move on to the library.
The library's next, huh?
I need some math reference books.
I'd like to get some books myself.
I want manga.
Are Nummy Sticks the "in" thing now?
It's dark in here. Can we turn on the lights?
We could, but then this room would be
too easy for people outside to see.
Oh, yeah! This is a test of courage.
What's wrong, Taroumaru?
Maybe he's scared to go inside.
Then I'll wait out here with you.
Okay, Taroumaru?
...ru?
Um, I'll wait here, too.
...ru, ru, ru...
I'm worried about you guys.
We'll go on in, then.
Can you put down the Nummy Stick already?
I'll see what I can do.
Textbooks, workbooks...
You're so studious, Rii-san.
No, these are for you, Yuki-chan.
You told me you were
struggling with math, right?
I-I'll go find some books, too!
Wait!
Yuki-chan, don't run off alone...
This series looks good.
Oh, Megu-nee.
Now, you know you mustn't
run off alone like that.
You gave Rii-san a real scare.
I'm sorry.
Now let's get back to the group.
Okay.
Huh?
A ghost?
Quiet.
Megu-nee, what was that?
It's okay.
Everyone cares about you.
They're all trying to save you.
As long as you have them, you don't
need to worry about any ghost.
Right?
Be still.
Hey, over here!
Oh, there you are.
Are you okay, Yuki-chan?
You're not hurt, are you?
I...
I'm so sorry!
There, there.
Staying put was very smart.
Yeah, that ghost was super scary,
but it was okay, because
Megu-nee was with me. Right?
Thank you, Megu-nee.
Thank you.
You too, Ebisuzawa-san?
It's all right. I am your faculty advisor.
Did you like our test of courage, Yuki-chan?
Yeah.
It was really fun!
Let's do it again next year!
Yeah, let's.
But you're all in your third year.
Are you repeating the year?
Yuki probably will.
Probably.
Kurumi-chan, Rii-san, you meanies!
Oh, but then I'd get to
graduate with Mii-kun!
I'd graduate with you?
I'll go to whatever college
you attend, Senpai!
That's right, you've gotta
graduate too, Taroumaru!
Huh? Tokyo U?!
Kurumi?
Senpai, you understand him?
Sorry. I'm coming.
Kurumi-chan...
Let's repeat... the year... together...
Goodnight.
Next Time!!
Kurumi-chan is so cool.
Megu-nee, you should start
carrying a shovel, too.
Huh? Me?
Then you'd be Shovel-sensei.
That sounds tough!
I can't carry heavy things...
Next time on Episode 3 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "That Time."
#3
"That Time"