Please !
Einzbern Consultation Room
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room.
Part 3
Please !
Einzbern Consultation Room
Part 3
I was right to go ahead and remodel the office!
Zecchan, do you like broccoli in your stew or not?
Yeah, I like 'em in.
I like scallops and shrimp in it too.
Okay!
Thunk
Chop
In goes the seafood!
By the way, Zecchan, what are you studying so diligently?
English.
I hear over half the Masters are foreigners.
So I figured if I didn't know English,
I wouldn't be able to communicate...
Zecchan, could it be...
Yes, a customer!
I'll show him in, so please get changed, Instructor!
Excuse me, there's something I'd like to consult.
Please, come in.
Finally, I have more than one c-
I mean, a customer has come.
If things start well, everything else goes fine.
I'll have to listen intently to his troubles and help him feel better!
Well, Zecchan?
What's our first customer like-
A skull!
What?
A skull appeared.
I don't know what's going on anymore!
Oh, my.
That must be Assassin.
Yeah.
It doesn't look like he has money.
I mean, he's not even wearing a suit.
He's a penniless, destitute, naked man!
No, Zecchan, you shouldn't judge people by their appearance.
He's an important customer no matter what Servant he is.
Now, let's take care of whatever he's troubled with!
Nice to meet you.
I am Zayd, one of the personalities of Hassan,
the Assassin summoned in the 4th Holy Grail War.
You can basically think of it as multiple personalities.
I am part of Hassan, which is part of Assassin.
Hahah, it actually sounds pretty cool when I put it like that.
Among Hundred-Faced Hassan, Assassin is indeed me, and I myself am Assassin.
We have women, machos, and even young
boys, not unlike garnish to go with sashimi.
This is bad, Instructor.
He lost me from the very beginning.
What is he talking about?
Shh, just accommodate him and hear him out.
It's a business basic to learn the personalities of your customers.
Both of you probably think Assassin is just there to get killed.
But in the Holy Grail War, the Assassin class is clearly distinct from the other classes.
With classes such as Saber and Lancer, Heroic Spirits with the relevant characteristics are chosen from all over the world,
but the Assassin class does not have this freedom.
It's always Hassan.
Everyone is Hassan.
All catalysts give you Hassan.
A great Mage of a Master will still get Hassan.
It's Hassan without fail.
It's constantly Hassan.
Hassan.
Hassan! Hassan! Hassan!
Ahh, how wonderful Hassan Sabbah is!
Could you wait just a bit?
We understand that only Hassan can be summoned as an Assassin Heroic Spirit.
Does that mean you've been participating in every Holy Grail War since the first?
No, that's not the case.
It's true that the only Assassin summoned in
the Fuyuki Holy Grail Wars is Hassan Sabbah.
The etymology of the word "Assassin" stems from he who
would come to be known in tales as the Old Man of the Hill.
The man who was mythicized from the actual religious organization of assassins, right?
He's known as the head of the mysterious
assassination organization, but what about it?
Hassan isn't a single person.
Hassan Sabbah
In fact, "Hassan Sabbah" is not the name of an individual.
Assassin itself is the symbol of the religious organization.
Hassan Sabbah
Thus, there were assassins under the
name of Hassan throughout that age.
I am one of them.
One of the personalities
Zayd-san
The Noble Phantasm Zabaniya gives rise to separate multiple personalities.
"Delusions and Illusions (Zabaniya)"
Hundred-Faced Hassan
That's who Hundred-Faced Hassan is!
So you're a fake among fakes!
Zecchan, you shouldn't say such things out loud.
Zayd once lived, though he quickly died in episode two.
He had no chance to prove himself!
Worse, he was tricked by his Master!
Yeah, they were relentless with him.
A discardable prop like him couldn't have asked for more!
Uh, could we get back to the subject?
Yes, please.
Zayd of Hundred-Faced Hassan,
what troubles might you be having?
As the young girl pointed out, it's
about my relationship with my Master.
Of all the Servants summoned in the Grail War,
none of them are as unfortunate as me, no?
Among those monsters of the 4th War, my Noble Phantasm is plain, my appearance is plain, and my class is plain.
Worse, my Master is that atrocious fiend, Lord Kirei.
What's more, his boss and his father see no use for us other than surveillance.
Yet, they call me useless and a loser...
I can't stand this cruel slandering anymore!
This isn't my fault!
I didn't do anything wrong!
This...
Yes.
...is bad.
Bad, indeed.
I see.
Your job is indeed quite shady.
I'll give you that much.
Yes, it's worth giving my sympathies.
Your job is rather tough.
However, is there really nothing wrong with you?
Huh?
No, there definitely isn't...
For example, you snuck in alone all proud of yourself
just because a cool-sounding Kajiura theme was playing.
You only needed to dodge, but you just had
to destroy the origins of all the magic fields.
You struck strange poses to dodge magic wires just to show off.
Despite being in a top-secret mission, you just had to say out loud that it was "too easy".
Too easy.
I'll ask you again, Assassin.
Are you sure you didn't do anything wrong?
That's what I did wrong?!
SFX:  Yay!
Yay!
I regret my actions.
I'll mend my old ways, so please let me work for you as a tea server representing the Assassins...
Oh, dear.
Zayd-san, is it really okay for you to represent them?
Of course.
There's no Assassin more assassin-like than me.
I appreciate your offer, but you can't, Zayd.
Your troubles have been cleared, right?
You should be hurrying to where you need to be.
There's got to be a battlefield that suits you.
Go and realize your ambitions as a Servant once more.
B-But it's a shady business!
Don't worry.
I'm sure you can do it, Zayd.
Now, believe in yourself.
You're one fine Assassin!
L-Lady Iri...
No one's ever thought so highly of me before.
I, Zayd, shall try my very best once more!
No matter how impossible the wish,
I'll get my hands on the Grail!
By the way, what's your wish, Zayd?
My wish is to leave my name on the pages of history.
We have no name.
Having been raised to become the
Old Man of the Hill, we have no identity.
That's why...
You want to retrieve your name.
You'll change the substitute name Assassin,
the title Old Man of the Hill, from Hassan to Zayd!
That's exactly right!
I'll take my leave.
After the King of Knights, the King of Heroes, and the King of Conquerors, you will know of a fourth king, Zayd, King of Assassins!
What a noble goal!
Best of luck to you, Zayd-san!
Instructor, I'm so moved!
This consultation room is here to save
troubled young men like Zayd-san, right?
That's not quite correct, Zecchan.
There's no saving Zayd.
Fate cannot be changed.
R-Really?
Then what was all that for...
The most I can do is listen to their troubles so they can pass away with no regrets.
It's also what they'd wish for.
There are no such things as solvable troubles.
It's about accepting inconsistencies and braving on forward.
That's all there is to human hope.
Realistically speaking, that might be true...
But that somehow doesn't seem right to me.
W-Well, the Grail can save anything!
It's just as Zayd-san said.
It can even change the past!
Indeed, I've gone too far myself.
The Grail has the power to rewrite Zayd's fate.
It's an omnipotent wish-granting device, after all.
Zecchan, how much do you know about the Holy Grail?
Yeah, I'll recite the contents of the textbook you gave me!
Teach me! Grail-san,
What is the Grail ?
～The 726th Grail～
The Holy Grail is a summoning system created by
members of the Three Families that uses the land itself.
Tohsaka
Einzbern
Matou
(Makiri)
Grail Summoning
Land of Fuyuki
The Grail doesn't already exist, but is summoned to this land.
A phenomenon corresponding to the Grail is recreated, allowing one to change the world at will.
Plan of the Wish
Energy
Grail
Modify the
World
Realize the Wish
It sounds difficult, but basically, if one comes up with a plan of anything one can imagine,
the Grail will provide the limitless energy needed to realize that wish.
Ooh!
Participants
Grail of Fuyuki
Church
Supervise
Also, despite its name, the Grail of Fuyuki
didn't actually once hold the blood of God,
but takes many various legends as its foundation and is a model for the omnipotent wish-granting container.
The Holy Church has confirmed this Grail as the 726th Grail.
Since then, they've been supervising to
ensure the Grail falls into the right hands.
That's it!
As for why the Fuyuki Holy Grail was created
and why seven Masters and Servants are required,
the textbook did not address these questions.
Yeah!
Well
done
That was perfect!
Zecchan, why don't you become a teacher?
I-I dunno...
I don't think I'm very good at teaching.
Nah, I'm sure you'd make a great teacher, Zecchan.
I give you my seal of approval!
I-I'll think about it.
By the way, what's your wish, Instructor?
I'll leave that for the main series to reveal.
What about you, Zecchan?
Hmm, I don't have one yet.
Right now, I'm just giving it my all to become
independent and have a wish I can be proud of.
Yeah!
Ooh, everything about you is so adorable!
It's unfortunate that a cute girl like you
had to end up here, but I suppose that's fate!
I'll be sure to protect you until you get your memories back!
Y-Yeah, I'll strive to improve as Student No. 0!
We've also had Zayd-san as a customer, so it's just
the beginning for your consultation room, Instructor!
Yes, let's work hard together!
My thoughts are clear!
I no longer have any doubts.
This time, I'll assassinate anyone,
anywhere, and earn Lord Kirei's respect...
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Is this the dynamics of change?
Fresh terror, or something like that?
Ahh, I can see it!
I can see the peerlessness of Rider slaying the other personalities one by one!
Assassins have no rights!
Who made things so cruel?!
The story progresses to the dramatic second half.
Next Episode Preview
In the land of Fuyuki, a small storm of
gunpowder smoke and conspiracy blows.
Master, this is bad!
We got a spot by the wall!
We succeeded, Zecchan!
The battle intensifies, and Masters and Servants fall one by one.
The situation tumbles non-stop towards its crux.
Now, surpass me, Zecchan!
What's the true form of the Fuyuki Holy Grail?
It's the duty of a student to surpass her instructor!
And what's the true purpose of the consultation room?
How can I?!
Next, on Please! Einzbern Consultation Room:
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room
Extermination of the Cheating Man
"Extermination of the Cheating Man".
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room
Extermination of the Cheating Man
Look forward to it!