Cal, what are you doing?
Cooking, what else?
What on earth are you making that with?
Those.
Come on, just try it out.
I made Judy breakfast every day, so...
This is good!
Right?
So I took an even bigger pot from the shelf,
pointed at the fifty dollar note,
and the shopkeeper's face went blank, it was so funny.
And then...
In other words, you want to train the girl into another hitman?
Cal.
What is it?
Do you know how to use a gun?
Yeah.
Do you feel lucky, punk?
That was an Eastwood line.
There's also...
I'm being serious.
That is to say, it's about avenging Judy.
Five million dollars isn't enough, to be honest.
I see.
However, the rest of the payment isn't much more.
You can earn it by yourself.
What should I do?
Be my assistant for a while.
I know how you feel,
but...
Awesome!
Awesome! So I get to be Phantom's assistant?
Hey...
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Hey,
does being your assistant mean...
...I can watch when we avenge Judy?
But before that happens, there's something you need.
What is it?
A new gun?
New clothes.
Let's go shopping tomorrow.
Ah, okay.
Are you going out?
Yeah, I have work to do.
Then...
You have to remain on standby at our hideout today.
What? That's boring.
Work is boring.
It's never fun.
Just wait here like a good girl.
Fine.
Five million dollars were stolen and four men killed.
It happened right in your territory.
Yet you won't give us an apology or a reassurance?
We lament your dead,
but we will not take responsibility as it occurred prior to the deal.
You bitch!
Muroto.
Yes, sir.
But indeed, our business has been obstructed.
We will provide you with all the power we have in pursuit of the truth.
So that we get our money back, right?
Hopefully.
Until we can reach a conclusion, we would like you to remain in Los Angeles.
Of course, a pleasant stay will be guaranteed.
But originally...
The money was taken...
...and our brothers were killed.
At any rate, we can't return to Japan empty-handed.
Hey, Shiga. How about extending our vacation?
What will we tell the old man?
Just tell him we have food poisoning.
The mastermind is Isaac Wisemel.
Wisemel?
No information about the deal seems to have leaked out.
It's an inside job.
But Wisemel took damage too.
True,
no one will think that he'd cause a ruckus in his own back yard just for five million dollars.
It's a great facade.
Wisemel's objective is to keep the Godou clan from joining Inferno.
He must hate that I would obtain such huge support.
The approach is too radical.
True, but do you really think he's an executive now just because of his foul mouth?
He's the kind of man who uses brute force if the situation calls for it.
He will surely attack Godou again.
Then why not let Godou return to Japan?
Fishing without bait is difficult.
We will be fishing for sharks.
Godou is the bait and you're the hook.
Yes, we will stay for a while.
I require your cooperation a little longer.
I understand.
Regarding our emergency preparations...
Save the boring talk for later.
The booze is losing flavor.
I will contact you later.
Have a joyous vacation.
We've found one at last.
A coordinator with no strings attached to Inferno.
That Giuseppe guy?
If it's true that he knows all there is to the underworld,
we won't have to arrange anything.
True, but...
Just drink.
It's Inferno's treat.
30 years old, Shiga-san.
Aye, I will partake as well.
Bait, huh?
Reiji.
Situation in our hideout is all clear.
You shouldn't shout that out loud.
Sorry.
Is this one of the pleasures you've talked about?
I wonder.
Don't worry.
I spoke true when I said we wouldn't go back empty-handed.
Your subordinate doesn't seem to like the prospect.
You mean Shiga?
Don't worry, he's following the oath we took.
It's just his job.
Is that so?
You should watch your steps too.
It's dangerous for you, isn't it?
Just so.
Traitors are shot no matter what country they're with.
But...
Soon the 3000 men of the Godou family will be supporting you.
So dependable.
Did you choose?
Wait a sec.
We've been here for two hours already.
But I can't decide.
You can't find something you want?
I found a lot!
Then...
I found a lot, but if you told me to choose between them,
I couldn't make up my mind.
Just pick the one you want the most.
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I were to choose one, I would have to discard the rest.
Don't worry.
We won't do this only once in our lives.
If you want something else as well,
I'll take you here some other time.
Really?
Yeah.
So just choose what you want to wear today for now.
Okay.
Umm, then...
Let me tell you this beforehand, I can't take you here every day.
I know that.
Does she really?
Hey, hey. Is it cute? Does it look good on me?
Yeah, it does.
This is the first time I've worn such light and smooth clothing.
Reiji.
Hurry up!
Go home without me.
A Sig Sauer?
It's the same as the Beretta you're using.
9 millimeters, 15 rounds.
This one is more compact, though.
As you said she has never used a gun before.
It doesn't seem bad.
Let's try it.
Thanks.
So?
What do you mean?
You're not here just to deliver a gun I never ordered, are you?
The topic of that girl, Cal, came up in today's executive meeting.
Was it Wisemel?
Worse, McGwire.
He wants to see what you've taught her.
At least teach her how to use a gun.
Welcome home, Reiji.
Oh, you've already changed?
That one is for going out.
This is enough when I'm at home.
You're right, those clothes do just fine.
Let's practice using a gun now.
Really?
Is this the training ground?
It's been a while since I last came here.
This place is pretty lonely.
Let's get started.
Hold it firmly and put some force on your grip.
Thrust out your right hand,
and pull it back with your left.
Yes, that's good.
Align your target with the gap.
Can you see it?
My hands are trembling.
Put pressure on it with your fingers instead of your arm.
Okay, just like that.
Pull the trigger slowly.
You're rushing it.
Slower, squeeze it.
Alright.
Ah, I hit it!
Did you see that, Reiji?
Strike!
Reload.
Okay.
She's careful and dexterous.
Alright, practice by yourself for a bit.
Will do.
A lonely place, huh?
Got business with me?
Huh?
You talkin' to me?
Okay.
You're dead.
Crap, I missed.
Cal!
You see, that was... um...
DeNiro was...
Do it one more time.
Eh?
That DeNiro thing there, try it!
Got business with me?
Huh?
Cut the talking.
Listen,
don't shoot right away this time.
Go into posture and fire one round.
Okay.
I hit it?
Alright! I hit it.
Yes.
Are the preparations for the shark fishing going well?
Godou was docile before, but he got bored.
He plans to go out big time tonight.
Your mission is to keep an eye on them,
and pick up Wisemel's trail.
Alright!
Not nearly...
What a conceited bunch.
Alright!
This is a bad day.
Don't feel down.
The goddess of victory only smiles on those who put faith in her.
You already have her half-naked, so why should I try my own hand...
Oh? You're leaving the table?
Booze is the only thing that never betrays me.
Don't drink too much.
I won't.
It's a good thing they act in a group like true Japanese.
Shiga, give it a shot.
Okay, brother.
Hey, don't mafia people like this kind of place?
This isn't a DeNiro movie.
She's probably a genius.
But is it okay to let her walk the same path I took?
I can't.
I need to set her free.
And as fast as possible.
Let's play poker.
Excuse me.
Yes?
An acquaintance of mine sat here just now.
Ah, a Japanese, right?
It seems he has returned to his room.
A young woman was with him.
They took the bait.
Eh? Damn.
No way.
Elen.
No, it's not her.
Elen died.
Because I killed her.