Run.
Good morning.
Nagi-chan, Yuuko-chan, good morning.
So, why did you stop in the middle of the hallway?
Look at this! This was stuck to my forehead.
You just noticed?
Yeah.
That's Run for you.
Really?
Run-chan!
Good morning.
Ruuun-chan.
Good morning!
Did you see that drama yesterday?
Yeah, I saw it. It was hilarious!
Run seems to have a lot of male friends.
You're right.
To-Tooru!
It's still morning, and she's this worked up.
What's wrong, Tooru?
Run-chan.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Love
Good morning, Tooru.
Small as ever.
Don't pet me!
Wait. How did you get so dirty?
Did you trip?
Well, Run-chan was...
Well, that's...
Don't tell me she was bullied!
...chasing a butterfly and almost got hit by a car.
You're really something.
See you later, Tooru.
Later.
'Til lunch then, Tooru.
Good morning.
Aoigaoka High School  Successful Candidates
It's me.
Hi, Run-chan.
Tooru! It's been a while!
Hey, can I come over right now?
Sure, you can. Come over any time.
Thanks. See you then.
A while, huh?
I was busy with my exams, so we didn't get to see each other.
Coming!
If it isn't Tooru-chan! It's really been a while.
I haven't been keeping in touch.
Run is upstairs.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I wonder if Run-chan will be happy.
Run-chan!
Run-chan, I managed to get into the same high school as you!
Ah, Tooru!
Wha-
That hurt!
Run, what's up with her?
Run-chan, who is this person? What was that just now?
You got in? Congratulations!
Who cares about that?
She's Tooru?
She really is small!
Is she the one you wanted to introduce to us?
Introduce?
That's right!
The list of the admitted candidates is being published today,
and I thought you would come over, so I called them too.
These are friends from my school, Yuuko-chan and Nagi-chan.
Hi there.
Friends?
Let's all get along, starting this spring, Tooru.
I think she's leering at us.
I think you left a terrible first impression, Yuuko.
You should explain what happened earlier.
Um...
You've misunderstood.
That happened because Run was trying to tickle me.
We weren't doing anything fishy.
We were just fooling around.
Hey! What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I'm glad they're getting along already.
Squeeze
Smack
Is it really okay not to stop her?
Gasp
Well, I'll give you the print-outs for your electives.
You did it last year, so you know the process.
Our homeroom teacher this year doesn't seem to care much.
Here. These are the print-outs for your electives.
Does anyone have any questions?
There aren't many electives for freshmen, but there are more for the higher grades.
These things can influence your career, so take them seriously.
If anybody has individual questions, feel free to ask me anytime.
I wonder if Run is all right.
What's she doing?
Time for lunch, time for lunch!
Tooru, let's eat together!
You're sure in a hurry.
Tooru isn't here yet.
Yeah, you're right. Habit, I guess.
She's here, Nagi-chan! That's Tooru for you!
Run-chan
No way... Did she hear that?
Hey, these squirrel picks are cute!
Right? They're my favourites.
I really love animals.
Really? Then what are your favourite animals?
Birds, I guess?
Like parakeets? They're cute!
Speaking of which...
Your head kinda looks like a parakeet's.
On top of that, they're delicious.
That's what you were talking about?
You can't eat a poor parakeet!
That's not the point!
Run-chan likes her poultry.
So that's it.
You should've said that you like poultry.
That's right, but I like all kinds of meat.
Let's eat yakiniku sometime, then.
I really want some beef ribs and salted tongue.
That seriously makes me want to eat yakiniku.
I can almost hear the delicious sound of meat being roasted.
Sorry. That's mine.
A ringtone?
Run's fried eggs look delicious.
Care to let me have a bite?
Sure.
Here you go.
Thanks a bunch.
Yum!
Run, did you make that?
Again?
Those two get along really well, don't they?
You call that getting along?
The bento was tasty, wasn't it, Tooru?
Yeah.
Run, where are you going?
Our classroom is over here.
You're right. It's the routine from when we were freshmen not long ago.
Hurry up, Run. You too, Tooru, or you won't make it either.
See you later.
Tooru!
You didn't fall asleep during the afternoon classes, Run?
No, the afternoon was okay.
Did almost falling out of the window wake you up?
You have to be more careful.
Sure.
Personally, I feel more sleepy in the afternoon.
That's right!
Wanna munch some candy to keep you awake?
Have some.
Thanks.
There. One for you too, Run.
Thank you.
That's the last one.
Oh, I see.
In that case, I'll keep it for Tooru.
But then you won't get to have any.
I'll share half of it.
You're so nice, Run.
How are you going to give her half of it?
I've got it!
A box cutter!
I wonder if I can cut it in half with this.
Be careful. You'll look like an idiot hurting yourself with a piece of candy.
It'll be okay.
Is it working?
Ah, it fell on the floor!
That's why I told you.
But I thought it would work!
Tooru.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Let's go home.
What's up, Tooru?
The smell of candy...
I smell candy!
Huh? You still have some?
Candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy!
I forgot to throw the bag away.
Aoigaoka
High School
Tooru, you're really something!
To be able to smell the empty bag...
Tooru just loves sweet things.
Sorry. We just ate the last ones.
I'll bring more.
I want amber hard-candy!
Hey, isn't there something, you know, less sweet? With less calories?
Why? Sweeter is better!
Okay, I understand. I'll bring it tomorrow.
What did the two of you choose for your electives?
What's that again?
Kamade-sensei was talking about it, remember?
Run was probably asleep at that time.
Now that you mention it...
By the way, Yuuko, why did you fall over?
Run was asleep, and looked like she was about to fall over, so I tried to catch her.
But then she suddenly stopped, and I fell over instead.
Hey, Tooru, what did you choose as your freshman electives?
Tooru?
I'd like to take the same classes as you, Run-chan.
With you.
It's okay.
We haven't changed.
Yeah.
You're just adorable, Tooru.
Stop, stop, stop!
Hey, Tooru, let's go and have some tea together.
Let go of me.
That's unfair, Yuuko. Let me hug her, too.
You're so soft!
What's up with you guys?!
Let's go, Tooru.
yume to harukaze no kagaku
夢と春風の化学
The science of dreams and the spring breeze,
tomaranai yokan
止まらない予感
I can't stop getting this strange feeling.
Lucky Happy kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky Happy この指に止まれ
Lucky Happy, please choose me.
itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
いつもかしましく走る　その先は
I'm always running boisterously.
wakaranai
わからない
I don't know what is waiting ahead,
kedo sore ga ii ne
けどそれがいいね
but I don't mind.
hajimaru yo
始まるよ
Everything begins now.
honpou my pace
奔放　マイペース
I shamelessly take things at my own pace.
jugyou chuu wa gahaku
授業中は画伯
During class, I'm an expert artist.
kirehashi ni wa keikaku
切れ端には計画
I write elaborate plans on my scraps.
doko ni ikou
どこに行こう
Where shall we go?
kitto ima ga paradise
きっと今がパラダイス
Today will surely be a paradise.
neji maki sugi no munasawagi
ネジ巻きすぎの　胸騒ぎ
I feel uneasy, like a screw that's wound too tight.
yakusoku wa chikoku
約束は遅刻
We made a promise to be late,
da kedo douchaku
だけど同着
but we arrive at the same time, anyway.
skirt no stage wa
スカートのステージは
Upon the stage that our skirts dance,
donna hibi ni naru no?
どんな日々になるの?
what kinds of days will unfold?
yume to harukaze no kagaku
夢と春風の化学
The science of dreams and the spring breeze,
tomaranai yokan
止まらない予感
I can't stop getting this strange feeling.
Lucky Happy kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky Happy この指に止まれ
Lucky Happy, please choose me.
itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
いつもかしましく走る　その先は
I'm always running boisterously.
wakaranai
わからない
I don't know what is waiting ahead,
kedo sore ga ii ne
けどそれがいいね
but I don't mind.
hajimaru yo
始まるよ
Everything begins now.
Hey, hey...
Run truly has a lot of male friends.
I wonder what they're talking about.
Run-chan, tell us Yuuko-chan's three sizes!
Keep it a secret, but it's 88-56-87 from the top.
Wow, that's amazing!
Doesn't that sound about right?
Wh-Why do you know my sizes, Nagi?
See you, Run-chan.
See you.
Huh? Now they've all left.
I see.
Hey, Tooru.
Run-chan.
All worked up this morning as usual, Tooru?
Tooru, like I promised, I brought candy.
Later, we can eat them together.
Why'd you do that?
Nooooo~
Those two get along really well, right?
You're right.
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
Even among candy, there are many different kinds.
Light rain, drizzles and tear drops!
Hey, you know some unexpected things.
And here comes a question, Mipo-rin.
What is it?
Who on earth are we?
Didn't you just give away my name?
Even for Yutaka, that was a pretty big mistake.
Next time, on A Channel, "On Rainy Days, Take a Bath"
Next Time!
On Rainy Days, Take a Bath
With us talking this much, do you think we'll be in the next episode?
That's a secret.