oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
40 meters down, 45 meters remaining.
He has a half body length's advantage.
Araki's in good form as he comes up on the 50 meter turn.
A
Delinquents are Scary
Wait a sec, wasn't he fencing before?
Why is he swimming?
It's a modern pentathlon.
They compete in shooting, fencing, swimming, horseriding, and running.
In Greek, pentathlon means "five competitions".
The triathlon is swimming, bicycling, and marathon running, right?
But I don't get the biathlon.
What do they do there?
Skiing and shooting.
What don't you get about it?
The triathlon has the general goal of moving as fast as possible.
The modern pentathlon gives off the imagery of the athletes fighting with swords and guns,
then breaking through the battlefield by running, swimming, and riding on horseback.
Sounds like a bloody competition.
But it feels very competitive, right?
I get it. With two sports, they could be doing anything.
At the Tokyo Olympics, there would be skiing and something else.
How about skiing and karuta? Or skiing and frisbee?
Or skiing and snuggling a warm table!
They'd just fall asleep at the warm table.
That reminds me, they combined shogi with boxing before on Knight Scoop.
That sounds tough.
But think about it.
If you took shooting away from the biathlon,
they'd have to run extra instead.
The message being that if you can't stop the bear,
then run as fast as you can.
I feel like someone's watching me.
A bear's coming?!
That wasn't here in the previous episode!
W-Who forgot to put the Hina dolls away?!
Hell will freeze over before we get married!
We all know that leaving the Hina dolls out means...
...that we'll freeze!
What a dreadful way to die!
It's "hell will freeze over before you marry"...
Hell? Freeze over? That doesn't make it better!
We're done for!
We'll be single until we freeze and die!
Now we've got no plots or dreams!
Girls, let's just calm down and think this through while sipping tea!
I'll go make some!
In a flash, we turned into the most hopeless sp*nsters!
There was some green tea here...
Hopeless moss?
Is there such a dreadful moss?!
Of course not!
It's moss!
The most hopeless sp*nster!
It's really like moss!
No, this is just tea powder!
Stay away! Don't infect us!
You're mean!
Crossed my fingers! Now I won't get cooties!
You're all gonna end up like this!
Kigu turned all of her cuteness into madness!
Now we're all covered in moss!
We're done for!
Wait. We still have a way out.
We should all turn into delinquents.
Why?
That should be obvious.
They all marry early. Without exception.
That's true!
Misfits all marry early!
My neighbor chick was such a crazy misfit.
She was married off in the blink of an eye at age 15.
But the legal age is 16, isn't it?
Like I said, she's a crazy misfit!
So...
So this means,
that with the misfit effect countering the spinster moss, we'll be at +/- zero!
I see!
But you can't just become a misfit in the blink of an eye!
Marii...
Please...
Be so kind as...
...to teach us!
Why me?!
I'm not a misfit and never have been!
Anyway, just be our head, 'kay?
Leader? I like the sound of that.
Marii liked the idea of becoming the head and brains of the group.
Head!
What?!
She got in the mood.
First off, squat down and gather.
We're all here already.
How can we become misfits?
Let's start with the looks!
This really works!
Just look at this.
A
Omelette Rice
Omelette... rice?
Yeah, misfits just love to use complicated kanji!
That means we're fit to be misfits!
Just think about it!
Blood E. Mary!
Breakwater Tetra PD!
Coolbu T. Specs!
Helloky T. Fursuit!
Youth N. Asia!
That's not all!
From now on, we'll use complicated letters too!
Eh?!
But that's crazy...
Stop complaining and just do what I say!
You're really used to this, Marii.
Of course I am!
But it's difficult...
You've gotta feel it!
Couldn't you just say "feel"? Why make it unreadable?
Huh?
This is difficult to understand!
Then let's focus on actions instead of words!
We'll go to school at night and clean the windows!
Clean them?
Yeah, misfits clean them! Sometimes they do nice things!
Aren't there any legends about misfits?
Legends?
Of course there are! Lots of them!
She bit on it again.
Legend like the Legend of Mana?
More like the Legend of the Galactic Heroes.
Naw, not like that.
That's a legend on a galactic scale.
A misfit's legend will only be known locally at most.
The Legend of Galactic Princess Yuna?
Don't forget the Legend of Moby Dick either.
Misfits don't have a bunch of fanboys,
so they can't compete with legends like those.
Then I'll make the Legend of Marii!
"Long ago in a place far, far away lived an energetic crossdresser boy called Gold-Marii."
A
Gold
"He spent his days doing nothing at all but lying around."
"The end."
That's an old story!
Old stories and fairytales are often quite surrealistic.
That wasn't even surrealistic!
No climax, no culmination, no meaning.
Well, legends are legends.
A compilation of old stories, that's all.
You want some misfit-ish legend, right?
How about this?
At your part-time job, you and your friend quietly...
No! Not that!
My blog would get spammed!
Anons would track me down!
They'd call my school about it!
Keep in mind that just because you're a misfit doesn't mean you'll marry early for sure.
Think about it the other way.
This room is isolated, as if it sat on top of a tower. Thus, the dolls are locked away.
I see! That's smart!
Then are we locked in the tower too?
Like a princess in a tower!
A princess...
Marii liked the idea of being a "princess".
Oh, look how late it is. Let's go home.
Yeah, the last train is leaving soon too.
Marii, you aren't going home?
The princess can't leave her tower!
Okay...
Don't just come in! Your footsteps are loud!
Marii, the princess isn't a shut-in, she's just locked in her tower.
She looks like some surreal modern Barbie doll...
Too bad she's missing her Ken.
Tsukiji!
Fish!
Tuna!
Marii is so full of energy...
Waking up early is torture for performers.
Girls! Kukuru isn't breathing!
I'm so sleepy...
That's eternal sleep!
Stay up to avoid the Reaper!
Dance and eat!
I want to eat tuna and dance!
Marii, a bluefin tuna weighs over 400 kilograms...
It also costs at least a million...
I'll devour it! Chew it apart! I'll rip it to pieces on stage!
Tuna from deep-sea fisheries are flash-frozen at -60 degrees Celsius...
Here a crab and there a fishie!
The more you catch the cheaper it gets!
She's annoying.
She's like those foreigners who disturb the auctions,
start touching the goods and take pictures.
They're so annoying.
Yeah, that pisses me off.
I get the urge to %&ß them with a tuna cleaver.
If the times hadn't changed, they'd suffer like the Tsarevich did at Otsu.
There'd be a huge diplomatic crisis!
There are tuna on sale!
Hey, is she pulling an all-nighter?
That's the reason she's so hyper?
Still, this is a country of law and order.
A
Fish Story
The noise makes it feel like a real marketplace.
Their hoarse voices are nice...
One of the top three hoarse voices.
Top three? What are the other two?
Obvious!
Ticket scalpers
and His Excellency Rozen!
What? No way! Are you serious?
The way they move around is nice too.
One of the top three ways to move around.
And the other two?
Rappers
and the "wanna have a drink" of guys inviting their colleagues to a pub.
Yeah, the guys working at Tsukiji are pretty cool.
Look, an electrocar! There's an electrocar.
Oh my gosh!
Watch out!
Don't fall in love!
Don't let it lead you astray! See it for what it is!
It's like the ski slope in winter, the beach in summer, or school uniforms!
She's right. She really is.
When you come home from skiing or the beach, he looks kinda ordinary in the streets...
Or if he changes out of his uniform and his own clothes are outright lame...
And after he parks the electrocar, he'll be just be some old guy.
He's just some old guy anyway.
You should see an optometrist.
Electrocars are so nice. I can completely understand those who want to drive them.
I'm pretty sure you need a license, though.
What? It doesn't count as a scooter?
I guess it needs more than 50cc...
If I could pick a car, I'd want a Lamborghini Countach LP500S,
and maybe a De Tomaso Panthera or a Porsche Carrera 2 Turbo to keep it company.
Yeah, supercars are nice...
I'd want one of those monstrous heavies at construction sites.
Monstrous babies?
Up there atop the buildings I could escape the heat.
Oh, those?
You're right. It does seem cool up there.
The chill comes from wondering what could happen if you dropped a steel beam.
That is chilly.
It made me shiver!
What about you, Kigu?
Oh, I want to drive a Merc—
You know, in theme parks, there are those pandas and bears that move if you put in 100 yen!
So cute!
Right?
That was the last time I did that shit for you.
A kilogram of dried bonito is 7000 yen.
You can only get a kilo of it at a market... No one would buy it elsewhere, anyway.
per kg
Bonito shavings
Dried bonito
Heave-ho...
She bought it.
You can't have any.
Just how many cats do you have?
No cats. It just looks yummy.
Sadly they're going to close it all down soon.
Yeah, they're moving it to Toyosu.
I'm used to saying "Tsukiji market" so "Toyosu market" sounds so weird.
The fish market was originally in Nihonbashi, not Tsukiji.
It was moved after the Great Kanto Earthquake.
This time the reason is politics and not tectonics.
Tuna
v(h)ale
Look, a tuna shirt!
Tuna
v(h)ale
Tuna's kanji is written with the fish radical and "to be".
I guess because its existence shouldn't be ignored?
On the other hand, there's no fish written with "nothingness".
That should be the glass catfish.
What's that?
An aquarium fish that's transparent except for its head and bones.
Then let's put "illusion" next to the fish radical, and let it mean the young of eels.
Huh?
It's always been a mystery where they come from
until they were discovered deep in the Mariana Trench.
Aristotle wrote that they emerge from mud naturally.
Then why not write it with fish and mud?
Why are we writing it with the radical "long" anyway?
Fish radical and "blue"!
That's how Mister explained the kanji for mackerel.
Are you
alright?
Mackerel
Why the English? Why katakana?
Write it with kanji like a good Japanese!
That's the Mistery part of Mister.
"Weird" and "human" would be read Mister.
Should be "human" and "super"!
The kanji for "extreme" would do as well.
Marii would be... "human" and "ass"?
Hey, what are you implying?!
You'd prefer "big sis"? Or "misfit"?
I don't want either!
Kigu should be "human" and the first kanji from "pure".
Really?
She's lovable, so it could be "human" and "love" too.
That makes me so happy.
I'll keep doing my best to be cute!
I'm shit tired of being your fucking role model.
Kukuru should be "human" and...
Clearly "suffering".
That's so cool!
Child poverty, abuse and neglect.
Crime, shoplifting, expelled despite counseling.
Early pregnancy, marriage,
domestic violence, drugs, arrest, divorce, sickness!
That life is stormier than the Drake Passage!
You could go on a talent show with that!
Hey, what about me then? A circle?
How about eight?
"Human" and "eight"?
"Human" and "eight" written with the Arabic numeral.
That's just about my glasses!
Then "infinite"!
You rotated it!
What about me?
You're quite neutral, so...
"Human" and a square!
A square?
You can insert whatever character you want there.
Even difficult ones like "rose", "azure" or "azalea".
You're making it too easy for yourselves.
More importantly, I'm really hungry.
Let's go eat something.
What should we eat?
Sushi, now that we're here?
Or one of those restaurants with seasoned fish?
In Tsukiji it has to be Yoshinoya!
Huh? Beef rice bowl? Not fish?
The first Yoshinoya was opened in Tsukiji ages ago.
Fair enough...
Yoshinoya
Look, the holy place!
Hey, wait for me!
A
Yoshinoya
What's wrong, Kukuru?
The manager really gave me hell.
Huh?
He was saying how this month's electricity bill was way too high.
But is there even anything in here that uses lots of electricity?
Well, there is, but that doesn't explain why this month's was so much higher.
A
Dressing Room Files
Save electricity, okay?
We mustn't waste any! It's bad for the Earth!
We gotta look into this and find out the reason!
I've been wondering about this for a while,
but doesn't the floor feel a little warm?
Now that you mention it...
Must be heated floors! You shouldn't leave them on all the time!
But they're tatami mats, not just wood.
If we open up the floor, we'll see.
Well, no heaters here.
Nope.
So, nothing noteworthy under the floor.
But... uh... wasn't there something a little out of the ordinary?
Did you see anything that uses electricity?
No, but...
In other words, nothing noteworthy.
But...
Don't worry about minor details!
We need to focus on our electricity usage!
Yeah! That's the important thing!
Otherwise, get ready for rolling blackouts! Price rises! Stockholder lawsuits!
O-Oh...
That reminds me, lately I've been hearing voices coming from the wall!
From the wall?
Voices?
There must be speakers built into the wall!
Like JBL or Tannoy...
You shouldn't just leave music playing all the time!
If we open up the walls, we'll see!
Well, no speakers here.
Nope.
Nothing noteworthy in the walls.
Uh, I think I might've seen something a bit unusual...
Did you see anything that uses electricity?
No, nothing that uses electricity, but...
Then there's nothing noteworthy.
But that's...
Are they the type who become so fixated on their goals that they can see nothing else?
Oh, right!
The ceiling's been shaking a lot lately.
Shaking?
Someone might be using a massage chair in the attic!
Modern massage chairs treat you from your shoulders to your back, from your legs to your arms!
They use lots of electricity!
If we open up the ceiling, we'll see!
Well, no massage chair here.
Nope.
Nothing noteworthy in the attic either.
Eh?
Um, I can't help but feel that ignoring what we just saw might end up being a fatal mistake...
Did you see anything that uses electricity?
I didn't, but...
Then there's nothing noteworthy.
But I mean...
So, if there are no electric devices behind the floor, walls, or ceiling,
that means it must be something inside the room, right?
That means...
It's your glasses!
Why's it my glasses?!
I bet they're actually a scouter! Those things use as much electricity as a supercomputer!
They are not!
Why would I care about your power level, anyway? It's practically zero!
Even the littlest things make a difference when saving energy.
That's not what we're talking about here!
But you know...
Saving electricity isn't forward-thinking at all!
Instead of placing restrictions on the consumers,
why don't they just think about how to make more electricity?
It's a human-powered generator!
Who's gonna pedal?
Marii, of course.
It has to be Marii.
She's the one who brought it up, after all.
Fine! I'll do it, then!
Where there's a will, there's a way! Nothing ventured, nothing gained!
Can you really make electricity with this?
There are plugs...
It's weaker than a bicycle's light... so that means it's outputting less than a AA battery.
I knew it.
Ouch, this hurts...
We gotta fix it, or the manager will get mad at us again!
I thought I saw a person walled up in there...
What does that have to do with generating electricity?
Who generates electricity by hand these days, anyway?
There are greener, more high-tech ways!
Neither solar nor wind power are working.
Well, we are in the dressing room.
The sun may not shine in here, but the wind could blow at least.
Speaking of the blowing wind...
At that moment, the wind blew around us.
A well-timed gust of wind is the perfect way to mark a fateful meeting!
Totally!
And don't forget, when two people get along really well...
They say you can almost see sparks fly!
Yeah, totally!
So the best way to generate electricity is to have people gettin' it on!
Chance
Love Cafe
Welcome!
Chance
Love Cafe
Please come in!
We've got lots of nice girls all waiting for you!
This is working out! I can almost feel the electricity in the air!
It's the police! Don't move an inch!
We got tipped off that you're engaging in suspicious business here!
Suspicious?! We're just trying to generate electricity!
This is outrageous!
You're siding with some paranoid informer instead of us, the citizens?!
Wh-What the hell?
So it was you who was using all that electricity, Kigu?
That's what you're surprised about?!
I'm glad we found out the cause.
Yeah, it's all good now.
Now the manager won't get mad at us anymore.
Oh, please...
Lucky it's a robot.
And what was the real Kigu doing at that time?
Why, she was at home, dreaming of electric sheep.
Two will be enough... Please understand...
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
I'm Anrakutei Kukuru.
Everyone's different, but that's what makes us special.
But I feel safer being the same, so what should I do?
Next time: Bag of Gold, Totter and Is It Over Yet?
will be performed in great distress.
A
Bag of Gold
Totter
Is It Over Yet?