Shireizan
in Mutsu
Poor thing...
Being treated like a deity in a place like this...
Almost like me.
This feels light, and has a good size.
This is good.
Or maybe it's bad?
This is Akutou Bita, after all.
Note: Akutou Bita means "Poor, the Evil"
I see...
I get it now.
Well, I've gotten my present now, so "hasten to do good"...
Or maybe "hasten to do bad"?
Why are you touching me without permission?
You...
Weed. Weed. Weed. Weed. Weed. Weed. Weed.
Weed.
If I wait in some obvious place, I'm sure they'll come to see me.
I guess it'll be the first time in half a year?
It'll be good if Shichika has grown a little.
Anyway, I feel rather good.
Or maybe I feel bad?
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
己をはらはら花に例えて　散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsumami aguneta guren no tama wo
摘みあぐねた紅蓮の霊を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarau kare no hi areshi mune yori
さらう彼の日　荒れし胸より
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
恐るるまま命は羽搏いて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
やがて　やがて　天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
朱く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai kira no yume wo ataeta mou
すれ違い綺羅の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabite meiyo ni samayoi
待ち侘びて冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
想いがはらはら舞う故に
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sora he egaite
絆を更なる空へ描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Nanami...
You are too exceptional.
I can't raise you...
Can't raise you...
You are a monster.
You shouldn't have been born.
Pitiful...
Pitiful girl...
You are truly pitiful.
You can't even die in peace...
Can't even die...
Can't even live...
You are a failure of life.
Someone like you...
Like you...
Someone like you should die.
Worthless.
The necromancy used by the holy guards of Shireizan...
I tried it out, but these are nothing but memories.
Nanami...
Disappear.
I don't need you two to tell me that.
Akutou
Bita
The Seiryouin Goken
Temple in Tosa
Emonzaemon-dono.
What, Strategian-dono?
Your job was to show us the way here, correct?
If that's the case, why don't you just return?
Unnecessary.
Such a concern is unnecessary.
Well, whatever your dear princess does is none of my business.
I just worry for the future of the Intelligence Division when I see you waiting around with so much spare time.
Needless.
Being present here, I am carrying out my duties to their full extent.
Being able to see up close what kind of sword it is that you are carrying is an extremely pertinent duty for me.
Why do we have to fight?
Shichika, don't waste my time.
Our two spectators have gotten so bored they've started chatting.
This stare down will get us nowhere.
You're always looking down on me like that.
I haven't just been playing around for the past half year, you know.
I can see that's at least partly true just by looking at you.
I'm much stronger than when I first fought you.
I don't want to injure you.
Injure?
Don't be so naive.
I said this was a serious duel.
Come at me to kill.
To kill...
I see you really have softened up.
Honestly...
I was worried from the beginning that this might happen.
Whose fault was it, I wonder?
Was it Uneri Ginkaku-san?
Tsuruga Meisai-san?
Sabi Hakuhei-san?
Azekura Kanara-san?
Or was it Itezora Konayuki-san?
Or perhaps...
Could it be your fault, Strategian Togame-san?
If you'd just hand over the Shikizaki sword, there wouldn't be any problem!
Two swordsmen are facing off against each other.
How could there be no reason to fight?
You're not a swordsman, Nee-chan.
You may be right.
I am a sword.
Are you any different?
I went to the trouble of obtaining one of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades because I figured you'd need a reason to fight.
If you want it, you have no choice but to defeat me.
That's a simple equation to understand, right?
I don't believe father brought you up to prioritize your sister over your owner.
Fine.
Whatever happens is on your hands.
Hey, Togame.
Give us the signal.
Alright.
Let the fight...
Begin!
Shichika...
I realize we're in the midst of a duel, but allow me to teach you something for the first time in a while.
You are mistaken.
Firstly, even if you have grown stronger than me through the numerous battles you've experienced this past half year,
in the end it means nothing,
because I have these eyes.
These eyes which take in everything.
When faced with these eyes of mine, your strength becomes mine.
The incredible skill to learn any technique and use it as her own after seeing it once —
Hidden technique: Migeika
Note: Migeika = "Sight training"
I can see through any technique, any movement, and any weaknesses...
She learned all the Kyotouryuu techniques with no training, simply by watching...
Is that really possible?
No, the fact that Shichika is currently at her mercy is proof enough.
Kyotouryuu ultimate secret technique!
Shichika Hachiretsu!
And even now, just like it was half a year ago, you're still much weaker than me...
Nee-chan...
What did you just do?
I grabbed you by the waist and threw you.
Don't be ridiculous!
R-Right!
There's no way you could throw me with those thin arms of yours!
That Ezo girl... Itezora Konayuki, was it?
Surely you remember this kind of brute strength.
It was you who wiped out the Itezora village?!
Good deduction.
As expected from you.
Be careful, Shichika!
Nanami has obtained Konayuki's strength!
No, not the undeveloped strength that Konayuki has...
She has the full strength of an Itezora adult!
She gained the ability by attacking the village!
I hadn't expected there to be any survivors, but you're correct.
It was me who destroyed the Itezora village.
I'd heard that Shireizan was annihilated,
but why did you need to destroy that village?
The same goes for Mt. Odori, and for that temple!
Why did you go out of your way to destroy them?
Because of you, Konayuki is...
You say rather strange things these days, Shichika.
I don't remember you complaining each time I uprooted a weed.
Weeding is my hobby.
Or are you trying to tell me that as a sword, you want to choose who you cut?
Togame-san, I may have been mistaken in entrusting Shichika to you.
I really thought I could leave him with you without worry...
You have no right to say that.
How I use my sword is my choice alone.
Is that not so?
I suppose you're right.
That was unreasonable of me.
Idle talk aside, that's how it is, Shichika.
I've been through some fairly tough battles on the way here to Gokenji temple.
I started with members of the Maniwa Insect Squad, then the Itezora clan, then the holy guards of Shireizan...
and finally Gokenji temple.
I've had to fight a lot of people.
And I've absorbed all of them.
With these eyes.
You fought the Maniwani too?
That's crazy...
As for your Shichika Hachiretsu, seeing it once was more than enough.
Though, I didn't know its weakness till I tried using it.
You really haven't noticed, have you?
Good for you, Shichika — all your opponents up till now were weaklings.
None of them were able to see this obvious weakness, after all.
What do you mean "weakness"?
I had left the island to tell you about it...
but after seeing how cowardly you've become, I've changed my mind.
I'd never tell you as you are.
Don't worry.
It was childish of me to say this was a serious battle with you.
As you are now, you don't have the right to stand against me.
For an opponent at your level,
my little finger here will do.
Don't be so conceited!
Kyotouryuu "Red Poppy" and "Daphne" hybrid striking technique.
Incidentally, I adapted Ninpou: Ashigaru for this.
I took the weight out of all the blows for you.
If I wanted to, I could have killed you 272 times over before you hit the ground.
What's wrong, Shichika?
If you want to say something, go ahead.
Like hell that was just one finger!
You heard me wrong.
I said I'd use everything except my little finger.
Nee-chan, what's going on here?
Huh?
Don't act dumb.
There's no way you could pull off an insane move like striking me 272 times with that body of yours.
That's right...
Nanami's only weakness is her fragile body.
She has no strength or stamina.
Ah, I hadn't told you about that yet.
This is how it is.
What!?
Nee-chan!!
Don't get so upset.
This is the way Akutou Bita is meant to be used.
With this lightning-charged dagger embedded in my chest, my body's weaknesses are forcibly healed.
It forces the body to rejuvenate.
That's Akutou Bita's focus!
Unlike your Shichika Hachiretsu, I no longer have any weaknesses or blind spots.
Come back when you've improved a bit.
One month earlier,
Togame the strategian and Yasuri Shichika were determined to return to Owari after putting Ezo's Mt. Odori behind them.
But upon hearing the news that Akutou, which had been enshrined in Mutsu's Shireizan, had been stolen,
they quickly followed the tracks of the culprit.
Tosa
Why are you here?
Need not say.
Who is this?
He's the henchman of the princess of Owari, Souda Emonzaemon-dono.
He's very strange.
Cannot agree.
I don't want to hear that from you.
I assume that unpleasant woman ordered you to investigate what we're up to?
Not wrong.
Well, that's exactly it, actually.
However, I'm just here to contact you this time.
How about I tell you where the culprit is hiding out?
That's right, where is the culprit who stole the sword from Shireizan hiding?
Not hiding.
The culprit is quite shamelessly staying in the holiest grounds for swordsmen — Gokenji temple in Seiryouin.
No, perhaps I should say she has occupied Gokenji temple.
The culprit who destroyed the first class disaster region of Mt. Shireizan,
and who is currently using Akutou Bita to occupy Gokenji temple in the holy grounds of Seiryouin —
Yasuri Nanami.
Owari
I have returned.
You're late!
Always, always late! How long do you intend to keep me waiting?
You fool!
My apologies.
And so?
How much truth was there to that ridiculous rumor that Shireizan was annihilated?
All of it.
It was all a lie?
It was all true.
And it wasn't just Shireizan.
Kyotouryuu's older sister, Yasuri Nanami...
She's a monster.
What?
Fuji Woodlands
I wonder what's going on there now.
Ah... yes...
To think the monster who annihilated Shireizan was Kyotouryuu's elder sister...
It wasn't just Shireizan.
Mt. Odori in Ezo was also likely destroyed by Kyotouryuu's sister, Yasuri Nanami.
According to the information you gathered, anyway.
Ah... yes...
Yasuri Nanami, the strongest in all Japan, huh...
She annihilated the Itezora clan?
How is that possible?
She didn't possess Akutou Bita at that point, did she?
That merely shows that she was already monstrous to begin with.
I'm quite happy to see that unpleasant strategian's plans being messed up,
but I don't like taking collateral damage.
What a miscalculation...
Dragging Kyotouryuu out to the surface was all well and good,
but it looks like we also dragged up something terrifying along with him...
How did it look?
Does Shichika-kun have any hope of winning?
None.
Seriously, this is far beyond the Sabi Hakuhei problem...
Gokenji temple is probably under her control by now.
What will that strategian do?
No matter how cunning her schemes, I doubt they will work on such a true prodigy.
Strategians don't fight...
But she may be able to come up with some clever idea.
Or rather, all we can do is hope that she does.
I don't think that anyone, including yourself, can stand toe to toe with Yasuri Nanami.
Quite frank, aren't you?
However, it is as you say.
There are only 4 of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads remaining now.
We can no longer afford to take any risks.
Which means that all we can do is rely on the strategian to defeat that monster...
This really isn't funny...
On the subject, how would you fight Yasuri Nanami?
I wouldn't.
I see.
If you were put into a situation where you were forced to fight her, what would you do?
I'd stall for time.
Enough time for you to escape.
Perfect score!
But as long as Yasuri Nanami possesses Akutou Bitou, we can't turn a blind eye.
Was that unpleasant woman doing well?
Yes.
She was noisy all the way to Gokenji.
She pretended to trip and kicked me a few times.
She can be pretty childish sometimes...
Um... Nanami-sama?
Will you be eating?
I'm not in the mood.
Don't worry about it.
As I am, it is unnecessary.
The reign of a suitable prodigy, huh...
For the holy land of swordsmen, where battle is hailed as the goal in life, the current state of things is certainly fitting.
One could certainly say that the holy land is now even more holy-like with Yasuri Nanami reigning over it.
However...
Why did I ever think I could win against Nee-chan?
There's no way I could.
I don't want to see a battle between siblings if I can help it.
Is there really nothing that will convince you to give up Akutou Bita?
You've very kind, as usual.
I entrusted Shichika to you because you are the way you are,
so it would be unfair of me to bear a grudge...
However, I never imagined that you would treat Shichika quite so humanely.
Back when he was on the island, he was more of a sharp sword.
Right now he seems more like a rusty one.
Rusty, huh...
Perhaps I should break him?
Don't say such horrible things.
What are you talking about?
The task you yourself are undertaking involves plenty of horrible killing.
So we can't avoid a duel?
There's no reason to avoid it.
T-Togame-san?
Cheerio!
How many days do you think have passed now?
How long are you planning to be like that?
I never imagined you'd get that depressed.
You're seriously troublesome.
I'm also shocked at how disheartened I am...
I'm supposed to be a sword.
Come here!
Time for re-education.
Shichika, I originally decided not to ask you this, but...
Why did you hide the fact that Nanami was stronger than you?
Because I wanted to be your sword.
That's what I thought when you came to the island.
You might have chosen Nee-chan if you knew she was stronger.
Idiot!
I'll only say this once, so listen up!
I don't know about half a year ago, but you're the only sword for me now!
Don't make me spell this out for you, idiot!
Shichika, look at me!
How many defeats do you think I've suffered up till now?
It's nothing to be proud of, but I've lost hundreds— no, thousands of times.
But even so, I've never sat around, doing nothing but being depressed like you are now!
And I've always won out at the end of the day.
Can't you see what a disgrace you look?
Well, I do feel embarrassed that I lost to Nee-chan.
Stand up!
It's exactly that depression and hesitation that's disgraceful!
I'll ask you just once!
I won't get mad at you, no matter what answer you give.
This is the only time I won't force you to do anything.
So answer me.
Will you have a rematch with Nanami?
I will!
I see.
Then I shall tell you the scheme I've come up with.
First, we'll start with your ultimate technique.
Let's discuss the weakness of Shichika Hachiretsu.
There is a serious weakness to Shichika Hachiretsu.
I didn't think it had one...
I'll put it bluntly.
It's a technique you came up with just half a year ago, right?
Don't you think it would be strange if it didn't have any holes?
When you put it that way...
This time is exceptional, so I'll get straight to the point.
Okay.
You describe Shichika Hachiretsu as a hybrid technique which releases 7 techniques at once,
but you just say that out of convenience, and in reality, it's just consecutive techniques executed in succession extremely quickly.
That's obvious.
To put it bluntly though, this technique fails as a combination move.
The fourth move "Ryuuryoku Kakou" is in the way.
I-In the way?
What are you doing?
Kyouka Suigetsu, Kachou Fuugetsu, Hyakka Ryouran.
Ryuuryoku Kakou.
This one!
It's an armor-piercing move that nullifies the opponent's defense.
It's definitely powerful, but the movement you have to undergo to perform it has a large defensive hole.
The fourth technique, Ryuuryoku Kakou, is unsuitable as a hybrid technique.
Once your opponent knows that, it's simple to defeat it.
My ultimate secret technique had a hole like that?
In the end though, your sister went soft on you.
She deliberately demonstrated a hybrid move and hinted at the answer.
It really is that simple.
And that's why she's probably expecting you to improve it before fighting her again.
I guess...
In the end, we won't get anywhere unless we defeat those eyes.
Well, I do have a plan for that.
I've been putting all my effort into thinking one up while you've been shamefully moping around.
I even comforted you, too.
Come on, say something.
Togame...
Thank you.
Don't look so happy after I bully you!
What kind of fetish is that?
Shichika, all that's left is for you to settle this.
Why is Nanami doing this in such a roundabout way though?
Why is she forcing the brother she doted on into a duel that he can't win?
Could it really be that when two swordsmen face each other...
I'm sure she doesn't really believe that one needs no reason to fight.
Hurry, Shichika.
Hurry up and come kill me...
Like you killed father.
No good, they don't chain well.
Given all 7 techniques, there are 5040 possible combinations,
but if you restrict yourself to using Ryuuryoku Kakou first, that becomes 720.
I need to find the combination amongst those with the fewest holes in it.
Togame-san...
Understood.
That's fine.
Or perhaps that's bad?
Either way works.
You seem surprised.
Well, if you accept then I'd be quite happy with that.
I have no reason to refuse.
I am a sword, after all.
Shichika said that he didn't understand the point of a sword owning another sword.
Is that so?
Shichika must have gotten over his depression if he's being that cheeky.
That boy will die.
Let's talk a little.
Do you know why our father was exiled to the island?
The war ended and he was gracefully segregated, right?
As an ally it's very dependable, but to have Kyotouryuu fighting against you is too dangerous.
That's not all.
Father was also accused of murdering mother.
700!
Mother belonged to one of the 6 Sengoku feudal lords' families, the Tetsubi family.
It wouldn't have been any surprise if he were executed.
But given his status as the hero of the rebellion, they were lenient on him.
So did he kill her?
Yasuri Mutsue's own wife?
Who knows?
The truth is hidden in darkness even now.
No, perhaps hidden in the bushes.
The last doctor was like a bush, after all.
Note: Pun on "bush doctor" (yabuisha) = quack doctor
That joke's not funny.
Either way's good.
Or perhaps either way's bad?
Do you understand why I'm telling you this, Togame-san?
Are you trying to tell me that it's perfectly natural for family members to kill each other in the Yasuri household?
Exactly.
720!
Now then, shall we see what you're made of, Strategian-dono?
You'll be showing your hand tonight, correct?
Well, not your hand, but your knowledge.
Who knows.
It's useless.
No matter what plan you come up with, it won't get past my eyes.
Plans are plans, but what I come up with are schemes.
Sounds good.
Or maybe it sounds bad?
No matter how good your eyes are, I will definitely evade them.
Well, either way is good.
And either way is bad.
I look forward to it.
Shall we head to the dojo?
No, not the dojo.
Your fight will be held not at the dojo, but in the arena of battle.
To allow you to settle this once and for all, I'll have you fight in front of the Buddha.
The Buddha?
I needn't explain —
The unprecedented evil decree that General Kyuu proclaimed,
and the final result of the 10,000 swords he collected in the sword hunt —
Your fight will be decided in the presence of the Buddha of swords!
I don't really mind if you want to look at it, so gaze however long you want, Shichika.
Nee-chan, can I ask one more time?
No matter how many times you ask, my answer will stay the same.
If you cannot beat me, I will not hand it over or give it up.
If you wish to collect this sword for the sake of your owner, you have no choice but to defeat me.
Come at me with the intent to kill.
I will also fight to kill you.
It looks like you've become a bit sharper.
But you're still lukewarm,
neither hot nor cold.
What I'm about to perform is a Shichika Hachiretsu that you've never seen.
You won't be able to block it like you did a week ago.
Possibly.
Hey, Shichika...
Do you remember when you killed father?
I guess I do...
I haven't thanked you for that yet.
But I'm not particularly grateful to you for that,
so even now I don't intend to say so.
Because, I would have been fine with being killed by father back then.
I would have been fine with it.
There's no point to me living, after all.
Nee-chan, that's—
So make sure you kill me now.
Togame-san.
That's the way it is, so please hurry up and begin the fight.
This might be the last time you two get to speak to each other, you know.
Saying something like that after coming this far...
Or perhaps you're trying to buy time?
Does your plan require time to take effect?
Fine, fine.
Go kill each other as much as you like, you sword-siblings.
10...
I won't hold you back anymore. Do whatever you want.
9... 8...
Let the fight...
3... 2...
1..
Begin!
0!
So this is their plan.
Let what fight begin?
This is just trickery.
All 300 candles must burn out and extinguish at precisely the same moment.
It took meticulous planning and preparation.
How's that?
We've overcome your Migeika.
Here I come, Nee-chan!
Kyotouryuu, ultimate technique!
Ryuuryoku Kakou has many blind spots,
so Shichika just needs to use that technique first.
If he can complete that part, Shichika's hybrid—
No, his forced combination technique becomes perfected.
Shichika Hachiretsu Kai!
Kyouka
Suigetsu
Rakka
Rouzeki
Hyakka
Ryouran
Kinjou
Tenka
Kachou
Fuugetsu
Signs: Shichika Hachiretsu Kai
Did you get her?
Shichika...
Togame, here.
How's Nanami?
Is she dead?
No.
I didn't really get a winning feeling.
Mostly thanks to your scheme.
Can you call a doctor?
Ah, sure.
Without Akutou, Nanami's life is in danger...
Watch out!
It can't be, but...
It would appear I was too naive.
Nee-chan, don't move!
Akutou Bita...
Regulating my strength with such a phony sword,
Dulling my strength by rejuvenating my life force...
Even though it's called "sight training", I was just trying to become a little weaker by using the strength of others.
Dulling your strength?!
Nee-chan...
You mean you've been learning others' moves in order to become weaker?
I...
I was too naive.
Trying to live a little longer...
And in that condition, fighting seriously...
I'm the one who was lukewarm.
I'm still alive.
Hurry up and kill me.
Nee-chan...
Come.
Stop it!
There's no meaning in doing this!
We've already taken Akutou Bita!
It's over!
There's no more reason for you two to fight!
Be quiet.
What?
Your head will come off with the next one.
Togame's hair...
Isn't that great?
Now we have a reason to fight.
I can't forgive that.
Even if it's you, Nee-chan.
You prefer girls with long hair?
You're much like father in that respect.
Quite bluntly, it's unpleasant.
That's why, rather than plucking grass, I'll scatter you like a flower.
Try it!
However, by that point you'll be torn into pieces!
You're finally going to go all out?
I am the 7th generation head of Kyotouryuu, Yasuri Shichika!
Here I come!
Without style or school, Yasuri Nanami!
Come!
A sword...
Nee-chan!
Shichika, my little brother...
You're finally going to put me to rest.
Nee-chan!!
Kyotouryuu, ultimate technique!
Shichika Hachiretsu Kai!
My body isn't able to withstand my full strength.
That's obvious.
That's why I've been copying others' techniques,
in order to become weaker.
In order to live just a little longer.
Nee-chan!
Ah, is that how it is?
Is this what happens when a sword tries to use a sword?
Kyotouryuu: Dandelion!
Hey, father...
In the end, I really am a Kyotouryuu.
Well done, Shichika.
Finally, finally...
Good job killing me.
Huh?
Did I mess up my line?
Kyotouryuu isn't a style that doesn't use swords.
It's a style that absolutely cannot use swords.
Nanami wanted to be killed...
I wondered why she got involved in our journey, which meant nothing to her...
I thought maybe she had some plan that involved dragging Shichika into it too,
but there was nothing like that.
The reason was simple.
She simply wanted to be killed.
Nee-chan was extremely powerful, but she was too powerful, and her body wasn't made to fight.
Her body was so weak because she was too much of a prodigy.
That's what I think.
All that talk about Shichika Hachiretsu's weakness was nothing more than an excuse.
Nanami simply wanted to be killed by you.
She wanted to die like an ordinary person.
Even so, I didn't want to kill her.
Dad, too...
I wonder if Nee-chan also wanted to be killed by Dad.
I suppose it's just like she said herself.
"I'm fine with being killed."
What's allowed and what you wish for are different.
But I'm sure Nanami loved your father just as much as you did.
Even so, I...
Can I touch it?
Do what you like, you hair fetish pervert.
That tickles!
Nee-chan was pretty good at cutting hair, huh?
I suppose so.
But I guess now both you and I are left with no family.
No family?
Don't be dumb.
What time period are you talking about?
I have you, and you have me, right?
You laughed just now!
You laughed!
I wasn't really laughing,
but weren't you embarrassed saying something like that?
Shut up!
Cheerio!
Whoops!
Over here!
And so the two of them finally departed for the Yanari Shogun's home territory of Owari.
There are five swords left.
The end of their journey slowly draws near.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
oide tan tan taan
おいで　タンタンターン
Come to me Tan tan taan
kotae wo
答えを
The answer
sugu ni oshie te ageru
すぐに　教えてあげる
I'll show you right away
koko he tan tan taan
ここへ　タンタンターン
Here Tan tan taan
hageshiku
激しく
Intensively
subete wo kaesu
全てを返す
I'll give you back everything
yagate ton ton toon
やがて　トントントーン
Before long Ton ton toon
hiraita higeki mukaeru deshou
開いた　悲劇　迎えるでしょう
We'll reach the open tragedy
yatto shizuka ni
やっと　静かに
Finally quietly
yatto higan he to
やっと　彼岸へと
At long last to the next world
shizuka ni
静かに
Calmly
yami hodoke te
闇　解けて
Darkness comes untied
uya nagare te
烏夜　流れて
Black night flows
maigo no karada minai de ne
迷子の　身体見ないでね
Don't look the lost body
yami tsurezure
闇　つれづれ
Darkness continues
uya horebore to
烏夜　惚れ惚れと
At the black night dreamingly
saigo ni
最期に
In my last moment
dareka wo miteita
誰かを　見ていた
I was watching someone
It's tasty, right?
Nee-chan...
To die like an ordinary person...
It's cruel how difficult it is to obtain such a simple thing.
Will Shichika and I be able to die like ordinary people?
Now then, our next destination is lake Fuyouko,
a designated first grade disaster region in Edo.
How will we fight a mechanical doll?
That thing itself is a sword??
The Shikizaki Deviant Blades have too much design freedom!
Next time on Katanagatari:
Bitou
Kanzashi
Bitou Kanzashi
Chest!
No, Cheerio!!