What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
Help! Help! Help!
--Help! Help!
--Help... Help...
I'm sorry.
"My Amazing Stage Debut!"
This is the city where Kaleido Stage is.
I'm finally here!
I'm going to pass today's
audition no matter what
and become a member of Kaleido Stage!
I will! I will! I will!
Now, which way is Kaleido Stage?
Is it this way?
Or this way?
Or this way?!
Which way is it?!
This is bad. Am I like totally lost?
Oh, there's a newsstand.
I'll go ask over there.
Excuse me, is Kaleido Stage
Kaleido Stage?
Excuse me...
You've got good, tight muscles!
What are you doing?! You pervert!
What?!
Watch out.
Huh?!
Don't change the subject!
What the heck else should
I watch out for, except you?!
Like your suitcase.
It's mine now!
Oh, hey!
Maximum speed!
He pisses me off!
Stop right there!
Use these!
Thanks!
Damn!
If that's how you're going to be...
Whoops, sorry!
All right, move it, move it,
move it, move it! Outta my way!
I'm taking this back!
Why me too?
There are always a lot
of runaways in this season.
I didn't run away from home.
I just got here from Japan...
From Japan?
It's rare to see runaways from so far away.
Like I said, I didn't run away from home!
I'm going to be late for
the audition! What'll I do?!
At the very least...
Think of how your
parents must be worrying...
Oh, please don't mind me.
I'm just doing warm-up exercises.
Don't worry, I'm listening.
I see, you came to
audition for Kaleido Stage.
I know I don't look it, but
I'm a huge fan of Kaleido Stage.
Oh, please don't mind me.
Easy for you to say.
It's fine, really.
Sora, we can see it now.
That's Kaleido Stage.
Really?!
Well, good luck.
Thank you, Mr. Policeman.
Shoot! I'm really late!
--So, we will be announcing the results
from the judges after the matinee...
--Is it here? Or over here?
--Or over here?!
Excuse me...
Oh, thank goodness! This is the place!
Um, who are you?
Sora! My name is Sora Naegino!
I am very sorry for being late.
Oh, the auditions ended just now.
What?!
But I came all this way
from Japan for this audition.
What? Really? Okay,
then come up on the stage.
Oh, thank you very much...
No.
Oh, Miss Layla.
The auditions are over.
Layla Hamilton... It's really her!
Oh, there's a reason for
why I was late and...
No matter what happens,
a stage production begins on time.
But...
Go home.
I can't just go home like this!
What are you doing?!
Miss Layla!
Please! I absolutely,
desperately want to join Kaleido Stage!
Miss Layla!
If Miss Layla says no, then it's no, so...
Come back and try out next year.
I made a promise with my mom and dad
that I would give up if I failed today.
I see...
Ever since I was a child,
it's been my dream to
perform in Kaleido Stage.
The show is going to start soon.
If you want, you can stay and watch.
What? Is it okay?
That's about all I can do for you right now.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm Ken. Nice to meet you, Sora.
Thank you, Ken!
Did you join because you fell
in love with Kaleido Stage too?
I actually wanted to be a cast
member, but I have a weak heart.
So, I decided I would provide
support from behind the scenes
and got into the
management side of things.
I see.
What?
Yuri...
It's really him.
He's so cool!
You think so?
I wish I could have stood on this stage too.
Watch out!
That hurt!
My arm got twisted!
I'm sorry!
No! I won't forgive you!
I told you not to touch the
stage sets because it's dangerous.
She's the one that's dangerous!
I can't go on stage now! Call the doctor!
--No! No! No!
--I guess it can't be helped.
--No means no! No!
--We've got a problem. I need a
trampoline cast member right away.
--There's no need for that.
Hey! What the heck are you doing here?!
Boss...
Boss?!
You fill the spot.
Huh?
What?!
What are you thinking, Boss?
There's no way an amateur can
perform in a real show right away.
Is that what she said?
No...
Then it's not your place to interfere.
This is... my chance!
Or am I in trouble?
Which is it?!
That is up to you to determine.
Anyway, I just have to think
of this as my audition, and do it!
You will be able to do it.
You will be fine.
A doll is talking...
No, that can't be!
She's laughing...
What incredible composure.
Sora, are you ready?
Yes!
You look cute...
What about that girl?
Oh, she just twisted it.
She'll be fine by tomorrow.
She always blows things out of proportion.
I'm glad.
Why did he pick that girl?
What could he possibly be thinking?
Is it one of Kalos's whims?
Oh, here she comes.
What's the big idea?
You.
You're the girl who was late to the audition.
What are you doing?
She's going to be appearing
in the trampoline show.
Take off that costume.
What?!
Being on stage is not so easy
that an amateur can just fill the role.
But Miss Layla...
Didn't you hear me?
No!
Please let me do this.
I'll show you that I can do it right!
I told her to do the show.
Kalos!
Go.
Yes, sir.
The performance is
just like I told you earlier.
Okay.
Don't forget to smile.
Shoot. What am
I supposed to do first again?
I wonder if she'll be okay?
Oh! A flip! Right!
Oh, man...
I'm sorry!
Sora...
Oh, no!
I can't do it!
I can't perform at all!
Miss Rabbit, hang in there!
That's right...
I can't say that I can't do it.
I have to do it right now.
I have to do it!
Miss Rabbit!
They like it!
Now, if she could just nail the finale...
I can't see below...
No!
Sora!
Out of the way!
Mr. Yuri?!
Keep smiling until the end.
Yes, sir!
--Good work!
--Good work out there!
Good work, Sora.
I'm just glad for you that
it all ended without mishap.
Right...
And the crowd was pretty into you.
There is nothing to be happy about.
How dare you make a fool of
yourself right before my show?
I just so desperately... wanted
to join... Kaleido Stage and...
And that's why the audience had to
see such a disgraceful performance?
You understand just how
naive you were now, don't you?
Yes...
There is no place for you here.
Please leave now.
Yes...
Oh, Sora!
Leave her alone!
The Golden Phoenix...
Miss Layla's big routine.
Even in death, Juliet's love
continues to burn for
eternity like the phoenix.
That is what the Golden Phoenix is about.
Compared to that,
I can't even flap my wings yet.
Good work!
Good work out there!
Where did she go?
Sora!
Sora, wait! Wait a minute!
What?
You don't have to go home!
You! Passed!
What?!
You passed, okay?!
I passed?
What are you thinking?
You're passing a girl
who didn't even audition.
Someday, the audience
will come here just to see her.
Is it true?
Yeah, that's what Kalos said.
Is it really okay?
Sure it is. Have confidence in yourself.
--Besides, I'm happy that I don't
have to say goodbye to you...
--Sora!
Mr. Policeman!
How did it go?
I passed! I was able to pass!
Is that so? I'm happy for you!
I had faith in you, you know.
Thank you!
Starting today, I'm your first fan, Sora!
This is the dormitory.
Just get some rest for today.
Thank you.
Kaleido Stage...
I'm really a part of it now!
This doll...
I'm pretty sure it's the same as
the one in the dressing room...
So, you can see me.
It... It really talked...
Why do you laugh?
My name is Fool.
I am the Spirit of the Stage.
Spirit of the Stage?
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
Let us see your Golden Phoenix.
And so,
I'm going to be trying Miss Layla's
big routine, the Golden Phoenix!
And Miss Layla's said she'll
have my resignation if I can't do it!
It's a difficult routine that expresses
Juliet's passion as she flies into Romeo's arms.
Everyone says Miss Layla is the
only person who can pull it off!
Darn it! I've come this far!
I just gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! Gotta!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"My Amazing and Lonely Challenge!"
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...