Kerry! Kerry!
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Kerry!
Wow! Amazing!
Nah...
That was nothing!
Shirley...
Shirley!
Kerry!
Hey, there.
Hey, Kerry.
Do you know where this island's name comes from?
Nope.
Oh, isn't Arimago the word for a type of crab?
Yup.
Long ago,
this was a place where they made offerings to the sea gods.
But one day,
a girl, with nothing to feed her sick mother,
took some of the food that had been offered.
Thus, the girl was cursed,
and transformed into a crab.
That's where the name comes from?
It's an awful story.
The shrine where they worshipped those gods
stood where your mansion now is,
up on the mountain.
That's why none of the villagers want to go up there.
They say it's bad luck.
They say if you go there too often, you'll be cursed.
They try to scare me.
Jeez.
But everyone's nice to me.
You don't feel like an outsider anymore, right?
In the village, they treat you like my little brother.
Oh...
Little brother, huh?
You've really settled in here.
Yeah?
When you first arrived, everyone used to bully you.
You had a weird name.
The hell?
You're the one who starting using it!
But why call me "Kerry"...
Because your name's really hard to say!
Kerry... Kerry...
Kiritsugu.
Kerytugu!
Not even close...
Huh?
What?
Okay.
Dad, is that new?
Yes.
This is my hundredth success.
These flowers never wither.
I've altered the flow of time.
They'll never grow beyond this.
But they'll also never wither.
Wow...
The problem is
whether we can get the same theory to work on humans.
Hey!
Shirley.
That's...
Look!
My first success!
Shirley's been following in my footsteps while she helps.
She does have talent as a magus.
Aw, didn't you do most of it?
I only helped a little at the end.
That's still amazing!
Hey, Dad.
Hmm? What?
Could I try the thing that Shirley did?
That'd be great.
If you had some help, you could do it!
Right?
No.
Kiritsugu.
It's still too early for you.
This isn't a game.
It's dangerous.
I only let Shirley try it because I think she has the necessary knowledge and experience.
Father, why won't you understand?
Shirley...
Everyone just misunderstands him!
Listen, Shirley...
Don't go back to that mansion.
Let's talk inside.
My dad should spend time with the villagers, too.
Maybe...
Father Simon really doesn't like him.
He preaches at me a lot.
He claims if I keep working there,
a demon will possess me someday.
Look at this.
He told me to keep it nearby
at all times.
He says that it's a powerful talisman.
Aren't you scared of my dad, Shirley?
Nope.
Sure, magical research isn't exactly normal.
But the things that he's uncovering could make history!
I think he's amazing.
That...
It's sharp and easy to use.
See you tomorrow.
Shirley, is something wrong?
Making a flower bloom forever...
It really is an amazing magic.
Shirley, you did it, too.
Working with flowers is all I can do.
He can do a lot more.
His medicines could eradicate human mortality.
I want him to use his power for everyone,
so they'll understand how impressive he is.
He's given up on that.
But, Kerry,
I think you can do it.
What?
You're his best student.
If anyone were to do it, it'd be you.
Not me.
I'm not his student.
The most I can be is his assistant.
Helping him with little things...
I'm not his student or anything else.
So even when the priest lectures me about him,
there's nothing I can say.
Kerry.
You're his heir, without doubt.
Everything he's working on,
he plans for you to continue.
It's just a little too soon.
Hey.
Come with me.
Kerry,
what kind of adult do you want to be when you grow up?
If you take up your dad's work,
what will you use it for?
It's a power that could change the world.
And someday, it'll be yours.
Yeah, change the world.
You can do it.
I guarantee it.
That's...
That's a secret.
Then,
when you grow up,
let me see what you can do.
I'll stay with you until then.
Okay?
Wh-Whatever...
Stop it!
Gotcha!
Oh, good morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu,
you didn't enter my workshop last night, did you?
Huh? Nope.
Very well.
Kiritsugu,
don't go to the village today.
Don't leave the house.
What's going on?
Shirley's late...
Hey.
Have you seen Shirley?
Shirley?
What happened to you?
Kerry...
Shirley!
I...
I only wanted to prove it!
His research...
But...
I guess...
It didn't work...
Kill me.
Use that.
Please...
You have to kill me.
If you do it now,
there'll still be time...
Please!
I can't stop it...
I can't hold it back anymore!
Hurry!
Was that really Shirley?
Kerry, stay here for now.
I'll go inform the village.
Wh-What is this?
Father Simon?
Looks like I'm late.
W-Wait!
Who are you?
Shouldn't you worry about yourself first?
Well, if you just sit there,
you'll join them soon enough.
What happened?
Who did this?
Burning down the village...
Surely you've heard of them...
Vampires.
We call them Dead Apostles.
Dead Apostles?
They drink blood to reproduce.
Nearly everyone on this island is one now.
So we're cleaning it up.
There are two groups of people down there who are trying to eliminate them.
One is the Church's Executors.
People who never doubt that you may slaughter anyone
who defies the will of God.
Of course, they'll show no mercy to any Dead Apostles.
They'll kill anyone they even suspect of having had their blood sucked.
And then there's the Magus Association...
Well, they're harder to explain.
They'd like to keep the secret of who made
something bizarre like the Dead Apostles all to themselves.
Unsurprisingly, considering they vow to keep everything to themselves,
they'll kill anyone they suspect of knowing the secret.
They'll do anything to cover up what happened.
They're the ones who burned the village.
Whose side are you on?
I'm like a salesman for the Magus Association.
Now, kid...
Answer my question.
I'm looking for a magus who's been marked for sealing.
A magus...
I'm sure that doesn't mean anything to you.
The first person to become a Dead Apostle here...
I suppose you could say the medium that made them a Dead Apostle...
What caused them to transform.
The renegade magus who made it should be hiding somewhere on this island.
Do you know anything?
Oh, Kiritsugu... You're safe.
I'm very relieved.
I told you not to go to the village.
Dad...
Why were you researching the Dead Apostles?
Kiritsugu, how did you know...
Shirley used the magic on herself...
Oh...
Well, it's very sad.
But you can't change the past.
Unwittingly, Shirley showed me the answer.
Will you use me one day like you used Shirley?
Don't be stupid.
A Dead Apostle that can't control its bloodlust is a failure.
But the Emiya family research requires unlimited time.
Akasha will never be attained with a mortal body.
It was a time-consuming experiment,
but it seems to have failed.
I'll have to rewrite my theory from scratch.
Kiritsugu,
we'll discuss this another time.
We need to run now.
Can we run?
I hid a motorboat on the south coast,
just in case something like this happened.
I'm sorry, Kiritsugu,
but I don't have time to let you gather your things.
Come on.
I'll do it.
There's a barrier around the forest.
A powerful one.
It'll take time to break.
But...
I can get inside.
I have to do it.
Kerry,
what kind of adult do you want to be when you grow up?
I was able to break that barrier fairly easily.
Are you mad?
It was only luck that you arrived in time.
Had this man escaped,
he'd have continued his Dead Apostles research elsewhere.
That's a terrible reason for a kid to kill his father.
You're a good person, aren't you?
I'll get you off the island.
You can decide the rest for yourself.
Do you want to take anything with you?
No.
The stars twinkle away silently to their deaths
Heaven and Earth overflow with unanswered prayers
Episode 18:
Distant Memories
The future glitters on the branch, yet unbloomed
Still reluctant, it slowly unfolds
Behold, the golden apple has ripened and is ready
But pick it and the world will end
Just as the falling snow is so pure that it vanishes at the slightest warmth
A single beautiful dream tore apart your heart
and destroyed the kindness in your cold eyes
Look at the violently twinkling stars disobeying the heavens
Not stopping till they destroy the sky
After leaving the island, I spent the next several years
with Natalia Kaminski, the woman who took me from there.
That meant choosing the same path as Natalia,
the path of a hunter.
Next Time:
Where Justice Is Found