Meet Mitsuki Koyama, 12 years old.
Her dream is to become a singer.
She did great at her audition
and is on her way to becoming a star,
but her debut song was up in the air,
and she had a disagreement
with her producer
and she told him that she'd
write her own song lyrics.
But everything worked out
and soon she'll be making
her debut as "Full Moon."
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Meroko, you look like
you're really happy!
Of course, I have to take
good care of my skin.
It seems like you're happy too.
What, you think so?
Oh...debuting as Full Moon...
I'm so happy that
it doesn't seem real.
Oh, it's Ms. Oshige!
H-Hello.
Oh, Mitsuki?
Yes.
I'm sorry it's last minute,
but we have a photo shoot
for a magazine.
A photo shoot?
That's right, and tomorrow
we're meeting at 9 in the morning.
What? Tomorrow?!
Her First Assignment
A photo shoot at the lake,
it's been a while since
I've been to a lake.
Why are you getting excited?
In any case, did you contact
that doctor of yours?
Yeah. When I told him that
I was going to the lake,
he said that it'd be good for my body,
so he was happy.
I see.
Yeah...
That's right!
Huh?
I should bring my bathing suit too.
Hey, don't forget your job
as a Death Spirit!
Oh, I know already!
Are you sure about that?
Wow! The air tastes so different!
Ms. Oshige,
can I go take a short walk?
Sure! But come back soon!
All right!
Hey, hey!
Where do you think you're going,
leaving us here!
I'm going to the lake, too!
Oh... Here it is, here it is.
There's no time for the lake!
Oh c'mon, it's ok!
I could never go on field trips
because I was always sick.
Yeah! It feels so good!
It feels so good to be able
to shout out loud.
She's so stupid.
Takuto!
Huh? What?
Don't be so silly!
You better remember what
you told me last night.
Last night?
We can't let her meet the person
who's going to change her destiny.
I know that!
More importantly,
you should get your act together!
It's not like we're on a field trip!
That's none of your concern!
Didn't we tell you not
to leave us behind?
What would we do
if something happened?
What do you mean "something"?
What? I mean...
Well, what if they found out that
you were actually 12!
No need to worry about that, see?
They're not going to find out
with me like this.
Mitsuki!
We're going to start soon,
so come back!
All right!
Then let's start, shall we?
Please be good to her.
Those are very cute stuffed animals.
Are they yours, Miss Full Moon?
Yes, they're my very good friends.
I see.
My name is Takeda and I'm from
the monthly magazine MYOJO.
Nice to meet you
Monthly magazine MYOJO?
It's that magazine with
all the famous singers.
Mitsuki...
Wow! Awesome!
Mitsuki!
What?! Oh, yes!
You have to introduce yourself!
Oh! I-I'm Full Moon!
Nice to meet you!
I'm sorry. It's just the way she is...
She's much cuter than I imagined.
Um, you're a high school student, right?
Yes, I'm 16!
My blood type is A, my hobby is reading,
and my favorite color is blue.
That's right, keep it up.
It was totally worth it
for her to have practiced!
Are you sure about that?
On my days off, I usually relax at home!
And I usually like
to hang out with myself!
You're a funny person!
Well yes...
I'm sorry!
I have to leave just for a second.
But please carry on without me.
It's fine!
This is your first interview,
so do your best!
Oh, yeah!
Hmm...my next question would be...
When did you decide that
you wanted to become a singer?
Since I was ten!
You have such clear answers.
Was there an episode that
triggered this?
What?!
So you can see Eichi again, right?
But that's...
Oh?
Is something the matter?
Oh? Nothing!
U-Umm...
It's so that I can have
many people listen to me sing.
I see...
Are there any singers
that you aspire to be like?
What?!
Oh no! We didn't practice that one!
What's the matter?
Maybe you don't have any?
U-Umm...
I like anybody
who is a great singer.
Maybe the question was too boring.
Then, what are your favorite foods?
Taiyaki and the shrimp pilaf that
comes with the school-provided lunches.
Huh? School-provided lunches.
Fool!
School-provided lunch?
Miss Full Moon, you said that
you were a high school student, correct?
Your school offers lunches?
That's not what I meant...
Um... I meant the shrimp pilaf
I used to have in elementary school
was so unforgettably my favorite!
Maybe Miss Full Moon, you actually
are an elementary school student.
Did he figure me out?
I'm just kidding!
Don't let it bother you.
Oh, y-yes.
I'll have to make her practice more.
It's getting complicated
because you're giving her
unnecessary information.
What?!
I have to be more careful.
I have to look and
act like a sixteen-year-old.
I wonder if I look mature enough?
Can you walk around a little bit for me?
Y-Yes!
Then, try lifting your arms a little bit.
What?! Oh...
Yes!
Um, do you think you can try
being a little more natural?
What?!
I'm sorry.
Even so, he should take into consideration
that she's still a novice at this!
Then, next look over to the lake!
As if you're looking at
somewhere far away!
O-Okay...
I have to act like a sixteen-year-old!
No, no!
This won't be any good!
We'll take a break!
I'm so sorry...
When he gets in that mood,
no matter who's around,
he gets like that.
No...
Our girl's still new and she hasn't gotten
used to these things either.
Well, it's getting cloudy,
so let's take a short break.
Mitsuki...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it!
Work at your own pace.
But...
Maybe you should go
walk around a bit?
You still have some time.
Go on. It'll make you feel better.
Okay.
That fool.
What is she getting all tense for?
That's not it!
It's because of that
incompetent cameraman pressuring her!
If I were taking the pictures,
I'd take such beautiful pictures of her!
You're right, he's not able
to capture her beauty.
Huh?
Capture her beauty?
Oh! What beauty?!
When you already have
somebody like me!
Make up your mind already!
It doesn't matter!
Takuto, you can't look
at that girl any more!
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?!
Now, back to work, back to work!
- Hey, Meroko take it off!
- Umm...let's see...
The key word is
"High School Girl"?
- What is this?
- Hey! Take it off!
- Are there any here?
- Hey! Do something!
I'm a little tired.
I wonder what would happen if
they found out I'm really 12?
Could they stop me from debuting?
If that happens, I won't
be able to see Eichi.
I have to do my best.
What made you want to
become a singer?
It's so that Eichi will find me...
That's right,
that's why I'm going to become a singer!
The only thing that doesn't change;
My dream that I've been holding.
How do I appear now
to those young eyes from the past?
Hey! Look above you!
Upon the wide night sky
I'll shine with all my might.
So hurry up and find the full moon.
Let's sing a song
I can bear any hardship
when I'm always together with you.
More and more—
I wanna be closer and closer to you
even though you are already here.
Many thanks for you!
U-Umm...
Who are you?
What?
We heard such a beautiful voice,
so we came over trying to figure out
what was going on.
Then we saw you singing your heart out,
we were so surprised.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
But, you really do have
a beautiful voice...
Hey, what are you doing
in a place like this?
What?! In a place like this?!
Could it be that you believe in
the "16-year-old's hill"?
The 16-year-old's hill?
Oh, no?
Darn...
We call this hill the "16-year-old hill,"
and it's thought that if you come here
on your 16th birthday,
you'll have a boyfriend that year!
And it's actually At-chan's birthday!
Yeah!
So that's why we came here today.
Boyfriend?!
Boyfriend...huh...
Then when I turn 16...
Oh...
That's right, my 16th birthday
won't ever come.
Oh!
Where did that girl go?
And I don't see any high school students.
Oh? This cell phone...
it's the newest model, isn't it?
Huh? What?
This one has games!
Games?
You don't know?
Yeah...
See!
Oh, yeah!
Once in a while, you'll bump into
high school students
who don't even know
how to use cell phones!
Could you be talking about me?!
Maybe you don't even know
how to text message?
Text message?
Just as I thought!
I had a hunch!
Maybe it's because I'm only 12...
Oh, by the way...
how old are you?
12.
What?!
Oh?!
NO way!
I thought you were around
the same age as us,
like 16 or something.
Oh! That's right!
You're right! I actually am 16!
You have to be.
There's no way that you could be 12.
Oh! Trying to fool us with your age!
What a relief!
They said that I look like a 16-year-old.
Hey, then do you want me
to teach you how to text?
Yeah!
Then let's exchange numbers.
Oh!
There she is!
More importantly,
I see high school students!
This isn't good!
Hey, you guys!
Oh?!
Move away from Mitsuki!
Meroko!
What are you doing?!
My job!
What?!
Ohh! What's going on?!
Meroko!
What are you doing in a place like this?
It says "High School Student"
as a key word!
It does?
That's why I'm trying to
get them to go away!
- Meroko...
- What is it?!
This!
Except those with loose socks.
Really?!
Oh... What was that wind just now?!
- Oh...that was scary!
- My hair is totally messy now!
Oops!
Oh, it's already time!
What, no way!
We have to get back now.
What? Oh, ok!
Then, see you again!
Oh, see you again!
Hope to see you soon!
I'll text message you sometime soon!
Ok!
Thanks...
Hey! I'm going to make
my debut as a singer soon!
What?!
Congrats!
Do your best!
We'll be rooting for you!
Thanks!
Oh! Because of you,
I got into trouble.
Hey! They told me that
I look like a 16-year-old!
Oh really?
I'm happy for you!
Hey, Takuto.
They told me that I look
like a 16-year-old!
Of course you do.
That's the way I cast the spell
on you so that you would.
I see. I get it now.
Where were you?!
I was just thinking of calling you!
Oh! The 16-year-old hill!
What's that?
We call this hill the "16-year-old hill,"
and it's thought that if
you come here on your 16th birthday,
you'll have a boyfriend that year!
That's what the local
high school girls were saying.
You're quite the funny girl!
That was pretty funny!
Hey! Let's start!
Y-Yes!
Now, let's do our best Mitsuki.
We're depending on you!
All right!
I don't have to act like
a 16-year-old!
I should just act like myself!
Yeah! You're looking good!
You're getting into it more!
Yes! Thank you very much!
Mitsuki looks beautiful.
Takuto! What are you ogling for?
What? You're the one who
said that she was beautiful!
Then, I realized that I didn't have
to force myself to act more mature.
You're right, I feel the same way
that I wouldn't want you
to stop being like yourself.
Ok!
But I should learn a little more.
Eichi would be disappointed
if I didn't know anything at all.
I wonder where Eichi is.
I want to see him soon.
Girls are so strange.
What?
Just when you think that
they're talking very innocently,
all of a sudden they look very mature...
R-Really?!
Oh, did I guess correctly?
What were you thinking of just now?
Mitsuki?
N-Nothing!
Oh! It's really nothing!
Whoa! What's with this girl?!
Where does she think she's taking me?
Takuto! You idiot! Why did you talk
when you're in your transformed state?
People can see you!
I had no choice! She said she was uneasy
and "can't record" all alone...
Well then, hurry up and escape!
That's true.
But hold on...this girl...
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Long Day in the Studio"
- Look forward to it!