"Episode 11
Yuuji, Shouko, and Childhood Memories!"
Where did I go wrong?
I wonder when I decided...
If I could do it all over again...
If I was given the chance...
Since the moment I saw his trembling
shoulders, that time, that place...
I want to set her free. It's wrong
for her to be held captive over this.
No... that's not it.
Because I know there's
more to it than that...
Because I found
something more important...
So...
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"There's a whiz kid in
Minazuki Elementary School."
I think it was several years
ago that the rumor went around.
That kid was indeed a little
smarter than the other kids.
On top of that,
he was serious and diligent.
Adults sang his praises
and had high hopes for him.
However...
You really are amazing, Yuuji.
What do you mean?
The teacher was raving about
your scores on the last prep tests,
saying, "That's our whiz kid."
That wasn't a big deal.
But you got better scores
than junior high students, right?
Yeah, I guess.
You really are amazing.
Those 6th graders who took the
test with you were biting their lips.
I made a mistake in the social
science test. If I didn't, I'd have been No. 1.
Around that time, I was always aiming high.
Everyone says it's a sure
thing that you'll get admitted to
Shimozuki Junior High on recommendation.
That's just a piece of cake for me...
...although the others don't stand a chance.
But that ego and attitude
of looking down on others
were completely intertwined.
Hm? Hey, keep working, Shouko.
Let's finish this quickly and go home.
But I want to talk with you.
No. I wanna go home.
I want to talk with you.
No.
I want to.
Listen, Yuuji. My boobs
are getting bigger these days.
Are you okay, Yuuji?
Where the hell did that come from?!
Since you were ignoring me,
I picked a topic that
boys might be interested in.
I-I'm not interested in stuff like that.
Well, I was interested.
Just work already.
I'll work, but I want to talk with you.
Why don't you talk with your friends?
Yep. That's why I'm talking now.
Geez...
Shouko didn't fit in with the class.
Her family lineage, academic
performance, athletic abilities...
...and her superior looks...
She was too blessed in every way.
I'm Shouko Kirishima.
--She's really cute.
--Whoa, amazing!
--She's pretty.
Hey, you go talk to her.
What? Why don't you go?
Ah, you like Kirishima, don't you?
That's not true!
Hey, isn't Kirishima
kinda trying to act cute?
Her family is rich, right?
So she's like a spoiled little princess?
She somehow seems hard to talk to.
Yeah.
As Shouko was like that,
maybe it couldn't have been helped
that she became attached to me...
...since I always treated everyone equally.
So it's already been 2 years
since you transferred to this school?
Yeah. I don't have many yet, but
I've been making friends little by little.
So school is more fun than it used to be.
What? School is fun?
When I'm at home, no one
plays with me or talks to me.
It's so big that I feel lonely, too.
So school is more fun.
Cry me a river.
I'm jealous that you get to
live in a big house like that.
Then would you like to come
hang out at my house some time?
No. It's 100 times more fun reading
books than hanging out with you.
That's mean.
Say whatever you wanna say.
Stick in the mud.
So what?
Pigheaded.
That's fine.
You...
You like me.
So you feel shy and
can't come hang out with me.
Why do you want me to
come to your place that badly?
Well...
What? Spit it out.
My grandfather often talks
about Seiryou Girls Academy, so...
Is that that famous school for rich girls?
Are you changing schools again?
Probably... since he often asks
me if I get picked on at school.
I see. So you wanna show your
friends to your family to fight back, huh?
I don't want to change schools.
I was finally able to make
some friends besides you.
Then, bring those friends to your house.
We're not that close yet.
I see...
Well, it's got nothing to do with me.
I treated everyone equally...
It was because I was
equally uninterested in anyone.
That was mean, Yuuji.
It wasn't mean.
It was.
It wasn't.
Yuuji...
I've got the biggest boobs in the class.
--Even so, it was probably enough for a girl
--L-Like I said, I'm not interested in that kind of stuff!
who was struggling with
loneliness.
"Stop"
Hey, Sakamoto.
Hey, don't ignore us!
Don't think that you can get away.
Don't get cocky.
Tsk.
This is why I wanted to go home sooner.
Huh? We can't hear you!
What do you want? I don't
have time to waste on you guys.
Shut up! Don't talk back to your seniors!
You sure are a smart
aleck for a 5th grader!
You've been lying in wait for me every
day since I beat your scores in the test.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Or... are you guys lonely
because you have no friends?
Aren't you the one without any friends?!
Don't get cocky just
because you're a little smart.
We're in 6th grade! Talk to us politely!
Talk politely? You guys are idiots, aren't you?
People talk politely to show respect to others.
What makes you think
I should respect idiots like you?
Wha...
We're 6th graders!
Ha! You did worse than me even
though you've been studying a year longer.
And yet, you tell me to
respect you? Don't make me laugh.
You guys should be talking to me politely.
What'd you say?!
Oh? You sure you wanna do it?
If something happens to me,
the teachers will know immediately...
...since I'm "special"...
If you get it, get out of my way.
Don't ever let me see your faces again.
He seriously pisses me off.
We'll definitely teach him a lesson.
But what're we gonna do?
Humph. If we can't touch him,
let's mess up his locker or something.
Yeah, then no one will know it's us.
Okay then. Let's teach him some manners.
Yeah, let's do it.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Yuuji.
You're home late today.
I did some work as a class rep,
so I couldn't come home early.
Oh I see.
I just assumed that you
were hanging out with Shouko.
Why would I hang out
with her? That's stupid.
But you two are friends, right?
No, we aren't.
Oh, come on... She'll be incredibly
gorgeous when she grows up.
Then, it'll be too late to think like
"I never thought she'd turn out to
be so pretty, like Mom is," you know.
I won't. Besides, it's not like you're pretty, Mom.
That's not nice.
I'll be late again tomorrow.
More work for your class tomorrow again?
No. I have a little something
I need to teach some 6th graders.
6th graders?
It's a long story.
I see.
By the way, Mom, I noticed you're
wearing an apron. Don't tell me...
I'm making your favorite, nikujaga, today.
[nikujaga: simmered meat and potatoes]
I'm peeling sweet potatoes and...
Why are you putting
sweet potatoes in nikujaga?!
Regular potatoes get soft and fall apart,
so I'm using a kind that won't soften.
Forget the potatoes falling apart,
the very idea of nikujaga is falling apart!
Oh well... At least it seems edible today.
Oh, and, I forgot to buy meat,
so it'll be meatless nikujaga.
That's just steamed sweet potatoes!
"Library"
If they couldn't touch me, they'd
do something to my belongings...
I provoked them because
I rather anticipated it.
I can't wait...
I brought the things I don't
want them to touch here.
I was gonna kill time until
those 6th graders made their move.
Once they started doing stuff to
my belongings, I'd go get a teacher.
Now, maybe I'll read the
book I started the other day.
Around then, I believed that I was a
hero since I was better than the others.
Hm? Come to think of it,
Shouko didn't follow me around today.
"Things that happened today"
"Chores: Kirishima"
Idiot Test.
Around that time, I was
always following Yuuji around.
Even though his attitude
towards me was cold,
he treated me equally
when no one else did, so...
I wonder if Yuuji is still around...
So I liked to be around Yuuji.
Dammit! They're not here, either.
He's so sneaky!
Could it be that someone
else has hidden his shoes?
That's possible. Other
people pick on him, too.
Oh well, then let's find something else.
"Sakamoto"
Hey, what should we write?
How about, "I cheat on all my tests"?
That's good!
Uhm...
Uhm... th-those're...
What do you want?
Th-Those're Yuuji's...
P-Please don't mess with them.
Huh? This is none of
your business. Just beat it!
But Yuuji is my friend.
"If Yuuji hears this, he may not like it..."
So I thought, but...
It is my business!
So he had a friend?
On top of that, it's a girl!
Hey, let's just let her be and
take care of this stuff already.
Yeah.
Let's do it real good.
Stop it!
Wh-What?! Stay out of our way!
I thought "Yuuji might get taken
aback, and say I'm not his friend."
Don't!
Enough already!
Ah, you!
Move! You're in our way!
No!
Quit getting in our way!
Even still, I...
No!
Hey, are you okay?
Ah...
Ah! What're you gonna
do about my clothes?!
I'm so pissed!
Don't...
It's too late.
Now... I wonder if they fell into the trap.
--You jerk!
--All right! They're doing it.
What're you doing?!
Wh-What the hell? Why is Shouko...
Don't tell me Shouko...
It was so obvious why
Shouko was dragged into it.
I-I have to save her.
That's right... just like the
hero I've always wanted to be...
After all, those guys are foolish
idiots and I'm a smart, special person.
We're in different leagues.
I don't have to hesitate.
I'll be fine. Don't be scared.
Guys like them... are no big deal.
There are three of them.
It's obvious how it'll turn out.
That's right! I'll go get a teache--
What about Shouko?
If the teacher tells her
parents that she got picked on...
Shouko will be forced
to change schools...?
That has nothing to do
with me! What else can I do?!
"What can you do?!"
Don't you actually know what to do?
All I wanted was to make
them regret what they did.
Then pretend that you saw nothing.
Th-There's no way I can do that!
No matter what you choose,
you won't stay unharmed.
You'll be hurt in one
way or another for sure.
Even so, you've gotta
do what you've gotta do.
But they're 6th graders,
and there are three of them!
There's no way I can beat them!
Who's fault is it that this is happening?
But...
Well, I guess getting beat up is scary, huh?
Of course it is!
I thought you were a hero!
A hero wouldn't hesitate.
Even if he knew he was going to lose,
in order to save someone, he'd...
Shut up! That stuff happens
only in manga and anime!
But you've been looking down
on those guys all this time, right?
That's because their scores were--
It's tough to be smart, huh?
You're desperately making
excuses and trying to find a way out.
Then, are you saying
it's better to be an idiot?
Yeah...
An idiot who can jump in
without thinking might be
a lot cooler than you are right now.
Why...? Why is this happening?
Why do I have to be the one to suffer?!
I'm not at fault at all.
They're the ones at fault!
And Shouko too, for acting rashly! Right?!
And yet...
Why?!
That's right... Shouko should call for help.
That's right. Shouko
should say, "Somebody, help!"
Then, even if the teachers find
this out and she has to change schools,
it'll be her own responsibility, right?
It won't be my fault.
Yeah, that works.
Say it, Shouko. Say, "Help!"
Changing schools is better
than being picked on, right?
Say it. Say it already!
Call for help! Say it, Shouko!
Say, "Help!" Say it! Say it! Say it! Say it!
No! I don't want to change schools!
Why...?
Y... Y-Y-Y-You jerks!
What the hell are you doing?!
Yuu... ji...
Th-There are some things
that no one should do!
Y-You guys are so low!
Sakamoto...
Tsk, so Sakamoto himself has shown up.
L-Let's go home, Shouko.
Hey! Hold it, Sakamoto.
Are you running away?
Yuuji...
You'd at least let Shouko go home, right?
But...
Just go!
I'll go get a--
You dummy! Just go on home already!
You'll be in my way if you stay!
Okay. I'll go on home.
On that day, I came to
realize how immature I was.
I felt miserable, pitiful,
and embarrassed about it.
After seeing Yuuji's trembling shoulders,
I was really frustrated with
myself for not being able to help him.
I created a reason for
Shouko to get the wrong idea.
It was my responsibility and a
mistake that I have to make up for.
No... That's not it, Yuuji.
That wasn't all.
I...
Welcome home, Yuuji.
Your school called. Did something happen?
No... Nothing happened.
There's no way nothing happened, right?
You fought until you ended up like that.
I slugged them because they ticked me off.
Yuuji, is that really all?
Stop pestering me!
I slugged them because they
ticked me off! That's all there is to it!
Because they ticked you off, huh?
Mrs. Sakamoto...
I'm sorry. Because Yuuji protected me, he got...
Don't worry. You told me the truth earlier, so...
But as it stands, he'll become the bad one.
The recommendation for
Shimozuki Junior High will also be...
That's okay, Shouko.
Yuuji isn't just smart. He became
a boy who can protect someone...
I'm very happy about it.
Say, Mrs. Sakamoto...
What is it, Shouko?
When I grow up...
...I'll marry Yuuji.
My, aren't you the hasty one!
I'll be sure to make him happy.
That's a line that Yuuji
should say to you, Shouko.
I made a mistake.
Then, I'll support you so that
he'll say that to you one day.
Really?
Yes, really... as long as you
don't turn sour on him, of course.
It'll be fine...
...because...
...I'm sure I'll like him forever.
Even now I can tell when it was
(My heart beats fast when I see her!)
It's not that I've forgotten, I remember
I acted tough and ignored her
(My heart beats fast when I see her!)
Don't look at me like that, I get the picture
Man, it's tough!
Today, I really have to go (no matter what)
I'm gonna lose this battle so I don't
want you to see (but I'm gonna win)
Good job, I say, with my thumbs up
I won't lose! I'm always pushing ahead!
(Hi-ho Let's go!!) Because I've got you
(Hi-ho Let's go!!) I can go
(Hi-ho Let's go!!) I get fired up
Day after day, you're always supporting me
My feelings grow for you each year,
but I'm too stubborn to say it
Words that history will forget
but will remain in your heart...
Just please, let me say
those amazing words to you
Question 12.
What do you call the situation
where a mysterious group
acts as if they own the place?
Guys who are popular
with girls are our enemies!
I'm referring to you guys.
Next episode!
"Idiots, Clownery, and Requiem!"
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!
Illustration: Mako Aboshi"