Seconds!
Okay!
That's not how it's supposed to be!
Huh?
Why have you even been eating breakfast at my house in the first place?!
And why do you just let her in?!
No reason...
And Taiga-chan is small, so she doesn't take up much room anyway.
Plus, the meals taste better when we all eat together.
Hurry up and serve me.
I cooked three cups...
How much are you going to eat?!
I-I'm sorry.
Gosh,
are you planning on making your pet go bald from stress?
Don't make it any more ugly than it already is.
Don't call her ugly!
Really!  They say that pets look like their owners.
You...
You ingrate!
I'm the one who makes you your breakfast and your lunch too!
You're so noisy, you mongrel.
Again?!  Give me back that lunch box!
Return my kind feelings!
Shut up and rot.
Hey...hey wait, Aisaka!
Since that midnight attack, Aisaka Taiga started showing up at our house more frequently.
I said wait!
And...
More importantly, when we get to school, remember what you need to do.
About the Kitamura-kun matter...
...make sure you...
...figure it out.
You promised that you would work for me like a dog!
...this is the way things have become.
If by any chance it doesn't go well...
Minori!
Taiga, you're late tod-
Good, you're full of energy as always.
Good morning, Minori.
Huh?  You're kidding...what?!
Huh?!
Two-shot: An outdated term referring to a man and woman being alone together.
Sorry, I didn't know that Taiga and Takasu-kun were in a two-shot, walk-to-school-together relationship.
No, it's not like that!
No one says "two-shot" anymore.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Oh, that's true...then nowadays...
I'm so confused that I can't remember what people say now!
Oh, I've got it, it's "avec".
"Avec" is French for "with".
No, I'm trying to say it isn't like that!
Aisaka and I just happened to run into each other over there.
Right, Aisa-
Oh, it was just coincidence.
I guess his house is close by.
Well then, see you later, Takasu-kun!
So, on TV last night...
I see how it is.
If I want to get together with Kushieda, first I need to hook up Aisaka with Kitamura.
That's a pretty good deal!
Okay now, that ends the stretching.
Now, we are going to have you pair up with a partner and practice-
Hey Aisaka, let's be partners.
Alright Takasu-kun, let's partner up.
...passing balls.
What's this?  Takasu and Aisaka, you're both spirited today!
Taiga?
What...what is this?
The plan is simple.
I will very gently hit Kitamura's partner with the ball.
And then...
You will overreact, make a scene, and insist on taking that person to the school infirmary.
And if that works, Aisaka and Kitamura will have to pair up.
Maruo.  Partner up with me.
Suehiro Maruo is a famous manga artist.
Sure!  I don't mind, but stop calling me that.
But it suits you well...
Wait...
H-Hey Kitamura-kun is with a weird lady!
What is the meaning of this?!
M-My stomach...
Kushieda!  Want to do it with me?
Okay, sure, let's do it.
Even Kushieda...
Oh well, the plan is still on!
What...but...you...?
We will not discriminate between genders.
Remember to keep the form of your upper ar-
Oh, Aida, what's wrong?
Without using the thumbs, throw it...
It's not reaching me, Kushieda.
It is a long, difficult journey to master passing the ball.
Huh?!
It's okay, only the people that can follow along...
That...
Hey, pass!
Hey hey hey hey!
Pass pass pass pass!
Ready, Maruo?
Yeah.
Nice energy!
What are you talking about, Maruo...?
Hey, pass!
Pass?!
At a girl...
Pass!
I'm sorry, Kihara, I'll pay you back later.
I'm sorry, Maruo.
What...what happened?
Takasu-kun knocked over Palm-sized Tiger.
Crap.
A palm-sized tiger that bites regardless of the person...
...but works so hard, to the point of looking bad.
It's not like I feel unwilling to motivate her.
Got it?  Make sure to give them to him casually.
Don't be so heavy and emotional all of a sudden.
Okay, I need to be light and carefree.
Lightly, craftily, and carelessly.
Let's go.
Wasn't Kitamura here?
Oh, Kitamura said he had something to do so he went over to the B-
T-Takasu-kun...he was just there so he can't be f-far.
Oh look, he's over there.
Let's chase him.
Okay.
What?!
Move, move, move!
It's Takasu!
She's fast.
She can probably catch up to him.
Ryuji!
Where are the cookies?
Oops...
Ouch...as expected, I have a lump.
Did you find them?
Were they whole?
Oh...I see.
Hey.
I wonder if I am a klutz?
She didn't realize that she was...
I wrote a love letter and I put it in the wrong bag.
I went in for a fight and I passed out from hunger.
I played basketball and I got hit square in the face.
I tried to give him cookies, and I tripped and fell,
and dropped them.
Hey hey, there's more isn't it?
Like forgetting to include the actual letter into the love letter envelope.
That's right...
Give me one of those.
H-Hey...no...they're all crumbs...and...
Delicious!
They're made properly.
That's just too bad.
Let's work towards the next opportunity we get.
I saw them for sure,
the two of them buying green onions and white radishes, are they practically a married couple?
Those two come out of the same apartment in the morning,
and they really reek of secrets...!
Those two were even feeding each other handmade cookies!  Like, "Open up," and, "Ahhh..."
Really, really?!
That can't be true.
Hey Minori, so how about your friend?
What's this?
Hey, hurry up and go in!
Ooo!
Ooo?
Can I have a moment?
The sunshine is cozy...
What happened to Kushieda-san?
I don't know.
Takasu-kun.
Yes?!
Me?
Please take care of Taiga!
Huh?
Taiga is my precious and dear friend!
Please, please make her happy!
Wait, Kushieda, are you-
Happiness?
Oh, that's how it is.
That's great news, guys.
Kitamura...why are you up there?
I noticed that you two were together a lot, but come to think of it, you're a matching pair!
Aisaka!
Get  a hold of yourself!
You, stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you ever make Taiga cry, I will never forgive you!
Kushieda...
I'm sorry...
I latched onto you and Minori got the wrong idea.
No...well, that's-
Your place...
felt really comfortable.
I didn't really get along with my parents,
so when I said that I wanted to leave the house
I was allotted that apartment.
Although I knew they were those kind of parents...
Those cookies were salty, weren't they?
When I saw them in crumbs, I got kind of sad so I tried some.
What were those?!  They were awful!
And still you ate the whole bag, and you even lied about it.
For a mongrel, you use too much energy on things.  You're going to go bald.
You don't need to worry about that.
Hey Ryuji, do you feel troubled thinking about Minori too?
Yeah.
Of...course.
Aisaka?
Why doesn't anyone understand?
We're both so worried about things,
but why doesn't anyone realize it?
Really...everyone, everyone, everyone, everyone!
It makes me furious!
Makes me furious!
What the hell is a palm-sized tiger?!
I'm not alright, at all!
Stupid Minori!
Stupid Kitamura-kun!
Why won't you listen to me?!
Papa and Mama and everyone!
You aren't willing to try and understand me...
I'm with you, here.
Sorry I'm strong!
And that I look like a delinquent!
Sorry that I have a weird name!
Sorry that I have scary eyes!
You...alright?
Ryuji, isn't this pole sort of tilted?
Huh, there's no wa-
It's tilted?!
I told you!
We won, we won!
Okay, I've decided.
Tomorrow I am going to confess my love to Kitamura-kun.
And I will end it.
End?
Your service to me as a dog ends now.
Starting tomorrow, we'll just be two classmates living next door to each other.
Nothing more than that.
Bye bye, Takasu-kun.
Ryu-chan...isn't today's breakfast kind of rushed?
I mean, I like canned mackerel, but...
I wonder if Taiga-chan is still sleeping...
Who knows?
Ryu-chan, did you have a fight?
No, we didn't.
It's so boring, isn't it?
H-Hey...
Is this...
T-Takasu...we're sorry we spread weird rumors about you.
Aisaka-san got mad at us.
"There's nothing going on between me and Ryuji," and
"Ryuji is not a delinquent."
Then she went into a rage...
Still, Palm-sized Tiger is dreadful.
But even I told you that Takasu wasn't scary.
Huh, when?!
Still, we need to clean all of this up.
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun, I'm sorry.
What?  Why?
Taiga told me that...
...she would never date you,
and that it was all a misconception.
She wanted me, at least, to understand that.
That girl has a serious, rather fierce expression,
but that is...
That is...
Hey, Takasu-kun...
Takasu-kun!
What is she planning to do...?
Isn't she going to confess to Kitamura today?
She shouldn't be worrying about anyone else.
"Starting tomorrow, we'll just be two classmates living next door to each other, and nothing more."
Nothing more, huh...
Kitamura-kun!
Kitamura-kun, I...so that, um...that, uh...
Hey, hey, this early?  If this goes badly, the whole day will be ruined.
Wait a second.  I can see where this conversation is headed.
But before that, clarify one thing for me.
You're not going out with Takasu?
That was Minori's misunderstanding.
Takasu-kun and I have nothing going on.
You don't like Takasu?
Nothing like that.
We just happened to live in the same neighborhood...it's nothing about liking him.
Then do you hate him?
I...don't hate him.
But it's different.  It's not like that.
Takasu-kun...well, he, um...fried rice!
Ryuji made me some delicious fried rice.
He comforted me, and even lied to encourage me.
He stayed with me.  Because Ryuji was there...because Ryuji was there for me...
...is how I can even have the courage to say this now.
I like you, Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, you're amazing.
Is that so?  Well, it's okay.
I think you were able to properly convey your feelings.
Kitamura-kun...
Do you remember last year, Aisaka?
Yeah.
You've really changed since then, and now you make a lot more interesting expressions.
I-Interesting expressions?
When you were with Takasu, you made some really interesting expressions.
Takasu is a very nice guy.
I think you are really an amazing girl for seeing him the way that you did.
Like just now...wait, what did I just say?
I'm only saying that I'm glad you were able to become friends with Takasu.
W-W-Wait, this has nothing to do with Ryuji!
Is my expression really that interesting?!
N-N-N-No, and the edge...what is the edge, wait, what, hey....did I say I liked you properly?
It's alright, Aisaka.
It's alright.
What is?!  I don't even know what I said!
It's okay.
I think from now on we will be able to become really good friends.
I'm not talking about being friends.  I'm confessing my love.
Friends...?
That's right, friends.
Oh, going to be late for homeroom.
Aisaka, you'd better hurry too!
I thought you would cry.
Y-Y-You, why are you here...you were w-watching?!
Not on purpose.
Even if it was not on purpose...
Never mind.  What are you going to do?
I'm going home.
Oh, if so I’ll go cook you something.
I mean you haven't had breakfast yet, right?  Did you eat properly last night?
You probably went to the convenience sto-
Stop it!
Why...if you do something like that, then everyone would be confused again.
I don't need any more of that!
I don't know either,
but I can't just leave you alone!
So I'm saying enough is enough.
You're not my dog anymore!
Right...that's right.  I'm not a dog anymore.
I'm a dragon!
That is why I can stay by your side.
Taiga!
Taiga?
Since ancient times, the dragon has been the worthy counterpart to the tiger.
I will become a dragon,
and as a dragon, I will stand beside the tiger.
Don't let it get to your head.  Know your place!
You...!
Hey!
Hurry up, I'm hungry!
Also, we need to plan our next strategy.
A little setback like this is not going to make me give up Kitamura-kun!
That means...
I don't care if you are a dog or a dragon.
You said you would stay by my side, so you better start working your tail off for me, Ryuji.
So we've reconciled, huh?
Hey, hurry up!
Yes, yes.
He called me Taiga...!
Club Activities Princess - Kushieda.
Princess of Services - Kushieda.
Uh, you are Kushieda.
Whenever, wherever,
sparkling all around.
Hit in one strike!