Ahem!
In Japan, when the rainy season comes,
and everything's all damp and gloomy,
a moment's rest can lead to a tenacious black mold infestation!
Normal bathrooms like this are particularly humid,
making them primo spots for mold hotbeds!
It's our duty to take this challenge head on,
and clean this place 'til it shines!
Hey, can you guys listen for once?
Boasting wastes time. I've no use for it.
We've got to finish cleaning before Master's bathtime.
I'm back!
This vinegar will take down the really clingy mold!
Just a piece of grandmotherly wisd—uaah!
What're ya doin', Lene?
I-I'm so sorry...
What happened, girls?
Are you all right?
Oh, you're so clumsy, Lene.
That's cold, Lene!
Master's always letting you off with the "you're so clumsy" shtick!
When you mixed detergent into Master's ramen,
when you blew up an egg in the microwave,
when you got sucked into the vacuum cleaner and got all the dust we'd just cleaned everywhere,
every single time,
Master just called you clumsy and laughed it off!
Meanwhile, I'm workin' my screw holes off, and I get jack in return!
Maybe it seems that way...
but I'm giving it my all, too.
If you were giving it your all, everything'd be just peachy!
Honestly, you just get in the way.
You don't have to say it like that...
H-Hey, let's stop fighting and make up!
You're sisters, so...
We're just configured that way!
It's not like we're real sisters.
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
It's a Race! One Lap Around the Park!
Once we're out of the rainy season, we'll be close to summer vacation.
It's summer, so we should go to the beach!
I would prefer the mountains.
I have long been interested in guerrilla warfare.
Is that a summer thing where you're from?
No matter where we go, it'll cost money.
I'll just have to keep working and saving.
Are you still fighting?
You can always make up...
Whatcha lookin' at all alone?
N-Nothing at all!
Hm? What're you doing?
You don't want to sleep next to me that much?
I-It's not that!
I'll be waking up early tomorrow,
so I don't want to disturb you when I do.
What are you waking up early for?
Um, well...
Good night!
Suspicious.
She's definitely up to something.
What's this?
Hey!
Are you joining the race too?
Huh? A race?
That!
Shinki-1 Grand Prix
It's that time of year again, folks!
The one and only event made by Shinkis, for Shinkis!
The Shinki-1 Grand Prix!
I'm your host, Mary Takigawa Celes!
And to help explain the rules, we have the tournament's committee head, the lovely Ia!
It's a pleasure to be here.
We have some truly delightful prizes in store this year.
That we do! Talk about a grand prize!
We've got a five-day, four-night trip to Okinawa for you and your master!
I see!
Lene's trying to show us up and give a present to Master!
Two can play at that game...
Lene and Ines are gone...
Strarf too?
Gone
to
work.
Work?
Think you can beat us in speed?
Our magnificent driving skills shall grant us victory!
You two are bike-model Shinkis, so why are you in karts?
What's with the getup, Ines?
I-I'm not Ines!
I am but a nameless, masked Shinki who fights for her Master!
Well, suit yourself.
I've got this in the bag anyway.
There's an Okinawa trip with Master on the line,
so I'm gonna win this no matter what!
Hmph! That's my line...
I won't lose.
And they're off! Every Shinki's crossing the starting line!
Now then, Ms. Ia, give us the course overview one more time.
Gladly!
There are a number of checkpoints that all make a lap around the park,
and following them all will bring you right back here!
It doesn't matter if you take detours, as long as you pass the checkpoints!
Ah! The racers have suddenly fallen into a pit hole!
And where're the fuckers that pulled this shit?
You've fallen for our trap, dummies!
We'll be taking the prize in a doggy bag!
Let's go, Mini Meowchines!
And to top it it off, those machines are breaking the rules!
Oh my, what a shocker!
Such an ugly tactic...
Let's do this fair and square!
Wowzers! It looks like Ach and Yda are making a comeback in Trike mode!
Well if that's how we're playing,
it looks like the Tire form I prepared will come in handy!
It looks like she's forcing a transformation out of her armor!
I'm gonna puke...
This race is coming apart at the seams!
Got any commentary for us, Ms. Ia?
There's not much we can do, right?
So from here on, let's change the rules a bit.
As long as you have tires, it's legal to ride!
And there you have it.
So move those asses, you fuckin' worms!
Wait, hold up! You're going alone?
Shoot! The jig's up!
You can't give up, Masked Shinki!
We can get through this together!
Where did everyone go?
Take what you want.
As long as we can find a toy with tires in here...
Ooh, found something!
See ya later!
Oh, um, I'll catch up...
The mini car is one thing, but how do we take a wagon,
Ms. Ia?
As long as it's got tires, what's the problem?
Lene?
Ann, perfect timing!
Lend me your armor, please!
Here's a reward!
I've got to get going!
Um...
Tamami and Potchi have reached the refueling station with a huge lead!
Let's lap up all of these before the other rats get here!
These are normal oil Jellycans.
However, we prepared an extremely rare strawberry-flavored can just for today's race!
I-I'm stuffed...
Let's give 'em these special Jellycans as a present!
She's switching the Jellycans with nitro-flavored cans!
Is this legal, Ms. Ia?
It livens up the race, so why not?
Wait a moment, Ach! If you drink that...
I'm goin' berserk!
Ach!
I must defeat this enemy of ours!
Ach, what's wrong?
My brakes got done in.
That's perfect! You gotta lend me that umbrella!
What's she planning to use an umbrella for, Ms. Ia?
Color coordination?
Well folks, when it rains, it pours!
This puts our racers at a steep disadvantage!
I don't care how caked in mud you fuckers get, just race!
Shoot...
I can't catch up like this...
Ann!
Hm? Ines?
Great timing! Ann, lend me that leaf!
Meanie.
A leaf surfboard!
Is this legal, Ms. Ia?
It may not have wheels, but she's still riding it, so why not?
Now, back to Tamami and Potchi at the head of the pack!
They just cleared a 90 degree turn with ease!
But Yda's gaining from behind!
She's really dogging us!
She won't claw her way up that easily!
They're neck and neck!
It's a dead heat, folks!
Yda springs into first!
Following behind are Ach and the joke rac—
er, I mean Kurara, and they're catching up fast!
The real battle begins now!
Can you keep up with my speed?
Ach's putting the pedal to the metal and catching up on the second place Tamami!
You shouldn't get too claws...
Oh, she meant to use the umbrella as an air brake!
The joke racer got caught in a pile-up and blew out!
That's feline retribution!
Tamami and Potchi are gaining on Yda!
Shoot! She's fast!
Well, how's she gonna like these apples?
You're not supposed to dodge them!
Okinawa!
Unbelievable! It's the Masked Shinki!
See you at the finish line!
Crap!
We're finally at the race's last course, the battlefield!
Will Lene hold on to her lead?
It looks like Yda's back, and she's catching up!
Or so it seems, but it's actually the Masked Shinki wearing Yda's armor!
The one to give Master that Okinawa vacation...
will be me!
Oh my! But the final battle starts here,
with the final obstacle of the race!
Strarf?!
Why? Are you trying to show us up too?
Wrong.
I was simply hired by the race's executive committee to act as a the final obstacle!
C'mon, go easy on me!
I'll hold her off!
You go on ahead, Ines!
Lene, you knew?
Just hurry!
Lene!
Ines!
I don't want to hear you say I owe you one.
That's a Strarf model for you!
She was definitely worth the huge asking price!
Fight! Kill! Bathe in their blood!
Oh my!
It's the joke racer, Kurara!
You shittin' me?
She's holding the steering wheel, so it just barely counts!
This isn't even a race anymore! It's a marathon!
The Shinki who's shaken off every ounce of misfortune in her way is running fiercely! Run!
And...
Goal!
That was a total mess.
And we were so close to getting Master that Okinawa vacation, too...
It's quite a shame.
What're you all smiles over?
You didn't do a thing in the end.
I apologize.
But I didn't enter the race for Master's sake.
I did it for this.
Strawberry flavored... Jellycan?
They offered this as a reward for staying the course, so I thought I'd get one for you.
Why?
Well... because you love strawberry Jellycans.
We used to split these in half and share them all the time.
So I...
Lene...
That's right, we used to split these in half between ourselves.
But the half she gave me was always a little bigger...
Sis...
Sister?
No, I mean, Lene!
It's not like we're real sisters...
Morning...
What's up with you three?
Not a thing!
Good morning, Master!
Master, you slept in! It's already past noon!
Hm? Hey, where's Ann?
Master!
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Look at this!
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
I got us an Okinawa vacation!
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Shopping District Lottery
Special Prize
Okinawa Vacation
Wh-Wha? Why?
Well, I took the mini car Ines left behind, and just started trading up!
Special prize, Okinawa vacation! You hit the jackpot!
Yahoo!
And that's how it happened!
Ann...
Hm? What's wrong?
Nah, forget it.
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Finally, summer vacation! I've waited forever to hit those Okinawan beaches!
I hear there are Okinawa-candy flavored Jellycans there!
Hold on, are we all waterproofed enough?
Our standard water protection is fine.
This is the ocean, so that's not gonna cut it!
Don't worry, this is why we have Swimsuit Armor!
Next time
"The Seaside Swimsuit Armor"
Next time on Busou Shinki:
The Seaside Swimsuit Armor.
Hey Strarf, what kind of Swimsuit Armor will you wear?
Ah, I...
You're wearing that?
Next time, Strarf wears a revealing seashell swimsuit!
I absolutely will not!