All performances are finished!
Geez, stop moving!
You don't need to...
This has to be done.
It's a beauty contest.
It's a festival dedicated to beauty.
How cute do you think you are?
In the end, her father couldn't make it to the pro wrestling show.
Kushieda, who had always cheered for Taiga, didn't come backstage.
This is 2-C, right?
You have twenty minutes until the meet up.
Crap!
I'm a host, so I still have to prepare for that!
Takasu-kun, how's the clothing going?
Oh, I'm done with it.
I just modified Taiga's dress a little bit.
It looks good, Takasu-kun!
R-Really?
The image I aimed for was Juliet's type of dress, an empire silhouette.
It's light and elegant...
Takasu-kun is dangerous.
It's not his face, but it's still a bit scary...
There some other props.
Taiga, do you want to try it-
Are you still waiting for your dad?
He won't be coming at a time like this.
I'm not waiting for him.
He's probably late because of his job,
so he's going to get me something to make up for it.
Anyway, I think your lines should be modified a bit.
There's no need to change them.
They're fine as they are.
But you're...
Kawashima-san, it's almost time!
Sorry, I'm coming right now!
So is it really all right?
You're annoying.
I see, that's fine with me.
Hey, what do you mean by lines?
It's nothing.
It's time to get changed.
Takasu-kun, please go outside.
S-Sure...
Aisaka-san, let's get going.
Yeah.
I can't just stand by and watch a friend get hurt.
Taiga's father...
You'll come for sure, right?
Regardless of how late you are,
you'll rush here, right?
That has to be it, because that's what it means to be a father.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
You guys must've waited a long time!
The Miss Oohashi Contest is about to begin!
Oohashi High School Cultural
Festival (Finale)
Ami-chan! Ami, Ami!
Ami, Ami, Ami is the best!
Everyone, quiet down.
I'll punish you if you don't.
So quiet down,
you bunch of worthless fools!
A pig who can't fly is merely a pig!
Just kidding!
Even though she says she's just the host,
all the attention is focused on her.
Let's begin now.
Entry number one, Mitsui Yuriko from class 1-A!
W-Welcome back, M-Master!
Isn't she a cute maid?
You're going for the look of a Victorian maid, correct?
Y-Yes!
Thank you very much!
No one is listening at all...
Now let me introduce our next contestant!
She's also a maid, but she has a great smile.
Entry number two...
A text message?
You've got to be kidding...
Could you please relay this to Taiga for me?
Tell her I have to leave for a bit due to my job.
Something has come up,
so we can't live together.
Please give my apologies to my princess. Thanks.
Why did I believe him?
I...
I believed that this was a good thing, and I supported Taiga,
but honestly, somewhere inside me, I felt lonely.
Taiga's father appeared and caused us to drift apart.
She couldn't look at the useless me.
What the hell is that?
Don't joke around.
This is it...
It was all because I was selfish...
I...
Takasu, are you all right?
You don't look too good.
Taka-chan?
How should I face Taiga?
What expression should I put on?
Everyone, the wait is over!
You're all familiar with the Palmtop Tiger from 2-C, right?
Here comes Aisaka Taiga-san!
No way...
Is she the Palmtop Tiger?
Amazing...
She's cute.
Um...
Today, in this auditorium,
Aisaka-san's father is here to cheer for her.
The lines they were talking about are...
If it's possible, Aisaka's father, please come up and say something!
Uh...
He didn't come, right?
Next, next!
Tai-
H-Hey, Aisaka-san?
Are you okay, Aisaka-san?
Hey, the delinquent, Takasu, is cheering for his mate.
Actually, the Palmtop Tiger is pretty cute.
All right! The Palmtop Tiger is the best!
But she's super clumsy!
Don't worry about your father!
He-
Who the hell cares about fathers?!
Chop them up and throw them into a mor... mor... morgue!
It's showtime.
Hey, give me that!
O-Okay!
Zip it up!
Um...
Don't pick it up!
Open it!
O-Okay!
I couldn't do anything for her.
This year's Miss Oohashi is...
Aisaka Taiga-san!
You're amazing, Taiga!
Ah...
Thanks to the praise from everyone, she...
No, that's not it!
Isn't she...
...alone?
Takasu?
I have to go.
I absolutely have to go.
Perhaps it won't work, but...
...even if that's the case...
What's going on?
It's pitch black!
What is this?
Now that the beauty contest is over,
it's time for the Mister contest!
The method of examination will be this:
Mr. Lucky Guy!
Mister?
Lucky Guy?
What's that?
A course has been laid out on the campus.
At any rate, just run.
Whoever comes in first will be the winner of the Mister contest!
A race during the cultural festival?
I don't feel like it...
By the way, I should mention what Mr. Lucky Guy will win.
You will be able to crown this year's Miss
Oohashi with this tiara and dance with her,
and you'll also get the notes from all my classes;
the class time memos, questions,
and the answers to the tests from these past three years.
The president's notes?!
Dancing with Taiga?!
This is impossible.
I want it!
Taiga...
I don't want the prizes.
I don't care about being Mr. Lucky Guy.
Anyway, no matter how,
Everyone, don't get hurt.
no matter who, no matter what,
Got it?
I have to...
I'm scared.
Move!
Crap, the delinquent!
He'll kill us.
On your marks...
Get set...
...get back to Taiga's side.
A lap around the school!
Run! Run! Run with all you've got!
Yeah! Takasu's down!
All right, it's our chance!
How can I...
...lose to them?!
They're here!
Go! Go!
Takasu's back!
That's right, I...
I'm sorry!
That hurt!
Damn it!
Get out of my way!
Oh, Takasu-kun!
Seriously?
That's cheating!
Why is he trying so hard?
Shut up!
I have my reasons, so mind your own business!
There's no way...
...I'm going to lose!
Why did you let him through?
You did too!
They're here!
The ones that left first are back.
Wow! It's the delinquent Takasu!
Ryuuji...
Mi-
Kushieda?
Why is there a girl?
Is that all right?
It's fine! Girls can participate too!
Takasu-kun, didn't you examine him carefully when you met him?!
Did your eyes not see him clearly?!
She was right. I missed everything.
He just gives her money every month and then ignores her.
He doesn't think about what Taiga wants and just takes her to random places.
He breaks his promise and sends
a text message as an apology...
He has never cared about Taiga.
But...
...I didn't see through him.
I'm so stupid!
Ryuuji...
Minorin...
Damn it!
The spirit of the track team!
Kushieda!
What are you doing to a girl?!
Aren't you men?!
Kushieda-senpai, take this!
All right!
Takasu-kun, go!
Run for Taiga's sake!
What are you-
This is our chance!
I'll take you all down!
Attack!
Kushi-
Go!
Faster than everyone else...
Faster than me...!
You guys don't have to worry about me, you know.
You can see it, right?
Even if I'm alone, I can stand up again.
That's why...
It's all right.
You don't have to worry about me.
I can stand up again all by myself.
Even if I'm all alone,
I will survive.
Our class! The beauty contest and the title of Mr. Lucky Guy!
Our class has won both of them!
The cultural festival was a huge success.
Yes, it's your last cultural festival.
I'm glad I could become the student council president of this school.
It was great being with you guys.
I still have some private matters to deal with.
Go and have fun, Kitamura.
But...
You're the reason the cultural festival was such a success.
A-All right, I'll go!
I shouldn't have cared about that guy from the beginning.
He doesn't matter at all.
But Taiga, you-
Putting that aside, you were so close to Minorin.
When did you two make up?
Why you...
Minorin!
Taiga, so you're here.
Minorin! Minorin! Minorin! I love you so much!
All right, I get it, I get it.
Taiga, you look so cute.
That tiara looks good on you.
That's because you put it on for me.
Takasu-kun did too, right?
I don't know. I didn't see it. I didn't hear it.
Oh, the Stupid Chihuahua is flirting again!
Ami-chan, please...
Ami!
Hey, what are you doing?
It was exactly a year ago.
Taiga's father showed up exactly the same way.
I was really happy that they could finally live with each other,
but in the end it was no different.
Her father just suddenly disappeared...
I'm sorry, Takasu-kun.
W-Why?
I should be the one apologising!
No, it should be me.
I knew her father's true nature, but I didn't tell you about it.
Taiga didn't say anything to me.
I really treasure Taiga.
That's why I was jealous of you.
Why didn't Taiga say anything?
She knew I'd get mad.
Taiga doesn't want people to think badly of her father.
That's why, since this day last year,
Taiga hasn't told me a single thing about her family.
Sheesh...
Where did the Stupid Chihuahua go?
Aisaka.
Are you alone?
If you don't mind, will you dance with me?
I guess that's a no, since I'm not the Lucky Guy.
Again...
Why are you always...
Aisaka.
It's nothing.
Thank you.
Then...
How do you dance?
We hold hands and look at each other,
then we go in circles until we get tired.
That's it.
Perhaps I like girls more?
Huh?!
I have this thought...
I-I'm not so sure...
You're probably right.
I'm speaking normally?
What are you doing, Taka-chan?
You're such a party pooper!
We should have fun together, because our class is the best class!
That's right, you two should come too!
Taiga?
All right, let's dance on the night of the cultural festival!
Tonight is a special night.
A lot of emotions are mixing together.
When I try to laugh, my heart hurts a little.
When this night ends,
I think...
...everything will be all right.
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
The Palmtop Tiger of Happiness
Everyone in front of the T.V.,
this is the duel of destiny.
I will activate the ultimate magic: "Legend of the Palmtop Tiger of Happiness!"
After this, it'll always be my turn.