Since when has it been a lie?
How did it all happen?
Does she have
something I don't have?
Images that I keep imagining
appear to me everywhere...
Everyone!
Thank you very much for today!
This is our last song!
N-No way...
E-Eichi?
You made your dream of becoming
a singer come true, huh?
Y-Yeah. You, too, Eichi?
Yeah.
That's great!
Mitsuki...
I like you.
Eichi...
Eichi!
A dream?
Eichi?
I Want to Sing!
Hey! Look above you!
Upon the wide night sky.
I'll shine with all my might...
It'll be okay, right?
Yes!
Upon the wide night sky.
I'll shine with all my—
Ouch...
Mitsuki.
I told you many times
to stop, didn't I?
Music is disgusting.
It reminds me of your father
and makes me sick.
I'm sorry. But I...
Don't talk back to me!
Okay.
Has your fever gone down?
Yes.
I see. That's good.
Dr. Wakaoji is here.
Get yourself together.
Dr. Wakaoji!
I'm sorry to trouble you
on your day off.
No, don't worry about it.
More importantly, how is she?
She seems quite a bit better
this morning.
I see.
Morning, Mitsuki.
Good morning!
The lump is a little red, isn't it?
Shall I apply some medicine on it?
Okay...
Okay, that's it.
Thank you.
Umm...Dr. Wakaoji.
What is it, Mitsuki?
Can you make it
so I'll be having a complete
physical examination at your hospital now?
I bet you're setting up
an alibi, right?
So, where are you going?
It's a letter of acceptance from
the first round of
the Seed Records new artist audition.
I sent it in secret
from my grandmother... So...
No.
What?
You developed a fever
and left early yesterday, right?
And there's the swelling
in your throat.
So as your attending physician,
I can't allow it.
But here I passed the first round!
But as you are now,
you can't sing in a loud voice, right?
Auditions will have to wait until after
your throat has gotten better.
Mitsuki, let's operate while
the lump is still small.
I don't want an operation.
I might lose my voice, right?
Given the location,
the possibility of that is undeniable.
Then I won't have the operation.
Doctor...
As opposed to dying, I'm really scared of
becoming unable to sing.
So...
I'm sorry.
Mitsuki...
About Mitsuki...
Could I ask you to somehow
convince her...to have the operation?
I told her many times!
But it's like she doesn't listen!
Everything about her
is just like my late daughter.
I've given up.
I see.
I messed up again.
So all I can do is wait
for my throat to heal?
Mitsuki. Promise me...
that we'll be closer to
our dreams when we next meet.
Me, an astronomer,
and you, a singer, okay?
Promise...
Yes...
But...I wonder when that will be.
Eichi.
What?!
All right.
Wh-Who is that?
And how did he
get through the wall?!
So this is her. Mitsuki Koyama.
Twelve years old.
Huh?
How does he know my name?!
Wait, Takuto!
A-Another one's appeared.
- What are these guys?
- You always go off by yourself.
It's just that you're slow.
Hey, is that the sort of attitude
you should have towards a superior?
Quit being so patronizing.
- My!
- Umm...
Who're you guys?
Can you see us?
Yes.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why can you see us?!
Real humans shouldn't be
able to see us, right?!
But I can see you.
What do we do at
a time like this?
Since it's come to this, we have no choice.
It's time for that!
Yeah.
It's unusual for us to give
our names after being asked, but...
We are the Death Spirits
who can even quiet crying children!
Takuto!
Meroko!
The two of us are...
- Green Onion Ramen!
"Green Onion Ramen," they said.
Sounds delicious.
Takuto, I really don't like
this duo name.
Deal with it.
The chief decided on it.
Rabbit ears and cat ears. How soft!
Th-This is for pediatrics, so...
Pediatrics?
What? They have Death Spirits
for kids, too?
Huh? Kids?
Come to think of it,
Death Spirits...
You've come for me?
That's right.
Whoa-whoa!
Don't say that!
It's too late.
I'm going to die today.
Keep cool.
You'll actually die in one year.
One year from now?
Could it be that my illness
will get worse?
Well, that might be.
Oh, I'm sorry. Please don't cry.
She's not crying?
Well, anyway, while
we still have the time...
Let's see. At a time like this...
Let me see, let me see...
Actually, it seems there's someone
who's attempting to prevent your death.
Then I'm not going to die?
No, that's not how it works.
You can't change destiny.
I see.
If I have only one year of life left,
then there's really no time to lose!
Hey, Takuto.
What were you thinking,
babbling like that?!
I'm going to report this to the chief!
It's cool.
We've been seen, anyway.
The point is that
one year later, she'll...What?
Where'd she go?
Takuto! Over there!
Wait, you shrimp!
Stop!
Hey!
Hold it!
Taxi!
Darn it! We were just a step away.
Out of the way!
M-Moron!
Thank you, Death Spirits.
I've made up my mind to audition.
If I only have one year left,
I'll become a singer by then!
Wow...
So this is the place.
At last, Eichi.
I'll deliver on my promise to you,
without fail.
Where'd she go off to?
She looks mild-mannered,
but she took us for fools.
Hey! She's here!
Really?!
I wonder what she's doing.
Who cares?!
Hey! She'll run away again
if we look like this.
Huh? I know that.
Jeez. Why won't it open?
I wonder if there is
a key somewhere.
Oh!
That's open!
Okay. All I can
do is go from there.
Yeah!
How cute!
I wonder what these are.
I wonder if they're decorations.
Let's see how it feels.
What?!
I got you.
Death Spirits!
We can't have you going out and
about on your own.
Now, let's go home quietly.
Right-right.
H-Hey, wait! I'm gonna audition!
I don't want to go home like this.
Then why were you trying to get in
through a place like that?
Yeah. Go in the front door.
I can't do that because
they said I don't look sixteen.
Don't I look sixteen?
Well...no.
What?
I'm going in through there,
after all!
Don't, you moron!
It's dangerous!
It won't do any good
if you get hurt or something!
But if I don't hurry,
registration will end.
I have to become a singer,
no matter what!
Is something wrong?
When...I talk...loudly...my throat...
Then an audition is impossible.
But...
Please. I have one year to live.
At the very least,
please let me audition.
If I fail the audition...
I'll behave and listen to what you say.
So...please...
You really will, right?
Okay.
I'll make you sixteen years old.
While I'm at it, I'll make your body healthy
while you're sixteen.
What?
Take it.
When I give the signal,
it will circulate through your body.
It'll feel strange, but stick it out.
Good girl.
Don't you feel it?
No...
Then go see for yourself.
Whoa.
Amazing! I'm really sixteen.
Thanks, Mr. Death Spirit!
Thank you very much!
Hey! Get away from Takuto!
Are you satisfied?
Umm...I'd like to dye my hair, too.
What's the meaning of this, Takuto?!
What?
To think, after ignoring
the orders of the higher-ups,
you'd use your powers on her.
You're asking for big trouble!
D-Don't tell me that
you're falling for that girl.
Huh?
N-No! You're mine, Takuto.
I won't hand you over
no matter what.
Since when do I belong to you?
Don't worry. That's not it.
Huh?
It'll be a problem if she whines and
doesn't go to the spirit world
when she dies because
she has a lingering attachment, right?
That's true, but...
But, what do we do if she passes?
That would be a lingering attachment,
wouldn't it?
It'll be okay.
She won't pass that easily.
She's sixteen and
she'll attend the audition.
She'll experience reality and sink
like a stone in the audition.
She won't have even
a bit of a lingering attachment.
Wow. There are only cute girls.
I wonder if I'm too plain.
Everyone's looking.
I wonder if I look weird...
L-Like a geek or something?
Can I sit next to you?
Oh... Sure...
Who're you affiliated with?
Affiliated?
Aren't you with a theatre group
or an office or something?
No.
No kidding?
What?
Am I supposed to be in
a theatre group or something?
Well, I feel bad for you,
but it's futile.
What?
This is just between us.
It seems it's already been decided
who's going to pass.
What? Then why
have an audition?!
S-Sorry, sorry.
Why?
This audition is going to be massively
covered by the morning news,
tabloid shows and the like.
With all that attention,
the girl who is "chosen from among
tens of thousands"
will be that famous.
It's the perfect chance
to market a new face.
I see...
So you...passed.
Sorry.
We will now begin the judging.
Bye.
When your number is called,
please enter.
Now then, starting with number one.
I see. So that's how it is.
It's kind of sad, somehow.
I thought it was
a more innocent world.
You're never to say that
you want to be a singer.
I disobeyed my grandmother.
Auditions will have to wait until
after your throat has gotten better.
And I was stopped
by Dr. Wakaoji, too.
You'll die one year from now.
One year from now...
What am I doing here?
Eichi...
...twenty-one...
Number twenty-one, come on in.
Number twenty-one, Mitsuki Koyama.
I'm very glad to be here.
What genre do you like?
I like...Japanese pop.
Is there something you want
to try doing if you become a singer?
Uh...I...I just want to sing.
I like singing, so...
Then sing.
Sound, please.
Oh, no. She's so nervous.
There's no way she'll pass.
The only thing that doesn't change
my dream that I've been...
Huh?
Hold on! You're voice is too soft!
Sing a bit louder!
What...louder?
What's wrong with your throat?
Does it hurt?
Then I guess singing
is impossible.
Impossible.
It's impossible, after all.
I'm sorry!
Are you going to run away?!
Mr. Death Spirit...
Your throat is okay. Sing.
You like singing, don't you?!
You truly do like singing, Mitsuki.
I also...love your songs.
Right...
I'm sorry. Please let me
sing again.
Oh, okay...
Sound, please.
It's okay if it's rough.
No matter how tight
my chest feels...
Pain... Affection...
They're all fragments of my dream.
The only thing that doesn't change
the dream that I've been holding.
How do I appear to you now to
those young eyes from the past?
Hey! Look above you!
Upon the wide night sky
I'll shine with all my might.
So hurry up and find the full moon.
Wow. My voice is loud.
I can breath all right, too.
I didn't know I could use
my voice like this.
How fun!
Let's sing a song—together forever,
that's everything I will do...
Day by day—I will hold fate
and the hope for tomorrow in my heart...
Let's sing a song—I can bear any hardship
when I'm always together with you.
More and more—I wanna be closer
and closer to you...
She...
...even though you are already here.
Umm... I'm finished.
Call Mr. Miya!
And Mr. Ishikawa, too!
Sure.
Nishida, send the others home.
We've settled on number twenty-one!
Okay!
What do we do about this?
What?!
They decided on me?!
Today's auditions are complete.
And the third round...
- Takuto.
- that we had planned will not be held.
W-What should I do, Eichi?
I passed.
What have you done, Takuto?
She really passed the audition!
Shut up.
I don't care.
Do you mean...
you've fallen for her?!
What? That's not possible!
You sure can't, because she loves
a boy named Eichi.
She wants to become a singer because
of a promise that she made with him.
W-What?!
That's an impure reason...
It's for a boy?
Next time on Full Moon:
"My Promise to Eichi"
- Look forward to it!