Kimblee...! Where are you?
This... this shouldn't
be happening...!
You guaranteed victory.
What happened to the turncoats
who would attack
from the inside?!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER A]
Cease fire, men!
[BUCCANEER]
That was too easy.
[MILES]
Yeah.
But why?
The crest is carved.
[MAY CHANG]
You aren't listening!
I told you...
Alkahestry is all about
reading the dragon's pulse!
[AL]
And I told you...
I have no idea
what that even means!
[MAY CHANG] Clear your mind
and think with your senses!
Like this...!
See, it's easy!
You're just pointing!
[MAY CHANG]
No, I'm focusing!
[AL] Can't you explain
it scientifically?
[MAN 1]
They're rambunctious, huh?
Yeah, no kidding...
Sorry to impose on you.
You're not imposing...
You're actually helping us out.
Ow! Stop pulling
my hair, you brat!
[MAN 1] You guys are a welcome
distraction for our kids.
We're gonna head out
to find some firewood.
Would you mind letting
Zampano know for me?
[YOKI]
Damn it!
Evil little children...!
And where the hell is Zampano?
Why does he get to wander
off while I get tortured?!
Hey!
[ZAMPANO]
They're close by... Follow me.
You lead the way... Zampano.
[BRADLEY] So I hear
that you've discovered
Selim's true identity.
Yes, sir.
And you're also
aware of who I am?
Yes.
Lieutenant...
I'm interested in
hearing your opinion
as a loyal citizen
of this country...
How do you feel about your
leader being a Homunculus?
I think it's sad the
family I've answered to
and trusted isn't real...
That you don't
even have that much.
[HAWKEYE]
You're just putting on an act...
Pretending to be the
humans you secretly despise.
[BRADLEY] It is true
that Selim was appointed
to be my son by my superior.
Everything from my
power down to my rank
was appointed to me...
Most of my life is just an act.
But my wife, at least,
was of my own choosing.
Are you finished with the tea?
Uh, yessir.
Delicious. Thank you.
[GERSO]
Are you serious, Doctor?
You were one of the
bigwig researchers
at the Fifth Labratory?
I wasn't that important...
I just had a few
men working for me.
It's been ages since I've
spoken with any of them.
[ZAMPANO]
Hey!
Who is this man with you?
He's just a, uh,
nice drifter I met.
He was hoping
you might be able
to examine him, Doctor.
You can stop, Zampano.
Nobody's falling
for your bad acting.
It's nice to see you, Doctor...
It's been too long...
I like what you've
done with your face.
Now who do you think you are...?
You honestly believed you
could pull one over on me?
[ENVY]
What is this?!
Zampano!
Now what were you
saying about my acting...?
It's bad?
Thank you, Envy...
You couldn't have made
our plans to lure
you here any easier.
You did just as we expected...
You take such
delight in your cruelty...
I knew you'd come to
capture me on your own.
Well you were right
about that one, Doctor...
And now that you've
got me here...
You asked for i-- Ahhh!!
What do you think, Envy...?
They're like landmines
loaded with alchemy.
That kind of alchemy
doesn't even exist!
Dammit...! You say
they're landmines?
Then all I've gotta do is
follow your
footsteps to avoid them.
Ahhhhhhhhh!!
What the hell?!
They're set to detonate
for Homunculi only.
We've littered the
entire area with them,
all hidden beneath the snow.
Well, Envy...
How does it feel to have
the tables turned on you...?
It's not as much fun
on that side, is it?
It's working perfectly.
He doesn't know it's
remote alkahestry.
[ENVY]
That's enough.
You should've just
done as you were told...
But if you scum
really want to test me...
then I'll show
you who's in charge!
[roars]
Doctor!
That was a close one!
Th... thank you.
You're fast for a fat boy.
You shouldn't
underestimate us "scum."
Dammit!
If you think you're
gonna win this...
You're fools!
[SCAR]
Is that so?
Now then...
What do you think of this?
[ENVY roars]
Is he dead?
Doctor!
Ha ha! I gotcha!
Whoa... Stay put...
Unless you want him dead...
Now then.
How should I punish you?
What do you think, Doctor...?
How about I wipe out a
village of innocent people?
[MARCOH] I'm not
gonna let you do that.
Quit trying to resist, Marcoh...
It just looks stupid.
There we go...
That slum is ripe
for destruction.
Don't do it!
But it would be wasteful
to simply kill them...
I could always take them
back to Central instead...
We are running
low on ingredients.
Monster...!
You're still using souls to
make Philosopher's Stones...?!
I won't let you...!
Let my research team go, dammit!
Huh...? Oh Sorry.
It's a little too
late to release them
now that we've turned them
into Philosopher's Stones.
You... You sacrificed my men?
What...? I forgot
to tell you...?
Oh, well, Doctor...
There's no point in crying
over spilled milk, now.
It's not right for
you to get so upset
considering all the
Stones you've made.
And all the lives
you put into them.
[MARCOH]
You're right...
I've sacrificed
many innocent lives
to make your damned
Philosopher's Stones...
I know better
than anyone else
how much pain goes
into creating them.
And not only do I know
how to create them...
But I know how to
destroy them as well!
[ENVY screams]
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ENVY screams]
[rumbling]
[MAN 2]
What's that?!
[MAN 3] That's where the Doctor
and the others were headed.
[ENVY]
It hurts so much...!
So much pain!
No, this can't happen!
It can't!
This can't be... No...
How can this...
How can this happen?
I could never be defeated
by pathetic
creatures like you...
And you... you Chimeras.
Don't... Quit looking at me...
How dare you look at me.
Don't look down
on me you worms!
Don't look... down
on... me... worms.
How pathetic...
This is the thing that
caused so much damage?
[labored breathing]
[SCAR]
We did it, Marcoh... We won.
Oh...! Hey look!
Here they come!
[WINRY]
Dr. Marcoh...!
Are you okay,
what happened?!
What's that?
Whooaa...
[YOKI]
I can't believe you guys
would keep me in
the dark about this.
That's what you get
for picking a fight
with us humans...
Grotesque tadpole.
Look at you...
Why would you do
something so dangerous?
Because I had to...
I've always done
what I was told to do.
I had to take a risk and
think for myself this time...
I put my fear aside...
and did what was right...
I wanted to be
like your parents.
You were... But try
not to be so reckless.
Sure.
[YOKI]
Yowww!
Mr. Yoki?
Help... Get it off me.
I've hijacked this idiot's body!
[YOKI]
Stop it! Let go...!
Somebody help me...!
I can't control my body!
That's right, you can't.
[ENVY]
Now if you want him to live,
you'll do as I tell you.
[GERSO]
Nah, he's all yours.
Do what you want.
[ZAMPANO] It's not like
he's our friend or anything.
Poor Yoki...
I'm sorry I didn't
know you better.
[AL] We'll never
forget your sacrifice.
Ahhhhh!!!
Please, Mr. Scar...
You won't stand back
and let this thing kill me...!
Right?
How can you turn
your back on me?!
After all that I've done...
[ENVY]
Wh... What is this...?
Doesn't anyone
care about this guy?
[MARCOH]
You're wasting your time, Envy.
We've accepted the
measures we'll have to take
to defeat you...
We'll destroy both you
and this man if
you don't surrender.
[ENVY]
Dammit.
[AL]
Got him.
I'm free?
[GERSO]
Nice acting, Doctor.
I'm afraid I'm not used
to bluffing like that.
Damn all of you...!
None of you guys
are my friends...!
How could you?
You're dead to me!
[ENVY]
This sucks.
[GERSO] So... This seems
like a good opportunity
to interrogate you.
I'm not talking.
Spit it out! You slug...!
You're either gonna talk or die!
That's it...!
Let him have it, Zampano!
Even if I do talk, you're
still gonna kill me...
So what's the point...? Fool.
What?
So what's the deal...?
Why isn't the Fullmetal
pipsqueak with you?
[AL]
Brother...?
I'm pretty sure
he's at Briggs by now.
Last thing that I heard,
he had gone missing.
[AL]
What'd you say...?!
He's missing?
Tell me!
He disappeared
after a mine shaft
in Baschool collapsed...
I wonder if he's still alive?
[WINRY] He's lying...
He has to be.
[GERSO]
So what now?
Should we head back
to Baschool to check?
[AL] No... That's not
what Brother would want.
He would trust
that I was alright
and wouldn't let a
rumor stop him...
So we're gonna do the
same thing and keep moving.
We can't give up hope yet.
[SCAR]
I'll go my separate way for now.
I've realized something
about the actions I've taken...
I don't intend to
simply punish this country
for what it did to Ishval.
I want to change it.
And I'll need
your help, Marcoh...
The two of us need
to set things right.
Alright then...
We'll travel together.
In order to change
this country...
[AL]
Actually...
I've got someplace I've
been meaning to check out.
[GERSO]
Oh...? Where's that?
[AL] It's a town called
Liore... I'm not sure...
But I've got a feeling
the tunnel runs under it.
[SCAR]
Here, May...
Take this thing and
return to your country.
Hold on!
It's the remnants of a seemingly
indestructible creature...
It might appease your emperor
enough to save your clan.
I can't...!
Who's gonna teach you
about alkahestry if I leave?
[SCAR] You need to think
about your own country.
Have you forgotten why you
came here in the first place...?
Your clan could lose
its power struggle...
And what explanation
will you have
for them when you return home?
Will you apologize and tell them
you were too busy
saving another country?
Now go home...
Forget this place...
Leave this country's
problems to its people.
Thank you, for everything!
[AL]
You take care, May...
Once I learn the
basics of Alkahestry...
I'll be sure to find
you to learn more.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, Alphonse.
Alphonse... I'll...
I'll miss you.
Good luck...!
I'll never forget
any of you...!
Thank you...! Goodbye.
[WINRY]
Have a safe journey, May!
[AL]
There she goes.
[MARCOH]
We should start moving as well.
[SCAR]
Let's go.
[sniffles]
Poor Mr. Greed...
[SOLDIER 1]
No luck...
Izumi Curtis and her husband
are apparently on vacation
and didn't say when
they're returning.
[SOLDIER 2]
Hmm... Is that so?
We should report back
to Fuhrer Bradley...
There's not much
else we can do.
[BIDO]
Bradley!
[BRADLEY] Now you stay
put, I'll be right back.
[SOLDIER 2] He might
have replacements for us.
Let's hope so.
[BIDO] I might find
Mr. Greed if I follow them...
But...
Uh, Sis?
Would you be so kind
as to possibly move
your foot, please?
[OLIVIER] You are to
address me as General!
Yes, ma'am, General!
You're just as gutless
as I remember you being.
So...
I heard your men
completely annihilated
the Drachma forces.
Of course they did!
But won't that hasten
the enemy's
transmutation circle?
I don't give a damn.
It was their duty to
defend the border...
And that's what they did...
And Drachma won't
even think twice
about attacking again.
Now they know that Our country
is not one to be meddled with.
Oh, my, you've only
grown more ferocious...
How will you ever find a
husband if you continue to--
That's enough of your
sniveling, you pansy!
I need to get
away from you
before I start to
catch your cowardice.
[GARDNER]
Ah...
I've been looking
for you, General...
Is this man your brother?
I don't consider
him my brother...
Not after he deserted
his country in Ishval.
Follow me, please...
There's something I'd
like for you to see.
[GARDNER]
Are you familiar
with the three state-appointed
tenets of alchemy?
Of course...
"Obey the military"...
"Do not create gold"...
"Do not create people"...
And that's it.
You know them well.
[GARDNER] Obeying the military
should go without saying...
The creation of
gold is restricted
to avoid financial disorder.
So then...
What about creating people...?
Why do you suppose the state
would so firmly
enforce this regulation?
[OLIVIER]
It's simply unethical, sir...
It's even taboo
amongst alchemists...
From what I understand,
they regard it as an
implicit sacrilege against God.
[GARDNER]
But that isn't why.
The state has no
interest in ethics...
They're too much of a
variable to use as a guideline.
The true reason is
far less abstract.
The third tenet is
to prevent someone
from creating their
own army... General.
[ZAMPANO]
This place is a disaster.
[GERSO] You think there's
anyplace left standing
where we could get
something to eat?
[AL]
I think so...
It's around here somewhere.
[AL]
Rose...! How are you?
What a surprise...!
So, Al...
What brings you
back to Liore?
[GERSO] Looks like the kid
knows her, doesn't he?
[AL]
Huh...?
Yeah, somewhat.
[ROSE]
Hey, Al...
Where's Ed...?
Isn't he with you?
[AL]
Uh...
No, we're traveling
separately right now.
Oh... that's too bad...
I've actually really missed him.
[AL]
Winry?
Wh... What, Al?
[AL]
Oh, nothing!
You just kind of had a
funny look on your face,
that's all.
I did not! You're
imagining things!
Okay, Rose...
These pots are as
clean as they get...
You have anything el--
[ROSE laughs]
[AL] Huh?
[HOHENHEIM, AL and WINRY gasp]
[NARRATOR]
Reunion, revival, and resolution
are all bound together
in a single moment.
No matter how
difficult the voyage ahead
may prove to be...
The living have no choice
but to continue moving forward
if they are to remain alive.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 44, "Revving
at Full Throttle."
Rise from your
slumber, humans...
This is the
beginning of the end.