You didn't die?
Cal... Devens!
What happened?
I saw... a ghost.
I vowed to protect her. I promised to come back.
And yet, I wasn't there when she was killed.
All this time, I thought that's what happened.
So it wasn't the case?
She's the one who fired that shot yesterday.
I see.
Cal joined Inferno... as a sniper.
Anger
Master Huang,
to think that you're accepting me
as your sworn brother on your memorable birthday...
This is such a delightful surprise for me.
Xu, don't be so modest.
It took me too long to praise your achievement of establishing
your turf in western Japan.
In the not. so. distant future, eastern Japan will be in our hands as well.
That's very reassuring.
Let's toast to our future, brother.
The Godo Family wants us to kill Xu, the head of the Chinese mafia, right?
Is there a problem?
Is it necessary to target the old geezer, Huang, as well?
He supports one of Inferno's rivals.
I heard that he looked after you after you got kicked out of Inferno.
He... knows too much.
Have you no sense of honor?
You can keep your honor. I'm different from you. That's all.
This is Gregor, over.
I'm listening.
Gregor Unit is in position. We can go in anytime.
Stay put and await orders.
Where's Phantom?
Beats me.
She wasn't eager about this operation in the first place.
We'll do it without her. All right?
True. This task may not be for her as it's just providing cover.
Gregor, we'll carry out the operation as planned.
Parker Unit, go in through the back door and take care of the guards first.
Roger.
So you'd say that it'll be about 3 minutes before they smoke Huang and Xu out?
You have a problem with that?
No, not at all... but...
she can do it within 10 seconds.
10 seconds?
Damn her!
You son of a bitch!
Wh... What's going on?
This is...
Watch out!
Dammit! What the hell is she doing?!
I think this is the most efficient and logical method.
We're in Japan! Causing such a serious incident will...
Whether it's Japan or the US the value of life... is the same.
This way, Master Huang.
Y-Yeah...
Who on earth is making such a daring attack?
I can think of one possibility.
You're Scythe's...
It was none other than I who helped that man!
Is this how he repays my kindness?!
Kindness? What does that mean again?
Master Huang!
Oh? You've got guts. You're still not giving up?
I like that. I'll go along with you.
Do you like playing games?
Shoot when the music ends.
How dare you make a fool of me! Whatever organization you're from,
don't think that you can get away with this!
I see. You don't know me, do you...
Phantom...
Being in the underworld, you've at least heard that name, right?
That's right. That's...
me.
If you can win here, I bet the whole world will throw themselves at your feet.
In your next life, try to pick a better job.
Adios, Chink.
I was the one who got her started.
I taught her how to kill... and led her to the underworld.
I messed up her life... with my own hands.
The arrangements for our escape will be completed soon.
Until then...
Yeah, I know.
Where did you go yesterday?
I went to see an acquaintance.
Did you come in contact with Zwei?
That's none of your business.
I'll hunt them in my own way.
I see.
You're next... Reiji.
Uhm...
Good morning.
Reiji, you went home early yesterday.
What?
Ah, uhm, when I went to see Sanae after school yesterday,
you were already gone, so...
Ah... I had some errands to run.
I don't mean to pry or anything.
I didn't think you were.
Okay.
Snow...
Yeah... the weather forecast didn't say anything about snow, though.
It's pretty... isn't it...
Yeah.
You guys made quite a big show, Ms. Garland.
The security police are on the case.
I recommend that those who participated in last night's attack
leave the country as soon as possible.
You don't have to worry about it, as most of them have already left.
Glad to hear that. In any case,
I appreciate that you killed Xu without leaving any evidence whatsoever
of the Godo Family's involvement.
However, I hope that...
you let me know your plans next time you operate in Japan.
Have a good day.
It wasn't a difficult mission.
If things had gone as planned, no one would've gone home in a coffin.
It was my fault. When she didn't... When Phantom didn't show up,
I should've anticipated something like that would happen.
You don't have to be so hard on yourself.
It's true that Drei has some issues.
But I can understand where she's coming from. She feels impatient.
She hasn't properly taken over the title of Phantom yet
as she didn't battle it out with the previous Phantom.
Once Drei truly wins the status of Phantom,
she will probably become suitably calm and composed.
In other words, as long as she brings down Zwei with her own hands...
Reiji.
You didn't bring your lunch today, right?
No, but, Motegi... how did you know that?
Then do you wanna go to the cafeteria with me?
That's fine, but what about your lunch?
I ate it after second period.
Well then, Motegi, in recognition of your notable service today,
I hereby allow you to sit here.
Yes ma'am! Excuse me!
Hi there. Do you remember me?
Of course. You're the unpopular Motegi, right? My brother told me about you.
What did you tell her about me?!
What about you? You sold me out, didn't you.
Please. Share your happiness with me. Just a little will do.
You sound desperate.
Well, Brother, something like this isn't too bad once in a while.
Right?!
Well, to think that Elen and I have the same opinion. I feel honored!
I wonder if we get along well after all.
Even Cal can't do anything in a crowd... huh?
Yeah.
Keep this seat for me. I'll go buy lunch.
Ah, okay.
I want Meal B!
Go get it yourself!
What? The urgent matter that Reiji had to attend to the other day was you?
There were some home matters I really wanted to discuss with him.
I'm sorry. I knew he was out on a date with you, Mio, but...
I-it wasn't a date.
Oh... if that was the case, you should have said so.
Well, I was kind of embarrassed, so...
Ouch!
You don't know how a girl's mind works!
A guy like that should be punished by losing some food... Ow!
Why are you eating it?
Because you're the one who gets all the happiness!
What do you mean?!
You're so dense! You still don't get it?!
There are tons of people in this world starving for happiness!
That's right!
Like Motegi here.
Wait, what?
I was asked to give this to you.
Thanks.
Sorry, I've got to go for a bit.
What?
Why?
What's the matter?
My junior wants me to do something for her.
My little bit of happiness is...
A little would do, right?
Well...
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to go make sure she doesn't get mixed up with the wrong guys.
Elen is popular among boys.
If you're always worried about her, you won't survive, you obsessed brother.
But...
Please go. She's your only sister.
Sorry. I'll make it up to you some other time.
What about making it up to me?
No way.
Elen...
Are you looking for someone?
Do you want to kill me?
That's right. You're capable of killing me.
Not because you've been ordered to, nor because you're cornered.
But simply of your own free will.
That's the one characteristic of yours that deserves a special mention... Zwei.
You and Ein are different, since you were driven by pure murderous intent
while her mind was strengthened by a cheap brainwash.
In a way, you are a failure...
but you still suggested a new direction for my research.
I've tried... exploring the theme of hatred.
Have you seen... my proud third work... Drei?
Cal...
What did you do to Cal?
To make a long story short, I did nothing.
No brainwashing. No hypnotic suggestions.
I didn't manipulate her memory or emotions at all, either.
I just thoroughly refined...
her natural hatred.
How nice of you to have left such a person of talent to me.
I cannot but appreciate it.
Scythe... You alone I can't...
Can't forgive? Do you detest me?
But you can't kill me here.
It's too risky.
Excellent self control.
You have both pure hatred and the ability to make levelheaded judgements.
What a wonderful balance you have.
In that sense, Drei goes a little overboard. She can't control herself.
However...
at least she seems to have enough sense to avoid crowds.
she seems to at least have enough sense to avoid crowds.
Don't tell me...
If you want to go help, you'd better hurry.
Why don't you just come out?
No one will interrupt us here.
How do you do, Ein?
Or should I say ex-Phantom?
Next episode
Rage
I've lived until this day in order to hunt down and kill that man.
Just for that.