To Mr. Junichi Katsuragi
I empathize with you. You were right about the way things are,
but we should stand up for ourselves. And so, I have decided to form
a publishing company together with a few of our comrades.
I would like you to see it as the same battle but in a new
form, and I hope you will join me in this endeavor. I want to talk to
you about this face to face.
- Arita
Arita
You changed me so much I don't remember what I was like before we met.
The breeze caresses our cheeks.
Lullaby of Birdland...
As we run down the slope,
our flimsy shadows extend.
It's like a neverending summer vacation.
It feels like when we snuck into the pool.
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
It's an intense spiral of temptation.
A beat pierces my heart. A strange one.
It vanishes after a quick spark.
Even on bad days, I dress up
and dance to some swing. The music quickly surrounds me.
What is this dance exactly? I can't stop it.
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
The melody...
is like love.
A Christmas party?
And we can go too?
Of course.
It's next Sunday.
We'll be there!
Since Olympus is hosting it,
will you play the guitar for us?
Well, if you've got a request...
Ri, are you going to the Christmas party too?
You can go with Nishimi, right?
I'm not really part of that group, so I'll pass.
Sorry, my church is having a Christmas party on Sunday.
I can't make it.
So Kawabuchi's going with you then?
Yeah.
We should've checked before.
Maruo, if you don't mind, I think I'd like to go to the party after all.
Really?
Of course, you're very welcome!
I never thought you'd agree to come.
It's best to start putting a little distance between us like this.
I'm sure of it.
Hey!
You're late, Richie-baby!
H-Hi.
All right! Next we'll play The Spiders.
What about The Beatles?
Let's go with "Bang Bang Bang"!
Nishimi, how about some cider?
Sure.
Feigning innocence, bang bang bang!
Bang bang, bababababababa-bang!
He's someone I can't beat!
Come on, Nishimi, let's sing together!
I don't really know the popular songs.
I wonder what he's doing right now.
Maybe he's talking to Ri at the church.
I go to a party, and all I do is think about those two.
I feel like a fool.
Kaoru?
Ri.
Why are you here? I thought
you were going to church.
Yeah. Their Christmas party is over.
He isn't here with you?
Does he have to be?
Um... He took the kids home.
I see.
It's cold, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey, come on!
I've got you, baby!
Come to think of it, isn't his birthday coming up?
I hope you finish in time.
Why?
Why do you say things like that?
You're wrong!
This is for...
Never mind! You're an idiot!
What did I do this time?
I don't get it.
Women are hard to understand.
Why did I lose my temper like that?
I'm the one who rejected
him in the first place.
Even if I finished knitting this,
I'd never be able to give it to him.
I'm relieved.
You're safe for now, Yurika,
but let me tell you something.
I know.
You're going to tell me not to see him, right?
You don't have to keep repeating yourself.
Chet, get back here!
Chet!
Sentaro? What are you doing here?
What am I...? I've been waitin' for you.
Wh-Why are you acting so formal?
Ri'ko...
I'm sorry.
I never realized how you felt till now.
I may have said some dumb things an' hurt you.
I'm sorry. But... Um... How should I put this?
About your feelings, I, uh...
Sentaro, why are you suddenly on your best behavior?
Stop it already.
This isn't a yakuza movie.
Did I get it wrong?
Yeah. You got it wrong.
O-Oh, a misunderstanding.
Sorry for talkin' so weird.
Right! We're like family. You made
me nervous for a second there.
I-In that case, good.
We're like family, so I couldn't stand
the thought of causin' you pain.
I'm glad I heard this now
and not a while back.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm never going to tell a blockhead like you.
There's something I have to tell you.
I'm going back to Tokyo soon.
You probably won't see me again.
An upperclassman from my college is
starting his own publishing company,
and he wants me to help.
I plan on leaving soon after New Year's.
It's taken me a long time
to get to this point,
but I owe it to you for making me think
I should give going back one more try.
I'm grateful.
"Idiot. I don't want to hear those words.
Just don't leave me."
But I couldn't bring myself to say that.
Not when he's finally trying to move forward.
Ritsuko!
Yurika!
Wh-What are you doing?
Looking for something.
I carelessly threw something
away that was important to me.
Hey, is that girl homeless?
Hey, Ritsuko.
Never mind me. Please, go on ahead.
A beautiful girl like you shouldn't be seen doing something like this.
Ritsuko.
I'll help you.
P-Please, don't!
It's something important, isn't it?
Yurika.
So, what am I looking for?
Here it is!
This is it, right?
Yes!
But I'll have to start over with clean yarn.
Is this going to be a present for someone?
Um...
Why did you throw away
something so important?
I was confused.
I suddenly felt stupid for knitting a
gift that I'd never be able to give.
Why wouldn't you be able to?
B-Because a lot of things
have happened between us,
and I hurt him terribly before.
You turned him down, didn't you?
And I couldn't tell him I
like him now after doing that,
so I decided to let it go.
But then I thought that wouldn't do.
See, there was another time when
I said nothing and just gave up.
Do you regret it?
No. I'd given up on that long ago.
Besides, I've realized this person has been there to support me all this time, whenever I've felt down.
I had no confidence in myself,
but he did his best to encourage me.
This time, I want to be the
one to tell him how I feel.
I finally decided to stop keeping my
mouth shut and waiting for things to end.
I'm sorry for talking about this.
No, I'm glad you did.
I think you've opened my eyes as well.
So...
Who is it?
Who's your prince?
Oh, that's...
Shall I try and guess?
Wh-What are you saying? Please, stop!
You're so cute!
Yes. I'm set to leave this weekend.
Working in Tokyo?
Yeah. A lot happened at college,
and I ended up dropping out.
But you'll come back once in a while,
won't you? Like you've been doing?
No. I'm never coming back to this town.
Kaoru, our sessions were fun.
I'll miss seeing you and Sen-boy,
but I don't want you guys
to stop playing jazz.
Jun! Haven't you told him you're going back to Tokyo?
Hey, Sen!
What's the hubbub, Richie?
It's about Jun!
Yeah, he's about to go back to Tokyo, right?
I heard from Pops.
Well, ain't got nothin' to do with me.
Now, wanna jam?
You're gonna let that be the last you see of him?
I got nothin' to say to him.
You've looked up to him like a
big brother since you were a kid!
You may never get the chance to see him again!
There'd be no point.
Once he's gone, it'll be too late!
Enough about Jun already.
Let's get started here.
If you don't feel like
practicin', I'm goin' home.
What's all the fuss about?
I guess college students from Tokyo
and all over have come to demonstrate
against letting the nuclear aircraft carrier into port.
That's terrible.
In their eyes, I'm a traitor.
They may never forgive me.
But...
all I can do is search in my own way from now on,
using a different method than them.
Oh, you're here, Richie.
Here, eat.
I made it myself, so it might be a little salty.
But if you're not gonna eat it, I will.
Is this any time to be eating?
Did you forget what I said?
What are you talkin' about?
Don't play dumb!
Are you going to be stubborn until it's too late?
He's leaving either today or tomorrow!
It's tonight.
I'm taking the night train, Kaoru.
Sen-boy, this was rather old-fashioned of you.
I thought it was some kind of joke.
It's no joke.
I wanted to have a serious showdown with you.
Wait, you're not really...
I made it in time?
Let me in on it too.
This is no duet.
They're seriously duking it out.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble, Pops.
Tell me about it! And when you reach Tokyo,
first thing you do is get to a barber!
Sure, sure.
Well, I'm off.
Jun!
I'll remember today's session for the rest of my life!
Yeah. Me too, Sen-boy.
What are you doing here?
I told you not to see me off.
I have four questions I want you to answer.
If you try to dodge them, I'll
get on this train with you.
So answer me truthfully.
Question number one: Why did
you tell me not to see you off?
I hate sad goodbye scenes.
Question number two: Did you ever consider taking me with you?
The work I'm going to be doing is kind of a gamble.
Even if I took you with me, there's no
guarantee I'd make any kind of living.
Besides, you're still in high school.
Question number three...
Why didn't you do anything more than kiss me?
Did you not touch me because you
intended to leave from the start?
No.
I knew. I knew how much you cared about me.
This is my last question:
Won't you take me with you?
I want you to take good care of your own life.
I figured you'd say something like that.
Now I feel like I've been set free too.
I'm going back to my own world.
Thank you, Junichi.
Goodbye.
Yurika, where are you?
Come out, Yurika!
How dare you embarrass us by walking out in the middle of an arranged marriage meeting like that?
Calm down, dear!
We're going back there together, Yurika!
Yurika, where are you?
I'm going back to my own world.
I pulled you aboard.
Now what?
What is there to do?
The train's already left the station.
You're right.
Well, when we get there, we'll go to my room first,
and maybe I'll have you cut my hair.
It's freezing today.
Yeah. Think I'll light the heater.
I was waiting for you on that slope.
We made a promise to meet after school.
The goodbye blurred into the distance.
So weak, so twisted, so fragile
had I been back then,
but you gave me a small pair of wings.
I'm searching the sky beyond the twilight
for the faint flicker of light
because I want to tell you I love you.
I wrote a letter to you in my textbook margins,
but I could never give it to you.
It's still just there.