Kanata...
is a prince?
I told you!
Don't act so familiar with His Highness!
But I've met him before!
The person who gave me this was Kanata himself!
Whaaa?!
Please, tell me what happened to him!
Well... we don't know.
Our home of Hope Kingdom...
is under attack by the forces of Dysdark led by the Witch of Woe, Dyspear!
Sir Kanata entrusted us with one task
before we were separated by the battle.
We were to travel to your world and seek the Dress Up Keys as well as the three Princess Precures!
I see...
There are three Princess Precures?
Yes!
The Dress Up Keys and the Princess Precures are drawn to each other!
I know we'll find the other two!
Haruka, will you fight Dyspear with us?
Yeah.
I'll do it.
For Kanata, too!
Thank you!
This marks your first step toward becoming a princess.
First step?
Didn't this Dress Up Key and Princess Perfume already turn me into one?
No, no, no!
You've got some nerve to think that that's all it takes to revive a legendary power!
A true princess must strive to have strength, grace, and beauty!
Only a princess with those three traits can become our savior.
I see!
Strength!
Grace!
Beauty!
Right?
Y-Yeah, sure...
We can do it!
We'll leave for now!
Make sure you keep what we said about the Precures a secret!
Okay!
I won't let you get into danger again.
Haruka?
Yui, are you okay?
Yeah...
Thank goodness...
Yui, will you listen to my dream?
Yeah.
My dream...
is to become a princess!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
I respect your initiative for taking a morning run.
I don't think I've got beauty going for me,
and I don't really get what grace is,
so I figured I'd start with strength!
You look pretty happy, Haruka!
You can tell?
A princess?
How cute!
That's a splendid dream!
Let's go, princess!
Let's go, perf!
Wait!
The Academy's Princess!
Cure Mermaid Arrives!
Bonjour!
Student
Orientation
Congratulations to all of our new students on being accepted.
Haruka, where are you?
We here at Noble Academy welcome you—
B-Bonjour...
Miss Haruno!
How could you be late for your own orientation?!
I'm sorry!
I got too worked up while running and wound up really far away...
Oh, Minami...
You have no self-awareness!
You don't deserve to be a Noble Academy student!
Teacher...
Minami...
The academy's princess...
Fostering student independence is one of Noble Academy's founding principles.
Perhaps we should let her decide how to atone for her error.
Very well...
What is your name?
H-Haruno Haruka!
Haruno, your actions have disrupted our ceremony.
Reflect on this and decide how you will recompense those you've troubled.
I will...
How gracious of her!
Oh, Minami...
Are you okay? Should I help?
No, I've got this.
I chose to do this, so I should do it myself.
But I really made a mess of that orientation...
But Kaidou is amazing.
Even the teachers respect her.
How graceful...
Amazing...
She's also an excellent equestrian and archer!
She's like a real princess!
She totally is!
She's got the beauty and grace that a princess needs!
I'd love for her to tutor me!
You're already on her bad side, though.
Oh, right...
But...
I want to be more of a princess!
It's worth a shot!
I'll go ask her!
Good job.
Same to you.
How splendid... I want to be like her!
Why not get her to teach you?
I'm too shy. I could never!
E-Excuse me!
You were exshellent!
You...
I finished weeding the garden!
And here is my letter of apology!
Very well.
I will present it to the school board after reading it.
O-O-One more thing!
I-I-If you happen to have the time,
could you please teach me ballet?
All right.
Wha?
You will?!
I don't have much time to spare,
so I expect you to spare no effort as my student.
Right! Thank you very much!
Let's begin with some stretches.
You got it!
Now you try.
Wha?!
Just take a deep breath and go for it!
Tendu! Jeté! Grand Battement!
Lift your thighs higher!
Concentrate on your toes.
Now stand firm.
Focus!
Now try again.
Sure!
Japanese 1
That sounds rough.
But if it'll help make me a princess, I'll do whatever it takes!
Let's go, princess!
Un, deux, trois!
That was perf-ect!
Now I just have to...
Haruka!
Haruno!
I didn't teach you that yet!
She's mad at me again...
Let me take a look.
It's sprained.
Is it too tight?
No.
You pushed yourself too far.
I'm sorry...
What makes you try so hard?
I have a dream to chase.
I want to be a princess—
A princess?
Uh, someone like you!
I want to be perfect!
I'm far from perfect.
How can you say that?
You're great at everything and everyone looks up to you!
Why thank you,
but even I made my share of mistakes at first.
I'm skilled at ballet only because I've practiced it since I was a little girl.
You mean you aren't a superwoman who's good at everything?
What did you think I was?
The student council president,
the academy's princess, and maybe...
just a little intimidating.
I-I mean, I don't think that at all anymore!
Being together made me realize just how nice you are,
and I'm super, suuuper happy
that you're teaching me ballet!
There, all done.
Thank you very much!
As for me...
hearing you ask me to teach you ballet...
made me glad as well.
Nobody had ever asked me that before.
I can't let 'em off the hook after reviving a Precure.
I'll bust that princess's key up.
Good luck at regionals!
Guess we've got some dreamers here.
What's so fun about all that running?
Lemme see that dream of yours!
I'm the MVP!
I'll toss that dream into the cage of despair!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Come on out, Precure!
Minami, what in the world is that?
A Dyspairvil...
Stay calm and evacuate!
Right!
Haruka!
Is your ankle okay?
I've got a bandage on it, so I'm fine!
I have to stop him.
Here I go!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Haruno...
Smash it all!
Dyspairvil!
Oh no you don't!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Ya kept me waiting.
Dyspair... vil!
Dyspairvil!
Ouch!
Flora!
Dyspair... vil!
Are you okay, Haruno?
Kaidou!
Thanks for saving me!
Wait, what?!
How did you know it was me?!
Stop this at once.
And who're you, again?
Dyspairvil!
Look out!
Haruno!
You really think I'd stop 'cause you said so?
Please, run!
I can't do that.
Protecting students is the student council's... no, my duty!
I will never yield to fiends like you!
What?
What is this?
That's a...
Dress Up Key!
Wha?! Why do you have that?
You've been chosen!
What? A parrot?
I am not a parrot!
Insert the Dress Up Key into this Princess Perfume!
And that will allow me to protect everyone, right?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
That was so pretty!
Cure Mermaid...
That's Kaidou...
Now there's two Princess Precures?!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Don't get soft, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
That was amazing!
Now unleash Mermaid's power!
Insert the Dress Up Key into the Perfume!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rage, O seas!
Precure!
Mermaid Ripple!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Again?!
This ain't lookin' good...
You did it!
All that's left is to release that boy's dream from the cage of despair!
Using this, correct?
Open!
The door to your dream!
Kaidou!
Know your limits!
Sorry about that!
But now you're a Precure too!
Really, now...
We only need to find one more Princess Precure.
I'm sure we'll find her soon.
Whaaaaaa?!
The third Perfume...
Is gone!
Huh?!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Oh no!
The rest of the dorm found out about Perf!
They don't allow pets, so I might have to say goodbye!
I'll have to convince them to let you keep her.
All right, time to show them what you're made of, Perf!
Operation: Let's Get Fluffy!
Go! Princess Precure:
Goodbye So Soon?
We Can't Keep Perf!
Go say bonjour to your dream!