Takasu-kun!
I...
will chase after her!
Takasu-kun, you go left, I'll go right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Student Council President, they're running in the halls.
I'll let them off this time.
What should I say when I catch her?
I don't know...
Even though I don't know...
Not here?
The entrance!
Taiga, can you hear me?
Taiga, you've always wanted to know, right?!
I... I also...
I like Takasu Ryuuji too!
I like him! I've always liked him,
but I thought I should let you have him!
I thought to myself, "If Taiga, my best friend, needs him..."
but that was just my arrogance confusing me!
I've underestimated you!
I said that my happiness doesn't depend on anyone but me, didn't I?
The same goes for you. Your happiness doesn't depend on anyone but yourself!
So...
So, Taiga...
Let me see what you're going to do!
Kushieda!
I... I tripped while I was running...
Sign: Infirmary
Has it stopped yet?
You scared me.
I thought you were crying for a second.
You thought I would cry?
Of course... Normally...
Well, I guess this is sort of a reward.
Remember when I talked about what I can see?
Yeah, I think so...
Actually, it's my willpower...
Willpower?
I told you my brother plays baseball, didn't I?
I used to play baseball too.
To be honest, I was better than him,
but I couldn't keep playing because I'm a girl.
That's why I plan to save money,
then get into a sports university and aim for the national softball league.
Then I'll shout out to the whole world:
"This is the happiness I chose and achieved!"
That's my willpower.
Kushieda...
But because I was obsessive about it, I decided to not to cry anymore.
Even if it's hard and painful, I've decided I'll try my best.
But...
If someone sees me go through hardship and pain and cry, I guess it's a reward.
What happened to that hairpin?
Oh, that-
That must be the present you wanted to give to me on Christmas Eve, right?
That's-
I'm sorry, I really didn't know at first.
I thought it was a present from Taiga.
Even though I decided to not take it...
Even though it hurt you...
I want to apologize for wearing it in front of you.
I'm really sorry.
Where is that hairpin right now?
It's in my room, but-
Yeah, I can't accept it.
You know, there's something else that I can see.
It's that you like Taiga.
Yeah...
All right, Takasu-kun, this is a giant goodbye.
Run toward the thing that you can see!
Yeah!
Go, Takasu!
Ta-ka-su, hey! Ta-ka-su, yeah!
Ta-ka-su!
I knew you'd come.
H-How?
You're an honest person.
I knew you'd come to work even though you ran away.
You know, about what happened...
I... uh-
I heard Minorin's voice.
Don't laugh!
I'm not laughing.
Don't laugh at me, please.
I have something to tell you after work.
If... If I want to run away again,
you have to hold on to me.
Please.
Sure...
Our paycheck's pretty big.
Yeah...
Um...
You both lied!
Y-Yasuko...
Taiga!
What are you doing here?
Don't touch me!
Don't act so spoiled!
What can you do by yourself?
Hey, Taiga...
You're Takasu-kun, aren't you?
Y-Yes.
Thank you for always taking care of her.
From now on, she'll be staying with-
Like hell I'd stay with you, that man and that brat!
W-Why?
What's happening?
I don't get this at all.
I'm the one who doesn't get this!
You promised you wouldn't work,
but you lied and broke that promise!
I won't forgive you!
You won't forgive me?
You fainted because you pushed yourself too much for my sake...
That's why I'm working in your place!
What's wrong with that?!
We're a family!
Because we're a family, we should help each other out-
I don't care!
I just want you to concentrate on your studies!
I want you to find something you want to do and live a good life-
Who's the one who didn't concentrate on their studies?!
The one who couldn't do what they want and failed in life...
is you!
Ryuu-chan...
Quit forcing your failure's on me!
I-
Taiga...
Taiga?
Taiga!
Come back, Taiga!
My Silky Love
nijuu yojikan zutto
Every hour of the day
My Silky Love
kimi no koto omoutabi
whenever I think about you
My Silky Love
modokashii kono kimochi
these impatient feelings
My Silky Love
tada afurekaetteku
just overflow
suki to ieba kantan nanoni
It would be easier if I just tell you that I love you
kimi ga mae ni kichauto
but when you appear in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
my personality stands up and interferes
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku nanoni
That's just the way I am
donna ganbattemitemo kabe wa kuzusenai
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
I want you to realize my feelings
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
That's why I always gaze at you with the message of
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
"I love you"
saidai no yuuki de
with all of my courage!
yaburesouna SILK no HEART
My heart made of silk feels like it's about to rip apart
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
After meeting you, I finally realized
ai ni wa bukiyou dattandatte
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
My scars from love that I've almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashitano kyun to
have started to ache all of a sudden
itsuka wa watashirashiku suki to
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
I must tell you that I love you, or else I'll become even weaker
Confession
That damned old man's business failed and he ran away.
Seriously?
Yeah...
Then he told my real mom to take care of me.
But she already has a new family,
and she's even pregnant.
Her new husband is tall,
so their child will definitely have long legs.
I'll pale in comparison.
How... How can I fit in with a family like that?
If I were there, I'd only make everything awkward.
It's the same at the damn old man's place.
Because of my presence, everyone...
I've always thought of this...
If I had never been born, Yasuko would definitely have a better life.
She's still young, so she could probably redo high school...
Ryuuji?
Adults are really selfish.
They bring others trouble because of their own problems.
But...
I think I might be the one who's troubling Yasuko...
I'm still a child, after all.
That's right, if I had never been born-
Ryuuji!
No, you pig-head!
Don't look down on life!
W-What?
I think you're misunderstanding something.
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Baldy! Baldy!
What can you solve by doing that?
How could you say something naïve like that?!
It's exactly what you were saying!
But I'm still alive!
It's all because you're here!
No matter who you like...
No matter who you spend your life with...
I don't care!
I just want to be able to see you, Takasu Ryuuji!
That's why... That's why you can't say things like ""If only I had never been born"!
What happened?! What are you doing?!
W-What the hell do you mean?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Gosh, that sucks.
It's cold...
I said I'm sorry!
No! You never said that!
You really dwell on trivial things, don't you?
What blood type are you?
I'm a Taurus!
I'm not good with horoscopes, but roast lamb is good.
I'm not talking about that!
I'll be eighteen in two months!
I'll run away from Yasuko and the others.
I'll run and run,
then I'll sleep and wake up and then I'll run until it's my birthday.
At that time...
Marry me!
That way, we'll both be adults.
No one will get in our way.
My life will be yours until I die!
I lov-
Hold it right there!
You're so unfair! Didn't I tell you to listen to what I have to say first?
You sneaky dog!
What?
Proposing should be left to guys!
Listen to me, I made a promise with Minorin.
I promised to show her what I'll do.
T-Then let's say it together...
I...
...lo-
...lov-
Who the hell is calling at such an important time?
Ignore it.
Let's keep going, it's getting cold here...
What do you mean?! It'll be a pity!
Just pick it up already!
F-Fine.
Hey, Takasu, what the heck are you doing?
Kitamura?
Your mom and Aisaka's mom are searching everywhere for you guys!
Whatever, just come to where I tell you to.
W-Wait, Kitamura!
You sneezed on my hair!
W-
Why are you two all wet?
Why are we meeting at your house?
Your mothers haven't come here yet.
My aunt isn't here today, so come in.
You'll catch a cold if you stay in those clothes.
Take a shower first.
Turn right at the end.
Here, this and this too.
I can't believe I'm troubling you.
Seriously...
Thanks.
Hey, Taiga, your shoes!
Seriously...
Kawashima?
Oh yeah, Yuusaku said he'll bring you a change of clothes.
Anyways, I'm sorry for bothering you.
Excuse me.
You love Taiga, don't you?
W-What are you talking about?!
You do, don't you?
Y-Yeah...
Say it seriously.
What's up with you?
Say it.
Why-
I love Taiga.
You look so dumb!
You were the one who forced me to say it!
Taiga!
I was worried sick!
How could you?! How could you?! How could you?!
Minorin! Minorin, I'm sorry!
Kitamura, I'm sorry for bothering you.
Taiga! Taiga!
It's all right. Anyway, what are you guys planning to do now?
Well, we...
...plan to run away.
Huh?
We're serious!
I see.
Two more months, huh?
Why are you supporting them?!
Running away and then getting married?
That's too fast of a development!
After Ryuuji turns eighteen, we'll-
Moreover, where will you be living?
Well, about that...
We'll stay in a business hotel or maybe even a manga café for now...
Do you plan to live like that forever?
No... Well, after I come back...
Do you think you can come back?
Just imagine search parties looking for you and everyone at school finding out...
You two might even get expelled.
Well...
You know...
All the things I want just end up breaking.
That's why I decided to not desire anything.
But my feelings were rewarded.
My wish came true.
That's why I want to break this "all the things I want just end up breaking" jinx.
No, I have to break it.
That's why... That's why...
These are my savings that I always hold onto.
They're my life savings.
What are you doing?
Takasu-kun, Taiga,
I don't think your actions are correct.
I don't think I'll be able to approve of them either.
Minorin...
But if this is what you want to do, I have no right to object to it.
So take it.
You have to pay me back one day.
Here.
This is the key to my villa.
You've been there already, so you should know how to get there.
Kawashima...
Don't forget about me.
Take these.
Thank you, everyone.
Ami, thanks for today.
Good work, everyone!
I have some things to discuss with Amin.
Huh?! Why do I have to-
So you're friends again!
That's great, stupid Chihuahua.
Whatever, just go!
You too-
See you again, Minorin, stupid Chihuahua.
We'll definitely meet again!
Yeah.
Bye.
Wai-
What do you have to discuss with me?
Get your hand off me!
I feel so weak that I can't even stand anymore...
Wait, what are you-
What are you doing? You wanted to show me your crying face?
Crying is a nosebleed of the heart...
And why are you crying?
Because Taiga took Takasu-kun away from you?
Or-
I'm not even sure myself...
Even though I decided to never cry again...
You're so embarrassing.
But I've understood something.
If you trip while running down a hallway, you'll get a nosebleed.
If you trip in life, you'll cry.
Are you stupid?
It's still too early for us to be talking about life.
From now on, for ten years, for twenty years, for sixty years,
life will go on.
You have to run out once you've got your things.
About Ya-chan-
Don't worry, I can do it.
Bye.
Wait!
Uh... Oh yeah! Remember to bring your hair dryer!
I don't want to carry too much.
Yeah, okay.
Don't bring too much light clothing.
It'll just be dead weight.
I know!
Come out right after you're done!
If something happens, call me immediately!
Yeah, I will.
I'm back.
She's not back yet?
I-Inko-chan?!
Yasuko...
To: Ryuu-chan
Unread: Thank you for taking care of me
Go to your grandparents' house.
Show them this watch and they'll understand.
Oh, Mirano-san?
She called at dawn saying she'll be taking a vacation.
She...
ran away.
She's such a child!
If I run away...
Even after my birthday...
I'll still be a kid.
Look! Look!
It's chocolate!
You've been showing it off since yesterday.
Eat it already; just how long do you plan to show it off for?
Until it expires.
Weren't you the one who said that school isn't a place for trading chocolate?
I'm not trading. I'm just bringing it.
Right, Taiga?
Huh?
She's absent.
Takasu-kun too.
What's going on?
Did they catch a cold together?
More like a "fever."
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
Oohashi! Fight on! Fight on! Fight on...
Hey, seriously...
You're not going to see them off?
What? I can't hear you!
Regardless how strong of a will she has,
she broke down after being dumped by both Taiga and Takasu-kun.
Why do I have to have a snowball fight with-
You bitch!
Take this! Pure white sphere!
Since it's food for running away, I picked something more mature.
Look, cigar chocolate, chicken wafers and-
I've made lunch too.
Here.
Shouldn't you buy lunch from train stations when you run away?
I'll eat it anyway.
What about your mother?
She only cares about her own requtation.
I don't think she'll make a big fuss out of it.
Hey, what about Ya-chan?
She's fine.
I'll only say it now because we're running away...
You know, when Ya-chan said we're a family of three,
I was truly overjoyed!
You know what my "family" is like.
That's why... When we're really becoming a family like this,
will Ya-chan cry?
No, I don't mean that!
It won't be goodbye forever! It's not that I don't want to run away with you...
I think it's great, but...
I guess.
Listen, Taiga...
Sign: Takasu
Dad! D-D-D-D-D-D-D-Dad!
This is really...
Then you must be...
Nice to meet you; I am your grandchild, Takasu Ryuuji.
Also, she's my wife.
Also, I have a request.
We're not escaping, we're...
Next Episode Preview
Toradora!
Ryuuji showed me his method of dealing with it.
Now it's my turn.
Hey, Ryuuji...
Don't laugh at me. Don't get mad at me.