I am so tired, like really...
What's up?
Well there's this article I have to do where I have to go eat some tarako spaghetti, which I totally hate.
TL Note: Tarako is like caviar.
Is it supposed to be western or Japanese food? I don't get it.
Tarako spaghetti's fine, it's perfect for someone who lives on convenience store food like you, stupid Chihuahua!
Shut up!
Damn, that manager is really useless!
The next time I see her I'll peel off all of her drying scabs.
That's because you've never had delicious tarako spaghetti.
What?!
Delicious tarako spaghetti?
Such a thing cannot possibly exist!
Yeah, and don't try to make it out to be some sort of gourmet.
How about we go eat some tasty tarako spaghetti?
Well, might as well tag along with you, stupid dog.
I don't really have anything else to do.
Hurray for Gluttons
Let's eat up all those little lives,
Granulated goodness, Viva Tarako Spaghetti  !
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for gluttons!
Let's eat up all those little lives,
Granulated goodness, Viva Tarako Spaghetti!
Here it is!
Welcome, please take a seat.
This is great! Seconds, please!
Minorin!
Hey, Taiga, Amin, what a coincidence!
Did you watch the shopping channel last night?
Yeah, there was a dryer on sale, right?
It's unbelievable that they wouldn't sell it as a set with the water tank.
I wanted to buy it but wasn't allowed.
Then I'll make Ryuuji buy it.
That's a great idea.
Even though my name came up, I'm still being ignored by Kushieda.
So what are you up to?
Well, we're going to have some tarako spaghetti because stupid Chi and stupid dog were insisting on it.
Yeah, the tarako spaghetti here is great!
I was going to order three plates.
You fool!
Yeah! Yeah!
You have no idea what tarako spaghetti is!
I'll show you how to eat tarako spaghetti!
Now open your eyes and watch.
It's a duel!
Hey, if it's a tarako spaghetti battle why's there meat spaghetti?
Never mind that, what's with them having a battle all the sudden?
First up is "Jonny's Tarako Spaghetti"!
It's tasty!
It's so good it makes my hair stand on end!
My, it wasn't too bad.
It's obvious, but there is no tarako spaghetti in Italy.
But, unlike most European cultures,
Italians are known for eating octopus.
Generally it is thought that Italians are a merry bunch,
but North and South Italy are different.
The Southerners are merry and lively,
whereas the Northerners are more shy and quiet.
It must be because of the difference in climate.
Stop trying to sound smart like you know everything.
He didn't even make the spaghetti.
The weakest dog barks the loudest.
Now it's time for my experiment, "Jonny's Meat Spaghetti"!
It's tasty!
It's so good it makes my hair stand on end!
My, it wasn't too bad.
Niku, in other words meat, but meat doesn't stop there!
The gag is how meat and meet sound alike.
In English meet usually means "to meet up" and can also be used to mean "to get to know".
Paths or roads meeting.
Hands meeting.
A sports meet.
To see, to hear, to touch,
et cetera, et cetera.
The meanings are endless!
Terrifying, respect it!
You took too long to explain,
are you pretending to be a New Yorker?
She didn't even make the spaghetti.
So who wins?
Hmm, hard to decide.
It was a magnificent fight from both sides.
In the South East Asian country Laos there is a tribe where the custom is to kidnap your bride.
When the women are taken they have to be kicking and screaming.
That's why this duel is a draw!
Tarako spaghetti, your secrets are deep and mysterious.
Deep!
Too Deep!
Hey, what does S.O.S. stand for?
TL Note: S.O.S. is also the name of a Japanese drama
"Strawberry on the Shortcake", I think.
There's been many great cakes in convenience stores lately.
Do you eat the strawberry first or last?
Today's Inko
Sh-sh-sh-sh-shok-shock-shock-shoku-shoku
Bread
Pan!
Chopin
Shopan-shopan-shopan-shopan-shopan-pan-pan-pan...
Panties!
To be continued