We're havin' curry for dinner tonight?
Some Shinpei curry?
Ushio?!
Again, huh?
Geez, ya look like ya seen a ghost.
Yer supposed to appear at the summer festival on the 24th!
How do ya know that?
Huh?
Y'might not believe me, Shinpei,
but somethin' terrible's gonna happen on the 24th.
Pitch-black Shadow-like monsters are gonna gobble everyone up.
W-Wait a sec, don't tell me yeh've also been to that summer festival?!
Huh?
Wait, ya did too, Shinpei?
Washing with water made it a little better.
Wh-What is it?
Is that curry I smell?
C-Correct!
Wow, I didn't realize y'could use those ingredients like that.
That was a mighty rumble from yer tummy, Shin.
Sounds just like Sis.
Thank goodness.
If yer hungry, that must mean yer okay.
Y-Yeah.
Calm down, calm down!
Dice onions
Grate garlic and ginger
Take a step back, recite the curry recipe, and calm down!
Roughly chop tomatoes
Julienne the peppers
Cut chicken thighs into small pieces, salt
Add 1 tbsp veg. oil, 3 tbsp butter to pan,
saute onions, garlic, ginger
Add tomatoes
Th-This is pretty bad.
Add 3 tbsp weak wheat flour
Add 2 tbsp curry powder, 1 tbsp salt,
and keep simmering (roux complete)
Move finished roux to a pot
Fry chicken in separate pan
Miss Nagumo,
this goes beyond just "different"!
Sorry I'm back so late, Shinpei.
Karikiri sure loves his speeches.
Welcome home, Alan.
I'm almost done.
Mio, y'should be lendin' a hand!
My expertise is eatin'!
Sure smells nice.
That's Ushio's favorite dish, ain't it?
Alan will go to the washroom in five minutes,
then Mio will use the restroom.
Go to my room when they're gone.
Don't let them see you!
Does she even get how serious this is?!
Lie on the phone to Totsumura
Tell Sou I'll call him tomorrow
Y-Yes! It's done!
Lastly, add the peppers and salt to taste
Huh? Where're ya goin'?
O-Oh, I was just gonna eat in my room.
With two plates?
Well, y'see, I'm starvin'!
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Curry!
Cur-ry! Cur-ry!
Th-This is her curry rhythm!
Memento
Curry, curry, hmph, hmph, hmph!
Shinpei's curry!
Damn it! Why is this happening?
Don't let the Shadows' words move you.
Can I dig in?
Go for it.
Yay! Time ta dig in!
Ushio's Shadow...
How did this thing manage to loop with me?
It's a natural thought.
Yummy!
Where'd ya come from and how'd ya get here?
Huh? I walked, duh.
But I was on Omoto Beach when I woke up for some reason.
Oh, don't worry. Ain't nobody saw me!
It's a monster!
It seems I'm a monster or somethin'.
I won't let nobody see me.
A monster? Th-That's not...
That's not... true...
The heck? That tickled like crazy, y'know!
What'd ya do?
Oh, I—sorry.
Geez, I got chills from that!
I can kill it right now if I stab its shadow with my knife.
So yum!
Just look at it. It's totally off-guard.
But she did actually help me back there.
This thing...
Tokyo?!
Alan knows someone there.
I'll be staying with them and go to culinary school there.
I'm not gonna try for a high school in Wakayama.
What the heck?
It's a done deal.
I ain't hear a peep about this.
It's not like I needed to tell ya.
Why? Ya can't just decide somethin' that important on yer own!
Why can't I decide on my own?
I can't be a Kofune kid anymore.
I wanna be able to make a living on my own as soon as I can.
I just can't keep bein' a burden to y'all!
A burden?
Do ya hate this place, Shinpei?
Huh?! Where'd that come from?!
No, Ushio.
Forget it! I ain't got nothin' to say to ya!
I... love ya!
No, you forget it!
I don't wanna keep being yer step-brother forever.
Hey, Shinpei.
Since today's yer last day,
I want yer curry for dinner.
What?
I got lots of packing and stuff to do, y'know.
Maybe next time.
Shinpei, ya dummy.
I thought there wouldn't be a next time.
But...
Ya finally made it.
I'm so glad I got to eat yer curry again.
I'm so glad to be alive.
Is it good?
Seconds!
When Dad makes it, the flavor's just not the same.
Yers is still the best, Shinpei.
This is Ushio. The real Ushio.
I see. That's good.
Hey, Shinpei, is the same thing gonna happen again when the 24th rolls around?
Yes, but I'm trying to stop it.
I'll help.
I'd hate for those monsters to ruin the Hitogashima summer festival.
And I'd hate it even more if Mio and everyone else disappear too.
Right. Me too.
Let's stop it together.
Yeah!
Can ya copy humans?
Looks like ya can't.
It is currently 8:45 PM.
Mio's Shadow should appear in another ten minutes.
How are things on your end, Nezu?
All clear.
The wind's blowing a little,
but there's enough visibility from the outside lights.
Any contact from Shinpei?
None.
Ryuunosuke, don't rely too much on what that kid said.
Prey has a habit of never doin' what ya want it to do.
Hunting is all about adaptability, got it?
Roger.
Hizuru
Any issues?
It's from Miss Nagumo.
Should I tell them about Ushio? Should I lie?
Hizuru
Any issues?
But...
Shinpei?
O-Oh.
By the way, how long are ya plannin' on lookin' like that?
Wearin' a swimsuit indoors is kinda weird, y'know.
Huh? Gosh, yer right. Why—
I didn't think it was strange until now.
Wh-Whoa!
What in tarnation do ya think yer doin'?!
It wasn't me!
My swimsuit just vanished!
Why? Why the heck?!
Maybe 'cause it was a copied swimsuit?
Just gimme somethin' to wear!
Huh? Mio's Shadow's comin'?
Didja lock up?
We're fine.
But I don't feel like there's much of a point in locking up, anyway.
They can withdraw into their own shadows and slip through even the tiniest crack.
What the heck? Can I do that too?
Don't worry about it.
It's never come into our house before.
Not even once.
Shin?
It's Mio! Hide!
Ya done eating?
Hm?
I'm trying to do the dishes.
Oh, right! The dishes!
Yeah, good to go?
Huh? Ya used two spoons?
And two cups?
Do you think that's strange?
I don't find it strange at all!
Why'd yer accent change?
What, is Sis here?
I mean, ya made this extra portion for her, didn't ya?
I'm sure she's here.
On Hitogashima, the souls of the dead return to their homes and become protective deities.
That's what Karikiri said.
R-Right.
Ya can leave the dishes.
I'll wash 'em later.
'Kay. Thanks fer dinner, Shin!
Holy cow. I think I lost a few years of my life.
Mio can be really perceptive.
Fat choy?!
Wh-What? Need somethin' else?
Huh?
That's not...
Ushio!
That hurts, dammit!
We can't possibly beat this thing in battle.
If I'm gonna die anyway,
I should do something. Anything!
What's the best thing I can do right now?
Bring it, Mio.
Fight me!
Sh-Shinpei...
Sis, why're ya on his side?
He killed a Shadow with Nezu and Minakata.
Well, yer pretty stupid, ya fake!
I love Shinpei.
What's wrong with sidin' with the person ya love?!
Ya died.
Ya died, Sis.
Yer dead!
Shin!
What did I tell ya?
It... It hurts...
Why? Shin, I...
Shin, I too...
Ushio!
Hey! Hang in there, Ushio!
Pardon me.
M-Miss Nagumo—
Why are you getting in the way?
First, I'm glad you're okay, Shinpei.
But what is that?
It's a Shadow, right?
Now, move and let me kill it.
N-No!
Did that Shadow poison your mind?
Remember what I said?
Talk too long to a Shadow and it'll lead you astray.
I know that ya hate the Shadows!
And I understand that yer goal is to eliminate every last one!
But!
This one has saved my life twice now,
shielding me with her own body!
Not thinking of the consequences,
leaping before even attempting to think—
She's that idiot Ushio!
So, Miss Nagumo, I beg ya.
Just like ya took care of my arm, please treat her wound!
Honestly, boy.
Not only do you beg me to let it go,
you want me to treat its wound?
If you have sided with the Shadows,
then I shall kill you as well.
That's fine!
Then I'll loop again and convince ya next time for sure!
Shinpei...
Mio...
Is the real Mio okay?
Sh-She's...
I confirmed earlier that the original is in the bath.
Really?!
I see.
That's good to hear...
That voice is the same.
Mis... Nagum—
It's the voice that led me to this island in the first place.
Adaptability, huh.
Very well.
Show me the wound.
Kofune Ushio sent me that message.
Summer Time Rendering
No way. What? Wait!
My arm's gone!
U-Ushio!
Huh? It doesn't hurt now.
That wound was a projection of the damage done to your main body.
I suspect your typical medical treatment will be ineffective. Don't get carel—
Aw, who cares? It don't hurt no more.
Yer sure takin' this well.
You sure have grown.
I'm Minakata Hizuru.
You may not remember me,
but I used to frequent Kofune.
Huh? Really?
Sorry, I don't recall.
Would you listen to this?
The summer festival... The Shadows kill everyone...
The only... can stop it... Ajiro Shinpei.
We need your help...
please...
Do you remember this message?
What the? That was my voice.
This is the reason why I came to this island.
So you don't remember it?
I see.
Then it's fine. Forget about it.
The more pressing issue is why Mio's Shadow veered from Shinpei's prediction and entered the house!
It seemed to know that Shiori's Shadow had been defeated.
They're clearly sharing information.
It's possible that Mio acknowledged us as a threat and moved to eliminate us.
She was after me and Nezu in the previous loop.
But the Shadows know Shinpei is one of us now.
So Mio made her way inside to kill him.
So it's because I joined y'all at Koba Mart?
But how did they find out?
I thought ya killed all the Shadows there.
No matter the reason,
I cannot continue to work with you.
As long as you intend to stick with Ushio's Shadow, that is.
It is true that Ushio saved you and most likely bears us no ill will.
But even if Ushio is as faulty as you claim,
there's no telling when she'll be fixed.
That's the greatest compromise we can make.
Miss Nagumo!
On the 23rd at just past 3, ya were killed by Mio's Shadow in the forest around the shrine.
We may have defeated Mio,
but a replacement might come after ya!
Please don't die!
"Fate can be changed."
This is the perfect chance to prove that.
Bistro Kofune
July 23rd
Shinpei.
Mornin'.
Y-Yer awake?
I'm hungry. And thirsty.
I'll get ya somethin' from downstairs.
Yay!
Oh, right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Thanks, Tokiko. I feel a little better now.
No, it's fine. Sorry to keep ya up all night.
Okay, talk to ya later.
Mornin', Shin.
I'm already up, so ya don't have to go to my room, okay?
Th-That's all.
O-Okay.
1st Loop
7/23 (Monday)
7:30
- Mio wakes me up
- Set up Kofune
- Eat breakfast alone
(leftover curry and bread)
Now she won't come to wake me up.
Wait, Shin!
Mio gave ya this?
Yeah, this is the original.
The original...
Does it jog yer memory?
Like about that stuff before ya died.
Bistro Kofune
Just think about it for a while, okay?
Huh? Where ya goin'?
Bistro Kofune
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
The restaurant's reopening today.
I see. That's so like Dad.
Alan always said that a restaurant's always gotta be there for people, never changing.
He's trying to preserve the sense of a normal life.
Hey, Shinpei.
Sorry, am I early?
Thanks for waiting.
Sure.
Here.
An umbrella? But it's super sunny out.
Never ya mind.
Have ya gone crazy or somethin'?
Ya probably already know what this is about.
There's somethin' I need to tell ya about how Ushio died.
The strangle marks, right?
Basically, we think I was murdered.
Yeah, actually—
Who the hell are ya?!
Ushio, ya can take the disguise off now.
Huh? Ushio?
Huh? Wait, b-buh—
Ushio?!
Yo!
He's frozen.
We told Sou everything.
And he, once again, listened in silence until the end.
Sorry. If only I resuscitated ya better.
If only it was better...
I know an apology's not enough! But at least...
At least punch me, otherwise I—
She kicked him!
Stand up, Sou!
Are ya happy now?
We're relying on ya here!
How long are ya gonna be a crybaby for?
This is the "private" beach behind the elementary school.
Is this where I died?
She really has no memory of it.
Right.
Oh, that's my phone.
I wanted to look through it, but it's locked.
Huh? The password's changed.
Oh, it opened.
Huh?
I used the fingerprint scanner.
Be it texts, notes, photos—just look through anything.
Friday was the 20th, right?
That was the morning of the day before I died.
Friday
There's a single video file from that day.
That must be it!
Gimme a sec. I'll play it back.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Flow, My Tears