Tomoe Mami here.
A senior at Mitakihara Middle School, just like you two.
And... I'm a magical girl that has made a contract with Kyubey.
Another weird dream...
Good morning, Madoka!
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll continue walking upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでく
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 2   I thought that was really nice
Are our lines too long for you?
Maybe it's because you're illiterate.
Also, we love all of you :3
This show is brought to you by the sponsors you see here.
Madoka, I heard you got back late last night.
An upperclassman from school invited me to their house.
I won't be an annoying mom and impose a curfew or anything like that, but make sure you call home before dinner.
I'm sorry.
I guess people really can't see him.
Wow...
What a beautiful room!
I live alone, so make yourselves at home.
I didn't really have time to get ready for guests though.
Mami-san, this is really good!
It's totally good!
Thank you.
Since you've been chosen by Kyubey, this is your problem as well.
I thought a decent explanation of what has been going on would be in order.
Sure! Just ask me anything.
Sayaka-chan, you have that backwards.
Wow, that's pretty!
This is a Soul Gem.
It's a jewel created by the girls that are chosen by Kyubey, born of their contract.
It identifies them as a magical girl and is the source of their magic power.
What do you mean by contract?
I'll grant each of you one wish, whatever you want.
What? Seriously?
A wish...
It can be anything.
No matter the miracle, I can make it happen.
Gold, silver, and priceless treasures... Immortality...
A Manchu Han Imperial Feast!
Umm, I'm not sure about that last one...
But a Soul Gem is produced in exchange.
Those that receive these jewels are charged with a mission to fight witches.
Witches?
Hey, Mom.
Hm?
What if... What if you were told that any wish you had could be granted with magic, what would you do—
I'd get rid of a few of those board members.
The president is getting a bit too old for this too—it's time for him to think about retirement.
But there's no one to replace him, so...
You should become president yourself, Mom.
I didn't think about that.
As long as I make sure I work things out with sales in advance, planning and administration will do whatever I want.
If that happens, the only problem left is the baldy in accounting.
I know... I'll just pull off his toupée.
Mom, you look scary.
What's a witch? Are they different from magical girls?
If magical girls are said to be born from positive desires like wishes, then witches are born from negative desires like curses.
Magical girls spread hope, where witches spread despair.
And to make matters worse, they can't be seen by normal humans.
Doubt and suspicion, extreme anger and hate.
They bring seeds of catastrophe to this world.
The curse of a witch is almost always behind unexplained suicides and murders.
They become a formless evil and eat away at humans from the inside-out.
If they're so dangerous, how come no one knows about them?
That's because witches hide within barriers and never show themselves to people.
The labyrinth-type area you wandered into before was one of their barriers.
That was pretty close.
Humans swallowed up by those barriers usually don't make it out alive.
Mami-san, you're fighting something that dangerous?
That's right. I put my life on the line.
That's why I think you two should weigh your options carefully.
Any desire you have can be granted, now that you've been chosen by Kyubey.
But doing so can lead to death.
That's a hard choice...
So, I had an idea. Why don't you come along with me while I take out some witches?
Huh?
It'll be better for you to see through your own eyes what it means to fight witches.
Once that happens, you can think about whether or not you have a wish so great that you'd risk putting yourself in danger.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good mor—
Morning, Sayaka.
Is something the matter, Sayaka-san?
I guess we really are the only ones that can see him.
Seems that way.
Umm...
Don't worry about it. Let's go.
It looks like we can talk to each other just by thinking.
Huh? We already have magical powers like that?!
No, no, I'm still just using myself to relay your thoughts.
But it's pretty useful for talking to each other without anyone hearing, right?
It feels kind of weird.
What's going on between the two of you?
You keep exchanging looks.
N-No, we've been... umm...
Have you two grown so close that you can understand each other by looking into each others' eyes?
Oh my! I can't believe you've gotten that close
to each other after a single day.
What happened after I saw you yesterday?!
That'd... never happen. Seriously.
It's true a lot of things happened, though.
But two girls mustn't do such things!
That's forbidden love!
You forgot your bag!
Hitomi-chan is kind of like Sayaka-chan today.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Are you sure it's okay for you to come to school with us like nothing happened?
Why?
I told you that the girl from yesterday transferred into this class, right?
Wasn't she trying to kill you?
I actually think school would be safer.
Mami's here, too.
Mami's a senior, so her class is kind of far from here.
No need to worry.
I can hear everything you're saying.
We're still in range of telepathic communication with distances this short.
Uh... Good morning.
I'm watching over all of you, so don't worry.
Besides, I'm sure she wouldn't attack any of you in public.
I guess it's fine, then...
Great. Speak of the devil.
Is that transfer student a... magical girl, as well?
Just like you, Mami-san?
Hmm, she definitely is.
It looks like she's quite powerful.
But that means she should be a force for good that tries to take out witches, right?
Why did she attack Madoka all of a sudden, then?
She was after me.
I imagine she was trying to stop the creation of new magical girls.
Huh?
Why? Wouldn't it be better to have as many people fighting the same enemy as possible?
That's not necessarily the case.
It's more common for it to become competitive.
Huh? Why?
You get a certain compensation when you take out a witch.
So, sometimes depending on the circumstances, people will race to be the first one to do it, and sometimes even fight over it.
So basically, she guessed in advance that Kyubey would try to talk to Madoka,
and that's why she's been going after her since this morning.
That's probably what happened.
Don't worry about it, Madoka.
If she tries to do something, I'll punch her lights out for you!
Mami-san's here to help us, too.
That's right. Ignoring Miki-san's potential help, I'm here for you, so everything will be fine. Don't worry.
Don't ignore me!
So like we've learned so far, phrases which have subjects that are the person or thing doing the action are called active voice.
In contrast, a phrase is said to be in passive voice when the subject—the object or person—receives an action, such as "B is verb'd by A."
Passive voice takes the form of the to-be verb plus the past participle.
For example, if I were to say "he likes me (kare wa watashi no koto ga suki)..."
Here you go.
Hey, Madoka.
Have you thought about what wish you want to make?
No, what about you?
I haven't either.
I kind of thought a whole bunch of things would just come to me...
There are many things I want to have and do, but the fact that we'll have to risk our lives kind of makes you rethink things, doesn't it?
You end up thinking that it isn't really worth that much in the end.
Yeah.
That's surprising. Most girls answer immediately.
I'm sure we're just stupid.
Huh? You really think so?
Yep. We're happy idiots.
It really shouldn't be all that uncommon—having a wish you'd go so far as to trade your life for.
I think there are a lot of people in the world with wishes and desires like that.
If we can't think of anything, it just means that we really haven't had anything that bad happen to us.
We've had too much given to us and have become dull and stupid.
It makes me wonder: Why us?
Don't you think it's unfair?
I'm sure there are other people who'd really want a chance like this.
Sayaka-chan...
Don't worry.
You trying to pick up where we left off yesterday?
No, that isn't my intent.
I wanted to handle things before he made contact with Kaname Madoka,
but it's too late for that now.
So what have you decided?
Are you going to become a magical girl, too?
I...
How is this any of your business?!
Do you remember what I said to you yesterday?
Yeah...
That's fine, then. I pray that my warning doesn't fall on deaf ears.
H-Homura-chan!
What... wish did you make to become a magical girl?
Hitomi, I'm sorry. We have a few things to do today.
My, secrets now, huh?
We...
I'm so jealous!
No one can come between you two anymore,
can they?!
Umm, we told you that's not what's really going on...
Akemi-san, would you like to stop by a café on the way home today with us?
I have something I need to take care of again today.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's begin our first lesson on the magical girl experience.
Are you two ready?
I'm not sure if it'll help, but I brought this!
I thought it'd be better than nothing.
Well, if your will is that strong, then that'll help.
Madoka, did you bring anything?
Huh? Oh... I have this...
Wow...
I-I figured I might as well think about what outfit I'd like to wear.
I guess you're plenty enthusiastic.
That's great. I can't top that.
This shows the magical residue left behind by the witch yesterday.
Searching for witches basically involves a lot of walking.
All you do is follow the Soul Gem as it picks up the witch's whereabouts.
That's surprisingly uncool.
The light hasn't changed at all.
It's been a whole day since we left the witch to its own devices.
There's very little left to track.
What would have happened if you chased after it right away, instead?
I might have been able to take it out,
but I wouldn't have gone after it if it meant leaving you two there.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Mami-san's one of the good guys!
That transfer student on the other hand... She pisses me off so much.
I wonder if she's really that bad of a girl.
Woe! Woe!
Thou hast her destroyed
The beautiful world,
By a mighty fist;
She tottered, she hurled!
A half-god beat her to nothing!
We bring
The ruins over the void and,
Dirges sing
Over the belost beautiful
This is from Goethe's Faust
Hey, Mami-san, do you have any idea where the witch is likely to be at least?
Witches' curses result in traffic accidents and injuries the most.
So it would be best to check big roads and highways and any entertainment districts that would be likely to see a fight.
As well as any places which are conducive to suicide that are devoid of people.
Additionally, the worst possible case would be if they possessed a hospital or something similar.
Since they're taking life energy from people who are already weak, it leads to a horrible situation.
These are rather strong pulses of magical energy.
It might be close.
I'm sure it's here.
Mami-san, look!
A kiss from a witch.
I knew it.
Is she...
It's okay. She's just unconscious.
Let's go.
More mightily
Earthen children
More splendidly
Build her again,
In your bosoms build
her strong!
New life-stories
Commence
With fair sense,
And new song,
To sound thereon!
I won't let you go today.
Wow.
It's nothing special, but it'll at least help to protect you.
Make sure you keep alongside me, okay?
Okay!
More mightily
Earthen children
More splendidly
Build her again,
In your bosoms build
her strong!
New life-stories
Commence
With fair sense,
And new song,
To sound thereon!
Stay away! Stay away!
Well, are you scared?
T-This is nothing!
I'm scared, but...
Keep it up!
We'll be at the core of the barrier soon!
Look. That's a witch.
It looks gruesome.
Are you going to fight that?
It's okay. I won't lose.
Keep back.
Someday the light of love you hold
within your eyes will transcend time
and destroy the dream of a world
racing towards destruction.
Now that you've drank every ounce
of your hesitation, what do you desire?
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow
for this greedy admiration?
I want to see you, smiling with the
power to destroy even God,
like the ancient magic you showed
me in my dreams when I was young.
Mami-san!
Don't worry.
I can't let my future mentees see me when I'm down.
Everything depends on these feelings of
courage from the flower that was plucked
that now lays in
my frightened hands.
This wish will
awaken that light.
Close, but not good enough.
Pilo Finale!
She won?
Wow.
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch egg.
E-Egg?
If you're lucky, sometimes witches will have one on them.
Don't worry. It's safe in that form.
Actually, it's extremely useful.
My Soul Gem is a little less bright than it was last night, right?
Now that you mention it.
But if you use a Grief Seed...
Take a look.
It's back to normal.
See?
Now the magic I've depleted is back to normal.
This is the compensation for defeating witches that I was speaking of before.
You should be able to use it one more time.
I'll give it to you,
Akemi Homura-san.
It's her.
Or are you unhappy sharing with another?
It was your prey. You should keep this for yourself.
I see. So that's your answer.
She really sucks!
It would be better if we could all just get along.
That only works if everyone feels the same way.
Where am I...
What was I doing?
Wh-Why was I...
Why did I do that?
It's okay. It's okay now.
You were just having a bad dream for a little while.
It kind of feels like it's all finally over.
Yeah.
It's too difficult for me to come up with a wish I want made true on a moment's notice,
but seeing Mami-san trying her best to save others was really amazing.
If someone like me can really help other people,
I thought that would be really nice.
Illustrator Hikawa Hekiru
Just acting cool, not able to talk to anyone about your problems,
even though you might be scared, even though you might be sad...
Just crying all alone...
It's not really that great being a magical girl.
Episode 3    I'm not scared of anything anymore
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Yumi & Yuka
Editor: guymam
Timer: kozu
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
limitbreakingcat
King_Arthur
goof
euronymous