We asked Dr. Wakaoji to
be Full Moon's producer,
but for some reason,
he wouldn't accept.
I tried different tactics,
but none of them worked.
Just when I thought,
"Dr. Wakaoji won't do it,"
all of a sudden, he said that
he would produce Full Moon's recording.
It seems like something that
Takuto said made him decide.
But I wonder what Takuto said to him.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
SHI-CHAN's Music Power!
Hello, It's SHI-CHAN,
also known as Shizue Oda.
How has everybody been?
Well then! Let's start with
this week's top news!
It seems Oji from Route L
is going to make a comeback
to the music scene by
producing Full Moon.
You do pretty well there, Oshige.
Who'd a thought you'd get Wakaoji?
Well then, let's both do our best!
Yes!
Anyway, the song is a phantom song
by Route L, called "Eternal Snow."
And on a different note,
the same song will be produced
by Kohei Takasu
for another newcomer,
Madoka Wakamatsu!
It seems that Kohei Takasu
has a new rival on the scene.
In the 60's, it was common
for two different singers
to sing the same song,
as a sort of battle,
but nowadays, that's quite rare.
It's going to attract a lot of attention!
He's late.
Oh, he's here!
Dr. Wakaoji!
Oh!
Dr. Wakaoji! You're...
What? It doesn't look good on me?
I thought I had to change my feelings,
so I thought maybe I'd change my look.
No! You look really good!
R-Really?
Really!
It's Takasu... So how is it?
Okay, okay.
Keep at it like that.
Yeah, okay...later.
Umm... It will be all right, won't it?
You mean... Will you win?
Yes.
You called me in because
you wanna win, right?
Y-Yes!
Then don't make that face
and believe in me!
Okay!
There's the face, that's the true face
of Madoka Wakamatsu.
Yes!
Yes? Already? You're fast!
No, it's not bad.
Just send it my way.
What? You sent it already?
You're fast!
I will not lose. I can't lose.
I-It's not yet been decided?
Yes.
Isn't that bad?
We're already behind them.
Being first or second isn't the issue.
We have to make something
we are satisfied with.
That's our job.
Even so...
What about the schedule?!
So you're saying you want
to compromise the quality of the song
in order to meet the deadline?
Compromise? I was just...
We can do something
about the schedule,
but we have to decide on
the concept, right?
That's right!
If we don't know the concept,
we don't know who to ask to arrange it.
Without that we can't do anything here.
So please decide as soon as possible!
Full Moon?
Y-Yes?
What is the message you want to
convey to your fans with the song?
My fans? Umm...
Well...
Just a general idea is fine.
Yes... Well... That's...
It's okay. You don't have to
give me an answer right away.
You can take your time
and think about it.
O-Okay.
We're finished for today then.
Be seeing you.
Will we make it?
I'm worried about this.
It's certain he has the talent, but...
Don't worry.
Just trust that doctor.
Huh?
Umm... Well, you seemed concerned
about something so I thought...
Oh. I was just thinking.
Up to now, I just thought about
what I wanted to convey to Eichi,
but I realized just now...
What do I really want to
say with this song?
Oh, that thing...
Hmm... "Your message," huh?
CHILDREN'S DICTIONARY
Let's see...
Eternal... Eternal...
Eda...mame?
That's not it!
What that doctor was trying to
tell you is something much simpler
than understanding the lyrics.
What?
For example, when people
hear your "Eternal Snow..."
Will they be unable to stop their tears?
Will they feel courageous?
Will they be unable to stop
themselves from smiling?
Or will they be unable
to stop laughing?
Hey! That's going too far there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's what he meant.
– Oh...
So, what do you think?
What? Well...
Well, think about it for a while.
Huh?
Did you find your answer?
No.
Don't tell me that you
didn't sleep again.
I did sleep,
but I couldn't stop thinking
about it and I woke up.
What were you thinking about?
I was wondering what Dad was
thinking when he wrote this song.
Huh?
Speaking of which,
what was your dad like?
I don't know, not just my dad,
but my mom too.
Even though they're your parents?
Yeah.
According to the teacher
from the orphanage...
My mom died right after
she gave birth to me,
and they told me when I was a year old,
my dad became a star in the sky.
Then I heard that my dad was a musician,
and that's when I started to listen
to the songs my dad wrote.
And two years ago...
Nice to meet you.
My name is Mitsuki!
When my grandma took me in,
I tried asking her about that, but...
There is nothing to talk about!
It seemed like Grandma didn't like
being asked about my mom and dad,
and it's been like that
until this very day.
Then let's ask that doctor.
What?
Wasn't he in the same band
with your dad?
Yeah, that's a good idea!
You should do that Mitsuki!
You might be able to
find out something.
Yeah!
Well, I only knew them
while I was in the band, but...
your mother, Hazuki,
used to help out just like that.
She was younger than me,
but she was mature like an older sister.
She was a very kind person.
And then one day, they found out
that Hazuki was pregnant.
You're going to elope?!
W-Wait a minute!
We're supposed to go on tour,
and if you, the leader, aren't here...
Hello?
Hello!
Aoi!
She was pregnant with me.
Yeah, but your grandmother
opposed their marriage.
Your father, the leader of the band,
left and Route L disbanded.
After that, nobody knew where
your mother and father went to.
But two years ago...
Now, Mitsuki.
H-Hello. My name is Mitsuki Koyama.
It's nice to meet you!
I thought you looked like her,
and it turned out it really was you.
I kept quiet because of
your grandmother.
Dad, Mom...
So, did that help at all?
Oh, yes.
Umm...
Could it be?
Dad wrote that song for Mom?
Could be.
I want to find out more
about my mom and dad.
I wonder if there's anything
that belonged to them.
Let's look around.
Yeah. If we look around the house
we might be able to find something.
Is there anything?
This is your grandmother
we're talking about.
She's probably thrown everything away.
You don't know that until you try looking!
But where?
Oh! If there is anything,
it should be there!
– Huh?
Inside the storage warehouse!
I'm unable to come to
the phone right now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Hey, Madoka?
It's me!
I haven't seen you much lately!
Let's go out again like we used to.
It's not like you to get all serious.
Full Moon...
I'm not going to lose to you!
Maybe I'm here too early.
Good mor—
Mr. Takasu!
Mr. Takasu...
He's been working all night.
Until now, everybody in this
world was so cold to me.
And for the first time...
Mr. Takasu...
I'm going to do my best to
meet your expectations!
Oh?
Oh, this!
Wow! It's an old RIBBON magazine!
Mom read RIBBON too!
That's so great!
Let me see.
– Look, Meroko!
– This is so funny!
Hey! Are we supposed to
fool around right now?
Oh, you're right.
Cripes!
Huh?
A rat! A rat!
I hate rats!
– This looks newer than the other things.
– Oh, I hate rats!
No!
Takuto!
Watch out!
Huh?
This...
That box seems relatively new
compared to the others.
Open it.
Yeah.
Oh! That was close.
But...
I was really shocked!
This again?
Me?
What is it?
No... It's not me.
– Huh?
That's my mom.
Oh! You look exactly like her.
Yeah.
Oh?
Oh? A musical jewelry box?
What?
Is it broken?
Oh?
H-Hey.
Look at this.
"To Hazuki with Love."
Hmm?
For Hazuki with all his love.
What? Then, Dad gave this to her?
Probably.
A music box that Dad gave to Mom.
It's inside here.
Dad's feelings for Mom.
You're right.
I want to hear.
Dad's feelings...
Wow!
It's a nice song.
Yeah!
What do you think?
It's warm.
– Huh?
It's warm...this feeling,
I don't know how else to describe it.
Oh! I wish I could express
it in better in words!
Hey, it's a phone call.
Y-Yeah.
Oh! Mitsuki?
We got a job just now!
Can you come out now?!
Y-Yes.
Then I'll see you outside the fence.
Okay!
I have a job right now!
What?!
Hurry! I'll stay here for you!
Yeah!
Huh?!
What?!
D-Did she find us?!
Here!
– Did she...
– ...figure it out?
Hazuki...
Huh?
Hazuki! Where are you going?!
I'm pregnant with his baby.
What?! That man's child?!
I'm going to leave this house
if you can't accept him.
Hazuki!
If you have a child with
your weak body...
Hazuki!
Music...
I hate music.
It always takes away
what's precious to me.
Where did you get that?
It was a present from
my dad to my mom.
Ms. Oshige, I figured out my message.
What is it?
I want to warm people's hearts with music.
Even those who hate music.
I want them to like music.
Isn't that right, Mom? Dad?
Oh no, Takuto!
It's in the tabloids...
"Full Moon and Doctor Wakaoji
are madly in love!"
Huh? That's impossible.
How could that happen?
Seems like Madoka is
up to no good again.
That girl just doesn't give up!
Just when we thought we got away,
here comes more trouble!
At this rate, how are we going
to do the recording.
What do we do?
Next time on Full Moon:
"I Won't Lose"
– Look forward to it!