The treacherous sunset wipes away those annoying sweat drops.
As if it wanted to tear it apart,
the machine roars as if it's singing a song.
Selty
Sturluson
The quiet fairy is over here.
Yagiri
Seiji
Atonement is a piece of a broken love.
Yagiri
Namie
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Heiwajima Shizuo
Over the valley of buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't be meaningless.
Erika
Karisawa
The morning sun rises, yeah!
Yumasaki
Walker
Kyohei
Kadota
Coming out of the darkness!
As long as you feel it now,
Togusa
Saburo
you'll see that dream isn't meaningless.
There's surely something only we can see.
Mikado
Ryuugamine
Something that no one will snatch away from us.
Masaomi
Kida
The fact that this aim isn't meaningless!
Anri
Sonohara
Dollars?
I don't know many of the details,
but apparently they're a big group who'll beat you to death on a moments notice.
B-But you cut class on the first day...
I said, I don't know what you're talking about!
Well, just stay away from a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo.
Orihara Izaya?
That one's extremely dangerous, so stay away from him.
Yeah. His name's Simon.
He brings in customers for that Russian sushi shop over there.
The sun rises, yeah!
Brezhnev
Simon
Over the horizon, oh!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
that light won't be meaningless.
Splendid! Splendid!
Russian Sushi!
It's delicious and cheap!
Mister! Don't run away!
Russian Sushi!
Excuse me...
Do you understand Russian?
Yes, I do.
Ah, great.
Could you tell us how to get there from here?
Oh, just go straight on this road.
Are you two tourists?
Yes.
This is an interesting city.
You'll enjoy your trip, I'm sure.
Thank you very much.
Please stop by the restaurant if you have time.
Ikebukuro... a hectic city that spans from the east to the west.
There's a big entertainment district to the north,
and at least a million people come to this city everyday.
In this huge city... Ikebukuro.
This city is filled with foreigners.
This boy,
and also, this girl...
both came to this city to find something they're looking for.
They came to this city to change something.
Rampant
Clean-up
Officers
Yamazaki
Nishizaki
Health
Officers
Tsuchida
Asakura
Disciplinary
Officers
Kuzuhara
Kanemura
Oh, we still don't have any classroom representatives.
Clean-up
Officers
Yamazaki
Nishizaki
Health
Officers
Tsuchida
Asakura
Classroom
Representatives
Is there anyone who would like to run for the position?
A new city...
where no one knows anything about who you are.
It's your one and only chance to become someone new.
However...
Sonohara...
Sonohara Anri?
Any other volunteers?
Well, then you're our female classroom representative.
I'll leave the rest up to you, Sonohara.
U-Um...
Are there any males who want to run for classroom representative?
I think I want to do it, but I also think it'll be a pain...
But I don't want anyone else to take the position either...
You do it.
Huh? Seriously?
Doesn't it look like it'll be a pain?
But you get to work with her !
Yes.
U-Um...
I'm Ryuugamine... Mikado.
Classroom
Representatives
Sonohara
Ryuugamine
Clean-up
Officers
Yamazaki
Nishizaki
Health
Officers
Tsuchida
Asakura
Sonohara-san!
Um... about the meeting tomorrow with the other classes...
T-This is my first time doing something like this, so...
Please, excuse me!
I have something I have to do, so if you'll excuse me.
Well aren't you the chick magnet?
In elementary school,
you used to cry when people spread rumors about you and a girl.
This time, you're taking chances, diving in head first, and getting all lovey-dovey with girls!
Yeah, yeah.
However, in the end you're still naive.
At this rate,
you won't be able to experience a high school love comedy even though you're finally in Tokyo.
That isn't really why I did it...
So...
...let's go pick up some chicks!
Now it's all me, isn't it?!
Is it my turn now?!
Now is the time for me to be popular with the ladies, isn't it?!
No one's going to take a high school student seriously, are they?
People come to the city seeking change.
However, things don't change that easily.
Although you're in a different place, you still remain...
the same old you.
No way.
I have a boyfriend.
That doesn't matter!
If a guy flirts with a girl and she ends up going out for some tea with him,
it's not considered, "cheating"!
Oh yeah, did you know...?
Apparently, Yumi's new boyfriend is a Dollars member.
Seriously?!
Isn't she scared?
That sounds really deep!
We should talk more about this over tea!
Are the Dollars some sort of motorcycle gang?
In this city, there are people who join up in committing violent acts every now and then.
Each group is represented by the color they wear,
they're known as, "Color Gangs."
However, the group that's been increasing their notoriety lately isn't affiliated with any color.
If you have to describe them as anything, you would have to say that they're transparent.
That's the color of the Dollars.
It's said that they're a special gang that gathers its members through their website.
I heard that the Awakusu group has their backs.
Isn't the headless rider a Dollars member?
The three strongest forces in Ikebukuro!
The Headless Rider
Dollars
Heiwajima Shizuo
What about Simon?
Oh, there's a rumor going around that the Dollars are behind the slashing incidents lately.
Really?
I keep telling you! We should talk more about this over tea!
Dollars?
Yeah, I know about them.
Really?
Really.
By the way...
Have you ever heard
of the Dollars?
Really.
By the way...
Have you ever heard
of the Dollars?
What kind of people are they?
The Dollars are amazing!
I heard they had a chat with the Chinese Mafia about recruitment.
Before that, there was also an incident where a grunt from the Dollars stabbed a Yakuza.
Aw, man...
Your gloomy face made them run away!
Kida-kun!
What's up?
Let's see... the one with the name like a manga character...
Mikado-kun, right?
Do you want to come with us to Toranoanoa?
Today Susie Yasuda-sensei is having a book signing!
You're not supposed to tell other people about that!
Why not?
What's wrong with talking about Susie-sensei?!
Dollars?
Yes, I heard the name before, at least.
I heard a rumor about them from a friend today.
Setton-san, have you ever
Hmm.
I've never seen them before. It makes me wonder if they really exist.
Do you think it was made up on the internet?
Well, I don't really know, but...
if the team really does exist, it's probably better to just stay out of their way.
Dollars?
They fight against the Flame Haze sealed beneath the Sunshine 60 day and night, right?
No, Yumacchi.
They're angels who fly in the sky while showing their underwear to everyone below them singing,  "pii piru piru piru"!
Why do you want to know about the Dollars?
Uh, I want to know because...
Did hearing about them earlier scare you?
I've heard various rumors about them, also.
I heard they're a pretty dangerous set.
Is that so...?
You shouldn't approach them them out of curiosity.
You also shouldn't try to stick your nose in their business.
You're so cool, Kadota-san!
You're like the main character's big brother!
You're the type of guy that lures in girls that dig the old man feel, right?
No, no, no, no...
Shut up!
In this city, there are places you shouldn't approach.
That is so tsundere!
You won't get a stomachache!
Just try it for yourself and see!
Just one try! You won't die!
I'm getting pretty hungry.
Yeah.
You wanna go get something to eat before we-
The headless rider!
No way!
Seeing the occult in broad daylight?
You're sure working hard.
Every so often, there are people who get swallowed by the city and just vanish without a trace.
There are also those who search desperately for said people.
I'll catch my love. I'll definitely find her.
My love will allow me to see her.
Harima-san?
Harima-san!
I was mistaken! P-Please excuse me!
And this city is overflowing with danger.
Hold on.
Right here...
Hey, hey, let's go out for some tea!
Here also...
He was supposed to be trying to change...
Seriously?
He thought something would change...
That something would happen, and that things would be different in this new city.
However, what awaited him...
were the dangers that dwelled in the unsightly shadows of this city.
His legs began to tremble.
They trembled at the thought of whether or not he'll really be able to continue living in this city.
I understand how you feel.
On the train people treat you like a molester.
If you walk in the streets, you get weird invitations.
And when you go home, you
you get in trouble with your neighbor!
Then there are the Dollars and the headless rider to worry about...
All of this is part of Tokyo, the concrete jungle!
However!
You just gotta roll with it!
If you swore to yourself that you'd become an Ikebukuroan,
you have to go through the trials, Mikado!
Ryuugamine Mikado!
Well, with me around you don't really have to sweat it.
Kida-kun...
And whenever you're trying to pick up some chicks, you have to smile.
Smile.
But I think it's impossible for us to pick up an adult...
What are you talking about?
All we're doing is trying to talk to them, so there's nothing wrong with that.
I heard even though Harima Mika went missing, you're still acting all high and mighty.
You're a class rep now, right?
She's being bullied!
Those bullies are so cliché.
Even with all of that makeup on, they're still not very scary.
Yoko's boyfriend is a Dollars member.
Hiroshi!
Yo, you!
Me and my Dollars blood are always heated when we get the call to pop shit off! You know what I mean?!
There are people like this everywhere in the world.
It's actually refreshing to see someone as cliché as this.
Just as I thought, I should help her, right?
But what can I do?
Hey you guys, cut it out!
That's no good, I'll just get beat up.
Then...
Ah, Sonohara-san, fancy meeting you here!
Later!
Wow... he's so cool...
That's it!
That's the only way to do it!
Bullies?
You're gonna go stop them?
And in this city, events that blow past our wildest imaginations tend to occur very often.
Uh, U-Um...
Huh? What?
W-What?
Huh? W-
Hold on a...
What?
U-Uh...
Bullying is lame.
It really isn't good.
This isn't any of your business, is it old man?
Whether you guys get beat up here on the spot, or end up dying in some gutter doesn't have anything to do with me.
Even if I hit you, and even if you call me an old man even though I'm only twenty-three...
we still wouldn't have anything to do with one another.
Huh?
Humans don't really make good adversaries, right?
Well, hurting girls isn't exactly a hobby of mine...
Therefore, I'll make it my hobby...
to stomp on their cell phones.
What the hell is with this guy?
I've had enough of that.
That puts and end to my hobby of stomping on cell phones.
H-Hiroshi!
Yo!
Hey, man!
Violence?
Wow, you're so  scary!
B-Bastard!
Whoa!
I give up!
Wait!
Wait up!
You better remember this!
Roger that. Come back with the fussy ones next time.
You're really something!
You tried to save a girl from being bullied.
It's been a while hasn't it...? Kida Masaomi.
Oh... hi.
That uniform is Raira Academy's, right?
Congrats on your admittance.
Yeah, thanks.
It's rare to see you in Ikebukuro, Izaya-san.
This person is the Orihara Izaya I shouldn't make an enemy out of?
Oh, he's just a friend of mine.
I'm Orihara Izaya.
Nice to meet you.
Ry-Ryuugamine Mikado.
That name reminds me of an air conditioner.
Uh, yeah...
So... why are you here in Ikebukuro?
I came to see someone.
But I already got in touch with them.
No way... was that a trash can from a convenience store?
It just came flying!
Why?!
Oh, shit...
Izaya-kun.
A bartender?
Didn't you get it when I told you not to let me catch you in Ikebukuro again?
Huh? Izaya-kun?
Shizu-chan...
I thought you worked by the west gate?
I got fired from there a while ago.
And didn't I tell you to stop calling me that?
I've got a name, and it's Heiwajima Shizuo!
Heiwajima Shizuo?
Another guy I shouldn't make an enemy out of?!
Don't be that way, Shizu-chan.
Are you still upset that I pinned that crime on you?
I ain't mad.
I just wanna kick your ass.
You're never able to be rational once you get violent like this Shizu-chan. That's not very good, you know.
Give me a break...
Just let it go.
There he is! That's him!
You bastard! You tried to make a fool out of me!
Let me show you what you get for underestimating the Dollars...
A bartender uniform?
No way!
Well, he wasn't there earlier.
H-Heiwajima Shizuo?!
Who the fuck are you bastards?!
When humans are afraid, they tend to lose the ability to think rationally.
You aimed for my head just now, right?
You know that you could kill someone by aiming for their head, right?
If you understand that, then that means you were trying to kill me, right?
Then, you shouldn't have any complaints about what I'm about to do to you, right?!
Those with overwhelming power tend to instill fear into others.
It's almost as if he's like violence dressed up as a person, or someone who can only live while resorting to violence.
No, this man...is just violence incarnate.
Idiots! Don't run away!
Well, thanks!
You're not getting away...
Why?
Why...
did he come from the sky?
That's not the real issue here, but, if you really need to know...
It's because I was making a delivery to one of our regulars that lives on the top floor of that building.
Simon, you bastard...
Shizuo, fighting isn't good.
Shut up! Don't get in my way!
Hey, Mikado! Now is when we...
No way!
Mikado!
Wait! Hold on!
I... can't breathe!
S-Sorry.
This city also gives you gifts every now and then.
Although it may appear small, it is a huge miracle.
The adventure he desired,
and possibly the beginning of a new tale.
And...
U-Um...
Thank you very much.
Please, excuse me.
...there are times when nothing begins.
I found you...
my love.
The Dollars did it again.
I know!
They had a huge fight with a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo this afternoon, right?
I heard the Dollars started a fight.
A brawl broke out between Shizuo and the Dollars.
That's what everyone's saying.
They're the cancer of society!
No, that's not true.
It seems like they got into it with Heiwajima Shizuo, too.
I happened to be there to see it. They were just posing as Dollars members.
They're the cancer of society!
That's not all...
Recently, the people who were calling themselves Dollars members attacked a random person and stole their money.
Huh?
The Dollars are so scary and so cruel.
You should be careful, too.
Thanks.
They're really scary, aren't they?
Those Dollars.
Izaya was in Ikebukuro earlier.
I was going to kill him once and for all, but Simon got in the way.
Come to think of it... I wonder why he was even here in the first place.
This city is filled with foreigners.
They all come here to find something they're looking for.
They also come to this city to change something.
Welcome! Welcome!
Myself included...
Eat sushi!
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our warm bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
I hear the voice of your wonderful heart perfectly.
We're no longer kids, but love is still right here.
It's okay to try to cry. It's okay to try to depend on me.
It was then that I decided to take away your pain.
I'm here
Wherever you may be.
Call me
We'll become one.
Trust me
These feelings for you won't change.
My dear
Just put down
Trust me
those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
I'm here
I'm right here.
Call me
I'm right by your side.
Trust me
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My dear
This invisible thread,
Trust me
exists because of our bond,
I feel so much warmth coming from it.
This is a work of fiction.
Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Durarara!!
Next Time
Loneliness
Listen to my story.
I want you to listen to this unique story about the two of us all the way through.
Next time: Loneliness.
I'm sure you'll be trembling with fear and excitement.