SELF-STUDY
Are you seriously going to help her?
And what if I am? This isn't fair.
She didn't even do anything to them.
Yeah, that's how bullying works.
The only reason they need is not liking you.
She was looking at us.
She wanted us to help her.
Well duh, we were the only ones there.
If you're really sticking your nose into this, count me out.
All you're going to get is them switching targets to you.
Then what's going to happen to her?
Not my problem.
Either she gets out of it somehow, or she just stops coming to school.
Or a teacher notices and steps in.
So we should just abandon her?
Seriously, why are you like this?
Just listening to you is getting annoying. I've had enough.
You’re not the only one!
I get where you're coming from.
But I can't accept this.
We're basically saying that the ones in the wrong are right.
I won't stand for it!
A dream, huh...
Do I have to go to the agency today?...
Crap, I overslept.
ROCK'N'ROLL WON'T STOP RINGING
I'll be frank. We haven't managed to sell even half the expected amount.
No surprise there.
With that amount of views on the song,
there's no way we'd suddenly be that popular.
Miura-san, what's your take on this?
The biggest problem,
is that you’ve never had this much exposure before.
If we look at search statistics, you're doing quite well.
Normally, this would significantly contribute to your view count.
And you're saying it didn't.
It's the agency's fault.
It means we haven't promoted the song well.
My apologies.
N-no, that's not what I was going to say-
In the era of self-promotion,
talent agencies need to evolve and adapt.
If there's no benefit for the artist, there's no reason for them to belong to one.
Agreed.
Give me a bit more time. I’ll come up with countermeasures.
I’ve never seen her like that.
She was a bit off, yeah.
Wait, where’s Momoka-san?
She just went “Sorry, see ya” and left.
She went back home?
Weren't we going to rehearse?
It's fine, let's just skip today.
I agree.
Momoka-san noticed, didn't she?
Well, obviously.
- Noticed what?
- You're really dense, aren't you?
What do you mean?
Remember what she said?
Our name gained traction, but our song didn't.  Which means...
The problem is the song.
Miura knew that Momoka-san wanted to say exactly that.
So she didn't let her.
But why?
So Momoka-san doesn't get hurt.
But that's not it! We just need to be patient!
It's an amazing song! Everyone was praising it.
Even Miura-san and Nakata-san!
If that was enough to sell your music, it wouldn't be a struggle in the first place.
But!
You know, it's like Van Gogh only selling one painting in his life.
But still...
People follow trends.
If everyone says something's great, you'll watch it.
But if it's something no one cares about, you probably won't.
That’s not…
Not true?
Out of two Let's Plays of the same game,
would you click on the one with 5,000 views or the one with 1 million?
Cut it out, it's embarrassing.
Okay, I get it...
THE NEXT DAY
"Picking a fight they can't win."
“I hate how pretentious they feel."
“They should just quit like the losers they are.”
Oh shut the hell up!
Screw off, you didn't even listen to the song!
And besides, we're not losing to you! Piss off!
Alright, calm down, calm down...
The two-day battle's coming up,
And Diamond Dust sold all their tickets...
No surprise there I guess...
A follow request?
From Hina?
It has the verified mark...
Yo.
Made you look.
It’s been a while.
Don't you need a disguise or something?
I'm not that famous.
You still like those, huh.
Yep. We used to eat those after school, didn't we?
I'll pay.
It's fine, it's my treat.
- So, what do you want?
- Nothing.
I just thought you might be misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding what?
I didn’t become their new singer on purpose or anything.
I told you about the auditions, didn't I?
Oh wait, that was after we stopped talking.
And you stopped coming to school by then.
So what, you came here just to gloat?
To tell me that this is all because I didn't just do what you said?
That everything would be fine if I just listened to you?
Exactly...
...is what I want to say, but that's only half-right.
- Your tickets aren't selling, are they?
- It's none of your business.
Actually, it is my business.
We’re playing together, after all.
It's not "together"!
Your agent, Miura-san, paid us a visit.
To ask us for help.
She did?
She wanted us to play on both days, since if we do,
we can have a two-day duel with both days sold out.
Your concert's only filling the venue to 30% of its capacity.
We can fit it in our schedule, so all that's left is for us to approve it.
But I thought I might as well  ask what you think about it.
So?
I don’t care.
So you're saying you don't need my help then?
Or will you gratefully accept?
Hear that?
It’s called success. A very important thing.
A crucial thing.
How about you just accept reality already?
"I was wrong. And Hina was right all along."
Admit that you should've listened to me.
"I'll live by baring it all", was it?
Admit you were wrong, and I'll gladly come to your rescue.
I'm out of here!
Here you go!
Thanks for the meal!
Yes, what is it?!
Sorry for calling you so suddenly.
Oh, it's no problem.
Did something happen?
Well, like I've already told the rest...
DiaDust asked us if we want to play on both days.
So that we can face off in front of the same audience.
Did Miura-san tell you that?
- Yes, what about it?
- Nothing.
What do you think, Nina?
How about you guys?
Well, you know…
It wasn't even a fair fight before, so why not?
But if we go with that,
it would mean that most of our audience will be there for DiaDust.
Isn't that basically the same as admitting our defeat?
So you're against this idea, then?
Yes. I don't want that.
Here we go again.
I get where you're coming from, but...
I don't want that. Never in a million years!
What did we get this far for?
To prove that Momoka-san wasn't wrong,
that her songs can reach people!
That's always been our driving force!
But reality's not that kind.
We sold less than 30% of our tickets.
It's worse than when we were an indie band.
So what?!
Are you going to take responsibility then?
Do you have any idea how much money is at stake here?
- Money?
- And I'm not talking just about the venue costs.
Merchandise, advertising. None of that is free you know.
We need to do what we can to mitigate the losses.
This is all my fault.
Sorry.
So we have to bow to DiaDust like this?
Nobody's bowing down to anyone.
Exactly, we're just accepting their proposal.
That is bowing down!
Do you really think they just offered this out of the blue?!
What do you mean?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Miura-san bowed down to them and asked for it.
She begged them to play with us. To help us.
Really?
How do you know that?
Hina told me.
She wanted me to admit that I was wrong.
Then she'll help us all we want.
I don't want to say that.
Because I know
that I wasn't wrong!
Nina…
So don't just go bowing down to them!
Don't reject who I was back then!
Money, responsibility, popularity…
I get it already!
I'm just frustrated… frustrated, frustrated, frustrated!
Just shut up!
- Nina?
- Nina-san?
You okay?
I'm so pathetic...
Did they do this to you?
I thought I told you already.
I won't be on your side in this.
Did you really hate me sticking up for her that much?
You know, talking to you always gives me this unpleasant feeling.
It's like you always radiate spikes of so-called justice, hurting everyone around you.
It always makes me feel like I'm the bad guy.
- And that was the end of your friendship.
- That's right.
Well, this is definitely a Nina-like story.
What happened to the bullied girl after that?
It's strange really,
but she started bullying me with the others in no time.
Then one day she talked to me in secret, and asked me to apologize to the other girls.
"They'll forgive you", she said.
and then I wouldn't have to be their target anymore.
The heck?
She was trembling.
She was terrified of them.
But you helped her. She owes you, doesn't she?
So that's how you stopped coming to school.
Yes.
"I wasn't wrong", huh?
But you were wrong, no matter you put it!
Tomo-chan…
But she was! No matter how you think about it, that Hina girl ended up being right!
But still...
Still...
I think that's part of why I was drawn to you.
I like your voice.
And Rupa, Momoka, and Subaru probably do too.
Tomo-chan!
- Wait, no, stop!
- Come here!
I don't like this kinda stuff!
I guess we have our answer.
But still, Miura-san and the others worked hard for us.
We’ll have to take responsibility.
Seriously...
Though I can't say I didn't see it coming from the start.
It's her we're talking about.
Yep, very Nina-like.
Hey!
- You're refusing the offer?
- Yes, our apologies.
They're offering you a fair fight, you know.
We're aware.
But still, at this point it would just look like they came to our rescue.
Maybe so, but regarding the audience…
Withdrawal request
We decided this together.
We know that it looks like
a selfish whim of ours,
and how it hurts the agency.
Please tell us the exact costs.
I can't say when, but we promise to cover them eventually.
Please.
Please, raise your heads.
Could you tell me the reason?
I got a message.
From DiaDust's Hina.
I truly appreciate you going so far for us.
We only went for it because of my selfishness in the first place, and you still helped us.
And I realize it's rude of me to refuse this offer.
I'm sorry for my selfishness.
Honestly, I did suspect that it would go against your principles.
Miura-san…
I guess I'm also to blame.
But let's be clear.
The money and the contract are our responsibility, not yours.
It's your personality that made me want to work with you.
Withdrawal request
At least let me be useful to you at the very end.
You're quitting?
Yes.
- For another agency?
- No, we're thinking of going solo.
Was there a problem?
No.
It's our own decision.
Nothing more.
- Is he mad?
- We didn't need to give him details...
(Nakata) Spoken like true greenhorns.
Come see me in 10 years
if you survive until then.
I'll make you something for free.
We will! Thank you so much, Nakata-san!
Time for some gyudon!
You just want to get wasted.
Of course not!
You're not fooling anyone.
Speaking of which, this is where we met you two, isn't it?
I guess.
Beni-Shoga, huh.
How about we make a promise? With you two as Beni-Shoga.
The name's special to you.
And we'll add a special promise on top of it.
What exactly are we promising?
To always stay together and never give up.
I guess we'll have to eat together then.
Works for me.
Just one drink, you hear me?
Momoka-san!
You know, I love this city.
This city, where I met friends who would laugh and cry with me.
I love it.
Kawasaki, right?
Yes!
We got wrecked, huh?
It's like losing every match in the qualifying rounds.
No miracles for us, huh?
Well duh. We're not a soap opera.
Huh, didn't know you like those.
I only watch
Detective Grandma's Case Files!
You wanna fight?
But you know, it's not like we haven't seen it coming.
We understood that reality's harsh, that it won't be easy for us.
Look who's talking.
You're the one who didn't understand that.
Can't argue there...
Well, guess you wouldn't be able to shout "I wasn't wrong" all the time otherwise.
Momoka-san...
By the way, we got a lot more comments after yesterday's DiaDust concert.
Weren't you the one who told me not to look at those?
Now, now.
Let's see.
"I like them."
"Why are people hating on them?"
"Oh shut it, music isn’t about numbers."
"It's not over yet, don't just assume they lost."
See, there are people who'd say these kinds of things for us.
I guess we really reached them.
Seems so.
Anyway, I didn't know you got so good at playing the guitar.
Didn't see that coming.
Are you sure I should play on stage?
Well, you did spend a lot of time practicing in the park.
Sure, why not?
Thanks, everyone.
It's time.
Got it!
To Nina ♥
Look up!!
- Hina
Up?
Look left ♥♥
- Hina
Left?
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Made you look ♥
- That little...
- She’s funny, I'll give her that.
Maybe that Hina doesn't actually want you to give up, you know.
How exactly?
She went out of her way just to get you to apologize.
Probably because she knew you'd be stubborn and refuse.
You're like the last boss of a video game.
The ultra-annoying Demon Lord of Self-Righteousness.
If she beats you it's game over, but she wants to play with you some more.
Gee thanks, I'm so happy.
It’s a compliment.
You know I’m right.
Alright everyone, it's time.
Umm...you already know this,
but this was supposed to be a duel against Diamond Dust.
And I guess the result is obvious...
I mean, thank you all for coming today!
Ouch.
You know, we were really focused on it.
Beating Diamond Dust, I mean.
We didn't want to lose.
We were serious about it at the festival too.
I know it's sudden, but I'll be rambling about myself for a bit.
Rupa-san, can I?
When I was in high school, I tried to help a girl who was being bullied.
On my way to where she was, I felt happy with my decision.
I felt like someone I could really like and be proud of.
But then I became the new target,
and I ended up dropping out of school.
But still, I never thought that I made a mistake.
I never thought that maybe it'd be better if I didn't help her.
And now, I can say that I regret absolutely nothing.
Momoka-san's song gave me the strength I needed,
and I always told Hina that-
Ah, I see.
Hina loved their music too.
It wasn’t just my song. It reached her too.
Once again, thank you all for coming.
You are the rebels who go against the grain.
And I love you all for that!
I will scream. Scream that we won’t give up.
That we weren't wrong!
Please become the witnesses of our beginning!
We're all the same
Dare datte onnaji
Living on top of life
Inochi no ue ni ikiteru
If you can't find a place of your own
Ibasho ga nai nara
Fly high
Tobidatte yuke
Fate tangled up, reverberating
Unmei ga karamatte, todoroite
I had taken all the other paths
Hokano michi yaritsukushite
I dedicate the rest of my life to singing with you
Watashi ni nokotta jinsei kimi to utatte iku koto
No light or wind, like an isolated prison
Akari mo kaze mo nai, maru de koritsu na rougoku
Pain and suffering
Scars all over, I hated it all
Kurushikute tsurakute kizudarake de zenbu ga iya dattan da
Even with my wings full of holes
Hirogeta tsubasa wa ana darake demo
Even in the depths of hell, if I could sing with you
Jigoku no soko datte kimi to utaeru nara
I flew away, wanting to disappear
Kietakute, habataite ima
But now I want to stay
Kietakunakunatta
I picked a budding bloom, waiting for it to blossom
Tsumitotte nokoshita koko de itsuka hana sakaseru
The me who wanted to disappear is gone
Kietakatta watashi wa mou inai
I'm glad I didn't disappear
Kienakute yokatta na
Because I met you
And our flower of fate bloomed
Datte kimi to deai, mebuite shimatta, unmei no hana
Three, two, one…
Thank you!