Jeez, stop licking me, Taromaru!
You're gonna wake everyone up!
Wait, huh?
Oh no! I'm late!
I gotta hurry!
I'm off, Taromaru!
Yuki
Reference Room
Bedroom
Fire Hose
I've really been loving school lately!
Morning!
And the thing I love most of all is...
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
The Beginning
I'm here!
Huh?!
School Living Club
Where're you going, Taromaru?
C'mere, c'mere!
Morning, everyone!
Kurumi
Hey, morning.
Good morning, Yuki-senpai.
Mii-kun
Ri-san
Morning, Yuki-chan.
You're quite the sleepyhead today.
I dunno, I wouldn't say...
That wasn't a compliment, you know.
Jeez, Kurumi-chan, it's early,
and you're already mean!
Wait, why do you have the shovel right now?
Oh, you don't know?
In the trenches of WWI,
Mii-kun, what're you reading?
it was the weapon with the most kills!
Don't call me Mii-kun.
Yes, to tell you the truth...
Hey, are you listening?!
Oh yeah, so the other day...
She's not listening!
I totally forgot about club and almost went home!
That was close!
Spaghetti
Meat Sauce
But Megu-nee stopped me.
That's good, I'll have to thank her.
Yeah.
You space out way too much, Senpai.
What's wrong, Senpai?
This smell...
It's spaghetti!
Oh, jeez.
I made spaghetti with meat sauce today.
Yay! I love you, Ri-san!
Hey now, could you get the rest of the plates for me?
Okay!
You can't sit on the desks. C'mere.
I-it's alright, Miki...
Taromaru...
No funny business, okay?
Oh, what's wrong?
I think Taromaru's hungry.
Okay! Let's eat breakfast together, then!
Let me help, too.
Taromaru is a doggie, after all.
Growl
I'll help, too.
Taromaru
Wait!
Aww...
Ri-san
Kurumi-chan
Is everyone sitting down?
Yuki
Alright, then.
Mii-kun
Let's eat!
Nom
Nom Nom
You should slow down and taste the food.
Just look at Miki.
It's so good...
Please stop staring, Senpai!
Sorry.
You should chew your food more, too, Yuki-chan.
R-roger!
It's so good...
You don't have to imitate that part.
Wha...?
I hate you, Senpai.
Wha?!
Please forgive me, Mii-kun!
I'll practice more!
Please, stop!
Oh, isn't it about time for you to go, Yuki-chan?
Oh, that's right! I'm on duty today!
Gotta hurry!
There's still food on your plate.
She's wolfing it down without chewing it much at all...
Right after I just told her...
School Living Club
Okay, I'm off!
Oh, thanks for the food!
Have a good day!
See you later.
I've really been loving school lately!
I know people'll say I'm weird, but school is so cool!
The science room has all kinds of weird devices!
The music room has lots of pretty instruments
and spooky portraits!
The broadcasting room makes
the whole school your stage!
School has everything! It's like one big country!
No other building can compare!
Takeya-san?
We all love school so much!
I wanna live here every day!
Yuki Takeya-san!
Megu-nee!
Don't call me Megu-nee.
It's Sakura-sensei, okay?
Takeya-san, no running in the halls.
I've told you this a thousand times already.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't notice you there.
It's like you're invisible!
Ah, I'm on duty, so I gotta go!
See you later!
I'm invisible...
Made it!
Slump
Hey, School Living Club.
Didja just come from club?
Yeah.
That's why you're always running
into class at the last second.
I love the thrill of making it just in time!
Hey, who's on duty today?
They didn't erase the blackboard,
and our teacher's on her way.
Ah, the teacher's here.
Okay, I'm gonna work hard from this second on!
She sprung back fast!
Well, I guess that's just like you, huh.
Let's start class.
Right!
Stand!
Bow!
Sit down!
Zzz
Whaaaaaa...?
She was fast to fall asleep, too.
Takeya-san? Yuki Takeya-san?
Oh, g'morning.
We're in class right now!
R-right, good morning.
Fall asleep again and
you'll have to take extra lessons.
Roger!
Yuki-senpai!
Oh, there you are, Yuki-senpai!
Hey, Yuki-senpai! Yuki-senpai!
Mii-kun, we're in class, we're in class!
The pot calling the kettle black, here...
Sorry.
What a cute underclassman.
Excuse me, Sensei?
I'm not feeling good.
Can I go to the nurse's office?
Go ahead.
Thanks!
H-hey! I thought you weren't feeling good!
Senpai?
Jeez, you really scared me, Mii-kun!
Sorry. And please don't call me Mii-kun.
Wait, are you nervous?
I know I'm your senpai, but you don't
have to be formal with me.
I'm not nervous at all.
Honestly, there's nothing about you
that'd make me nervous, Yuki-senpai.
Anyways, we've got a problem.
Taromaru's gone missing.
Oh, no! We have to find him!
Right.
Taromaru!
He's not here.
Hey, Mii-kun, they're in class right now!
I've been calling for him but he hasn't come out.
Huh...
Well, Taromaru doesn't really like you that much.
I-it's not that he hates you or anything!
Taromaru's a smart dog!
Maybe he's just scared of you, Mii-kun!
Scared of me?
I can do
anything!
Scared, like, of that "I can do anything"
aura that surrounds you, maybe?
I see...
Sluggish...
I don't have that sluggish aura
that surrounds you, Yuki-senpai.
That's right!
I've got this sluggish aura...
Hey! That's not right!
I'm kidding. Let's go.
I'm glad.
Glad about what?
You're not nervous anymore.
Really, I wasn't ever nervous.
Really?
I was just worried about Taromaru.
Oh.
It's okay, leave it to me!
Over there!
There he is!
Hey, Taromaru!
Don't worry Mii-kun like that!
Hey, Senpai!
Use your sluggish aura, remember!
Wait!
Chasing him isn't going to help!
N-no, it's okay, that way's a dead end!
Wh-when did he learn how to do that?
Home Economics
It's over there!
Why're you closing the door?!
This is really bad!
Let's go!
W-wait!
They're in class right now, Mii-kun!
We're from the School Living Club.
We're here to catch our dog.
Mii-kun, he's in the hall!
Taromaru!
How did he run up the stairs that fast?
That's our Taromaru!
Now's not the best time to praise him for that!
Sorry.
Hurry!
Roger!
There he is!
Taromaru!
Wave
Good boy, come here!
C'mon!
What're you doing?
Kurumi-chan!
Zoom
You were chasing after Taromaru, huh?
Uh-huh! What're you doing up here, Kurumi-chan?
And with the shovel again!
What do you mean? I was doing club stuff.
Helping out the Gardening Club.
Umm... sorry.
It's alright, it's not your fault, Senpai.
It's my aura.
Aura?
There he is!
Alright, leave it to me!
Hey, hey, hey!
What're you doing with the shovel?
It's okay, I won't hit him with the sharp part.
Oh, okay!
That's not okay at all!
Taromaru!
This way!
Whoosh
Hold it right there!
Ru...
Taromaru?
You know you're not allowed in the garden.
Rumble
Alright! Nice one, Ri-san!
School Living Club Rules!
Number one!
Right!
School Living Club members live at school
and must strive to work closely with...
work closely with...
...With other school departments
outside of the classroom, and through that...
...foster their independence and
be role models for all to follow.
That's right, good job.
Sorry!
It's alright.
But you did cause trouble for
the people in the Gardening Club.
Yeah. Sorry, everyone!
Sorry.
I-I'm sorry.
You're upperclassmen, after all.
You've got to set an example.
Oh, right!
Taromaru!
Over there!
Sorry, Gardening Club!
Sorry!
Alright, I'll show you the power of a senpai!
Huh?!
I'll get you this time!
Hey, you're not sluggish at all again!
Science Lab
He went in there?!
Senpai!
Music Room
On Air
Jeez, stop licking, Taromaru!
Oh, no!
Senpai!
School Living Club
Hardtack
I love hardtack!
Is it really that good?
I hate the aftertaste.
It just has that taste of survival, you know?
Yeah, I get it.
Taromaru!
What, you want hardtack, too?
Jeez.
It's your fault I'm all tired!
I'm pretty tired over here, too!
If he can open doors now, we should probably
have a leash on him, even in here.
He's too smart for his own good.
Taromaru is really smart!
Right?
I-it's okay, Miki...
Letting him run off during class time like that...
There'll be a staff meeting about this.
I'll have to write another apology letter...
Meh, I'm just glad there were no repercussions.
But there were!
Sorry!
Please be more careful from now on, okay?
Taromaru must've really wanted to go for a walk.
Who was on walk duty yesterday?
You totally forgot you were on duty, Senpai.
Yuki-san?
I'm sorry.
You should apologize to Taromaru, not me.
That's right. Sorry, Taromaru!
I'll let you off for skipping class.
So you better do your homework, alright?
Okay!
What's up?
I can't find my bag.
I left it in the classroom!
She's always having so much fun.
She's such a scatterbrain.
I think it's fine.
I guess.
Well...
Stare
Huh? What is it?
Did you forget something?
Not that, I just...
...wanted to say I love you all.
What's this all about?
I mean, I forgot we were staying here
and almost went home,
but it's not like I forgot about all of you or anything.
We understand.
That was it!
I'll be back!
What's up?
Will she be okay on her own?
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Could you go with her?
Okay.
There it is!
Hey, you alright?
Huh?
You went to the nurse's office, right?
Or were you skipping class?
No fair!
No, no, Taromaru was running away from us!
Who's Taromaru?
Yeah, who? A guy?
Well, he's not a girl.
What's he like?
Ummm...
Oh, he wears a collar just like that one!
He wears a choker, huh?
He's got good taste.
And this morning, he jumped up on me and
I totally thought he was gonna pull my skirt off!
He sneaks into the classroom during class
and jumps up on my desk...
That's not good.
But I think he's cute when he does that!
That's cute?!
Seriously, what is Taromaru?
He's a dog the School Living Club is taking care of.
Jeez, that should've been the first thing you told us.
The School Living Club does everything, huh.
Taromaru can go anywhere he wants!
He can open doors with his paw!
Are you sure Taromaru is a dog?!
If we let him go out on his own, he disappears on us!
He's such a pain!
And when we're feeding him, he looks soooo cute,
I just wanna hug him so bad!
Senpai!
Oh, Mii-kun!
What's wrong?
Umm...
Huh? Yeah, she's my underclassman.
Yeah, her name's Miki-chan, so I call her Mii-kun!
That's right, Mii-kun's really smart!
Okay, see you later!
Sorry to make you wait!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Mii-kun, is something wrong?
Guess you really are nervous, huh?
I'm not nervous.
I told you, I know I'm your upperclassman,
but you don't need to be nervous!
I told you, I'm not nervous!
What did you want?
Ri-san told me to take care of you.
Said you'd get caught up in a conversation
and forget to do your homework.
Oh, come on!
I wouldn't forget that!
Alright, then.
Oh, I forgot!
Just kidding!
Oh, the window's open.
Talking on our way home
Telling each other our secrets
Even when the 5-o'clock chime rings out
I wonder why I feel we still haven't talked enough
A tiny four-leaf clover
Sways in the gentle breeze
Hey, I'm sure that yes, I'm sure
I hope tomorrow will be sunny, too
We walked the road together
Always saying we'd meet at the usual place
Ah, the fluffy clouds above
Seem like they'll be burned, they're shining so bright
Even if, one day, these days
Are but a faded memory
I want to give you
A lot of smiles right now
Next Time!
Taromaru is so cute!
And he's smart!
Yes!
He can open doors, and slip out of
his leash really quick, too!
That's not good at all!
Memories
Next time on School-Live, episode 2:
"Memories"