Hi, everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Have you ever created
something with your friends?
Working hard toward the same goal,
cooperating with all sorts of people
and helping each other makes you feel good.
Please support our new show.
Please support! Please support!
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
It's amazing how time passes by so quickly.
It's already been two weeks
since we moved in here.
And yet, not only are we far from
creating our own Kaleido Stage,
but also we have no jobs.
I told my mother and father
not to worry, but...
I wish we could practice someplace a
little bigger than here, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I hope something like a dream happens.
Right, right. Something like a dream...
Wow... It's like a dream all right...
What's wrong, Sora?
I just thought I'd try combining tightrope
walking and the cushion throw.
Anyway, Mia, Anna, please make
sure no one sees your panties.
We're all girls here. So who cares?
Yeah...
No, no!
What are you gonna do if a peeping Tom
or a perverted spirit is watching us?
Who are you calling a perverted spirit?
"An Amazing Change From Zero to Hero."
Oh, and Yuri's Kaleido Stage is to
face the colorful opening date today.
What shall we do?
Shall we go?
He took the trouble to send
invitations. It means...
Harassment?
No... This could be a challenge...
Want to go?
Everyone,
Kaleido Stage has been reborn.
The show we're aiming at is a fantastic
show which has never existed before.
Now the revolutionary flame is
ready to blaze up in entertainment.
It looks like they spent a lot of money.
I wonder if he did this
to rub it in our faces.
I co-starred with Miss Layla on that stage.
Everyone did their best,
and we received enthusiastic
applause from the audience.
But... this is no longer our Kaleido Stage.
It was fun!
It was like I was in an amusement park.
It was great!
What's wrong, Sora?
What?
Are you looking for somebody?
Yes.
I just thought Miss Layla might be here also.
Yeah, she could be here.
I assume she also got an invitation.
But she could be busy.
It seems she's doing another
movie. It was in the magazine.
I guess she's not doing stage shows anymore.
I just can't...
I just can't see that happening.
Oh, it's Yuri.
Mr. Yuri, can I have your autograph, please?
All right.
Me too.
Okay. Wait one second.
Why do we have to hide?
You want to take a chance and rent
the Empire Stage for $350 a day?
If we rent it for three days, we'll be broke.
Unless we can find a place much cheaper
and rent the place for at least ten days,
our reputation will not have time to spread.
Hmm... I see...
Oh!
Did you find a good job?
"Wanted: performers to participate in the
grand opening of a giant seafood restaurant."
They pay pretty well too.
Sounds good.
Yes.
But it says that you have to audition.
We're more than happy to audition!
Then you want to try their audition?
Yeah!
So this is it. Everyone, are you ready?
Of course!
Let's get the job by all means!
Get!
Passed!
We did it!
Oh...
Welcome.
If all we had to do was wear
this and hand out balloons,
we didn't need to audition.
At least you're in a crab costume.
On the other hand, I'm a shrimp. A shrimp.
Anyhow, both of you, motivate
yourselves and let's do our best.
Yeah!
There, there, there!
I'm spinning more than usual.
Mia!
Yeah!
There, there, there, there, there, there!
There!
What are you doing detaining
customers at the entrance?
Please let customers go
inside the restaurant.
You guys are supposed to
be delicious ingredients.
Yes.
Please...
Eat...
Delicious us!
Please!
Instead of doing all that,
I just want you to hand out balloons.
Then why did you audition us?
Mia, smile, smile.
Right now, it's taking a
little time to be seated.
You're better off than I
am. 'Cause you're a crab.
I, on the other hand, am a shrimp.
You too, Anna!
Even if you tell me to smile...
Why don't you try some delicious seafood?
Yuri...
What?!
You must be kidding.
What are you doing?!
Oh... Well...
Oh, sorry.
You look so perfect in that costume.
I just can't help myself...
Sora...
Mr. Yuri Killian, are you all right, sir?
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm very sorry. I reserved
you a special seat.
So, please come this way.
You're fired.
Of all people, we just had
to be seen dressed like that
by the person we least wanted to be seen by.
A crab costume would be one
thing, but why a shrimp costume?
Yes.
Who?
I'm back!
Miss Sarah!
When I asked Mr. Policeman,
he told me you were here.
So I came right over.
There we go.
This is a nice room.
Did you finish your training?
Yes.
There is nothing like the "Unryu" style
when a sumo wrestler parades in the ring.
Didn't you go to train for singing?
Are you kidding? I trained for sumo.
Anyhow, seeing your faces calms me down.
Miss Sarah,
don't you need to go back to Boss?
What? To Kalos? Why?
Why? 'Cause... You know...
Yeah, you know...
I haven't talked to Kalos in a while.
What?!
I think he's taking some time by
himself to think about his future.
You think? Aren't you worried about him?
Worried?
Being unfaithful or something...
I don't need to worry about that.
Thanks to what happened the other day,
I found out Kalos is still head
over heels in love with me.
By the way, I found you a job.
What?!
Look at this.
"Wanted: performers to perform on
the open stage at Marine Park"?
I just happened to find
this while I was in town.
So, I went to Marine Park,
thinking I had nothing to lose.
Then I was able to sign a
temporary agreement with them.
That was fast!
But, it's only for one day,
the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
The group that is performing right
now suddenly can't perform that day.
So they're going to remove
the current set at night.
Because of this, you don't have
time for rehearsal either.
What do you think?
Of course we'll do it. Right?
Yeah. We have no reasons to reject it. Right?
If we can get a good reputation,
they may ask us back next time too.
Thank you!
I'm glad you like it.
Anyhow, you should take a
shower and get some rest.
That's a good idea.
Take your time.
Hey! I haven't done anything...
yet...
What are we gonna do?
If it's the day after tomorrow,
we don't have enough time to
create anything with a story.
Then you want keep it simple
and just do a performance?
Hey, I wonder if we could contact
the cast members from "Freedom"?
Oh, good idea. I'll e-mail them right away.
Oh... Miss Layla too...
I think we should contact Miss
Layla too. Don't you think so?
Miss Layla... I don't
know if she's interested.
Yeah... But if Sora wants to do it...
Right. Shall we visit Miss Layla's house?
Yes.
So, we want to create a new Kaleido Stage.
And we thought it would be
nice if you could join us.
I have a camera test for
the movie later today.
Then tomorrow, I have a costume fitting.
There's no way I'd have time
for anything like that.
First of all, my father is
managing my schedule right now.
Really?
Then, you're...
I only do my best in the
situation I'm in right now.
You haven't done your
last show yet, have you?
I... I still want to appear
on stage with you, Miss Layla.
Sora.
Yes?
Did you gain weight?
It seems you still don't
understand how hard it is
to get everything back if you
skip your training even one day.
Sorry...
It seems Miss Layla started
walking a different path from us.
Miss Layla has her own battle.
Yes.
If you act now,
this three-volume instructional video
is yours for only $200!
I want to get them!
We're back.
Welcome back. How was she?
As expected, Miss Layla cannot do it.
Really?
Well, it's disappointing,
but what can we do?
We got some e-mail responses.
Really?
From Elena, Jeanne, Claire...
and also from Emilio.
Everyone's coming!
Really? Wow... All of a sudden,
I'm getting motivated.
Even though it's only for one day,
we want to make it the best show.
Oh!
What?! What?!
Rosetta...
What?!
It's been a long time.
I've read your e-mail.
I'll go there immediately. Rosetta
I never expected her to come,
but I sent her an e-mail just in case.
Here. It's here.
What?
Keep your eyes ahead of you.
This is tough.
What can they do? The rent is cheap...
Hey, will you...
Yes.
We're coming in!
Wow! Come in.
And so, the performance will
be held the day after tomorrow
on the open stage at Marine Park.
I want to hear your ideas
on how we can create a show
that we can prepare for in such a short time.
At the same time, I want to get your ideas
on how we can make the show interesting.
On the way here,
I stopped by to look at
the actual stage, but...
How was it?
The ceiling is lower than I expected.
Then we can't do showy jump maneuvers.
Also, the stage doesn't have much depth,
so basically, you can only
do horizontal movement.
So even if Elena and Jeanne come,
it'll be impossible to let everyone
be on the stage at one time.
It means that Rosetta cannot perform
her diabolo to the fullest either.
We're handicapped like this.
Can't we just get rid of the stage roof?
No, we can't.
Then we have no choice but to do every
possible variation of maneuver we can do,
and do our best like the
force of angry waves.
Yeah.
It's not the perfect situation,
but still, we're going to perform
after doing nothing for so long.
I can't sleep!
And we'll get to see Rosetta too!
I can't wait!
Oh, it came off!
Yes. Jump, right there!
Claire, Jeanne, give me a faster tempo!
Yes.
Aren't you happy that everyone got together?
Yes, but... I measured the stage today.
It was smaller than I expected.
So it may not be possible to let
everyone on stage at one time.
Still, wouldn't it be nice if
we could do a big maneuver?
Yeah... But this time,
there's nothing we can do.
You're right.
Rosetta!
Long time no see!
Sora!
Thank you for coming all the way here.
But are you all right being here?
I'm fine.
Besides, I have so much to repay you for.
Well, since I'm here you can rest easy.
The stage is quite small...
I don't know if it will be all right.
It will be all right as long
as we can do Diabolo Battle.
What?
Diabolo Battle?
You're talking about that
Diabolo Battle, right?
Sorry, but it's impossible.
What?
Oh... I didn't know.
Rosetta...
Well... I'll see what I
can do, and do my best.
Thank you.
Then let's practice a little more.
Yeah!
What?!
It must be a mistake.
But I'm sure that there was
a call to cancel the show.
It must be a mistake.
Anyway, can you cancel that cancellation?
But we didn't disassemble the stage set.
There's no way we can disassemble it now.
I wonder who?
Yes?
Who called you?
Oh, I'm sorry, but I can't...
Hey, I bet it's Yuri.
It could be.
We may have to give up this time.
I wonder if we have no choice
but to give up this time.
After everyone was nice enough
to come, and even Rosetta came...
Can't we just get rid of the stage roof?
The roof...
I know!
What?
What? Are you serious?
Of course you are.
Oh, but we won't get paid,
so I can't make anyone do it.
That's right.
What are you saying?
I can't go home without doing anything.
Not after I came here all the way here.
Rosetta...
Me too.
Everyone, thank you.
Then, from this moment,
this entire amusement park will be our stage.
All the customers are our audience.
Our costumes are what we're wearing now.
Then let's raise the curtain.
Let's start!
Yeah!
Do you think it will be all right?
Who knows?
A man thinking.
A man running.
A man falling down.
Hmm? They're not here...
What's that?
Oh, Miss Sarah!
Oh, Marion.
What's happening?
As you see, they're in
the middle of the show.
I know how you feel.
What the hell is this?
It seems the ones who were supposed
to appear on the stage are going wild.
What shall we do, Owner?
Ready? Go!
Oh... A rose?
Mr. Dio!
Is that the person you
met in Theatrical Camp?
Yes. I asked Mia to send him an e-mail.
Thank you, Mr. Dio.
I just happened to drop in.
I didn't know he was this nice-looking.
It turned out to be better not
being able to use the stage.
That's true.
Oh...
I wonder if the person who
cancelled the show today is...
It was Kalos, wasn't it?
If they performed on that small stage,
they couldn't get this kind of reaction.
It's just like him.
If Miss Layla were here with us...
Huh?
Hey, Sora.
What's that?
No clue.
Who is that person?
"Next Kaleido Star"
It was the biggest success since
we opened this amusement park.
And so, thanks to the appearance
of that masked star,
our amusement park operation
has ended in success.
Not only that, we got a contract.
Miss Layla is amazing...
That's what I thought, but...
But that person is someone else?
After we got a chance, we got into a pinch.
We got into a pinch. We got into a pinch.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Mystery Star."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing