I'm Ryugamine...Mikado.
No way! That's really you, Kida?
Gang activity has been declining recently, too.
They got into a fight with some Saitama
guys and a bunch of people got arrested.
I'm Sonohara Anri. I hope the year goes well.
Harima!
I thought you were someone else!
You pledged to become a fine Ikebukuroer,
so show us all and overcome this tribulation!
I found you, my...love.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
Please, forgive me.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
It's all my fault, Celty.
It's all because I made you take that ridiculous job.
I should've finished it without any problems;
it's because that thing showed up randomly.
You're not human. You're a monster! A monster! A monster!
You heard a voice coming from your wound?
It called me a monster!
What a rude jerk. It should've at least called you an enchantress.
What is that thing?
What if it's an alien?!
Celty...
Is that supposed to be funny?
Mo-Monster!
Let's go!
This city is apparently comprised of jokes, caprices, and coincidences.
Saika has entered the chat room.
Humans
The strong
Hope
Love
Humans who love and hope
Because hope is strong people human love. Because because because hope is is.
I
am I, so I hope.
...
Strong, people
Hope
I, love
because
This situation may also be one of God's jokes or caprices.
There are thirty-seven girls I've fallen in love with at first sight since entering high school.
And like a plot twist in a drama, I get to walk home from school
with one of my top five, who happens to be this girl with glasses...
But this country bumpkin is getting in the way.
That must have been pretty tough on you.
Um, yeah...
This isn't good.
I was totally surprised back there.
I can't believe you ran away without me.
It's wasn't like that...
No way! Mikado!
But you did help me.
If I were you, I wouldn't have passed up a chance like that.
Right now we'd be in West Gate Park voicing our love to each other...
And on that note, please go out with me!
Wai—, Kida!
Umm, I...
You don't have to answer right away.
There are currently seven girls I'm waiting to hear from,
and I'm still deciding which one I'll actually date.
You don't have to take him seriously, Sonohara.
He'll just tire you out.
He makes it sound like he's toying with you, but
it's no big deal. Even if he hits on you, ultimately—
Hey, you, Mikado!
This guy's my best friend, Ryugamine Mikado.
He's a country bumpkin who's only been in Ikebukuro for a few days.
Even though he's unsophisticated and naïve, he's
oddly stubborn and someone you just can't leave alone.
I'm somehow involved in a love triangle with this pure boy.
Is this what they call "youth?"
Ow, that hurt—
C'mon, Kida!
You're...quite friendly with each other.
Yes, we are.
We don't want to be, but we're inseparable.
Uncle, uncle, uncle!
To explain how this all came to be...
We'll have to retrace our steps back to the opening ceremony.
I'm Yagiri Seiji.
I hope the year goes well.
Well then, Yagiri, you can sit down now.
I won't need to.
Huh?
I don't think I'll be coming to school for a while—no, I might not ever come again.
It's something very important to me.
I have no time to waste with the likes of you.
Please, excuse me.
Yagiri, wait. I said, "Wait!"
The world is full of different types of people...
Yagiri, wait!
Or so Mikado tells me.
Please, wait!
Could this be what it's like to fall in love?
Yagiri, isn't there something—
My chest throbs just by having her smile at me!
I don't know!
Bu-But...being absent on your first day of school...
Well, I guess she wasn't smiling, but still...
I said I don't know!
Wait!
Umm...
Is something wrong?
Anyway, that's the day I immediately updated the
number one ranked girl on my list of possible girlfriends.
Hey, Sonohara.
You on your way home?
Yes.
Hey, Sonohara, something's bugging you, right?
Maybe you're being bullied or you're involved in some trouble?
No...
If something ever happens, tell me right away.
I'm okay...
Is that so?
Oh yeah, Harima still hasn't come to school yet, has she?
Even though you two are in the same class...
I worked hard to get you two in the same class, you know.
Mr. Saitou from your middle school also insisted that you two be together.
So you don't have to hesitate.
That's right, how about I take you home today?
You do know that The Slasher appeared in Ikebukuro again, don't you?
Mr. Nasujima, are you sexually harassing her?!
Jeez, making our glasses-wearing class rep scream?
Isn't that full-on sexual harassment?
Or is it more like sexy embarrassment?
C'mon now, Kida, stop goofing off.
Sonohara, you wouldn't misunderstand and start weird rumors, would you?
Does she look like the frivolous kind of woman?
You're right, I'll leave her with you.
Don't worry, I'll be the one spreading rumors!
Does this make me a crusader of justice for the moment?
I was so cool just now, wasn't I?
Anyone would fall for me after that.
Kida? And Sonohara?
Could you have come at a worse time?
Sorry for the wait.
Here.
Thank you very much.
But still, you should be careful.
Most of the rumors about Nasujima are mostly just
that, but it is true he's laid his hands on a student.
Eh?!
A second-year student named Niekawa Haruna transferred out during the second term.
Apparently the reason was that people
would find out she was dating Nasujima.
Really?
No one knows whether she wanted to transfer, whether
Nasujima threatened her into it, or if the school forced her.
Anyway, if something happens to you,
Mikado and I will do something about it.
Right, Mikado?
I don't totally grasp the situation, but I'll do whatever I can.
Ugh. This is where you're supposed to say, "I might not
be able to do it, but I'll be able to with the power of love!"
You're not a man if you don't say something to that effect.
Eh? Isn't that a contradiction?
I'm just going with the flow.
More importantly, about before...
Huh?
Those girls who were bullying you were from your middle school, right?
H-How did you know?
Well, listening to your conversation, I figured they had to be.
Like a, "you were saved by a good person, but now that she's disappeared they've come back," kind of thing.
Hmm? Your friend's disappeared? And no one's found her yet...
It's Harima Mika from our class, isn't it?
Mika's just marked as absent at school, but she
hasn't been home since before opening ceremonies.
That's totally something you should tell the police about.
She contacted my cell phone and Harima's home.
She said, "I'm going on a trip to heal my broken heart. Don't worry."
A trip to heal her broken heart? Did something happen?
Umm...will you promise to listen without freaking out?
I'm not surprised by much anymore
after what's happened these past few days.
Harima...is a stalker.
I see.
So that's what you were asking that guy about.
Mika went on her broken-heart trip after being
dumped by the guy she was stalking—er, courting.
I guess we can't do anything but leave it to her family.
If she still doesn't come back, all we can do is call the police.
Was she a close friend to you, Sonohara?
What's with the interrogative?
It's true that we were always together.
I guess his intuition is good with some things.
I'm awkward with a lot of things and not very good at
dealing with people, but Mika would always pull me through.
I felt bad that she even chose the same high school as me.
Well, that's...
Even if you think Mika didn't want to let go of her because she
was using her to stand out, you shouldn't actually say that, Mikado.
I know.
Eh?
You know what?
That she was just using me to look cool.
And I used her as well.
I thought that life would be easier, that
I couldn't live without depending on her.
Okay...
But now I don't think it's that important.
I've adjusted...to living without her.
I became a class rep because she wanted to,
so I figured I should at least do it in her stead.
I felt like if I became a class rep, then I could surpass her.
That's kind of like cheating though, don't you think?
In my opinion, what's cheating is telling people all that.
It sounds like you're trying to get someone to forgive you.
Trying to surpass Harima is the right thing to do.
So you should hold your head high and be more confident.
Umm...
You're right.
Thank you very much.
That's what I like about this guy.
Kida!
You're so lame!
"Lame," huh?
Eh? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yes, the strongest.
You from some magazine?
Whaddya mean by "strongest?" That's too funny.
If you're talking about the strongest person in Ikebukuro, it's gotta be that black biker.
I've heard of that.
He has no head, right?
Like, no way!
What about The Slasher?
Oh yeah, that.
But you'd hafta say the strongest group here is The Dollars, right?
The Dollars?
Yeah, The Dollars!
I go a different way from here.
Thank you very much for today.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye, Anri!
I've thought of this before, but maybe
we'd find that Mika girl with Yagiri after all.
You mean like a stalker and her victim?
Maybe she abducted him.
I get it.
People are missing...
But how are we going to look for them?
Just leave them be. She said not to worry.
Only an organized group would be able to pull this off...
Like The Dollars.
Mikado...
You're not thinking of joining The Dollars, are you?
Eh? No. No way!
You better not.
People only join gangs when they're young and impressionable.
Besides, most people regret joining them.
Umm...yeah, but we're still young and impressionable...
I'm spent.
Why?
I was extremely depressed before Mikado came to Ikebukuro.
I'm able to make it through the day thanks to lots of people...
But it's also thanks to Mikado.
He's new to Ikebukuro and still vulnerable to the sweltering atmosphere.
Because he's new, he's more likely to get into trouble.
That's all?! It can't sell much worse than that!
I can douse him with cold water, but when I look into his gleaming eyes,
I know not even that will work.
That's why I try to be with him as much as I can.
I don't want him to get near the darkness this city holds.
Or me.
Bang.
I told myself I'd never...go there again.
Saika has entered the chat room.
Stronger
Strong, Love, Hope
I, want, to hope
I, want, stronger, love
Strong, person, to love
Hope, me, mother, mother
Mother
Saika has left the chat room.
Could someone be spamming us?
It's like an alien.
Maybe it's laughing...
How scary...
Look, the kanji for mother is "haha," so...
No, I'm not afraid it's an alien.
Or anything like that.
TsumiUta?
Or maybe it's "Zaika."
"Zaika" as in "property?"
I'll look into it later.
More importantly, Celty, I have a job for you.
It's from Mr. Shiki of the Awakusu Association again.
It's not that great a job, but will you do it?
Another courier job?
Yes, it's a courier job.
Although, you have to start by getting the merchandise back.
I don't know what the merchandise is, or I
should say it was a "don't ask, don't tell" situation.
Understood.
Okay, now about the item. The guy who stole it is running around somewhere.
You know where most of the hiding spots are,
so you should be able to corner him easily.
Roger.
Be careful; that Slasher's been out and about lately.
The Slasher?
Yeah, The Slasher. He appeared again.
He just leaves after inflicting wounds, but never kills anyone.
Then you can't call him the strongest, can you?
The strongest person in this city's gotta be...
Simon from Russia Sushi.
That information guy moved over to Shinjuku, but what about him?
Orihara Izaya.
No, it's gotta be...
Heiwajima Shizuo!
The strongest Color Gang?
Nowadays it's The Dollars?
But The Dollars don't have a color.
That yellow gang held the most sway until last year.
Yellow?
Yeah, they're called The Yellow Scarves.
I heard they had an insane brawl with
The Blue Squares and lots of people got taken out.
Yeah, I heard they're back in the game.
Come on, keep the orders coming!
We have Engawa scallops. They're cheap, they're cheap!
Say, don't you see them a lot these days?
See what?
Guys in yellow, right? So you did notice.
Yellow? You mean—
The Mellow Scars!
You mean The Yellow Scarves.
Yeah, that's it.
That's Hermes' line.
They should've been eradicated after that battle with The Blue Squares.
Yeah, I guess.
Their boss supposedly left.
Just call me over any time. Ah, welcome!
Can you please tell me about The Dollars?
Huh?
My friend's thinking of joining them, but I want to stop him.
Why're you asking us?
Well, I can't ask anyone else.
You wouldn't want to ask Orihara Izaya anyway.
It's not like we know much about The Dollars.
But I'll tell you everything we do know.
Sometimes...this city can almost swallow you whole.
However, I won't let you go that far, Mikado.
Mikado?
Sorry!
You can't just do that.
You can tell just by lookin' that we be Yellow Scarves, can'tchya?
Yagiri!
Huh?
That's not...Harima Mika.
I don't know who you are, but don't interfere with our flight of love.
"Flight of love...?"
Let's go.
Then who is that?
Kida!
Are you guys really in The Yellow Scarves?
Yeah, of course!
I'm asking you because I can't tell.
You...
Kida!
Oh no, Mikado, why you, too?
Mo-Monster!
Huh?
Let's go!
Man, you had me worried!
Same here!
In the end, I might be the one who's dependent upon him.
I guess.
After Mikado came here, I feel like my bravado's turned into real courage.
I might just be able to face her without running away now.
Yes?
The more she expects me to, the more like I'll be able to do it.
I didn't think you'd ever come here again.
Izaya.
Hey.
How's your boyfriend been?
He visits me sometimes.
Like he did just before now.
I'm home.
Haruna, did you make sure to eat?
Haruna?
Oh, I banned the spammer.
Now it can be peaceful again.
It'd be nice if that were so...
By the way, I heard that members of The Yellow Scarves got slashed.
What are The Yellow Scarves?
Maybe The Slasher is working for The Dollars.
What? No Way!
A war might break out.
The events which occur in this city may
seem completely unrelated upon first glance...
But they definitely connect at some point...
Yo!
And probably hold some twisted knowledge that we can't even fathom.
Good morning, Kida.
Yet...
Good morning!
Good morning, Sonohara.
I just noticed it, but this relationship feels pretty comfortable.
Good morning.
Points will connect with each other eventually...
And even if something we can't say right now gets exposed...
I believe that our relationship will stay the same.
The Dollars?
I can't say much about them.
Anyway, I'll tell you everything about the already-famous Kaztano Incident.
Next time: Run Around.
Also, don't call me Dotachin.