[scene]
What's the matter?
Oh really?
So, you're going to Mistral.
Tough luck.
But I hear they have good food and women.
It's already been half a year since Armistice.
It's great that we're both still alive.
Take this!
Hey that's bad.
Damn it.
Hey girl, you awake?
Here's your share of our war booty!
Oh... caramel!
Th-Thank you so much for giving me something so expensive!
Uh... Dear, Sergant.
Oh it's nothing.
If you're nice to the trumpeter, you'll be able to hear the retreat calls well.
It's rare we get new soldiers since the draft was abolished.
Did you volunteer?
Yes! I wanted to learn music!
Huh?
Oh... It's not like that, but..
Good to be honest.
Honesty is fine! Work hard, girl!
Private second class, your name is?
Kanata
Sorami Kanata is my name!
Sora No Oto
Resounding Sound -
The City at Dawn
Seize is having a festival today.
A festival?
So I can only deliver you up to right here.
Look.
That is where you have been assigned.
It's commonly known as the Time-Telling Fortress.
You'll be heading in that direction.
Yes!
Order
Private 2nd class, Sorami Kanata.
Assigned to 1121 Platoon of Trois State, Seize.
Helvetia Republic Army Headquarters
Mission accomplished at 1320 hours!
Thank you very much!
The city of glass and lakes, Seize.
Wait a second!
1500 is the time to report in.
I can finally let you sing.
Direction check, fine.
Time check, fine.
Equipment check, fine.
March on!
G-flat
What a marvellous sound.
Oh wow! A fish.
10yen 25sen...
Oh what a beautiful doll-
I'm sorry!
What's the matter, Rio?
A cat that got excited from the festival...
went shooting off in some random direction.
That's how it is.
Cats are supposed to wander around.
That's what makes them cute.
If it's a stray cat that's fine.
But unfortunately, that one has a master.
I'm so surprised.
But I found something wonderful.
What's the matter?
Thank you!
Huh?
Oh, a soldier!
A girl from the fortress?
That's a good omen!
Thank you for the fire!
Thank you!
All right!
Thanks for that!
Take aim,
Fire!
Thank you.
Thank you, too!
Hey!
Are you some idiot?
Getting all involved in it...
What are you going to do with your uniform all like that?
Umm.. Well...
Take care...
Thank yo-
Come with me!
Huh?
Phew...
How's the bath?
Yes, I'm happy!
How nice.
Looks like you were an easy target.
Couldn't you at least try to evade them?
Oh, this dye will come off when its dry.
So no need to worry.
That's was part of the festival, right?
It's based on a legend of Seize.
A legend?
What kind?
The Fire Maidens protect the city...
I'm sorry I troubled you.
You owe me one.
The repairs for that are done too.
And this too.
Filishia eh?
That meddler!
Late!
She is soooooo late!
We came all the way to pick her up!
Okay let's wait patiently.
It was a present from your father, right?
It's a good piece.
D-flat.
It was a wonderful bath!
I don't know why, but I often get lost.
But thanks to that, I was able to experience something wonderful!
Don't mention it.
But don't get lost in here, okay?
Huh?
Oh wow!
You understand notes?
It's a very clear sound and somehow brings back memories.
That's not what I meant-
Thief!
You idiot!
Thank you very much.
Geez.
Were you going to die for something like that?
But, that bell...
It's fine.
This must have been how it should be.
She's late.
I'm happy.
[Scene]
Umm...
I have some business to take care of, so I'm leaving.
Don't get lost any more, okay?
That bell...
It must have been something important...
What should I do?
Oh no...
That way?
March on, forward!
The Fire Maiden?
Long ago...
It's about the world before it became like this.
Under the valley, in this city, a winged demon once lived.
The demon spread fire and shook the ground, causing the people to suffer.
Finally it stole the all the maidens in the fortress,
and trapped them in an underground maze.
However, the maidens did not give up...
and called upon each other with the golden horn given to them by the Lord.
After they escaped the maze, the maidens cooperated with a very large spider and defeated the demon.
After they beheaded the demon,
its head violently shot out flames.
At the rate the fire was spreading, the town above would have been burned down.
To stop the erupting fire, the maidens, in turn, continued to embrace the demon's head.
Everyday, the villagers kept spraying water on both the blazing head and the maidens.
After a year passed, the fire was finally extinguished.
Ever since then, to comfort the spirits of the maidens who saved the village,
the water spraying festival was celebrated.
The new girl didn't come after all.
That doesn't matter any more.
Look, captain, it's Rio senpai!
Yes, she fits the role quite nicely.
I was correct in entrusting her with this task.
Huh? But that was by lotter-
I got lost again.
I'm so needless.
Being lost is fun sometimes.
But that's because you get to see someone you didn't know before.
I don't want to be all alone...
Are you lost?
I want to see my mommy!
It's all right.
If you want it,
that feeling of wanting to see her will get across.
Really?
Yes.
Sound always resounds.
Always resounds...
Always resounds, and...
And will get across.
The Fire Maiden sleeps here.
Embracing the demon, and relieving the curse...
not to let it awaken once again.
This is...
The golden horn?
Could the demon have...
Awaken?
Kureha!
Receive it, someone!
Accept my sound!
It was received.
Sound resounds, and...
Wake up already!
Private second class, Sorami Kanata!
Huh?
Where am I...
When will you wake up all the way?
This is the Time-Telling Fortress,
the 1121 platoon's station!
I'm very sorry to have troubled you yesterday...
You really did...
I'm sorry!
But...
I'm just kidding.
But don't do reckless things.
Just for one bell like this.
I'll teach you...
A trumpet!
why this fortress is called the Time-Telling Fortress.
It's the sound of the sky.
Kazumiya Rio,
That's my name.
I shall train you as the trumpeter.
Nice to meet you, Sergeant Major Rio!
Just call me Rio.
It's Filicia, our captain's policy.
We don't talk about rank here.
Umm...
Then...
Rio-senpai!
So then,
let us begin right now.
Blow the Morning Call.
The new girl is bad.
Next Episode: First Battle - A Story of the Chair