Don't make me laugh!
He sent a little brat to collect my debt?
Well, whatever.
You're lucky, kid.
I've been winning today.
Here's seven days' interest.
Take the money and go home.
Now, let's get back to the game.
Hey.
That's not what you promised.
Mr. Sugi asked you to pay your interest in person every day.
This isn't just about paying your debt.
Don't take me for a fool.
You fucker!
Don't press your luck, or I'll crack your head open and drink your blood!
Pick up...
the money.
Shut the fuck up!
Keep your jokes to yourself.
Want me to say it again?
Say what?
Pick up the money!
You can tell me about your head-cracking skills after you apologize to Mr. Sugi.
And... how may I help you?
Turtle... do you...
Will you please tell me where to find Maeda Noboru?
I can't do that.
I don't know anything about you two.
Look, old man!
Mario!
We're begging you!
Please tell us where he is.
We have to take him to a hospital.
It seems like you have your reasons.
He's currently out in Mishuku collecting a debt for me.
A debt?
If all goes well, he'll come back alive.
The borrower isn't exactly the gentlest of men.
I promised I'd lend Noboru some money if he could collect this debt.
Money?
Why would he need money?
For his family.
Or so he told me.
How much does it take...
to grant your little dream?
Noboru, you couldn't be...
I'm going to Mishuku!
Wait, I'm coming too!
No, you're not!
You heard him!
We're up against a violent—
Like I care!
He's doing this for me—
Turtle...
Hey, move your feet.
Mario!
Lily!
What are you doing here?
Do you really have to ask?
Hey, 'sup, Lily?
What's with the long fa—
Ow!
Lily...
Hey.
You idiot.
You... idiot.
Hey, why are you crying?
"I had cried out of sorrow and humiliation,
but I had never cried out of happiness."
In this world barren of kindness and care,
Turtle considered Lily as his family.
For her sake, he'd put his life on the line.
Lily couldn't hold back her tears.
Thank you.
I'm glad I finally get to see you in person.
I'm not!
You gotta be kidding me!
He almost bit through my tendon!
O-Okay!
I'll go!
I'll go pay my interest, so stop!
This is no laughing matter!
You've got a scary-ass pet.
He's a "turtle" all right.
Let's go!
The Next Day
No way!
I'm not going for a check-up!
Give me a break, Turtle!
Shut up!
Let me go, Mario!
The doctor said I had a cold!
I'm perfectly fine anyway!
Please, Noboru.
Let me go!
You need to get checked out properly.
Let me—
You survived the bomb.
Let me go, Mario!
Mario!
You told her, didn't you?!
Hey, Turtle.
I heard you told Mr. Sugi that you needed money for your family.
You meant Lily, right?
But...
What do you think she was up to
when you were doing that for her?
I-I don't know.
She was taking some serious abuse to get you checked out at the base.
That was... all you.
I didn't do anything.
Hey, Turtle.
Lily feels the same way.
She's worried sick about you.
You're like a brother to her.
If you guys are a family, you need to listen to your sister.
My sister...
Right, Lily?
I don't remember ever having such a disobedient brother.
Now, let's go!
Jeffrey!
You came here to greet us?
Thanks.
Mr. Maeda Noboru?
I'll be interpreting for you. I'm pleased to meet you.
O-Okay...
Well, let's get going.
Anyway, Mario...
I'll be away for a while.
Where are you going?
Taking care of a little business.
Watch out for Noboru.
Lily!
Hey, Jeffrey...
I don't know what you're saying.
I'm back.
How'd it go?
They'll get the results in a week, so I'll know then.
I see.
Let's head back.
Yeah.
See ya, Jeffrey.
I had fun boxing with you.
Where's Lily?
Taking care of something.
See you tomorrow.
Can I help you?
Well, then I'll see you later.
Would you please...
not lend Noboru... the money?
He doesn't need it anymore.
I'm going to disappear from his life.
So please, don't make him take any more risky jobs.
I just need to disappear.
I don't want to be a burden.
A family.
Is that how a family works?
I will lend him the money.
I set him a test, and he passed it magnificently.
This is a promise between him and me.
But that's because he—
In fact, it doesn't concern you at all, since you'll never see him again.
Now then, farewell.
Please, wait!
Will you...
Will you buy me?
One Week Later
The results from last week's check-up are in.
You're pretty healthy.
There's nothing needing treatment.
However, it's still uncertain whether or not you'll develop symptoms from the bomb explosion.
You should get a periodic check-up, or so it says.
That's great, Turtle.
Now you can relax.
Why are you looking so serious?
Show a smile, okay?
How can you be so carefree?
I'm talking about Lily!
She's been gone for a week to "take care of a little business."
Well, let's go there anyway.
Wh-Where?
To Mr. Sugi's place.
You promised you'd tell him the results, right?
Y-Yeah.
I see. That's good news.
Well, here's your money.
Thank you very much.
But I don't need this money anymore.
Hey, is the tea ready yet?
It's coming right away!
L-Lily?!
I heard that the results were good.
That makes me feel better.
Lily, you're getting better at this.
Yeah.
What does this mean?
What the hell's going on here, Mr. Sugi?!
Hey, Turtle!
You sex-crazed old bastard!
You bought her, didn't you?!
Noboru!
I...
I came to you...
just to keep Lily from doing this!
You must've tricked her with your stupid Buddha face!
How old do you think you are?!
Calm down, Turtle.
Shut up!
Mario, don't tell me you're in on this too?!
What's so funny?
Hey...
This isn't funny!
Sorry, Turtle.
Try not to get mad.
You reacted exactly as I thought you would, so it was just too funny.
Sorry, Noboru.
I'll explain everything.
On the day of your check-up, I went to see Mr. Sugi.
Will you buy me?
If you buy me, then I won't have to get Noboru involved, so...
You don't understand him at all.
He risked his life so that you wouldn't have to sell your body.
Come with me.
Then I told him everything.
How I'd lived my life until now.
How I was secretly stealing money from a U.S. Army general,
and how he swiped the cash back from me.
Telling him everything really made me hate myself.
You should thank that general.
Thank him?
Even if you had started a business with that money,
you would've gone bankrupt in no time, because you don't know how to survive.
That can't...
Missy, the business world isn't very kind.
Then what do you expect me to do?!
I don't know what to do anymore.
This house...
It's a little too spacious for an old man to live here all alone.
I'll pay you 15,000 yen a month.
You can be the housekeeper here.
You'll learn what it means to work,
and what it means to run a business.
Even if it takes a year or two,
you'll learn the principles with your body and mind.
Maeda Noboru is still young, but he knows the mechanics of running a business.
By the time you learn how business works,
he'll have transformed that 300,000 into something much larger, enough to open up a shop.
So...
that's why you live here?
Yes.
Mr. Sugi!
I'm terribly sorry for saying all those horrible things!
I leave Lily in your hands!
Noboru...
Thank you for lending me this money.
Starting tomorrow, I'll work like a dog at One Percent Loan!
One more drink!
Man, you drank way too much!
Well, I guess that's because you passed the check-up and Lily's safe.
Must be a load off your mind.
But you know...
I wonder why Mr. Sugi lives in that huge house by himself.
Why do I live in this big house all alone?
Yes.
Family.
Are they your...
My wife left me, but I built this house for my sons.
I have yet to receive their bones.
None of their comrades saw them die,
so I'm positive that they'll come back.
That's what I believe.
More!
Shut up, man.
Haven't you had enough?
Mario.
Noboru's definitely okay, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Even if it isn't, we won't let him kick the bucket.
It's just a cold!
I know.
Mario, let's switch.
No, don't worry.
I want to carry him.
All right.
A load that's heavy to carry alone...
is lighter when several people share the burden.
Lily understood the family bond for the first time,
and she chose a way of life for herself and for Turtle.
Thank you, Noboru.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
A dream he can't let go.
Mario risks everything on one small chance.
And then...