When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
It goes so fast.
The new term starts today already.
I'd better work hard with a
renewed sense of enthusiasm.
A commendable attitude, as always.
Oh, good morning, Maria.
I'll go wake the Miss.
Oh, there's no need for that.
I've decided to let her stay home today.
Oh, I see.
Wait, what?!
She seems to have caught a cold.
Hayate? Are you there, Hayate?
Y-Yes, Miss!
I am going to school.
You mustn't!
Playing hooky is for when
you're healthy and well.
My pride as the queen of
unproductive members of society
will not permit me to stay
home over a fever like this!
There she goes spouting nonsense again.
What are you doing, Hayate?
Please just rest quietly.
I'll stay home as well
and look after you today.
Hayate...
You cannot!
What?
If you miss school with me,
it will affect your grades.
One day won't make that big a difference.
You're not a super genius like me!
The points you lose from
missing just one day of school
will prove fatal for a transfer
student like you at Hakuou!
Miss!
Do not mind me!
I...
I will be fine. I will
not be done in so easily.
So leave this to me...
No, Miss!
Go, Hayate!
Miss!
What's up with this anime?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Okay, we're going to start class!
Miss Makimura, I have a question.
Yes, what is it, Azumamiya?
The Chief's so cool as a teacher, too!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
A Non-Kiddy Genius Teacher Appears
I wonder if the Miss will be all right...
Morning.
Hinagiku!
Doesn't it feel like it's been forever?
Now that you mention it, it does.
So, were you able to master
your lethal technique?
What?
Oh, well, I made various
efforts at it, but...
It's okay, there's no rush.
Thank you very much.
So? Is Nagi playing hooky as always?
No, that's not it.
She's already caught her first
cold of the school term.
What? Oh, that's worrisome...
Yes.
Maybe I'll go visit her.
Oh, please do! I'm sure
the Miss would like that.
Then I'll drop by for a bit after school...
Hinaemon! Help me, Hinaemon!
WHAM!!
Honestly! What a racket
so early in the morning!
You're so mean, Hinaemon!
You want to borrow money again, don't you?
Do not! Big Sis has lots of
problems other than money, too!
Don't be proud of it!
Um, what happened?
So good of you to ask, Ayasaki!
You see, there's a new teacher coming in,
so I got demoted from homeroom teacher
to assistant homeroom teacher!
A new teacher?
Shiori Makimura
Nice to meet you!
I'm Makimura and I'll be in charge
of this class starting today.
What?!
I look forward to teaching you!
Hmm, Miss Makimura, huh?
I just hope she's easier than Yukiji.
Well, I don't really care.
Why? What's the creator of the
caregiver robot doing here?
I'll explain then.
Model 7, Model 8, Model 9,
10, Model 11, and Model 12...
Every unit has gone berserk
or was seriously damaged
and went up in flames.
I see...
Makimura, what are your thoughts on this?
Um... Um...
Not enough firepower?
What would be the point in
causing more explosions?!
I-I'm sorry!
Do you know what's the most
important thing to a scientist?
The most important thing?
That's right. The important thing
as a person who makes things.
Naturally, that's...
Oh, I know! Cake! It's cake, isn't it?!
Sweet things are important for your brain.
Yup! Exactly! Because it
stimulates the pleasure center
and releases endorphin
into the brain! Wait...
WRONG!
It's heart!
As a person, the most important
thing is to have heart
and you are definitely lacking in that area!
Makimura, in order to have you
learn what heart is about,
I am going to have you teach at
Hakuou Academy, your alma mater.
What?
Well? Do you understand the situation now?
Hayate and you, there, sitting
in front of the television!
Yes, sort of.
But the way Miss Katsura
is looking at Miss Makimura
seems tremendously scary to me...
Everyone, let's work hard again
today with big smiles on our faces!
Hah! What's with her?!
Now, I want to know what level you're at,
There's no way she can
win them over so easily!
so I'd like to give you a pop test!
What? Is she serious?
This sucks!
Oh, dear. This is a bit of a pickle.
I've won!
The students won't go along with such
hardcore methods right off the bat!
Okay, time's up! Please
collect them in order.
That was pretty hard, wasn't it?
Give us a break.
I think it's about time
for me to show off the popularity
of the veteran teacher.
Man, good work, everyone!
It wasn't fair to spring a test
on you right after summer break.
I totally understand how you all feel!
So, an average score of 82.3...
You're all so smart.
Miss Segawa and Miss Hanabishi,
you seem to miscalculate a lot.
Miss Asakaze, your weak
point is story problems.
And Ayasaki, you've got
the fundamentals down.
Um, Miss Makimura, what
are you talking about?
What do you mean? I'm just
announcing the test results...
Wait! Do I have to mark everything
with a red pen when grading?!
Oh, no! What a pain!
Oh, I know! Miss Katsura,
could I ask you to do that?
I'll be counting on you.
Wait, why should I have to...?!
Miss Makimura!
I have a question about Problem 2!
Miss Makimura, please teach me how
to get the solution to Problem 5!
Um...
I see.
Her intelligence is on the
order of a supercomputer.
It's no surprise that Katsy got demoted.
Farewell, Yukiji.
I wish you well, even after
you've quit teaching.
Like hell I'm quitting!
Goodbye, Miss Makimura!
Bye-bye!
This is bad...
At this rate, my position at Hakuou...
No, my position in this very
anime is extremely precarious!
I have to do something about
this as soon as possible.
But what?
It's finally over.
School seems so dull without the Miss around.
Hayata!
Here, the printouts from today.
Make sure you give them to Little Nagi, okay?
Oh, thank you very much!
You owe me one now.
But why are you doing this?
Why? But of course!
It's because Izumi is the committee
chairman of this class!
Committee chairman?
Oh! You're the student council
committee chairman, right?
Hayata, I am the leader of this class.
We can't have you forgetting that.
That's right. She's Red.
Miss Committee Chairman,
Red!
And I am Blue.
The vice chairman of this class, Blue!
Furthermore, who knows? Friend or foe?
Disciplinary committee member, Black!
Together, the three of us are...
Hakuou Sword
...the student council officers!
That's great. Sounds like fun.
And now, Hayata, we'll specially present you
with the designation of Ocher,
which is currently available.
No, thank you, I'll decline.
But doesn't student council
work keep you rather busy?
Aw, not really.
Even if we do a so-so job,
our absolutely perfect student body
president will handle it for us.
That about sums it up.
Bwahahaha
Hinagiku really has it rough.
But I guess being committee
chairman can be a pain sometimes.
Report
For example, there's this Class Report.
It has to be submitted by the end of the day.
Wow! There's so much to fill out!
But it's no problemo!
These are the times when the three of us,
Red, Blue, and Black, join forces and...
O-Ocher! L-Let the two
of us join forces and...!
I understand. I am not Ocher, but I'll help.
Oh, there you are! Ayasaki, would
you come with me for a sec?!
Just hurry!
What about the Report?!
Hehehe, I love apples.
(Ihihihi, ringo daisuki.)
Your villainy is known to us!
(Kisama no akuji minuitari!)
Miss Katsura, what in the world?!
Okay!
Listen to me, Ayasaki. Stand
right there for a while.
What is this about, Miss Katsura?
Would you like to know my
thoroughly calculated strategy?
Strategy?
I'll make an exception and explain it to you.
First, that woman will come
out of the faculty office.
And I'll place this Gundam model there!
Then...
Oh! My hand-made Nightingale that's
more important than my own life!
How dare you?!
But in her path will be...
SIGN: Wet Rag
And I'll follow up on that!
Hayate
Makimura
If I spread photos like that,
she's sure to be forced to quit!
Do you understand this
masterful plan of mine now?
I understand that you're
not right in the head.
What did you say?!
Please excuse me.
Wait!
Students have to listen
to what a teacher says!
Please let go of me!
I don't want to help with such a childish
Kasukabe Defense Force-like plot!
Just shut up and work with me!
I don't want to!
Um, is something the matter?
I heard something about a plot...?
N-No, um, so...
I was teaching him that at the station,
you wait behind the plot line.
Wait, that's not "plot
line"! That's "white line"!
Oh, what fun! What fun!
Come on! You say something
smooth to back me up, too!
Go on!
Heaven is on my side!
I never imagined I'd get
such a photo by accident.
I have to hurry and post this on
all the school bulletin boards!
Hey! What are you thinking?!
I will become the god of the new world!
N-No, there's no reason to panic!
We just have to explain that
it's a total misunderstanding!
Isn't that right, Miss Makimura?
After what was done to me...
I'm ruined for marriage now!
No! Not like that!
This will be embarrassing for the Miss...
Did you know? Miss Sanzenin's butler was...
No way! That's terrible!
I must protect the Miss's
honor, no matter what!
Right around then, not knowing any
of this at the Sanzenin residence...
I'm relieved to see you doing
better than I expected.
Yes, my fever is completely gone now, too.
That reminds me, what did
you do during summer break?
What?
I enjoyed it pretty fully.
First, I went to a fireworks
festival with Hayate.
Then, I went to the seaside camp with Hayate,
I went to the amusement park with
Hayate, and I went fishing with Hayate.
Also, with Hayate...
Is something the matter?
Nothing, it's just that you
sound so happy talking about it.
What? I-It's not that big a deal...
Come on, tell me more.
Sure! And I also played
lots of games with Hayate!
Oh, that's right. I also watched
"Soft Tank" with Hayate, too. And...
A lively chat about summer memories.
Miss Katsura, please wait!
Like hell I gotta, panna cotta!
Haha! Bye-bye!
I'm going to take it from you,
even if I have to do it by force!
Aw, man, I never did get to see
Hayate during summer break.
Wh-Why?
Why don't you think about giving up soon?
You're awfully persistent yourself.
Oh! I found you, Hayata! Gotcha!
SIGN: Report
You're awful! You said you'd
help me write the Report!
Miss Segawa! You've come at the perfect time!
Please take out the memory
card from that camera!
What photos are on here?
Photos of Ayasaki tied up with rope
and looking like he's in ecstasy!
Please don't make stuff up!
I knew it. So you do have a
taste for that sort of thing.
What?
You're kind of girly, so I thought
you might like being punished.
What?! Since when did my
character get that reputation?
Don't get so depressed, Hayata!
You know, how do I say this?
I like being punished, too.
What?
Oh, no! I didn't mean it like that!
Sheesh! Now Hayata thinks I'm a
weird girl because of you, Katsy!
I cannot let you get away with this now!
Oh-ho. Then what will you do?
I am going to take this memory card.
This is the end of the line for you.
If you'll take my side,
I'll help you with all of your
homework for the next 3 months!
There's no way you can
win her over like that...
Here you are.
The deal is sealed!
What?!
Sorry about that, Hayata.
And away I go!
You're...!
Uh...
And who might you be?
Are you the one who made my sweet honey cry?
N-No, I'm not!
I-It was him! Him!
Eight!
I'm so sorry, Eight.
For acting in a way that
betrayed you, my lover...
Like I said, nothing happened!
Actually, wait, when did you two get
into that kind of relationship?!
Unforgivable!
Interesting!
You've made me get serious!
If you've got a fight for me, I'm
buying, even if I have to go into debt!
Why does it end up that way?
And she's fighting him like an equal, too!
Why you!
Watch out!
You're pretty good.
Same to you, too!
Please stop! Don't fight for me!
Wow, I wonder how it's going to end!
So thrilling! So exciting!
What should I do?
Don't Push
Any way you slice it, that's
a self-destruct button.
All right! If I just push that...
Oh, but no! I can't do that!
If I push that button now, there
will be a humongous blast!
When that happens...
When that happens, Miss Segawa will be...
It's no problem, Hayata.
Uh, but with someone in
a skirt nearby... um...
Oh!
I wear bike shorts under it like
Hina, so it's totally okay.
Thank you, bike shorts!
Blown to smithereens!
Eight...
So futile... This is so terribly futile.
What?
But I mean, isn't that right?
Fighting doesn't give rise to anything!
Miss Katsura...
Everything that happened is all his fault.
But I'm begging you!
Please... Please, for my sake,
as his teacher, forgive him!
You see, adolescent boys are really
bad at controlling their emotions.
And it's my role as a teacher
to guide and instruct them.
At times, the way they're
almost painfully delicate
is heartbreaking and agonizing,
and you hit a wall sometimes...
But I will never turn away from them!
Because... Because I'm a
teacher! Because I love them!
Miss Katsura! I... I finally understand!
That it's important to have heart!
Miss Makimura...
I admire you, Miss Katsura!
I want to become like you, too!
Really? But the path of a
teacher is fraught with peril.
You still have a lot to learn.
I am ready to face it!
All right. If you're
prepared to go that far...
Starting today, I'll hold
study sessions for you!
Mainly at pubs! For about the
difference between the salaries
of a homeroom teacher and
an assistant teacher!
My! How reassuring you are!
Just as I planned!
And thus...
I know a good place that I go to often.
Hey, sounds good!
...the ultimate battle of clever
strategies came to an end.
Leaving the butler-in-debt behind,
thinking about how there
are all kinds of smarts.
What was all the trouble I went through for?
Now, now. The Report got written
without any mishap, too,
so it's a happy ending.
Th-This is...
I played with Hayata and the others
today and it was a lot of fun!
P.S. Sorry, Hina. I'll leave the rest to you!!
That's a journal entry!
Cheers!
Oh, that's right. Miss Katsura, we'll
be counting on you to pay the bill.
What?!
I mean, you are older and also
senior to me as a teacher.
Thanks for treating.
What?!
Doooom
You reap what you sow.
Humans are so interesting.
Next time is a must-see for girls, too!
He will be fighting his
numerous appealing qualities!
I had very little screen
time in this episode!
Now, now, that's going to
happen once in a while.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
I love you to Earth! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Nice to see ya again! It's
Sakuya. How've ya been?
But this sure is a girlish song, quite
different from your image, Saku.
Do you think so?
I believe the powerful tone of
this song fits Sakuya perfectly.
What's with the two of ya?
Makin' these random comments...
The truth is, ya hadn't heard the
song yet when ya recorded this.
Whoa, she went and said it!
The director and the staff're in a bind,
so I'm beggin' ya, Geneon, get the
songs in as early as ya can...
See you again next time!
Hey, what're ya doin'?!
Preview
My dear Hayate, you seem
rather happy for some reason.
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
I am. A certain person thanked me.
Oh, my.
With the string of mishaps and people
giving me unfriendly looks lately,
I'd been feeling a bit down, so...
My dear Hayate.
Yes?
I want you to know that I
love you, my dear Hayate.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"I've Never Had the Trouble
of Being Too Popular".
When I saw them yesterday, it looked
to me like they were embracing, but...
I've Never Had the Trouble
of Being Too Popular
Om Shura Sowaka!