Gotta go.
Mission to Initiate Action for the
Maintenance of the Direct Line to Headquarters for Extraordinary Emergency Situations?
Th-That's quite an overwhelming title, isn't it?
It's an extremely important mission.
If we fail, the entire platoon will face disciplinary actions.
Depending on the situation, a level one warning will be issued,
and this entire division could be placed under emergency deployment.
That's right.
It's a really important duty, isn't it?
Wh-What kind of mission is this?
That is...
Phone duty.
You do know that this is the hotline to Headquarters, right?
Has it ever rung before?
No.
That's right.
Good thing too.
Could it be...
Yes, we'd be troubled if it rang,
but it would be even more troubling if it doesn't ring when it should, right?
So, every six months, we confirm that it connects properly.
And that is...
Well... err...
Geez, remember it already!
Direct Line to Headquarters for Emergency situations... err...
No, it's Direct Line to Headquarters for Extraordinary Situations... hmm...
Mission to Initiate Action for the Maintenance of the Direct Line to Headquarters
for Extraordinary Emergency Situations.
That's it.
Me, me, me, me!
Please let me do this mission!
I've always wanted to try talking on a phone.
Is it that exciting?
Basically, it works just like Takemikazuchi's intercom.
Only at a further distance. That's all.
But it's amazing to be able to talk to people who are far away.
It's wonderful.
Well, it certainly feels strange to talk with people you can't see.
And it's not a big deal once you get used to it.
However, what's troubling is that we do not know when they will be calling today.
Even then, will you still do it?
Of course!
All right.
So, you'll stay by the phone all day.
Ring, ring, ring.
This is Private Sorami Kanata of Platoon 1121 of the Helvetian Army.
When the call ends, place the receiver back on top of the phone.
All right!
My, you're so cute.
Filicia-san.
What are you doing?
Geez, how embarrassing.
The train is leaving.
Train?
There are some documents I must rush to Headquarters.
And Klaus-san won't come until next week, right?
So, I'll send them to the station...
I'll leave the phone up to you, all right?
Okay.
If you happen to fail, they may even decide that we've been attacked.
Do it well.
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Y-Yes!
I wasn't sleeping!
Not sleeping at all!
Have you seen Noël?
She's not in her room.
Is she at the hangar again?
Fine then...
Now, Kanata,
what do you want to eat for lunch?
I-I-I'll make it.
Don't worry about it. It's my turn.
But...
Hey. Why don't you and Kureha
ever let me do anything when it's my turn for kitchen duty?
I used to cook all the time even before you all came.
Well, that's because...
It can't taste that bad either.
W-Well, it certainly doesn't taste as bad as it looks...
What?
No. It has a distinct taste. It's wonderful.
Is it?
Then I shall put even more effort into it today than usual.
Hey! Is anyone here?
Yes!
Senpai!
It's Naomi-san.
I'm busy.
But I have to stay by the phone.
Hey, you have a visitor!
Tch! I guess I have no other choice.
Okay, I'll be right there.
I don't want to eat another sandwich with chopping board chips.
Is that...
Some drinks.
It's apple cider.
It's home made from where we get our apple juice.
So, these are in exchange for our Calvados, aren't they?
Ah, that's right. She found out.
Two bottles will do for your refreshments, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Refreshment?
There's a meeting for the town's merchant guild.
We give them refreshments to make things go smoother when we need favors.
Remember that.
All right.
What's that about?
The girls all tried so hard to hide it from her.
How did you find out?
W-Well...
I'll tell you next time when I get the chance.
That aside, how about joining us for lunch, Naomi-san?
What?
Are you saying I should attend too?
You see, about that piece of news in the papers this week,
everyone seems to want a proper explanation from the military.
News?
About the cease-fire agreement meeting having difficulties.
Is that so?
They're picking at the details about the reparations, supply of provisions and such.
It's only natural that it's been dragging on for so long.
Well, the true motives of the old guys at the guild
is probably just to see you though.
Ever since you played the Fire Maiden at the Water-Throwing Festival,
your fans have increased.
That was quite embarrassing.
Good grief...
This means that I will have to go.
I'm a Fortress Maiden in my heart and soul too.
I will complete my mission.
I understand. I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
Kanata.
I'll let you have these.
They're my old ones though. Sorry.
These are...
...trumpet...
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful!
Thank you very much.
Your bugling has improved quite a lot.
It's a reward for practicing so seriously.
Also, this will prevent you from falling asleep as well.
Err... this is C,
D, E, F, G...
A.
Summer will be over soon.
Iliya?
Maybe I drank too much.
Noël-chan! Are you there?
It's raining!
The laundry will get soaked!
It's still within my field of operations!
Kanata!
Let's play!
Yeah!
Kanata!
Let's play!
Save me!
Thanks for helping.
Not at all.
I'm just glad that your laundry is fine.
Seriously...
Oh, I'm sorry to have made you help so suddenly.
Don't let that bother you.
We are sorry for dropping by so suddenly as well.
I must leave for Treize tommorrow, so I've come to say good-bye.
T-That's terribly kind of you-
There's no need to greet soldiers.
That is not true, Seiya-san.
I have heard that this child has been rude to people at your base,
and I would like to apologize for that as well.
Where are the other people?
Everyone has gone out.
Rio-san as well? That person with black hair.
Yes.
I see...
I wanted to meet her at-
Is this your book?
What is it?
A book on trumpeting.
It's something I got from Rio-senpai.
I see.
I should have known...
No, no, pardon me.
I was just thinking out loud.
Are you house-sitting by yourself?
That's right.
Well,
I'm on a Mission to Initiate Maintenance
of the Direct Line to Headquarters for Extraordinary Emergency Situations.
That means she's waiting for that phone to ring.
Yes.
But, it's my first time using one.
I'm a little nervous.
Will I be able to speak properly, or...
Well, how about we practice then?
So, Yumina-san is going to the guild meeting as well.
Yes. She is going to collect donations from people at the guild.
Here. Enjoy.
Yummy!
Isn't it? Have some too, Seiya-kun.
I'll drink it, but...
...don't think you can win me over with this!
What are you making?
Do you two know what this is?
Ah, a phone!
Is this really a...
Yes, it's a phone.
I make them sometimes to entertain the kids.
Now, Seiya-san.
Okay.
A phone, huh?
Hello.
Hello!
Amazing!
That's amazing, Seiya-kun.
I can hear you clearly.
That's not right.
You should say, "Hello" first.
That's a phone custom.
H-Hello!
Hello?
It's amazing.
It really is. I can really hear his voice!
That's fine for practice, isn't it?
Yes.
This is...
Hello!
H-Hello!
This is Private Sorami Kanata of Platoon 1121 of the Helvetian Army.
Good. Not too stiff.
I-It's very kind of you to take the trouble of calling.
Yes. Not too bad.
So, err... well...
Wait, birdie!
Mishio-san!
No!
Mishio-chan!
What happened?
The phone!
Are the Pastor and our-
Yes?
Oh countless gods!
How did this happen?
You came here to thank them for everything they've done and say good-bye,
but just fooled around and caused trouble, instead.
No dinner for you guys tonight!
Yes.
Me, too?
It's all right, now.
Thanks.
But your clothes are all wet.
That's fine. I have spare-
I have a good idea!
This is...
embarrassing!
Not at all!
My, you look so pretty!
Thank you anyway, Yumina-san!
I'll wash and return these clothes.
No. Please keep them.
They're too big for the kids
and I can't imagine anyone more suited for them than you.
I'm sorry, Kanata.
Will you play with us again some time?
Sure.
Come again too, Seiya-kun.
I...
I-I'll come to play if I'm free.
Please excuse us then.
May you all be blessed.
Th-Thank you!
Now, then.
I better clean up around here.
I forgot.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Gotta go.
Someone, hurry up!
Hurry...
Geez, those old men...
What's wrong, Kana-
Senpai...
Please...
Save me!
What's wrong, Kanata?
I can't hold it anymore...
I'm gonna pee myself!
Go on quickly or you'll get sick!
Thank you very much!
Was she holding it in this whole time?
Either she's really dedicated, or just foolishly honest.
What's wrong?
I-It's all right!
Kanata!
I can't... I can't move to reach it at all!
Her timing's really terrible.
Hello?
This is Master Sergeant Rio Kazumiya of the 1121 Platoon of the Helvetian Army.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I heard we were confirming your line,
so I insisted...
Are you going to run?
No!
I'm not running!
I see.
You still haven't forgiven me.
After all this time, what do you want?
Please!
I wish for you to save this country... save Helvetia.
Good morning, Kanata.
Noël-chan, have you been in there the whole time?
Yes, I sleep well in the toilet.
No way!
We're back-
My,
you're dressed so adorably, Kana-chan!
And, what are you two doing in the hallway?
Kanata fell and can't get up.
Are you hurt?
Then just stand up!
Fine then, geez...
Spoiled little girl...
No... Don't...
One... Two...
No~!
Next time:
Passing of a Typhoon!
Virtual and Real Image