World conquest log
Owner: Edogawa Jou
First year, Arahabaki
Tamamo-no-Mae
And now
priestess of the new world
ruler of the new world
valuable reso
priestess
Sasami@Unmotivated
World conquest log
Owner: Edogawa Jou
World conquest log.
Owner: Edogawa Jou.
I've finalized my plan down to the smallest detail. It's all coming to fruition.
To execute it, I performed the ritual to summon Kuzuryuu.
As...
As the day shifts to night, we'll switch places.
My name is Awashima-sama.
I'm another personality that takes control of this body while her spirit rests.
I was once a god that she decided to eat.
I just grow a penis every now and then!
Damn it, I should have come up with a better excuse...
So it just happens to you?
She believed it?
Yeah, it randomly comes and goes, but it'll be gone soon!
So... you're a girl, right?
Yeah. But please, keep it a secret from everyone else.
Yeah, sure thing.
It'll be our little secret.
Uh... Thanks.
But... People can't catch that condition, right?
Huh?
I won't start growing one, will I?
Don't worry about that!
I think I've managed to fool her.
It's quite a mess if you ask me.
First year, Arahabaki
Tamamo-no-Mae
You've been watching, Tamamo-no-mae?
First year, Arahabaki
Tamamo-no-Mae
The way you're talking... you're still a male, aren't you milady?
No need to worry, we're switching. Jou's better at rituals.
Yeah! The sun's already up, Awashima-sama!
Oh please! Sasami almost found out!
The events were beyond my control.
Let the ritual commence.
Come forth, Winged Warlord Garuda!
Garuda, you stand guard in watching out for danger.
Tamamo-no-Mae, you set up a barrier and get rid of people.
Understood.
And now I will call upon the full strength of the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki
And now
and initiate our plans of world domination.
All for the sake of my happiness.
All for my desires and curiosity!
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
Sasami@Unmotivated
Finale
No efforts tomorrow
In that case, may I call you Jou?
That moment, I embraced false expectations.
Kagami...
I invite you to the organization.
Become my servant and use your powers for me!
Kagami!
What's gotten into you?
Didn't you see? Kagami!
Kagami!
What's going on? Explain!
You're becoming my servant, right?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa!
I've gotta go!
I'll call you later!
Hey! Wait, Sasami!
Very well! Then don't come!
That's right. All expectations result in disappointment.
Especially if the subject is a human.
I actually had a relative interest in going to the festival with you.
Why won't she do what I want?
This is why I hate humans! I hate it that I don't understand them!
It's pointless to get involved with others! It's total nonsense!
Milady, all of the preparations for the plan are complete.
Very well.
This is my fate.
I'll accept it and march forward, laughing out loud.
Even if I am alone.
Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki, commence an all-out attack!
Let's run!
I shot the shopkeeper!
Can we get him as a prize?
We already have Meat as our pet.
We can't keep any others.
We could keep him at Mamarin's place!
Tama, wait here. I'll be right back.
What's wrong?
I hope I'm just over-thinking.
Excuse me for a moment!
You're getting the shopkeeper?
I don't think so.
What? What's going on?
Mamarin, help me blurb!
Tama? Tama!
They drugged Tama and it affects me too...
This was struck by lightning too...
The torii and the local deity's forest
the travellers' guardian gods and the protector Buddha too.
Even giant trees and cliffs, all of the spiritual spots were destroyed.
I'm worried about those guys who
accidentally joined our chat earlier too.
This isn't looking too good.
Oh? What's wrong, Ms. Tsurugi?
A barrier! We're locked in on the island!
Uh, what are you doing?
Ah, the tide's rising.
I'm not a kid, you know.
Though I don't mind that my yukata doesn't get wet.
And here I wanted to find out who you really are now that we're by ourselves.
Oh well.
It's just a little more, right, Brother?
Long time no see, Kagutsuchi, Lord of Fire.
Oh, you go by Yagami Kagami these days?
I heard that my sister met you,
but I thought you were dead.
Garuda, the Winged Warlord is here as well.
Aren't you happy, as a former comrade?
So the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki still exists?
In my right, the Sword of Stones.
In my left, the Sword of Roots.
These are the divinified swords that cut down Kagutsuchi, the Lord of Fire!
Indian variable style, Chinese strategic style, and Japanese ceremonial style.
Which one do you prefer?
I, the beauty of three lands, will cut you down!
Hello there, Tama.
Where am I?
Where's Mamarin? Mamarin!
Why isn't she answering?
This island's been closed by a barrier.
Tsukuyomi Sasami's will from
Ame-no-Nuboko can't reach you.
What are you doing?
This is the secret festival.
And you're gonna help us too.
The secret ceremony of this shrine is a play that demonstrates how Kuzuryuu was slain.
You are the hero who kills the evil dragon.
New gods defeat the old gods.
Isn't that a fitting role for you?
New generation god, Yagami Tama.
I am a forgotten, elder god,
Arahabaki the Unworshipped.
Perfect for the role of the Kuzuryuu, don't you think?
Kill me with that sword now.
No!
Kill me!
Can't you?
Because that's... wrong...
I'm glad you're kind and stupid.
The ceremony is just history repeating itself.
The cycle just continues on and on here.
I'll use Tamamo-no-Mae's power to mislead the world!
I'll change the history so that the Kuzuryuu defeats the Yamato court!
Does it hurt? It does?
You're a god, and it still hurts?
Why are you doing this?
You're Mamarin's friend!
The monotheistic god Arahabaki made himself whole, all alone.
He became omniscient and omnipotent all alone.
He doesn't need family, friends, servants, or anything.
The ritual is complete!
History willl alter itself and Kuzuryuu will emerge victorious!
And now, at the end of that history, Kuzuryuu regains its true form!
Slander the history of Yaoyorozu!
Rid history of Yaoyorozu!
All for the sake of my happiness.
All for my desires and curiosity!
Tama! Tama!
Mamarin... You're back...
What happened, Tama?
They destroyed the island...
I was... I was eaten!
A really scary god destroyed it all!
Don't cry, Tama.
We should do something about this.
I can't!
I was eaten!
Don't give up, Tama! There must be something we can still—
That's right.
We can still use you.
You're...
Tamamo-no-Mae who plays with the scales!
You're late, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
I've been waiting for you to call. I opened a window on the barrier just for that.
What on earth did you do?
As you can see, we revived the elder god Kuzuryuu and destroyed the island.
We will use the gargantuan power of
Kuzuryuu to declare war on the world.
But...
Be proud, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
My master thought highly of you
and chose you as the priestess of the new world,
priestess of the new world
which means, the ruler of the new world!
ruler of the new world
An invasion is a failure if you annihilate the enemy.
Humans are a valuable resource.
valuable resource
To use them well, a priestess is necessary to act a liaison between the gods and humans.
priestess
Don't listen to her!
They're bad people!
They're just tricking you!
We are negotiating.
Using the power of Kuzuryuu, we could
evaporate Ama-no-Nuboko where you are.
Can I trust you?
But of course.
We lost.
We couldn't stop you and countless innocent people were involved.
It's pointless to fight until we're all dead.
So if you want me...
Mamarin!
Then swear! Swear to the gods!
"I, Tsukuyomi Sasami, will become Arahabaki's priestess!"
To the gods?
An oath to the gods is absolute.
You can't go back on those words.
We'll only bestow our trust in you if swear by this oath.
Mamarin, don't!
It's okay, Tama. It doesn't matter anymore.
But...
After all, this...
was enough to buy time!
What?!
You shouldn't have let your guard down, Tamamo-no-Mae.
That cannot be! I disposed of you myself!
Those swords are my natural counters, so I deemed the fight hopeless and feigned death.
You played possum? Against me, a fox?!
I am a spiritual robot inhabited by a god.
If I am defeated, I only need to abandon my body and look for another.
And you inhabited this Sesshou golem?
I'm really sorry, girls.
I kept a secret from you.
Mamarin...
I wanted to go on the trip as soon as I felt better.
So I moved my entire house inside your body, Tama and came along with you.
I controlled you from the inside. This house was my driver's seat.
So you've been inside the island's barrier all along?
Though I lost consciousness briefly because of that drug.
Sometimes I took control. For example when I went to bath with Edogawa.
Your mistake was thinking that you defeated the Yagami sisters
and opened a window on the barrier to communicate with me on the outside.
Tsurugi should be outside the barrier coming up with a plan about now.
She was alive?! This is bad, I must warn milady!
Did you honestly think you'd get away?
The Lord of Fire, Kagutsuchi, will burn you up!
Now I'm the owner of this body.
Are you okay, Tama?
Kagami! Kagami!
Tama...
We don't have time for this.
First, let's fix this destruction.
I will use the Yata Mirror.
Tama, you'll have to defend yourself.
Restore the world of man to its original state.
This island was uninhabited?
I thought the world was destroyed. Was that just an illusion?
It seems that Kuzuryuu wasn't
perfectly revived for some reason.
If it was just an illusion, then everyone might be still alive and well.
Edogawa too...
That's Tsurugi.
I just came by because something felt off.
Why do I have to do minor crap like this?
Kuzuryuu could be revived because you didn't close the entrance of the underworld properly!
Hey... In Japan, islands are considered one with the gods, aren't they?
Yes.
Gods become the islands, and islands become the gods.
Does that encompass this island as well...?
This is Kuzuryuu.
I haven't cut up anything this big since Yamata-no-Orochi.
Decree heaven's judgement on him! Ama-no-Habakiri!
Chill out, you retard!
Sasami and the others are still at the island!
I'm sorry...
I couldn't go to the festival with you.
I don't mind.
I'm sorry.
I got a bit scared of it, you know.
Of what?
If I got everything and became the supreme god of the world,
then I could never go on a trip like this anymore,
have people call my name, laugh, or eat with you.
I'd be all alone.
But that's obvious and I thought I wanted that...
I know. Being alone is a terrifying feeling.
What do you even know about me?
I've worked really hard since I was younger, as the head of the organization, shouldering huge expectations.
I've worked hard, incredibly hard.
And still...
You're right. I guess I don't know anything about you.
But if you run away, you lose.
I'll kill you one day.
Well, until that day, let's be friends.
You're such a weirdo.
And you're mean, Jou.
I'll pass out until rescue comes.
I'm so worn out.
Me too.
I can smell Sasami's scent! It's coming from that direction!
Are you serious?
Now that my spiritual power is low, his nose is our only lead.
Paparin! Full speed ahead!
Sasami! I'm on my way!
Even considering your desperate situation, your downfall is outrageous.
Especially Ruza's decadence is outright scandalous.
I have no words of excuse.
You turned away from your duty and sunk into a deviant lifestyle. How foolish.
I shall return you to the right path.
As you wish. But...
Hm?
You're cute when you're so jealous.
We aren't putting forth any more effort today.
Sasami@Unmotivated
Even if you say "see you tomorrow" as you leave
I end up wanting to meet you right away again
I want to listen to you talk
All the way until I get on the train
You smile at me with a disappointed look.
Hey, let's go home together.
I can hear your voice.
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony.
Light shines down like love.
Let's hold hands forever.
I can feel our osmotic pressure,
and I don't want it to stop.