Apprentice Negi Springfield was sent to Japan to teach a class of Mahora Academy’s middle school girls for training.
Meanwhile, however, there is a vampire on the loose within the Academy.
And, on a moonlit night, a vampire girl appears before Negi.
I’ve waited for this day, Negi Springfield, son of the Thousand Master!
Who is she? What is her motive? What is it?
Release Nodoka-san right now!
Fine. I’m done with her anyway.
Negi-sensei…
Well, aren’t you the kind one, little boy.
Now that I have a virgin's blood, do you really think you can match my magic?!
Aniki!
I underestimated you. That much power for a 10-year old…
I see, no doubt you’re his son.
Who exactly are you?
Hey, wait!
Where was the last time you saw her?
At the entrance hall!
Negi-bouzu!
Konoka-ojousama!
Ojousama!
Huh…? Secchan?
Are you okay?
I…don’t know…
You don’t know?
There’s an injury on Ojousama’s neck!
Nodoka-san! Nodoka-san!
Huh? It disappeared…was it just my imagination?
Eh? What is…?
Nodoka!
Nodoka! Wake up!
Nodoka-san…This is great! You’re okay now!
Eh…? I never noticed it because of her hair, but…she’s got a really cute face…
Ne-Negi-sensei’s face is so close... W-what do I do…?
Hmm now…
Ah, that scared the crap out of me. But Aniki, isn’t it great that they didn’t see your magic?
Yeah, I guess you’re right.
Asuna-san!
But I did.
Mr. Mage!
Are you freaking serious?!
Uwah! The rat can talk!
Dumbass! I’m not a rat! I’m an ermine!
Mmhmm; you made this rat talk because of your magic, didn’t you?
Hell no! I’ve been like this the whole time!
And I’m not a rat, I’m an ermine! An ermine! Remember that!
You’re noisy as heck!
I’m sorry!
What?
The fact that you saw me use magic isn’t something I can let slide. Asuna-san, I have to erase your memory!
My memory?
Finished! Okay, now, Asuna-san, exactly what am I?
A mage, of course.
CORRECT!
Eh? What?
Didn’t go away, Aniki.
Ow!
What in the heck are you doing, Aniki?
What’re you trying to do, you brat?!
Ow!
This ain’t gonna work.
So you finished your classes as a mage...
Yes.
If he’s able to complete his training and find a partner as well, Aniki’ll be able to rank up as a mage.
A partner, you say?
Yes. If I’m aiming to reach the highest level of mages, Magister Magi, I have to find an appropriate partner.
Aniki isn’t an adult yet, so he can’t make an official contract with a partner; he can only issue provisional contracts.
Provisional contract?
In exchange, he is able to give pretty much anyone a provisional contract under an alias and can exchange them as he pleases.
So in other words, you’re still a mage apprentice.
I graduated from the Magic Academy! I’m not an apprentice anymore!
An appropriate partner, eh…?
Konoka-ojousama, I promise I won’t let events like the one from tonight repeat.
We have been protecting the Konoe house for generations...
and I, Setsuna, with pride for the Sakurazaki family, will protect her, even at the cost of my life.
Whaddya think, Ane-san? Wanna make a provisional contract?
Ch-Chamo-kun!
How do you make one?
Eh? Uh…um…well…
What are you getting all hot n’ bothered about, Aniki?!
I-I’m not hot and bothered or anything…
Tell me! What do you do?
Gotta KISS, Ane-san! Kiss!
For mages, exchanging a kiss will enable the partner to bind to the provisional contract!
Easy, isn’t it?!
Oh…really? I-is that what it is? That’s pretty easy-
B-but it’s not like I’ll want to be your partner, okay?
Y-yes, I know! A mage and his partner must be together, and if they have no confidence, then it’s no good!
Then it’s impossible!
Yes, VERY impossible!
Oi, oi, you guys are acting like kids, geez! Learn to get along!
You guys are gonna be under the same roof living together!
Say what?! Together?!
Well, ya see…
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT!?
Negi…
When did you get in? Is it even okay for a teacher to enter a student’s room without permission?
This isn't good, Eva. Countless full moons and you’re doing that?
I’m a vampire, you know.
I erased the wounds after you bit the girls; they’re not going to become your servants.
It’s good to prepare.
It’s my job. Don’t do it again, okay? You’ll receive a heavier punishment otherwise.
I’m not afraid of that!
Evangeline.
I’ve waited 15 years for this.
EAT THIS!
That imbecile casted a spell on me.
This is the result of it all. I have to be the one locked up in an Academy.
This is your punishment, though. Eva.
But if I…was able to take the blood of the son of the Thousand Master, I-!
Don’t even think about it, Eva. I understand how you feel, but don’t resort to this.
What in the hell do you know?! Growing up to be a normal man…living freely.
How in the hell can you understand the pain and suffering I feel from having to live an eternal hell?!
Eva…
Just leave.
Gotta deliver papers…
Why the hell are you sleeping here?! You’re supposed to be on the floor!
Aigh, I shouldn’t have let him here in the first pla-
Onee-chan…
You’re such a kid. When you wake up, you’re in for it big time.
So all together, this makes three people.
See? I told you it was real!
I guess, but unlike you, we didn’t get anything.
But about that…last night, it disappeared! See?
I told you the blood sucking ordeal was a farce. All three of you just happened to see the same dream.
Pres!
Did it happen to look like this?
Is that it? Is that the chupacabra?
Well…we were together, but I didn’t see that creature.
I don’t think that’s it…
I knew it! It was Dracula!
Dracula!
I see…so there was a Dracula in there…eh?
Hmm…It wasn’t just a chupacabra; Dracula was in there, too…this’ll be interesting.
After all, it’s Chupacabra vs Dracula; it’s gonna be the Academy’s greatest epic battle in that aspect.
Battle?!
But like, what's with you guys and chupacabras?
Idiots, all of them.
Homeroom will now begin.
Rise!
Oh my goodness!
What happened, Negi-sensei?!
Oh, nothing, I just…
What happened? Did someone hit you? Who was it? Who was the banshee that did it?! As class president, I cannot allow this!
What the heck does being president have to do with it…?
I’ll be fine, Iinchou-san; I just fell down, that’s all.
It doesn’t look like a bump from falling. But Negi-sensei, if I were to protect you from that banshee…!
Oh, kind me!
Ugh, you piss me off, you Shotacon woman!
Anyway, let me take attendance.
Those two are absent again…
Oh, Eva and Chachamaru? They’re never here, so don’t worry about it!
They ditch class, aru!
Is it senpai?
If that’s the case, it’s sabotage!
Even if you say sabotage is okay…
What’s that supposed to mean?
Ah, it feels great out here…
Ah, thank you, Nekane-san!
It’s too bad that I have to say goodbye to all this scenery…
London is a very nice place, Anya. It’s most suitable for your studies.
You said the same thing to Negi.
Oh my…did I now?
I wonder if Negi’s doing well…
He’ll be fine…I’m sure he’s fine…
Negi…
The day is finally over! I did a bunch of studying today!
More like a bunch of sleeping.
Yeah, pretty much!
Goodness gracious.
Asuna! Let’s play badminton!
Sounds great! Count me in!
Oh man!
Why didn’t you bring this up with me last night, Eva-san?
I’m sorry. I didn’t think it was going to be this bad!
I’ll be okay, Master.
Not with those wounds! Goodness, what made it so bad?!
Eva-san, Chachamaru-san.
Pleasure to meet you. I’ll be the new homeroom teacher for the A class. Did…did something happen?
Chachamaru’s going through a break down!
…break down?
Can’t you tell? She’s broken! Look!
…a machine?!
Why the shock, Negi-sensei? I made Chachamaru. Didn’t you hear about it?
Chachamaru is a robot?! I thought she was a student this whole time…
I’m a student.
I am a robot, but I am also an 8th grader.
I…I see…
Is that so wrong?
Oh, no! It’s not a bad thing at all…
Oh dear. Looks like something bad happened.
We have to hurry!
A robot student…living in the Academy…
Hmm? Wait a minute…
Could it be that…? If that’s the case, then the vampire is…
You’re correct.
Takamichi!
I’m sorry if I’ve caused any trouble.
Good grief.
Evangeline is a vampire. When she was 10 years old, she laid her eyes on a vampire.
She was bitten and had her blood sucked. Once that happened, a curse was put upon her.
A curse?
She would be forever cursed to live a life in the body of a child.
Perpetual youth? So, you mean to tell me that the figure from last night was…
On every night with a full moon, Eva can use her power to transform herself into a woman of her dreams.
Takamichi…you were the one that cured the wounds of Nodoka-san and the others, right?
It doesn’t matter what her reasoning is; I can’t forgive her if she harms people.
It’s a sin.
Eva-san, fetch me that item there.
Heck no. Do it yourself.
I can’t let go of the hand. Hurry.
I told you ain’t doin’ it.
This thing, right?
Oh, please discard the insulation tape before using it.
You’ll get an electric shock otherwise.
Should’ve said it first, you idiot.
She can’t leave the school grounds?
Precisely. The Thousand Master had made it that way.
Dad did…
As a vampire, Eva imposed a lot of faults. This is to make up for it.
She’ll be with her classmates through middle school. But once they graduate, she reverts back to the 7th grade. She just relapses.
Every... Single... Time.
I understand why Eva causes mischief with Chachamaru. Like Eva, Chachamaru will be a figure that never grows up.
Repairing complete.
Ah. Really now?
Try not to touch her so much. She’s a robot, meaning she’s very delicate.
In any case, I’m glad.
Is Eva-san after me?
Eva is after your blood.
My blood?
If she gets her hands on the blood of a relative of the Thousand Master, the spell will be eradicated.
She’ll be able to flee from this place. She can live in the free world. If that were to happen…
We can't afford to let her free.
Takamichi…
Tonight…the target of the vampire girl is only one person.
Fate starts to deceive; it's a grieving fate indeed.
What's on your mind, Negi?
What will happen next?! You’ll have to wait until next time!
The enemy’s running away and carrying something with him!
Alright, let's go, de gozaru!
Go, Baka Rangers!
Wait a minute!
I didn’t even get to finish my announcement!
Oh? Is that all, aru?
It doesn’t matter, does it? We’re in a hurry, you know.
I didn’t get to go yet, it’s not fair! I didn’t get to finish!
Aigh, fine, fine!
Okay then, let’s give it another go.
Really?! Thanks!
The Mahora Sentai Baka Rangers have arrived!
Always having fun! Baka Red!
Preference for negatives! Baka Black!
Even if I get a dog! Baka Blue!
On the side of the mold! It's... Baka Yellow!
Everyone gets along! Baka Pi-