The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
She's being bullied!
And the bullies look so cliché.
Turning right!
Okay, I've got some things I want to ask you.
To be precise, the human
experimentations you guys are taking part in.
That was me. It had to be.
I wonder where I was headed?
Found you...
my love.
I didn't ask for excuses.
Or would you rather become 'materials' yourself?
Just give up.
Maybe you really don't need to have a head.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Kanra-san has entered the chat.
Good evening.
Good evening!
Tanaka Tarou-san has entered the chat.
Good evening.
Is it just me, or do we always tend to lose belongings that are particularly valuable?
Good evening!
Like a brand new umbrella.
In comparison, I've had this cheap, vinyl umbrella for so many years...
Losing an umbrella isn't a huge deal, but it's a shame when you lose a winning lottery ticket.
You take the effort to put it somewhere safe, then you forget about it.
And while you're looking for it, you always find things that you don't even care about.
And it always feels like the one thing you can't find is something really valuable.
Setton-san has entered the chat.
Evening!
Are you two looking for something?
Setton-san has entered the chat.
I sometimes wonder...
whether my head is awake while I'm asleep.
Ever since my memories started feeling vague,
I feel like the flow of time has started to feel vague as well.
I wonder when...
I stopped having dreams where I was one with my head.
There, and here.
I wonder what my head is capable of seeing right now?
What is she seeing?
I try to find the answer to that question in this dream that is repeated over and over again.
But...
the dream is always the same...
Life is Transient
Selty, I realized something amazing!
You told me last night that you didn't have any work today, right?!
I just calculated it and found out that today is your first break in 265 days!
You're looking a little gloomy.
As always, he reads the expression on a face I don't have.
I heard that people dream in order to organize their memories.
Is that true?
What's this all of a sudden?
You want to know why people dream?
To answer that as simply as possible, I'd have to say, "We don't know."
There are a lot of things in the medical field that have yet to be made clear.
Especially things related to the brain.
Dreams mostly occur during REM,
or Rapid Eye Movement, sleep.
He's a doctor.
An underground doctor, to be precise.
But I'm not fully aware what exactly he does for a living.
He lets me live here,
and it's also thanks to him that I'm able to continue working as a deliverer.
Well, there's also a question about what exactly 'memories' are.
You listening?
I'm thankful for him.
And recently, I've started to realize that this feeling I get when we're alone together is 'love.'
But...
I have a feeling you believe that your
memories are contained in your head,
but you can't be certain about that.
Of course they are.
But more importantly, hurry up and get dressed!
We're going out today! Just the two of us!
I'm taking the day off as well.
See? I'm turning off my phone, too!
Oh.
I should also pull out the telephone wire.
I won't be checking for mail!
We'll have so much fun without a care in the world!
So, where should we go?
Should we head down to the beach with your beloved horse?
Or would you rather hit up a hot spring instead?
I don't want to go anywhere.
Why is that?
Since I have the day off, I'm going to cook you a meal to repay you for everything you've done for me.
Your own cooking?!
What would you like to eat? I'll look up the recipe.
I'm touched, Selty!
I wonder what I should ask for.
I'll be borrowing this. Sorry for the trouble.
You saved me.
I overslept this morning.
Don't worry about it, kiddo.
It's about time you started feeling tired after moving to Tokyo.
But really, you should take advantage of situations like this.
You're supposed to ask a pretty girl who sits next to you if you can share her textbook,
all the while leaning up against her shoulder!
Guess you forgot your tie, too?
You all right?
Didn't forget your wallet, did you?
No way...
Huh?
Where did I...
It's delicious!
Russia Sushi!
Simon!
Would you happen to have seen Yumacchi around?
Oh, Karisawa!
Want to eat sushi?
I haven't seen him.
No luck, huh...
The shopkeeper has a stomachache today.
"Axel World" published by Dengeki Bunko came out today.
But he's okay now.
I went out and bought it with him, then went for tea afterwards...
He's already had his medicine.
But he couldn't go to stock up today.
And then a maid from the cafe came to deliver this phone to me,
So we're out of fish today.
but this is Yumacchi's...
I'm looking for some right now.
Huh? Then why are you trying to get customers?
Hello! Excuse me!
What are you looking for?
I told you, I'm looking for Yumacchi-
Wait, who are you?
Looking for something?
"Looking for something?"
Write down what you're looking for.
Looking for something?
Tell me!
Wow, have you been doing this around here for a while?
I'm asking everyone!
My phone!
Welcome home, master!
I wonder what I'm looking for...
The fact that Kaztano was safe is enough for me.
I made a promise with Karisawa and Yumasaki that
none of us would try to dig deeper into the matter...
"Yagiri Pharmacy"...
There are rumors that the pharmacy is
actually connected to the Awakusu group,
and also 'Nebula,' a corporation in North America.
Well, standing out here won't help me discover anything new.
Have you seen Karisawa-san?
No.
Oh...
Would anyone like to join us at Russia Sushi?
Selty!
Let's use an ordinary knife like everyone else, okay?
This is really good!
Amazing!
So good!
Hang on. Why are you crying?
Huh? I'm crying?
I must have been deeply moved.
I'm telling you, this is amazing.
These incredibly sweet kinpira...
The bitter and salty miso soup...
Something's wrong.
No, your cooking is very particular.
Just like you!
That's not a compliment!
I get it. I must have messed up the seasoning again.
That's enough!
You don't have to force yourself to eat any more!
I'm not forcing myself to do anything.
This is so good!
Stop eating!
What are you doing?!
How does this work?
You definitely have a knack for cooking.
Come on, it's just that you don't have a refined palate.
What? "A refined palate"?
I'm talking about your sense of taste.
Tastes that aren't engraved in your DNA can't be recognized by your brain.
Your body doesn't need to eat.
Your brain doesn't seem to have anything to do with it.
Come on, don't feel so down.
What do you say we play some video games?
Quit treating me like a kid.
I really hate that.
That wasn't my intention.
You've taught me a lot of things,
but there are only vague remnants of my memories from one hundred years ago.
There should be more in my head.
Do you really need those memories?
What do you mean by that?
I keep telling you.
You're fine the way you are.
You don't understand!
I'm close to forgetting my own face!
Wait!
That was terrible of me!
Selty!
You're back!
I need you to be more responsible, Doctor.
It's an emergency, and I can't even get in touch with you.
Something wrong, Sonohara-san?
They're missing.
"Missing"?!
What?!
What's missing this time, Mikado?!
Sonohara-san's shoes...
Again?
How sly of them.
I have a pretty good idea of who would do something like this.
Kida-kun?
Okay.
Whoa, hey-
Kida-kun?!
Kida-kun looked a little scary. I've never seen him like that before.
Really?
He just ran off.
How troublesome.
When I was little, I'd always lose things.
I'd go around saying "It's gone, it's gone," while being on the verge of tears.
My mom would always help me look for them.
Sounds like a kind mom.
Yeah.
Both of my parents are kind.
I'm fine now.
I'll go home in these slippers.
Thanks for helping me look, Ryugamine-kun.
Quit trying to look for the culprit, Kida-kun.
No.
Sonohara-san went home already.
Huh?
I don't know.
Me?
Obviously I'm still looking for them.
Anyway, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
There they are!
What am I doing?
Isn't it strange?
You don't remember, do you?
Vacant lots are so strange.
Once the buildings are gone, you don't remember what used to be there.
It was here until just a little while ago, right?
Considering the size of the lot, it must have been a pretty large building.
What am I doing?
I get angry every time Shinra tells me to give up looking for my head.
But I still work and get acquainted with people I can call 'friends.'
It's like I've turned human.
Wait, didn't you need something from me?
I remember now.
There used to be a tall, narrow, blue building here.
Oh, that shabby one.
There was an old woman running a cigar store on the first floor, right?
Can't put anything past a deliverer.
I feel the presence of my head somewhere in this city, but...
Hello! Good day!
Huh? Are you talking to me?
I'm looking for beautiful Japanese.
Please tell me what you're looking for from the bottom of your heart.
Okay...
Umm... could I see that for a second?
Okay!
Signs: Hanejima
Yuhei
Love...
Signs: A lost cat
Signs: A job!!
Signs: To Yumacchi
I'll be waiting for you on the
first floor of Tora no Ana.
I wonder if she was able to meet up with him...
Signs: My head
I looked for a lot of things today.
And...
some I found, some I didn't.
I couldn't find his briefcase, so I figured he was at work.
But...
I felt like something was off.
Yagiri Pharmacy Kantou Research Laboratory
Fireworks?
Yes, he caused quite a ruckus.
It took a few of our men to bring him down.
Just for fireworks...
The people who work for you must be quite violent.
Seriously, what a troublemaker.
He comes here, accuses us and says, "My girlfriend has been kidnapped."
"She only remembered this location. Tell me what you did to her."
I don't think that's an accusation, but rather the truth.
Doctor, could you make it so that he won't
remember anything about us when he awakens?
There's no way to mess with someone's memories so conveniently.
And besides, I'd still have memories of him in my mind.
We'll let him leave.
Well, there's no knowing whether he'll make it back to his own home.
Doctor, both the chief and I place great trust in you.
You've kept your secret about 'that thing' as well.
Oh, I've also heard that you live with quite an oddball.
At that moment, I had forgotten.
About my head, and the memories contained therein of existing as a Dullahan for a couple hundred years.
I wasn't thinking about any of those.
Just... Just...
Hey, will you go out to dinner with me?
They won't complain if I order enough for two people.
There's a good place I know of.
Please, Selty.
It's lonely to have a meal by myself.
What is this mysterious dish?!
Fried chicken sushi.
Cheese sushi.
Sichuan-style sushi.
Borscht sushi.
This one is sour cream sushi.
You didn't have to make it into sushi!
What are you saying?!
It's a special set!
A grand service!
And fortune cookies for dessert?
Geez...
By the way, there's a written oracle in here.
In other words, fortune-telling.
Here, I'll break yours for you.
This one's yours.
Sign: You shalt find what you've lost
Let me see what you got.
Oh, this means you'll find what you're looking for.
You shouldn't take it too seriously...
Sign: Your love shalt not come true
I'm happy, Shinra!
What did you get?
I guess they forgot to put it in.
I'm physically unable to cry.
I wonder if my head cries while I'm shrouded in sadness.
Connection
Thank you.
I wouldn't mind if that weren't the case.
I hope it's smiling.
What's wrong?
You look frightened again.
There's no one here but the two of us.
Do you feel as if you're about to remember something?
Yeah.
You don't have to remember anything.
Didn't I tell you?
I don't need your past or your future.
Just your present self.
I want what we have now to last forever.
I love you, Selty.
That night, for the first time in a while, I had a dream where I was one with my head.
I'm here.
Right here.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Madly in Love
My love is different.
It's different from a love where you're only seeking, and where you're only fawning over the other person.
It is more absolute and perfect.
Next time: Madly in Love.
The one Seiji really needs is me.