Mitsuki has an unexpected
visitor from America.
It's Ms. Kazumi, who took care of Mitsuki
before she started living here.
Upon talking with Mitsuki,
Ms. Kazumi promises to find
Eichi's whereabouts in America!
Isn't that great?
Now one of her dreams may come true!
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
A live show at this university's
school festival, eh?
Sounds like fun!
Yeah, really!
Besides, I can't believe that
these beautiful buildings are a school!
It's so different from elementary schools.
Oh, they even have a planetarium.
How wonderful!
Yeah.
A planetarium...
Thinking about Eichi again?
Huh? Y-Yeah
In any case, planetariums are so nice.
I want to go there with Takuto.
Jeez, I can't take this anymore!
Wow.
There are little shops too.
It's a pretty serious deal!
No! I said I am going!
Hey, listen!
We are not here to play around!
Just for a little bit!
I'll give you some apricot candy
if I win some!
I prefer plums!
Anyway, that's not the point!
Come on, let's go!
What's happening?
Are they having another dispute?
Yes. Seems like Meroko
wants to go to the booths.
Meroko, let's all go together
when we have more time later! Okay?
Okay.
You have...
...a favor to ask?
Yes. For the live show in the evening,
you perform after Scanty.
But before the show,
we have an event in which
we would like Full Moon to make
a guest appearance as a princess.
I'm sorry, but it's too sudden.
We heard that it would be a live show,
and we've planned accordingly for that.
But could you...
Please...
But...
A role of a princess? Sounds like fun!
Ms. Oshige, I want to do it!
What?
Well... If you really want to do it,
Mitsuki, I won't say no.
So that's okay?!
Thank you so much!
All right!
Hold on one second!
I didn't say okay yet!
Well, I guess that's that,
so shall we go somewhere till it's time?
Wow, I thought we were going out
when you said we'd go somewhere.
But universities have everything.
Yes. It's very different
from your school, isn't it?
Yes.
Oh, looks like in universities,
classes are called lectures!
And they are 90 minutes long!
On top of that, there are so many
courses that I have never heard of!
Let's see...
Quantum Mechanics, Psychoacoustics,
Ergonomics, and Cultural Anthropology?
They sound so difficult,
it's making me dizzy.
But I know that one.
Huh? Astronomy?
Oh, that's right!
Eichi was studying astronomy, right?
Yes!
Not Eichi again!
Oh? You got jealous just now,
didn't you?
What?! No I didn't!
See! You're getting defensive!
I was right, wasn't I?
No!
How dare you,
when you have someone like me.
How vexing!
Takuto, you are a cheater!
Huh?!
Fine, if that's the case...
I am going to enter this!
I'm going to be in it, and make you realize
how attractive Miss Meroko really is!
You've gotta be kidding.
I'm going to win!
And then, and then...
Meroko, I didn't realize
how attractive you were.
I... I...
That's okay, Takuto.
Now you understand.
- Meroko...
- Takuto...
All right!
Just you wait, Takuto!
Oh! Meroko!
Where are you going?!
Jeez...
Man, what an idiot.
Just let her be.
- Nice pose!
Don't you want to...
...give us your autograph...
- ...on our biceps?
Run, Mitsuki!
Huh?
Just hurry!
- Don't be so shy!
Stop right there!
I spent two years as a popstar and have
ten years of experience as a manager.
I, Masami Oshige, who has lived through
this shrewd world of showbiz, won't let—
you pass!
Takuto, I can't run anymore!
Keep going towards that elevator!
Mitsuki!
- Give us your autograph!
- Full Moon!
Ouch!
Stop following Full Moon!
- O-Out of the blue...
- Who the heck are you?!
I'm Full Moon's bodyguard!
What? They can see Takuto?
A bodyguard, huh?
Do you wanna fight against us?
Takuto...
What should we do?
- I-It was unopened!
What fight are you talking about?
We can handle empty cans.
But an unopened one...
- It's such a waste!
Uh... Well...
You're running away for the wrong reason.
What?
Takuto, you can transform into a human!
That's amazing!
Oh, this?
If I concentrate, I can.
But I spend so much energy to do it
that I can't use any of my other powers.
But Takuto, you were like
a real bodyguard back there.
You were so cool!
Wha—;?!
Thanks!
S-Sure.
Takuto, why don't we
go play for just a bit?
No! What if there are more weirdos?!
It'll be fine since you'll be with me.
Right?
Wha—;?!
Come on, let's just go for a while!
Hey!
Hey, hey...
Doesn't this feel like a date?
Sexy!
Look this way!
Oh, how stupid.
Come on, didn't you wanna
go to the planetarium?
Huh? Oh! Wait up, Takuto!
- Wow...
There are so many!
It's beautiful!
Yeah! There are too many stars,
I can't tell which ones
are which constellation.
Yeah! Eichi taught me so many of them
a long time ago, but I forgot them.
The sky I gazed at with Eichi
was so pretty.
B-But I know that one!
There!
Oh! The Big Dipper!
Yeah.
The Big Dipper is shaped
like a dipper, right?
And, if that...
If that had water in it,
I'm worried it would spill out.
Don't worry,
there's no water in it!
Oh! I see!
There are stars in it then!
And we see shooting stars when
it's filled so much it overflows?
You may be right.
Now that I think about it,
I was saying strange things,
but Eichi never made fun of me,
and he always listened to me.
He was really so kind.
Eichi...
Hey, why are you walking away
before it's over?
Are you upset about something?
Not really.
I just thought it's about time we go back.
Really?
Yeah.
You're lying!
You always get mad when I mention Eichi!
Well, if you think so,
then why did you talk about Eichi?
That's...
I don't know what to do
when you talk about those things!
Besides, I am not
a substitute for Eichi!
MISS FULL MOON'S
GREEN ROOM
Oh no.
If I can't protect a talent,
I've failed at being a manager, haven't I?
Oh, sorry.
Only authorized people
can come in here.
What are you talking about, it's me.
Huh? No... Well...
Takuto! Wait!
What? Y-You're Takuto?
Y-Yeah!
Oh? Umm... But...
Nice to meet you, I'm Oshige.
Oh, nice to meet you too, I'm Takuto.
Full Moon!
Please be ready soon!
Yes!
Everyone!
Thank you for waiting!
It's time for our Nandai festival's famous
"Love Love Attack"!
And here is today's princess...
Full Moon!
Hi everyone, I'm Full Moon.
Thank you for having me today!
Well, so, let's get started then!
Here are the candidates who will
compete to be Full Moon's knight.
Looks like it's a pretty big deal.
Yeah...
I wonder if Mitsuki will be all right?
Those guys!
Why are they here?!
The lucky male students on stage
will participate in many different games
to contend for the princess!
The winner that remains
at the end of the game
will receive a kiss from Full Moon!
What?
- All right!
A kiss? I...
So we meet again!
Let's have fun!
S-Sure.
Hey, you!
You never mentioned
anything about a kiss!
Well, the presenter chooses
the prize on a whim.
It wasn't planned for.
What should we do, Takuto?
They might do something
weird to Mitsuki!
Takuto, please! Do something about this!
We can't stop the event now!
Please protect Mitsuki!
I am not a substitute for Eichi!
Hold it there!
I'm participating too!
- What?!
Oh?!
A new contestant has jumped in!
This is unheard of!
Will the committee okay it?
Takuto!
Okay!
This is getting fun!
Let's get it started then!
You're the bodyguard we saw!
You were talking so big,
but you're after the kiss prize too!
Shut up! I'll never let
omeone like you win this!
The first battle is
"Super Spicy Attack"!
The first 10 people that finish
this super spicy hot pot
will be able to go on
to the next battle!
Now, get set.
Crap, I can't eat hot things.
Damn!
Good luck, Takuto.
Takuto...
Time is up!
H-Hot...
I hate spicy things!
This year's Campus Queen is...
Entry number three...
Miss Meroko!
- Meroko!
And now, a trophy will be given
to the winner, Miss Meroko!
Yay! Thank you!
Oh, that must be the event
they were talking about.
Huh?
Is that...Takuto?!
Why is he participating?
And he's even in his human form!
- Congratulations...
- That Takuto!
Umm... Hey!
Where are you going?!
It's an emergency!
I'll be back to pick it up!
See ya!
Time's up!
We now have the contestants
that will go on to the final round!
All right!
Way to go Takuto!
The final battle is
"Hold Your Breath in a Basin Attack"!
Whoever keeps his head in the basin
the longest is the winner!
I won't let you win!
Shut up!
Okay, get set.
All right, everyone has started now.
Who will be the one to get a kiss
from the beautiful princess?!
I can't lose!
A kiss if I win!
A silent battle of men.
And watching over them,
we have Princess Full Moon!
Who could her gaze be on?!
Takuto...
I made him so upset then.
I'm sorry Takuto.
Takuto...
It's starting to get tough!
Oh? Looks like we have contestants
dropping out one after the other!
Go Takuto!
You won't die even if you don't
breathe for two or three hours!
- Go!
- P-Please calm down!
Now we have
two contestants left.
Who will be the winner
of the victorious crown?!
A kiss if I win!
Just win!
Now we are in
the most crucial moment!
Judgment will finally be
passed on the two of them!
I should have trained my lungs too.
We have a knight!
The winner is this one that
jumped into the game, Takuto!
Huh? Me?
Yay! Awesome, Takuto!
Now, Full Moon will
kiss the knight!
Huh? Um...
Hey, you two!
How hot and heavy!
Ms. Oshige...
W-Well, I guess we
just have to do it.
Just do it on my forehead
and get it over with.
O-Okay.
Just hold it there!
How dare you,
when you have a girl like me!
You cheater!
Oh my!
We have an unexpected
development here!
Looks like this year's knight and
this year's Campus Queen were lovers!
No!
Yes! Takuto and I are so in love!
What?!
If you want a kiss,
I'll give you one!
Cut it out, you dummy!
You are so shy,
don't run away like that!
Help me!
Takuto!
Who is that girl?
Well, things turned out crazy,
but thank you so much for today, Full Moon.
Good luck in your live show too!
Yes!
Takuto... Thank you.
Hey, that mean girl is back.
What?!
You mean, Madoka Wakamatsu?!
Yeah. But she's still arrogant as usual.
I thought she would've
been a little disheartened
by losing to Mistuki in
the recording competition,
but I can't believe
she hasn't changed!
Wait a second.
She's fighting with her manager.
Something seems funny!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Real Madoka Wakamatsu."
- Look forward to it!