Judy.
Just leave him be, Cal.
He probably ran out of booze again.
I'm going.
I'll come home in the morning like usual.
Be careful.
This way!
Phantom!
Inferno's...
Phantom.
Only during the past year, at least twenty men of high importance have become victims of this inexplicable purge.
These are being called "Phantom Assassinations" and are sending fear through the country.
She overdid it as always, huh?
That Missy.
It's not a laughing matter, brother.
It could be our turn in tomorrow's news.
The Gambino Family's number two, Delacruz, has passed away.
And the Gambinos are gutted now?
We've taken it...
The east coast.
This is one of Phantom's accomplishment.
The previous Phantom was astonishing,
but that boy has gone beyond expectation, hasn't he, Claudia?
Giving us such astounding results...
...makes it a little frightening.
You did well in binding him to us so closely.
I didn't bind him to us.
His decision to come to Inferno was of his own will.
Is that so?
I always thought he was working hard for the sake of your boobs.
In any case, Mr. McGwire.
The investigation into the case of the Godou clan has concluded.
The new Japanese organization that planned on joining us?
They developed their own domestic market in Japan,
raising their profit significantly.
However, the supposed source of their goods,
a dealer in Southeast Asia, received a devastating blow.
Currently, the Godou clan has no goods in stock.
If we establish business relations with the Godou clan now,
we can monopolize the sale of goods in Japan.
I have set up a five million dollar deal with the young leader of the Godou clan, Mr. Daisuke Godou, for the end of the week.
A token of friendship to begin with.
Hold on a second!
You're even in charge of negotiations, what's the meaning of this?
Are you passing us over?
Stop it.
But...
If the negotiations proceed smoothly,
there is no reason why we should find someone to replace her.
Well then, I shall continue with my work.
Good work.
Hey, aren't you pushing it too hard lately?
You think so?
I know you have something in mind,
but if you put too much effort into one organization, you'll only burden yourself with unnecessary trouble.
Don't worry, I'm doing fine.
You're early.
I have returned,
Miss McCunnen.
Zwei,
I heard from Lizzie about the events in New York.
It was a success I see.
I'm grateful for your compliment.
I'll get the car ready now.
Who's driving?
I'll leave that part to you.
You look fetching there, Phantom.
How is New York?
Nothing but cold weather.
Isaac said you only remain as Phantom for my body.
That sounds like him, alright.
Is he right? Both of you are men.
Who knows.
I've forgotten about the reason.
I guess you have.
It doesn't matter any more.
You are here of your own will.
Like hell I am.
I have no will.
I have nothing now.
But sooner or later, you will feel nothing.
The past and the future...
We don't have either.
It's just as you said,
Elen.
Your handling is stiff.
That's because we have 25 kilograms of cocaine as our passenger.
Just the two of us?
This is a deal to build some trust on both sides, so...
If we brought too many people, they'd be laughing at us.
I see.
So, who are we dealing with?
People from your home country.
Those Yakuzas?
Are we really doing it in this place?
This here has been the Bloodies' territory for a long time.
Isaac Wisemel.
That's right.
There aren't any idiots nowadays who would cause a fuss here and make themselves the Bloodies' enemy.
That's why...
This is the safest place for Inferno.
Is that them?
No one's coming.
Something's weird.
Zwei?
Stay in the car.
A solo assailant.
The weapons used were a pistol with silencer and...
...a large knife.
He took down his enemies in the dark one by one while they were confused.
He's skilled.
I told you to stay in the car.
What's the meaning of this?
It means the trade tonight has fallen through.
Who did this?
I don't know.
It's no use trying to figure it out here.
Go back by yourself.
I'll return later.
What will you do?
I'll take care of the bodies.
You've gotten us into a hell of a mess, eh?
Answer me!
The police patrols got there before us,
and the dealers and the girls are too afraid to do their jobs.
You messed up my territory!
Didn't you, Claudia?!
Are you trying to run from your responsibility?
Mr. Wisemel.
What did you say?
You have a responsibility to keep your territory safe.
My customer was robbed of five million dollars in your back yard...
...and four men were killed.
I would like you to consider carefully who should fall on his sword here.
You bitch! Since when do you talk to me like that?
This is unsightly.
Claudia,
what's the response from the Godou clan?
They were furious. But as you have heard, it's under control.
Alright, I'll leave it to you to attend to them.
Lift their spirits as best you can.
We need to return our customer's money as soon as possible.
Along with the corpses of those who took it.
It's your job to do so,
Isaac.
Wait a minute!
Those Asians were our customers!?
I didn't agree to that.
It's a matter of dignity.
A group that asked for help from Inferno has been attacked.
We'll treat them the same no matter whether they are a customer or a beggar.
Are you saying we should overlook such violence on our doorstep?
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
Is the situation inside the same as always?
I've investigated the corpse.
Her name was Judy Devens, 26 years old.
It seems she's been living in that area for a long time now.
No suspicious connections whatsoever.
She was independent and didn't rely on a pimp.
What about her room?
I've searched it.
Not even a bat or a knife there.
She had a room mate, but we haven't gotten hold of her.
Got any idea?
I'll leave this place to you, Lizzie.
What?
Jeez, you're a man with a lot of requests, huh?
Fine, go ahead.
The police and mass media have left the scene.
Is this where Judy Devens died?
Who are you?
What about yourself? Judy's acquaintance?
Were you Judy's friend too?
I'm her sister.
What?
Is it weird to have a sister with different skin and hair?
No.
Who killed Judy?
Do I look like I know?
Do you know who might have done it?
Are you saying Judy had a reason to be killed?
I asked a stupid question, didn't I?
Wait!
What are you going to do after you find the guy who killed her?
I'd make him feel the same fate as her.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Then...
Then take me with you!
I can be of use.
No way.
I know who killed Judy.
I saw it all.
When Judy was shot here last night...
I was with her.
I was picking Judy up because she was drunk and we were on our way home.
But Judy...
...protected me.
Hey, will you take me?
What's your name?
I'm Cal.
Cal Devens.
What's yours?
I'm...
Azuma Reiji.
So you're Japanese?
Okay, Reiji.
We'll be partners from now on.
Partners?
Yeah.
We will avenge Judy with one mind and body.
I'm sure I can be of use to you.
Very well.
We'll be partners from now on.
Though it will probably only be for a bit.
It was a small hand.
And I...
...keep on sinning.
I, whose life has been tainted,
inside that whirlpool,
taint the lives of others.
What should I do?
Where should I go?
I don't know anything.