Production for Full Moon's next single
has finally been put into motion!
She has decided to sing
a song her father wrote.
The only thing left to do was
to ask Mr. Takasu to produce it!
Unfortunately, Madoka Wakamatsu has
already tapped him
to produce the same song!
So who're we gonna ask to be
the producer for Full Moon?!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Dr. Nakamura of Internal Medicine.
Please come to the pharmacy.
– Hey...
– O-Okay.
Why? Aren't you gonna knock?
Huh? What's the matter, Mitsuki?
What are you doing here?
Umm... I was in the neighborhood so...
Well... See you!
Huh?
I see. It was difficult to
raise the subject, huh?
In that case,
I'll speak with him directly.
Mitsuki, you stay there.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Gimme a break.
I'm the one who wants to sigh.
Why couldn't you just
come out with it?
I mean... How can I put it?
It felt like trying to involve
Dr. Wakaoji in some childish stuff
and I just couldn't go forward with it.
It isn't childish!
You're so concerned about others.
That's not very childlike, you know?
Y-You really think so?
You don't think I'm...childlike?
And that Takuto,
I invited him to come along,
but he said "I'll refrain!"
What the heck is he thinking?!
Takuto's "I'll refrain" is...
That's not a lie.
What do you mean?
He thinks that Dr. Wakaoji doesn't
think too highly of him.
What's that about?
I'd like Dr. Wakaoji and Takuto to
get along,
but maybe that won't work after all.
Them being a doctor and
a Death Spirit and all.
So what I'm saying is that if you,
Doctor, as a former member of Route L,
would agree to be the producer,
not only would it be a news hook but
we would also be able to target
the housewife demographic
that used to be Route L fans.
Something like this.
Wow, it feels like a power game
between two adults.
Yeah, yeah.
I will have to decline.
Huh?
C-Could you tell me
the reason why?
To tell you the truth...
If you don't agree to do it, Doctor,
this plan will just blow over.
Please, just agree to do it
for Mitsuki's sake.
I have to decline.
Why?
Just because.
– I can't believe this! I mean...
– That's what I thought.
– You are the only person we can turn to!
– It won't do, will it?
– While we're doing this, the other side...
– I know we're asking a lot, but...
This is our concept for this project.
Th-That's pretty daring.
It's kind of mismatched.
That's what I was aiming for...
mismatching.
Huh?
In order to call attention to
Madoka Wakamatsu's primitive rawness,
I intentionally juxtaposed that against
the inorganic antithesis. Get it?
H-Huh?
All right then, I want each
of you to start working
from the base of this conceptual image.
Are there any questions?
Kohei Takasu... He certainly isn't
called a hit maker for nothing.
I'm certain that he will...
Madoka, turn this way!
Okay!
Make me into a superstar.
Oh my gosh!
– Huh?
I'm sorry. I messed up on
that strategy a little.
We need to turn over a new leaf.
But I wonder what strategy
we should go with.
Hmm...
Umm... Ms. Oshige... It might be
bothering the doctor too much.
Hey, come on,
don't say things like that!
It's your song, you know?!
Yes.
Mitsuki, why are you holding a pillow?
Huh? Huh?
Huh?!
What's that?!
PRODUCER'S CHAIR
Goodness gracious.
Meroko is asking you too.
Please return that to me.
If I return it, will you
agree to my request?
Hey!
Please!
Here! Here! Here! Here!
Here! Here!
Please! Please!
Please, please, please, please...
Please!
Please, please, please,
please, please...
Please!
You're in the way!
Gimme a break!
What is up with that doctor?!
Taking that attitude when he knows
she doesn't have much time left.
He said something before
like he wouldn't "allow it."
Right. In other words,
the length of her life.
It's not that I don't understand
what he says
from the point of view
of a doctor, but...
He's totally inflexible!
Huh?
Hey, hey, what have you been
doing all this time?
Yes... Well...
Umm...
FORGET IT
ASK FOR IT
Huh?!
What is she doing?
She's drawing fortunes.
It happened again.
What are you doing?!
It's the same, no matter
how many times you do that.
You won't be content,
no matter which way it goes, right?
First of all,
I don't think much of trying
to decide by drawing fortunes!
I guess you're right.
I think the doctor is aware of
the fact that
your feelings about this
are still wavering.
Makes sense!
That's why he didn't give his okay!
First of all, you have
to make up your mind.
I agree!
I couldn't...
give up music...
but Dr. Wakaoji was able to
give up music.
Something he loved so much.
To do that must have taken
a great deal of resolve.
Much more than it would take me.
You may be right.
But you're not about to say
you're gonna give up
singing "Eternal Snow"
because of that, are you?
No, I won't give that up.
I see...
If so, I guess it's okay.
What's our next class again?
The movment of constellations
and the moon.
Huh? They bought you a computer?
Yeah.
I'm so jealous.
My father's nice, so he agrees
to anything I ask him!
I wouldn't call that nice,
I'd call it being soft.
That's awful.
Dr. Wakaoji, this is Mitsuki's request.
Please be my producer!
If it's something you're requesting,
Mitsuki, I can't turn you down.
Yippee! I'm so happy!
I love you, Dr. Wakaoji!
But it's not a request
of that level, is it?
We want to go with "Eternal Snow,"
no matter what.
Why are you so insistent
about it?
Because you're telling me to
change the song, Department Manager!
But realistically, it's impossible to go
with "Eternal Snow," right?
'Cause no producer will
agree to handle it.
There's someone
I'm negotiating with right now!
Well, I sure hope Seed Records
will agree to that person.
I believe that they will agree.
I don't want to say this,
but if things continue this way
you might be transferred to
a different department.
Are you saying that
they'll switch managers?
To be totally honest, that's exactly it.
That's...
This is Cassiopeia at 7:00.
Two hours later, at 9:00.
The shape is the same,
but the position is like this.
I see. Thank you.
Please return to your seat.
What's the matter?
You don't seem to have any pep.
Oh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
I can't consult Tomoe
about something like this.
As Tomoe explained,
the shape of constellations
do not change even if the time changes.
But the position changes
as the time changes.
All right. Next, let's look
at the relationship
between the moon and the earth.
As you all know, the moon does
not emit light.
Huh?
So what makes it appear bright is...
Do you know why, Hasegawa?
See, Mitsuki, the moon
doesn't shine on its own.
Then why does it shine?
That's because...
With the sun at the center...
It's because the earth and
the moon are revolving around it...
Because it reflects the sun's light
just like a mirror
which makes it look
like it's shining.
So if there weren't a sun,
the moon wouldn't shine?
That's right.
In that case...
In that case?
You're my sun, aren't you, Eichi?
Not just me.
The people at the facility,
the teachers at school and your friends.
And also your late father
and mother, Mitsuki.
I think they're all
making you shine, Mitsuki.
Yeah.
So you should just be true
to yourself, Mitsuki,
because we'll all make you shine.
Eichi, I'll...
I'll ask him, after all!
M-Mitsuki?
Can I ask something too?
I sure would like you
to take your seat.
Huh?
Mitsuki, you are blushing.
And, what is it?
Please, Dr. Wakaoji!
Please agree to be
the producer!
That again?
Even if you ask me, Mitsuki,
there are things I can
and cannot do.
I understand that.
But, I want to ask you to do it,
Dr. Wakaoji, by any means.
I want to ask you, Dr. Wakaoji,
to produce "Eternal Snow."
That's impossible, Mitsuki.
I'm happy that you feel
that way but...
I see.
Maybe he still has lingering regrets.
Huh? What did you just say?
I said, maybe he still
has lingering regrets.
W-What do you mean?
Mitsuki, who are you talking to?
Don't tell me it's those two?!
It looks like she isn't able
to say this to you,
so I'll say it to you directly.
Don't you still have lingering regrets
about music?
Not at all.
I'm envious.
What do you mean?
In my work as a Death Spirit,
I've seen a lot of different people.
Despite it all, when it
comes time for them to die
they all say "I wish I had done this,"
"I wish I had done that."
S-Stop it, Takuto!
It may be strange coming from me,
you can only do things
you like while you're alive.
And therefore, you
should live to the fullest!
I don't want a Death Spirit to
tell me something like that.
That may be true.
And moreover, the words of
a stuffed animal like me don't carry
the least bit of weight
to convince you.
But, as I said earlier,
you can only do things
you like while you're alive.
And this girl here is working hard
to do exactly that.
Putting her short life on the line,
and with that petite body.
There may be difficult
and sad times,
but it's nothing compared to
singing the songs that she loves!
I'm...I'm sorry, Dr. Wakaoji.
I'm sorry to have troubled you.
Goodbye!
You darn brat!
At that time,
when it was completely decided
that Route L would break up
I cast aside music.
I decided to walk another
path in life
that was unrelated to music.
I chose the path of medicine.
I don't have any regrets
about that decision.
The work of a doctor has many rewards.
However...
My heart ached every time
I heard music.
As if it were touching an old wound.
Are those lingering regrets?
In that is the case, I...
Compared to me, Mitsuki is...
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes and
it sounds almost sad.
Only while one is alive, huh?
I can't believe you,
you idiot, Takuto!
Why did you say something
like that to Dr. Wakaoji?
Because I couldn't hold back
from saying that!
Hey, hey... Did something happen?
Darn him! That blockhead!
Hey! Am I gonna be
the only one left out?
She's late.
Yeah... I wonder what's the matter.
Mitsuki...
Ms. Oshige...
Sorry I'm late.
W-What's the matter?
You look pale.
Yeah, I drank too much last night.
A broken heart?
No, I was so angry.
About what?
The department manager...
That has nothing to do with you!
Okay, we're going to work!
Ms. Oshige, be careful!
All right, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hey! She's done!
Is your hangover better?
A little.
D-Dr. Wakaoji.
Huh?
Oh...
The matter we discussed other day...
I have given it
careful thought.
Doctor, I'm so sorry.
– I won't bother you again like that.
– On certain conditions...
I will agree to be Mitsuki's producer.
– Huh?!
– What?!
U-Under conditions?
If you're talking about your fee...
I don't care about the money.
Because I'll be able
to play music again.
Th-Then what are your conditions?
Are they something we can do?
My conditions are...
Mitsuki...
Y-Yes?
First, that you'll undergo
regular checkups for your throat.
And second,
when push comes to shove,
you will follow my instructions,
including undergoing surgery, okay?
S-Surgery?
That's...
Of course, I will do the surgery
when the time comes.
Although, I'm not full-time now,
only part-time.
Huh?
Are you serious, Dr. Wakaoji?
I had already decided on you
for the next hospital director.
I need some time.
I apologize for my selfishness,
but I ask for your understanding.
Doctor...
It's also for myself.
I haven't been able to
forget music, after all.
I actually wanted to be cool
and hand in my resignation,
but there's one thing besides
music that I still have to do.
And that is to mend
your throat, Mitsuki.
Doctor...
I would love to hear you sing
"Eternal Snow" too, Mitsuki.
I would like your father and mother
to listen to it up in heaven.
I believe in you, Dr. Wakaoji!
You, if anybody, will make me
shine more than ever!
That's my intention too.
I want you to shine more and more
so that Eichi will take notice, okay?
Okay!
And also, this...
It was on the floor of
the hospital room.
I asked everyone
but nobody knew who it belonged to.
So I thought it might be yours, Mitsuki.
Thank you, Dr. Wakaoji.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working
with you too, Mitsuki.
Rather... Full Moon!
Yes!
Why the long face, Meroko?
It's fine that we asked Dr. Wakaoji
to produce her record,
but he won't let her rehearse
her song at all!
And he's asking her what she
wants to do in the song!
At this rate,
we can't record!
Don't worry.
I'm sure she'll find the answer.
Next time on Full Moon:
"My Message"
– Look forward to it!