I'm losing strength.
Goddesses inside an Anti-Crystal field will continue to lose their strength and energy.
Who are you?
My name is Arfoire.
I'll be the one to bring joyous tidings of chaos
to this world ruled by you four young ladies.
And I'm Pirachu.
The third-most popular mascot in mouse society.
Mouse...
Don't steal my spotlight!
Listen to yourself.
I was the one who dug up the Anti-Crystals from the Lastation caves and the Leanbox seafloor.
And it was my discovery of the first crystal in a Planeptune forest that set everything in motion.
Not to mention, did I not carry out the unenviable task of stealing one from Lowee's Basilicom?
Lowee's Basilicom?
Blanc, did you know about that rock...
Yeah, I did.
I had it under tighter security than Fort Knox,
but after the kidnapping incident, it was nowhere to be found.
If you'd just told us about it...
How was I meant to know there were so many of 'em?
The caves?
Don't tell me...
What's wrong, Noire?!
Zoinks!
My transformation...
I believe I told you
that as long as you stayed in that field,
you'd continue to lose your strength and energy.
How could this be?
Sis...
Sis!
Nepgear?
Get back on, Nepgear.
But Sis...
Nepgear!
Right now, we have to get out of here!
That one's getting away.
It matters not.
She's a mere CPU Candidate who can't even transform yet.
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#04 The Sisters' Resolve (Turn)
What's this all about, IF?
I'm not exactly sure,
but they mentioned an "anti-crystal" or something.
That's probably what's sealing the goddesses' powers.
"Anti-Crystal"?
Could you look into it for us, Histoire?
Certainly, but it'll take me three days.
As soon as possible, please.
I'll see what I can do.
Anyway, Nepgear and the gang should return to Planeptune.
I believe it'd be better for Uni and the others to go back home too.
Good bye.
Well, you heard her—
Hang on!
Do you seriously expect us to just go home because she says so?
Give us a proper explanation!
Usually, Sis would knock baddies out in one blow!
Is Sis gonna die?
I-I'm sure she'll be fine.
Goddesses don't go down that easily—
But...
I heard something about "sealing their powers" earlier.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, Ge-Ge.
No.
That rock I picked up back when we went shopping...
Surely that had to be an Anti-Crystal.
Let's not do this.
Hindsight is 20/20.
Why?
If only I'd thought more carefully about why I felt dizzy back then...
If only I'd told Sis and the others about it...
You idiot!
My sister is really, really strong,
but because of you, she's...
You should've taken her place instead!
Aww, jeez.
I'm bored outta my skull!
I wanna play some games!
What is wrong with you?
We're captives, you know.
But I wish I could at least use Four Goddesses Online's chat system.
I'm supposed to be meeting my fellow guild members.
Not you too.
Well, it's good to see you're still the same as ever.
Okay!
Let's go out on a limb and make some demands!
Hey!
I know you're there!
Bar Whore!
Who're you calling a bar whore?!
Uh...
CFW Magic?
That's someone else entirely!
Okay then, Arfaemon!
Gimme something to kill some time with.
I'm gonna die of boredom otherwise!
Either way, your lives are headed toward their end.
Huh?
She didn't object to that one.
Can I just call her Arfaemon from now on?
I don't care!
Hey, you listenin' to me?!
Someone's sentencing you to death here, you know.
What? Come again?
Take a look beneath you.
Zoinks!
What the hell is this?
It's creepy.
Is this another effect of the Anti-Crystals?
Soon, you will begin to suffer, and eventually, you will die.
Enjoy what little time you have left.
Nepgear.
Come on!
I know.
Uni.
Let's make up.
I went too far.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I know.
I know!
It's not your fault,
Yeah.
And I know how you feel.
I thought there couldn't be anyone stronger than my sister.
That everything would be fine as long as she was around.
I'm the same.
I can't do anything without my sister either.
Even now, I have no idea what to do—
It's simple!
We just need to rescue them!
I want to save them too.
But we can't transform...
Then we just need to change that!
Let's learn how to do it.
Can we?
Sis said something about how
I can't transform because I'm
subconsciously limiting myself.
Limiting myself...
Like, the things we're scared about are holding us back.
I'm scared of monsters.
Yup, me too.
Then let's train until we're not scared of them anymore!
Sounds good!
Yeah.
Uni?
Rom! Ram!
Your ride's here—
Owwie.
This hurts quite a lot!
You okay, Compa?
I'm perfectly fine!
This is training!
Huh?
This is Vert's game, isn't it?
We figured we'd get some combat training done.
Remember how she said there was a combat simulation mode?
I took on the role of the enemy.
If this can help Ge-Ge and the gang transform, I'll be super glad!
Transform?
We all decided to go save our sisters!
That's why we want to get stronger.
Hold on, Nepgear.
We're up against someone who already captured the goddesses!
Even so, I believe we have to do this.
We've inherited the goddesses' power, too.
I had a feeling this would happen.
But you're not a good foil, Compa.
I'll do it.
Iffy.
Relax. It's fine.
Let's do this.
Ga-thunk!
Found you!
Huh?
Hey!
Aren't you done uploading the pictures yet?
Never in my wildest dreams did I imagine I'd have to use an analog connection.
Not to mention, the modem we found in the trash was a 56k one.
I'm about to cry here.
You were fully aware there was no cellphone reception in this area!
Mistakes made in the field are an employer's responsibility.
Anyway, get on with it.
Tell the modem to get on with it.
Oh?
I see it's just the Candidates here.
None of the CPUs are around, huh?
I knew it! Something went down, didn't it?
Uh...
If I'm not mistaken, you're Abnes, right?
Hey, we're busy!
Do not disturb!
Who's she?
The little girl lover who they say got Neppy mad back at Lowee.
Abnes...
We don't really have time right now—
Shaddup!
Ex-little girls who've grown all half-assed are trash!
Now that the goddesses aren't around,
this is my chance to let Rom and Ram go back to being normal little girls.
Nice idea, even if I do say so myself.
Or should I say, "a flash of inspiration"?
Come now, little girls.
Let us hold hands and play!
Um, we don't wanna hold hands.
We wanna play that instead.
That?
Please!
Well, if you insist.
S-Say, little girl.
Are you really okay with this?
Why don't we play something a little more girly?
Charge, girls!
Take that!
Hold on a second!
Iffy, apparently you can fight AI characters too.
Wait!
All right, let's do this!
I knew it.
I'm sorry!
Nearly every game has that mode.
Wanna tell them about it?
I'm sorry!
Why don't we...
save it for later?
They look like they're having fun.
Never give up...
on little girls!
This is the end!
Wow!
They gave that Ancient Dragon a good beating!
Ow!
That hurts, you quack nurse!
I'm sorry.
We killed quite a lot of monsters,
but it's not helping us transform.
Yep.
But if we kill a lot more...
Looks like we don't have time for that anymore.
News of the four goddesses' capture will soon spread like wildfire.
The goddesses got captured?!
That leaves the little girls wide open—
You need some rest!
If the public saw these pictures,
it might lead to a Share crash.
And if that happens...
...we'll receive less power from the Share Crystals.
That means we need to save our sisters before this gets in the way!
Yep.
It's accumulated quite a lot.
What'll happen to us when we get swallowed by that?
I should've looked into some counter-measures.
But I only thought about keeping it as far from me as possible.
Chin up, gals!
We're fine right now,
and there's still hope for us!
I don't usually mind your optimism,
but it gets really annoying at times like these.
You're trying to escape from reality.
I'm just saying, it's better than thinking we're doomed.
False hope never did anyone any good.
I don't think it's false hope at all.
Huh?
You what?
Have you forgotten about your sisters?
Uni?
She's never even fought without me by her side.
Rom and Ram are still at an age where I have to keep them safe, too.
Nepgear seems level-headed, but she's quite spoiled.
I think it'd be too much for her.
Isn't that just your ego at play?
Sure, they're extremely lovely girls.
I'd love for them to forever stay the way they are too.
But those thoughts might be
what's letting them stay as "precious little sisters who can't transform".
Do you not feel that way?
They're here.
As expected, the CPU Candidate came back with friends.
Hmph.
What can they do?
They probably can't even reach this place.
Don't you agree?
They still can't transform, yet...
It doesn't matter if the goddesses fail.
People will come to terms with it if their sisters give it their all.
That'll reduce the damage done to the Shares.
You're right, but...
Also,
I want to believe in them too.
I want to believe they can do it.
Iffy...
Ready, girls?
You'd best prepare yourselves!
I'll keep you safe, Ram!
Okay!
And I'll take care of the rest!
Hit!
Pain, pain, fly away!
Outta my way!
Nepgear!
Ram!
Rom!
Rom! Ram!
Regroup!
Uni...
Behind you!
I refuse to lose!
Get away!
Stay away from me!
What have I done?
I was mistaken.
It was too early for us to go into battle!
Iffy, they're all gonna be killed!
Everyone will die because of me!
I know!
I can't do a thing!
Help me, Sis!
I'm relying on Sis again.
But I...
really do need Sis by my side!
Sis said something about how
I can't transform because I'm
subconsciously limiting myself.
Limiting...
Like, the things we're scared about are holding us back.
What I'm scared about is...
losing Sis.
No longer being Sis's kid sister.
No, that's not it.
I'm scared of becoming stronger than her!
Iffy!
Look at Ge-Ge!
I wanted to keep looking up to her forever,
but if this is what it takes to bring her back...
I'll become stronger than anyone else in the world!
I wish  /  I will be here where we met
Nepgear!
I would go fight  /  Until my life bears fruit
Nepgear.
Amazing!
I won't forget  /  I will start on an endless journey
I cannot retreat here.
My promise to you  /  Only one vow will accompany me
So...
I gotta do this!
The sad things, too, let us forge a closer bond
The goddesses taught me that
Everybody now, remember the sky we saw
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
I won't lose, I want to be happy
I won't give up, everyone
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
Let us find our future
Love & Peace
Everybody now, spread your wings
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
Let's set flight now, for we can be free
That's the dream we pursue, everyone
Happiness? Lucky? Your smile?
Let us find our future
Love & Peace
Looks like we don't have time for that anymore.
Huh?
No, wait, this doesn't count!
Let's have a do-over!
It's just, Compa sort of happened to say I could stay over,
The Goddesses' Resonance (Over Limit)
and I wouldn't have taken this except I woke up at midnight and—