It's kill...
or be killed!
You woke up?
Training
You don't have to be scared.
I'm not gonna attack you any more.
You are...
My name? I don't have one.
If that's a problem for you, call me Ein...
since that's what everyone calls me.
Ein...
Why did you attack me?
To verify your talent.
My talent?
You have natural talents.
The talent to kill... the talent to survive...
The talents of an assassin.
No way...
This makes no sense! To start with, what makes you think that?!
You tried to kill me.
In that situation...
an ordinary person would've panicked and been killed.
But you were different.
You survived by taking action before you grasped the situation.
Zwei...
Zwei?
That's your name.
No, it's not! Don t call me by that strange name!
I do have a name!
My...
name is...
You no longer have one.
You're wasting your time thinking about it.
What do you mean?!
Your memories were erased...
by Inferno.
Wonderful.
Your Phantom is the best, Scythe Master.
I feel honored, Mr. McGwire.
How it was executed... It's hard to believe that it was done by a kid.
That's right. That's exactly why we gave her the title of ''Phantom".
It's quite the feat...
creating a ghost that's not of this world.
Well, it's all thanks to Ms. McCunnen's backing.
You've got a good subordinate, Claudia.
By the way, about getting rid of that journalist,
I hear you had quite a bit of trouble.
Not really...
I heard that the execution was witnessed... by an ordinary traveler.
I don't know where you got that information,
but we've already gotten rid of the witness.
We took care of the body as well.
Oh? Wonderful. You used Phantom for that, too?
Yes.
You were supposed to be killed...
in order to eliminate all evidence.
But Master noticed your talent and thought it'd be a waste if you died.
Master?
Scythe Master... My boss.
Master decided to take your memories away and prepare you for another life.
One as a member of Inferno...
as an assassin...
Assassin? Me?!
We're having you become my double, Zwei.
Don't be ridiculous! Why would I do such a thing?! Killer?!
It's okay to refuse. But if you do...
as we originally planned, you'll die... right here, right now.
If you want to live, you have to be reborn.
You are now only allowed to exist for the purpose of killing people.
I...
don't want to die.
It's a dream... This is all a bad dream.
It's okay to think that way if it comforts you.
Just think that everything is a dream.
But... it'll be a long dream.
Change into those clothes.
From today on, you'll be with me all the time.
Follow all directions. Got that?
Let's start.
Zwei's progressing as planned.
He's faithfully carrying out his training without making a fuss. He's obedient.
If one trains that hard every day, even thinking would be a pain.
Yes. That's how you tame someone.
You won't be disappointed in the results, Ms. McCunnen.
You think I'm looking forward to it?
My pawn is your pawn.
Everything is an offering to Inferno.
You hold it like this. Don't put your finger on the trigger.
For your arms, focus not on your shoulders but on the fingers holding the gun.
This is the rear sight. This is the front sight.
You aim by looking at the front sight through the dip of the rear sight.
When you have a gun at the ready,
stabilize it by stretching your right arm and pulling your left arm.
Even then, the part you focus on the most is your hands, not your arms.
When you pull the trigger, don't rush. Pull it quietly as if you're squeezing it.
Now, shoot.
Shoot the remaining five bullets continuously.
At this distance, every shot must hit.
Once you can do that, we'll work on the speed.
Your goal is six shots within four seconds.
Focus on hitting the targets first.
You're still slow.
Looks like you can now hit them all,
but with that speed, you'll die before you finish shooting.
Do it again... Do it again...
I simply carry out the given assignments.
As long as I keep doing it...
I don't have to think about anything.
As long as I do it... I feel relief.
I even forget the many questions I have...
and the day... disappears...
I'm going out. Carry out the same training procedure.
Going out?
Work.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
So that man is Scythe Master.
This is your first sniping assignment in a while...
though it'll probably be a piece of cake for you.
Seven hundred yards to the target. I got a .308 caliber Remington for you.
The weather there is cloudy with a slight breeze.
According to the forecast, there won't be any change until tomorrow morning.
The details are inside that envelope.
Any questions?
No.
Good... By the way, how is Zwei doing?
The basic requirements have been completed.
He starts some new training tomorrow.
Maybe I should prepare a skills test for him soon.
Disregard me. Continue what you're doing.
Perhaps I should say ''how do you do?''
I'm Claudia McCunnen.
Don't you have any questions about me other than my name?
No.
But you must be interested in Inferno, the organization who took you in, right?
I'm taking no reply as an affirmative, okay?
Inferno is... yeah, it's a group that tries to create a different kind of order
in this world where there's no legal order... I think...
If we compare gangs and mafias to countries,
Inferno is like the United Nations.
Inferno's goal is to unify the underground world.
Such a pipe dream would have been laughable a while back,
but what makes it into reality is... Phantom.
That's right. Your instructor.
The power of Phantom... is absolute.
She eliminates the target without fall.
Her existence gives Inferno the greatest confidence...
and brings tremendous fear to organizations that defy them.
She is truly the most powerful assassin.
But...
she's a human who's just being used by the organization.
Both Phantom and I have no choice but to live like slaves, right?
It's true that we're forcing you two to live this way,
but you're not slaves.
Even you have freedom.
Speed...
Speed?
Even when your course is set,
you can keep picking up speed for as long as you want,
so long as you have the desire and put effort into it.
You may even be able to reach the top of the organization.
How you dash through it... is up to you.
As long as you think that way, you're letting those who look down on you win.
I wanted to talk more with you, but there's some business I must attend to.
Goodbye, Zwei.
Cars are meant to be driven by humans...
not puppets.
Even when your course is set,
you can keep picking up speed for as long as you want,
so long as you have the desire and put effort into it.
Desire... Effort...
I'd forgotten those words all this time.
Ein...
What is it?
Today's assignment... Did you kill someone?
Yes.
Why did you become a killer?
I don't know. They never told me about my life before this.
That's...
Right. Just like you...
My memories were erased, too, and I was made an assassin.
But what about it?
It's all about surviving one moment to the next.
A killer... doesn't have a past... or a future...
They have nothing.
But... a woman named Claudia said...
Claudia?
She came here during the day.
She said that we're not slaves and that we're free.
If you want to believe it, go ahead.
But you'll eventually come to feel nothing, too...
since there's no other way to bear this way of living.
You'll eventually become like that, too.
You'll know once you start killing people.
It's easy to pull the trigger...
if the target is just a brick.
But...
Shoot.
Shoot, Zwei.
Zwei...
Practice
Next episode
This is the continuation of the dream...
the dream that you'll never awake from until you die.