I'm sleepy.
Geez.
That reminds me...
...you left a tissue in your skirt pocket and threw it in the laundry basket, didn't you?
It was a mess.
Also, don't forget to separate your clothes by type, colored clothes go in the orange basket-
Shut up, shut up!
You are way too picky.
If you consider yourself a man, you should be bold and-
Give 'em a hell of a hit yay yay yay!
Don't mind!
ALL RIGHT!
Next, it's finally my turn!
Captain, fight!
Thanks for your support, everyone!
Kushieda...
Now... give me everything you've got!
That refreshing smile.
All right!
Kushieda, those sparkling sweat drops...
One run hit, yay! Two run hit, yay! Going through third, and home run!
That off beat singing voice...
Home in!
Kushieda.
As usual, today you're also...
You're making perverted eyes, useless dog.
Kushieda.
This weekend, about the co-ed practice...
Kitamura-kun! I was just now...
Hey! Do you get it, you stupid dog?
Hey, stop it!
It's good to see those two running around, even though they just got here.
Health is the most important thing.
Decorating phones eh?
Minorin, you're really skilled with your hands.
Yeah, I'm actually pretty handy.
Kushieda?
What's she doing?
All right! This one is done!
Okay, next.
What's with that noise? It sounds like someone's trying to strangle you.
N-Nothing...
I know!
Want me to do yours too?
I work part-time as a cell phone decoration artist.
A-an artist?
How about I write your name in purple Swarovski...
Kushieda will? For me?
No!
I...
Kushieda! Please take care of ours too!
Oh, an order?
Please write your name on this paper,
what you would like, and what color you want.
I'd like pink... With a big heart...
Working part time decorating cell phones?
The dazzling Kushieda and her sparkling cell phone is a strong combination.
Hey Yacchan's not going to eat with us tonight since she's eating with her client before going to work right?
In that case let me have her-
And she also remembered my name...
That's because I'm always calling you that way, right?
Anyway, Yacchan's food...
She said so many things to me...
Hey Taiga I wasn't all nervous and wacky, was I?
Listen to me!
Let me tell you...
that you were totally off!
Is dinner ready yet?
That HURTS!
It'll be ready soon.
We are having rice bowls today, so as long as the rice is ready there's no problem.
Huh?!
What's wrong?
The rice cooker is broken.
Welcome! Good evening!
What should I get?
All the way to a family restaurant?
We didn't have rice, but we had bread.
Whine all you want now useless dog.
Soon you'll realize how grateful you should be.
And here we have two...
We still haven't ordered...
It's a secret, but it's a Taiga special with lots of ice cream.
Eat it away from the sight of other customers, 'kay?
Thanks as always, Minorin!
Always?
Takasu-kun, you don't like sweets?
In that case, wanna have french fries?
I'll super-size it, really super size it!
No... I...
Minorin's working at a convenience store and a karaoke place too, right?
Yes! And from last week, I added a Boiled Beef Restaurant!
That many?
And I'm still limiting myself.
I can't skip club activities because I'm the head of the girl's softball team.
Is there something you want to be working that hard for?
I have time! I've got to work!
Work?
Yes! I'm making a portfolio of odd jobs.
It really brings you back to life!
You guys are really close, aren't you?
Excuse me! Could I get some water?
Then take your time.
You...
Just today my eyesight has definitely gotten worse.
Even though you're just a useless dog, you're drooling all over Minorin's waitress outfit.
Me?!
I was just...
thinking her smile was really bright...
Not my eyes!
Any more and my fingers will be tainted.
Damn it!
But, why is she working so much?
She said it was for her work portfolio, didn't she?
Does she have a reason to be in such a need for money?
Like a family problem,
helping out her sick mother or...
She said it was work.
But...
You should quit thinking that way.
That "I'm the only one who really understands her!" thinking.
It just makes you more disgusting.
Walk away from me will you, since you're so disgusting.
Hey!
Taiga! What's up with you? That's cold!
I said get away, didn't I?
Has there ever been a time when I wasn't cold to you?
That's true...
Inko-chan, here's your dinner!
Extra, super extra servings!
In...
Inko-chan, you're going to do it, right?
Ink...
ENKA.
Note- "Enka" is a traditional Japanese music genre.
The morning on a day off is great.
Right, Taiga?
I knew I shouldn't have told you.
Did you say something?
Skipping out on making food, going to a family restaurant just to see Minorin...
It can't be helped, the rice cooker is still broken.
Then we should go to the electronics store first!
And you said you hated bread.
If it's for breakfast, it's okay even if it's bread. What are you so happy about?
Those clothes don't suit you.
I forgot something...
You're a pain in the butt.
For god's sake, let me go.
It doesn't matter what you wear.
Hey, you.
You're Mirano-chan's son, aren't you?
Mr. Inage.
Mirano?
It's Yasuko stage name,
Something like a work alias.
Go straight for 200 meters after getting out of the Northern Entrance ticket gates,
I'm Bishamon Heaven's Mirano-chan!
How old do you think I am? 23?
You're right!
I'm pretty lucky.
Let me touch Mirano-chan's DNA...
It's good, it's good, nice and firm. It's good to be young.
Let's go.
This guy makes me mad.
Hey, you two.
If you haven't had breakfast yet, I recommend Fish sausages full of DHA and calcium!
Huh?
Kushieda?
Minorin?
Okay, carry this.
W-Why?
All right.
One more.
Wouldn't it be better if I...
It's okay! Mirano-chan's son should just sit and have some tea.
Why do I have to do this?
It's only on holidays, but I'm asking her to help out.
Kushieda, work hard!
Yeah! I've got it!
All right!
But it's been busy recently,
and we haven't had enough hands...
Hands?
I've got it. Young lady, since you're a friend of Kushieda's, why don't you work here too?
I'll even add a bonus for your work!
Yes!
I'll do it!
With her.
I can't do this!
Hey, don't make a scene. It'll cause trouble for Kushieda, won't it?
Then you work by yourself!
Little girl, I've got a delivery for you.
Three of those beer cases.
Yes, gladly!
Okay!
It's done!
Take care.
What's wrong, Taiga?
You...
can't ride a bike?
SHUT UP!
So what if I can't ride a bike?!
It's okay as long as I deliver it, right?!
That's wrong, that's wrong!
You're flying, Taiga.
She's fierce.
Well, it's safer if she pushes it, right?
Oh, that's right, we have to get the out the liquor.
Note- "Shōchū 焼酎" Japanese alcoholic beverage
I...
I'll help out too.
It doesn't feel right if I don't do anything.
Okay, thank you.
Yes!
Um... The liquor is...
Note- "Imojouchuu 芋焼酎"  Shōchū made of sweet potatoes.
It's kind of dark, so it's hard to see.
This place isn't used much.
We don't open it more than once a week.
If we got locked in, it would be troublesome.
We could enjoy what disaster feels like.
That kid... leaving it open like that.
Hey! There are still people inside!
S.O.S!   S.O.S!
Calm down, Takasu-kun!
Kushieda?
It's in times like these that it's effective.
Effective?
Stupid.
There's no reason for me to try so hard.
I can't keep up with this.
With what?
Ki.. Kitamura-kun!
Why are you... he-here?
I had practice.
Is that your bike?
Y-Yeah... kinda...
Wow...
You learned how to ride a bike.
That's great progress.
Um... really... ride... that is...
How do you know that I can't ride a bike?
Well, last year I used to watch you a lot.
Bikes are great! It makes your world a lot bigger.
See you tomorrow then, Aisaka.
Last year, I...
D-Damn!
Ouch...
Damn it!
A world Kitamura-kun's not looking at is just...
It doesn't matter if it expands or not!
Damn!
Hey, it took you a while.
You... Your clothes...
It's nothing.
What about the other two?
That's right, where did Kushieda wander off to?
There's nothing wrong with Ryuuji-kun though..
While I'm working so hard, that useless dog is skipping off and having fun...
What are you talking about?
The next delivery is...
Ryuji! What the hell are you doing?!
The bridge that connects to the future.
It's Ohashi, Ohashi ~
My throat is worn out.
I can't believe no one noticed us even though we've been so loud.
Around this time the old man is immersed in horse racing...
I see.
It's gotten a little cold...
If you'd like, I can lend you my clothes...
All right!
Let's warm up!
The pitcher's scared! Hey, hey, hey.
Scared? But you're the pitcher...
Scared! Hey! Scared! Hey!
The pitcher's scared! Hey, hey, hey.
You're actually scared?
Scared! Ha!
Your hand is shaking.
Ah, no, no! It's just excitement, excitement...
All right, here I go!
Strike!
Change.
Let's switch positions.
Okay.
There's no point in being scared.
So...
I'll knock all my fears out of the park!
Kushieda.
What if...
Look, Takasu-kun!
Think we can get out through there?
Where? Where? Where?! Where?!
Hey, Takasu-kun.
There?!
What if the reason Kushieda always appears so bright is not only because she's so energetic and light-hearted...
Careful!
Kushieda! I'm sorry! Are you okay?
A nosebleed?
It's nothing!
Nothing?
A nosebleed is your heart's sweat!
There's only a little bit left!
Let's pile these up, Takasu-kun.
Yes!
I see.
Knocking all your weaknesses out of the park...
All right! We'll definitely succeed!
Of course! Fight!
Hey, if you say fight, you have to say...
O-One hit?
That's right!
Fight!
O-One hit!
That's right.
Kushieda was shining from the start,
from the moment we met.
Fight!
And even now.
One hit!
Shining!
I. Found. You.
Taiga! How did you get here?
How? With a ladder.
All right! Did you hear that, Takasu-kun? Now we can get outside!
But...
Thank you, Taiga! This really is a ladder that leads to the future.
But, Minorin...
Takasu-kun, you have to hurry and wake up.
But!
The ladder just fell down.
Sealed in a corner of my heart.
A memory I can't tell anyone else, for just the two of us.
But I told Takasu...
Kitamu-