- Awesome!
- There's snow everywhere!
It's so pretty!
Yeah, it's nice and all...
But aren't these outfits a bit loud?
Even for rentals.
Come on, now. We shouldn't
let this trip go to waste!
All together now!
Yoo-hoo!
Whew, I'm actually better at snowboarding.
Don't act so cocky—you're Haruta.
Hey, I can do this.
Keep my legs spread...
I haven't skied since middle
school. It's not so bad.
Hey, hey!
Ho, ho!
Wow, not bad, Minori-chan.
You're a natural athlete.
You think?
You're pretty good yourself, Amin.
Nah, I'm average.
Wh-Wh-Whoa...
I'm moving forward.
What do I do?
Turn sideways, against the slope.
S-Sideways?
Wh-Whoa!
This isn't fun.
Move it! Move it!
Outta the way!
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Jeez, don't run me over with a sled...
Why're you even on one, anyway?
Can't Help Myself
It's not by choice.
Oh? You can't ski?
What's with the smug look?
I thought I was the only one,
but you can't ski either!
End of the world, huh?
Man, skiing is so boring.
What's the point in strapping on two
long sticks to glide across snow?
I agree with you, but you could
ask Kitamura to teach you.
What can he teach me if I'm on a sled?
Why don't you go ask Minorin for lessons?
Jeez...
No point in being independent
if you're gonna be so useless.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! You can ride
the lift two at a time, right?
I wanna ride with Maruo!
Not that I mind, but shouldn't
you ride with Kashii?
Nanako and I want to take pictures
of each other on the lifts.
Yeah!
What're they up to?
What?
Well, normally you'd be like,
"What's with that bimbo who keeps
throwing herself at Kitamura-kun!?"
before going on a rampage.
Seriously...
Did something happen between
you and Kitamura?
N-No, nothing...
You sure?
Nothing happened!
Not a thing!
Though, maybe you could
say something did...
Which is it?
Didn't I tell you?
I bumped into Kitamura-kun on New Year's
and we got something to drink.
Then we went to a shrine for
the typical New Year's ritual.
But that's all.
So something did happen.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you were in bed with the flu.
I couldn't brag while you were suffering!
Why do I need an excuse, anyway!?
I'm not obligated to tell you
every single thing I do!
Why are you getting so mad?
My point is...!
Why do you have to butt in every time!?
Why do you always interfere!?
You're a big pain in the ass!
You're the one who's being selfish!
Don't use little tricks because you want
to throw yourself at Kitamura!
I didn't use any tricks!
You did! You definitely did!
It's none of your business, anyway!
I'm trying to help our buddy find happiness!
Right, Haruta?
Yes!
Wait, what?
Sorry, but your little tricks are
lame and destroy the vibe.
- Like I care if a moron thinks they're lame!
- Hey, guys...
Calm down, everyone. Let's all get along.
This is our class trip,
so let's not fight, okay?
I'll settle this for you.
What would that accomplish!?
What's with you guys?
Could everybody just calm down?
Please.
Like, seriously...
Yusaku, are you clueless by nature,
or are you doing it on purpose?
What are you implying?
If you've got something to say, spit it out!
Gosh, are you really such
a simpleton, Maruo?
It's almost oppressive...
After a first day like
this, I can forget about
finding out how Kushieda feels...
Doubt I'll get the chance to talk
to her before the trip's over...
Why so down, Taka-chan?
Everybody's acting weird today.
They're all so gloomy.
Yeah...
Taka-chan?
Bathroom.
Come to think of it...
Kitamura never mentioned anything
about going to the shrine with Taiga.
I've no idea what any of them are thinking...
Caught you sighing.
Ku—
Kushieda!
Going to the bathroom?
Nope.
I saw you leave the dining hall by yourself.
Can you keep a secret?
A...A secret?
I've actually been waiting
for this chance.
S-Same here—
You know how Noto-kun and
Maya-chan got into a fight?
I want to help them make up.
I mean, this is our class trip.
It'd suck if they ended up
fighting the whole time, so—
Huh? What's wrong?
Y-Yeah, I agree.
I was thinking the same thing.
Is there a good way to solve this?
There's the issue of Maya-chan wanting to be
around Kitamura-kun all the time...
But that's only half the problem.
Y-Yeah...
Know why Noto-kun is interfering
with Maya-chan's advances?
It's because he mistakenly thinks
that Taiga likes Kitamura-kun.
So he's trying to help her out.
And that's why...
Are you sure that he's wrong...?
You don't know everything about Taiga.
Not true!
There's nothing I don't know!
I know everything about Taiga.
Where'd you get that?
Oh, this?
Taiga gave it to me.
She told me to treasure it because
it's really important.
Cute, huh?
Oh, I mean the hair clip, not me.
It's no use, Taiga...
It doesn't matter how hard I try...
I have to face reality.
Kushieda isn't going to accept my feelings.
She's pretending that Christmas Eve,
my unrequited love, never happened.
You okay in there, Takasu?
Something wrong?
We're worried about you—really worried!
Are you really asleep?
Better make sure.
Whoa there, Kitamura!
What are you doing!?
Why are you taking your clothes off!?
You've gotta be really sick
to only take your pants off!
And what're you dangling
over Takasu's face!?
Uh-oh, I can feel some sort of
gas about to exit my butt...
You jerks!
Er...
So?
Something happen?
Ku-Kushieda!? As in the Kushieda!?
Do we know any others?
Yes, I'm talking about Kushieda Minori!
I've been in love with that
oddball for over a year!
So shoot me!
But I was rejected on Christmas Eve.
She cut me off before I
could tell her how I feel!
I-I see...
But why would our Kushieda turn you down?
Beats me.
That's what I'd like to know.
If I were a girl, I'd definitely
go out with you, Taka-chan!
Uh, that doesn't help.
It's settled! Let's go!
Where?
To ask her.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Hold on!
No sweat, Taka-chan.
Yes, this is just like Chushingura.
You're Asano Takumi-no-Kami,
and we're the Ako Ronin.
Yep, yep. And Kushieda is Kira.
Oh man, Kira's so cool!
Kitamura only wants to
get even with the girls.
He's just using me as an excuse.
The battle is joined, girls!
Surrender quietly or...
Er...
Huh? Nobody's here.
And they left the door unlocked...
The hell...?
Why is it such a pigsty?
Takasu! Control yourself!
You can't clean this up!
Oh! I just found a light blue camisole!
I found a slightly damp towel!
Hey, stop that!
Takasu, that's a little...
No, you've got it all wrong!
It's not how it looks.
I just can't stand seeing lone socks,
so I'm pairing them up...
Why'd it have to be Tiger!?
Oh, oops.
You're using that to wipe the floor!?
Rub-a-dub-dub.
No! Don't dry your hair with it!
Breathe, Takasu!
Hey, the door's unlocked.
Maybe Tiger came back before us.
Nobody's here.
- Jeez, did we forget to lock the door?
- Please, don't make a sound!
I'm begging you!
This is the only favor I'll ever ask.
Whew, that felt so good.
Nanako, you really love to take baths.
And Ami-chan, you should seriously
try to get into swimsuit modeling.
You'd be a huge hit.
You think?
But I'm not that interested
in becoming a celebrity.
Anyway, where'd Taiga run off to?
Didn't she come back before us?
- Kushieda, that's body cream.
- Think she went to the guys' room alone?
She could be with Maruo this very moment...
As if. You're imagining things.
But I can totally see Yusaku walking in
on her and Takasu-kun
leaping in to intervene.
Really?
Aw, no! That would suck if it were true!
How's Tiger really feel?
Is she after Maruo?
Kushieda, do you know?
Does Tiger's heart belong
to Takasu-kun, or Maruo?
Well, I can't say I know about that.
You'll have to ask Taiga when she gets back.
But she would never tell us!
By the way, haven't you been sorta quiet?
Have I?
Guess I pushed myself
too hard on the slopes.
I'm beat.
Hey!
Don't expect to get any sleep tonight.
We're going to have some serious girl talk.
Actually, Takasu-kun and Tiger
should just hook up already.
Then all our problems would be solved, right?
Ouch...
And Minori-chan falls silent.
What are you talking about?
I'm totally curious.
Oh? You heard me?
Sorry, Minori-chan.
See what happens when you play dumb?
Now I've said something I shouldn't have.
Come on.
Don't just stare at each other.
Spill the goods, Ami-chan!
You heard Maya.
What should I do, Minori-chan?
Tell them?
What are you talking about?
There you go again!
I'm talking about how you
cut off Takasu-kun as he was
trying to tell you his feelings.
Did you forget?
What!?
Tell us!
Takasu-kun was going to ask you out?
And wait.
How do you know about this, Ami-chan?
How, indeed. What a mystery.
Why did you have to bring this up?
Because you won't stop playing dumb.
I can't believe you can sit there and
say those things with a straight face.
Takasu-kun is in love with you, not Tiger.
But you shot him down.
And now you're acting like you
forgot it ever happened.
What with your little
"friends forever" pitch.
Sit here with a straight face?
Did you actually see it happen?
Do you know how I feel?
Are you a mind-reader now?
You know what...?
It's none of your business, anyway.
None of my business, huh?
Oh, I see how it is.
So this has nothing to do with guilt?
Here I was convinced that you were
interested in Takasu-kun...
and you only rejected him out
of guilt for a certain someone.
But okay.
You rejected him because you don't like him.
I'll be sure to let him know that tomorrow.
I mean, shouldn't I?
It's better to drive the
last nail in the coffin
rather than let him think there's hope, right?
Suit yourself.
Okay, maybe I'll go tell him now.
Fine!
Go right ahead!
That's some mask you're wearing.
Cut it out!
What's wrong with you, Ami-chan!?
This is our class trip! We shouldn't fight!
She's right.
Ami-chan, you crossed the line.
Apologize, then let's drop it.
Sorry Minori-chan, I went too far.
Could you forget this ever happened, too?
Sure. Deal. It's all good. Never happened.
So anyway, Tiger still isn't back.
You're right!
I wonder where she went?
M-Maybe we should go look for her.
C'mon, Kushieda!
I'm pretty sure we weren't
supposed to hear that.
Wow, Kushieda sure was...
Am I the only one who doesn't get
what they were arguing about?
How is Ami-chan involved in this?
Hey, Taka-chan! What's up?
I-I'd like to know that, too!
Anyway...
We saw nothing, we heard nothing.
Got it?
Seriously...
This sucks...
What are you doing?
I was tired, so I'm taking a break.
So...
I have something to confess.
It might be my fault that
Minori-chan rejected you.
A while back, I said something spiteful to
Minori-chan when you weren't around.
Why did I say it?
I really don't know...
What exactly did you say?
Yesterday, she and I got into a fight.
It just pissed me off to see her face.
I mean, she refuses to be honest with me.
I keep pushing and pushing, but she
refuses to tell me how she truly feels.
And that infuriates me.
I hate you for being an idiot.
That again?
I hate myself for being an idiot.
My guilt made me screw everything
up again and again,
and now here we are.
Dumb-chi!
Outta the way!
Oh, jeez...
I told you to move!
How many times are you going
to hit me with that sled!?
How stupid are you!?
Come on, I'm trying to apologize.
Oh, I'll buy you ice cream when
we get back to the lodge!
Screw that! It's freezing!
Sorry for not stopping, Amin...
Sorry, my ass!
That was on purpose, right?
It had to be.
Of course not.
We just couldn't stop the sled—
You were targeting me!
It's because you're still mad about what
happened yesterday, aren't you?
You came crashing in just because
I was talking with Takasu-kun!
What happened yesterday?
You mean when you tried
to pick a fight with me?
- I let it go, but you want to rehash it!?
- Hey, that's enough...
You let it go?
You've been ignoring me all morning!
That superior attitude pisses me off,
Little Miss Musclehead!
What superior attitude!?
I'm trying to be the bigger person,
but you keep crossing the line!
Bitch!
Don't you hit my face, you freak!
It's not like you're an actress!
Taiga!
I hated you the second I laid eyes on you!
- You pissed me off!
- Yikes, that doesn't look good.
- Oh, really? So what!?
- They going at it again?
- I don't give a damn if you hate me!
- Fools! Don't just stand there. Stop them!
- Minorin!
- I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
Kawashima!
Could you calm down?
H-Hey!
Takasu!
Everything okay!?
The hell are you all doing!?
Cut it out!
What's going on?
Ami-chan!
Stop already!
Enough!
Girls!
What's going on here!?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
- Kushieda, what's wrong with you!?
- Huh...?
Taiga?
Hey, Taiga?
Taiga had vanished.
The lodge has staff out searching.
If they can't find her,
they'll call the police.
Takasu!
Pull yourself together.
They'll definitely find her.
Y-Yeah...
Taiga...
It's a blizzard out there.
Kushieda!?
What's with the getup?
I'm going out to look for her again.
Are you stupid? You'll end up
stranded out there.
But...I can't just sit here and wait!
I'll be back soon!
I'll just check the area where we were,
and then I'll come straight back.
But...
I'll go with you.
Takasu!?
Damn it...
Count me in.
Ami!
Let Teach know we headed out.
Huh? But wait...
Taiga!
Aisaka!
Takasu-kun! Kitamura-kun!
Over here!
There are signs that she
slipped down here!
Be careful.
That's...
What is it?
Did you find something?
I think.
Hurry and get some help.
No, I'll...
Ta—
I did it again.
I left her all alone.
She was right next to me,
and I didn't even notice...
Damn it...
Stupid klutz...
Next time I catch you, I'll never let you go!
Taiga?
Taiga!
Wake up!
It hurts...
I fell...
Ryuji?
Oh, Kitamura-kun?
Huh? Oh...
I thought you were Ryuji...
Because Ryuji's always the one
who comes to my rescue...
Sorry...
Forgive me...
You know, Kitamura-kun...
You're not doing your job as the
Patron Saint of Broken Hearts...
My wishes haven't come true...
Erase these feelings...
Make me strong...
I'm hopeless...
I can't stop myself...
from loving...
Ryuji...
I ate the orange today but cried
because it was still too sour.
orenji kyoumo tabete mitakedo
mada suppakute naita
It reminded too much of me,
watashi mitaide nokosenai kara
so I finished the whole thing.
zenbu tabeta
I love you. It's bitter.
sukidayo suppai
It makes me cry. I love you. I love you.
nakeruyo sukidayo sukidayo
When You're Around
Taiga loves me...
Why me, of all people?
Hey, super thick stud!
Sorry, but I'd say that's a stretch.