Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I can sense a powerful light inside of you.
Perhaps the power of your newly obtained Sun Arcana is the cause.
I was wondering...
Have you heard the "Long-Nosed Song"?
Vel-Vel, vel, velvet!
My master has a long nose!
That brings back memories.
I used to sing that song with my younger sister.
It truly takes me back.
Hide and seek it wants to play again
Like a detective, I won't let it get away
It's constantly costuming with loads of fake
I will strip search if I have to
Though I'm not afraid to know it, don't know how
I am so determined
To chase after what's hidden and seize this day, this moment
WANNA KNOW
Enter key to accelerate
WANNA GO
Ignition turned on
It's about that time to drive to truth
WANNA SEIZE
Stranger than in movies
Ignorance is not bliss
They say that truth will out
Can't keep on hiding
There's no turning back now
I'm gonna go on
I'm gonna go get what I want
The main events of the culture festival have been concluded.
Festival committee staff, assemble in the A/V Room.
And there.
All done!
Sweet! So, what's next?
Wanna grab a bite to eat?
Sounds good! The Prince of Junes can treat us!
Don't even go there.
I know. Why don't we have the two Miss Yasogami winners treat us?
How dare you ask a maiden to pay?!
Give me your heart!
Don't call yourself a maiden!
C-Can we all just forget about the contest? Really, now...
Anyway, wouldn't it be a shame to just call it a day?
Indeed.
Big Bro!
Nanako, you came to the festival?
Yep! I got some stir-fry noodles!
I danced, went to the haunted house, and even saw the fortune-teller!
You saw the fortune-teller?
Actually, this pretty lady said you're a, um... uh, play...
I'm a play-what?
Pla-Player!
She said you're a natural player.
We had a hard time finding you, but I'm glad we did.
I need to be at the prefectural office early tomorrow,
so I have to head out tonight.
I need you to house-sit with Nanako.
Sure thing.
I appreciate it.
Take care!
Yeah!
I better go.
Oh, are you leaving already?
Yeah.
I can watch the house by myself.
That's okay.
I-I'm sorry, Nanako! I didn't mean it like that.
Nana's a good girl!
Hey, Nanako.
Why don't you and your brother stay with me tonight?
Wha-What?! Yuki, what's that about?
"Why don't you spend the night with me?"
We're partying at the inn?
You sure?
Actually, Nanako—
Oh, sweet! We're staying at the inn!
I only invited—
Can we eat eggs boiled in the hot springs?
Is it just for the night? I should inform my grandfather.
Hot spring, yukata, and flushed skin! Yahoo!
Oh, it's Naoto. Mr. Yakushiji, is Grandpa available?
T-Teddie! You're being gross!
Is it a slumber party?
We'll all have fun together, okay? So you should come over.
Is it okay?
Yeah.
I'll go! I'll spend the night!
In that case, I better go home and pick up a few things.
Let's all gather up at the Amagi Inn!
Yeah!
On second thought, I'll head out after I stop by—
Good evening!
Welcome!
Ms. Kasai, we'll be staying the night.
Sorry we're such a large group.
Not at all. We've been expecting you.
Welcome!
Wow! Yuki, you're the steamy young mistress of the hot springs!
I am not! I'm just a waitress.
I'm sorry,
but a large party suddenly showed up.
Uh-huh.
Yuki, you should leave that group to me and enjoy the time you have with your friends.
But don't you need help for the party?
Allow me to escort you to your rooms.
Sure, I'd appreciate it... Huh?!
Aika?!
What are you doing here?
A part-time job.
Didn't I tell you?
She helps out from time to time.
Seriously? But what about Aiya?
It's fine.
Your room is this way.
Don't you think it's a tad bright?
Really?
Yeah, I think softer colors would be visually relaxing.
She's kinda cool!
Let's take some out and—
So they aren't putting us all in one room?
Of course not!
I could handle it if they were next door, but they're so bear-y far away!
Apparently, most of the rooms are full, so the girls are on a different floor.
Grr!
But man, we've really slept together a lot these past six months.
The tent, the hotel, and now the inn.
You got changed quick!
Excuse me!
Your meal is ready.
Thanks for the feast!
Phew, I'm stuffed!
So full!
This is paradise!
Any problems with your room?
Huh?
Enjoy yourself.
This is the life!
So, what should we do?
Wanna play trump?
The girls said they're hitting the bath.
Is the bath co-ed?
Of course not!
I don't like bathing more than I have to.
You cool with hitting the baths once before bed?
Sounds good.
By the way, got any idea what's up with this room?
It looks really expensive.
You noticed that too?
You don't normally see a room like this open during the busy season.
I'd almost forgotten about that.
Do you think something happened here?
W-Why did everyone suddenly get so quiet?
Oh no, no, no!
K-K-Kanji!
Huh?
Answer it!
Wh-What are you guys so afraid of?
Pick it up!
Okay...
Hello?
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
Oh, really? Thanks!
She said that the open-air bath is practically empty right now.
That panicking really worked up a sweat.
Then let's go rinse it off.
Sure!
I'm looking forward to bathing with everyone.
Teddie's Imagination
We'll face the same direction as
we wash each others' backs
and sing songs while
staring at Mt. Fuji, won't we?
Yeah. It'll be fun.
This world is full of so many fun things.
I wouldn't be here without you, Master. Thank you.
Hey, the elevator's here!
Open-air Bath
Large Bath
This is great!
This feels great!
Naoto, come on over! There's plenty of room.
Uh, okay...
Naoto, your skin's so smooth!
You're right! It's so soft!
Lucky you! Your skin's like porcelain and your hair's silky.
Sto— Hey! Don't touch me there!
You're so soft!
Nanako!
Will you be okay spending the night here? Aren't you scared?
It's fun! I'm always home alone until Big Bro gets back.
I see.
I'm good at staying home alone!
When I'm alone, I don't open the door for any strangers.
I hold down the fort!
Really? That's amazing!
Say, Nanako. Would you like to swim?
Is it okay?
I've been doing it since I was little.
You still do?
Well...
Say, "No," Yukiko!
Then let's race to the other side!
Loser has to buy fruit lattes!
I'd prefer a Cielo Mist!
Huh? Am I racing too?
Me too?!
Ready, go!
It's so big! I'll show you my bear-paddle!
Hey!
Huh?!
Teddie?
What's up?
Y-You jerks!
Wh-Wh-What are you doing here?!
That's my line!
No!
Ew!
Leave!
Oh no, no, no! Ouch!
Oh, ow, ow! Damn that hurts!
Y-Yu!
This situation is terrible.
Scumbags!
What should we do?
Please leave already!
Naoto?!
Hey!
We should gather up our courage and stand our ground!
Yeah!
No!
I can't believe you!
Hey, what's the point in showing off our courage?!
Good point.
We have no choice.
Retreat!
Peeping is a crime!
You've got it wrong!
I won't forget this!
W-We'll have to punish them later.
Amazing! You sure got them good!
We're not half bad, huh?
I wonder if they saw anything.
Oh!
What?!
This bath is open for men right now!
Huh?!
I got the times confused.
Don't give me that. Are you serious?
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Saintly
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
That was a great bath!
Hey, why don't we take another dip later?
It's open 24 hours,
so feel free to whenever.
Yuki!
A moment please...
What's wrong?
It's those men from the TV station.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
I checked, and the open-air bath is supposed
to be open for guys right now.
They're horrible.
They're absolutely horrible!
I'm sorry.
If only I hadn't misjudged when we should retreat.
It isn't your fault, Master.
So...
Guys, did you see anything?
Nope...
Nothing.
Dammit! Nothing good ever happens to us!
I have to do something to clear my head!
You up for it?
I worked up a nice sweat!
Wanna go wash it off in the other bath?
Baths
Pervert!
What's your problem?
Baths
M-Moron! If the open-air bath is open to guys, this one's open to chicks!
Open-air Bath
Large Bath
Currently open to:
Dammit!
Owie, owie, owie! My head's getting all lumpy!
Currently open to:
Retreat.
We've already turned your program down.
There's no need to take that tone with me,
Miss "High School Heiress to a Cursed Inn."
What cursed inn?
I know all about it!
Isn't there where Yamano Mayumi stayed before she got killed and strung upside down?
You've lost customers since then, haven't you?
So I thought up an awesome idea!
"A High School Girl's Embarrassing Battle to Save the Cursed Inn!"
Whatcha think?
Explain further.
I'd love for you to play the lead, Yuki.
There'd be a steamy scene of you in the hot springs!
Sound good?
I'll have to decline.
You what?
But we're trying to boost your popularity!
Don't you want to get more customers?
As the inn's heiress, I think you're capable of making the intelligent decision.
Besides, "traditional" just means that it's "old."
The food's bland, and the portions stink.
You have to "sell yourself" if you want to attract customers!
"The Cursed Inn Where the Late Announcer Spent Her Last Night!"
Doesn't that sound good?
You're screwed because you don't use this stuff!
You punks!
Give it a rest!
You're monsters...
Just stop it.
Huh?
I've had enough of your degrading remarks!
I refuse to ever let you take footage of our inn for your program!
Say what?!
If that's how you're going to be, I'll air that spiteful remark!
Go ahead. Air it as much as you like.
I'll complain to your show's sponsors if you do.
C-Couldn't that cause us trouble?
G-Go ahead.
Why are you still recording, moron?!
See ya!
I said some incredible things.
Yukiko!
Were they with a TV station?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Did you guys chase away those reporter jerks?
Yuki chased them away!
I'm not surprised!
Who'd want to rely on creeps who peep on girls bathing?
Oh, about that! The open-air bath was open to dudes!
Huh?!
That was your fault, you know!
Uh, well...
Now then, let's hear an apology.
But it doesn't change the fact that you peeped!
We didn't see anything!
Pervert!
What?!
Come on. Let's go! Let's go!
H-Hey, wait!
Are you going to falsely classify us as perverts?!
Teddie, Big Bro...
Are you perverts?
Rawr!
Persona!
Women sure are scary...
We never did get to take our baths.
Damn! Damn it all!
I swear, absolutely nothing good ever happens to us!
Let's go to bed.
Hold up, will you?
Can you hear that?
Wh-What was that?
I-I heard it...
Th-There isn't one...
is there?
O-One... One what?
I remember now after hearing those guys from the TV station.
What? What? I don't remember anything!
Well... this is the room where the late Miss Yamano stayed.
You just had to say it!
And here I managed to forget! But you just had to say it!
Come to think of it, after dinner...
Any problems with your room?
Damn you, Amagi! She pulled a fast one on us!
Dammit! First the bath and now this!
She's totally screwing us over!
I can't go to sleep in a room that's haunted!
I've made up my mind! I'm going to stay with Yuki!
Huh?
I won't be able to relax and sleep if I'm not gazing into their sleeping faces!
Wait! Sleeping faces?
Are you sneaking into their room?!
That's nuts!
Let's go.
That was quick!
Ladies, good morning to you all!
It's "Candid Early Bird Camera"!
Scratch that. It's "Caught Asleep"!
I'm your guide, Reporter Teddie.
When did you put that on?
I get nervous without it, so I always bring it with me!
Quit talking like that!
This is...
Huh?
...a brush! It has long hair in it.
I'm surprised you're getting into this.
This is a brush, but not just any brush! It's a toothbrush!
It has a faint minty scent.
Crap! Now I'm starting to get excited!
Oh, but Nanako's here...
That's okay! Nana is nice.
Leave her out of this.
Try not to wake her up.
I've finally made it to their beds! They're sound asleep!
Pardon me!
Yuki, I'm scared of ghosts!
Oomph.
H-He did it!
A-All right! I'll prove to you that I'm a man!
S-Satonaka, please be gentle!
You didn't go for Naoto?!
Huh? Aren't they short some futons?
Gosh darn, what gives?
Geez...
Oh, my!
Goodness, you had a thing for us?
Really, you should've said so sooner!
You're such naughty boys.
M-M-M-Monsters!
We were just crying our eyes out.
We thought there weren't any men out there who appreciated a real woman's charms.
Very well. Come on over!
But don't tell anyone about this, you hear me?
Come on!
Retreat! Retreat!
That was something no man was ever meant to go through.
This feels great!
Where's Nanako?
Sound asleep with Naoto.
Th-This sucks.
Nothing good ever happens.
Stupid!
Sowwy!
Thanks for earlier.
Narukami?
Are you always up this late?
Yeah, I have to prepare for tomorrow and study for my license.
What license?
I thought it would be nice to do something extra to help the inn.
Remember how I met my Shadow after I got thrown into the TV world?
I was shown how, deep down, I felt like I was a bird trapped in a cage.
But that was all in my head.
So I decided to open the door to the cage on my own.
That resolve is what let you defeat your Shadow.
Right.
And then I realized it's okay for me to follow my own desires.
I had considered leaving and living by myself.
But strangely enough,
once I opened the door and looked back,
I realized how dear this place is to me, and now I want to protect it.
I'm glad I realized sooner.
If I had struck out on my own, I know I would've regretted it.
I wanted to become completely self-sufficient.
But I think I was being presumptuous.
I have the inn, my family,
and the waitresses and chefs who made me the person I am today.
When I think of it that way,
my problems aren't just my own.
That's why...
I'm choosing to stay here by my own will.
I think the time I've spent with you and the others has helped me realize all of that.
You did a good thing by getting rid of those guys from the TV station.
Thank goodness! I was afraid you'd think ill of me.
Want some?
Thank you...
But I wanted a soft drink.
Sorry.
Sorry!
I look at the rustic scenery
along the path to school
we walked together
Campus in spring,
the summer festival
These were the days we spent
shoulder-to-shoulder
laughing together
From past to present
I've always
looked back on these
carefree days
From today to tomorrow
We move forward while treasuring the bonds we've made
There was a letter for you in the mail, Big Bro.
To Narukami Yu
Don't rescue anymore
I'll tell you the truth about everything.
He's been locked up?!
The case is still on!
What's this?
Damn brat, you aren't getting away!
You promise?
Yep! Let's play a whole bunch!