Ah!
What?
Rin.
Hey!
You losers shouldn't gang up on
someone and bully them like that!
You guys suck, you really suck!
What's your problem, Tohsaka?
There's nothing here that concerns you.
Yeah, in that case, why don't you do the same to me?
And then it will concern me.
Come on, this is getting lame.
Here.
You used too much mana all at once.
Maintain a calm mind.
In order to control magic, you must first
achieve complete control of your thoughts.
Lose control and the mana will
suddenly rebound back to your body.
Too much power or power in the wrong form
will endanger not only you, but those around you.
Strive to consistently maintain the proper flow.
That is the Tohsaka family motto.
It means always remaining reserved
and elegant.
You shouldn't let them get way
with it when they try that stuff.
If they're in the wrong, you just have
to get mad and do something about it.
You're amazing, Rin, the way you
always speak your mind like that.
I'm not amazing at all.
I think it's normal. I mean, it's only natural.
That's right, it's only natural.
Hold out your hand.
Oh.
Father, oh please teach me more.
How do I make something like this?
Well, my dear, that might be a
bit difficult for you right now.
But if you work hard every day,
you'll be able to make it eventually.
After all, Rin, you're a daughter of the Tohsaka family.
Hey, Rin, could you please show me how to do this part?
Of course, which part?
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
Oh, this was on page 23 of the textbook.
You see, you just did the math wrong here.
For this problem, it's just like this example, see?
Kotone, have a seat, I'll help everyone in turn.
Okay.
Do I really have to go and live with the Zenjo family?
Once the Holy Grail War begins, it
will no longer be safe for you in Fuyuki.
But I... but I want to do something
to help you with the Grail War, Father.
Rin, you mustn't cause trouble for your father.
Do you think that we're in the way?
Not at all.
Please try to understand, I need
to make preparations for the battle.
Those preparations include doing
what's necessary to ensure your safety.
And for me to do that, you simply can't stay in Fuyuki.
But I'm certain there's something I can do to help!
That's right, I just haven't learned how to yet.
So, all I need to do is study on my own.
I don't understand any of this.
What is this?
Tease!
Oh.
I have to close it.
It won't move.
Rin!
Are you all right?
It's still too soon for you to read this book.
Some things in this world contain their own mana.
This is called a mana compass. Normally, it doesn't
point to anything except for mana traces in the area.
Rin, try generating mana in this.
Okay.
Ah.
You see?
And with that book.
Anything that provokes a reaction like that
is beyond your ability, so be very careful.
Ah.
I'll give this to you as an early birthday present.
Oh, thank you so much, Father.
Once the Holy Grail War is all over,
you and I will try some real jewel magic.
And then strange things began to happen.
They said we have study hall again.
There was another kidnapping on the news this morning.
...the sudden disappearance of children
has police investigators baffled.
The teachers have been in a meeting all day.
They said we won't have fifth period today.
All right!
But they said we should stay home.
Why?
Another kidnapping.
They say only children have been kidnapped.
Hey, did you hear?
Uh.
Apparently there's no body inside
the coffin, it was in such bad shape.
It definitely happened in Fuyuki, right?
My name is Tohsaka and I'm in Kotone's class...
The person you are calling is not home.
Please leave your message after the beep.
Thank you.
Please be safe.
Kotone.
This is Fuyuki at night.
It's different than during the day.
Ooh, it's really cold and creepy.
What is this?
I've never seen it do this.
Does this mean there are traces of magic all around here?
I've got to find Kotone.
Huh?
Someone out with their kid this late?
What was that flash?
Oh, no.
That was close.
If I'm spotted, they'll take me home.
Come on, you've got to walk, kid.
Two of them?
He's gathered more kids.
But why?
Wait, why am I hiding?
I can't accomplish anything this way.
Looks like no one's here.
Hey, hey you?
Kotone, Kotone, Kotone!
Something's been done to her.
What do I do?
Think, Rin.
Well now, are you lost little girl?
No, um I...
Perfect timing.
We were just about to get the party started.
But we still don't have enough guests.
Want to help?
It'll be fun.
When it comes to parties, the
more the merrier I always say.
No!
What, what just happened?
Don't run from me.
Is he controlling them with that bracelet?
Ow!
I've got it.
Well, well, you're gonna help me after all?
Huh?
What is that?
You use too much mana all at once.
I can destroy that!
What?
Kotone!
Rin?
What's going on?
This is not the time to cry.
Run!
Hey, wait!
Oh, man.
I hope the big guy won't be too pissed.
Where's Rin?
It's gonna be okay, sweetie.
Good, it's done.
I did it, Father.
What?
Ah!
Anything that provokes a reaction like that
is beyond your ability, so be very careful.
Ah.
Rin, I just can't believe she went to Fuyuki.
Rin!
Rin.
Rin is fine.
She's just asleep.
Kariya.
What's happening here?
What are you doing here?
Your face.
Behold the family magic of the Matous.
You offer your flesh and your life is slowly devoured.
That is the magic's price.
But Sakura will be fine.
I'll save her before this happens to her.
Zouken's only desire is the grail.
He gave me his promise that he'll release Sakura
as soon as I win it for him.
If you win the grail?
Yeah, so don't worry.
My servant is the strongest.
It won't lose to anyone.
Considering what she's been through, hope would
be nothing but cruel torture to Sakura right now.
So, pray for her since she can't.
Pray for my victory, for Sakura's future.
Kariya, wait.
Someday I'm sure we'll all play in this park,
just like we used to back in better days.
And Rin and Sakura will be sisters again.
So, Aoi, you don't need to cry anymore.
Kariya, are you going to die and kill Tokiomi too?
Mother?
Rin, I was so worried about you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Master Kirei, are you certain that you wish to
allow Tokiomi Tohsaka's wife and daughter to go free?
It's fine.
You are to continue monitoring Berserker's master.
Understood.
It wasn't much, but I did manage to do something.
I guess I'm not a full‐fledged mage yet.
I passed out half way through.
That means I need to work harder.
But that's just for now.
I have plenty of time to train more.
And someday, I'll take my place as a Tohsaka mage.
I'll have to practice really hard and obey my
father so that I'll be ready when that day comes.
And when the time does come,
I'll do it to the best of my
ability, as elegantly as I can.
A king without greed is even worse than a figure head!
Worthless is a king who fails to protect the weak.
We stand to lose nothing.
A reality marble?
I shall take great pleasure in killing you myself.
Wasn't your goal supposed to be world conquest?
Argh!