Meet Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
She had a shampoo commercial
audition today and I was with her.
There we met this nasty girl.
Her name is Madoka Wakamatsu.
It seems she has some kind of grudge
against Full Moon
and does nothing but harass her!
And to top it off,
she even ends up complaining
about her passing the audition!
Jeez, it makes me mad!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
We would like to have Miss Full Moon
and Miss Madoka Wakamatsu,
the two of you, in this commercial.
W-What's up with that?!
Madoka...
I look forward to working with you.
Let's do our best together.
Please decide on one person!
What?
I don't want to work with her!
Huh?!
W-Why...?
Uh-oh.
You see...
I'm concerned because Full Moon
and I have such different images.
I wonder if we can make
a good commercial.
Who'd be fooled by
such contrived acting?!
Hmm, you have a point.
Hey, Kuwahara.
But, like I said, my vision is...
But sales will be totally different depending
on the character in the commercial.
That's why...
Umm, everyone's waiting.
Something must be done quickly.
Madoka. Why...?
Umm, thank you for waiting.
Getting right to the conclusion,
we will hold a camera test
for both parties.
And therewith, we will make
the final selection.
What?!
And so we will be deciding on
one person as planned.
Thank you!
No kidding. That's too bad.
Is that it?
Don't you think that
Madoka Wakamatsu is terrible,
or Meroko's cute or anything?
Hmm... Well...
We're trying so hard!
Say something more!
So I'm saying that's
too bad, aren't I?
Not that.
Cripes! Will you get serious
about this?!
What?
Do you have a fever or something?
Maybe a cold?
Wrong.
But your face is all red.
Th-This is...
Yeah, he really is all red.
Takuto?
I-It's that... You, too...
Huh?
Nothing.
Where are you going, Takuto?
I'm coming, too!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Don't be coming along.
The bathroom?
A Death Spirit shouldn't have
to go to the bathroom!
He's really acting strange.
It's like he's angry.
I need to chill out.
I'm the only one who's
all concerned about it.
I have to encourage her so
that she'll do well in the audition.
I wonder if Takuto is opposed to me
being in a commercial, after all.
Why?
He was a singer before
he died, wasn't he?
What?!
He might be thinking something like,
"appearing in a commercial
isn't necessary for music!"
Say, do you know what kinds
of songs he sang, Meroko?
Where did you hear
that Takuto was a singer?
Huh...? Well...
Takuto said before that
he sang songs when he was human.
You little jerk!
What're you doing
snooping around?!
But...
Is it fun for you to probe
into someone's past?
Besides, it doesn't have
anything to do with you, does it?
Is it true that you
talked about it, Takuto?
Well...
Why'd you talk about it?
And to a human at that?!
It's my business, right?
Your business?
Takuto, what's the big idea?
Nothing, nothing at all!
Just shut up.
I'm talking with her right now.
I'm talking to you, Takuto!
Get out of the way!
No!
I-I'm sorry!
I said something
I shouldn't have.
I was just wondering what
kind of songs Takuto used to sing.
- Shut up!
Takuto!
Hey, Takuto!
I'm not finished.
Takuto!
It's your fault if something
happens to Takuto!
What...?
Takuto's wings are still replicas.
R-Replicas?
It means they're artificial!
They're not real.
Takuto is still a rookie and
he hasn't completely become
a Death Spirit yet.
He's immature.
It's dangerous while
he's still in that state.
If he recalls all of the memories
from the time he was human,
his soul will be pulled back
into this world.
What?
Do you get it?
He won't have a body to return to
and he'll turn into a ghost!
If you get it, then don't ever
say anything again to Takuto
that'll make him recall his past!
Meroko.
Meroko!
What should I do?
I did something terrible.
The two of them didn't come back.
Meroko...Takuto...
I wonder where they went.
Mitsuki.
Mitsuki!
Oh... Uh, yes?
I'm sorry!
You seem kind of tired, Mitsuki.
As I recall, today's a school day, right?
If you're not feeling well, skip school
and we'll go to the hospital.
Oh no, I'll be okay.
It'll be okay, right?
I'm sure Takuto will come back
by tomorrow's audition.
Takuto?
Oh, Tomoe.
Who's Takuto?
Oh... Well... Umm...
I bet it's the name of
a person you like, right?
No, you're wrong!
Don't hide it, don't hide it.
Come to think of it,
you suddenly look grown-up.
Something happened during
two weeks of the summer vacation, right?
I'm telling you,
nothing happened.
Then who's Takuto?
Takuto is...
To me, Takuto is...
Takuto is a dear friend.
Yikes!
Are you okay?!
Uh-oh!
- What're you guys doing?!
- Yikes!
All right.
Finally dry.
Thanks, Tomoe.
What?
My throat hurts a little.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'll scold those jerks and
teach them a lesson!
You don't need to do that.
You can't go easy on them.
It's proper to apologize
if you do something bad.
I see... You're right!
Thanks, Tomoe!
M-Mitsuki?
I'm home!
Takuto!
Meroko!
They're still not back.
I want to apologize properly.
Hello?
Oh, Mitsuki?
Can you watch TV now?
And so, it seems
Madoka Wakamatsu here
and Miss Full Moon will
be competing
for the coveted spot in
the new Mermaid Tear commercial.
Yes. It's an honor for me to be
with Full Moon who's so hot now.
Whoa!
It seems Madoka Wakamatsu's
office set it up.
They're trying to give her
the edge in tomorrow's audition
by monopolizing
the conversation.
But you don't need to get nervous.
Mr. Kuwahara, the director,
has made it so clear
that you're perfect for
his vision, after all.
- Please tell us about
- Okay...
your goal in
trying out for the final selection.
Yes. In this audition,
I hope to learn various things
from Miss Full Moon.
Congratulations, Madoka.
Here you go.
Let me tell you one thing.
This won't make me change
my mind about the image.
I think only Full Moon can express
that mellow feeling.
Oh, no. That's not my intention.
It's just that Madoka was
really nervous yesterday.
I wanted you to see
her true self today.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh!
Madoka?
Hey, are you okay?
Oww! I went and did it again. Oopsy!
I'm sorry. Madoka has
gotten nervous again.
Well...
Madoka's mellower than I thought, eh?
She works very hard and
is often misunderstood.
Well, I'll be darned.
I guess the clients were
looking closely, after all.
Ohh, I'm embarrassed.
I'll make myself the desired image
by any means necessary.
Full Moon, I won't lose to you!
Takuto...
The pendant Eichi gave me.
Eichi, I said something that
hurt a very dear friend.
Please help me so that we can
be friends once again.
Eichi.
Takuto.
Where are you?
Come back.
Takuto.
Shouldn't you go?
The audition's tomorrow, right?
There shouldn't be any work today.
Then it'll just be the two of us today?
I'm happy!
Let's have a lot of fun and
just forget about yesterday, okay?
That girl's really a bother, isn't she?
She can't do anything without you.
She should just think about Eichi.
Right, Takuto?
Shut up, Meroko!
Can't you keep quiet
even for a little bit?
Takuto?
Jeez! How irritating!
I shouldn't have
said that I sang.
It was bound to interest
that singing idiot.
I was just wondering
what kind of songs...
I forgot that stuff when I died.
That jerk.
I forgot!
Takuto.
Takuto... Why won't you come?
I want to apologize.
Summer's all about ice cream.
Madam won't be home until late,
so I'll just relax like this.
Mitsuki?
I wonder what she's doing there?
Mitsuki!
Oh no!
Dr. Wakaoji!
How's Mitsuki?
She has a high fever.
I can't say that she's in
very good shape.
To be on the safe side,
she should probably stay
in the hospital for a few days.
Ma'am!
It's because she went
walking around on her own
even though I repeatedly
told her not to.
She's the only one.
What?
She's the only kin that
my daughter Hazuki left me.
Even if she's that man's child,
she is my grandchild.
I've had enough of those feelings...
like those when I lost my daughter.
Where am I?
I didn't realize it was morning!
I have to go.
Though, I can't audition
in this condition.
No, I'm sure Takuto will come.
I'm sure we can make up
if I apologize.
Today, at last.
The whistle isn't sounding...
So I guess that girl gave up, huh?
Say, I've been thinking.
Since it's come to this,
let's ask the Death Spirit division chief
to change who's in charge of the girl.
Isn't it better for all of us?
Let me see, the procedure
in such a case is...
She's not the kind to give up.
Huh?
Takuto, don't tell me...
She's waiting.
I can't blow her off.
Takuto!
Hey, wait!
Backwards letters again!
Ma'am!
Mitsuki isn't...
Mitsuki isn't in her room!
I have to hurry.
Here I rushed over here.
Where'd she go? Jeez!
Meroko!
I won't let you go!
What's with the silly stunt?
Look at this!
This is...!
Right. A message hastening
her death has appeared again.
And the keyword is...audition.
So don't be transforming her
and helping with her audition!
But...
We're Death Spirits.
We're here to let her live out her life!
I know!
No, you don't!
You don't at all, Takuto!
Don't get involved with her.
I'm sick of you and that
girl being together!
I didn't want to say it,
but something about you
and that girl is similar.
You're sure to recall the time
when you were human if
you associate any more with her.
You know what'll happen then, right?
- I love you.
- Huh?!
I never want us to part.
I don't want you to turn
into a ghost, Takuto.
Wait, Mitsuki!
I'm coming to get you.
Takuto, why do you back
that girl so much?
I don't know myself!
But I can't just leave her,
so it can't be helped.
No. I won't let you go,
no matter what!
Takuto, you'll get in big trouble
if you stay by her side.
Get out of the way, Meroko.
I don't care what happens to me!
I'm...I'm going to help Mitsuki,
no matter what!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Run to the Audition"
- Look forward to it!