Good afternoon, Renji-kun.
Good afternoon. You took your time today.
Yes. I finished writing the novel.
I wrote the last part myself.
I-I see.
What's wrong?
Congratulations on completing it.
Thank you.
But it's not done yet.
After you finish reading it, if there isn't a problem, then it's done.
This is something the two of us wrote together.
Which ending did you choose?
Did you end it with the girl entering the paintings, or the boy coming out of the paintings?
You haven't decided on the ending yet, right?
About that... you'll know when you read it.
Okay.
Please wait.
Please read it after I've gone home.
It's embarrassing.
I should express my gratitude to you.
Gratitude?
I couldn't have finished writing the novel by myself.
This is all thanks to you.
I didn't do anything.
You had the ability to write it to begin with.
No. I don't think I could've done anything without you.
You created the chance for me to fulfill my only dream.
Yes, with this, I'm...
Please let me express my gratitude to you.
I want to express my gratitude to you.
Chihiro.
If there's anything I can do, please tell me.
Then... will you go on a date with me?
A... date?
Will you?
Going on a date is something lovers do.
Can't we be lovers?
As I thought. I won't do after all.
That's not... It's not like that.
Okay. Let's be lovers.
But only for one day.
Only for one day?
Yes. You and I will be lovers only for tomorrow.
So let's have a date.
Only for tomorrow?
It's called a trial period.
Then how about starting the day after tomorrow?
Let me think about it tomorrow.
Can you read the novel another time?
Please read it after our date tomorrow.
The two of you are really similar.
Who am I similar to?
I wonder. I've already forgotten about her.
The person you're waiting for?
I forgot about her too.
Erm...
Hmm?
What does it feel like to fall in love with someone?
Let's see. You feel like there's no helping it.
There's no helping...?
When you finally notice, it's already too late.
It's too late no matter how you feel.
In that case, it might be too late for me too.
I see.
Erm, thank you for everything.
What's the matter? You're so formal.
I just felt like saying it.
If I don't say it when I want to, I'll forget about it.
I didn't do anything.
You said the same thing as Renji-kun.
We're similar too.
Give this to him.
What's that?
Just a little custom.
Good morning.
M-Morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing... those clothes...
Since it's a date, I dressed up.
Onee-chan bought it for me, even though I didn't try it on before.
It's great. It's really cute.
Thank you.
Do you have a plan in mind?
I thought about seeing a movie first.
What do you think?
That sounds good.
What kind of movie should we see?
I guess... at a time like this, a love story would be best...
As long as it's not a sad one.
Not a sad one?
I might cry real hard.
Then how about a comedy?
That sounds good. I like it.
Ah... sorry. Well, I didn't think it would have a bad ending.
That was totally unexpected.
I'm sorry. I-I'm... going to... wash my face...
Do you need a tissue?
I brought some with me.
Excuse me.
Welcome back.
It was a really good story though.
It was interesting how the story took an unexpected turn.
I thought it would be slapstick, but it turned out to have emotional development.
Yeah.
And it had a bad ending.
A happy ending would've been nice.
It would've ... really been...
I'm going to wash my face.
Erm... do you need tissues?
You're mean.
Where are we going next?
Let's see. Since you don't like crowded places, a game center wouldn't work out...
Want to give it a try?
Yeah.
That was a bit hard.
The setup of the spring was weak, and the material was slippery.
The rabbit next to it seemed to be easy though.
Oh, yeah. I'll buy you a similar one next time.
I know a place that sells them.
Our eyes met.
It said I should bring it with me.
Let's go back.
You want that one, right? I'll definitely get it.
This time for sure. This time for sure. This time for sure.
Go!
Got it!
Don't slip off.
Keep going... Keep going... Keep going...
All right!
Finally got it!
Here.
Thank you.
Poyo.
Poyo?
The one I have at home is Piyo-chan. This one is Poyo-chan.
I-I see.
Can we play that one too?
Please give me one piece.
There are plenty of them. Let's split them half-and-half.
Just one piece is enough.
Really?
Thank you, Renji-kun.
Yeah.
Today was really fun.
That's good to hear.
Erm, Renji-kun.
What is it?
Can we... hold hands?
Y-Yeah.
Thank you.
We're lovers, after all.
You're right.
Somehow I always feel at ease when I'm with you.
What should we do now?
Let's go to the beach if that's okay with you.
The beach?
It seems lovers go to the beach.
Really?
Yes. That's what the books say.
What do lovers do after they come here?
It wouldn't be bad just to remain like this, without doing anything.
Yeah.
We came here before too, right?
A lot of things happened, right?
Yeah.
A lot of things happened.
I know about them because I've read my diary over and over again.
But I don't remember them.
I'm sure by tomorrow I'll also forget about today's...
It'd be nice if tomorrow never came.
You shouldn't say something like that.
Couldn't tomorrow possibly be a better day than today?
You're right.
Oh, I totally forgot about it.
Himura-san told me to give this to you.
Apparently, it's a duplicate key to the school rooftop.
Huh, why?
The view of the streets from the rooftop in the evening is supposed to be really beautiful.
That's not what I meant. Why did Himura-san have this?
I wonder why.
He's a really mysterious person.
Apparently, it's a custom in that school to pass down this key from one person to another.
Eh. Let's go and try it out.
Yes.
Amazing.
I should thank Himura-san after this.
Yeah.
Amazing, amazing.
Don't get too close to the edge.
It's all right.
It's really amazing.
Yeah.
Chihiro.
Yes?
I love you.
I'll also love you tomorrow and the day after. I'll always love you.
Saying something like that doesn't suit me, eh?
I yearned to say it though.
I love you.
Can we kiss?
Kissing is something lovers do.
I'm your lover.
In that case, you should just kiss me without saying anything.
You're right.
Yes.
Our teeth knocked against each other.
Then... let's try it one more time.
S-Sorry. I got a little carried away.
Please don't stop.
I've finally come all the way here today.
I don't want you to treat me like I'm far away.
Chihiro.
Please make us into a real pair of lovers.
Why me?
I wonder why.
How about you? Why me?
I wonder why. Just that...
Just that?
I love you too.
Chihiro.
What is it?
I love you.
Eh?
I know.
Renji-kun.
What is it?
Kiss.
W-Wait a second.
Don't.
Geez.
Is it about today?
Yes, about just now.
What have you written?
I won't tell anyone no matter what.
Tell me what you can then.
Well then, our teeth knocked against each other.
You were right. You can't say anything beyond that.
I can't.
Ten o'clock in the evening.
That means the memory of our meeting at the station at nine this morning will disappear soon.
From now on, an hour of Chihiro's memories about what happened today will disappear as each hour passes.
They will all disappear.
What's wrong, Renji-kun?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Yes. Everything is fine.
Today has passed.
Yeah.
Your trial period has passed, hasn't it?
You brought it with you, eh?
Yes, please read it. Then it will be completed.
Chihiro?
I'm embarrassed after all for you to read it in front of me.
I'll read this on the rooftop.
I want to reread all the things that have happened from when we met up until now.
Please tell me after you've finished reading it.
Okay.
See you later then.
A
The furigana next to it says "Kanjou", which means "Feelings."
"The girl is the only one in the world."
A
Reference Note: Most of the lines below can be found in the opening animation.
"That made her the God of this world."
"Something mysterious happened."
"The two in those paintings had moved."
"The god looked inside the paintings."
"The two in the pictures seemed to be having fun, smiling at each other."
"But the paintings were blurred."
"The world itself appeared blurred."
"Why, the girl thought."
"A strange feeling developed in her mind."
"She could not describe what it was."
"She wondered why the paintings became blurred, even though she painted them so clearly."
"The two in the paintings were smiling at each other."
"That was what she felt."
"She repainted them."
"She repainted them over and over."
"But the results were exactly the same."
"She was at a loss."
"She began to be unsure of everything."
"The girl is the only one in the world."
"That made her the God of this world."
"So she thought she should make her world much cleaner."
"She burned all pictures."
"She set fire to the mansion and the old castle."
"Along with the structures, she burned all her memories."
"Lastly, the God threw the trash, the only trash left in the world, out from the cliff."
Renji-kun.
I finished reading the novel.
How was it?
Hmm, I was a bit surprised.
It's a sad ending.
That's not true.
For the girl, it's the happiest ending.
The girl shouldn't have contact with other people after all.
Because she has found out what loneliness is.
Chihiro...
That girl is us.
Renji-kun, let's break up.
I don't want to.
Even if you're obstinate about it, I won't give way about this.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to.
Did I tell you the story of the sheep?
The story about the sheep tied by a chain, that died after eating up all the grass.
Yeah.
I'm tied by a chain that's twelve years long.
No matter how much time goes by, I can't get to the outside world from there.
The farthest my hand can reach is thirteen hours from there.
The story I wrote was about my dream inside those twelve years.
That's why after I finished writing the story, everything of mine is done.
I decided at the very beginning.
I'd disappear from your sight after I finished writing this novel.
I thought I'd disappear quietly without leaving behind any memories, like a mermaid princess turning into a bubble.
But I'm weak. I became like Cinderella instead of a mermaid princess.
That's all right. It's ridiculous to call me a prince, but...
You're wrong, Renji-kun.
I was happy.
I was really, really happy.
I love you.
But, since I'm like this, I don't want you to disappear from my heart.
I want to break up while I can still say, "I love you."
No way...
That logic doesn't make sense.
You let me write the novel that I abandoned a long time ago.
You let me wear a uniform and go to school.
You brought me out of the station where I was marooned.
Before then, I had been doing nothing but looking up at the sky.
I always felt like crying.
I always looked up at the sky because I felt like my tears were going to start.
You hugged someone like me tightly.
You suffered and cried for my sake.
That's why I want you to be happy too.
I don't want you to be unhappy.
Chihiro...
If you stay with me, I believe you'll keep suffering from painful memories.
I don't want that.
I'm not disappearing because I hate you.
Even I have a way to prevent you from being unhappy.
Even though I shouldn't be able to do anything, I've found a way.
I don't want to!
Please praise me.
I love you.
How can I praise you for something stupid like that?
Please smile.
I don't want to.
Let's part with your usual smile.
I'm sorry.
Farewell.
Chihiro!
This is...
This is me.
The diary from the day I met you until today.
With this, the "I" that knew about you has disappeared.
With this, I won't remember you anymore.
With this, we've really broken up.
The end of the season is a time of beginning.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories:
Love.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?