Everyone, draw your swords.
When that thing shows itself, we'll only have a moment.
Run!
It's fast!
We can't escape it inside this forest!
It's catching up to us!
Captain, can we switch to our 3D Maneuver Gear?
Captain?
You're not getting away!
Reinforcements from the rear!
Captain! Orders!
Let's do it!
That thing is dangerous!
We have to take it down!
It's catching up to us!
Let's kill it here!
That's why we're in the forest!
Isn't it, Captain?
Captain, orders!
Everyone, cover your ears.
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
muimi na shi de atta to iwasenai
until I am the last one standing
saigo no hitori ni naru made
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
ryoute ni wa Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
utau no wa Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
senaka ni wa Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
nigirishimeta ketsui wo hidarimune ni
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
kirisaku no wa Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
soukyuu wo mau
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit
Bite
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 3)
A sound blast?
What is your job?
Does it entail letting yourselves be ruled by fickle emotions?
Not in my book.
Our squad's mission is to keep this stupid kid far out of harm's way.
Even if it costs us our lives.
It wasn't to keep watch on me?
We'll continue fleeing on horseback.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
Continue fleeing?
Where to, exactly?
Besides, it's already right on our asses!
Again?!
The reinforcements!
If we don't help, they'll get wiped out like the others!
Eren!
Eyes forward!
Günther!
Don't slow down!
Keep going full speed!
Eld!
Why?!
If the Levi Squad doesn't stop it, who else will?
Another fatality!
We might've been able to save him!
There's someone still fighting!
It's not too late yet!
Eren!
Face forward and run!
You want me to turn a blind eye to the fight?
Leave my comrade for dead and run?
Yes, that's right!
Follow the Captain's orders!
I don't see any reason to abandon him!
Why won't anybody give me an explanation?
Tell me why!
The Captain has deemed it unnecessary to explain.
You just don't understand because you're still a newbie!
If you do, then shut up and obey!
Wait...
I can fight just fine on my own.
Why am I relying on other people?
I should just fight it myself.
What are you doing, Eren?
You're only permitted to do that when your life's in danger.
Didn't you make us that promise?
Eren!
You're not wrong.
Do as you must do.
It's clear to me...
He's truly a monster.
It's not because he can transform into a Titan.
No matter how you try to suppress him, whatever cage you lock him inside,
he will never submit. Not to anyone.
I just want to kill as many Titans as I can.
Eren, our decision contradicts your sensibilities because of the gap in experience between us.
However, you don't have to depend on that experience.
Decide.
Will you trust only in your own strength?
Or will you put your faith in the Recon Corps, including myself?
I don't know the right answer.
I never have.
Whether I believe in myself or whether I rely on my comrades...
Either way, no one knows the outcome.
That said, all you can do is...
Try your best to make a decision you won't regret.
Eren!
Have faith!
I figured out a way to avoid killing you.
Pardon?
I originally thought that disabling your Titan form would require killing you,
but this method would only severely injure you.
However, great skill is needed to pull it off.
Basically, we'd cut you out along with the nape of the neck.
In the process, your limbs would be severed, but you can regenerate those like a lizard, right?
How disgusting.
Hold on!
I don't know how to grow those back.
Isn't there another way?
You think there's a way involving no risk and no sacrifice?
N-No.
Man up, then.
We're in the same boat.
We run the risk of being killed by you.
Don't let it trouble you.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
S-So, now can I experiment on him?
The risk is too high.
However, at the least we need to inspect him.
I can make the plans, right?
Eren, if there's something you don't understand, you must learn to comprehend it.
It's more than worth risking our lives for.
Can we get started soon, Eren?
I'll fire a signal flare for you when we're ready.
After that, whatever you do is your call.
Yes, ma'am!
This old well should be able to restrain a Titan even if Eren loses control...
Hopefully.
That's the signal.
I need to become a Titan.
I haven't done that since I sealed the Wall.
If I go berserk again, will Levi's squad kill me this time?
I wonder if he missed the signal.
No.
His ability just isn't that reliable.
Hey, Eren!
Stop the experiment!
Did something happen?
Hanji, I can't transform.
You can't even heal your self-inflicted bite wounds?
I can't.
If you can't become a Titan, then our mission to seal Wall Maria cannot progress.
This is an order:
Make it happen.
Yes, sir.
Don't be so discouraged, Eren.
But...
Well, it just means you're more human than we thought.
I prefer this to rushing things and getting people killed.
This wasn't meaningless.
Yeah, we can't be too careful.
Why is everyone so calm?
Don't they mind that I can't transform into a Titan?
You okay?
Yes.
Hey, what happened?
What was that explosion?
Why now?!
Calm down.
Captain Levi!
This is...
I said calm down, everyone.
Currently Disclosable Information
Flare Signals (pt 1)
A small gun that can fire a flare using gunpowder.
You use it by switching out the flare signal pipe every use.
Currently Disclosable Information
Flare Signals (pt 2)
The color depends on the information to be relayed.
Red - Titan found.
Green - Change of direction.
Black - Abnormal found.
Huh? What was that sound?
Eren, explain yourself!
Excuse me?
Why did you transform without permission?
Answer me!
Eld, wait.
Answer him, Eren!
What're you thinking?
No, save the explanation for later.
Prove to us... that you aren't hostile toward the human race!
Prove it right now!
That's your responsibility!
If you move that arm an inch, your head will roll!
I'm not bluffing! I mean it!
You want to try me?
Oluo!
Calm down!
Captain, get away from Eren! You're too close!
No.
You guys need to back away.
Now.
Why?
My intuition tells me so.
What's wrong, Eren?
Say something!
I...
Don't do anything weird!
Prove it to us, Eren!
I don't even...
Answer us!
You don't think we can kill you?
I'm dead serious!
Prove it right now!
Can you hear us?
We'll kill you right now!
For fuck's sake, please shut up!
Eren!
Can I touch your arm?
Pretty please? It's fine, right?
I'm just gonna touch it!
Hanji!
Wait!
It's hot!
It's so hot without the skin!
It's scorching!
Captain Hanji, you're being too reckless!
Hey, isn't it hot for you, Eren?
How's it feel where the right arm connects to you?
I really want to see it!
That's right! If I just pull out this hand...
Damn thing...
Hey, Eren!
Don't try anything stupid!
Eren! It can't be over yet!
I still had more research to do!
Captain.
How do you feel?
Not... Not so good...
When I saw that they all seriously intended to kill me,
I realized just how little faith everyone had in me.
Naturally.
That's exactly why I chose them.
We say you're not a real member of the Recon Corps soldier until you've come back alive from an expedition.
Every time we encounter a Titan, we're lacking information.
There are far too many situations we can't anticipate or predict.
So what we must do is act quickly and decide
ruthlessly by assuming the worst-case scenario.
However, it's not like we've become completely inhuman.
It's not like they felt nothing when they turned their blades on you.
Captain Levi.
Yes?
Captain Hanji is calling for you.
Were you taking a long dump?
Not at all.
It came out nice and smooth.
It just took time to explain things to the brass.
Anyway, take a look at this.
A teaspoon?
Yes.
Eren's transformed right arm was holding it.
Like this, between the thumb and index finger.
It's hard to believe that was just a coincidence.
And for some reason, the spoon didn't deform from pressure or heat.
Can you think of any reason?
I was trying to pick it up.
That was when the transformation started.
I see.
Maybe that's why you couldn't transform earlier.
Killing the Titans, blocking a cannonball, lifting a boulder...
In all those cases, you had a clear objective before you transformed.
Self-injury probably isn't the only trigger.
Perhaps you need to have a goal as well.
That's true. The transformation this time was similar to when I blocked that cannonball.
But... Transforming just to pick up a spoon?
What the hell is that about?
So you didn't intentionally transform without permission?
No, sir.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Ouch.
That's tough.
Eren, I'm surprised you can bite so deeply.
We made the wrong call.
Just a token expression of apology.
Not like it makes much of a difference.
Our job is to keep you under control.
And there's nothing wrong with that!
So don't get cocky, kid!
Sorry, Eren.
We were really on edge.
You're probably disappointed in us.
However, even so...
We'll keep relying on you, and we want you to rely on us...
So... have faith in us.
Eren!
Hurry up! There's no time!
I'll keep running!
Let me go!
I'm sorry!
Target is accelerating!
Don't stop! Keep running!
It's impossible.
We can't outrun it.
If we keep running with our backs to the target,
we'll all be stomped to death!
But...
We're on the brink of death,
but we all chose to continue onward,
even if it meant abandoning our comrades.
Captain Levi isn't looking back.
And the veterans are putting all their faith in him.
I need to believe in them too.
Just like they believed in me!
Fire!
Move a little further ahead and tether your horses,
then switch to 3D Maneuver Gear.
I'll be acting independently for a bit.
Eld, I'm putting you in charge.
Keep Eren hidden an appropriate distance away from that Titan.
Someone take care of my horse.
Could it be...
They're going to capture it alive?
See that Eren? Did you?
We captured that Titan!
This is the strength of the Recon Corps!
Don't underestimate us, stupid!
Now do you see what we can do?
Yes, sir!
Looks like we've immobilized it.
We can't let down our guard just yet,
but good work luring it to this location.
We only managed to buy enough time thanks to the rear guard sacrificing themselves.
This wouldn't have been possible without them.
Is that so?
Indeed.
Thanks to them, we can meet the person inside this thing.
I hope they haven't pissed themselves.
tatoeba ore ga ore ja nai to shite
If we suppose that I am not me
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitai da
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
I broke out of the deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We used to feel like living corpses
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
But now we're breaking out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
Erwin Smith's secret mission—
The capture of the female-form Titan.
The elites of the Recon Corps try to uncover its identity, but...
Erwin Smith
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 4)