Ouch!
On that day, I learned the true meaning behind boxed lunches.
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong.
pure purepare-do
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday.
yudan shitara sono yubi
When your guard is down,
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
be prepared for an attack.
chiisai kedo hasamu no
Even though I'm small,
mijinko mitaina anata
I'll grasp you like a water flea.
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart.
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing.
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing.
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated.
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things.
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss.
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric.
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings.
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy.
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no
I get hurt, I hurt you,
junjou purepara-to
it's a naive preparation.
atama no naka wa
In my mind,
itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade.
The essential points
of boxed lunch
It sure is nice.
Doing things like this.
Guys and gals getting along...
The four of us eating lunch together.
It's just us guys!!!
And there aren't even 4 people here.
And Kitamura-sensei, who organized this, is nowhere to be seen.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Sorry folks!
I went to the student council room to get this.
As you can see, it doesn't fit in the locker.
Say, what exactly is that?
Could it possibly be...?
B-Boxed lunch?
Yes.
And then...
Man, you are amazing!!!
You can't joke about it when you carry that around!
Haruta, it's quite rude to laugh at peoples' boxed lunches.
Wow!
Is this a "half-priced" lunch on sale...
or an all out lunch box??
It's packed with delicious food, you know?
What's all this fuzz about!
I also want to see it.
Minorin!?
What is that!?
Looks like a complete buffet!
What kind of party is this?
The lobster in the middle.
Huh! 39, could it be...?
C-Could it be...
Kitamura
creates
39 PLAN
Creators 39?!!
That's right.
Yuusaku-kun, your grandma made this, right?
Eh!
Your grandma made it for you?
Yeah.
My parents are on a business trip.
So my grandma came to make me this lunch.
This is a hand made lunch!
And it looks great!
As you can see she went all out,
And made this lunch box.
She loves her grandchild.
Her effort makes me really happy,
but she went a little overboard with this.
So, I was thinking that everyone should eat some.
Huh?
Is it all right for us to eat it?
Seriously?
Sure!
I feel bad for your grandma,
All right!
I wonder if the girls would like this one better?
Thank you for the food!
What is this? It's delicious!
Tasty!
As expected of Yuusaku's grandma.
Woah, I have a second stomach for these.
What's wrong? You should eat some as well Takasu.
O-Okay.
T-Then, I'll have this fried chicken.
Hmm?
Taiga...?
What's wrong Aisaka?
Don't hold back.
Then, then I...
I want to eat the lobster.
Man you're something!
What's with the fidgeting!
I was wondering why you're so tense, but now I see you're thinking of eating the main dish!
It doesn't concern you!
Huh! Well, you see...
Come now, come now.
Go ahead.
Absolutely delicious!
The more I chew, the better the lobster tastes.
I feel so happy.
Hey, what about your own lunch?
Of course, I've eaten it already,
but lobster is more important to me.
This lobster is the best ever!
Not only does it look good,
but the taste is perfect too.
Takasu,
can I take a picture of your lunch?
Eh?
I want to show grandma what a normal lunch looks like.
Well I made this in a hurry, and I used all the normal ingredients.
Come on, it's fine!
Ok, thank you Takasu
To think... that this is the best... I could do.
Hey everyone! Please eat some more.
Man, you just can't stop eating lobster after having a taste.
Same goes for crab.
Tasty.
Damn it Yuusaku, I ate too much without thinking.
K-Kawashima.
Say...
Huh? What?
Is Kitamura's grandma...
a chef or does she have a shop or something like that?
Like, is she a pro or something?
That isn't right?
Huh?
I think that she's just a normal housewife.
A normal housewife...
Yeah... I think it was something like that.
By the way, what's her name?
Huh, how would I know something like...?
Whoa, what's with the creepy face!?
Man, I was surprised!
Ah!
I remembered it after seeing your creepy face!
Mio-chan.
Ebidoshi's Mio-chan.
Mio-chan, huh...
Can I see your, "I gave it my all boxed lunch"?
Bring it on granny!
The next round will be the real battle between us, Mio-chan!
Hey, are you all right?
Kitamura-kun!
Let's eat together.
You had your grandma make your lunch today, right?
Yeah, but today's lunch is...
Here,  a double decker lunch.
That's right, it's cheap and it's a breeze to make.
It's also enough to make a highschooler feel full.
We're both following the rules...
This is going to be a fair fight!
Now then...
Hmm? What's wrong?
Ok...
Bring it on, Mio-chan!
Oh, very nice Takasu!
You have pork as a side dish today!
Ah, these are just the leftovers from last night after making some pork cutlet.
I just made it in an instant this morning, and added eggs to it.
Ok, now it's my turn.
Now then, what will happen...?
Did she add some super high quality, rule-breaking ingredient?
Will it be cabier cutlet?
Or some chicken cutlet?
What the...
S-Sure is simple.
I did say that some rice balls would be fine...
It seems that she made it really simple.
This one...
It's too simple and too small to think of it as a lunch for a high schooler.
This match...
No...
That texture of sparkling and brightness is...
TL note: Komabura is a sort of oil
Komabura!
Which means!
Wait a second, that is...
Tasty!
This is grilled meat!
Yes, I'm surprised it has meat in it!!
So, this seaweed is Korean.
Yup, I like this type of lunch!
Oh! This one is pickled plum!
And this is...
Yes!
It's a great finish with a Suanma filling!
I like this one the best!
So, she selected that route!
Huh?
Grilled meat makes one happy,
A pickled plum to follow,
A pickled plum to follow, and then Kitamura's favorite, Sunamayo!
Based on her selections, she's a real housewife.
And compared to that...
I have sweet stock flavor,
this forever continuing flavor...
Ryuuji,
thanks for the meal.
It was tasty, wasn't it?
Yesterday's eggs?
H-Huh. Yes.
I see.
Oh, those rice balls look tasty too.
It'd be nice if we had rice balls for dinner tonight.
I think it was tasty, but after eating pork for 2 days straight, I got tired of it.
I know, but um...
there was a lot of pork, so...I made it without thinking too much.
That's not it...
I was feeling envious of Mio-chan, so I was thinking of making something grand.
But if you want to play by the rules of making the lunch of a high schooler,
you need to include the leftovers from last night.
Yes, I wanted to make a grand lunch,
so I put eggs in the cutlet as I made it to save some pork...
Those who take on the road of becoming a house-wife,
Must think about what to cook day after day.
I almost went overboard last night, but I've realized my position!
Wahhh!!! Mio!!!
You ditched the honorifics for my grandma's name!
Super market: EGORO
Boxed lunch...
Snacks
Chocolate
Desserts
Boxed lunch...
Discount
What should I make?!!
What can I add to make it better...
Boxed lunch...
Say, what're we going to be using as fillings for the rice balls?
We need salmon for sure.
Ah?
But not the salted one, just the plain salmon...
Ah! Rice balls!!
Do you think I have a chance of winning by making the same lunch as Kitamura?
Eh, well, I meant dinner not lunch.
That is secondary.
I had confidence in my skills as a housewife.
I also had pride.
Huh?
But, in the end, that was just me, a high schooler.
Even if I made it to the top, I can't beat someone with such a varied skill set like that.
I was just at the mouth of the river.
Then I was dragged down to the the deep sea,
and was eaten by a shark named Kitamura Mio!
Hm, this dried seaweed will be good as well.
Hey, what're you doing?
Huh? What are you saying? I'm actually buying stuff instead of barking like a dog.
What do you mean "buying stuff"?
All you have here are some snacks and pudding.
What's wrong with you? I have some nutritious foods as well.
That is desert!
Did you know, if you put salt on pudding it'll taste better?
That kind of thinking is too old, and you're also a bit off the mark!
Oh, was I?
I don't have time for this!
I know!
Something that a frog has and a shark doesn't!
That is...
Youth!
Oh! Huh?
Oi, Taiga!
Say, have you seen Kitamura...
Hey, you should pour it 5 mm below the marker line!
No more, no less.
It'll be full soon, almost there...
Shut your trap.
You always tell me not to eat this kind of food and now you're lecturing me!
Are you making Cup Noodles?
Ah Minorin.
You even have a thermo-flask!
Man, that's so cool!
You guys just seem like a two man uncle-sam!
What is it?!!
Are you eating Cup Noodles for lunch?
It feels good, I'm tired of cold lunches.
That smells nice.
Seems tasty!
It might be normal to eat this at home, but eating it in the classroom is new.
It'll make the everyday lunch a fun-filled event.
Kitamura's grandma doesn't have a sense of youth.
Today's match is mine.
Minorin, want to eat with me?
Well, we have a club meeting during lunch break.
Yo yo, Kitamura man!
Let's get rollin' man!
Sorry.
Y-Yo Kitamura, I overslept by accident so...
I'm eating Cup Noodles today.
Does that mean you have hot water?
Y-Yeah...
Then let me have some as well.
Man, you saved me!
My grandma had gave me a Cup Noodles.
There must be some students eating Cup Noodles, right??!
Just make them give you some hot water.
I thought, no way, but...
The timing was perfect
Today I'm having this and sandwiches.
Seems perfect for today's meeting.
Kitamura-kun!
I'll be right there Kushieda.
Let's go!
Well then later, okay.
Hey.
A sandwich sounds good too.
Then don't eat it.
Huh?
No, on second thought, don't eat this!
Hey you!
What are you doing?
You shouldn't!  I said no!  You shouldn't!
I wonder what they're doing.
Didn't you say that Cup Noodles doesn't have enough calcium for your body?
Visit us at #Hadena@irc.rizon.net  or   http://www.facebook.com/HadenaFansubs
It's hot!
Here you are!
It doesn't have...
Nothing at all.
So now that you've seen...
A different plate has it all!
Thank you Minorin!
Hey, no need to thank me.
If this isn't enough, don't hold back, just tell me.
I'll give you more, a lot more!
And I'll bring it to you.
OK!
I never thought you'd eat again after eating all of that in school.
I won't fill up on Cup Noodles!
I got tired of eating that as well.
I'm fine with Ryuuji's everyday lunch box...
He might be thinking of something weird.
Oh Taiga, you're such a pitiful woman!
You became unable to live on without eating Takasu Ryuuji's daily handmade meals, right?
W-W-What!!
Come on now.
Food is essential for everything.
It can't be helped if he's making you a meal.
Well then, take your time.
Lunch boxes, huh?
No,
this isn't right.
Not at all!
This isn't right at all.
What's all this? It looks like a party.
Looks so tasty.
But I can't eat this much.
Ah, what about Taiga-chan?
Don't know.
Ah, can I take it to the shop?
Yaigai-san's wife ran away from home.
He'll be really happy.
Your cooking's incredibly delicious.
I'm off!
Guess I'll eat dinner as well.
What's with her?
If she's at home, she could just come over to eat.
She might be angry about this afternoon's incident.
Like I can keep looking after her.
I'll make the best lunch-box and defeat Kitamura's grandmother.
I don't care what it takes.
For instance,
Put some curry inside rice ball.
Put raw fish in cooler box and and make a fresh rice and fish bowl!
Or small monaccos...
Hey, don't put in background voices like you are eating food scraps!
O... One more.
Are you going to eat more?!!
Not that...
Food scraps...
These are leftovers.
The leftovers are mixed with eggs, so they aren't very appealing.
Well then...
There can't be anything more fresher than this.
A freshly made steaming...
I see, that is it!
That'll be perfect!
Cheating now are we?  Oh, I don't mind Inko-chan, say whatever you like.
Inzagi!
Well whatever.
Philippines.
Inzagi...
That's right, I don't mind cheating.
I'm going to win this battle!
Hot! Hot! This is hot!
The Hayabusa Bullet Train debuted on March 5th on the Tohoku Shinkansen Line.
Thrilling rail fans and the people living in northern...
Hmm.
This smell...
What's this...?
This is...
The sound is...
No, it can't  be...
No way it would be that...
But...
Huh... Rice cooker...
Seriously?!!
Rice cooker?
No way!
But it smells good.
What a tasty smell.
I got hungry.
Then, why did you do something like this?
Takasu-kun...
Takasu?!
Come on Taka-chan, don't go cooking a warm meal in class.
This is something!
Everyone wait a sec!
Please wait teacher!
Why'd you think that the culprit is me?
To jump to such a conclusion is...
Well, who else would think of such a thing?
This is bad!
I understand.
I'm the criminal here.
Please forgive me, teacher!
Please don't do that!
Soon, it'll be done very soon!
Please don't be so cruel!
What...what in the world?!
Idiot!
It's over!
Such a waste!
You could just put the switch back, and you might be able to do something with it.
The flavor will be different.
So, what if the flavor is different? It still would have fallen short.
This autumn is also short.
Mai-take, hira-take, and lots of bamboo sprouts.
Huh!?
I thought I had a chance at winning if it were a freshly made meal.
But that wouldn't be a boxed lunch anymore.
I know.
Breaking the rule I made...
And because I cheated I lost the war.
There's no such thing.
You self-destructed all on your own.
Here.
I thought of making this, since I had a feeling that I wouldn't get anything decent to eat for today's lunch as well.
I didn't try too hard.
I'll let you eat it.
These are...
Did you make them?
By yourself?
Don't make fun of me.
I can make it if it's just rice balls.
You showed me how to make them.
Hot!
Hot meals are a dangerous weapon!
Have some patience,
It's a no go if the rice isn't made into a ball while it's hot.
Look
Hot!
What?
I didn't want to give it to someone who doesn't need them.
I'll have some.
Thanks for the meal.
How is it?
Huh, what are you doing?
Shaking in excitement?
Salty!
If we put stock in it...
The saltiness will go away.
Hurry up!
Well, wait just a second.
We have to add the wild chervil.
Here.
Diggin in!
Hey, take it easy!
Tasty!
This is the best!
There is just an accent of the flavor of rice balls.
I'm a genius!
I see.
That's how it is.
Me a genius?
Yup,
Apart from the boxed lunch from that time.
No, that too.
Mio-chan's boxed lunches were stiffs to make Kitamura happy.
Onigiri was something she made by taking Kitamura's request.
And gave him the soup knowing he'll be in the meeting at lunchtime.
All of it fits Kitamura point of view.
And on the other hand I was...
Thanks for the meal!
You're the one who eats my boxed lunches.
What?
What're you saying?
Man, I'm a lot hungrier after eating just a little!
I want to eat more.
I think pork cutlet sounds good.
Pork cutlet lightly browned!
Eating pork cutlet in a middle class family?!!
Ah, we still have a bit of left over meat though.
That's it!
Mirphi pork cutlet!
I think it's cooked with warm rice, it'll be nice too.
We can eat it with the side dishes.
Looks like I have no other choice here.
Aren't you going to use the rice balls?
Ah, I don't mind eating it that way.
I was surprised back then but,
It's not like you can't eat them.
Hm...
Aren't you saying something rude?
Eh, not at all!
No it was rude!
That's why you should put cheese in between the pork cutlet.
What!
I got the essential point of boxed lunches!
It's for someone.
Making lunch while keeping someone in mind...
It would be delicious no matter what's inside.
Banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
Amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet.
Dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else,
so I want to disclose myself.
shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
Demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
Modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
Demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different...
Watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for.
"Shiro" to iwaretara "Kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black.
Sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself.
"Suki" to iwaretara "Daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you.
Ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
Amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla.