Hey, wanna go shopping this weekend?
Yeah, sure!
Reunion. Good day to you.
Hello.
Rechallenge. Have you re-evaluated your situation and decided to battle yet?
Doubt. Are you scared of losing?
Warning.
You cannot escape this battle.
For memories everything is given life
for memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Tell me of enigmas and fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Die memory, if only I could see you
die memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurisaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Selector
Honey and Poison
Hey.
You're about to hit a time limit.
If you don't do something, you're going to lose a coin.
I know.
You need to battle.
I know that. But if I lose...
There's a Selector.
Where?
In front of you.
Found ya!
Hi, girl! You're a Selector, right?
Yeah.
Shou-chan, Shou-chan! This girl's a Selector!
Wanna battle?
Come on, do her a favor.
Wait, are you just ignoring me again?
Um...
Sorry, Shou-chan's not really one for battle.
What does that mean?
It's his principle or something.
But...
I intend to run away from every battle until the final limit.
There you go again.
Can you... really do that?
I plan to.
Why don't you hit up a card shop?
There might be other Selectors there.
Maybe you'll be able to figure something out.
Later!
Could it be that you're relieved
you didn't have to battle?
I wasn't thinking that.
There's nowhere to run.
I know.
He's late again...
Dinner time.
Oh, yeah. Do you ever eat, Ril?
I don't.
That's too bad. Food tastes the best
when you eat it over conversation.
Do you think I should go to the card shop after school tomorrow?
Good idea.
You might be able to find some information.
You think so too?
Yeah, that's right.
What's wrong?
You've been silent this entire time.
I guess it's because I'm kind of scared.
A word of advice.
Sure, what?
You shouldn't be afraid to act.
It's the same in battle. Your opponent will take advantage of that weakness.
Yeah...
We'll be fine if we're together.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
See? We did it perfectly!
Y-Yeah.
Now let's try going to that postbox.
Do you think we can make it?
If we're together, we'll be fine.
Okay!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
It really was fine because we were together!
See?
Oh, crap. I'm out of Ener.
Is there another one here, Ril?
Yeah? Does that mean I win?
Then I'll attack!
Yeah, the person in the far back.
Him?
Yes, he's a Selector.
You're a Selector, aren't you?
I am.
Would you have a battle with me?
Man, this month's column got rave reviews again.
The survey results weren't half bad either.
Delightful. I'm happy about that.
I guess you owe it all to actually playing the game yourself, Hanna-chan.
Naturally.
I would think that is normal.
Nah, not so much as you'd think.
There are plenty who only know the basics.
So, has anything caught your eye as the next big thing?
Multitudes. I may eventually be able to write about them in a column.
Well, I'll be looking forward to it then!
Can you battle me?
Sudden.
I have no time!
We'll be fine.
Yeah...
Is something the matter?
No.
Then let's begin.
Open!
Take a deep breath.
Okay.
I'll introduce you. My LRIG's name is Aaya.
I'm happy-happy to meet you!
Same here.
Let's start already!
Sure, it's about to begin.
His LRIG sure is cute.
You shouldn't judge a book by its cover.
Onii-chan, let's boomy-boom her up!
Okay. Aaya, Grow!
I summon Browcra and end my turn!
Ril, what should I do?
Let's attack all-out from the onset.
Okay. Grow, and I summon Nohime!
Attack!
She's pretty good.
Onii-chan, don't take her lightly!
Yeah. I won't, Aaya.
It's hard for me to oppose those eyes.
Onii-chan!
Aaya thinks the best way to deal with girls like her is to crush 'em quick!
Whatever you say. Aaya, Grow.
I set Comrus on the field.
I also play an Arts, Trip Trap. Banish Sha Wuji!
Ril?!
Suzuko, don't hold back.
Okay!
Come on, let's get started already.
Impatience. At least introduce yourself.
I already told you that I'm out of time!
Impatience. That will only lead to your downfall.
Introduction. My name is Mikage Hanna.
Mikage Hanna... you're that female high school game writer?
Correct. I'm impressed you were aware.
Shit, this is the worst...
I knew I should've asked the Bookmaker.
Bookmaker...
I'll tell you about him if you beat me!
Open!
Ril, summon Akechi!
Then I use the spell Ark of Fighting Spirit
to search my deck for an Odanobu!
Aaya, let's use it.
Sure!
Coin Bet!
Holograph!
Team Aaya...
Takes the stage! Thanks for the love, Onii-chan!
Aaya, you're so cute.
Just the cutest!
Gross.
Thanks, Onii-chan!
Which should I target?
Right! The right one!
Too bad!
You missed!
Pointless attack!
What a waste!
Aaya, that's the way.
"Even if I lose today, I'll still have a coin left."
Huh?
You shouldn't be going "huh?" at this point.
Don't you understand anything?
If you lose now, it'll be the end of you.
That's right... at this rate, I'll be the one to end her.
Stop it... don't look at me with those eyes.
The hell're you doing?! Get your shit together!
Right... Sorry, Aaya.
You don't have the skills to let up for a single turn!
Come on, just kick her ass already!
All right, already.
Honeytra!
Hiyaa!
Suzuko!
Coin Bet!
Honest!
Narumi-san, which is the real Aaya-san?
The middle one, but why should I have to tell you that?
What?! Why the hell did you tell her that, you dumbass—
I'm sorry, Aaya! Are you okay?
Ow... Does it look like I'm okay, you jerk?!
We'll be fine. We can do this if we're together, Suzuko.
Yeah!
Don't make me laugh.
You'll never win if all you can do is preach!
Yeah, that's right, Aaya.
You can try, and try, and try all you want and still not win.
I'll make you know what that feels like!
Destruct Through!
Ril!
I'm fine...
But...
Keep going.
Ril...
I made her cry... what should I do?
Huh?
I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't do it, Aaya!
I can't make her cry!
This again?
Look at how much pain she's in.
This is no different from tearing out the feathers of a fragile chick—I can't do that!
I can't!
Don't piss yourself! Are you retarded?!
That girl isn't your fucking sister, you siscon bastard!
Scoop out your eyes and take a good look!
Or what?! Are they so rotten you can't see a thing?!
Suzuko.
Let's go.
Okay.
I play three SIGNI and cast an Arts!
Perfected Firedrake!
All-out attack!
Aaya!
Onii-chan, are you okay?
She must've reminded you of your little sister.
But that's no good. Your little sister is now Aaya, and that's me.
Yeah...
Excuse me...
You really do remind me of her.
Of who?
Onii-chan's little sister.
I do?
That's why whenever he battles girls like you,
it always flips his sadness switch.
My sister disappeared.
Dammit, I'll use a coin!
Predict.
Well now, I wonder what power she has.
Haven't you ever heard of the phrase "haste makes waste"?
Commence. Next is our turn.
What's this now? You must be rather confident to reveal your draws, Hanna-sama.
Compulsory. They flipped on their own.
I assume it's her ability.
Oh? In that case, this matchup is good for us.
Nihokokabi and Parain.
Okay, and if she plays those cards, then I just need to stop her with my Arts.
Coin Bet.
Blind.
What a surprise. I cannot see them.
Is this defensive? Or an attack?
Hanna-sama, you're such a demon.
Not to mention how utterly starved your opponent was for information.
What now? Should we just take the hit?
I do not know. I will only do as you instruct.
Then we'll take it!
Understood.
I will attack now.
Disappeared?
Please wait! What do you mean?
My sister, Aya...
Huh? Aya?
Isn't it disgusting? He named me after his sister.
A few months ago, Aya was chosen to be a Selector.
But back then, I was busy with college work.
Onii-chan, have you heard of Selectors?
Nope.
I'm a Selector now.
So what's a Selector?
It's, well—
Sorry, Aya. I'm kind of in a hurry.
Tell me about it later.
S-Sure.
Hey, Onii-chan. Do you have a minute?
Sorry, I've got to get this report done by tomorrow.
I see.
What, is something wrong?
Yeah.
I lost again.
I'm running out of coins.
Coins? Didn't you say you could
get them back by winning?
Yeah...
Do your best.
Sure.
Not only did I handwave all her concerns,
I never once gave her a serious response.
Aya, you were talking about that whole Selector thing the other day.
How's that going?
If only I had listened to her earnestly,
I wouldn't have this many regrets.
What a letdown. In the end,
it's just for your own sake.
That might be the case.
Hanna-sama, shall we be putting her to rest soon?
Agreement. I'll do just that.
Wait!
Just wait. If I lose now, then I'll disappear!
So just wait!
Reject. Would you not hit your time limit either way?
I still have a bit of time left.
Please, I'm begging you!
There's someone I need to see before I disappear!
Please—
Summon Oigona.
Wait... wait, hold on!
Please, I don't want to disappear!
Lose to me!
Irrational. Reject.
You want me to endanger myself for your sake?
Can you say what benefits that would confer to me?
You... You won't disappear even if you lose today!
Obvious. Those are the rules of this battle.
Sickness Love.
Do you know the true meaning of what it means to disappear?
Huh?
Oh? Are you trying to atone for some of your sins by telling her that?
Enough.
The true meaning?
What are you talking about?
Question. There is something I would
like to inquire of you right away.
I believe you mentioned a bookmaker...
When they say "disappear",
they don't just mean losing your memories.
Your identity itself disappears.
No way... that's what you meant by disappear?
Then I was chosen to be a Selector.
At first, I thought that I could search for where Aya had disappeared to.
But... it's impossible now.
I can't afford to do it.
I shouldn't have underestimated this.
Everyone is desperate not to disappear.
People go so far as to hurt others, push them off the brink, or try to buy victory with money.
You should just do that then, Onii-chan.
These days, there have even been times
when I've wanted to disappear myself.
No way!
Hey, Ril.
Is what he said true?
Were you deceiving me?
I didn't intend to.
Liar! I won't just lose my memories,
I'll lose everything about me!
You never told me what disappearing really meant!
You never asked.
How am I supposed to recognize Chii-chan
if I ever get to see her again?!
Horrible... it's too horrible...
Save me, Chii-chan...
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
You pull back your tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no da
And I can no longer remember
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
Bookmaker?
It seems like there's someone who will book Selector battles for you.
Won't you bet your worries on me?
Chii-chan is a Selector?
Homura Suzuko and Morikawa Chinatsu.
You're Chii-chan, right?
I'm glad we met again.
Next time: Reunion / Illumination and Chaos.
Reunion
Illumination and Chaos