Class 5-4
Hinazuki Kayo
To hell...
Mom...
Kayo!
Where were you these past few days?!
You little...
You two!
I should've known you were involved!
How could you take away someone else's child?!
You got me needlessly concerned!
You'd better prepare to hear from my lawyer!
Did you look for Kayo at all over the past three days?
What? You're trying to paint me as the bad guy here?
Go to hell!
Kayo?! Let go of me, you idiot!
"Needlessly concerned"?
The only thing you're concerned about is yourself.
What?!
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
Dammit!
What do you think you're doing, Kayo?!
Let go!
You're disobeying me?!
Stop it, Ms. Hinazuki.
Kayo doesn't want to see you like this either.
You stop it!
You're treating me like a villain in front of my own daughter!
And after you kidnapped her, no less! Who the hell do you think you are?!
Shut up! We did it because you're the kind of mother who locks her child in the shed
and doesn't care if she goes missing for three days!
You have no idea about the pains and responsibilities of parenting,
so don't run your mouth, you snot-nosed brat!
You—
You're Ms. Hinazuki Akemi, yes?
We're from Ishikari City Hall's Child Welfare Center.
We've come to discuss your daughter, Kayo, with you.
You set me up,
you sickos!
It seemed we couldn't get you to meet us by ourselves,
so we asked Ms. Fujinuma for help.
Who said I wouldn't meet you?
Oh, my apologies.
Sorry we asked you to do this.
Don't be, Mr. Yashiro.
I wanted to give her a piece of my mind,
so I'm actually glad to be of help.
They're the ones who kidnapped my daughter!
Hurry up and call the police!
No, we first need to discuss your habitual treatment of your child.
What're you even talking about?
What's wrong with how I treat Kayo?
We've decided that your daughter, Kayo, needs to be taken into custody.
Custody?! I'm her legal custodian!
But you didn't even look for her
when she went missing for three days.
That's child negligence.
But it was all that brat's fault!
Why am I being treated like a criminal?!
Now, now, Ms. Hinazuki.
Please calm down.
Fine, then!
I'll go to the police myself!
If it's a fight you want, you've got one!
Come, Kayo!
W-Wait, Ms. Hinazuki!
That won't do.
Please calm down!
M-Mr. Yashiro...
Come on!
Quit dragging your feet!
Kayo!
I said come on!
Akemi.
Akemi, my girl.
Mom...
Forgive me.
We've been estranged ever since I
made you break up with that man,
but I've been worried about you and Kayo ever since.
I know better than anyone how hard it is for a single mother to raise a child.
You must've been so lonely.
It must've been so hard on you.
I should've helped you.
But I made you...
Divorce Application
shoulder it all yourself.
This is all my fault.
Please don't think badly of Akemi!
Mom...
Mom!
Those tears were probably borne out of self-pity.
Lacking the kind of mother she could cling to and cry,
Kayo looked away from the one she did have.
Akemi, my girl.
Don't worry about Kayo.
I promise to take good care of her.
My child is the most important thing in my life.
He means the world to me.
I'm sure you must've felt the same way at some point.
Thanks, Mr. Yashiro.
No need.
You're the one who got us to act.
There's no way we could let your
courageous efforts end in tragedy.
Kayo will be all right now.
I hardly have any memories of my own father,
but I wonder if this is how a father's words sound.
Thanks, Satoru.
For getting me out of here.
Shall we go, then?
"The Town With Only Me Erased," by Hinazuki Kayo.
When I grow older, old enough to go wherever I want by myself,
I want to go a faraway country.
I want to go to a faraway island.
I want to go to an island with nobody around.
I want to go to an island with no sorrow or suffering.
Thank you for dinner!
Next time, I'd love to cook with you.
Kayo
On that island, I'll climb trees when I want,
swim in the ocean when I want,
and sleep when I want.
When I think about the town from which I've been erased, I feel lighthearted.
I want to go far, far away.
I finally managed to save Kayo.
I made sure her life would last far into the future.
From here on, Kayo will walk down her own path.
I believe that the future she heads toward will be a bright one.
Episode 9
Closure
Satoru's been like this all day. Is he gonna be okay?
He looked like a hero until savin' Hinazuki, but now...
Hey, Satoru. Are you all right?
Yep, I'm fine.
You don't look fine at all.
Can ya blame him? Hinazuki's gone.
Yeah.
All's well that ends well, though.
Satoru.
Come with me for a sec.
Staff Room
I think Kayo's mother will have to
stay away from her for a few years.
Which means Kayo's going to start a new life with her grandmother.
Thank you, Mr. Yashiro.
Oh, no need for—
That's not what I'm talking about.
You said you couldn't let my
courageous efforts end in tragedy.
Those words mean a lot to me right now.
Well, I felt your actions merited a reward,
though calling it that might be trivializing it a bit.
Didn't you want to see Kayo smile?
Looks like I get my reward as well.
By the way, Satoru. Was Kayo at your place the entire time?
No, at a hideout.
A hideout?
Yeah.
We hid Kayo in a bus that the Izumi Grade
School hockey team wasn't using anymore.
So only kidnappers like you would think to go there, huh?
Y-Yeah...
If that's a joke, it ain't funny.
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Now that Kayo's gone, the killer's targets are down to Hiromi and Nakanishi Aya.
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Right now, what I have to do is
make sure they aren't left alone.
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (11 y.o.)
Just like with Kayo.
Hiromi's one thing, cause he's my classmate,
but it'll be hard to approach Nakanishi Aya, who goes to the nearby Izumi Grade School.
Apparently she often hangs out with Mr. Yuuki, but how am I supposed to talk to her?
She has no clue who I am.
This is going to be pretty difficult.
How to become friends with someone you don't know?
Just go right at 'em and ask them to be your friend.
As if that'd work—
You're thinkin', "As if that'd work," ain'tcha?
Is she psychic?
You've already got Kayo, but your eyes are wanderin', eh?
H-How did you know that?
It was just a bluff.
Well, okay, it is a girl.
She's always by herself.
You won't get anywhere with that pessimistic mindset.
Just focus on a positive outcome.
As they say, nothin' ventured, nothin' gained.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
I need to drop by someplace.
You guys are going to the children's center, right?
Yeah.
I'll meet you there, then.
Ta-ta.
Ta-ta!
With Mr. Yuuki by the river
Hamanasu Cram School
So she gets out of cram school at 6:30 PM.
I should be able to walk Hiromi home and still get back in time.
First, I need to get a handle on their daily routine.
With Hiromi and Kenya at the Children's Center
Parted with Hiromi and Kenya
Followed Nakanishi Aya after Cram School
Nakanishi Aya's daily routine was simple.
If she were to be abducted, it'd most likely happen at this time, right after her cram school lets out.
Satoru!
Am I ever glad to see you! Help me out 'ere!
Way to show up right when I was going to follow her and find out where she lived!
Why would you buy so much stuff at once?
What could I do? It was on sale.
Too heavy...
Don't say it out loud. It'll only make it feel heavier.
It'll be just as heavy if I keep my mouth shut!
You're a lifesaver, Mr. Yashiro.
Mom went crazy shopping.
Don't call me crazy!
Say, Mr. Yashiro...
Why won't you get married?
Wh-Where did that come from?
Listen, Satoru.
You can only get married if you have someone to marry.
And then they need to be ready for it,
and the time has to be right for both of you...
It's complicated.
No, maybe I'm being overly cautious 'cause I've been through a painful experience once before.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it. I didn't mind answering that question.
Actually, there's something else I wanted to ask you.
How to approach a girl you don't know?
Yeah. I know her, but she doesn't know me.
Well, I'm the cautious type,
so I'd start by making her less wary of me, even if it meant beating around the bush.
Make her less wary?
Yeah.
In other words, show off your good side.
Like, if you're good at sports or cooking.
Use whatever you can.
The moment she takes an interest in it,
she'll let her guard down.
Don't be so impressed.
I'm not good at expressing my feelings in a
straightforward manner, so I just rely on logic.
Something's sticking out.
Don't touch that, Satoru!
I-I'm sorry—
This is...
So you saw, Satoru.
Candy?
Now that you've seen it, no point in hiding it anymore!
You eat some too! Become my accomplice!
Ever since I quit smoking three years ago,
I've gotten hooked on candy to satisfy the cravings.
I can't relax in private without it.
Wh-What a weirdo.
Thanks.
Gimme one too.
Here.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
I'm gonna go do my homework at the children's center.
Okay.
Wait, Hiromi. I'll go with you.
First Hinazuki, and now it's like you're Hiromi's guardian too.
Y-You think?
Can we talk in private, Satoru?
Sure.
Sorry, Hiromi.
I'll join you later.
Got it.
What's really on your mind, Satoru?
I've seen first-hand your resolve
to save Hinazuki no matter what,
but even though it went well,
now there's something off about you.
If something's bothering you, could you tell me about it?
I can't explain it too well. It's too far-fetched.
I wanna dig deep and take a step forward, like you.
I wanna become a hero too.
If you're still on that wild ride, take me with you.
What do you make of these footprints, Kenya?
An adult came and went once.
Not just that. Take a closer look.
I think they had their shoes wrapped in cloth.
It wasn't to prevent them from slipping, was it?
Probably to avoid leaving distinctive footprints.
The backpack is gone.
So's the box with the briquette.
I think there are fewer boxes in general.
A lot of torn up cartons, too.
Somebody must've taken only the contents with them.
What's your point, Satoru?
Do you remember the man who supposedly
showed up late at night when Kayo was here?
Yeah.
The guy who left a dangerous-looking backpack here, right?
I'm pretty sure that guy's a murderer who's going after children.
What are you even talking about, Satoru?
I know that this sounds unbelievable.
What makes you so sure?
I can't give you a proper explanation right now.
But when I saw the contents of
the backpack and the briquette,
it made me think this was where a serial killer kept his tools.
Even I know that it sounds crazy.
But that's how I feel.
And since it's all over, I'll tell you now:
the whole Kayo thing?
Preventing her mother's abuse was only part of it.
I also wanted to protect her from this murderer.
That's why I didn't want to leave her alone.
Satoru...
Are you hoping to become a detective or novelist when you grow up?
The key here isn't whether your
scenario is too far-fetched or not.
It's whether I believe you or not.
You don't have to walk me all the way home. I'll be fine.
I'm a guy, you know.
It's fine.
I had something to do here, anyway.
Satoru...
What?
I want to believe in you too.
I'll do everything I can,
so tell me if you ever need help, okay?
Of course.
Later.
Ta-ta!
See you tomorrow!
Honestly, Satoru, 99% of me thinks
your theory couldn't possibly be true.
But the other 1% thinks it's not completely out of the question.
Yeah.
From the outside, it probably looks like I'm playing detective, making up crimes that don't even exist—
Playing detective is fine by me.
It might be because of what's been happening lately,
but I feel like your train of thought
will definitely lead to something good.
You believed in me and gave me your side of the story.
So I want to do my part and believe in you too.
So I want to believe you for my own sake.
It's like someone wanting to be believed, but with roles reversed.
Thanks, Kenya.
Thanks, Hiromi.
I could've saved her!
Eighteen years ago, I think I said
those words to my mother and cried.
I never want to go through that again.
I won't leave anybody alone.
I can save them!
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Remember to get your parents to fill out that handout!
Okay!
I want you to come with me somewhere.
Satoru, what say we hit up the hideout now?
Sorry. We've got something to do.
See you later, then.
Ta-ta.
Oh, okay.
Ta-ta...
What're they sneakin' around for?
They're no fun.
Wanna follow them, then?
Sure.
Let's go!
Okay!
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory