Cat Killing Chapter
furimuita sono ushiro no shoumen daare?
I looked back behind me; who’s there?
kurayami ni tsume wo tatete yoru wo hikisaita
In the pitch dark, I raised my claws and slashed apart the night.
amadare wa chi no shizuku to natte hoho wo tsutai ochiru
The raindrops turn into droplets of blood and travel down my cheeks.
mou doko ni mo kaeru basho ga nai nara
If there’s no place for me to return to anymore...
kono yubi tomare watashi no yubi ni
Take these fingers, my fingers...
sono yubi goto tsuretette ageru
I’ll take you away with that finger.
higurashi ga naku akazu no mori e
To the sealed forest where cicadas cry...
atomodori wa mou dekinai
I can’t turn back anymore.
Kei-chan.
Since you have less than ten coins...
...if someone now bets the max of ten coins...
...it means you will automatically have to fold.
In other words...
...no matter how good your hand is...
...we can bring you down by force.
Keiichi?
Today's punishment game is a grand march around the village wearing pretty clothes.
So I'm sure Keiichi will end up being forced to wear school swimsuits, garter belts...
...corsets and maid outfits!
Bingo!
A three of a kind and a joker!
That means a four of a kind!
You'll be forced to parade around the village...
...while blushing and fidgeting awkwardly!
Rena.
The amount you won from me just now...
Could you lend me around ten coins of it...?
I won't.
A battle is ruthless.
Damn...
It takes a true club member to turn the game around at this point!
You understand very well.
But what are you planning to do?
I-I...
To make up for the coins I'm short...
...I'm thinking of betting something other than coins.
How about it?
Do you accept that?
I figured you'd suggest this.
So?
What will you bet in exchange for the amount you're short?
I'll wear a school swimsuit, a garter belt and a miniskirt maid outfit for you...
...and allow you to take me home!
And how about I clean your ears as well!?
I like it, Kei-chan!
The guts to bet your body for the amount you're short.
I like it!
Somehow Mii's face is bright red.
I'm sure she's imagining being alone in her room with Keiichi...
- Is this the spot, Mion?
- Yes, right there!
...with her head pillowed on his lap, blushing and squealing!
- Does it feel good?
- It's amazing...
I-I-I'm not thinking about that!
A-As club president...
...I'm just genuinely enjoying this game!
If it means I can take Keiichi-kun home, I won't lose!
So how about it?
Is this enough of a substitute for the coins I'm short?
It's plenty.
More than plenty.
You don't need to pay any coins.
Having you clean our ears while we pillow our heads on your lap is worth ten coins.
All right!
So the game is on, right?
Don't be too shocked when you see my cards!
Get a load of this!
Four of a kind!
Looks like the goddess of victory fell in love with me!
Let's move on!
I want to play, but...
All right!
In that case, if I lose next time, I'll become an apron maid...
...and make the winner dinner and desserts!
I guess!
My!
I can't fold with this hand either.
In that case, I'll add ten coins...
...as well as the right for the winner to have me feed them lunch in an outfit of choice!
In that case, I'll bet ten coins...
...and add in the right to put a collar around my neck and walk me like a dog!
S-Seriously!?
This has gotten pretty interesting!
The spirit of betting risky stuff over coins!
I love it!
Of course you will bet something too, won't you, Mion?
Let's see now...
Then I'll dress up in whatever way the winner wants me to...
...and do their homework for them.
Well?
Having Mion-san do my math drills isn't too bad.
No!
I will win and take all of you home!
Shut up, shut up!
I will win!
And then I'll enslave everyone and have them do this and that for me...
Keiichi, your drool is overflowing.
The battle is on!
Huh?
In the end...
...everyone kept winning and losing at the game...
...until all of us ended up having to walk around the village cosplaying.
What was that game about?
There was no single winner...
...so everyone just ended up being the loser?
Fighting brings forth nothing.
Where do we go next?
Where?
This road leads to the Fukudaya's.
Or do we go that way, to Takatsudo?
Or Yagouchi?
I've never been to Yagouchi.
What kind of place is it?
There are no houses in Yagouchi.
It's a very lonesome place.
Then it's decided!
Let's go there!
I don't want to run into any more villagers!
Well, if you insist...
...I guess we can go check it out.
I feel like taking a walk.
All right, let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
I guess I have no choice...
I...
...think it's better if we don't go there.
There really is nothing here.
Are there people living here?
In the past.
This place has been deserted for ages.
There are barely any lights around here...
...and there are rumors about wild dogs appearing when it's pitch dark at night.
We should probably go back now.
You're right.
If we get lost in such ridiculous outfits...
...it will become an embarrassing story talked about for seven generations to come.
You can say that again.
There's nothing beyond this point anyway, is there?
There's a quarry site on the backside of that mountain.
A quarry?
It belonged to a cement company.
They went bankrupt quite a while ago, so it's deserted now.
A deserted quarry site deep in a lonesome mountain range?
That sounds pretty interesting!
Don't go there!
Good kids shouldn't go near the quarry.
That's right.
It's even written in our summer vacation guidebook not to get close to that place.
It's male instinct to want to sneak in there even more after hearing that.
There might just be...
...a mountain of treasure rivaling the size of the one at the dam site!
A new mountain of treasure!
Then I wanna go too!
I don't really recommend going there.
They say there's a pit there.
A pit?
What's that about?
I've heard stories about the pit as well.
But are they true?
I think it's best not to get close to the pit.
Mii-chan, what is this pit, I wonder?
Ah, right.
You and Kei-chan haven't heard about it, have you?
They say two people died there.
It's sort of a ghost story.
A ghost story?
I remember it as if it were yesterday.
Whenever I think it could have been me who fell into the pit...
...I get really scared.
You?
It was around six or seven years ago.
The dam war was still going strong back then.
The children were playing normally in the fields and mountains like they do now.
Then one day...
...the company owning the quarry went bankrupt.
The kindhearted company president was tricked...
...into accepting a position of co-signer for his employees.
They slipped out en masse.
Didn't that president commit a family suicide?
He killed his wife and young child in a prefab office at the quarry...
...then poured himself in kerosine and barbecued himself alive.
Huh?
But didn't Rika-chan just say that only two people died?
According to that story, three people died.
Sorry about that.
These three don't count for the pit story.
Anyway, due to this suicide...
...the quarry was closed down and deserted.
The president's vengeful apparition is still roaming about the site of the suicide...
...or so the rumor went.
Wouldn't such a rumor be immensely interesting to children?
Certainly.
And so we ended up going there.
You all went there?
I've never been there.
We were still really small.
We ended up playing kick-the-can with a can we happened to find lying around.
No one really paid it any mind...
...but there was a strange smell in the air since we entered the quarry.
It smells...
It smelled?
How should I put it...
It smelled like rotten eggs.
Rotten eggs...?
Sulfur?
Yes, that's it!
Wouldn't you normally only smell sulfur near a crater?
Did the smell come from the quarry?
No idea...
But the smell soon stopped bothering me.
We continued playing kick-the-can...
Found Takashi!
You found me!
Suddenly, some man looking like quarry personnel appeared out of nowhere...
...and came running in an incredibly threatening manner.
You fucking brats!
This ain't no place to be screwing around!
Get the fuck out of here!
In the end...
...everyone fled the site...
...and ended up separated.
What?
It didn't end with that, did it?
No.
What's up, Mii-chan?
There was one boy...
...who never returned home.
He never returned...?
After being yelled at by that man, we scattered out and went home separately, so we couldn't tell.
But by that time...
...he had probably already disappeared.
Does that mean...
He was hit by Oyashiro-sama's curse, and demoned away...
...or so people say.
Demoned away?
A ghost story of sorts here in Hinamizawa.
A ghost story, huh?
That boy's parents called everyone of us...
...but there wasn't a single kid that went home from the quarry with him.
So what happened?
His father speculated he might have gotten into an accident on his way home...
...so he decided to go to the quarry by car.
So did he find him?
On the contrary...
The father never returned either.
If I remember correctly...
...the car the father and his son were in...
...was found in a valley along the road from Yagouchi to Hinamizawa.
Such a sorrowful story.
He was able to find his lost child, and they were on their way home...
That's where the story gets a bit odd.
I remember that the scene of the accident was quite close to the quarry.
What's odd about it being close to the quarry?
Think about it...
It was already quite late when his father came searching for him by car.
The surroundings should have been pretty much pitch black...
It would mean that the boy stayed at the quarry all that time.
Perhaps he was caught by the man at the quarry...
...and subjected to a good tongue-lashing?
About that...
When the police investigated later...
...they stated there was no one at the quarry that day.
There's no way that's true.
We were most definitely chased out by an intimidating man!
There was definitely someone there!
As a result...
...it's said that the workman might have actually been a ghost.
There's no way!
Such massive ghosts loudly stamping their feet like that don't exist!
That man's true identity aside...
What we don't understand...
...is why that boy remained at the quarry until it was dark.
Rumor has it he might have fallen into the pit.
The pit?
We're back at that pit again...
Just what is it?
A pit!
And it's incredibly deep...
...reaching all the way to the realm of demons deep below the ground.
According to Onigafuchi folklore...
...there exists a demon realm deep below the village.
Basically, hell exists there.
So there might be a pit somewhere that leads to that place.
I see...
So that's what being demoned away is about.
But that boy didn't disappear, did he?
He met up with his father safe and sound, and got in an accident on the way back, right?
I mentioned earlier...
...that there was a strange smell in the air at the quarry that day.
The villager who first discovered the car...
...detected a faint smell of rotten eggs when he peeked inside the car.
Sulfur!
A sulfurous smell certainly isn't normal.
Was it called hydrogen sulfide...?
It's a poisonous gas with a sulfurous odor.
Sometimes, there are news items about laborers dying from poisoning...
...while cleaning liquid waste tanks in factories, right?
Could there have been such a tank at the quarry...
...which ruptured at some point, causing harmful gases to leak out?
Surely, things make sense if that were the case.
While playing kick-the-can...
...the boy stepped into a strange place...
...inhaled harmful gases emitted from the liquid waste...
...and collapsed on the spot.
And when his father arrived at the scene...
...he must have inhaled the harmful gases as well.
It all makes sense.
When you explain it like that...
...it feels like a long time mystery has been quite easily unraveled!
Well, God knows what actually went down.
But still...
...I can't help but feel that there's something concealed here that makes this not just a mere accident.
If this was not just a mere accident...
...what do you think is concealed?
Let's see...
There are a few points.
A worker that wasn't supposed to be there...
...and the reason the boy remained at the quarry until nightfall.
And finally, their mysterious death inside the car on their way back.
We might find out if we go to the quarry to check if there was a leakage of dangerous gases.
Mion.
You aren't thinking of going there...?
If that theory is correct...
...the ruins of that quarry should still be a dangerous place.
I don't agree with going to such a place...
...I think.
My interest has actually been piqued.
Listening to Kei-chan...
...I've gotten the feeling I can finally get to the truth behind this ghost story.
Aren't you interested?
Don't you want to find out the truth?
Some places in this world are considered taboo.
That's a pretty deep thing to say, Rika-chan.
What do you mean by that?
Keiichi.
In this world...
...where there is light, there is always shadow...
...and in the same way, where there are good places, there are bad ones as well.
There are instances where treading upon such places will make people miserable without reason.
When us humans are unable to define such dreadful places well in words...
...we call such places "taboo."
They say curiosity killed the cat.
If there are bad rumors about this place...
....it might be best not to let morbid curiosity get the better of us.
You're right.
I'm of the same opinion as Rena-san.
Is that so?
Let's go home!
My dad will get worried if I'm not back before nightfall.
Guess so.
If his daughter comes home late at night in such an outfit...
...your father might faint on the spot!
That's the same for you!
Oh well!
Let's call it a day and go home!
Let's go home!
Keiichi?
If I were to go explore the quarry...
...would I fall into that pit and be demoned away?
You would.
I see!
Then I guess I'd better stay away!
Kei-chan!
Aren't you seriously scared?
D-Don't be stupid!
His knees are shaking!
As if!
Hey, wait!
This is for the best.
Even if you don't seek it out yourself...
...the curse will come for you on its own.
After all...
...Watanagashi will soon arrive.
To get my happiness I had done everything...
...but had done nothing to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps became louder every day...
Then I noticed the fact there was no time.
I was a believer in life to be myself always...
...and was asking whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason why not to adopt in this way...
...or judge me to be guilty of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why, or why not. Complaining way too much...
...maybe I overlooked something fatal for me.
One-blow Cat Killing
Aren't there a lot of cats around?
And they seem to be angry about something...
What could have happened to them?
Well, the title...
...you know?
The end.
Title: Kon