It's pretty easy once you get the hang of it.
There's no way I can lose now.
You can have it.
That's what you were after, right?
Hey.
I don't want to owe you anything.
This makes us even, okay?
Let's go home, Madoka.
Sayaka-chan...
Sorry...
I'm just a little tired.
Don't push yourself. I've got you.
That idiot.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 8
I really was an idiot
Service for today has ended.
Sayaka-chan, you shouldn't fight like that.
You say it doesn't hurt, but you're lying.
It hurt just watching you.
You shouldn't be hurting yourself just because you can't feel it.
I couldn't have won otherwise.
I have no talent, after all.
Even if you fight like that and win,
it's not going to help you out in the end.
And what would help me?
Now that I've been turned into this thing, how can anything help me?
Sayaka-chan...
I'm just a rock that's good for
.nothing but hunting witches.
I just pretend to be alive by dragging my own corpse along on strings.
What could anyone do to help a rock like me?
There's no point even thinking about it.
But I just want you to be
..happy again, Sayaka-chan...
Why don't you fight them, then?
Huh?
Kyubey told me. You've got more talent than anyone else, right?
You could easily beat witches
without struggling like I do, right?
I... That's not...
If you want to do something for me,
why don't you try and do what I've done?
But you can't. Of course not.
You can't just give up your humanity out of pity.
It's not pity. I...
You could be all-powerful, but you just
.sit there and watch me suffer instead.
Don't act like you know how
I feel from the sidelines.
Sayaka-chan.
Don't follow me.
I'm such an idiot!
How could I say that to her?
I'm beyond help now.
Homura  Akemi
The Walpurgisnacht should
appear within this area.
What are you basing that on?
Statistics.
Statistics?
I've never heard of the Walpurgis coming to this city before.
So where are these
.statistics even coming from?
Neither of us is exactly
.the trustworthy type,
but I don't you think you have to be that secretive about it.
I'd like to know as well, Akemi Homura.
How dare you show your face here after what happened?
My, my. I get the feeling I'm not welcome.
And here I came all this way just to give
.you some rather important information.
Huh?
Miki Sayaka is depleting herself far faster than I expected.
It's not just all the magic she's using;
.she's started to carry a curse within herself.
And whose fault do you think that is?
At this rate, it might become an issue before the Walpurgisnacht arrives.
You'd best be on your guard.
What does that mean?
What are you talking about?
Perhaps you should ask her instead of me.
You already know the answer, don't you, Akemi Homura?
I thought so.
I'd be most interested to hear where you obtained that information.
Could you be...
I've heard all I care to hear from you.
Begone.
You're just going to let him go?
Killing that thing won't solve anything.
Anyway, what's this issue he
.mentioned with Miki Sayaka?
Her Soul Gem has become too tainted.
If it's not purified soon,
.the damage will be irreparable.
Homura  Akemi
The auxiliary verb "must" means that someone has to do something—
an obligation of sorts.
But "have to" has a different—
Miki
Absent
I should've gone after her back then, but I...
By the way, do you live in this direction?
I don't think I've ever seen you go home this way.
You're right. To be honest, I live in exactly the opposite direction.
Huh?
So why did you walk this way today?
Kamijou-kun...
I have something I need to tell you.
Huh?
She hasn't come home?
Not since last night?
Okay... Um... I understand.
Okay. Thank you.
I need to find Sayaka-chan.
Why don't you get it?
You can't afford to
.waste any more magic.
Focus on witches, not familiars.
Shut up.
Mind your own business.
Your Soul Gem is already at its limit.
You need to purify it right now.
Use this.
What are you planning this time?
Don't be a fool.
You're in no position to be
.questioning others right now.
Or does being helped by someone else bother you that much?
I won't be like the rest of you magical girls.
That's what I've decided.
I won't associate with people who use or abandon others.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own benefit.
You're going to die.
Only when I can no longer
.kill any more witches.
And then I wouldn't be
.any use anyway, right?
That's fine.
Someone like me has no
.other place in this world.
Why are you doing this?
I only want to save you.
Why won't you believe me?
I don't know.
I just get this feeling...
that you're a liar.
You have the eyes of someone who's given up on everything.
You're always saying empty words.
This is no different.
You say you want to help me,
but I know that's not
.what you're really thinking.
You can't fool me like that.
And that's how you keep
.making Madoka suffer.
This has nothing to do with her.
No. Everything I do is for her.
You're pretty sharp.
Yes, you're right.
I don't want to save you.
I just don't want Madoka to
.see you destroy yourself.
If you refuse me here,
.you'll die either way.
And if you keep making Madoka suffer...
then I might as well...
kill you myself, here and now...
Miki Sayaka.
Hey! Hurry up and get out of here!
What is wrong with you?
Weren't you trying to save her?
Let me go.
I see. You can't use that weird technique of yours when I'm holding onto you like this.
Huh?
Damn it.
No way, man. You can't let that dumb slut make any excuses.
You gotta get hold of
.all the money she makes.
Women are idiots, y'know?
The moment they get some money they'll blow it all on stupid shit.
Yeah, seriously, man. You can't treat those bitches like real people.
Gotta train them like the dogs they are.
My bitch gets off on that, you know.
You just gotta threaten to smack 'em one and they'll shut right up.
But give 'em an inch and they'll be all over you, whining about getting married and shit.
You just can't let up on 'em.
Like a cabaret girl like her's gonna make the same kinda money in ten years.
Bitch needs to learn her place, right?
And man, don't get me started on what a pain it is to dump 'em.
You're damn good at that,
Shou-san. I'm really jealous.
Dude, I gotta learn from—
Hey, tell me more about her.
Huh?
The woman you were just talking about. Tell me more about her.
You in middle school, kid?
You shouldn't be out so late at night.
That woman probably loves you and tries her hardest to make you happy.
You knew that, right?
And yet you're comparing her to a dog?
Are you not even going to thank her?
You're just going to get rid of her when she's no longer useful?
What's her problem? You know this kid?
N-No...
I wonder if this world is even worth fighting for.
What have I been fighting for? Tell me.
Tell me right this second.
If you don't, I'll...
Sayaka-chan, where are you?
Do you hate me too?
If I did, would you turn Sayaka-chan back?
I can't. That's beyond my power.
You once said I could become a incredibly strong magical girl.
Was that true?
Incredible doesn't begin to describe it.
You'd become a magical girl
of unimaginable power.
Probably the strongest in the world.
If I'd accepted your offer, would Sayaka-chan still have become a magical girl?
Sayaka made her own wish come true.
In the end, you had nothing
to do with her decision.
Why me?
I don't know either.
To put it bluntly, your latent power is on a level beyond what should be theoretically possible.
I'd like to know just as much as you do.
I see.
If you were to release your power,
.you wouldn't just unleash a miracle—
you might be able to bend the very laws of the universe itself.
I can't even imagine why you alone have so much potential resting within you.
I always thought there was
.nothing special about me.
That I'd just kind of stumble through life,
never being of any use or help to anyone.
It was frustrating, and it
.made me feel really lonely.
But I thought I couldn't
do anything about it.
Looks like reality turned
.out to be quite different.
Madoka, if you wish for it, you might even become an all-powerful god.
Would I be able to do what you couldn't?
Like what?
If I made a contract with you, could I return Sayaka-chan to normal?
That would be child's play for you.
Is that wish worth trading away your very soul?
If it means I can help Sayaka-chan, I'll do it.
I'll become a—
H-How could you?!
You didn't have to kill him!
Why... Why are you always sacrificing yourself?
Don't demean yourself by saying that you
can't help anyone or that you're useless.
Think about all the people
who care about you!
Just cut it out!
Why don't you understand that there are people who would grieve if you died?!
Why don't you consider the people who try so hard to protect you?!
Homura-chan...
Have we...
Have we met somewhere before?
We...
I'm sorry.
I need to look for Sayaka-chan.
Wait.
It's too late for Miki Sayaka.
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
You knew that was pointless,
but you did it anyway.
You just don't learn, do you?
I have plenty of spares, but you can't just go around destroying them for no reason.
It's a waste.
That's the second time you've killed me.
But I'm starting to understand how you fight.
That was time-manipulation magic, wasn't it?
Thought so.
I had a feeling that was the case.
You're not from this timeline, are you?
I know all about who you are
.and what you're planning.
I see.
That's why you're trying
.so hard to stop me.
Are you that determined to change Kaname Madoka's fate?
Yes.
Mark my words, you will
.not have your way.
Kyubey.
Or should I say... Incubator?
I finally found you.
Just how long are you gonna keep this up?
I'm sorry for wasting your time.
Huh? That doesn't sound like you.
Yeah.
That's because I don't really care anymore.
I can't even remember what I thought was so important, so worth protecting...
None of it makes any sense anymore.
Hey...
The balance of hope and despair
.in the world cancels out to zero.
You told me that once, didn't you?
Now I finally understand what you meant.
Sure, I managed to save a few people,
but in exchange, hatred and
jealousy filled my heart.
I even hurt my best friend.
Sayaka, you're not...
Whenever we pray for someone's happiness, someone else must be cursed in exchange.
Turns out that's how we magical girls work.
I really was an idiot.
Sayaka!
In this world, women who have yet to fully grow are called "girls," right?
In that case, it only makes sense that you, who will one day grow into witches,
should be called "magical girls."
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki wo koete
will transcend time
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume wo
and destroy one of this world's dreams
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai wo nomihoshite
What is it that you seek
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani?
now that you're done hesitating?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no?
beyond this greedy admiration?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
I want to be armed with the power
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no youni
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
the next time I see your innocent smile.
微笑む君に合いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In my trembling hands I hold
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
the courage of a plucked flower
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings are all I can rely on;
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari wo yobisamasu
the prayer that awakens
光を呼び覚ます
negai
the light
願い
Illustrated by   Fujima Takuya
Assisted by   Kentaro Tanaka
This may sound foolish,
but I don't want to give up until we
know for sure that she can't be saved.
Episode 9
There's no way I'd allow that
There's no way I'd allow that.