They were sold out of yakisoba bread...
You just got bread today?
It's almost Mother's Day, you know?
My mom's been super busy at the shop,
so she's been oversleeping!
I can't really blame her, but only having bread for lunch really doesn't cut it.
Well, if you like, you can have some of my side dishes.
You don't mind?!
Sorry to trouble you like this.
I'll take this, then!
It's delicious!
Oh, I've got it!
Hey everyone, if you have any side dishes you don't need or want, feel free to let me know!
I'll accept them most graciously!
What is she, a trash collector?
Naminami, you got anything you don't need?
Whoa! Naminami, your lunch box is really cute!
Isn't it?
It really is!
Your mother is amazing, Shiku!
Tsubomi...
Naminami's mother passed away.
Huh?
I-I'm so sorry!
Don't get upset over it!
I'm not upset about it, so it's
no good if you are, Hanasaki!
You've gotta keep smiling, right?
Yeah!
Who did make this lunch box, then?
Me.
Huh?!
My little sister tells me to make them cute, you see.
That's amazing! Being able to make something like this is really neat!
You're like a mother yourself.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Fashion Club
in progress
Now recruiting!
We'll be waiting!
Well then, let's get the club started.
Right.
Sorry to interrupt you during your club.
Erika, can I get that thing you mentioned at lunchtime?
Oh, sorry, I forgot all about it.
Here you go. As thanks for the delicious lunch!
Thank you! My little sister will love it, I'm sure.
Did you design that?
It's really well done.
Huh?
It's not that good! I mean, it's still just a draft...
Though now that you mention it, what club are you in, Shiku?
I'm not in any clubs.
Really?
Then why don't you come join the Fashion Club?
I can't, sorry!
I need to hurry back and pick my sister up from nursery school.
Fashion Club
in progress
Now recruiting!
We'll be waiting!
Mother's Day in Tears!
Protect the Family's Smiles!
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
Welcome!
Yo, Nami, Rumi!
I'd like some carrots and potatoes, please.
Thank you! That'll be 250 yen.
We've got a fantastic bargain on tomatoes today too!
Only 100 yen for three!
Then I'll take those too! How about 300 yen for the lot?
300 yen for the lot!
I can't beat you two, can I, Nami?
Go on, I'll throw 'em in for free.
Yay!
Let's see... I didn't forget to get anything, did I?
Hey, Mommy?
What was this flower called again?
Well, that flower is called a "carnation."
It's really pretty!
Rumi?
Sis! I want a carnation too!
Huh?
Still, it's impressive just how many carnations you've got out here.
Things like roses and gerberas are selling all right,
but carnations are definitely the most popular at the moment.
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
Naminami!
It seems everyone at the nursery said they wanted to give their mothers carnations,
so Rumi wants to as well.
Although in our case it's more of an offering.
Well, it's the sentiment that's important.
I think working so hard to decide what to pick is just as important as the gift itself.
I'm still not sure what to get for my mom either.
Every year I get her a handkerchief or an apron or something...
She's always grateful, but it's kinda getting predictable.
Same here.
I know it's the thought that counts, but...
Well then, why not try buying Mother's Day presents for each other?
Huh?
Then you'll have a different
present from usual, won't you?
I see!
That's a nice idea!
I-I'm so sorry!
I really shouldn't be asking you about Mother's Day, Shiku...
You're making such a serious face again.
You really need to stop worrying.
I-I'm sorry...
Smile, smile!
You've gotta keep smiling!
Right!
Sis, I want this one!
Okay.
Hanasaki, how much is it?
Let's see... 450 yen.
We can bring it down a little more! How about a nice round 400 yen?
How about it?!
S-sure...
You sure are tough, Naminami!
You could outmatch any adult!
I am the holder of the purse, after all.
And...
I have to be a mother to Rumi too.
We're back, Mom.
We're back, Mom!
Hey, Mom! I got a carnation for you!
It's really pretty, isn't it?
Do you like it, Mom?
Sis! I want to give Mom the carnation!
Huh?
I want her to say "Thank you!" to me!
I'm sure she'll be happy with it.
You can't know that for sure!
Rumi, don't ask the impossible.
Come on now.
No!
Idiot!
Rumi, can you set the plates?
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Sorry I'm late.
How's dinner going?
It's just about ready.
Sorry to burden you like this.
What is it? What's the matter with Rumi?
Well...
Well, you can't blame her.
Rumi doesn't have many memories of her mother.
She must be really lonely.
I know, but...
You must feel really lonely, huh?
Would you like to sleep in Dad's room tonight?
You're in the way! Move, will you?!
For... for me?
Well, if you insist... I'll gladly take them.
Hey, if you're going to give them to me, just hand them over already!
When did I ever say I was giving them to you?
Huh?
This is my bouquet.
I merely wanted to show off how much it suited me.
Adieu!
What the hell is with that slithering narcissist?!
I'm so pissed off! So unbelievably pissed off!
I'm going to unleash this anger on those damned Precure!
I'm sorry about this, Nanami.
It's my day off, but they still need me at work for a few things.
It's all right.
Do your best at work, even if it is your day off.
I will.
I'll make dinner for you tonight, okay?
All right then, I'll be off.
Take care!
Rumi, what do you want to do?
Do you want to play house?
Or do some drawing?
Rumi, will you answer me?
I don't wanna!
Rumi!
Rumi! It's dangerous to run off on your own!
I don't wanna!
Rumi!
I hate you so much, Sis!
Fine! See if I care, Rumi!
You idiot, Rumi! You don't even understand how I feel!
I...
I miss her too...
Mooooooooom!
I've gotta keep smiling! I have to...
But what made me have to...
What have we here?
I've found a sad little girl.
She's locked her own heart away.
I'll set your heart free for you!
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
Sis...
Sis!
Right then, let's make a distraction and lure those Precure out!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Erika, about the present for your mom...
Sis!
Huh?
What's the matter?!
My sis has...
Shiku?!
We've got trouble!
There's a Desertrian!
We have to save Naminami!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
So you finally show yourselves.
I'm feeling really pissed off today, so I'm going to beat you both to a pulp!
Argh, just thinking about it pisses me off even more!
Desertrian, get them!
Waaaaaste!
Sis!
Rumi, hide over here!
Huh?
Your sister will be fine!
The Precures will save her!
Precures?
I've gotta keep smiling!
Huh?
I'm not as tough as I seem!
There are times when I want to cry too!
I'm lonely without my mom too!
Sis...
I'm still only in junior high!
It's difficult having to be a mother to her as well!
Blossom!
Waaaaaste!
I want to be able to play more too!
I want to be able to join clubs like everyone else!
Sis!
Hmph! If you want to play, why not just play?
If you aren't able to do that, you must be a really weak person!
Shiku isn't weak at all!
She works hard for others!
And when things get tough, she keeps smiling!
She's a very strong person!
Keeps smiling?
If you just keep smiling like an idiot, that just means you're weak!
I won't forgive you for toying with her
kind heart which values smiles so dearly!
I've had it up to here with this!
Snackies!
Marine Impact!
Blossom Impact!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Now I'm even more pissed off!
Precures, save my sis!
She'll be fine! Just leave it to us!
Sis!
Nanami? What's the matter?
Hm? Did you make that at nursery school?
Don't look at it!
I wasn't any good at making it...
Hey, Nanami,
do you know what makes me happier than anything else in the world?
What makes you happiest?
It's the smiles of my whole family.
That's why no matter what, you've gotta keep smiling.
I see...
Those were Mom's words...
Sis!
Rumi?
I'm sorry, Sis! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry too, Rumi.
You just wanted to know more about Mom, didn't you?
I just felt so sad when I remembered her that I tried to forget.
If you keep crying, you'll make Mom sad, you know?
Huh?
Mom said this to me:
"What makes me happiest is
the smiles of my whole family.
That's why you've gotta keep smiling!"
I've gotta... keep smiling?
That's right.
Dad's smile...
My smile...
And your smile!
When you cry, both Mom and I feel sad.
There are times when we'll want to cry, but we'll get through it together.
Okay?
Yeah!
I love you, Sis!
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad...
I really am so glad!
In the language of flowers, a carnation means "love for one's mother."
Now that the sisters are reunited, their love for their mother shines through!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born...
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Morning!
Good morning!
My mom really loved the carnation
corsage you picked out for her, Tsubomi!
And my mom was really happy with the apron you made for her, Erika!
We managed to come up with some good presents in the end, didn't we?
We sure did!
Hanasaki! Erika! Morning!
Mornin'!
Good morning!
Naminami, what's up?
Um... I made this.
Is this...
Clothing designs?
Yeah.
The truth is, I've always been interested in
fashion, and wanted to join the Fashion Club...
I wouldn't be able to show up every day, but...
Would that be all right with you two?
That's totally okay! Right?
We'd be glad to have you!
Thank you so much!
That's great, Sis!
Here!
Huh?
Thank you for everything.
Rumi!
Smile!
You've gotta keep smiling!
Yeah.
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
I love cool things, but I love cute things too!
Hanasaki Tsubomi and...
...Kurumi Erika!
Combine their strength with the student council president...
...and complete this beautiful tunic!
Try it on, President!
It's beautiful! It's so beautiful!
I've been enraptured by the student council president's charms!
HeartCatch Precure:
What?! The Student Council Prez
Wears Some Cute Clothes!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!