Aren't you going back...?
You'll be left behind.
[ROY]
Who's that...? A war buddy?
No, it's...
It's an Ishvalan child...
One left dead with
nowhere to call home.
Let's go...
The war is over now.
[HAWKEYE]
The fighting, maybe...
But the nightmares of what
we did in this place
are far from over.
[HAWKEYE] They'll stay
with me for as long as I live.
[HAWKEYE CONTINUES]
I believed in you...
I trusted you with
my father's research.
And I applied
to the military academy
because I hoped
to help other people.
The way things turned out,
it's not what I wanted.
But there's no
escaping the truth.
I can never atone for
the suffering I've caused.
[HAWKEYE CONTINUES] I have
a favor to ask... Mustang.
Please burn this off.
Deface my back.
But how could
I ever do someth--?
[HAWKEYE]
At least...
I may not ever be able to atone,
but at least I can destroy
the secrets on my back.
There can be
no more Flame Alchemists.
[HAWKEYE]
Can you do this?
If so... please release me.
I want you to set me free
from my father's burden...
[HAWKEYE] Please...
set me free from his alchemy.
I'm begging you.
[ROY]
All right...
...I'll leave
as little trace as I can.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
[FOOTSTEPS ECHOING]
What are you doing,
Lieutenant...?
Do you know
who your gun's pointed at?
Who...?
Don't make me laugh...
When it's just us...
...the colonel calls me
by my first name-- Riza.
[ROY INTO ENVY] So you
two are that close, are you?
I lied.
But it was still very nice
of you to fall for it, Envy.
And now you can
do me the favor of dying.
Ow! That hurts!
[ENVY YELPS WITH EACH SHOT]
[ENVY] Damn it! You are really
annoying with that thing!
Ha ha! I'll dump you
at his feet... like a rag--!
[FIERY EXPLOSION]
Colonel!
[ENVY PANTING]
[ROY SNAPS]
[ENVY SCREAMS IN AGONY]
What in the hell are
you doing to my Lieutenant?
Don't interfere, Lieutenant.
I told you I would
take care of him myself.
You damn human... don't you
[ENVY SCREAMS IN AGONY]
underestimate meeeee!
[EXPLOSIONS]
[ENVY SCREAMS IN PAIN]
[ENVY WHIMPERS]
[ENVY]
Damn it...
This again?!
So this is
your true form, then?
[ROY]
You're ugly.
Envy means "jealousy."
That's what
your name means, right?
I get it.
[ENVY]
Please don't.
No, don't!
And jealousy...
...is an ugly thing.
[ENVY] No, I don't
want to die! No! No!
I'm not giving you a choice.
[ENVY SCREAMS]
[ROY] Now burn in hell!
[HAWKEYE COCKS HER GUN]
And what do you
think you're doing?
[HAWKEYE]
That's enough, Colonel.
I'll deal with him from here.
He's as good as finished.
Lower your weapon.
I can't obey that.
Put your hand down.
Dammit!
I won't ask again!
[ENVY SCREAMS]
Ah, Fullmetal...
...I'll be taking that.
That is an order...
Give it to me right now.
No. I won't.
[ROY]
That thing...
deserves
the worst death possible.
[ED]
No!
Give him to me!
Or I'll burn up your hand
along with him!
Try it then...!
If it's a fight you want, fine!
But first, maybe you should
take a good look at your face.
Is that the face
you plan to wear
when you're
leading this country?
Well, is it?
Is that what you
want to be, Colonel...?!
Another monster?!
And then in turn...
...they'll protect
the ones they love.
[ROY] It seems like the
least we tiny humans
can do for each other.
You've got my support...
But you could've
just asked me...
It ought to be fun
to watch, though...
And maybe it might
even do some good.
[SCAR]
Are you becoming a beast?
Giving in to its passion...?
You can if you want to.
I won't stop you
from giving in to revenge.
Hey!
What right do I have to stop
someone from taking vengeance?
[SCAR] But still... I shudder
to think what kind of world
a man held captive
by his own hate would create
once he becomes its ruler.
[HAWKEYE] Colonel...
I can't let you kill him.
That being said...
...I have no intention
of letting him live...
I'll dispose of him.
But I did it...!
I finally ran him down!
I know that!
But still...
But still... you're about to do
something reckless...
This will not help--
not your country
or your friends...
This is pure hatred...
...and I will not
let it take you.
You're better... I know
you're better than that.
[SILENT FLASHBACK]
[ROY GRIMACES]
If you're going to shoot me,
shoot me.
But then...
...after you've done
that, Lieutenant...
...what will you do?
I can tell you
I have no intention
of carrying on by myself.
This fight will be my last.
Once all of this is over,
I'm going to end my life...
...and remove my secrets
of flame alchemy
from the world.
[ROY BELLOWS OUT IN ANGER]
[EXPLOSION]
That can't happen.
I can't...
...I can't afford to lose you.
[ROY] What kind
of madness is this?!
[ROY] Scolded by a child...
Lectured by a man
who has been my enemy...
And you...
[HAWKEYE GASPS LIGHTLY]
[ROY]
I've done it again...
I've hurt you.
How foolish can one man be?
Please forgive me.
Are you a moron?
Some nice, flowery words...
and feigned empathy...?!
You make me sick to my stomach.
[ENVY] Are you humans
always such pathetic worms?
Why can't you just
listen to your gut
and do what you want to?
Colonel Mustang,
have you forgotten...?!
Your pal Scar here
was going to kill you.
And what's more...
wasn't he the one that killed
the parents of the
pipsqueak's girly friend?
Oh, yeah... and what about
that little girl
who became a chimera?
Scar was the one responsible
for her death, too...
And as for you...
have you completely forgotten
your hatred for what they did
to your Ishvalan countrymen?
And then this woman...
[ENVY] ...she has the arrogance
to claim the sight of a hawk...!
She shot your buddies
left and right.
You'll never get
another chance!
This is the perfect time!
[ENVY]
The ultimate opportunity.
Hate and weep.
[ENVY]
Kill and be killed.
Fight each other!
Grovel in the dirt!
[ENVY] How could you four
hope to team up?
You're way beyond the point
of kissing and making up.
Right, pipsqueak...?
Right Hawkeye...?
Mustang...? Scar...?
There's no way.
[ENVY] No!
No, you can't! Never! Never!
[ENVY]
It's impossible...
How could you?
How could you do it?
Howwww...?!
Now I see...
You're jealous...
You're jealous of humans,
aren't you?
We humans...
according to you,
we're supposed to be nothing
when compared to Homunculi.
[ED] And yet, when we're beaten
down, when we stray and fall...
...we face the challenge
again and again.
[ED] Our loved ones are always
there to pick us back up.
And you're jealous...
[ED] You envy us
because of that.
[ENVY'S VOICE]
Fool. You just have to
forsake one little village
to save an entire country...
Too bad you don't have the
stomach to do the logical thing.
Can you really shoot
such a sad face?
Can you, boy?
[ENVY'S VOICE]
I shouldn't be surprised...
...that's just how
all you humans are.
This time around, I'll go with
a younger, cuter model.
What do you say?
You humans don't make
any sense to me.
You throw away
your lives for nothing.
Another foolish human.
Humans...? Humans...?
[ENVY STRUGGLES]
Hey, what do ya think
you're doing?!
[ED] Hold on a second!
[ED] Idiot!
Where are you going?
Ow!
[SCAR]
Wait.
He won't last long.
[ENVY]
Humiliating...
Ending up so pathetic like this.
[ENVY STRUGGLES]
[ENVY]
Trampled on by humans...
Those loathsome beings.
Weak, useless people.
[ENVY BEGINS TO LIGHTLY WEEP]
[ENVY] What's worse...
out of all the scum out there,
you just had to be the one,
didn't you, pipsqueak?
[ENVY WEEPS]
[ENVY WAILS]
Damn! Damn it! Damn it!
I've been humiliated!
Humiliated!
[ENVY] Me...? Envy...?
Jealous of you?!
Of you humans?!
I'm a Homunculus.
How could this pipsqueak kid
see through me?
It's the ultimate humiliation.
[ENVY CRIES]
[ENVY BEGINS TO LAUGH]
[ENVY] I guess we'll see
how long this adorable
little alliance of yours
can hold up.
Ah, well, best of luck
with that, pipsqueak!
[ENVY WEEPS]
[ENVY STRUGGLES IN PAIN]
[ENVY CRIES IN PAIN]
[BURST]
[ENVY] Goodbye...
Edward... Elric.
[ED GRIMACES]
He took the easy way out
and killed himself.
[ROY]
Cowardly bastard.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SLOTH CHOKING]
[ERIC] Whoa,
his wounds are healing!
[GUSTAV]
Monster!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 3]
What is that thing?
[ERIC] Come on!
Get over here! Give us a hand!
[CASPER]
Give you a hand?
No, we can't do that.
We're under orders
to kill General Armstrong.
General! Major?!
You're here just in time.
From this point on,
I'll be running the show!
Help us out, or we all die!
[CASPER]
What the hell are those?!
[ARMSTRONG]
Everybody get down now!
Bullets have
no effect on them...
Go for their upper jaws...
If we can get rid of those,
at least we won't be eaten.
[OLIVIER] Attack in pairs,
and take out at least one.
Get ready to fight,
Central Soldiers...
Show me your courage, men!
Let's see... where was I...?
[SLOTH]
Ah, I remember.
I kill the woman general.
[ARMSTRONG]
Oh, no, you don't.
Let go!
This would be so much easier
if I could use both arms...
Major!
General!
[CASPER]
He's gonna kill him!
[ERIC]
Someone should help!
[OLIVIER]
Leave him!
That's my brother!
[OLIVIER] He's trained better
than to be killed like this!
[SLOTH GROWLS]
This is it...
It's the end.
The Major!
[ARMSTRONG RAGES]
My shoulder is back!
Nice!
My incredible strength
and the art of my alchemy
work beautifully together.
You'll find the two to be
an unconquerable combination.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 6]
That's right.
The Armstrong estate
is completely empty.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 7]
Damn it...
Is this where they
assembled that blasted tank?!
[EXPLOSION]
[SOLDIERS YELP IN SHOCK]
This is the gate commander...
calling Operations!
[GATE CAPTAIN]
We're taking fire from
what we believe
is a Briggs tank.
Come in, Operations!
[CREMIN]
Stop shouting! I can see!
No matter... Return fire!
But the civilians
haven't left yet, sir.
And if we wait, we're guaranteed
to lose the main gate!
Get a move on!
Tell the main batteries--!
[EXPLOSION]
Damn, what was that?!
So you planned to open fire
on a populated area?!
Do you want that info
to go out over the radio, too?!
Where did you...?
[CREMIN]
This equipment is from Briggs...
How did you get it here?
[BUCCANEER]
Ahh!
A man formerly from
Command Center One
who has a rather
sharp memory...
...he helped us out,
and pointed us
to the exact location.
And after that,
getting in was
a piece of cake, really.
[BUCCANEER] We just had
to find someone to dig a tunnel.
Who could pull off
something like that?!
Would you like me
to introduce you to her?
Wait... Who in the--?!
[IZUMI] When people ask,
I say I'm a housewife...
It does make sense.
[IZUMI]
But today...
...I've shed that
particular disguise.
I am an alchemist!
You've come alone.
I expected you would bring those
boys of yours along with you.
[HOHENHEIM] What help
do I need from children
when I'm dealing with
something as lowly as you?
To me, you're still
a dwarf in a flask...
...Homunculus.
And you're still
Slave Number 23, aren't you?
You gave me part of your body.
Today, all these
many years later,
you will become a part of mine.
[HOHENHEIM GROWLS]
[NARRATOR]
And so...
...what will you
do now, little humans?
Who do you need
to become after this?
Why does it all work this way?
Next time, on "Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood"...
Episode 55:
"The Adult's Way of Life."
The time has come
to thrust out your chest
and move forward.