When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Roasted Sweet Potatoes
Yum!
It's February already...
And I have yet to even see
Hayate once this year...
But my greatest opportunity
of the year is coming up soon!
That's right! For a young lady, the big event in February is...!
Oh, please! Mister, how could
you in front of a young lady?!
Me?!
Demons be gone!
Good fortune, stay within!
Um, why are you doing this now?
Hey, now, what are you saying, Maria?
That's right. When it comes
to the big event in February,
there could be nothing else but
the bean-throwing exorcism ceremony!
Well, I don't really care, but...
Nagi, it's late, so get ready for bed.
Right.
Then to wrap things up, we'll eat
as many beans as we are old.
Here.
Oh, yes.
Hey, Maria, you want some, too?
Oh, I suppose.
It's for good luck, after all.
What's wrong? All three of you are staring.
N-Nothing!
Oh, it's nothing!
Don't tell me...
Were you thinking, "Huh?
Aren't there too few beans here?"
Oh, no! Nothing like that!
No matter who looks at you,
you're a young and fresh 17-year-old!
Then why are you all covered in sweat?
All three of you, hurry up and go to sleep!
A demon!
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
I swear!
Oh, my back... Owowowow...
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
It is Maria Appreciation Day! In February
Video Rental V Tachibana
Good grief. We ended up
offending Maria again.
Indeed.
Don't make too much trouble for her.
She's not going to be
young forever, you know.
Don't say something so terrible!
Please do not say such a terrible thing!
But Maria works non-stop.
No matter what kind
of expert she is as a maid,
it's a fact that she must
have a lot of built up fatigue.
She is always being so good to us.
It would be nice if we could
show her our appreciation somehow.
All right! This is where
I'll become a maid and...!
I-If you do that, it will be
even more exhausting for Maria.
But she's not the sort to take a break
just because you tell her to.
Th-That's true...
I know!
I have just the right plan for you.
A plan?
Approximately an hour later...
What is going on?
Where in the world
are we going all of a sudden?
Oh, I wonder where.
You'll have to wait to get there to see.
This is...
We are going to be staying here today!
What?!
Saki actually gave us a great idea, you see.
Ladies' Stay Plan, Relaxation Tour?
My friends went there the other day.
You stay at a luxurious midtown hotel,
go to the spa and get beauty treatments...
You just sit back and relax.
It's like rewarding yourself
for your hard work.
I hear it's popular among
working young women.
Working...
...young women...
Young... Young... Young!
Is that the key?
Yes, this is it! Make the
arrangements right away, Hayate!
Yes, Miss!
And so, we call it "Thank you
for everything, Maria.
"The big sister appreciation
relaxation plan!"
What?! B-But... um...
This is a present from the Miss
to show you her appreciation
for what you do every day.
Thank you for always working
so hard for us, Maria.
But for today and tomorrow,
forget about your work and enjoy
a day off in the city at your leisure.
I-I see...
Thank you very much.
Then I will take you up on your offer
and take a nice long break...
Good. Work off that fatigue
to your heart's content!
Then let us go.
Yes.
Welcome!
I never imagined Hayata and
his gang would be coming to stay here.
Then I shall take that room.
I guess Maria and I will
take the room over here.
Oh, then I shall start
by getting the tea ready.
You are on break, so please take it easy.
Oh, y-yes, that's right.
Hayate has made all kinds
of arrangements for us.
Hello? This is the Imperial Suite.
We would like some room service.
The pool, the jacuzzi, the gym,
plus the nail and beauty salons.
Um, a pot of royal milk tea, please.
You'll have free access to all of them.
I see...
It seems this hotel's selling point
is their service towards young women.
What?
It's truly perfect for you,
a working young woman!
You needn't emphasize the
"young" part so much...
Please excuse me. Room service.
Oh, yes, thank you!
What do you think?
Don't I look cool? Surprised?
Committee Chairman! Why?
It's a one-day hands-on
internship through our school.
I heard about this on the news before.
Oh!
I see!
What is it, Hayate?
Oh, no, today was specially
discounted by 5 for some reason.
That's why I settled on this place, but...
I see.
Yes! Today, this hotel is riddled
with people from Hakuou.
I saw Hayate and his gang just earlier!
Oh, is that all?
Darn. I was hoping we might
get to see Yoshizumi or Orlando.
Yoshizumi? Because the Tokyo Metropolitan
Government building is right in front of us?
Well, never mind. Anyway, where's Hina?
She got caught by the manager.
Now that I think back,
it was during the Tokyo Olympics.
That was when I got into this line of work.
I don't get what he's saying at all...
Come on, Hayate!
We came here so Maria
could have a relaxing time!
Pardon me. My thrifty habits
got the better of me...
Hot!
Oh, I'll do that.
Thank you, Maria.
Look! It's already happening!
Maria, I'll do that!
You know...
So, what are you guys doing here anyway?
Th-The truth is...
That's great! I'm so moved!
Okay, I'll help you!
I'll ask everyone to help, too!
Oh, Miss Segawa!
Oh, I have a tremendously...
...bad feeling about this...
Um, if it's about me,
please don't let it bother you.
I am already relaxing more than enough.
No! We cannot lose heart now!
We will protect Maria's
day off, no matter what!
Let us split up!
Miss, you and Maria will go
on to Stage 2 of the Plan!
We will meet again here in 3 hours!
Leave it to me, Hayate!
Oh, uh, um, wait...
Th-This is starting
to look a bit like a battle...
It was true. In a certain sense,
it was a battle.
How's it going, Maria?
Are you working off that fatigue good?
Yes! Thank you very much.
My! How fabulous!
It's like a rose petal bath.
Oh, but this is the pool...
That's strange. I don't recall
asking for such a service.
No thanks needed. In exchange, take this.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Bill to: Sanzenin Nagi
Roses
What?!
Um, who might you be?
Hey, Himuro, is that enough now?
That was satisfactory. Did you
learn something, Little Master Taiga?
Yeah! It's tough to have to work.
Meanwhile, as for Hayate...
Oh, man... The people of Hakuou
are already here, too...
What is the matter, Young Master?
At that rate, it w‎ill be
utterly impossible for you
My hand is my foot... My foot is my hand...
to satisfactorily entertain the guests!
My neck...
All right!
Let's pull ourselves together
and go for beauty treatments next!
Do your best to get that fatigue
worked off for sure this time!
I-I-I will, but Nagi...
Super Special Marvelous Anti-Aging Course
About this "Super Special
Marvelous Anti-Aging Course"...
Don't sweat the details! I'll be next door!
I have been waiting for you.
Gack! Y-You're that piece-of-junk robot!
Now, please come this way.
Hey, you're actually pretty good.
Well, of course, because I'm always
doing massages for Miss Makimura.
Now, then, I guess I'll do my best
to work off my fatigue, too.
Hey!
I heard about what's going
on from Miss Segawa.
Wh-Why are you here, too?
It was a nice opportunity
and I thought I'd learn
a trade, so I'll be fine,
if I ever get fired from my teaching job.
I-I see...
Now, just leave it to me!
I'll use all my powers to totally
work off that fatigue of yours!
I-I sense a rather serious error...
I mean, I sense danger here.
Oh, there goes my fatigue!
My fatigue's totally going away!
You seem to be awfully weary, Miss Katsura!
You know, somehow, I'm already 28 years old.
Is it okay that I'm still up
to the same old silliness?
I wonder sometimes, you see?
But you are still you, after all.
No matter how you agonize over it,
you'll never be someone else.
Please be true to yourself.
Though, please do be careful
not to drink too much.
See how your liver acupoint is?
Thank you, Maria!
I feel like I've met a great senpai of life!
But um, I'm over 10 years
younger than you...
Hey, Maria, is something wrong?
I just got a whiff of something ominous...
O-Oh, no, it's nothing at all!
I just got a sense that
something sinister is coming...
Your new outfit suits you
very well, Mistress Kuzuha!
Ah, yes, I special ordered it from COSPA.
I believe that in the end, I ought to
always be dressed up in formal attire.
You look fabulous, Mistress Kuzuha.
All right, Sion.
Before I inspect this place, I am going
to raise my blood sugar level a bit!
Yes, Mistress Kuzuha!
Gack!
To be continued, in an ever less
soothing and relaxing direction.
Laid back and relaxed.
(Nonbiri yuttari.)
Rhythmically start the word game!
(Rizumu de shiritori sutaato!)
Tan-tan, nta-nta, paseru!
I wonder if they are both enjoying
their relaxed day off in the city.
Hey, Hayate, I'm back!
Welcome back. Wait, um, where's Maria?
She's going for a stroll around the garden
or something and taking it easy.
She's taking it easy?!
That's right! She's taking it easy!
Hold on!
If Maria isn't going to be coming
back to the room for a while...
Hayate and I will be alone together?!
I will make us some tea now.
A-And we're in a suite, like the kind
a newly-wed couple might stay in!
Is something the matter?
I-It's nothing!
Even taking a break
is not easily accomplished.
But those two have shown
such concern for me...
While we're here, I should do
as they wish and take it easy.
Um...
Isumi!
Um, um, I would like to ask you...
Could it be that this is where
Hakuou's internship is...?
Yes, that's right...
I am so happy!
Here we are in Episode 45
and for the first time
I have reached my destination!
I was afraid that I would never
reach it for the rest of my life
and I felt such uncertainty
and anxiety and confusion...
Let us start by going to
the front desk together.
But I never expected that you would
participate in an event like this.
I thought I would use this opportunity
to learn a little about the ways of society.
Oh, Maria!
Oh, ladies of Hakuou.
Maria! Maria!
Is something the matter?
You do not seem to have been
focusing for a while now.
I-It's because it's a bit too quiet.
Let's turn the TV on!
I love you, Mr. Sanma!
Not good! This will put Hayate in the mood!
I love you, but it's too soon
for us! It's too soon!
Oh, I actually like
this actress quite a bit.
She's gained a noticeable glow about her
since she split with that kabuki actor.
Wha?!
But what is Maria doing?!
How much freedom must she enjoy?!
She's actually not taking it easy.
See? Make sure to also tuck in
the top sheet properly
and then line up the bedcover neatly.
That's the key to making it look beautiful.
Thank you, Maria!
Whoa! I accidentally double-booked a room!
Hello? I am so very sorry.
If you would like a twin bed instead
of a double, we could arrange that.
Thank you, Maria!
Ah, yes.
I came here and started working
in the year of the Japan
World Exposition. Back in 1971.
Oh, please, sir.
The Japan World Exposition was in 1970.
What?
As I recall, total attendance
was 64,218,770.
77 countries participated, including Japan,
as well as 4 international organizations.
P-Please excuse me for a moment.
Thank you, Maria.
But you're on break, aren't you?
Shouldn't you be taking it easy?
Please do not tell Nagi
and Hayate about this.
Sir! There's trouble! Big trouble!
Wait... Maripon, what are you doing here?
Maripon?
Hello, Miss Makimura.
Um, could it be that
you two know each other?
Yes, well, you could say that.
I'm so glad!
There's something I want you
to help me with, Mariachi!
Mariachi?
Is something the matter?
The thing is, the cafeteria is just
all "high school" and it's bad!
Miss, please don't hold back the 6.
Huh? I dunno what you're talking about.
There are only two of us here!
Hello?
Oh, Mari...
Shh! Don't let her know I'm calling you.
What?
Um, you see, the truth is...
I wonder what Maria wants...
M-Maria!
I was cleaning when I found
something a guest had left behind.
What was the room number?
We'll look up the guest's
contact information.
Um, where's the concierge?
He was over there just a moment ago.
Um, excuse me.
Oh, ni hao. Wo jiao Maria.
Maria.
Please don't tell Nagi about this.
Certainly, I understand.
So, what did you need me for?
Would you mind doing something for us?
Is the next sweet ready yet?!
Please forgive us!
Our patissier was creating sweets
at a furious pace to keep up with you,
but he has collapsed
due to utter exhaustion...
How feeble of him!
I have still not had enough to eat!
Thank you for your patience.
This is our special mont blanc
from our secret menu.
Th-This is...!
This rich, yet refreshing sweetness,
which envelops the tongue like velvet!
So it is delicious?!
Yum-o!
Yes, I am satisfied.
I am canceling my inspection!
I am going to return to the academy
before this aftertaste vanishes!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
But wow, Maria's recipe worked like a charm.
Of course, because it's been
proven effective before.
Oh, no. Ignore what I just said.
What are you doing here, Miss Makimura?
What am I doing? I'm just
reading a book and eating cake...
No, I mean, what about providing guidance
for the interns or something?
Oh, hey! You're appalled, aren't you?!
Cake is important for the brain, you know!
Then please show him
to the washroom immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
Maria! I knew it had to be you!
That cake tasted the same as what
I once had during the school festival.
It has been a long time.
It has been a while since I have been
fully satisfied. You have my thanks.
Do as you see fit!
Now, I think it's about time
I got back to Nagi.
Nothing happened after that
and the day ended.
I'm so tired. I'm hungry.
Then, want to eat something on the way home?
But...
You don't have any money,
right? We'll treat you.
Really?! Woohoo!
Sis...
Don't you have any pride as an adult?
It's fine! Because
I'm gonna be true to myself!
It's unusual for her
to fall asleep at this hour.
I wonder if the unfamiliar
surroundings wore her out.
The Miss was really geared up, after all.
She was determined that you
were going to have a good time.
Then I will see you tomorrow.
Yes, good night.
I see, Maria. So your
exhaustion's disappeared.
I'm glad. I'm grateful
for everything you do.
Being at the residence really is the best!
What?
Then what about the appreciation tour?
Oh, thank you very much to both of you.
I am the one who should be grateful.
But seeing the bright smiles on your faces
and the faces of everyone
here at the residence
is the best gift there is.
Ah, that is wonderful to hear!
I look forward to continuing
to work with you, Maria.
Certainly.
By the way, your skin
is shiny smooth, Maria!
Maybe that Super Special Marvelous
Anti-Aging Course worked, after all!
You practically look like a young lady!
You truly look rejuvenated, Maria!
I see. So 17 is no longer a young lady...
Or am I really...
Uh, no! No, you're not, Maria!
And so, next time, they'll battle
the brilliant sweat of youth!
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Student Council Girl Trio
Lettering by Eri Nakao
The student council girl
trio's Butler Report!
Butler Report
Hey, there, friends, I'm Izumi Segawa.
I'm Risa Asakaze.
I am the warrior of freedom, Miki Hanabishi.
Those of you watching TV
are naturally certain to have
memorized our image song already.
Of course, because they should be listening
to it at least 100 times a day!
We have happy news for you!
If you collect 10 belly bands
from our CDs and send it in...
You won't win anything in particular!
Ooh! That's amazing!
And now, here's today's fan service
shot you've been waiting for.
Ooh, this one's pervy!
Man, talk about daring,
first thing in the morning!
Farewell!
Preview
What the heck is going on here?! Tell me!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
You ask the most nonsense
questions sometimes, you know that?
It's weird, isn't it?!
Isumi put on a blazer and got
on a bus with no hesitation!
Maybe she's fallen
for a guy at another school,
so she's sneaking in
by wearing their uniform.
What?!
Next time, "His Name Is
Magic Ball Pitcher Wataru!!!"
The Young Sir won't come to me
for advice, and yet...
No, it's probably
because it's easier for him
to talk to Miss Nagi, who is his age,
or some other equally trivial reason.
His Name Is Magic
Ball Pitcher Wataru!!!
And so, Cross Triangle with "Hayate
the Combat Butler" again next time!