Everyone, Kaleido Star is going to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. What are you good at doing?
Cooking? Participating
in sports? Or studying?
Mia is very good at coming up
with storylines and writing.
I'm so excited to find out what kind
of story she is going to write.
Let's support our hard-working
Mia. Let's support! Let's support!
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
One week...
Make it so you can perform
this on stage in one week.
Yes!
"Fire It Up! Amazing Mia."
As a first step, come up with
a tentative plan in three days.
In three days...
Go, Mia!
Everyone's future is on your shoulders, Mia.
Why do you have to pressure me like that?!
I'm trying hard, but I can't write!
Sorry...
I have to write.
Maybe this is impossible for me...
I don't think so.
Not at all. Not at all. Not at all.
You think so?
You're not good at working under pressure.
That's right. That's right.
You can't write because you're trying to
write a masterpiece from the very beginning.
Be yourself. Be yourself.
You're right.
Maybe I'm a little too zealous.
We also have to be careful that
we don't say anything unnecessary.
Telling you how much we're expecting
from you is not a good idea.
Okay, then.
First, I think I should relax and...
Did you write that fantastic masterpiece yet?
I got so excited, I couldn't sleep,
so I brought you something to eat!
Huh?
Oh, dear...
It's not a laughing matter.
Now, now, have a break.
First of all, why does the
Boss want me to correct this?
I don't know what he wants from me when
he just says, "Not good. Correct it!"
Now that you mention it, he
always just says "Do it!"
Even when we played The Little Mermaid,
he just told Sora to create her own
little mermaid at the beginning...
You're right.
If he'd told her what needed to be done,
Sora wouldn't have suffered as much.
What do you think, Miss Sarah?
What do I think?
Kalos has always been like that.
Kalos has been like that since
he started Kaleido Stage.
So, in those days, he used to revise the
contents of the performance every day.
So the contents of the show
were different every day.
Since Kaleido Stage has grown so much,
performing exactly the
same show became ordinary.
Still, the way Kalos handles
everything has not changed.
How?
Take your Little Mermaid, for example.
If you based that character on what someone
told you to do, how would you feel?
Do you think you'd be as attached
to that character as you are now?
Well... It could be...
But, of course,
maybe he just doesn't want
to think of it himself.
By the way,
do you already have a rough idea of
what kind of story you want to write?
Well, sort of...
Considering the number of people we have,
I'm thinking about writing
that ghost love story.
But I think something is still missing
if we want to make it work onstage.
Well...
You may find a hint in the
materials in this room.
Isn't this performance
using the cloth pretty?
I want to try this.
I wonder if I can do fire-breathing?
What? Even though you're a diva?
I wonder if I should try
something with a motorcycle.
In the end,
I think the performance we can
do depends on who we have left.
That's true.
Does everyone really think that Yuri's
theatrical company is that great?
According to the rumor,
anyone who leaves Kaleido Stage
can join his theatrical
company unconditionally.
Seriously?
You want to go?
Maybe we're too talented, and he's,
like, afraid of asking us to join.
That's right.
You know, I think he, like,
just forgot about you.
How dare you!
Let's go, Mia! Go beyond Shakespeare!
Miss Sarah...
Since Mia is working hard,
I also have to work hard.
Kaleido Stage is not as
great a place as you think.
Kalos has misled everyone.
You look like you're having
a hard time sleeping.
Are you worried about something?
Kind of...
Oh, you don't need to read Tarot.
What?!
Besides, I know it will
just show something bad.
Well...
Then I will sing a lullaby for you.
What?!
Okay. Then,
♪ Lalalu, lalula, sleep, good girl. ♪
♪ Lalula, lalalu, go on and... ♪
You sound creepy. I can't sleep!
Okay...
Oh, Mia. You woke up?
Where is Sora?
She came here first thing in the morning...
...and she went to the practice room.
Really?
Something happened?
Yeah...
As of today, thirteen
more people are leaving.
Oh...
Sora... Is she crying?
Sora! Sora!
Hang in there, Sora!
Thanks...
It's dangerous to try that by yourself.
If you ask me,
I'll teach you how to do it properly.
Okay.
Anyway, thirteen more people are quitting.
What?
The way things are going now,
we will end up having a little
over ten people left with us.
Simon!
Simon Park!
You were saying?
Please continue what you were saying.
Yeah.
I already heard about Kaleido Stage's
situation through the grapevine.
And yet,
Kalos is ready to let an absolute amateur
take charge of the next performance.
Frankly, I'm disappointed in him.
That's why I'm asking you to do this.
Okay, no problem.
Okay?
You accept that easily?
I've been interested in Kaleido
Stage for a long time.
But I don't know what
Kalos will say about this.
I will persuade him.
What?
Well, I thought you were a pretty cool woman.
Please listen to me seriously.
I am listening.
After three days, a tentative
plan will be ready.
Once he sees that plan,
he'll have no choice but to
acknowledge what we have to say.
Unless we do something, Kaleido
Stage will be finished.
Yes.
It's Naegino.
Come in.
Why don't you have a seat?
Yes.
I'm so happy that you came here to visit me.
Well...
About that thing you were
talking about the other day...
Since I don't know what will
happen to Kaleido Stage,
I thought maybe I should just cut
all ties, cleanly and completely,
take care of everything once and
for all and join your place.
But then, I still can't
decide what I should do.
Your acting is terrible.
Oh...
I know you want to say something.
I want to know why you are trying
to destroy Kaleido Stage.
I want to find out why...
This is...
revenge!
Really?
Yeah...
When did you find out about this?
Only a year ago.
So, that's what's going on...
Yuri Killian is Arlon Brass' son.
It seems that Killian is
his mother's maiden name.
Yuri is trying to take revenge on me.
That's right.
I have been waiting for this day to come.
My father was a trapeze artist like me,
and he was also one of
Kaleido Stage's founders.
But Kalos killed him.
What?!
Uh...
Sora, please come to my place.
We still don't have a female top star.
And you're qualified to be one.
I need you.
I...
In the end, only about ten
people are going to remain.
Yuri... I really can't forgive him.
Are you okay, Mia?
If this was when we had so many people...
Oh...
What?
How about if the leading character of
the ghost is the owner of a circus?
The protagonist became a ghost.
He's alone, recalling a time
when the circus was cheerful.
I know this story can give everyone a
chance to show off their best talents!
And the only person left by his side
is the woman who was his lover.
Yeah, yeah...
The last scene is a touching farewell.
He says goodbye to the one he loves the most
while he's lost in beautiful reminiscence.
It'll make people cry. I
know it'll make people cry!
There is a chance that this
could be an amazing masterpiece.
Go, Mia!
I may surpass Shakespeare!
Really?!
Finished!
Kalos,
as I expected, the things I
was worried about came true.
After all, Mia is still an amateur.
With the help of Simon Park's direction,
let's re-create Cinderella.
You don't have any objection, do you, Kalos?
What?
Mr. Simon Park is here.
Let him in.
So, everything is set, right?
Mia, you can leave now.
Yes...
No...
The next show will be directed
and produced by Mia Guillem.
Kalos!
Revise the script.
You still have four days until the deadline.
Then...
Let's just say we weren't meant
to work together this time.
We should do dinner some other time.
Simon Park!
Please wait.
I want you to be a supervisor.
I'd like to ask you to support Mia Guillem.
Kalos, I think that is so rude.
No. It sounds interesting. I will do it.
Oh...
Well, I have places to go, so
I have to excuse myself now.
Send the script to my address.
As for everything else,
please talk to my agent.
Well then, take care of the rest.
That Simon Park is going to support me?
All right.
What?!
That is amazing!
Yeah, yeah.
Right? That genius, Simon Park,
is going to read my script.
That itself makes me so happy.
I will strive to revise any
corrections to perfection.
Yeah!
First of all,
I should revise the parts I don't like.
Mia is making steady progress.
I shouldn't be feeling this way either.
About Mr. Yuri...
I think I should talk to the
Boss and make sure of the truth.
Oh, sorry.
Me too.
Going out?
Oh, yes. Well...
Huh?
So Yuri said that...
Yes.
Kalos forced my father
to do a risky maneuver.
And he used my father's death for promotion.
It's true that investors at
that time hid Arlon's death.
Which actually led to the
rumor spreading more,
and our audience numbers increased.
But I will tell you this.
Arlon was the one who tried that
maneuver, by his own choice.
Then, Mr. Yuri is...
In fact, Yuri also should know better.
No matter how much you force a person,
if that person is afraid of
doing it, he never can jump.
But Kalos has been blaming
himself for what happened.
That's why he stays silent, just
watching what Yuri is doing.
This is something very hard to deal with.
You and your friends don't need to
worry about something like this.
Instead, you should only
focus on your performance.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, hello...
Yes, could you please wait for a second?
A call from Simon Park to Mia.
What!
Yes!
So, you want me to delete pages 2 through 4.
Then, you want me to delete
from the middle of page 5...
...to page 24?
Yes.
Then, you want me to change the last scene?
Excuse me,
but that's the scene when the protagonist
and his lover say good-bye, and...
I know. But we see this kind
of last scene all the time.
To replace the sections we deleted,
why don't we do something fun?
And come up with a few more
highlight scenes for the climax.
Yes.
Okay. Take care...
Um...
Mia...
In short, I need to rewrite it all.
All of it?
I will go to apologize to the Boss.
What?
I will tell him, "Sorry,
but I can't do this."
I'm sorry, everyone.
Wait, Mia!
Are you going to quit?
Because, if I continue and
can't finish writing it,
I will end up troubling you all. So...
You can do it!
Don't say something so irresponsible!
I think you can do it.
Because I know Kalos never asks something
of someone who is not capable of doing it.
But...
I want you to write it, Mia.
I don't want you to give in to the pressure.
Once you make up your mind
saying that you can't do it,
that will be the end of it.
When we did the Triple Illusion,
I thought "we'll never
make it" so many times.
And I even stepped down from the role once.
But you said,
"I'd rather perfect it with Anna and Sora."
At that moment, I thought, "I
have to do this no matter what."
I thought, "No matter what,
I'm going to perfect it."
That was why I could push myself.
Mia, let's do this to the last.
Don't give up...
and do it to the last.
Don't give up... Don't give up...
Don't give up?
Don't give up!
A story about people who don't give up.
This could be a good one.
It's perfect for us.
The number of members decreased,
but Kaleido Stage still exists.
If this show becomes successful,
some of the people who left
Kaleido Stage may come back.
That's right.
If I make this wish into
a part of the story...
Yeah. I think I can do this.
I wonder if I can gather everyone now.
Okay.
Right away.
So, since we don't have that many people,
each of you, please be ready to perform
at least three kinds of
routines from your repertoire.
Unless I know the story, I can't do it.
The script is not finished yet.
Not yet...
How can she...
Can you finish writing the script?
I will finish it. Absolutely...
Then, everyone, let's start practicing.
Yes.
Good. Wrap the cloth tight around your body.
Then I'll revise it so it
will go in that direction.
Light B5 is okay.
Everyone is working to create
their own performances.
It seems we are back to
the way we used to be.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Don't you think you can still make it better?
Hey, take a look at this.
What do you think about this kind of swing?
It looks interesting.
I also want to try it.
Sora...
Yes.
Out of everyone left in Kaleido Stage,
the only person who is capable
of being my partner is you.
Even if you say no, I'm
still making you my partner.
Yes.
Hmm, it's almost perfect.
Yes!
Since we still have eight more
hours, we should do one more push.
Yes!
Let's make it so the whole cast's mood
builds up at once toward the last scene.
I know conveying that kind of buildup to the
audience is Kaleido Stage's charm, isn't it?
I understand. I will try.
Mia...
You think you can make it?
Ouch!
I have one favor to ask.
Yes.
Shorten all female performers' skirts.
What?
Your script is perfect.
We will raise the curtain for
opening day one week from today.
Start rehearsal immediately.
Let's go, Mia.
Yes. Thank you very much.
The stage is the world of fire and darkness.
This is a story about two groups of
young people fighting in that world.
In that scene, I want you
to perform more wildly.
Oh...
but, maybe it's okay the way
you're doing it right now.
Direct with confidence!
Yes.
Originally, they were
friends in the same group.
While young men fight each
other, they begin to change.
It seems the director
gets new ideas every day.
She's a sceneman's worst nightmare.
Jean, you're so alive.
You too.
Anna, more speed!
Sora, move bigger!
I thought of a title.
Yume, Kibou...
Those are Japanese.
I started studying Japanese recently.
Not good enough.
I agree.
Soon, they start thinking that they want
to live together the way they used to.
And then, their wish reaches
everybody's hearts.
They acknowledge and forgive each other,
and decide to cooperate and
live together once again.
Amazing!
I can definitely feel the
excitement on the stage.
When they free themselves from fighting,
I think that's the time
they obtain real freedom.
That's why this story's title is:
"Freedom"!
Yeah!
You did it, Mia!
Everyone is enjoying it. I'm happy.
One day, I'm sure the day
we can hear this applause
with everyone, even all the
former members, will come.
I'm sure...
"Next Kaleido Star"
Hey, apologize to everyone!
And so, Mia's direction was a
big, big, big success! Yet...
Because of Yuri's plot...
Today is Kaleido Stage's last day...
Miss Layla,
what on earth are we going to do
now? What on earth? What on earth?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Yuri's Amazing Trap."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru