Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Sontokkya chanto release yo
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Nan kataru nan taberu
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
It's what you call a normal girlie
Odoroita atashi dake?
Am I the only one surprised?
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Bonbon ouendan
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Ranran kangeikai
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Motteike!
Take it away!
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I should be the one who'll be laughing in the end
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
n n n n n n n n
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
It's only Monday!
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
Ganbatte harikitte
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin' darlin' please!
My darlin', darlin' please!
On your mark!
Get set!
You've done it again, Kona-chan.
That was amazing.
How come you aren't on any sports teams...
...when you're so athletic?
'Cause if I join a team...
...I'll miss my prime time anime.
Speedy
Lady
Say, Tsukasa.
Which end of a chocolate cornet do you start from?
The head, I suppose.
I see.
By the way...
Which side's the head?
The fat end or the thin end?
I would guess the thin end.
Oh.
I thought it was the fat end.
But why would the thin end be the head?
Well, doesn't it look like a seashell?
Why did you think it was the fat end, Kona-chan?
'Cause, you know...
It looks like a caterpillar?
A caterpillar?
But I guess it works better if you picture a seashell.
U-Um...
You could cut off the thin end...
...and eat it with the excess chocolate.
Now I get it.
Good thinking, Miyuki-san.
You're so smart.
Not at all.
Everyone has their own approach to eating.
How do you eat cream puffs?
Cream puffs, you ask?
Well...
I start by splitting it in half...
...and eating the lid after dipping it
in the cream from the bottom...
And then I eat the bottom half.
This way, I don't have to worry
about any cream spilling out...
...while maintaining a balance between cream and puff.
What about the ones that have
both custard and cream inside?
How do you eat those?
Do you mix them up?
No.
I wouldn't do such a thing.
But how would you mix them?
Just asking.
When do you eat the strawberry on a strawberry shortcake...
...or the chestnut on top of a Mont Blanc?
Let's see...
There are also strawberries tucked
between layers of sponge cake.
I follow a normal distribution of
strawberry, cream, and cake as I eat.
So there isn't a set time for eating the strawberry.
You really know your stuff.
I always save the strawberry for last.
But then I get full sometimes...
...so I end up not eating it...
...or someone in my family takes it.
Your favorites hafta come first.
Actually, I don't think I've ever seen
anyone take a strawberry from Sis.
That's Kagami for you.
Doesn't miss a step.
Are you able to eat the last bite of a popsicle without dropping it?
Dropping it?
If you aren't careful...
...you drop the last bit, right?
What do you do, Kona-chan?
Suck it down to nothing.
You could rotate the popsicle as you eat.
That's a good idea.
I'm not very fond of ice cream cones.
Why?
I can't stand it when only the cone is left.
That's right.
You always end up with some cone left.
I push the ice cream into the cone as I eat.
How do you push the ice cream?
I do a little push and pull action as I eat.
Push and pull, is it?
Yuki-chan prioritizes balance, right?
That's right.
Then what do you do with curry rice?
Do you mix the sauce with the rice?
No.
I dont mix them...
...but I make sure that they're equally proportioned.
I mix mine up.
What about you, Kona-chan?
Depends on the curry.
If there's any Worcester sauce or raw egg in it...
...I guess I do a little mixy-wixy.
Worcester sauce in curry?
It's good stuff.
Do you also put Worcester sauce on your fried eggs?
I put soy sauce on fried eggs.
I use mayonnaise.
On your fried eggs?
I don't mean boiled eggs.
You see, mayonnaise...
...goes well with most egg dishes.
Do you put it on your curry?
It's a must on white rice.
But the sweetness also goes well with beef bowls.
It's also good with parent-child bowls.
You know how eggs and
chicken meat are child and parent.
So once I add mayonnaise, which is made from eggs...
...I call it an expanded family bowl.
Also...
I usually can't stand natto...
...but I was able to eat it once I added mayonnaise.
Can't imagine it.
But...
...putting mayonnaise on soft-boiled eggs might be best.
The fried eggs at my house are also half-done.
It's how my dad likes them.
He likes to suck out the yolk.
And if it's overcooked, he can't suck the yolk.
What about skewered chicken?
What about it?
Do you leave it on the spit?
Or do you use chopsticks to take it off?
Let's see...
If I'm eating one by myself, I leave it on the spit.
But if I'm with other people, I'll take it off.
Yeah, yeah.
Isn't it a little awkward when there's only one left?
I can't bring myself to take the last one.
As time goes by without anyone eating it...
It starts getting dry...
...and looking anything but appetizing...
...and no one's willing to make a move...
...but when the busboy takes it, yo go...
"Wait, we're not done with that yet."
...kinda on reflex.
But then you end up leaving without eating it.
Such a waste.
I feel sorry for it.
And when you grill meat...
...I feel sorry for the meat that's
all charred and stuck to the grill.
You have to eat while you're grilling and chatting...
...so it's a busy ordeal.
It's even worse with onion beef
tongue slices since they're done in'no time.
You're right.
They're done after just one flip.
Flip?
Onion beef tongue slices?
You can't flip those.
Really?
If you flip them over...
...the onions on top will fall off.
Oh, yeah.
They'll finish cooking without any flipping.
I see...
I'll do that from now on.
You can never flip them.
Really...
By the way, is the fat end or thin
end the head of a chocolate cornet?
Locked
up
for
two
months
I wanted
to make
her my
slave
Locked
up
for
two
months
I wanted
to make
her my
slave
Super bad boy.
There've been a bunch of kidnapping cases recently.
Guys forcing girls to address
them as "Master" and stuff.
Isn't that less...
...an issue of morals...
...and more an issue of playing too
many dating sims and adult games?
It's a commonly used scenario.
Aren't you talking about yourself?!
Er, wait a tick.
Why are you so well-versed in the adult game scenarios...
...Miss High School Second-year?
First Semester
Midterm Grades
Miyuki
Takara
First Semester
Midterm Grades
Miyuki
Takara
First Semester
Midterm Grades
Miyuki
Takara
First Semester
Midterm Grades
Miyuki
Takara
Your grades are always so good.
Don't you have any faults, Miyuki-san?
I'm ashamed to say...
...that I have a tendency to brood over things...
...or space out.
I've cut my finger while using a slicer.
Ow!
And tripped over myself while in a hurry.
And gotten my bag stuck in the door on a train.
Miyuki-san.
Those aren't faults, but elements of turning people on.
Turn-ons?
The clumsy factor.
What was going on inside
Kona-chan's head during all that?!
Miyuki-san, why do you wear
glasses when you're actually attractive?
You'll only nab a niche audience.
Nab's a little...
Setting aside the issue of popularity...
...why don't you wear contacts?
I heard that glasses make your vision worse.
Um...
I'm ashamed to be saying this in high school...
B-But...
I'm...
Scared!
Of contacts!
Or to be specific...
...putting things in my eyes.
I can never open my eyes when I'm underwater.
Curses!
She's cute to the core!
Must be innate.
Isn't that Miyuki-san?
YOSHIMIZU
OPTOMETRY
Is she here for an eye examination?
To get contacts?
YOSHIMIZU
OPTOMETRY
Miyuki-san's probably better off this way forever.
That looked painful...
A pillar of evolution.
Kagami's at home with a cold?
It looks like she doesn't have the flu though.
I'm stupid so I don't have
to worry about getting the flu.
I've heard that applies to colds...
...but it also applies to the flu?
Kasukabo
Exhibition Hall
There's a difference between a cold and the flu?
I thought the flu was like a super cold.
I-I think they're different...
But now I'm not sure anymore...
The difference between the flu and a cold?
Well...
The flu is caused by a virus.
The symptoms are a fever
and aching throughout the body.
And there is a risk of complications.
On the other hand...
...the symptoms of a cold are
a sore throat and runny nose...
...and the fever doesn't run as high.
And there are a number of other minute differences.
Which is why...
...they are different illnesses.
I see...
H-However...
Well, they share many similarities...
...so you could possibly say that
it's an upgraded version of a cold...
I see!
Kona-chan.
Whats with the pensive face?
Oh, nothing big.
I was just curious about something
after our conversation this morning.
About a cold and the flu?
You didn't disagree when I said I was dumb.
N-No!
It's not like that!
Konata-chan.
Welcome.
She's here to visit Sis.
Thank you for visiting.
It's nothing.
Sorry to intrude.
Kagami actually looks pretty cute when she's asleep.
What is it?!
Why are you here?!
She's up. She's up.
Get out!
Visiting?
You?
For my sake?
That's right.
B-But I don't want you to catch the flu from me.
I appreciate the thought though.
Hah.
You know you're happy about it.
Is she worried about me...
...because of the new virus going around?
I figured she only ever had games and anime on her mind.
I'm a little touched.
Well...
I wanted to see your homework from the other day.
And I got to see your face while you were sleeping...
...so don't sweat it.
Get out!
Kagami!
Miyuki-chan's here to visit you!
Okay!
I'm sorry to intrude.
Sorry you had to come on a day off.
Is it all right for you to be up?
This is a little something.
Thanks.
I'm a lot better now.
My fever went down after I took some medicine.
Here.
Flowers and fruits! I'm overjoyed!
Have a seat.
Thank you very much.
I intended to visit earlier
with Izumi-san and everyone...
...but my schedule hasn't been very forgiving.
S'okay. S'okay.
I brought some materials from the student council meeting.
Thanks!
If you could take a quick
glance without straining yourself...
Also, here are the budgets for each club.
And what else was there...
Um...
If I'm tiring you out...
...I'll leave.
This is how a visit's supposed to be!
D-Did something happen?
Actually, Konata showed up yesterday...
It was like, good grief.
That may just be how Izumi-san expresses herself.
The homework may have been an attempt at humor...
...in order to cheer you up.
And perhaps she saw how your
face looked while you were sleeping...
...because she didn't want to wake you up.
Is this woman a saint?!
That would've never occurred to me.
Come to think of it...
Is Tsukasa-san not here today?
Good morning.
Are you feeling better, Sis?
As you can see...
She's more laid-back than the person who's sick.
U-Um...
I'm not like this every morning...
Just that I haven't really adjusted to daylight savings...
It's a little late but welcome.
I completely understand.
I've been having a hard time waking up as well.
Th-That's right.
You get so sleepy these days.
Indeed.
And it's especially warm today.
That's the truth!
It can't be helped.
And you know how our last day off was also warm?
When I woke up, it was already evening.
I spent most of the time sleeping.
It's good to rest when you have a day off.
So I ended up wearing my pajamas the whole day.
I guess I still am.
Those are pajamas?
That's right.
They're quite adorable.
I can't tell that they're pajamas.
Really?
I wonder if I can just stay in them.
You could walk outside in them.
Could I go into a convenience store in these?
It's like an endless loop of dumb and dumber!
Nobody would blink an eye.
NURSE'S OFFICE
It's gone up a little...
No.
That might not be the case.
I'm wearing a wired bra with extra padding...
...which means extra weight.
That has to be it.
I wonder how many grams that adds.
Once you subtract that...
NURSE'S OFFICE
It's over...
I totally screwed up.
I forgot we had examinations today...
...so I wore my print underwear.
I'm so embarrassed!
NURSE'S OFFICE
I haven't grown at all...
Curses!
You get to look all happy by yourself!
Yo.
I'm here.
Sis.
I was wondering.
Kagami comes here a lot.
Do you have no friends in your class?
Don't put me on your level.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Oh.
I thought you were being ostracized or something.
Worry less about me...
...and more about your lack of a social life.
You don't have to worry about that.
Believe it or not, I have around a hundred friends.
And I'm pretty good at social dealings.
And I'm in a party every night.
My comrades and I strive
to recover the light stolen from
the crystals to save the world from oblivion...
...and rescue kidnapped princesses...
Aren't you talking about a game?!
I haven't seen that person in a while.
Who?
She's probably talking about some friend from a game.
He plays a warrior.
He went somewhere with a lot of monsters to
train his battle skills, and I haven't seen him since.
I heard from someone else...
...that he was lying low in the sewers.
I wonder if he's okay.
Everyone's worried since he hasn't come out.
He isolated himself in the game?
I don't know the details...
...but his log-in info implies that he's been online the whole time.
So he's isolated in both the real and virtual world?!
Well, it's the same person in both cases.
That's right...
How did you two become friends?
A huge fishy-looking foreigner
was about to take Tsukasa away...
...when I happened to show up.
Using my special fists of fury...
...and beautiful hurricane kick...
...I saved her.
Why do we always end up talking about games?
Well, that's what happens when
you run into an experienced fighter.
I'm not sure you should've
resorted to violence so quickly...
...but you did a good thing.
The foreigner was actually
just asking me for directions...
...but I was having a hard time
understanding him when Kona-chan showed up...
Hey!
You were totally at fault there!
And why do you look so proud about it?!
It's that time of year again...
Is something going to happen?
No.
I was thinking that the Tigers' season had started...
You don't like watching sports, Kona-chan?
You're really athletic...
...so I thought you might enjoy it.
Because if the game goes into extra innings...
...the schedule for new anime gets all messed up.
Sometimes, the show gets canceled altogether.
It sucks when you lose something you like.
When do you eat the strawberry
on a strawberry shortcake, Kagami?
Why you asking?
I was wondering if you were the type to save your favorite for last.
I usually eat my favorite stuff last...
...but with strawberries, it depends on the situation.
Then do you grill both sides of an onion beef tongue?
Onion beef tongues?
It's done in no time anyway...
...but it'd go even faster if you did both sides.
You can't.
The onions will fall off.
Don't you add the onions after the meat's done?
Then the onions won't be grilled.
But aren't the onions just a topping?
You have no idea...
W-Well...
Wouldn't they both work...?
Do you think the fat end or thin
end of a chocolate cornet is the head?
The fat end?
We think the same.
Seriously?
Then which end do you start eating from?
Don't you cut off the thin end...
...and eat it with the excess chocolate?
Have you ever made any real-life friends besides us?
I guess I had a really close friend back in middle school.
So you had one.
I haven't been in touch for a while...
Wonder what she's up to...
She wrote in our graduation book...
...that her dream was to become a wizard.
So she was one of your kind?!
Good lucky!
It's finally time for Lucky Channel!
Now being broadcast on TV!
Okay!
Hello to everyone who's meeting us for the first time!
I'll be your navigator, Akira Kogami.
I'm Shiraishi.
Who're you?
Just kidding!
This person will be helping me out now.
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Da-dada-dum!
Uh...
I'll be serving as Akira-sama's assistant.
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Nice to meet you.
Say what?
You're such a stick-in-the-mud.
Come on.
We're on TV now.
Be more crazy!
Just kidding!
Sorry.
I'm not used to this.
Okay!
Let's get rollin'!
We've received commemorative
postcards from lots of people!
Ah, right.
Um...
This is from Berryz Lover in Osaka.
Congratulations on Lucky Channel making it to TV.
Thanks!
By the way, I have a question for Akira-san.
You are a well-known super idol.
How much exactly is an idol paid?
Please let me know.
Pay?
That's a rather direct question.
Y'know...
What's the point in even asking that?
A-Akira-sama?
Well, if you really want to know, I'll tell you.
To be frank, it jumps all over.
Sometimes, it's just cheap pay...
...and then there's your agency.
I'm still on a fixed salary...
...so who knows how much they're skimming off.
And I've been working since I was three...
...so all the money still goes to my parents.
They, like, give me an allowance.
And boy, do they skimp.
Come to think of it, Mama's been
buying a bunch of name brand purses recently.
Is she paying for that with the money from this show?
Don't mess with me!
Am I supposed to be Cinderella?!
Wait...
Just because Papa hasn't
sent you any money recently...
Hold on!
...doesn't make me your piggy bank!
You don't have to bring that up!
Oh no!
It's time to say goodbye!
Akira's so sad!
And so...
Send us any questions or
comments about the show please!
Shiraishi-san, ask them with a please!
Then we hope you'll be back next time.
See ya!
Oh, yeah.
Are you seriously going to show up in the actual show?
Who told you that?
The four of us don't karaoke together very often.
I rarely come to these places.
C'mon. C'mon.
We only have two hours so start singing!
You don't need to rush us.
We still have time.
This is kind of exciting.
It's really fun.
It feels really good when you sing.
Huh?
Where's the catalog?
Catalog?
The catalog.
The catalog, is it?
You know.
The thing with all the song numbers in it.
This?
Yes.
Then I'll start!
You move fast!
And she already ordered three songs!
It'll be a waste if you don't load up the list.
What's this song?
Space Ironmen Kyodain!
You've gotta start with this one!
Never heard of it.
Go for it, Kona-chan!
Konata!
You're too loud!
Turn it down!
Why does she know this song?
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
So sleepy...
Why am I always so sleepy...
...the day after I get a lot of sleep?
Doesn't that defeat the purpose of sleeping a lot?
Next time:
「Effort and Results」
Effort and Results.
Look forward to next time!