Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, everyone, are
you really able to tell your feelings
to your mom and dad?
Stuff like, "This is what I want to do."
Of course, I know I shouldn't
make my parents worry,
but I don't want to have any regrets, either.
I want to tell them how
I really feel, you know?
You know? You know?
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
"My Amazingly Distant Family."
The curtain rises in 15 minutes.
Mia, how did your grandma's surgery go?
They called me a little while
ago and said it was successful.
That's great.
Yeah, thank...
We'll have to give it our best too.
Stop that.
Unless I'm doing something funny,
I feel like my mind's going to go blank!
On the other hand,
unlike us, Sora's already
had stage experience,
so she's calm and composed.
Maybe not.
Sora!
Miss Sarah...
The false appearance that deceives the world.
What?! Did you have to go that far?! Ouch!
- -She's still the same inside.
--That hurt!
Excuse me, where is Kaleido Stage?
Kaleido Stage?
Yes...
Are you Japanese?
Yes.
You're in luck. Today's the day the
world-famous star from Japan, Sora,
will appear on the stage.
Sora will?!
Do you know her?
She's my daughter.
Papa!
Pa... Papa?!
The surprises are yet to come.
We have just a few more
minutes until the show starts.
Take this time to say your fond
farewells to your humdrum daily life.
We need to make sure
we don't make any mistakes.
Yeah, I know. Let's do it.
The seats are packed. Break a leg.
Packed?!
Sorry. Did I make you nervous?
There's no such thing as a performance
that will not make you nervous.
I never realized. Even
Miss Layla gets nervous.
Don't forget that you
guys are just barely passable.
Yes, sir!
You didn't have to go to the
trouble of driving me there...
Sora and I are friends.
Let me do this for you, Papa.
Miss Layla truly is good. She's so composed.
After all, she's been through
lots of opening days already.
Miss Layla really is amazing.
She's even livelier than she is at practice.
Being good during the real
thing is what makes you a pro.
When Miss Sarah's song ends,
it'll be time for you fairy
godmothers to go on stage.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's do our best.
We've done everything we
can to be ready for this. Right?
Let's go!
Oh, Sora...
Be confident.
And keep in time with each other.
Good!
Now, it's finally the scene
where we cast the spell.
The Triple Illusion that we
worked our hardest to get right.
No! I was late.
I'm going out!
What? But...
Prepare the smoke and flash!
Yes, Ma'am!
Miss Layla!
Miss Layla ad-libbed to cover for us.
Sora!
Excuse me, I can't see!
No, no. Smile, smile.
I'm sorry.
It's because I made a mistake...
You think the audience will
accept that kind of excuse?
Sora, I'm sorry. I'm more to blame than you.
No, it's my fault for
not being able to respond
to Miss Layla's ad-lib at all.
Sora, you have a guest!
What?
Sora.
Dad!
What?!
Sora's... dad?
Hey, do you think he came to take Sora back?
He was against her joining
Kaleido Stage, wasn't he?
Dad...
Oh, Dad, this is Mia and Anna;
we joined at the same time.
Thank you for being friends with Sora.
Uh, hello.
Why didn't you let me know you were coming?
Oh, well, I came here on
short notice because of business.
How is Mom?
Oh, she's worried about you.
I see.
Excuse me...
Dad, this is Ken.
It's nice to meet you. Here you are.
Thank you for coming to
see me on stage today.
Even though you saw me
in an awkward situation...
Oh, this?
I just bumped into something during practice.
Sora.
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Okay...
Are you going to stay here tonight?
Yeah.
I wish I could show you around, but...
Don't worry.
Oh, I know. Why don't we go
to the hotel restaurant tonight
and have a Japanese meal?
Well... But I'm supposed to
practice with Mia and Anna, so...
I see.
Oh, but come to think of it, I'd like that.
I haven't had Japanese in a while.
Don't push yourself.
Then I'll say goodbye here.
Okay.
Oh, Dad! Come to see me tomorrow too!
I see. So, that's how it is.
Your current parents are
not your real parents.
Oh... Oh!
Oh, Sora, I think my hair got caught...
Dad came all this way to see me,
so I'm going to do my best!
Oh, this is terrible!
This is just totally unacceptable.
Good morning.
What was that about? It wasn't very nice.
It's a review of yesterday's performance.
What?
"In Kaleido Stage's new production,
Layla's big performance
drew the audience's attention.
I appreciate the idea of the fairy
godmother being played by a trio,
but their mistakes stood out and
their performance was also dull."
Having that kinda of
critique written about us...
Today's audience members have
probably read that, haven't they?
Mia, let's pull ourselves
together and do our best.
What are you doing?
Boss!
What are you doing, being
affected by a newspaper critique?
Just watch, I will cover for
any mistakes that you make.
Both Mia and Anna's jumps
are smaller than yesterday.
Hey, those fairy godmothers are the ones
the newspaper wrote a
terrible review of, right?
Yes, they are. I feel sorry for Layla.
This way, Mr. Naegino.
What are you three doing?!
If you're going to perform like that,
step down from the stage right this minute!
That is an important
scene where the spell is cast!
I'm very sorry.
I can't believe they have the
nerve to appear on stage like that.
No kidding.
Sora.
I need to talk to you.
Sora, come home.
What?
Come back to Japan.
Dad?
To tell you the truth,
I came to see how you're doing.
Your mom is also worried about you.
She wants me to bring you home
if you seem to be having a hard time.
I should have opposed it more
when you started telling me that
you wanted to join Kaleido Stage.
I should have stopped you no matter what.
Such a dangerous job...
Besides, I don't want to see
you struggle any more than this.
Sora, let's go home together.
I'm not leaving for Japan until
you say that you're coming with me.
Sora!
We came looking for you,
since you were out for so long.
Oh, sorry for making you guys worry.
So, what did your dad say?
Well...
Sora?
He told me... to come back to Japan.
Sora, you aren't going home, are you? Right?
I don't want to go home!
But I couldn't say that to my dad.
Because... Because...
Starting today, we'll be your mom and dad.
Back before I was in grade school,
my real mom and dad
were killed in a car accident.
My current dad is my real dad's cousin.
It's because he's not your real dad
that he's telling you to come home,
ignoring your feelings.
No, you're wrong.
Mom and Dad both raised
me with a lot of care.
And I really love them too.
That's why I couldn't tell him
that I didn't want to go home.
Why don't you just tell
him your honest feelings?
Sora! Something terrible
happened! Your dad...
They said your dad collapsed!
My dad?
There was a call from the police.
Your dad was apparently
taken to Cape Mary Hospital.
What'll you do? The evening
show's going to start soon.
We need to be on standby.
Oh, Sora!
Sora...
I'll end up being absent for the performance.
They may not forgive me for that.
Miss Layla might be able to get
on stage as usual in this situation.
But even though they may say
I'm not being professional, for me...
Dad?!
Dad...
Sora...
There's nothing to worry
about. Just let him rest.
Dad, I...
I think maybe I will go
back to Japan with you.
Sora...
I figured I'd stay near
you and Mom after all.
Sora...
Dad...
What is that girl thinking?!
As I said, her dad was...
It doesn't matter what reason she might have!
We'll need a substitute for...
We'll do the show with
just two fairy godmothers.
Layla, cover for her.
It's already started.
Miss Layla!
Excuse me!
You!
I'm very sorry.
You think you can get
away with it by apologizing?
I'm...
Going to quit Kaleido Stage.
I'm surprised.
I didn't know you could be
clever and live your life that way.
I wonder if she's serious?
You sound disappointed.
You're kidding me, right, Sora?!
You should really think
it over one more time.
Sorry, but I've already decided.
We can't play that part without you.
It's not too late. Let's go
apologize to the Boss right now.
You can do that part even without me.
But I'm the only child Mom and Dad have.
It was fun getting to
perform in Kaleido Stage,
even if it was only for a short time.
The Moon. Wavering emotions.
But when the clouds clear,
your indecision will also vanish.
Are you sure you don't need to stay
in the hospital here a little longer?
Since you told me that you
would come home, I got better.
I'm glad.
Hey, Dad.
That was the first time
you saw Kaleido Stage, right?
How was it? Did you enjoy it?
Yes.
Wasn't Miss Layla amazing? Mr. Yuri too.
I can't believe I got to be
on stage with those people.
When you said I could go to the audition,
it made me so happy.
When I told you that I'd been accepted,
you said, "Congratulations!"
Even at that time...
I was so happy,
because I knew that you and
Mom were actually against it.
So when you came to
see me, I was really happy.
I wish I could've shown you
a better performance, but...
Sora...
I'm sorry. I don't know what to do.
To be honest, I don't
want to quit Kaleido Stage.
But I don't want to make
you and Mom worry, either.
What should I do?
Sora, I'll go home by myself.
But if it gets tough, you can
come home whenever you want.
You're our precious daughter, after all.
Dad...
Be careful not to get hurt.
Dad!
Thank you.
I'm very sorry!
I know what I told you yesterday,
but I just love Kaleido Stage.
So, let me try one more time. Please!
We are not the ones you need to apologize to.
You're greatly indebted to the
audience who came to see the show.
Show them your best performance.
I will!
Someday, I want to be
able to tell my mom and dad
to come to see my
performance with confidence.
Someday, I'll be able to.
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
And so, I brought home a seal.
What?
His name is Jonathan!
But I heard we're not
allowed to keep any pets here.
You say you'll take care of it yourself,
but there's the cost of feeding him too.
All right! In that case, the three
of us will enter a juggling contest
and aim for victory.
Yeah!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Seal."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...