Don't kick the pear, huh?
Minami, do you want to stay in Germany?
If you really want to, then I'll make arrangements so you can.
Sis...
You aren't coming with us?
I'll go.
I'll go to Japan with Hazuki.
I need to go
to Japan.
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Question 8
Me, Japan, and a Language I Don't Speak!
Fumizuki Academy
Oth
Entrance Ceremony
It was a year ago, on the day of the entrance ceremony.
I had just come to Japan and didn't understand Japanese very well.
Nice to meet you!
"My first impression will decide whether or not I'll fit into a Japanese school."
"I should make sure I don't do anything strange."
With those things in mind, I nervously awaited my turn to introduce myself.
Next is, Shimada Minami.
Shima
da
I'm Shimada Minami.
Nice to meet you.
What is it? Did I do something strange?
Ms. Shimada has been living abroad in Germany.
She's only just returned to Japan, so there are a lot of things she doesn't understand just yet.
Everyone, please help her out.
It's all right, Ms. Shimada.
You'll learn kanji little by little.
Kanji?
Shima
da
Mi
hami
Shima
da
Nice to meet you.
They could've told me that I made a mistake.
It's mean to just laugh without saying anything.
My dad told me all Japanese people are nice, but this class is already starting to make me feel uneasy.
I'm Sakamoto Yuuji from Kannazuki Middle School.
That's the legendary demon of Kannazuki Middle School!
Shit, he's in our class!
Sakamoto Yuuji
Is this normal in Japan?
No, Dad said Japan is one of
the world's safest countries.
I'm sure I'm just getting the wrong impression.
I'm Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
I'm glad to meet you all.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi
Why is she wearing a boy's uniform?
I'm sure she's just not used to skirts yet.
Reliable
Righteousness
There's nothing strange about that, right?
Dad said there's absolutely
nothing scary or strange in Japan.
Tsuchiya Kouta
Tsuchiya Kouta. My hobby is peep—
Never mind.
I'm good at eaves—
nothing whatsoever.
You dropped something.
Forget what you just saw.
That's normal, right?
He's using it to record lessons, isn't he?
I can trust what my dad told me, can't I?
My name's Yoshii Akihisa and I'm
from Nagatsuki Middle School!
Nice to meet you!
Akihisa Yoshii
I have been deceived.
My dad lied to me!
Shimada, did you really live abroad?
When did you come back to Japan?
Were you born over there?
Everyone was looking at me curiously, as if they had never seen someone whom had grown up overseas before.
Are you good at English?
Are you going to join a club?
Do you have a boyfriend overseas?
What should I do?
I don't understand Japanese all that well, and they're all talking to me at once.
How do I tell them to be quiet in Japanese?
What are your hobbies?
What's your favorite food?
What's your bust size?
Oh, right!
There was a girl this morning who
silenced people with a single phrase.
I can use that.
Shut...
Shut?
Shut up, you disgusting pigs!
H-Huh?
I messed up on my first day.
I later asked my dad what I had said, only to discover I'd been extremely rude.
Math I
Shimada Mi
Shimada Mihami
After that, there were none who tried to befriend me.
Save for one, that is.
Um, Shimada, was it?
Yes!
Huh, what's wrong?
Why are you wearing...
Oh, this?
This is because, um...
I overslept this morning and I was in a hurry.
Japanese boys wear sailor shirts
when they're in a hurry?!
Maybe what he said was just too complex for me.
Hey, idiot.
Quit your moronic babbling and get out of my way.
Stop it, Sakamoto.
Shimada just isn't used to Japan
yet; don't call her an idiot!
I'm talking to you, Yoshii!
How am I an idiot?!
Your very existence proves it!
What?! You can't just go around judging people based on how they look or act!
What else could I judge someone by?!
Well, then you're an idiot too Sakamoto!
A hot babe talked to you this morning and you gave her the cold shoulder!
The hell does that have to do with you?!
That dumb ass face of yours
has been pissing me off all day!
That's my line!
How dare you call someone you just met an idiot, you damn mongoloid!
A guy who wore a sailor shirt his first day of school has no right to lecture me about manners!
W-Well then, see you.
I didn't quite get what they were
saying, but I instinctively realized
I'd forever lose the chance to have a normal school life if I got involved with them.
Will I really be okay at this school?
I followed dad to Japan in order to stay with my sister, Hazuki, but still... I'm so nervous.
The women's restroom is blue
and the men's is pink in Japan?!
I would've embarrassed myself
if I hadn't paid attention.
Why are two girls in here?!
Wait, I'm not a girl!
Come here, Kinoshita!
This is a misunderstanding!
Why did I have to leave?!
What are you doing?
That's a toilet for men!
What's wrong? Why are you so angry?
I'm really a guy. I didn't do anything wrong!
Hey, Shimada!
Shimada
I don't understand Japan very well
yet, but it's only my first day.
I'm sure I'll come to understand things as time goes on.
Until then, I'll take it easy and
try to get along with every—
I-I can see...
I really don't understand Japan.
How was the school in Japan?
What happened?
Nothing much really.
I met a lot of very unique, wacky people.
Everyone was a little weird.
I see. I'm glad you had fun.
I hope you make a lot of friends, Sis.
Y-Yeah.
Friends...
huh?
Question 8
Translate the following English
sentence into correct Japanese.
Shimada Minami's Answer
Music not only provides
entertainment but also
enriches the mind.
*I believe this is German,
not English.
Sakamoto Yuuji's Answer
The question cannot be
answered because the
sentence is in German,
not English.
Teacher's Comment
I am very sorry. I put the wrong question by
mistake. Shimada, your response is indeed
the correct Japanese translation. However,
as this was an oversight on my part,
everyone will receive credit—
Tsuchiya Kouta's Anwer
<- Invisible writing
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
<- Stupid people can't
see it
Teacher's Comment
—actually, I'll make an exception for you two, you get no credit.
A week has passed since that day and classes have actually begun.
I intend to see whether a
woman can produce one of
those diaries men are said to
write.
The departure took place during
the Hour of the Dog on the
Twenty-first of the Twelfth
Month in a certain year.
I will set down a
few notes about
the journey.
Having come to the end of
a four- or five-year tour
of provincial duty, a man
finished the usual tasks,
got a clearance, and
set out from his
official residence
toward the port of
embarkation.
Since I still wasn't used to Japanese,
I struggled with Modern Japanese class;
whereas Classical Japanese may as
well have been from another planet.
Yoshii, what is the conjugated form of "haberi"?
Yes!
It's "hannari".
I asked for the conjugated form of a classical word, and you replied with something from a modern dialect.
It's refreshing to see someone get something so completely wrong.
Eh, what?
Shimada Mihami
I intend to see whether a woman can produce one of those diaries
men are said to write. The departure took place during the Hour of
the Dog on the Twenty-first of the Twelfth Month in a certain year.
I wil set down a few notes about the journey.
Having come to the end of a four- or five-year tour of provincial
duty, a man finished the usual tasks,
<—Shifting provincial duty
Please review what we've learned
today before our next lesson.
It had finally ended.
But just when I thought I'd be free to leave that dull and tortuous class...
Where are you going, Shimada?
What is it?
U-Uh...
I'm going home.
Huh, "what a sea"?
Wa-ta-shi!
Oh, I get it! You're heading home!
Sorry, I didn't quite catch that earlier.
I thought you were talking in a foreign language since you just came back from overseas.
With my Japanese skills still lacking, I couldn't
keep up with the pace at which he was speaking.
Although I tried hard to understand, I felt like my head was about to burst from the effort.
I know you want to go straight
home, but you can't just yet.
There's still home room after this.
That's why you can't leave.
What's he grinning at?
Is teasing me about my poor Japanese really that funny?
Huh?
What club were you in during Middle School, Minami?
Is he asking what clubs I was in during middle school?
No, it doesn't sound like it.
Is he even using correct grammar to begin with?
I DON'T KNOW!
What should I do?
Why won't anyone try to understand me?
I'm trying as best I can.
I'm back.
Ah,
welcome back, Sis!
Maybe they all hate me.
How was school?
It was really interesting.
Maybe this place isn't for me.
Did you make any new friends?
Yeah. They were really good people.
Really?
I...
Yes! Japan's a great place!
I'm happy for you!
I couldn't fit into the class.
I couldn't understand Japanese, which meant I couldn't make friends; I had no one to talk to.
It was a catch-22.
Shimada Mi
It was all because I messed up my name's kanji that first day, ever since then...
da
Mi
hami
Shimada Mi
Shimada Minami
Huh?
I thought this was written incorrectly.
Why...
Hey, the guys from Akemono Middle are betting their lunch on a game of basketball. You in?
Totally, my lunch budget is really tight this month!
I'll help.
Guess I'll join in too.
It sounds kinda fun.
When did those guys become such good friends?
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
What's wrong with this guy?
He's spouting nonsense again.
I don't understand Japanese!
What the hell's "mon amie"?
I'm not Monami, I'm Minami!
You can't even remember my name, and you're still trying to get close to me?!
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
Tu ne—
Don't talk to me you idiot!
I am a man. Are you?
Man
I'm a guy, but...
Wait, don't tell me she's a guy too?!
He doesn't understand English?!
She means you're annoying.
Idiot
Really?
Calling a pissed off girl a man,
you've sure got guts Akihisa.
That's not what I meant, Shimada!
It's not like I think you're a guy because you've got such a flat chest, it's just th—
You're breaking my arm!
I don't understand Japanese, but I heard that 'flat chest' part loud and clear.
This totally sucks.
I shouldn't have come to Japan.
Hey, Shimada!
I don't know much about that guy since we just met; but that idiot's pretty interesting, don't you think?
Id-iot?
You should look up what he's been saying to you.
Idiot
Idiot, huh...
I know he's an idiot.
Idiot
"Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?"
What does that even mean?
I'm sure he was just making fun of me again.
Fine, I'll look it up and get you back!
Tu ne voudrais pas... Tu ne voudrais pas...
Tu ne voudrais pas...
That's not even in this dictionary!
Just what was he saying?
Is that even Japanese?
He even got my name wrong.
I'm not Monami, I'm Minami!
Monami...?
mon amie
Why are they calling me?
No silly, that's not it.
They're not saying Minami, but "mon amie".
I got it!
Minami in France, 3 years old
It's in French!
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
It's not Japanese at all!
It's not German either!
That guy got it wrong and used French instead!
He really is an idiot.
There weren't any German to
French dictionaries in the library.
Idiot
I could only translate it to English, and then to German.
I didn't know how it was spelled, so I'm not sure I got all the words right.
Idiot
But...
"Tu ne voudrais pas" means "could you" in English.
"Devenir" is "become".
It's not Monami, but rather "mon amie", which means "my friend".
If you put them all together...
Could you become my friend?
Tu ne voudrais pas devenir mon amie?
I'm sure he had to piece it together too.
Even though it was in an foreign language...
Even though he could hardly grasp the classical form of his own language...
Akihisa Yoshii
Even though he's an idiot...
Such a big idiot...
Idiot
I'm the idiot...
Will you be friends with me?
With me...
Morning, Yoshii!
Morning, Shimada.
What's wrong, Shimada?
You know, Yoshii...
Um?
Wa-ta-shi...
What a shit?
Sorry, did I make you mad again?
No! What I...
Hey, Yoshii...
I—
Let me...
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
shinten shinai yo
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Question 9
Answer the following question.
What is the term for the
activity in which an
organization solicits politicians
to influence government
policy?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Lobbying.
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Just as I'd expect of
you, Himeji. The word
comes from the fact that
the lobbiests would interact
with members of the
legislature in the waiting
room, or "lobby."
Shimada Minami's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 9: What is the term for the activity in which an organization solicits politicians to influence government policy?
Dinner parties?
Who's the king?
Next episode: Me, Romance, and Diplomacy!
Me, Romance, and Diplomacy!
This will be on your test.