Master Kiritsugu!
Your child has been born.
She's so cute, she's adorable,
and so small, so very delicate.
Look, Kiritsugu.
She has your eyes too.
She's beautiful.
I'm so happy that I could give birth to her.
Iri, I...
I will be the cause of your death.
I know.
The Einzberns have dreamed of the day.
It is the very reason I exist.
When I came to know your ideals,
I made your wish my own.
You made me who I am today.
You have guided me on my path.
You offered me a better life than that of a simple puppet.
You needn't pity me, because I am part of you already.
So.
But...
I have no right to hold that child.
None.
Kiritsugu, don't forget.
You're striving to make a whole new world
where no one cries.
This is what your whole life has been about.
Eight more years, and your fight will come to an end,
and our ideal will become reality.
The Holy Grail will save you.
I'm certain of it.
So take this child, Ilyasviel, and hold her close.
Hold her and be proud, like any other father would be.
A Command Seal?
Yes.
The mark identifies you as a
participant in the Holy Grail War.
A stigmata bestowing upon you
the power to command a servant.
Kirei Kotomine.
The Holy Grail War,
the battle for an ancient relic that performs miracles.
But why me?
Normally, those chosen by the Grail as masters for
the servants are experienced and accomplished mages.
It is highly unusual for someone like you,
who has no connection to magic
whatsoever, to be chosen to participate.
Heroic servants.
I still find it strange to command the summoned
spirits of ancient heroes to fight as familiars.
Of course, I know all this can
be very difficult to believe,
but heroes from every age and nation
will come back to life in the modern world,
killing one another to vie for supremacy.
That is the Holy Grail War.
Also, there is an unspoken agreement among all involved
to keep this all secret.
To ensure this rule is kept,
someone of the Holy Church is always sent as an observer.
Should one of us really be judging?
A secret battle between godless magicians?
A Mage's Association member
would be too partial to one party to assure fairness.
And so once again,
just as we did some 60 years ago,
we've recruited your father to
watch over and referee our battle.
My father will be coming to Fuyuki?
But wait, how can this be considered fair?
It's a conflict of interest for the
overseer's child to also be a participant.
Tokiomi?
Perhaps it's time we got to the point.
Kirei, everything we've spoken of thus far is
just the official background of the Holy Grail War.
However, there is an additional reason I've
introduced you to Mr. Tokiomi Tohsaka here today.
And what would that be?
Actually, we found proof a long time ago
that the Holy Grail that will appear in Fuyuki
is not the sacred relic that belonged to the Son of God.
So I gathered.
Otherwise, an order to retrieve it would've
been given to us of the Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
Be that as it may, Fuyuki's Holy
Grail is far too powerful to ignore.
It is an omnipotent wish‐granting device.
Who knows what disaster it could unleash
should it happen to fall into the wrong hands.
In which case,
the best course of action would be to ensure
that the Fuyuki Grail falls into the right hands,
hands that would not misuse it.
The Tohsakas are a family of mages,
but they are mages with a long
history of friendship with the Church.
We know what kind of person Tokiomi
is, and more important than anything else,
the Tohsakas' ultimate intentions
for the Grail are plain and honorable.
To reach the root.
That is the Tohsaka family's sole desire.
But the Einzberns and Matous have both
forgotten the wish we once shared with them,
and have other less altruistic plans now.
It goes without saying that the plans
of the other masters will be even worse.
Who knows what dark desire they may harbor
for the power of the Grail should they obtain it.
That being said, I assume that the goal of my
participation is to ensure Tokiomi Tohsaka's victory,
rather than to prevail myself.
To achieve that goal
we will conduct ourselves in a manner that
will maintain the appearance of us being enemies.
However, we will actually be working together
in total secrecy to soundly defeat the other five masters,
and assure our victory in the end.
And so, Kirei,
you will be officially transferred
from the Church to the Mage's Association
where you will become my student.
The official orders have already been issued.
You must go to Japan and study the principles of magic,
and become a mage of sufficient strength and skill
to command a servant in the Holy Grail War
in three years time when the battles begin.
Now then.
Do you have any questions for us, Kirei?
Only one.
How exactly does the Holy Grail
go about selecting its masters?
What kind of criteria does it use?
Hm.
The exact criteria it uses is unknown, but
it chooses those masters who need it most.
So all the participating masters
have a reason to covet the Grail?
Not necessarily.
I'm told that in the past there
were cases where Command Seals
appeared on those whom you would never have expected.
Oh, I think I understand.
You're still puzzled at being chosen
to be a master by the Grail, aren't you?
I didn't expect Kirei to give his consent so quickly.
My son would jump into fire if
the Holy Church ordered him to do so.
To be honest with you, I'm even a little shocked.
From his perspective,
he's being drawn into a senseless war
that has absolutely nothing to do with him.
No, this is as it should be.
Perhaps this ordeal will do him some good.
Only a few days ago, my son lost his wife.
I believe that a complete change of
scenery and a difficult new mission to focus on
may be exactly what he needs to nurse his wounds.
Hi, Aoi.
Kariya, it's good to see you again.
You're back from your trip?
This one seemed to last a long time.
Yeah, I guess it did.
Uncle Kariya!
Uncle Kariya, welcome back!
Hi, Rin.
Did you bring me a present again?
No, Rin, you're being very rude.
Here.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
You are very welcome, Rin, I'm glad you like it.
Where's Sakura?
Sakura's gone now.
What did she mean?
Sakura is...
well, she's no longer my daughter or Rin's little sister.
She's now with... the Matou family.
But why?
The Matous want a child who
carries in them the blood of a mage.
You know why, better than anyone else.
The head of the Tohsaka family decided to give our
ancient allies, the Matous, that which they requested.
It wasn't my place to speak out.
You're all right with that?
When I married into the Tohsaka family,
when I decided to marry a mage,
I knew what might be required of me.
And you're all right with that?
The reality is that a clan bearing mage blood can
never expect to enjoy the happiness of a normal family.
That's not true!
When you married him you wanted happiness, you wanted...
Enough!
This is between the Tohsakas and the Matous.
You left the world of mages a long time ago.
This doesn't concern you.
If you get the chance to see Sakura again,
please be kind to her.
She was always very fond of you.
So, the failure actually had
the nerve to show his face here.
I distinctly remember telling you to stay far away
from this house, and to never darken my doorstep again,
Kariya.
I heard you adopted the Tohsaka's second daughter.
Then you have sharp ears.
Is it really so important to keep mages in
the Matou lineage that you have to do this?
Would you tell me we're wrong to?
You of all people?
Tell me who's fault do you think it is
for our present reduced circumstances.
Kariya,
had you only agreed to carry on the family name
and to learn the secrets of the Matou,
things would never have gotten this bad,
and that little girl would still be with her mother.
You're not fooling anyone, you vampire.
You only want the Grail to give yourself eternal youth.
You just wanna live forever.
Nearly 60 years have passed since
the last time the masters gathered,
but the Matous have no pawns yet to
offer for the fourth Holy Grail War.
Though you have it inside you, your brother
Byakuya lacks the power needed to control a servant.
But even if we forfeit this round, we could still
win the next in 60 years if we prepare ourselves.
The Tohsaka girl's womb will one day bear
us a powerful mage, one who could prevail.
She has a lot of potential,
that one, she could be the key.
So then in other words, if you
can get your hands on the Grail,
you won't need Sakura Tohsaka anymore.
What is it you're scheming, Kariya?
A trade, Zouken.
Next year I will return from the Grail War, Grail in hand,
and in return, you will release Sakura.
Don't be a stupid idiot.
You're a failure and you haven't
trained a day in your life.
You actually believe that in a single year
you'll achieve the power to control a servant?
You have the secret magic to make that happen
and you know it, using your special worm techniques.
So?
You can implant me with your crest worms.
Kariya, you want to die?
The Matous should rely on
themselves to gain what they want.
I won't let anyone else get involved.
Surely you're not concerned for my well-being, Father.
If what you're trying to do is keep her out of all this,
Kariya, I'm afraid you're a little late.
You bastard, you didn't!
For the first three days in there she did
nothing but constantly scream her head off.
But on the fourth, she settled down and finally stopped.
Early this morning, I threw her down into
the worm pit to see just how long she'd last.
She's been in there for over 12
hours and she's still breathing.
The Tohsakas have very powerful inner spirits.
Sakura!
What will you do now?
She's a broken little girl ripped from the life
she knew, and violated by worms from head to toe.
But if you still wish to save her from this ordeal,
I might be willing to think about it.
I agree.
But I intend to continue her
education until you show results.
That point is not negotiable.
I still expect to achieve victory
in the next war 60 years from now,
but should you somehow manage to retrieve
the Grail in this war, all the better.
Naturally, I'll no longer need the girl. In
that case, her education will only last a year,
and then she'll be free to go where she wants.
You won't renege on your words, Zouken Matou?
You can start by serving as
the breeding ground for a week.
If you don't die or go insane then I'll concede that
you're actually serious and will keep my word completely.
It's finally here.
What does it say?
It's a report from the spies I
sent to the London Clock Tower.
It says that the Grail chose
a master from within the tower,
the headquarters of the Mage's Association.
Who is it?
A rather big problem.
The eldest son of the Archibald family,
a ninth generation mage.
Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald.
In the world of mages, a long and
distinguished lineage is everything.
Nothing else matters.
This is because magic will not yield
up her secrets in a single generation.
A parent passes on the fruits of a
lifetime of magical training to his child.
Thus, the older the family of mages,
the greater their power ultimately becomes.
You are no doubt wondering why I begin
today's lecture with something so basic.
It is because a student from this class
submitted a fascinating paper to me yesterday.
"How Wizardry Should Be in the New Century."
It attempts to make a case objecting to the
longstanding traditions of which I just spoke.
It claims that if one were to achieve
a deep understanding of the techniques
and precise control over mana application,
it would allow one to overcome
any difference in inherent ability.
In short, even someone with diluted blood could,
through his own efforts, become a master mage.
To be honest, I've learned
something from reading this paper.
Silence, please.
I will be perfectly frank.
This paper is nothing but immature juvenile fantasies.
Huh?
Blood determines a mage's powers and abilities.
This is a hard and unchanging reality of this world.
Even for you, Waver Velvet.
I am very, very disappointed that one of my
students would indulge in this moronic nonsense.
Sir, I was only trying to raise a question the
Mage's Association has become too reluctant to address.
Mr. Velvet, if I recall correctly,
your family has produced mages for only three generations.
Isn't that right?
Listen to me, compared to the Mage's
Association's long and illustrious history,
your family is no more than a newborn baby.
Don't you think a baby should learn to
speak before it tries to voice an opinion?
He made a fool of me,
he made a fool of me,
he made a fool of me!
Is that any way for a teacher to act?
Reading my paper made him
jealous and he couldn't handle it!
The pompous ass is afraid of my talent.
That's why he embarrassed me in front of everyone.
Whoa!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You're in the Spiritual Evocation Department.
Why aren't you in class?
Well, uh,
Mr. Archibald asked me to run an errand for him.
That's why I was in a hurry.
I see, that's great.
Would you mind giving this to
him when you go back to class?
Okay, sure, why not?
Just make sure he gets it, it's supposed to be important.
It's important?
Package origin, Macedonia?
This is it.
So it seems that all the rumors about that
bastard Kayneth Archibald preparing to fight in some
kind of mages tournament in the Far East soon are true.
The Holy Grail War.
According to the legend, 200 years ago,
the Einzberns, the Makiris, and the Tohsakas,
collectively known as the three first families,
worked together to summon the Holy Grail,
said to have the power to grant
any wish, and eventually succeeded it.
But the Holy Grail would only grant
one of the family's supplications.
Their cooperation quickly turned
to violent and bloody conflict.
That was the beginning of the Holy Grail Wars.
Ever since then, once every 60 years,
the Holy Grail appears in the city of Fuyuki.
It selects seven mages from across the
globe to compete for it, and grants them powers.
Each magically summons a heroic spirit known as a servant.
Archer, Saber, Lancer, Rider, Assassin,
Caster, Berserker.
Divided into these seven classes of
warriors, the servants, guided by their masters,
fight each other to the death in secret battles
to determine who is worthy to win the Grail.
So it appears that this Grail War
is a battle of pure strength where stupid
titles and influence mean absolutely nothing.
That looks like it's the perfect place for me.
Wait, in order to summon a servant some kind of
relic related to them is needed to act as a catalyst.
A relic.
That device always strikes me as being indecent.
There's a report from the Clock Tower.
It looks like Lord El‐Melloi has acquired another relic.
His participation in the war is certain now.
It troubles me that two of the
slots are still unaccounted for.
Don't worry, when the time comes, the
Grail will select seven, regardless of skill.
The ones it selects to round out the group are...
well, often weak and inexperienced.
Don't concern yourself.
Speaking of matters of real concern, Kirei,
I trust that no one followed
you or saw you enter this mansion.
No, don't worry.
No familiars or devices, visible or invisible,
are watching me or this mansion right now.
On that.
You have my guarantee.
No matter what tricks or deception they
use, no one can deceive the eyes of Hassan,
the spy heroic spirit.
There is no trace of anyone following
my master or watching this house.
Please, you can put your mind at ease.
If a servant has been manifested by another master
my father is certain to be aware of it.
The other mages will not take action,
at least for a little while longer.
Assassin, you may go, continue
guarding the surrounding area.
As you wish.
It's only a matter of time before that changes.
Very soon now this place will be swarming with familiars
and magical devices sent by other masters to spy on me.
What is that?
Another investigation.
I've been gathering what information
I can on the Einzbern master.
Nine years ago, the Einzberns, a family
notoriously proud of their pure blood,
suddenly allowed an outsider
mage to marry into the family.
The Einzbern mages have devoted
themselves solely to alchemy,
rendering them unfit for combat.
Their losses in previous Grail
Wars can all be traced to that fact.
They must have finally run out of patience.
The man they chose was perfect for their needs.
Kiritsugu Emiya, the man known as the Mage Killer.
We finally found the relic we've been
searching for in Cornwall all these years.
If you use it as a catalyst you'll be
able to summon what is widely considered
the strongest of all known sword‐wielding servants.
Kiritsugu,
this is the greatest gift the Einzbern can offer
to the man who is working in service to our needs.
Thank you, Elder, I am honored.
This time there are to be no survivors.
You are to hunt down the six
other servants and eliminate them,
and fulfill the third magic, Heaven's Feel.
Yes, sir.
Kiritsugu Emiya?
Yes, I know that name.
So, even the Holy Church has heard of this man.
Kiritsugu Emiya, the Mage Killer,
was quite infamous in his time.
Officially, he was a rogue mage
who didn't belong to the Association,
but the higher ups found him, shall we
say, convenient for their own purposes.
It sounds to me like he was quite similar to us.
Executioners for the Holy Church.
Far worse, I assure you.
He spent his life as a freelance master assassin
who specializes in exterminating mages.
He knows what mages are capable of, so he deals
with them in a way that is unlike a mage as possible.
Read that.
Sniping, poisoning, bombs in public places.
He once brought down an entire jetliner
just because his target was on it.
A man who will do anything without a second thought.
It is because mages function
outside the laws of the regular world
that we must diligently obey the strict
laws that we have set for ourselves.
But this man lacks even a single
trace of a mage's pride or honor.
The methods he employs are unforgivable.
Then tell me, what does this Kiritsugu Emiya gain...
by hiring himself out as a killer?
Money, I would imagine.
As you can read in that report,
he's been involved in more than just mage assassinations.
He's appeared in war zones all over the
planet offering his services as a mercenary.
I see.
May I borrow this for a while?
Let's go over what we know, Iri, all right?
Of the seven masters that the Grail will
choose we have identified four of them.
Tokiomi Tohsaka, Tohsaka family head.
Fire mage, uses jewel magic, very formidable.
Kariya Matou.
So they took the kid who left the
family and made him a master, huh?
That old man must be desperate.
Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald.
Wind and water affinity.
He's a top expert in necromancy, summoning, and alchemy.
And next...
Kiritsugu Emiya.
Newest member of the Einzbern family and
their trump card, and the man that I love.
And the fourth master... no, I mean the fifth one,
is representing the Holy Church.
His name is Kirei Kotomine.
He's from the Church?
He's the son of the overseer, Father Risei Kotomine.
Reports say he studied under Tokiomi
Tohsaka starting three years ago,
splitting with him after his Command Seal appeared.
Did something happen?
This is his personal history.
Read it for yourself.
Kirei Kotomine followed his father on
pilgrimages around the world since childhood,
graduated from the St. Ignatius
School of Divinity in Manresa,
skipped two years, graduated valedictorian.
He sounds pretty impressive.
But then suddenly, he leaves the primrose
path and volunteers for the Holy Church.
Why would someone like that decide to
work for a secret Church organization?
Maybe because of his father?
It says here that Kotomine is a member of
the Holy Church's Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
Then he would've pursued that
path from the very beginning.
But until he arrived at the same place as
his father, he changed positions three times.
At one time he was even an inquisitor.
An inquisitor?
A heretic hunter.
In essence, exactly what I was.
A ruthless mage killer.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
His assassinations were always carried out in
clusters over a relatively short period of time.
During the same general time periods,
he appeared in a number of war zones,
but only when the combat was at its fiercest.
It was almost as if he had some
obsession with chasing his own death.
These were clearly the actions of a man bent on suicide.
So then why is he doing this?
Alchemy, necromancy, summoning, divination, healing.
Interesting, look at all the
categories of magic he studied.
Why did he try to study so many?
He gets almost to the point of mastery of a discipline,
then switches to another field,
and never looks back again.
It's... it's as if he throws away
everything he's learned like yesterday's trash.
Iri, this man, Kirei Kotomine, terrifies me.
He has no concept of self interest.
His actions are completely disconnected
from any thought of risk versus reward.
No way, there's no way he's just
a freelancer in it for the money.
He's never shown any passion
for anything at all in his life.
He believes in absolutely nothing.
He has no deep desire, no wish of any kind to be granted.
A man like that...
Then what is he after?
Why would he put his life at risk to get the Holy Grail?
But the Grail chose him to be one
of its seven masters for this war.
You're right, he must have some reason
we don't know about to want the Grail.
But I can't even begin to imagine
what it is, and that terrifies me.
Kirei Kotomine.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
His endless string of battles came to a sudden halt
nine years ago, and he virtually vanished from sight.
It appears that his final
encounter with the mages of the North,
the Einzberns, is where he at last found his answer.
So, I must ask the question,
what did he seek in those battles?
What was he looking for?
And what exactly did he find?
Well, you just barely made it.
If the Grail has chosen you, that must mean
that you've made at least some progress as a mage.
I'll give you that much, Kariya.
But look at you.
You look like bloody hell.
Is your left leg working all right, eh?
Now don't get angry, you know if you get the crest worms
inside you worked up too much they'll simply devour you.
Either way, I'd give you perhaps a month at best
before they do their damage and drain the life out of you.
That's plenty.
What did you say?
I said that that will be plenty of time.
Kariya, this is your present for surviving an entire year.
I found the perfect relic for you.
Don't let your loving father's kindness go to waste.
I did it, I've got a Command Seal too!
The Grail chose me as a master!
My incredible talent has been recognized by the Grail!
I can't just sit here.
I have to prepare to summon my servant.
Mikina Nishimoto, the missing sixth grade girl from...
Good morning, Waver.
Good morning, dear. How did you sleep?
Morning, Grandpa and Grandma.
Fuyuki's getting bad these days.
Yes, it really is.
By the way, Martha, it's very strange.
I've heard roosters making a big
racket since the sun came up this morning.
What's that all about?
It's because there are three roosters in our yard.
What're they doing there?
I don't know.
I've been wondering where they might've come from.
Oh, sweetie, you want some coffee?
Mhm.
Waver.
What happened to your hand?
Crap.
That mark.
What mark?
You didn't have that mark on your hand yesterday.
Ah, bugger!
I really wish you hadn't noticed that.
What's wrong, Waver?
What is it, dear?
Nothing's wrong, here, have some coffee.
I put lots of milk in it.
You two like coffee, right?
What a pain in the ass.
Do I have to start their hypnosis all over again,
starting from me being their grandson back from abroad?
I need to think of a cover story
for those roosters I stole too.
I can't believe they really found
the legendary Excalibur's scabbard.
There's not a scratch on it.
Is this thing really 1,500 years old?
The object itself is a type of conceptual weapon.
It doesn't rust or degrade as
ordinary physical objects do.
Just like in the legend surrounding its existence, it
heals its owner's wounds and halts the aging process.
Of course, that's only when supplied
with its original owner's mana.
In other words, the master can use this
in tandem with the summoned heroic spirit
to protect himself during the course of a battle.
That's just like you.
What you're saying is that a tool is just a tool?
That's right, I am, and that goes for the servant too.
No matter how famous the heroic spirit,
when summoned as a servant they're nothing
but a tool for their master.
Anyone who lets their fantasies get the better of them
will never have the wherewithal to win this battle.
And because you're the way you
are, my great‐grandfather decided
this scabbard was the perfect relic for you.
What do you think?
Does his gift not satisfy you?
Of course it does.
Acht did a wonderful job.
None of the other masters have something this powerful.
What's wrong with it then?
Given how perfectly the ancient relic is connected to it,
the heroic spirit, the one we're after,
will surely respond to the summons,
the King of Knights, Arthur Pendragon.
My own compatibility with him is a secondary concern.
But Arthur, the wielder of Excalibur,
is sure to be the strongest Saber class
servant the Grail Wars have ever seen.
That's true.
I'll have a servant far stronger
than any other in the battle.
The question is, how best to use that power?
How to make it work for us?
To be honest, in terms of ease of use,
Caster or Assassin would be far
better suited to the way I usually fight.
What good will it do to worry about
that before you've even summoned him?
After all, we don't know what
the King of Knights was like,
and besides, no matter what your strategy is,
once he learns of your ideals, of your dream,
he'll understand, I know he will.
Just like I did.
What is it?
I've found my strategy, the way to get the best use.
From the strongest servant fighting in the battle.
Hello, Rin.
Oh hello, Kirei.
Heading out?
That's some heavy luggage you have there.
That's right, I have to go live
with the Zenjou family for a while.
You're staying to fight alongside
my father in a coming war, aren't you?
That's why I'm here as his student,
to help him and to learn from him.
Kirei, can I depend on you?
Huh?
Will you promise to protect my father to the end?
Will you promise to keep him safe?
I'm sorry, but that's impossible.
If this battle were going to be simple
enough that I could honestly make that promise,
we wouldn't have to send you or your mother
away from here to keep you safe and sound.
I guess that means I just can't like you no matter what.
Rin, you shouldn't just blurt out
what you're really thinking like that.
People might start to cast aspersions on your father.
He is the man who's educating you after all.
My father has nothing to do with it!
Listen, Kirei, if you somehow get sloppy and
because of that my father gets hurt or worse,
I'll show you no mercy, got it?
Rin, what're you doing out there?
How come you're yelling at him?
Um, I... Well, you see...
Oh, she was just giving me a bit of
encouragement before we said goodbye, ma'am.
Rin, allow me.
That big suitcase is far too heavy for you to carry alone.
No thank you, I'll carry it myself.
Kirei, do your best to take care of my husband.
Please help him to achieve his desire.
I will do my best.
Please, don't worry.
Excuse me.
You've arrived at a very opportune time. The relic
I made arrangements for finally arrived this morning.
Have a look.
What is it?
A fossil of the very first skin
shed by a snake on this world.
If we use it as a catalyst and are lucky enough
to summon the heroic spirit that we're after,
total victory is as good as ours.
Hey, Sakura.
Did I startle you?
Yeah, your face is...
I know.
Seems I lost a little bit of it
to the worms that are inside me.
I guess I'm just not quite as tough as you are.
Uncle Kariya, you're turning
into a different person, aren't you?
Yeah, maybe.
You know, I don't have to go
to the worm pit again tonight.
Grandfather said there will be a more
important ceremony that I have to attend.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm going to the
basement tonight instead of you.
Uncle Kariya, are you going somewhere far away?
Well, I have an important job
that I need to do for a while.
I might not have much time to talk
to you then, at least until I get back.
I see.
Hey, Sakura.
When my job is finally over, you
wanna go somewhere and just have fun?
With your mom and your sister too.
I don't have anyone I can call Mom or Sister.
Grandfather said that I should just think of them
like they never existed.
I see.
Uncle?
All right then.
When this is all over let's
take Aoi and Rin from the Tohsakas
and go somewhere as far away
from this place as we can get.
We can hang out and have fun like we used to.
Does that mean we'll see them again?
Yeah, you will.
You have my word on that.
All right.
I have to get going now.
Mhm.
Bye‐bye, Uncle Kariya.
Bye‐bye.
I assume you've memorized the summoning spell correctly?
Sure.
Very well.
But I'm going to have to add two
extra lines to the basic incantation.
What do you mean?
It's really quite simple, Kariya.
Because of your short time in training,
your rank as a mage is somewhat lower than that
of the other masters that the Grail has summoned.
That will affect the servant's base abilities.
This means we have to boost the servant's parameters
by attempting to modify the
servant's class as much as possible.
Kariya, to that end, I want you to add the
affinity insanity to the servant you summon today.
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill.
Repeat five times, but when each is filled, destroy it.
For the elements silver and iron, the
foundation stone and the Archduke of Pacts,
and for my great master, Schenewerk,
raise a wall against the wind and
close the gates of four directions.
Come forth from the crown and follow
the forked road leading to the kingdom.
Is a simple ritual like this really
enough to summon a heroic spirit?
Surprisingly, yes.
You see, the summoning ritual doesn't
require a big elaborate evocation.
The actual summoning is preformed by the Grail itself.
My job as a master is to firmly anchor
the heroic spirit in this world and to supply it
with enough mana to take physical form.
That should do it.
Iri, put the relic on the altar.
That is the final step.
Heed my words, my will creates your
body, and your sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call and obey my
will and reason, then answer my summoning!
I hereby swear that I shall be all the good in the world,
that I shall defeat all evil in the world.
Then let thine eyes be clouded
with the fog of turmoil and chaos.
Thou who art trapped in a cage of madness,
and I the summoner who holds thy chains!
Seventh heaven clad in the great words of power,
come forth from this circle of binding,
Guardian of Scales!
Behold him, Kirei.
We have won the battle.
Victory is ours!
Impossible.
I ask you...
Are you worthy to be my master?
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is right and just.
The world cannot serve two lords.
Then I promise you, you are not worthy to gaze upon me.
You are so cool!
Eliminate Tokiomi Tohsaka at once.