Oreki Hotaro-dono,
"Oreki Hotaro-dono,
Greetings. I am currently in Varanasi. Sorry for
being so late but congratulations on passing.
You ended up going to
Kamiyama High School, I see.
Now that you've safely become
a high school student,
I have some sisterly advice for you.
Join the Classic Lit Club.
It's a time-honored club.
It's also the club that I was in.
From what I've heard, the club
currently has zero members.
Without any new members this year,
the club will be done away with.
As one of the club's old girls,
I couldn't bear for that to happen.
Hotaro,
preserve the Classic Lit Club,
the site of your sister's adolescence.
Even if you just put your name in.
I mean, you don't have anything
else you want to do, right?
Sincerely, Oreki Tomoe."
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
1, 2, 3, 4!
lt's been a month since the
Classic Lit Club made its comeback.
The Prestigious Classic Lit Club's Activities
The Earth
Science prep room has become more familiar than I expected.
... Hello.
... Yo.
If I feel bored after school,
that's where I go.
Help yourself.
Hmm?
Some snacks from home.
Help yourself to anything you like.
Thank you.
It's not as though I ever
disliked being with anyone,
so long as it didn't wear me out.
This is fruitless.
You mean planting two crops a year?
No, that's double-cropping.
Were you trying to make a joke?
Don't ask.
No, I don't mean that.
This is fruitless?
Yes, fruitless.
What is?
Our whole afterschool time! Our days
being spent aimlessly is not productive!
I couldn't agree more.
So, is there something you're
hoping to get out of the Classic Lit Club?
Yes, there is.
Oh?
But that is a personal matter.
She said that before, too.
Right now, I'm talking about
the Classic Lit Club.
As a club, we should have
some club activities.
There's no point.
Yes, there is. We'll submit an anthology
to the culture festival in October.
Anthology?
Yes.
Let's not. It's too much work.
No, there has to be an anthology!
If you want to get involved
with the culture festival,
there are other ways to do it.
Like a refreshment stand.
Kami High's culture festivals have
traditionally prohibited refreshment stands.
Besides, we'll get a budget
provided for the anthology,
and our advising teacher
has asked us to do one, too.
Also, an anthology has been
a tradition for over 40 years,
and they don't want to break it.
In that case, why didn't you say so sooner?
All right, we'll do it.
Okay!
So then, what is this anthology
supposed to contain?
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
Sorry, I thought we could
look into that now.
Anyhow, if there are any back-number
issues, I thought we could start there.
Let's look for them.
They aren't here.
Well, maybe they're in
the library. Let's go see.
What are you doing?
Oreki-san, you're going, too. Come on.
I'm in no mood for this.
It's Friday, so the person
on library duty is probably...
Library
Oh, if it isn't Oreki. Long time
no see. I haven't missed you.
Yo, Ibara. I came to see you.
This is educational sacred ground.
It's not really your bag, is it?
So then, you're saying that it
is yours? How laudable of you.
You're as awful as ever. If you're
here to crack wise, go away.
Um...
Hey, Hotaro! Fancy running into you here.
I see you two are as chummy as ever.
What else would you expect from
Kaburaya Middle School's "Best Couple"?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'd rather be with a slug
than this dismal downer.
Slug...?
Look here, Fuku-chan, you've got
some nerve knowing how I feel
and still making a joke like that.
Ah, sorry, Mayaka. Did I offend you?
There you go again, trying to
change the subject by joking.
Seriously, cut it out, okay?
How do those two know each other?
She's had a crush on Satoshi
since middle school.
Oh...
Ahem...
Chitanda-san, this is Ibara Mayaka.
She went to Kaburaya
Middle School, same as us.
It's a pleasure.
Mayaka, this is Chitanda Eru-san.
She's the president of the
Classic Lit Club, which I recently joined.
The pleasure is all mine.
So anyway, what brings
the both of you here?
Oh, right. Um, Ibara-san,
there's something I'd like to ask.
Okay.
Do you keep any club anthologies here?
From the Classic Lit Club?
The Classic Lit Club...
I don't think we do.
If they're not out here,
maybe they're in the back stacks.
Oh, I see.
Why do you need the anthologies?
We've decided to make an
anthology for the culture festival,
so I thought we'd have a look at
the previous anthologies first.
Oh, yeah? We're presenting it at Kanyasai?
I'm surprised Hotaro went along with that.
It was largely ex-post-facto approval.
"Kanyasai"?
You've never heard of it? It's an abbreviation
for "Kamiyama High School Culture Festival."
It's not another one of your
thought-up abbreviations, is it?
It's for real! All the guys in
the Handicrafts Club call it "Kanyasai."
How about you, Mayaka?
They call it "Kanyasai"
in the Manga Club, too.
"Kanya"? How do they write that?
I don't know. I have asked
around about it, too.
Though it probably started as
Kamiyama High School Bunkasai
being shortened to "Kamiyama-sai,"
then "Kanyama-sai,"
and finally "Kanyasai,"
or at least that's what I think.
So anyway, Chitanda-san,
there may be anthologies
if we check in the back stacks,
but the librarian is out
at a meeting at the moment,
so we can't get in there right now.
I think she'll be back in another
30 minutes or so, though. Want to wait?
What should we do?
Wait, I guess.
You could always leave, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, Hotaro!
Mayaka, can I tell these two
the story you told me earlier?
Huh?
Hmm, okay. Oreki, feel like putting
your brain to work for a change?
No.
What story is this?
The story of the Most Favored
Book of Disfavor.
The Most Favored Book of Disfavor?
It is quite the peculiar tale.
No matter how I look at it,
it doesn't add up.
It has Mayaka and I both
just about baffled.
Please, tell us about it!
I come here every Friday after school,
because I'm on duty, right?
And every week, the same
book gets returned.
Today marks the fifth week in a row.
That by itself is unusual, right?
This is that book.
Wow, what a pretty book.
Kamiyama High School's 50-Year Progress
It's huge.
Would you mind if I looked inside?
Go ahead.
Oreki-san, here, look.
It's a normal school history, huh? Hmm...
It looks like it would be a lot
of work to read through this.
Hmph. It's not so unusual that
someone would check this out every week.
You've never borrowed a book
from here, have you?
The checkout period
at this library is two weeks.
So there's no need to borrow it every week.
Despite which, this book is
also returned each week.
Do you know who it was that borrowed it?
Of course.
The checkout list is inside it,
so take a look.
Huh? Oreki-san, please look at this!
Each week, a different person checks it out.
Suzuki Konoe
Shima Saor
Yamaguchi Ryoko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Kyoko Machida
What's more, they all return it on the very same day.
Suzuki Konoe
That's right. It gets
checked out and returned the same day,
for five weeks in a row now.
I even know the times,
and all five of them check it out
at lunch, and return it after school.
How about it? Got you curious, right?
Yes.
I am curious!
Let's think about this
for a bit, Oreki-san.
Damn it, Satoshi!
See? What do you think? Interesting, right? You
knew this would happen when you stopped me, huh?
Oreki-san, you did such a nice
job of solving that lock matter,
and that secret club business, didn't you?
What do you mean?
It involves a deeply provocative
facet to Hotaro here.
Knock that off. You make it sound sordid.
In any event, it inspires curiosity.
It does not.
It does so!
It does not!
Oreki...
Be quiet. You, too, Chitanda-san.
Right.
Yeah...
That was careless.
Any further refusals or prevarication
will be an inefficient use of energy now.
As such...
Yeah, all right. I guess
I'll think about it.
Okay!
Fuku-chan, was Oreki ever smart?
Not so much. But when it comes
to useless stuff like this,
he can sometimes be helpful.
You're not holding anything back, are you?
Rikka ('Dawn of Summer')
When we hail the rise of summer
Hyouka
For five weeks straight, different people
have borrowed this book,
and then returned it the same day.
It would be easy to insist
that it was a coincidence,
but Chitanda probably
wouldn't be convinced.
The truth isn't what's important here;
it's being able to convince Chitanda.
Now then...
Lunch Break
borrowing the book at
lunch and returning it after school
After School
doesn't leave
very much time for reading it.
Lunch Break + Class Break + Class Break = 65 minutes:
Insufficient
School
Home
If they're not taking it home with them,
No
they can just read it in the
library without borrowing it.
Conclusion: This book is not being
used to fulfill a literary purpose.
Which would mean...
If you were to use the book for something
other than reading, how would you use it?
If you stack a few of them up,
it might make a good pillow.
If you put it on your arm,
it would serve as a shield.
Think about this more seriously.
He's right. There must be some way
that this book in particular is being used.
Okay, Chitanda-san, what do you think?
Let's see.
If you make a stack of them,
they could serve as pickle press.
I'm going to stop asking you guys.
Is Chitanda really an honor student?
She strikes me as being just a doofus.
Let's look at this a different way.
What does it mean that each week,
a different person is borrowing it?
Looking at the names,
they're all girls, aren't they?
One
Two
There are two ways to think about this.
Friday
The girls have nothing in common,
but the book comes into
vogue every Friday afternoon.
Or, the girls use the book as a group,
Friday
and they each take turns
borrowing the book for them to use.
One
Non-group
Two
Group
In vogue, huh?
For fortunetelling, maybe?
Oh, like this! "Your lucky item
this week is the school history!
If you borrow it Friday afternoon,
and return it that same day,
you will get on well with
your boyfriend," maybe?
That's ridiculous.
Besides, it's five weeks in a row.
I was just thinking out loud.
Their common points are
that they're all girls,
and they're all 2nd-years,
but in different classes.
I wonder if there might be some
reason why they're all girls.
There's really no telling. If you pick
five random people out of the school,
there's a fair possibility that
they would all be girls.
It's also not unusual for members
of the same sex to group together.
What if it were some kind of signal?
Like if the book is returned
face-up, it means "yea,"
and face-down means "nay."
Hmm... I don't think you could
signal by which side was up.
See?
Fair point.
Returns Corner
You can't tell which
of those face up or down, huh?
Hmm...
Well, no matter how hard Oreki
racks his brain, that's what you'll get.
After all, Fuku-chan and I thought
as hard as we could about this...
Wh-What is it?
It has an odor about it.
It does?
I don't smell anything.
No, I'm sure of it.
It's a kind of acrid odor.
Like paint thinner.
There's no doubt about it.
Is she a dog?
Yeah, well, if Chitanda-san insists
she smells it, she can't be wrong, huh?
Which would mean...
Hotaro, you've got that look
like you've figured something out.
Huh? Really?
Well, maybe. I can't be positive, though.
Chitanda, are you up for a little exercise?
There's somewhere I'd like you to go.
All right!
Er, no, I'm not going, just you.
Just me? How come?
Well, um...
You're right, Chitanda-san!
You shouldn't let yourself
be used by Hotaro!
Hotaro is most helpful when
you make use of him.
That's a hell of a way to talk about me.
Oh, no, I just thought that if I was
going somewhere, we could go together.
Ah, I see.
Okay, let's go, Oreki-san!
Come right on in.
Welcome to our establishment.
We have two menus prepared for you.
Gray Course
Rosy Course
Which one would you like?
I recommend this course.
Today's problems might end up
costing you surprisingly dearly.
Rosy Course
Oreki-san...?
Ugh, all right. Today's gym class
got washed out due to rain,
so I still have some
discretionary energy left.
Okay!
Just how limited is your energy, anyway?
Leave me alone.
Okay, let's go.
Right.
Hold up.
I'm going, too. I'm a little curious.
Fuku-chan, would you cover
my desk for a bit?
Huh?
After all, I can't just abandon
my library duties, right?
See you, Satoshi.
Hold down the fort here.
So then, Oreki-san, where are we going?
The art room.
In the building across the way?
Yep, far away. That's why
I didn't want to go.
You really are lazy, huh?
What's over there?
First, let's set things straight.
Lunch Break
As far as how the book is being used,
After School
there aren't any girls using anything
that huge during their breaks.
No
Which means the only conceivable
use would be during class time.
Class
What are the only classes that have
students from the same year,
but taken from different homerooms?
Gym and fine arts subjects, right?
Gym
Music
Art
Calligraphy
Right. Each week before class, those five
took turns coming to borrow the book.
I don't get why they would do it each week.
The checkout period lasts for two weeks.
With a book that big,
it would be easier returning it each week
than lugging it around, right?
Ah, that's true.
What's the matter?
It's the same smell as the book.
Really?
Look inside and see for yourself.
That's what the book is being used for.
The 2nd-year D, E, and F combined classes
painted pictures for their art class.
The book's binding makes it
a perfect motif for a painting.
It was the smell of paint.
How did you figure it out?
How did I...?
Just a stroke of inspiration.
I simply got lucky.
Library
Wow, nicely done, nicely done!
I never would have imagined
using it as a motif in a painting.
How did you ever figure that out?
Oreki, you're weird.
What are you talking about?
There's nobody more average than I am.
Well, I don't know about that.
Still, you really did
surprise me, Oreki-san.
I'm interested in what goes on
inside that head of yours.
You're interested?
Yes.
I'd even like to crack it open
and look around inside.
It's not that fancy a brain.
There's nothing for an honor student
like you to gain by looking at it.
Oh, yeah? You're an honor student?
That's right. We haven't
had our midterms yet,
but I'm sure her grades will be
at the top of the class for our year.
Oh, no. No matter how good a grade I get,
it's nothing more than
putting all the parts together.
It's not the individual parts, but how his
system of thought develops that I want to know.
Uh-huh...
For that matter,
it's her sense of smell that remains
a far greater mystery to me.
Knowing Oreki-san, it's
just possible that...
Hmm?
Oh, nothing. Never mind.
Well, in any event, I had a
fairly entertaining time of it.
What about you, Chitanda-san?
Of course I had fun!
The time seemed to fly by.
I spent hours on it, and still
didn't get it. It's so frustrating!
Didn't I tell you he could
come in handy once in a while?
But I just can't accept
being outdone by Oreki!
It really is frustrating!
Now, now, Mayaka, take it easy!
Something's off.
Something is off here.
I can't ever be like this.
What's off here? What is it?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Once in a long while,
there's a flash of light,
and in an instant...
Oreki-san, you can't leave!
Why not? Oh, the anthologies.
That's right. We have to
wait for the librarian.
Sometimes Hotaro does
go out to lunch, huh?
Sometimes? Are you sure you
aren't overestimating that?
Hmph.
Ibara-san, thank you. You can leave now.
Oh, right. You are back, Itoigawa-sensei?
Sensei, I am Fukube Satoshi,
from the Classic Lit Club.
We are looking for back-number issues,
so we can make our own anthology.
Would it be okay if we checked the stacks?
Classic Lit Club? Anthologies?
You're in the Classic Lit Club?
Oh, unfortunately, the anthology
back-numbers aren't in the stacks.
Are you sure they haven't been overlooked?
If they were there, I'd remember.
Well, if you'll excuse me...
Huh... Thank you!
There you have it, Chitanda-san.
This is a problem.
We'll find them soon enough.
What do you say, Oreki?
Was it refreshing to solve that problem?
Not especially.
Oh, really?
I guess that's that. Let's go home.
I did glean something today, and all.
What does that mean?
Nothing. It's a personal matter.
Oh, that again?
Yes, knowing Oreki-san,
it's just possible...
Yes, Oreki residence.
Hello? I-It's Chitanda.
Chitanda?
Um, I'm sorry. You weren't
sleeping, were you?
Oh, you know. I thought you
were my sister calling.
So, what are you calling for on a Sunday?
If you'll forgive me, I'd like
to see you today, if possible.
Pineapple Sand
There is something I
earnestly need to speak to you about.
She's taking her time.
P-Please excuse me for
bringing you out here.
Yeah...
So, was there something you wanted?
Huh?
I'm asking you why you asked me
out to this coffee shop.
You're the one who suggested
this place, Oreki-san.
I'm out of here.
Huh? P-Please wait!
It's my precious Sunday! I can't squander
it playing along with one of your bits!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm just nervous.
Nervous, huh?
Are you planning to confess
your love to me, or something?
There may be something
I have to confess, yes.
Huh?
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "The Circumstances
of the Classic Lit Club's Scion."
The Circumstances of the Classic Lit Club's Scion