When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Here, Kuzuha-sama.
Say "Ahh..."
Ahh.
Our school's butler field rating has...
...Dropped by three points.
They're slacking.
A butler shall stand firm even after getting run over by a car speeding at 80km/h,
or even after getting stepped on by a giant robot.
Excuse me, you have cream on by your lip.
They only deserve to be called professionals when they can do those.
Am I not right, Shion?
Yes, you are.
But still...
Let's see...
If a butler with a poor man's face that makes me want to hit him,
in his late teens, 168cm tall, and about 57kg existed somewhere...
If one existed...
I wouldn't mind having some fun with him.
It's autumn.
It sure is.
Tama, stop it.
Hey, stop it.
I get the feeling someone, somewhere, is calling for me.
Let's get the new one going, shall we?
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
Yes! I just came up with a great pastime.
Um, who are you?
I've done it. It's finally complete.
Congratulations.
I'm sure you'll get the rookie award this time.
Y-Yeah.
Then... take this manuscript...
Yes, I will send it to the publisher.
And, when you got to school, bring my *S* back from my desk.
You left something behind?
I left C**sis Core in it.
So, thanks.
Milady, please get a good rest.
Yeah...
It's a normal, peaceful day.
Although it's a bit of a shame that Milady couldn't come with me.
Good morning, Hayate-kun.
Hinagiku-san.
Are you by yourself?
Is Nagi skipping again?
Well, yes.
Good morning, fellow students of Hakuou Academy.
I have an announcement.
This voice is-
Hinagiku-san, look!
Just so you know, this is not a joke.
I'm serious.
What is this?
She's planning on doing something stupid again!
Wait!
What's this?
Sh-Shine!
The First...
...Hakuou Academy...
...Butler...
...Battle...
...Tournament.
Hinagiku-san.
Um, please calm down.
What's going on?
Stand back, Hayate-kun.
I'm surprised you found me.
You indeed are the school's Student Council President.
Um, who is she?
She's this school's superintendent.
S-Superintendent?
That's me.
What is this?!
Butler Battle Tournament? It doesn't make any sense!
It's as you see.
I wanted to test the levels of the butlers we have on campus.
And I also have a personal interest, too.
A butler who's strong, tough, and worth playing with.
I'm looking for someone like that.
I... I felt a chill down my back.
Anyways, she seems like a really wild person.
So basically, you want to make
the students toys and play with them!
"Play" you say?
Power levels are one of the most important aspects looked for in butlers.
But the butlers in this school are all diligent students.
For example, we have Hayate-kun here.
I see.
Then I'll ask him directly.
What? Have I been made
the center of attention without knowing it?
Boy.
From the looks of it, you're a butler, too.
Answer my question.
Yes.
A battle tournament to measure
the butlers' strength is meaningless.
Yes or No?
U-Um...
Tick
I won't call it "meaningless",
but aren't there more important things?
Like a caring heart towards one's master.
You don't understand anything, boy!
Hayate-kun, use this!
Not too bad.
Don't drag me into the battle world.
But, you're nowhere near strong enough!!!
What should I do? This is my fault.
A butler is the person who must protect
their master even at the cost of their life.
Boy, what would you do if I were someone after your master's life?
Can you still say that strength is meaningless to a butler?
That's...
An opening!
Educational guidance!
Watch out!
Her battery ran out.
No... My blood sugar level...
Sh-Shion...
S... Snacks...
Yes, I have them ready in your office.
Are they sweet?
Yes, very.
Shion.
Kuzuha-sama.
No~
What is wrong with these people?
Allow me to explain.
Hakuou Academy's Superintendent, Kuzuha Kirika,
possesses a power level three times that of an ordinary person,
however the moment she uses up her energy, she drops to the floor.
How dare you do this to my dear Kuzuha-sama.
I won't forgive you.
What?
This is all my fault?
Could this be a territory created by her aura?
My name is Shion.
The kanji goes "poem" "sound".
And you read it as "Shion".
I-I see.
I'm-
She's good.
She took away my freedom of movement instantaneously.
The world's coming to an end for the likes of you to be a butler.
You're so weak.
How about you quit being a butler and become a maid instead?
It's more fitting for you.
If it's frustrating, then come to the tournament.
The winner receives the right to challenge me.
But then, I'm sure it's impossible for you.
Um, Hayate-kun.
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
It's fine.
Um!
Will you act like... that... never happened?
O-Okay.
What's with this flow?
Butler Battle Tournament?
Um, I have something I want to ask.
The superintendent of Hakuou Academy... what is she like?
And is there something between her and Hinagiku-san?
Oh, you met her?
Y-Yes.
That superintendent is a real problem-causing character.
Like changing the field trip site to the Amazon just
to kill her boredom. Mind you, not Amazon on the 'net.
Another time, again to kill her boredom, she tried to put a ****k in the pool.
I see...
So just like that, Hinagiku is trying to protect the students and the world from the evil superintendent's hand.
W-Wait!
That last cut was...
I won't say much.
It's best that you stay away from
the superintendent and her butler.
But, Butler Battle Tournament, eh? That came out of nowhere.
Let's see.
The winner gets a hundred credits as the prize?
So basically the winner can skip school all they want.
Hayate, why don't you try competing in this battle?
What? You're not trying to get-
No, I don't care about the hundred credits.
Whatever happens, I'll skip when I feel like it.
Rather than that, Hayate...
I want to see you win the tournament with my own eyes.
W-Win the tournament, you say?
Yes! Since Sanzenin butlers have to be invincible.
In other words,
you're invincible!
Invincible!
Therefore you'll win!
Milady...
Things are heating up.
I bet you can do this.
Or this.
You can do all sorts of stuff.
And I don't have the chance to see them that often.
Um, so judging from the flow,
I have to go to the tournament no matter what?
But, if Milady has such high hopes in me...
Katsura Hinagiku-kun.
This is a warning.
You're only a commoner without a butler, after all.
You're better off not butting in and staying out of this matter.
I found it in the Student Council's drop box.
For your information, the exterior was initially sticky from black honey.
I see. So she had a Japanese pastry for her snack today.
Note: This is a pun - Japanese pastry (Wagashi) versus My Master (Waga shi)
We don't care about that!
Is there any way to intervene in this tournament?
But I don't have a butler...
What should I do?
I know what I'm doing.
I'll ask Kotetsu-kun for a favor.
Lucky to actually have a butler.
Yes, the hundred credits are appealing.
What should Miki and I do?
You there! Don't be lured by evil's temptation.
Hina.
I have an idea.
Um, I think you should stay out of danger.
No, I've made up my mind.
Maria-san, I will enter the Butler Battle Tournament.
I can't betray Milady's expectations.
All right, I'm on fire now.
I will choose to go with the flow!
H-His simplicity doesn't change even if it goes into a dashing storyline.
What will butler Hayate's destiny be?
And, the day of the tournament has come already.
Bushi ni nigon ha nai.
Bushi ni nigon ha nai. = A samurai does not take back his words.
Ichido shineba nido shinanu.
Ichido shineba nido shinanu. = Die once, and you'll never die again.
I-Is that fire?
We will now start the
"Shine! The First Butler Battle Tournament!"
I am the superintendent of this school, Kuzuha Kirika.
Fight, everyone!
Compete!
I'm counting on you all for a fight that's not shameful as butlers!
It's finally the day, Hayate.
Yes.
I'll make it to you, Poem-person.
We will now start the first match!
In the red corner!
Butler of the Something-or-Another family!
Extra One!
In the blue corner!
Butler of the Segawa Family!
Kotetsu!
I never knew our class president had a butler.
I don't see anyone coming out.
I asked him so many times, too!
Farewell, Urakari Railway.
I can't get enough of this round body.
Right? Right? Don't you agree?
W-Winner, red corner!
Don't make fun of me!
Moving to the second match.
Hey, Ayasaki! You're competing, too?
O-One of the very kind people?
Why are they here?
I hired him as my temporary butler.
Asakaze-san.
I lost to Miki in janken.
So I used my connections.
What kind of connections?
Janken?
Fight!
Kill that guy!
Give 'em a lesson!
I-I give up!
Please! Keep that hidden!
Allow me to explain.
A butler's soul is his necktie.
Regardless of the amount of damage,
the butler who has his necktie taken away loses.
W-Winner, the Asakaze butler, Kashiwagi!
S-So his name was Kashiwagi-san.
But...
Well done. Keep it up and get the hundred credits for me.
I'll do what I'm paid for.
SFX: Giggle
So dark.
Something is really dark.
Next is the third match.
In the red corner, the Azumamiya family butler.
Nonohara Kaede!
Nonohara! Win this tournament!
Get the hundred credits!
Fight! Go!
Nonohara-san.
And he's facing...
It's me.
Hanabishi family's temporary butler!
Katsura Hinagiku!
Wh-Why is Hinagiku-san here?
A-A butler?
That's because I gained the right to negotiate by winning in janken against Risa.
Hina wants to fight against the superintendent.
I want to get the hundred credits.
You can call it a consensus over motivation.
We practically have the victory.
My my, a temporary butler, are you?
Our profession really has been looked down upon.
I'm sorry if I insulted you.
But I didn't enter to belittle the event.
Then let's get this started!
Yes.
W-Wow.
You're pretty good.
You're really laidback, Nonohara-san.
Why aren't you using your ultimate move?
Th-That's because...
Nonohara! Win!
Get the hundred credits!
But don't hit Katsura-san!
No matter how strong your attacks may be,
I, Katsura Hinagiku, will do whatever it takes to evade them!
Very well.
Then here I go.
Safety Shutter!
I won't lose!
What's wrong? Is that all?
Safety-
Nonohara-san, your move takes
a little too much time to get going.
Looks like I win.
W-Winner, Katsura Hinagiku!
Thank you for not going easy just because I'm a girl.
No matter who it is, it's a butler's duty to fight them seriously.
Besides,
my master doesn't wish for me to win against you.
Nonohara-san.
How's that?!
I'm a step closer to where you are!
So good.
Yes, very good.
Hinagiku-san.
And Hayate's turn is here.
All right, the next match.
In the red corner, the Sanzenin family's butler,
Ayasaki Hayate!
All right, let's do this.
And who's my opponent?
In the blue corner!
Who could be under the mask?
The Mystery Butler!
Unauthorized K!
Who could it be? I sense a master's aura.
Yeah. And he even has a tiger with him.
Who could he be?
No clue.
But don't let your guard down, Hayate.
Who could this mysterious butler and the tiger be?
Next week, we'll fight against a crisis.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
'morning. It's Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
Starting today, the opening and the ending are brand new, giving us a fresh start.
You're right, Milady.
We should be able to go for another half a year.
I had a lot of worry in my head, but things do work out.
Not really.
This show is being watched from many different angles.
About the new opening, theme.
The theme is as large as the galaxy.
You think?
Of course, it's a pretty good song.
Later!
So many months have passed since then.
Hayate, thank you for your hard work.
Milady.
Hakuou Academy, Butler Battle Tournament.
It's come down to the finals.
What will happen to Ayasaki Hayate?
Will he be able to stand to the last?
I have something I must protect.
Hayate.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Black Hayate.
When crossing a crosswalk, make sure to look both ways even when it's green.