Yuzuki-san was crying...
And with a pillar right there...
it'll feel like the city is just about to disappear.
If everything disappears...
Will Yuzuki-san's sorrow disappear too?
I'm home, Grandma!
Welcome back!
H-Huh?
I was thinking of staying over tonight.
Yuzuki-chan is helping me out with dinner.
She's really skilled with a knife.
Oh stop it, Grandma!
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
These stewed potatoes are really tasty!
Why, thank you. Eat as much as you want.
Okay! Ruuko, c'mon and eat some more!
O-Okay...
Is it really okay for Yuzuki-san not to go home?
Whew! That bath felt really good!
Yuzuki-san...
Stuffed myself with food and took a hot bath. Now I'm Enercharged!
Orichalcum, Attack!
Th-That tickles, Y-Yuzuki-san!
Take this, and that!
S-Stop it!
Sorry about earlier...
I said some horrible things to you.
I don't know what you're thinking, Ruuko!
I don't know what she's thinking...
No, it's fine! Don't worry about it.
It doesn't bother me one bit.
You know...
In my battle against Akira...
I didn't want to lose no matter what.
I know.
I...
have someone that I like.
But he'll never return my feelings...
How can you know? I mean, you are cute and all.
No, it just won't happen.
It shouldn't...
But if my wish came true,
I could like him just like anyone else...
Wait. Could it be that you like Kazu—
Attack!
Oh, stop it already!
I wonder what it feels like to be in love.
I guess it gets you really excited, right?
Excited? Excited in battle! Tama!
Sender: Kazuki
Subject: Dinner
We had your favorite
okonomiyaki for dinner.
I kept some for you,
so warm it up
tomorrow.
Kazuki...
Received Mail
Sender: Akira
Subject: Hey there!
Introduce me to your
friend!
Sender: Akira
Subject: Hey there!
Introduce me to your
friend!
Received Mail
Sender: Akira
Subject: Hey there!
Introduce me to your
friend!
Received Mail
Sender: Akira
Subject: Want to battle
I want to battle Ruu-Ruu.
Sender: Akira
Subject: Want to battle
I want to battle Ruu-Ruu.
Received Mail
Sender: Akira
Subject: Want to battle
I want to battle Ruu-Ruu.
Received Mail
Sender: Akira
Subject: Don't ignore me
No ignoring, no bullying,
got it?!
Huh? She went home already?
Yeah, like, a while ago.
Okay, thanks.
Hitoe-san was writing about decks and battle progression.
So I decided to try to do it, too.
That's a good idea. You can look at your deck objectively like that.
Hitoe-san?
She ran away...
Um...
U-Um, I...
I...
I would like to be friends with you, Ruuko-san!
I want to be your friend...
Huh?
Thank you!
Yeah, we're friends!
Yuzuki-san, you too!
You don't mind, right?
Being her friend? Sure, why not?
T-Two friends at once?!
WIXOSS is so wonderful.
Huh?
When I was battling Akira-san, it was so painful that I thought I was going to break.
Yeah, I know that feeling.
Selector battles are painful.
I thought that was natural since
you're trying to attain your wish.
But while I was battling Ruuko-san,
I enjoyed it from the bottom of my heart.
Really? Me too!
Well then, let's play a game of WIXOSS to celebrate our friendship.
That's a great idea!
B-But, if Selectors battle each other,
someone's wish will...
No need to worry.
As long as Hanayo-san and the others aren't in our decks, we can just hold regular card battles.
O-Oh...
All right, you three wait here.
Have fun, Hitoe.
I will!
Turn end.
It's your turn now, Hitoe-san.
Okay!
I want to play, too!
We did rock-paper-scissors, remember? You're next.
Okay...
Jeez...
I'll summon Baromet.
Huh?
U-Uhm...
Baromet's power is 7000, so won't it get banished by Yuzuki-san's LRIG's ability after it grows?
You're right...
Hey, Ruuko! Stop saying stuff from the sidelines!
I-I'm sorry...
Tama wants to join!
Tama and Ruuko are really alike.
I guess Hitoe's wish already came true.
She doesn't need to battle anymore.
Are you sure you're okay with that?
Yeah.
But that means you...
It's fine...
Not that, Yuzuki!
What?
Ah, I'm sorry. I called you by name.
It's okay, I don't mind.
I'm calling you by name already too, y'know?
I can feel your friendship, it's so beautiful.
Then why don't you call us by name too, Hitoe-san?
I'll call you "Hitoe," too.
O-Okay... Then, R-Ruuko, Yuzuki...
That feels so weird!
Oh, come on.
It's so weird!
I haven't seen Hitoe smile like that before.
I wish I wasn't her LRIG.
We're not allowed to say that.
Right...
Tama likes Ruu!
I like Ruu. Tama likes being Ruu's LRIG!
But...
That's right.
After all, Tama and Ruuko are friends.
Yup!
Hanayo, Tama is...
Yeah, she doesn't know.
I see.
I'm next!
You really like WIXOSS, don't you?
Yup, I really, really like it!
Right! At the entrance gate!
What happened?
It looks like Akira is here!
You mean the model?
No way!
Aww... Ruu-Ruu went home already?
That's so mean, breaking a promise like that.
Akira knows Kominato-san?
Who's Kominato?
How dare she make Akira sad.
No...
Ruu-Ruu didn't do anything bad.
I'll come back again...
But what should I do if she goes home early again?
It'd be great if someone would let Akira know about Ruu-Ruu...
Akira's so gallant!
I'll do it! I'll let you know for sure!
I'll do it!
I'll let you know, too!
Thank you! Well, I have a shoot I need to go to, so see you!
I don't wanna go home...
You can't be running from Kazuki forever, you know?
But...
Yuzuki!
Akira...
It looks like Akira came to our school.
You're too strong, Ruuko!
Now then! Milk tea for me!
I'll have some sweet bean soup.
Right, right. I come back and all of a sudden I'm the errand boy, huh?
Come on already!
Ruuko, you look happier now.
Huh?
Next, Ruu-chan is going to battle me. Whoever loses has to clean the bath.
But Grandma, you're too good!
I wish we could battle and have fun like this all the time.
But...
Battling with Tama is a lot more fun.
Not just for play.
But in a battlefield.
Battles against Selectors.
But those are battles for everyone's wishes.
I don't have any wishes,
so I shouldn't get in their way.
Ruu-chan?
Ah, sorry! It's my turn, right?
Akira-san is looking for me?
Yeah.
She really wants to battle you, Ruuko-san.
Man, she's so persistent!
But I don't have any wishes.
Even if I lose to Akira-san,
it won't mean much...
Stop right there!
I'll protect you, so don't you worry.
O-Okay...
Listen...
There'll probably be some bad rumors
about you, but just try to ignore them.
She's trying to disturb you as much as she can.
That won't be a problem.
I don't even have any other friends.
Ruu-Ruu!
Good morning, Ruu-Ruu.
We've been waiting for you.
Let's go to class.
Oh, that's right. I just got a message from Aki-lucky.
She invited us to come down to the photo studio with you.
And she said she'd show us around the studio if we went together.
We might even get to meet Iona—
We can't go. We have something to do after school.
You're not invited, so shut it!
What?!
C'mon, Ruu-Ruu!
Let's go!
Uhm, but...
Ruuko...
"There is no stronger bond of friendship than a mutual enemy..."
Okay, that will be it for today. The remainder...
Ruuko, let's go home!
Yuzuki...
Hey, now...
Can students from other classes please refrain from entering?
We're leaving anyways!
C'mon, Ruuko!
C-Coming...
I won't let you go!
Hey girls, what are you doing?
Shut it, Scrub-face!
S-Scrub-face?
Don't let them get away!
Send a message to everyone!
There they are!
Go!
Get out of the way, gramps!
Ruuko, this way!
Okay!
They're really persistent!
It's okay, Yuzuki. I'll just go and battle her.
Remember how I said that I didn't know what you were thinking?
Well, I do know one thing now for sure.
That you really like having WIXOSS battles.
Battling Akira is going to be really painful.
Battling her may make you hate WIXOSS.
I don't want that to happen.
Yuzuki...
Did they go this way?
The freshmen said they saw them.
This is bad.
I'll draw them outside, so you stay put here.
Huh? But...
Don't worry. I'll catch you later.
There they are!
Don't let them get away!
Yuzuki must be really worried about me.
There's no way I can tell her...
That even if I'm hurt or pained...
I want to battle Akira-san...
Ruu?
Ruu and Tama are same!
Want to battle Akira!
Tama is... scary...
I'm... like Tama.
...scary.
I don't know what Ruuko is thinking about.
She's scary.
No!
Yuzu—
Ruu-Ruu...
Found you.
We've brought her!
No ways! Seriously? Shucks, thanks!
Anything for Aki-lucky!
You're awesome! Yay!
Okay then, Ruu-Ruu, let's go!
Um, what about us?
I've got a photo shoot, so leave.
W-Weren't you gonna show us around the studio?
This is no place for uglies like yourself.
Don't bother me.
No one will get in our way here.
Now, let's start our battle.
A battle against Akira-san...
Hey, if you're going to battle, let me in too.
She's...
Damn it! Stop trying to take my prey!
I don't mind facing you either.
What?!
Why don't you want to battle me?
Are you scared of me?
Akira!
What are you doing? You're up next.
W-Wait, uh, just a moment. I'm...
Hurry it up!
I mean, just wait a...
Just hurry up! Everyone is waiting for you.
Th-Thank you very much.
Why are you thanking me?
Huh?
You wanted to battle, didn't you?
You wanted to battle Akira.
No...
Anyone would have been fine so long as you could play WIXOSS.
You wanted to play for real, right?
Do you want to...
do it with me?
You...
don't have any wishes.
For someone without a wish to participate as a WIXOSS Selector is...
blasphemy.
That isn't allowed.
That
Wish
is
Blasphemy
Blasphemy...
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
WIXOSS party?
There might be Selectors there, you know?
Why didn't I notice?
I figured I could tie it up for once.
Stop saying weird things like that.
That's kind of scary.
That
Vow
is
Illicit
That vow is illicit.