Just like the cruel angel
Young boy, become a legend
Even though the untested breeze
taps at the door to your heart
You just look solely at me and smile
So intent on seeking out that gentle touch
Such innocent eyes, still ignorant
of their destiny
But someday, you are sure to realize
that upon your back
You have the wings with which to fly
towards the distant future
The cruel angel's thesis
Soon, you will take flight from the windowsill
With your torrent of ardent pathos
If you are to betray our memories
You, who embrace these heavens and shine
Young boy, become a legend
Hey, Shin, did you change the soup stock?
Yeah, it's a bonito stock.
It's a gift from Miss Ritsuko.
That was HOT!
I'm sorry.
You always apologize right away,
but do you actually feel sorry?!
It's like you apologize automatically
so that you don't get yelled at!
I'm sorry.
Exactly like that. You're just
fundamentally too self-deprecating!
Now, now, that's just his way.
Just his way?! You're being too soft on him!
Haven't you been a little
too soft on Shiniji lately?
Have I?
Maybe you and Mr. Kaji have hooked up again,
but don't project your happiness
on other people!
There's nothing between Kaji and me.
Hey, Katsuragi, I've found a bar
that serves a decent drink.
How about tonight? Bye!
Sure, I've never been involved in
an indecent adult relationship!
And here you're acting like a proper guardian?!
You hypocrite!
You make me puke!
Episode Sixteen
Sickness
Unto Death,
And...
B-type harmonics test, no problems.
Projected adjustment values have been cleared.
You look tired, Miss Misato.
Yeah, for a lot of private reasons.
Kaji?
Shut up!
Well, how's the Third Child doing?
Take a look.
Let me see.
I hope that knowing this
will boost his confidence.
Can you hear me, Shinji?
Miss Misato, how were my test scores?
Yes! You are Number Onel!
Oh, man! He beat us so easily.
To be honest, getting beat that easily
is a little frustrating, don't you think?
He's amazing, wonderful,
awesome, too awesome!
The great invincible Shiniji!
This just means we get to
take it easy now, right?
But I guess we should at least
do our best not to be left behind.
Goodbye.
New Tokyo-3 — Yumoto Station
Please press this button
if you would like to get off
Next stop is Seisho Kabuse.
Next stop, Seisho Kabuse.
Convenient to the Bashar, used books
and video game stores...
All right.
Alert
Five minutes until evacuation of
the Western District is completed.
Target is advancing slowly at 2.5 kmfhr.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
What's going on? What about
the radar observation center at Fu;ji?
They didn't detect it. It just suddenly
appeared directly above us.
Pattern orange. No AT Field detected.
What does that mean?
A new kind of Angel?
The Magi are withholding judgment.
Damn! Commander lkari just had to be gone
at a time like this.
Can you all hear me?
I've sent you all of the target's data.
That's all we know right now.
Approach it carefully and observe its reactions,
and, if possible, lure it into the airspace
outside of the city limits.
One of you take point and the other two
are backup, got that?
Ma'am?!  think Shinji ought to take point!
Well, this is a job for the
high-scoring, utterly fearless,
Number One synch-rate holder, right?
Or don't you feel up to it, Shin?
I can do it!
I'll show you how it's done, Asuka.
What was that?!
Hey, you two...
You said it, didn't you? "You are Number One!"
Well, that was...
Combat is a man's job!
Talk about out of date!
Unit 02 will back him up.
Unit 00 will back him up as well.
Damn kids, running with it...
Shinji's gotten to be quite admirable, hasn't he?
No, I'm going to have to chew him out
when he gets back.
You'll make a good guardian.
Power Source Ahead
State of Emergency Declared:
Closed to General Traffic
Ayanami, Asuka, are you in position yet?
Not yet.
You know there's no way
we could move that fast!
Not yet.
You know there's no way
we could move that fast!
Power Source
Not there yet?
Il go ahead and stop it on my own.
It disappeared!
What?!
Pattern blue! Angel confirmed!
Directly beneath Unit 01!
What?!
Pattern blue! Angel confirmed!
Directly beneath Unit 01!
A shadow?!
What is this?! It's weird!
Shinji, get out of there! Shin;ji?!
Ikari?
You idiot, what are you doing?!
Miss Misato, what's going on?!
Miss Misato? Asuka! Ayanami!
Where's the backup?
Miss Misato?! Can you hear me?! Miss Misato!
Eject the plug! Send the signal!
It's not working! No response!
Miss Misato! Miss Misato!
Shinji!
Asuka! Rei! Rescue Unit 01! Hurry!
That idiot. What's the point of doing well
only on practice exams?!
It disappeared again.
Asuka, be careful.
A shadow?
No!
The city!
Asuka, Rei, pull back.
Bu...
Wait!
Unit 01 and Ikari are still in there.
This is an order. Retreat.
This must be tough for Major Katsuragi.
They reeled the umbilical cable back in,
but the other end was missing.
Then...
There's not much energy
in the internal batteries.
But if Shinji doesn't just
flail around with the Eva,
and can hang in there in life support mode,
then he can survive for sixteen hours.
Second Tank Platoon deployed.
Roger. Hold your current positions and stand by.
Sub laser circuit has been opened.
Transmitting data now.
Confirmed. New line transmitting data.
The UN forces have completely surrounded it.
What about the shadow?
It hasn't moved.
It stopped spreading once it reached
a diameter of just over 600 meters.
But are the ground troops going to be any use?
They think they're applying pressure on us.
Good grief!
Taking matters into his own hands,
ignoring the plan.
Honestly, talk about getting what he deserved.
Just because he got a little better score
on yesterday's tests,
he was going to show me how it's done?!
What a big-headed idiot!
What? Is my bad-mouthing of Shinji
that much of a problem for you?!
Do you pilot Eva just for the praise of others?
No! Not of others! I do it because
I want to be able to praise myself!
Cut it out, you two!
That's right, he went out on his own.
So I'll just have to scold him
when he comes back.
I never thought sleeping
could be this exhausting.
Still blank.
No radar or sonar reflections at all.
This space must be too big.
It's been twelve hours since
I switched to life-support mode.
So my life will end in another four or five hours.
I'm hungry.
So, that shadow is actually the Angel's body?
Correct. It's six hundred eighty
meters in diameter
with a thickness of three nanometers.
The ultra-thin space is supported by
an inwardly-directed AT Field.
The inside is an imaginary space,
called a Sea of Dirac.
I think it's probably connected
to another universe.
What about the sphere?
It disappears when the imaginary circuit
of the body closes.
The object in the sky is the real shadow.
So the black shadow that swallowed
Unit 01 is the target.
Then there's no way that we can fight it.
The water is getting cloudy!
The purification system is giving out.
It stinks in here!
Blood! It smells of blood!
No! I don't want to be here!
Why can't l open the lock?
Open up! Let me out!
Miss Misato, what's going on?!
Miss Misato! Asuka! Ayanami!
Miss Ritsuko!
Father...
Please, someone help me.
A forced Eva salvage?
It's the only possibility that might work.
We would drop all 992 existing
N2 mines into its center,
while simultaneously activating the
AT Fields of the remaining Evas,
disrupting the Angel's imaginary circuit
for one millisecond.
In that instant, we'll concentrate
all the explosive energy,
and destroy the Angel along
with the Sea of Dirac that forms it.
But with that, the body of the Eva...
There's no telling what would happen to Shiniji.
That can't be called a rescue operation!
This operation's top priority is
to recover Unit 01 itself.
Heavy damage to the body is irrelevant.
Now wait a second!
In this case, the pilot's life is not our concern.
If Shinji's lost, it's your fault. Don't forget that!
Why are you and Commander lkari
so worried about Unit 01?
What in the hell is an Eva?
I've given you all the information.
You're lying!
Misato, trust me.
I'm taking command of this entire operation.
We'll be sending some flights to
Kansai International Airport as well.
Contact Air Traffic Control and the
JADF's Air Transport divisions.
Roger.
The Second Impact, the
Instrumentality Project, Adam...
There are still secrets that I'm in the dark about.
Who's there?
Shinji Ikari.
That's me.
I am you. People have another
self within themselves.
The self is always composed of two people.
Two people?
The self which is actually seen,
and the self observing that.
There are many entities called Shinji lkari.
The other Shiniji Ikari that exists in your mind.
The Shiniji Ikari in Misato Katsuragi's mind,
the Shinji in Asuka Sohryu,
the Shinji in Rei Ayanami,
and the Shinji in Gendo lkari.
All are different Shinji lkaris,
but each of them is a true Shinji lkari.
You are afraid of those Shiniji lkaris
in other people's minds.
I'm afraid of other people hating me.
You're afraid of being hurt.
Who is at fault?
Father is the one who is at fault.
The father who deserted me.
It's my fault.
There you go, always immediately thinking
that it's your fault!
That's why I say you're self-deprecating!
I can't do anything.
You just believe that you can't do anything.
Don't you have faith in your father?
I think I hate him, but now I'm not sure.
Good work, Shiniji.
My father called me by my name.
I was praised by my father!
You're going to spend the rest of your life
ruminating on that happiness?
If I believe in those words, I can keep on living.
As you continue to deceive yourself?
Everybody does it!
That's how everyone survives.
Believe that you're fine with the way things are,
or you won't be able to keep living.
There's too much hardship in this world
for me to keep living.
For example, the fact you can't swim?
Humans aren't made to float!
That is self-deception.
I don't care what you call it!
You've shut your eyes and turned a deaf ear
to the things you don't like.
His sister was injured during the incident.
Who cares what the others say?!
Leave!
No, I don't want to hear this!
See? You're running away again.
There's no way you can live by linking
just the enjoyable moments like a rosary.
Especially not me.
I've found something I enjoy!
Finding something you enjoy
and doing nothing but that...
What's wrong with that?!
In theory, the entry plug's energy reserves
should be reaching their expiration point.
The plug suit's life support system
will be getting close to redline.
Advance the schedule by twelve minutes.
Let's do it while there's a chance
that Shinji's still alive.
Father, am I unwanted?
Father!
You're the one who ran away.
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
Expedition
Team
Returns
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
Second Impact’s...
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
“Crystallized DNA” Theory
Pride of Our Nation’s DNA Field
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
Dark Side of the U.N.
Thareams He roy e gy O P
of killing his own wife!
That's right! He may be guilty
U.N. Undisclosed...
Thatrighti Tia R Bequilty
of killing his own wife!
That's right! He may be guilty
What is the secret of the “Dead Sea Scrolls” that
the sélihat'sirightlsHe;may*be:zguiltyificial
Evolutief killing:his-ewn-wifelrching?
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
The Light and Shadow of the
Tokyo University Academic Clique
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
Enterprise and Adhesion
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
Year 2004
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
DNA Manipulation
That's right! He may be guilty
of killing his own wife!
He killed his own wife!
At the Artificial Evolution Laboratory
A Critical Accident?
He killed his own wife!
Fear of Biohazard
Engineers Eating Away
at God's [i9&rfied his own wife!
He killed his own wife!
Fear
One Dead
He killed his own wife!
Dead
...to conduct research for...
...researching in the same lab...
...Ms. Yui lkari (27)...
...fell victim to it.
...mistake in control.
He killed his own wife!
...Mistake!
Questions of Human Experimentation
He killed his own wife!
Man-Made
Calamity
He killed his own wife!
Bioinformation...
He K PHEOR Aite!
NoMRieratel.
No! Mother was...
Established Risk
Former Research Colleagues Criticized
No! Mother was...
Bribery
Director Gendo lkari
No! Mother was...
Genome Biology
Supreme Court Rules Not Guilty
No! Mother was...
The Deficiency of Bioethics
God’s Art
No! Mother was...
Smiling...
You did a very praiseworthy thing today.
Shinji, you must not run away.
Do your best.
I hate this place.
I don't want to be alone...
...anymore.
The heating and the oxygen circulation
are already out.
I'm cold.
It's useless, the suit is giving out too.
So this is the end.
I'm tired...
Of it all.
Mother?
Are you ready?
Well, that's good for you.
Both Evas are in position.
AT field generation ready.
Roger.
Sixty seconds to mine drop.
What's happening?!
Status report!
Unknown!
All meters and gauges are going off the scale.
But we haven't done anything yet.
No way, Shinji?!
It's impossible!
Unit 01's power level is zero!
I'm piloting something like that?
What kind... what kind of monster
have we copied from?
I know that the Evas aren't just
copies of the First Angel.
But what is Nerv going to do with them
once all the Angels have been destroyed?
Shinji?! Shinji?! Shinji?!
Shinji?! Are you all right, Shinji?!
I just wanted to see you one more time.
Weren't you going to scold him?
I have never thought these Evas
were as frightening as I did today.
Are the Evas really on our side?
They may hate us.
I think that Major Katsuragi
may have noticed something.
I see. Let her be for now.
If Rei or Shinji were to find out the Eva's secrets,
they'd never forgive us, would they?
Stay in bed for today.
We'll take care of the rest.
But I'm fine now.
Well, that's good for you.
The smell of blood won't come off.
To Be Continued
Preview
Eva Unit 04, which was being built in America,
vanished along with Nerv's 2nd Branch.
This incident forces them
to select a new Eva pilot.
Next episode: "The Fourth Qualified Individual"
Next Time
The Fourth Qualified Individual
Next episode: "The Fourth Qualified Individual"
Next Time
The Fourth Qualified Individual