THE APPRENTICE WHO
SUCKS AT STORYTELLING
"Just out shopping for dinner," you say?
You expect me to believe that load of crap?!
My apologies, but I am in a hurry.
This… is Don Pacino.
You're gonna tell me everything
you know about this man.
Until you do, I'll have to hang on to this.
You will return it if I talk?
Of course. You have my word.
Very well. I will talk.
Suddenly you're very reasonable.
This must mean a lot to you.
Yes, it is very important.
You know, when you're
soaking in a hot bath,
everyone says "ahh."
I wonder why everyone says that.
That is true.
I mean, wouldn't "eee" or "uuu"
or "ohhh" work too?
"Eee"?
Yeah. Try it.
Say "eee" for me.
Eeee…
How's that?
Don't ask me.
How was it for you?
I am sorry…
I feel no difference.
Eeeeee…
How was it?
Hmm… I can't really get into it.
It's gotta be that "ah" sound.
Then how about "sahh"?
"Sahh"?
Doesn't feel right either…
Oh! "Fahhh."
Not bad, huh?
Fahhh…
Yeah, not bad at all!
Master.
Technically speaking,
that sound isn't "fah."
Truth be told, I am equipped with
a perfect pitch function.
Really?
Yes. That "fah" sounded a little off.
If you want "fah," then I think "fahhh" is better.
Yeah? Fahhh… Like that?
That "fah" was sharp, Master.
Fahh?
That would be "me."
Okay, "meeee."
That's "me," Master.
That's the note for "me"!
"Meeee…"
You know, you can take off without me.
Wouldn't want you to get
a chill after your bath.
But hey, don't lose that.
These are crazy times.
Losing your keys will only lead to trouble.
That is how important the key is.
Your stories are terrible.
No one gives a crap about "fah"!
Your "fah" is wrong.
It should be "fahhh."
In any case, the key is important and I'd like it back.
I'm sure you must have one
or two things important to you.
My family is important to me.
I'd do anything for them.
As I would do anything for Master Saitama.
Saitama?
Never heard of him.
Master Saitama has given me a job to do.
Is that right? A job, huh?
Let's hear more about this "job."
So you decided to wait after all?
It's so cold, too…
Are you okay, Master?
It's freezing.
The chill's getting to me.
Did you just look at my head?
No, I would never.
Hey!
A hot pot? Sounds good!
Really warms you up.
It appears the ingredients are on sale.
Dinner target acquired.
What kind should we have?
There's yosenabe, ishikarinabe, tori no mizutaki…
Crap!
What's wrong?
N-Not this one, not this…
Here it is!
Premium chicken sale…
for a limited time?!
I totally forgot!
Master, this store's sale is still going.
What?
Hmm… We can just make it.
Oh! But at this store, the cabbage is—
Master! If we split up, we can do it.
So when you said "a job,"
you actually meant "running errands"?
Like I said before,
I am in the middle of shopping.
Now I have told you about the errand
I am on for my master.
I've had enough of your—
And that is where I met this man.
Master asked me to go to…
two supermarkets.
There it is.
An alert from a shopping district
five kilometers away.
It is four kilometers to the store.
The disturbance is in the wrong direction,
but they are only six klicks apart.
If I end the trouble quickly,
I can make it!
I see.
And that's when you bumped into us.
Not quite.
What?
I'm done for…
I am only two seconds late.
Please make an exception.
I understand, but—
You still have the merchandise!
But a limited time sale is just that, limited time…
The attitude of that clerk!
Have you any idea how
I felt at that moment?
What the hell are you talking about?
What I want to hear is how you
and this idiot know each other!
Cut to the chase and tell me
what you have to do with him,
the number two guy in the Typhoon Family!
Be patient.
There is an order to things.
I missed the limited time sale
at the first market.
So I went on to the second market.
And that is where I ran into you.
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Hey, why is this place closed?
There is supposed to be a sale here today.
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
They skipped out.
I'm sure Don Pacino's behind it.
He recently drifted into this area
and has been poking his nose
into our business.
He must've demanded a huge sum of protection money and forced them to leave.
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Protection money?
What is that?
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Hey, are you okay?
This here is…
Don Pacino.
That's a nasty look you got in your eyes.
Hey!
Hold on!
I can't just give this back to you.
Are you with him?
Come on, I wanna have a word with you.
So… you're telling me that
there's no connection
between you and him?
That is right.
I have zero connection to this man.
In other words, we are strangers.
You mean you've been
running your mouth all this time
just to tell me that?!
Well, you asked.
And now that I have told you everything,
give me back the key as you promised.
You wise-ass!
Don't you know who you're dealing with?
We're the Pacino Family,
with a C-class bounty on our heads!
Is that how it is?
I thought something was off.
Huh?
I assumed you were going to do the right thing
and report the lost key to the police first,
then return it to me, the rightful owner.
But you are all wanted men.
You would never do anything so honest.
In other words,
you had no intention of
returning it in the first place.
You dimwit, how stupid can someone be?
I cannot go after law-abiding citizens,
but with you…
I have no reason to hold back.
Take him down, boys!
Do not move.
And that is how I was able to get the key back.
But I missed the sale.
Well…
I had a spare key, so I was okay.
It sure sounds like you had a lot to deal with.
Master, I am still too incompetent
to even run your errands!
No big deal.
We'll just have a tofu hot pot tonight.
This will not make up for it…
Huh?
…but I went by another store on the way home.
But this is the super-expensive meat!
Good thing we had eggs.
Let's dig in. Sukiyaki.
Okay!
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore wa tandoku de seigi
katsudo o shiteiru saibogu,
I'm a lone cyborg
working to uphold justice
genosu toyuu mono da!
My name is Genos
kosoku sekkin hanno...
Object approaching at high speed...
kuru!
It's here!
kazoku no ada o utsu tame ni
For the sake of avenging my family
hakase ni moratta kono karada
I received this body from the doctor
ima koso warumono haijo seyo
Now is the time to eliminate evildoers
kono atsuki honoo de
With these red-hot flames
tsuyosa no hiketsu ga shiri takute
I must learn the secret to his strength,
nikki ni shirusu no sa
so I write in my journal
a kaki kaki kaki
Ah, scribble, scribble, scribble!
toire no soji mo nikka desu
Toilet scrubbing is also
in my daily routine
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
ore ni wa taosaneba naranai
shukuteki ga iru n desu!
I have an arch-enemy that
I must defeat at all costs!
saitama-sensei, ore o
deshi ni shite kudasai!
Master Saitama, please
make me your apprentice!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March