THE DISCIPLE WHO
SUCKS AT STORYTELLING
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
Notice:
Shop is Closing Down.
Thank You For Your
Loyalty
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore wa tandoku de seigi
katsudo o shiteiru saibogu,
I'm a lone cyborg
working to uphold justice
genosu toyuu mono da!
My name is Genos
kosoku sekkin hanno...
Object approaching at high speed...
kuru!
It's here!
kazoku no ada o utsu tame ni
For the sake of avenging my family
hakase ni moratta kono karada
I received this body from the doctor
ima koso warumono haijo seyo
Now is the time to eliminate evildoers
kono atsuki honoo de
With these red-hot flames
tsuyosa no hiketsu ga shiri takute
I must learn the secret to his strength,
nikki ni shirusu no sa
so I write in my journal
a kaki kaki kaki
Ah, scribble, scribble, scribble!
toire no soji mo nikka desu
Toilet scrubbing is also
in my daily routine
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
ore ni wa taosaneba naranai
shukuteki ga iru n desu!
I have an arch-enemy that
I must defeat at all costs!
saitama-sensei, ore o
deshi ni shite kudasai!
Master Saitama, please
make me your disciple!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March