Irisviel.
Are you all right?
They waited for Kiritsugu to leave
before launching a frontal assault.
That sudden lightning and that
unscrupulous appearance of his.
The enemy.
His likely Rider.
Whoa!
Huh?
Hello, Saber.
Rider?
I came because I wanted to see your castle.
It's kind of gloomy here, don't you think, hmm?
And what's with the tasteless armor?
Are you going out to fight someone right now?
Why aren't you wearing your
fashionable clothes like I am tonight?
Rider.
What are you doing here?
You mean you can't tell?
I've come to drink, what else does
it look like I've come here to do?
So stop standing there like
statue and show me around this place.
Surely you have a garden here suitable for a banquet.
Honestly, this castle is far too dusty to be in.
The Grail is said to be fated for the
hands of the one most worthy to possess it.
And the epic battle taking place here in Fuyuki
will determine exactly who that person is.
And if it's simply a means to decide that
fact, there's hardly a need for bloodshed.
After all, if the heroic
spirits can agree on our rankings,
then the matter can simply settle itself.
Oh.
Then I assume you wish to compare
your rank against my own, Rider.
Indeed I do.
As one who also claims the title of
king, you can not refuse this opportunity.
You might consider this a Grail
dialog, rather than a Grail War.
And the matter of who among us who
is most suited to claim the Holy Grail
will become clear to us as we drink our fill and converse.
I believe that is quite enough nonsense.
You mongrels.
Archer, what are you doing here?
Ah, yes, well,
I saw him in town so I thought I might
as well invite him to our little gathering.
You're a little late don't you think, goldie,
though it stands to reason since
you traveled by foot unlike myself.
You actually chose to hold a banquet
of kings in a depressing place like this?
How will you recompense me for
the rudeness of calling me here?
Oh, why don't you just relax yourself.
Here, start with a little drink.
What is this disgusting swill?
You really thought we could discern a
hierarchy of heroic spirits with this?
You don't like it?
This cask was among the very best I could
find at the city marketplace this afternoon.
You are pitifully ignorant of true drink.
Of course you believe that.
Stupid mongrel.
Ah!
Now behold and acknowledge your folly.
This is the beverage of a true king.
A fine treasure, indeed.
Aaahhh.
Ah, magnificent.
My treasury houses only the very
finest of drinks and the finest of swords.
This alone should indicate which
among us is the greatest of kings.
Archer, your finest drink is indeed
worthy of the finest vessel in all of history.
But the Holy Grail is not a drinking cup.
First, we must hear what wish
you would have the Grail grant
should you win it.
The wish is what gives the Grail its purpose.
You are not ruler here, mongrel.
Already you wantonly disregard the time honored rules
which dictate we fight for the Grail.
Hmm?
Besides all that, the Grail already belongs to me.
All of this world's treasures without
exception trace their origin to my treasure house.
They do, do they?
Then I assume that means you once held the Holy Grail,
you can identify it by sight.
No.
Huh?
Do not consider me as you would a lesser being.
The amount of wealth in my treasury
long ago surpassed my own knowledge.
But that the Holy Grail is a treasure
also means that it belongs to me.
And any who would take it for themselves
is not but a filthy scoundrel and a common thief.
Your words are no different than
Caster's senseless and insane rants.
It appears he isn't the only
Servant to have gone completely mad.
Come, let's not go that far.
However, I believe I now have a clue
as to what goldie's actual identity is.
So then, Archer, you suggested if we desire
the Grail we must first get your permission?
Indeed, however there is no reason whatsoever
for me to reward lowly mongrels of your ilk.
Wait a minute, you're going to be stingy?
Fool, my magnanimity is limited to
my vassals and to my loyal subjects.
Which means, Rider, if you were to swear fealty to me,
I could lend you a Grail or two,
whenever you felt the need for one.
Sorry, that is totally out of the question.
But tell me, Archer, surely you have no
special interest in the Holy Grail itself, do you?
Of course not, but I must render my judgment upon those
who would dare to steal treasure from me.
It's simply a matter of principle.
Hmm, I'm curious, Archer.
On what morals and reasoning are
these principles of yours based?
It is the law, my law which I
set down as the rightful king.
Perfect.
Living by one's own law is the epitome of kingship.
Nevertheless, I desire the Holy
Grail so badly I could almost taste it.
And it has always been my style to just take what I want.
After all, the Great Iskandar
is the King of Conquerors, is he not?
Right and wrong are irrelevant.
You break the law and I will punish you.
There is no place for discussion.
Hmm.
Which means that all we have left to us
is to meet on the field of combat.
So then, Archer, would you still like
us to help you finish this off tonight?
There'll be plenty of time to kill each other after.
Indeed, or do you dare sit there and cast aspersions
on the superior drink I did you the honor of providing?
No, of course not, I wouldn't dream
of letting this drink go to waste.
King of Conquerors.
Hmm?
A moment ago you agreed that the Holy Grail's
rightful ownership lies with another and not yourself.
And yet you would just take it by force?
What makes the Grail so important to you?
Reincarnation.
Huh?
What?
Wait a minute, wasn't your goal
supposed to be world conquest?
Ah!
Idiot, as if I would leave
the conquering to some mere cup.
Conquering the world is my dream to make true.
The wish I would ask of the Holy Grail
is the first step towards that goal.
Mongrel, you would dare challenge me for my treasure
over something so trivial?
Even in magic lends us form in this world,
ultimately we remain Servants.
I wish to live as flesh and blood
within this world in which I find myself.
And with nothing but my body
I shall defy both heaven and Earth,
succeeding in that endeavor
is the true meaning of conquest.
Thus it begins.
Then proceeds onward and finally is finished.
Such is the path of my conquest.
Hmm, then the matter is settled.
I shall take great pleasure in killing you myself.
You don't have to remind me of the obvious.
I have every intention of plundering your abundant
storehouse until it's been laid bare, so get ready.
That is hardly fitting of how a true king should behave.
Oh, well then, let us hear
what you would ask of the Grail,
if you were to win it.
I wish for my homeland's salvation.
With the omnipotent wish granting device,
I shall avert Britain's fate of destruction.
They're having a drinking party of all things?
Shall I continue to leave Archer to his own devices?
Hmm, it can't be helped.
After all, when one is King of Kings, it simply wouldn't
do to turn one's back on an interesting invitation.
Incidentally, Kirei, how do you judge
the relative strengths of Rider and Archer?
Rider may very well possess a trump
card that surpasses the gordius wheel.
I believe we should put this to the test.
Hmm, with Rider and his Master
drinking and their guard's down,
a better chance to attack them
will never again present itself.
The odds of victory don't matter to our overall plan.
Even if Assassin is defeated,
as long as he can gauge their relative strengths,
our objective will be accomplished.
We do have the option
of launching an attack right now, Kirei.
I have no objections.
I believe it will take roughly ten
minutes to summon all the Assassins.
Fine, give the order.
It is a large gamble, but even if it fails,
we stand to lose nothing.
Use a command seal to give Assassin the following order.
Be victorious no matter the cost, got it?
Hey, King of Knights, did you
just say that you would change fate?
Does that mean that you wish to change events long past?
Indeed, even if it is a wish that
a miracle alone can not fulfill.
If the Holy Grail is truly omnipotent,
then surely...
Um, Saber, just so I am clear on this,
it was back during your time that his
country you call Britain was conquered and fell?
When it was under your rule?
Correct, that is why I can not allow it.
And that is why I regret it.
Why I want to alter that outcome,
for it was I and none other who was to blame.
Archer, what's so amusing?
You call yourself a king and are praised by all as such,
and yet you feel regret.
How can I not laugh at such nonsense?
Saber, surely you do not really mean
that you would erase the marks that
you yourself have left on history?
I do, and what of it?
Why do you laugh?
My beloved country to which I
devoted my whole life was destroyed.
Why is my sadness about that strange?
Did you hear that drivel, Rider?
Did you hear what this little girl
who calls herself King of Knights said?
Her beloved country to which she devoted her whole life.
Why is that humorous to you?
For their country's prosperity,
a true king should be willing to make any sacrifice.
You are wrong.
The king does not devote himself.
It is the nation and the people
who must devote themselves to the king.
You have reversed the concept.
I what?
Those are the words of a brutal tyrant.
Just so.
We are heroes precisely because we are tyrants.
However, Saber, if a king regrets his rule or
regrets the manner in which his rule came to an end,
that king is nothing but a fool,
worse than the tyrant you disdain.
Iskandar, your reign ended with all your heirs slain
and your great empire broken up by civil war.
Do you mean to say you have no regrets about that end?
None at all.
Not if it came to pass by my own decisions and by
the considerable sacrifices of my many retainers.
Its destruction was inevitable.
I shall mourn it and shed tears over it,
but I shall never regret it.
But you...
Let alone undo it all!
Such an act would be an insufferable insult to
all those who fought and bled and died alongside me.
It is only a warrior who can find glory in destruction,
worthless is a king who fails to protect the weak.
A just rule guided by just laws,
those are the true duties of a king.
So you, the king of your realm,
are a slave to what is right?
I am.
Kings are martyrs to their ideals.
That is not the way a person should live.
If I rule a nation as king,
I can not expect to live as a person.
King of Conquerors, you seek the
Grail merely for your own benefit.
And as such, you could never understand that.
You, who became a ruler only
to satisfy your endless greed.
A king without greed is even worse than a figurehead!
Saber, you said you would martyr yourself for your ideals.
In life you must have been something
akin to the purest of all the saints.
A proud and noble figure at the very least.
But who can truly admire the rough and
thorny path that a martyr must follow in life?
Who actually dreams of such an ending?
A king must be greedier than any other.
He must laugh more loudly and rage for much longer
and embody the very extreme of all things good and evil.
That is why his retainers envy his very existence.
And adore him as well.
And why the flames of aspiration
to be just as the king is
can burn within his people.
Proud king of chivalry,
the righteousness and ideals you embraced in life
may have indeed saved your nation
and her people once.
However, surely you must know what
became of those who were saved by you.
But then were left to fend for themselves.
What are you saying?
You may indeed have saved them,
but you never led them.
You never showed them all what a king should really be.
You abandoned your men when they lost their way.
Then alone and untroubled by that fact,
you went on to follow your own
pretty little ideals to the end.
Thus, you are no true king.
You spent your life enraptured by a false
idol of a humble king who always serves others.
You're just a little girl.
I...
What are you laughing at, Archer?
Oh, nothing.
I simply felt that your anguished
face was a rather lovely sight.
It was the face of the virgins who
showered me with flower pedals in my bed.
A woman after my own heart.
Bastard!
Huh?
Hmm.
Ah.
Ahhh.
Assassin.
So is this all your doing, goldie?
Tokiomi, what a shameful cur.
This isn't fair. Why are there
so many Assassins surrounding us?
We are one divided into many.
An army and also one.
A Servant with many shadows.
And one.
A Servant with separate bodies for
each of his multiple personalities?
Rider, um, I...
Oh, calm yourself.
Nothing to worry about, boy.
Even those rude enough to interrupt our banquet
may yet show us which is the greatest king.
So I suppose you'll invite them all to our
little banquet as well, King of Conquerors?
But of course, a king's words are
meant for all to hear and absorb.
If they have come here to listen, it
matters not if they are friend or foe.
Now then, don't hold back.
Any who would speak with us, come forth and take a cup.
This drink is as your blood.
Very well.
As I said, this drink is as your blood.
If you insist on spilling it here tonight,
then so be it.
Saber, Archer, here is our banquet's final question.
It is, does a king always stand alone?
The king must indeed be alone, always.
No, no, you obviously don't understand.
I suppose I'll just have to show you both right now
exactly what a real king is all about
when faced with an adversary like this one.
Huh?
A reality marble?
That's impossible.
A mental image materialized into the real world.
My glorious armies once rode across these sands.
A place that all the heroes who stood with
me through joy and sorrow will never forget.
I can make this world as real as real can ever be.
Because it still exists deep within our hearts.
Behold my endless armies.
Their bodies utterly destroyed and their souls
offered to the current world as heroic spirits of old.
And still, these legendary
heroes pledge their loyalty to me.
My bond with them is my greatest treasure.
My path to kingship.
The ultimate noble phantasm that I possess!
I order in Haitari.
Wait a minute, so each of these is a Servant?
It has been a long time, partner.
Hear me!
A king must live a grand life and
embody his people's image of admiration.
Aye, aye, aye.
He who is worthy of all heroes envy and
he who leads their way, that is a king!
Therefore, the king is not alone,
for his will equals that of all who would
follow him to his ultimate glory combined!
Aye, aye, aye!
Now then, shall we begin our battle, Assassin?
As you can see, what we have created is a vast plane
and with our superior numbers, we hold the advantage.
Annihilate them!
Aaarggh!
That ending wasn't as much fun as I'd hoped for.
We have said all there is to say.
I suppose that will do for today.
Wait, Rider, I have not finished.
You may keep silent.
Tonight was for a conversation amongst kings.
But I no longer recognize you as a king, Saber.
Little girl, you must wake from
your sad dream and see the truth.
If you don't, you'll someday lose even that
modicum of pride you retain as a heroic spirit.
The dream of a king you spoke of earlier is a
curse and a burden which blinds and cripples you.
A what?
Pay that base mongrel no heed, Saber.
You are correct, follow the path you believe in.
Your agonizing pain and terrible sorrow
as you bear a burden of kingship
that is too heavy a weight for any
is quite a splendid and marvelous thing to look upon.
Keep at it, oh great King of Knights.
It is possible you may prove worthy
of still more of my magnificent love.
Saber.
I remember now.
There was once a knight who left Camelot
claiming the king didn't understand how others felt.
Well, perhaps that... that sentiment was shared by
all of the knights who sat with me at the round table.
This will begin the second stage.
I'm not in any way a normal human being.
But Irisviel, that simply can not be all there is to it.
Do it all exactly as you desire.
Your path is now clear, Kirei.
But that is the soul of a Godless sinner!