Lulu!
Don't worry. I'll exclude you now, too.
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become true
friends with you. To cross the wall...
Ginko, Kure-chin, thank you.
I love both of you.
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
We must be invisible!
Let us begin the Exclusion Ceremony.
"Friends" are more important
than anything else, agreed?
The friends gathered here right now: that's us.
People who contradict our
feelings are a disgrace, agreed?
People who stick out from
our crowd are just no good, agreed?
People who refuse to fit in
with us are a nuisance, agreed?
People like that who can't
follow social cues are evil.
Humans and bears are severed.
Yet certain people are
trying to cross that wall.
We must decide here and now
who is the evil to exclude.
Let's search evil!
"The Invisible Storm - (Exclusion)"
"3."
"4. Exclude"
"2."
"3. Exclude"
"1."
"2. Exclude"
"1. Exclude Evil"
Select! We have our evil.
I assume everyone's ready.
We will now exclude the evil!
Nega-kuma energy replenishing!
Buzz buzz! Nasty nasty!
Nasty... nasty... nasty...
Nasty nasty nasty nasty!
If we shoot her with that,
she'll be way blown to bits.
The bear will be extinct in no time.
Wait! I'm the evil, aren't I?
All you need to do is exclude me!
That's exactly what we plan to do, of course.
"Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
The lily opens!
This is your punishment.
You're going to kill your friend.
You don't follow this
world's rules, so you're evil.
We must be invisible.
If you're invisible, who will find you?
Friend?
Don't be ridiculous, growl.
That girl isn't my friend.
I came here to eat Kureha Tsubaki. That's all.
Kureha is my prey.
I've never once considered her a friend!
Ginko...
Kureha Tsubaki is not my friend!
Liar!
That's a lie.
Why did you cross the wall, then?!
To eat you, growl.
If that's true, why did you stay by my side?
You two tried to protect me
from the Invisible Storm.
Because you wouldn't taste good
if you went invisible, growl.
You can stop now. Ginko, you were
my friend from the beginning.
You crossed the wall, and you
found me in the Invisible Storm!
You gave me love!
You're wrong!
I'm your enemy. I came to eat you!
I'm... a bear!
The bear's shown her true form!
Time to exclude her!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
I just remembered everything.
"Flashback"
--Please stop!
--Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude all traitors!
Growl...
Lick... lick...
Why?
Does she not get approved 'cause she's a bear?
Is being a bear the problem?
Growl...
If... If she were a human girl...
Could we be together forever?
Could I protect Ginko?
Please tell me, Lady Kumaria!
That's right. It was me
who hoped for a Promise Kiss.
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Kureha Tsubaki, this is a challenge
from the Wall of Severance.
Is your love the real thing?
Yes, absolutely.
If they grant a bear yuri approval
in court, she can become a girl.
But to do that, you have to let go
of whatever you care about most.
What do you mean?
This is just my theory, but I bet in
Ginko's trial, she let go of your love.
No, Lulu. Ginko wasn't the one
who let go of love to get her wish.
That...
...was me.
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Defendant Kureha Tsubaki,
is there anything you wish to say?
I want to be with Ginko forever!
So please, make Ginko a human girl!
Your Honor, the defendant has
committed the crime of pride.
Therefore she is guilty!
"Pride"? What's that?
You basically want to
transform Ginko Yurishiro, right?
I have to, because bears get excluded.
And Ginko will be happier as a human anyway!
Whoa, you're sure confident! Sparkle!
That's what we're telling you is pride.
I don't care if it's pride!
Please make Ginko a human girl!
Very well. However, there is one condition.
What?
You must relinquish love.
In other words, you'll forget Ginko.
When you wake up,
you will most likely reject her.
Reject?
That day, I wished something
that no one should ever wish.
I was foolish enough to believe
my selfish love was the real thing...
You must wait. One day the time will come.
When the Invisible Storm arrives,
you will find Ginko Yurishiro.
If you can make friends with her again
and exchange Promise Kisses...
...then you can be together forever! Sparkle!
Really?!
Now, defendant Kureha Tsubaki, I ask you:
Will you make Ginko Yurishiro human?
Or will you give up on love?
I won't give up on love!
Make Ginko a human girl!
Lulu, I'm afraid I wished
for Ginko to be human,
in exchange for what was most precious.
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Defendant Kureha Tsubaki,
do you admit your crime?
I do.
I once committed the crime of pride,
and wished for you to make Ginko a human.
And did you find what you
hoped for in the Invisible Storm?
Yes. There was a girl...
"Flashback"
...who taught me.
I...
I found what I hoped for: true love!
Sumika...
Thank you.
I'm not scared anymore.
As long as I don't forget love,
I'll never be alone.
If I don't give up on love,
even if I lose something,
I'll never be invisible. So...
I'll leap into the storm!
Wh-What does that mean?!
Lulu, thank you. I'll deliver this star,
this true love, to Ginko.
Stay away!
Nasty...?
You're my friend.
No! You're no friend of mine, growl!
I'm a people-eating bear, Ginko the
Lone Wolfsbane, and I came to eat you!
Stop... Stop it!
Hurry up and shoot me!
Or else I'll eat all of you!
I'm a criminal-bear, growl!
Ginko...
You can't, Kureha!
I finally found you.
I have a wish, Lady Kumaria!
It's Lady Kumaria...!
She's regaining her form!
Well then, let us be off.
This is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo!
This is so cool!
Sparkle!
Kureha Tsubaki, is your love the real thing?
It is.
I will...
...smash myself!
Lady Kumaria, please...
Make me into a bear!
Yuri approved!
Wha... What is this?!
Kureha, how could you...?
Ginko, thank you for not
forgetting love, and never giving up.
A Promise Kiss for you.
We'll be together forever now!
Together forever, growl!
Yuri approved!
W-Way unbelievable...
A person, becoming a bear?
It's so revolting!
Nasty...
We... can't shoot anymore.
Nas... ty...
Wh-What are you waiting for?
That thing's not human anymore!
It's a bear! It's evil!
We have to exclude evil!
Don't waver!
Don't think!
Shoot!
We worked together,
and we got the job done.
That's right: we successfully excluded
the terrible evil that overran this school!
We've been right all along--we must be invisible.
Let us begin the Exclusion Ceremony.
"Friends" are more important
than anything else, agreed?
The friends here right now: that's us.
Shoot!
"Flashback"
People who refuse to fit in
with us are a nuisance, agreed?
People like that who can't
follow social cues are evil.
Now, let us decide on
the next evil to exclude.
Nasty!
Nas... nas... n-nasty...
"Defective"
Nasty!
Nasty? Nasty...?
I found you.
"YURI KUMA ARASHI"
"And so, having
completed their Promise Kiss,
the two began a journey beyond
severance, guided by the star of love."
Hey, Sis, what happened to them next?
That's a good question.
What do you think, Milne?
Hmmm...
I dunno!
But I did figure something out.
What's that?
Smooch!
I could've just given
you the Promise Kiss myself!
Milne...
Right?
We'll be together forever.
Yep! I love you, Sis!
Thank you!
No one knows where the girls have gone.
But that's as it should be.
You see, it is with your own love
that the world awakens and changes.