Please have a match against me.
That's...
...a national representative's uniform.
Let's have a match.
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Invoke the big halation
ano hi no chikai wo hatasu tame
あの日の誓いを果たすため
To fulfill that promise you swore on that day
hirake! new formation
開け! new formation
Open out, the new formation!
shisen no aizu yobiau
視線の合図呼び合う
Call out to each other with eye contact
kibou o nosete hanate arch
希望を乗せては放て arch
Bear and release the arch of hope
itsumo no toori ni ne
いつもの通りにね
Just like always
shinjiteru (makasete)
信じてる (まかせて)
I'll believe in you (Leave it to us)
mune ni te wo atete
胸に手を当てて
Bring your hand to your chest
hikiyoseta heijoushin
引き寄せた平常心
and tug at your usual attitude
kanaete dekita koto
叶えて来たこと
The things I fulfilled,
sorezorega oboeteru
それぞれが覚えてる
I can remember them all.
ano hi hisoka ni naita koto mo
あの日密かに泣いたことも
Including that day when you cried in secret.
onaji yumemiteru no wa
同じ夢見てるのは
Surely, we can't be the only ones
watashi tachi dakeja nain dayo ne
私たちだけじゃないんだよね
having the same dream.
me no mae ni arawareta
目の前に現れた
Appearing in front of our eyes,
yuru ganai hitomi hibana chirashite
揺るがない瞳火花散らして
is an unfaltering spark that's dispersing.
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Drop the big halation!
hiraku space e hashiriko me
開くスペースへ走り込め
Run into the open space!
wazukana sensation
僅かな sensation
The slight sensation
senobi shite ita kinou e
背伸びしていた昨日へ
when you were overstretched yesterday
wakare wo tsugetara
別れを告げたら
Announce your goodbyes,
egao wo tsunagete
笑顔を繋げて
Connect your smiles,
yume mita basho e hanate arch
夢見た場所へ放て arch
Release the arch to where you see your dreams
Flying Match!
Bien.
A feint!
Tomoka might have seen through it,
but that girl is doing pretty good too.
Yes, I'm enjoying this too.
Are you okay?
Merci.
You can go on offence this time.
Now!
Très bien!
I committed a foul.
The basket counts, and you can have a free throw too.
But there wasn't much contact...
Do it.
So beautiful....
I lost to a girl.
My first was taken.
I'm sorry!
I just thought that it would be disrespectful if I wasn't serious!
Well, that was great!
I got to see something good.
Dad?!
Long time no see, son.
Hey, when did you get back?
I just arrived in Narita a while ago.
Where's Nayu-nayu?
Mum is inside.
More importantly....
Mimi Balguerie.
Nice to meet you.
She's my important kid, so take care of her.
I see....
So Mimi-chan is a student of yours, Dad?
Yeah.
Mimi is the daughter of a French professor from the excavation project in Hawaii.
During my stay, she asked me to teach her basketball.
You as a coach, huh....
I didn't earn my reputation in the past for nothing.
Ginga-kun was awesome back then.
He was Nashiba High School's basketball club's legendary ace!
You're flattering me, Nayu-nayu!
Am I?
Sure are, Nayu-nayu!
Idioticouple.
Is that so, Ginga-kun?
Yes, geez!
Are you Tomorouchi?
I'm Tomoka.
Tomoka, you have a slight bulge.
Is that true?
Oui.
Whereas, I'm still a flat-chested girl.
But Mimi-chan, you're still in fifth grade, so you'll get bigger from here on!
I'm waiting eagerly for it.
Tomoka.
W-What?
I hope you can play a basketball match against me again!
Me too, let's have a fair match.
Private
Keishin
Academy
That sounds cool, Mokkan!
Something so interesting happened to you at the end of summer vacation?
Yeah!
Mimi-chan was really good at basketball, so it was great fun!
She said she would still be in Japan for a while.
Then, if we ask Hasegawa-san, then we could meet her too!
Oh~!
Hina wants to meet Onii-chan's dad too!
What kind of person is he?
He's a really great dad!
He also knows a lot about basketball.
Nee-sama.
Kage-chan!
Oh~.
Kage, what's wrong?
Mimi-chan!
That girl?
She transferred to my class.
She wanted drop by and say hi after we talked about you all.
Oui.
I heard that everyone here plays basketball.
I will be in your care from now on.
No, the same goes for us.
Then, let's go.
Okay.
See you later.
She looks like a doll!
Yeah.
We should start an interest group soon.
We didn't meet up as much during summer vacation either.
But I was thinking it's about time to settle down and study for exams.
That's fast!
You already started?
Well, that's how it is, so I won't be make it often.
How about increasing the number of members?
Well, that would be great....
Do you have anyone in mind?
Well, I'll find something.
All right!
We'll have to do our best again today!
Yes!
Nii-tan, you're cool!
Look here!
Look at us!
Hey Take, they're here again.
Your younger sisters are as lively as always.
I thought I already told them not to
come to our club activities anymore.
Can I make a request?
Hmm?
Isn't that Hakamada's younger sister?
Who is the girl next to her?
What is it?
Is there something you want?
Erm, that's....
Was it crashing the gym?
Huh?
I will take over the basketball club.
Captain, have a match with me.
Hey, what on earth are you-
Erm, Mimi-san wants to form her own team.
Team?
She had a match with Tomoka-senpai a few days ago.
It seems she wants a rematch.
So she thought....
She thought what?
Mimi-san wants to join the boys' basketball club, and challenge the girls' basketball club.
Huh?
What on earth are you saying?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I can't have a match in the same team as Tomoka-senpai.
I want to be on another team.
Even if you say so....
Incoming Mail
Fujii Masami
Subject: Passionate love
leaked!!
Fujii Masami
Subject: Passionate love
leaked!!
Fujii Masami
Subject: Passionate love
leaked!!
Fujii Masami
Subject: Passionate love
leaked!!
What is that?
Masami, this is....
Passionate love leaked!
It's a precious photo, isn't it?
I'm going to spread this everywhere around Suzuran shopping district.
This would lead to a decline in reputation of you and your family.
I don't think anything will come out of doing that.
You won't be so relaxed afterwards!
See you.
Gosh.
Hello?
This is Saki.
I have something to tell you, Hasegawa-san.
What's the matter?
Erm, actually, my childhood friend took a photo of us at the summer festival.
A photo?
Yes, it was from when Hasegawa-san was teaching me how to shoot.
I'll send it over.
Shooting?
Why?
Passionate love leaked?
Hello, Saki?
This photo...
Well, I don't think anyone will misunderstand,
but it would be bad if it caused trouble for you.
I was thinking about getting Masami to delete the photo.
This is bad.
If this causes a bad rumour to spread....
It's the rumoured lolicon!
So perverted!
Apparently, he said elementary school kids are the best!
The best!
Saki, I'll come too!
I'll be there in a drifty, so wait for me!
[Name] Mimi Balguerie
[Birthdate] March 3rd
[Blood Type] AB
[Class] Grade 5 Class D
[Height]
[Bust] None at all, wants to grow bigger soon
[Rival] Minato Tomoka
Sorry for having you come all the way here.
No, it's nothing.
But how did it end up like this?
Masami is a year younger than me, and my childhood friend.
Our families are very friendly, but for some
reason she treats me like a thorn in her side.
In a survey of the shopping district, my family, Nagatsuka's store, became first in the ranking.
Masami's family's store, Sushi Fuji, is a sushi restaurant.
It placed in second.
So that's how it is.
But then, Sushi Fuji is just slightly high class, so it's that much harder to get votes.
In any case, let's talk to Masami-san.
Okay.
Masami!
I knew you'd be here.
Whenever you bought a toy or something that you liked, you would definitely be here.
Shut up!
The two of you really are dating, aren't you?
That's not true.
We came here to resolve that misunderstanding.
What's there to talk about.
If I mass-sent this photo, it'd be the end of everything.
I see.
Then, do as you like.
Really?
Then I have to notify Suzuran Avenue of my discovery quickly!
A discovery, you say?
Do you really think your family's shop will
become better than my family's with that?
What do you mean?
Even if our ratings drop because of that photo, it doesn't mean Sushi Fuji's ratings will go up.
Not only that, but rumours about using underhanded means could spread
and in turn tarnish Sushi Fuji's reputation.
What is with your proud statements?
Deleted
Wait and see.
Even without this, we will place first this year!
Thanks, Saki.
No, actually, I was worried in my heart that it wouldn't go well.
Hey, Saki.
What is it?
Does Masami-san play basketball?
Well, she was wearing basketball sneakers.
No, I don't think she plays.
I see.
Wouldn't it be great if Nii-tan and Mimi formed a team and managed to defeat Maho Dumbo.
That's right, that's right!
In fact, we are better than Maho Dumbo.
I'm fine as long as we can play that match.
Hey, Kagetsu.
Is it true you practice basketball with Hina occasionally?
Ah, yes.
We practice passing, dribbling, and run as well.
Hinata praised you.
That means you're getting better, Kagetsu.
To think that Nee-sama said such a thing....
W-Well, it's just what I heard.
Hey, tell me.
If we had to play a match against Hinata, what would you do?
Oh~!
The sponge is crisp and feels good!
Oh~....
Oh~!
Erm, Nee-sama...
Oh~?
If we had to play a match, what would you think?
We cannot fight!
It's not a fight!
Oh~!
A match to see who can hold her breath the longest!
Hina, enjoys having matches against Kage!
Nee-sama....
You're only practicing long-range shots as usual, aren't you?
I'm just practising on a whim.
I was the one who made that goal, though.
I'm sorry for using it.
No, anyone who wants to improve is welcome.
You've been coming here every day since summer vacation, right?
So, how are you supposed to show Saki what you trained?
How?!
It's kind of well known that you see Saki as your rival.
Don't you want to have a match with her?
A basketball match with Saki.
Please!
Mimi-chan!
TsubaHii?
Stop calling us TsubaHii, Maho Dumbo!
The fifth graders are here to crash the girls basketball gym!
Gym crashing?
First up is me, ace Takenaka Tsubaki!
Another ace, Takenaka Hiiragi!
France, Mimi Balguerie.
Sniper, Fujii Masami!
Nee-sama's younger sister, Hakamada Kagetsu.
One, two!
The five of us are the new Keishin Girls Mini Basketball Club!
Eh?!
Wow.
So, the sixth and fifth graders are playing a match.
Yeah.
The winner gets the right to use the gym.
I see.
But anyway, everyone was excited to have a new opponent,
and are all raring to go.
Definitely, with opponents come progress.
I'd like to see a showdown between Mimi and Tomoka-chan.
Also...
...I have a request.
I'm looking forward to the match on Friday!
That's right!
Let's show them our strength!
Hey, Hina, why did Kage join TsubaHii's team?
Oh~?
Hina doesn't know.
However, if we could have a match against Kage's team,
Hina would be happy!
That's true.
If we play seriously, it would be great if everyone improves as a whole.
Everyone, let's do our best!
Oh~!
All right.
Then for today's match, I don't have any specific instructions.
Strategise as a team and create your own rhythm.
Tomoka, try to match everyone's rhythm.
Yes!
Saki, I'll leave you to be the playmaker.
Set up the offensive pattern however you think it should be.
Yes!
Maho, go out there and keep scoring!
Just do as your instincts tell you to!
Yep!
I'm good at that!
Airi, everyone will help you out.
Just shoot as much as you want.
Yes!
I will do my best!
Hinata-chan, let's give Kagetsu-chan the shock of her life.
Oh~!
I'll do my best so that Onii-chan and Kage will praise me!
Then...
...let's start the match!
Nice, Hina!
Here!
Oh~, Saki!
Oh, you really know which one of us is the ace.
We won't lose to Maho Dumbo!
Oh~!
Why isn't anyone marking Kashii?
Kagetsu, close in on Kashii!
Oh~!
We don't need two people on someone like Maho!
Don't assume Saki only goes for long shots!
Ah, geez.
Everyone's doing what they want, and it's just too messy!
Getting a team together is not an easy skill to master.
As expected, the twins have good chemistry.
6th Grade
5th Grade
Tsuba!
Hiki!
Oh~!
Hina's turn!
What?!
I'll go!
This time, it's Hina's turn to shine!
We'll stop you.
Hina!
Oh~!
All right!
6th Grade
5th Grade
Let's get back a basket first.
Hey, why are you intercepting your own teammate's pass!
I won't get the ball otherwise.
Tomoka, it's a showdown!
But...
...the two of us aren't the only ones on the court!
That's right!
Hina!
Oh~!
Hey-
6th Grade
5th Grade
The difference is just....
What are those guys doing?
If you don't cool them down,
the situation will become irreversible.
Even if that's not the case, the team was just formed recently.
You want me to do that?
No matter what you say, it's impossible.
I don't have any coaching experience.
It's definitely difficult.
You're late, Dad.
Sorry.
D-Dad?
Timeout!
Everyone, gather round!
Ginga...
Subaru-san's father!
Everyone, listen up.
I will be taking over the post of coach for the 5th Grade team for a day.
Nice to meet you!
Eh?!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつずけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show your guts cool say what it's the best! Yay!
karada mo kokoro mo SS dakedo
カラダもココロもSSだけど
Although our bodies and hearts might be small in size,
yume wa LL datte ii jan! ii jan!
夢はLLだっていいじゃん! いいじゃん!
isn't it good enough that our dreams are large!
seishun miman no onayami ippai
青春未満のお悩みいっぱい
We are full of worries about growing up
hitori janai kara norikoerareruyo
ひとりじゃないからのりこえられるよ
We're not alone, so we can get through this!
motto umaku naritaina
もっと うまく なりたいな!
I want to become better!
(motto)
(もっと)
(Much)
(umaku)
(うまく)
(better)
anatano (oh...) odoroku (sugoi) kao ga mitai no
あなたの(おぉ...)おどろく(スゴイ) 顔が見たいの
I want to see (boo~) your surprised (Impressive!) face!
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
chikyuu wa okki na Basket Ball
地球はおっきな Basket Ball
The Earth is just a big basketball.
ashita wo shinjite ikuyo! (hai i-ku-yo)
あしたを信じていくよ! (ハイ い・く・よ)
Believe in tomorrow and move forward! (Yes, let-us-go!)
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
uchuu wa okkina Basket Court
宇宙はおっきなBasket Court
The universe is a big basketball court.
anata ni todoketai na... (se-no!)
あなたに届けたいな... (せーのっ)
I want it to reach you... (One, two!)
pasu! pasu! pasu!
パス! パス! パス!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
uketometekudasai!
受け止めてください!
Please receive it!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつづけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show you guts cool say what is the best! Yay!
Today, we got to meet Hasegawa-san's father!
Oh~!
Onii-chan's Papa!
Is he a dandy?
What does that mean?
Oh~...
I don't really know!
It's kind of difficult.
Hard~
Next Time:
Ginga Paradigm
Hmm~?