Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Misat
West
Festival
Misat
West
Festival
Yuu-chan, I finished the knot.
Thank you, Haruka!
I'll start sewing.
Ow!
Are you okay, Yuu-chan?!
Why do we have to make costumes for the recital?
Yuu-chan's cute even when she's sulking!
Cultural Festival ☆ Sleepover
Man!
I can't finish this costume!
I know right?
There's just an endless amount of work.
You two need to stop messing around, and get to work!
The culture festival is tomorrow.
At this rate, we're not going to make it.
How about we stay overnight?
So that's what you've been planning.
Sensei!
We're going to stay overnight!
I'll pass on the message.
Are all of you going to stay?
Are you scared of the school at night?
Haruka, are you going to stay too?
I need to finish this...
I'll stay too.
Everyone's staying.
Shizuku-chan, you'll stay too, won't you?
Yeah, I will.
CLATTER
Just how nervous are you?!
Shizuku-chan,  you've never spent the night before a culture festival at school before?
In middle school, we always had to leave by 8 pm.
Our school let us stay overnight, right?
Yeah!
How about your middle school, Haruka-chan?
Our school let us stay too.
I'm the only one who hasn't done it before...
But Yuu-chan would go home, so I went home too...
I-It was because we finished early!
Not because I was scared of the school at night!
I got it, I got it already!
Oh right.
Shizuku-chan is the only one from a different middle school.
But Kotone and Shizuku-chan, you two have gotten
really close ever since the entrance ceremony, right?
You're even living together, aren't you?
Kotone is a relative to begin with.
We've been close since we were little.
You could say we were close,
but it was more like Kotone was always teasing me.
No!
No way, Shizuku-chan!
You're embarrassing me!
Hey, now.
I wonder what living with the one you love feels like.
Haruka, good morning.
Good morning!
Yuu-chan, there's some on your mouth.
Haruka, have a nice day!
Be a good girl!
Haruka, welcome home!
Food, quickly!
Sakura
I like how the school gets in the days before the cultural festival.
I know the feeling!
The decorations always change the atmosphere.
Just looking at them makes me happy!
I can't calm down either!
Well, you're always like that.
But that does happen!
I know, right!
Haruka-chan, we're turning the classroom into a haunted house, so...
We can't sleep here.
Let's sleep in the hallway?
That's being decorated too...
Sweat
This is a problem.
H-How about an empty classroom?
We can do our work there, too.
Huh?!
What happened?
I got the key!
Thanks, Kaede!
Rumble
It's full of desks.
So it's been turned into a storeroom, huh?
Some were probably here to begin with,
and the rest would be from other classrooms.
How do you know?
H-Huh?
N-No, I don't actually...
Should we look for some other empty room?
Wait!
If we pile them up, there'll be more space!
Shizuku-chan's trying her best!
Yup!
Don't just stare, help me!
Okay!
There's a lot of space now!
So we'll all be sleeping on the floor?
Huddled together?
There.
I brought the blankets.
Really?
Thanks!
She really is doing her best!
What?!
Hey, look, Shizuku-chan!
Huh?
Crepes
Food      Court
There are so many signboards!
Crepes
Misato Festival
Food      Court
Quite a number.
Crepes
I want to eat already!
Takoyaki
That's what you meant?
Sakura
Let's take a break.
I'll go check on our class.
I'll come too.
Shizuku-chan,
Let's go take a breather on the rooftop.
Okay.
Let's finish this quickly!
Yuu-chan!
Yeah...
Ouch!
This might take a while...
It's okay now!
Thank you!
Hey, Haruka, what are you going to eat tomorrow?
I'm at least getting some crepes and buttered potatoes!
I know!
If we pick different things, we can compare them!
Sounds great!
When we're done with this, let's go check out the food stands!
Oh wait, you'll probably get scared.
I have to brave it!
She's sleeping?!
We talked for only a little bit!
Aren't you pushing yourself?
You know, with the witch and everything...
It's rare for you bring these things up yourself.
What do you mean?
Well, you were like this before...
The cultural festival is too much work.
Was I really that pretentious?!
That might be true.
Actually, we could stay overnight for
the festival at my middle school as well.
But I didn't have a group of friends,
so I went home even if I hadn't finished my work.
So, why did you stay this time?
Because of you.
I always found it strange that you enjoyed events like this,
so I thought I might understand you better if I tried it.
Why do you enjoy this so much?
You weren't like this before.
Three years is a short time.
Maybe it's because my big sister told me to treasure it.
Three years feels like a long time for me, though.
But you know,
when you're with people you love,
whatever you do ends up being fun, right?
I'm having fun now.
You know, I...
I'm having fun too.
I'm not trying too hard.
I know what kind of expression you have.
You know without looking?!
Let me see.
It's dark, so I'll have to get closer to see.
What kind of an expression do you have?
Stupid.
Yuu-chan, don't sleep!
We aren't done yet!
Heehee!
If you don't wake up, I'll kiss you!
Geez, Yuu-chan, wake up!
Geez, I'll really kiss you if you don't wake up!
She won't wake up!
I'm actually awake, though.
Maybe I should sleep too.
I don't care if we don't finish.
Good night.
I'm not awake yet.
Wake up!
I'm awake now.
Cultural Festival ☆ Sleepover                       The End
Misato
West
Festival
Welcome!
Would you like a frankfurter?
Live
Handmade
Dolls
We have a costume café!
A cappella concert starts at 11!
Cultural Festival ☆ The Real Thing!
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who is the fairest of them all?
Snow
White
Class G'Morrow - Recital
What should I do?!
Let us run away!
Come with me, beautiful princess!
Thank you, huntsman!
Misato                                               West                                                 Festival
And so Snow White escaped danger.
However...
...the old woman held a bright red apple out to her.
Snow
White
A present for the beautiful lady!
Ah, what a delicious looking apple!
Snow
White
What to do, what to do?
Snow White has died!
Snow
White
The bright red apple was poisoned!
Snow
White
Oh, she is so beautiful!
Snow
White
It's as if she were sleeping!
Snow
White
The prince instinctively kisses Snow White, who lies in a glass coffin.
Snow     White
What happened to me?
Where am I?
Misato                                               West                                                 Festival
Beautiful princess!
You are with me now.
Please stay with me forever!
And they lived happily ever after.
Misato                                               West                                                 Festival
This was a recital of Snow White by Class G'Morrow!
President Mitsuki!
Snow     White
Snow      White
I was so nervous even though I only had to recite it!
Well done, comrade in arms!
Yeah...
Snow        White
Just now, the two witches buried the hatchet!
I've never heard of two people playing one role.
Onee-chan, thank you for participating!
Did that make you happy?
Yes!
Snow     White
Snow      White
I'm really glad you were Snow White, President Mitsuki!
You sounded so dignified!
It really gave the feeling of the main character!
Snow     White
Snow      White
What?
Your hair is so fluffy and princess-like!
Princess?!
It stood up!
Big
Sister
All                    Done
Big
Sister
Oh yeah, Yuu,
you'll visit the food stalls with your sister, won't you?
Uh, Yuu-chan and I-
Yeah, let's go!
Misato        West
Where should we start?
Let's see...
Misato        West
W-What?
D-Do you want to come with us?
Yuu-chan made a promise with me!
Geez...
It's the last time they'll be able to have a culture festival together.
Let them enjoy it.
I know that, but still!
So insistent...
Can't you look at me every once in a while?!
S-Sorry!
There's someone my heart is set on...
That wasn't a confession!
Class representative, come here!
Okay!
See you in a bit.
We'll wait here.
Kaede-chan's the class representative,
so we won't really be able to do anything with her.
Well, that can't be helped.
Yuzu-chan handles the loneliness so well!
Don't just make stuff up!
Misato       West
Why is Kaede-chan the class representative?
She has been doing it since elementary school.
I don't really know why though.
You don't know even though you've been together for so long?!
Is that a problem?
I only met Yuu-chan in middle school,
but I already know everything about her!
Follow my example!
Just so you know, that's not something worth boasting about.
All right, tell me something about Yuu that I don't know.
Sure!
Yuu always sleeps on her right side.
I see.
She has a mole next to her belly button.
I know that.
That seemed to worry her.
Hey.
Sorry to make you wait.
Kaede
Kaede-chan, Yuzu-chan is bullying me!
Hey, now, don't bully her.
How was that bullying?
Yuzu, you're unexpectedly knowledgeable about Yuu.
Not really.
Yuu was just talking about it earlier.
Yuu-chan...
Oh.
But you don't know why I'm the class representative?
I-It's not that I don't know, I just can't remember!
Can't be helped.
I shall tell you.
You don't need to.
I'll try to remember it while we're walking.
As expected from Yuzu-chan. That's how a friend should be.
As expected from Yuzu-chan.
That's how a friend should be.
Huh?
Maybe Yuu-chan doesn't remember...
...what she promised to do with me.
Haruka, let's go!
Misato Festival
Food      Court
Takoyaki
Ah, I'm getting excited!
Let's eat!
Yeah!
This sata andagi is a bit oily.
Want some takoyaki?
Thanks!
Ya               ki                so               ba
There's yakisoba!
Here, one yakisoba!
Yuzu-chan, have you remembered?
Not yet.
I forgot...
Sakura
Eat Till You Drop
I have five plates!
Seven, eight, nine...
Nine plates!
I ate more after all!
Treat us to some juice!
What?!
Haruka, you don't have enough willpower.
So frustrating!
Why are you competing in something like this?
Friday, April 15th
Second Elementary School?
Does anyone want to be the class representative?
Me!
Here!
Oh, Kaede-chan too?
How about we decide with rock-paper-scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes, I win!
So Yuzu-chan will be the class representative.
I'll steal away the class representative's position next year!
Mark my words.
And she's been competing with me ever since?!
Nope.
What was it then?!
Workbook
Japanese
One day, you were carrying a huge pile of notebooks.
Since you couldn't see anything, you ended up falling down the stairs and hurting yourself.
Something like that happened?
And so to make sure that you never
experience something like that again,
I decided to take on this job.
So that's what happened.
Misato               West            Festival
Yuu-chan!
Haruka, where'd you go?
Weren't you the one that broke our promise and went to the food stalls with President Mitsuki?!
I was going to go with you after that!
My sister has student council work to do!
I didn't hear anything about that!
I didn't tell you!
Yuu-chan!
Haru
I'm sorry, Haruka!
Let's go see the stalls together!
I'm full already, so no thanks.
That's mine...
Then... let's go see who's performing!
I'm eating right now, so no thanks.
Then, uh...
I'll give you this hair ornament which has been passed down through the Sonoda family for generations,
so let's go!
Giving such an item to someone like me...
She believes it...
Sold out, sorry!
You would be stupid not to buy this!
Hurry up and buy it!
Sheesh, Sensei, why are you so hopeless?
Misato
West
Head
Over
Heels
Got it, Josefina?
Who's Josefina?
Misato                                               West                                                 Festival
Catharine!
Who's that?
Simone!
Yes?
I love you.
What's that?
I'll take this end!
Misato                                               West                                                 Festival
Thank you very much!
There's a band next.
Did you like that performance?
I just thought we match.
hiru sagari hizashi atatakakute
The rays of the early afternoon sun are warm
昼下がり日差し暖かくて
I'm really sorry, Haruka.
tsui utouto shichau kedo
So I accidentally doze off
ついウトウトしちゃうけど
Don't worry about it, I'm not angry anymore.
But, while I was making fun memories,
anata ga tonari ni iru to kokoro
But when you're next to me, my heart
あなたが隣にいると心
you were feeling depressed.
We can do whatever you want for the time being.
ukiuki nemuku naranai
Feels so cheerful I won't feel sleepy
ウキウキ眠くならない
Is she joking?
chikazuite yuku
You get closer to me
近付いてゆく
She isn't, is she?
futari no kyori wa ato nanmiri
How many millimetres are there left between us?
二人の距離は後何ミリ？
I'll do what I want then.
pukapuka ukabu kumo wo yubisaki de tsutsuite
I poke the fluffy, floating clouds with my fingertip
ぷかぷか浮かぶ雲を指先でつついて
sotto ugokasu
Gently making them move
そっと動かす
Yuu-chan and I kissed until the gym's lights came on.
sonna watashi wo mite warau anata no egao ga
You watch me do that with a smiling face
そんな私を見て笑うあなたの笑顔が
daisuki da yo nante ienai
A face I won't say I love
大好きだよなんて言えない
zettai
No way!
絶対！
The band's performance ended at some point,
so there was nothing else to listen to.
All I heard was Yuu-chan's heartbeat,
deep breaths,
and the faint sound of our lips.
Big
Sister
Little
Cultural Festival ☆ The Real Thing!               The End
Sister
Little
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Hey, Yuu,
do you eat together with President Mitsuki?
I do.
I wonder if it's really food?
What?
Does President Mitsuki do anything special at home?
Special?
She studies and sleeps a lot...
That's it!
What's it?!
Next time, Trick 7.
Swimsuit Fanservice ☆ And Some Crying
Shopping with Yuu-chan
"Swimsuit Fanservice ☆ Some Crying" and "Shopping with Yuu-chan".
Look forward to it!
I sleep a lot, too.
So that's not it, huh?