Morning!
Oh, morning!
Long time no see!
Whoa, you're tanned! Did you go to the beach?
Yuuko-chan!
Hm?
Yuuko-chan, morning!
Ah, Run, Tooru! Good morning!
Morning.
Well, school's started.
That's right.
It's a shame summer vacation's over.
But we had a lot of fun!
I guess so.
Ah. Nagi.
Nagi-chan, good morning!
Shh!
What are you doing?
You'll be late.
Good morning!
Uh-oh.
Y-Yes! G-Good morning, Kitou-sensei!
What's the matter?
It's the long-awaited new semester!
You ought to have more pep in the morning!
Let's try that once more.
Now!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
Still not enough!
One more try!
Good morning! Go on.
Good morning!
I'm sorry, Yuuko!
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
Won't you come with me?
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう？
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　あつまるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日射し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ちあわせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
And we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
New Semester
First morning of the new semester and you're already too intense.
The students are gonna hate you.
I-It's not like I'm trying to be friends with the students!
Rather, these students need a mentor.
But all things call for moderation, no?
Sometimes you should just leave things alone... right?
Satou. Mornin'.
The way Kamate-chan leaves things alone is sublime.
It lets you relax in tense situations.
Ah, it sends shivers down my spine.
Yes... this indifference that seems to deny my very existence...
Don't utter such sickening remarks! It's highly unpleasant.
Kitou, you should just ignore him.
Utterly abhorrent!
Kitou-sensei,
that shouting of yours is giving me a headache, so would you stop?
Well, dear sir, perhaps a return to the nurse's office is in order.
Why don't you head to your classroom?
Your beloved students are there. Run along, now.
What kind of attitude is that?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Close enough whatever-they-are's to argue, huh?
There you go again!
My deepest apologies.
Hey, why aren't you two dating already?
You never treat anything seriously-
Even for a joke, that's not funny.
You're perfectly synchronized, too.
She's way too intense this early in the morning.
Really?
Morning, Run-chan!
Morning! Long time no see!
Morning!
Ooh, you're tanned!
Where did you go?
The boys are at it again.
Belize.
Thailand.
Really? How nice!
And there she is. The first-year that loves Run-chan.
Hard at work as soon as the semester starts.
Even though she's tiny.
Tooru?
You're tall!
W-We're sorry.
That was awful of you to leave me behind like that.
Aw, we're sorry, Yuuko.
Honestly, it was terrible-
Huh?
Why are you holding a chair?
I wonder.
Good morning!
Right, right, that's what I'm talking about!
It was in the paper this morning.
Toorun and Miporin are chatting!
Ah, what did it say?
Let Yutaka join in, too!
Japan's political and economic situation...
Easing of regulations should come first, shouldn't it?
What's wrong? Yutaka?
Japan's political and economic situation... easing of regulations...
It's too complicated. More than Yutaka can handle!
Oh yeah, did you see that drama yesterday?
Yeah, I did. The hot-blooded school-life drama!
The person playing the teacher was really intense.
But that's what I like about it.
Toorun! Miporin!
Good morning!
Cut it out! It's hot, Yutaka!
Heheheh...
Okay! Return to your seats!
Good morning!
The second semester starts today!
Let's all get energized!
Good morning!
Hot...
Begin warming up!
Don't be sloppy or you'll hurt yourself.
I just can't get enough of that lax attitude.
Hey, Tooru-san.
What?
Continuing where we left off earlier...
Tooooruuun!
Now it's Yutaka's turn!
S-Stop it...
Now see here...
I missed you so much! Summer vacation was too long!
You met her at the mid-break review, didn't you?
Don't remember that!
Oh, really?
Hm? Is this...?
Huh?
Okay! Three minutes is up.
Step away from Tooru-san immediately.
Whaaat? Already?
Yutaka!
Yes, ma'am!
The Three Minute Rule.
That's the rule for Tooru-san fans!
Um, you said you were a "fan" before, too.
Did I do something special?
Tooru-san, you're good at everything,
but you're not stuck-up about it.
That's right, that's right!
Plus, you're always so cool and collected.
Right?
Well, I'm sure you hear this all the time...
Huh? Tooru-san?
Where's Tooru-san?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Tooruuun!
Tooru-san! May I have a moment?
I'd like to ask a favor.
Oh. Certainly, Kitou-sensei.
Toorun...
Sorry for interrupting your conversation.
I'll be borrowing Tooru-san.
I'd like you to go get the assignment notebooks.
Understood.
It's not fair.
What is?
Even if she's the teacher, she should follow the Three Minute Rule...
Wait!
In that case, I'm counting on you.
Got it.
That's far enough!
Three minutes are up!
Any more than that-
See you later, Tooru-san!
Th-Three minute- three...
Here.
Take care of these, please.
Understood.
Oh, I forgot.
Can you take these, too?
Uh, sure.
And while you're at it, get me a coffee from the vending machine.
Wha-?
Kamate-sensei! Don't take advantage of the students, please!
I don't want to hear that from you.
Well, you could buy it instead.
Go buy it yourself!
Let's see...
Ah, excuse me for a second here...
K's Poems
Now I wonder whose notebook this is?
You're fine with black coffee, right?
Thanks a bunch.
Toorun's taking too long. Yutaka is lonely.
She'll be back soon.
Ah!
That's...
What is it?
It's the upperclassmen Tooru-san's always with!
You're right!
That Fair-Skinned-senpai is pretty cute!
Yeah.
Glasses-senpai has a very intellectual air.
Oh.
The one who looks like a model...
She's Tall-senpai, isn't she?
Where's the fire?
No. That would be Mop-senpai.
I see!
What's up? Caught a cold?
I know a way to get rid of it!
I think you're supposed to hit her hard in the middle of her back.
What?
That's for hiccups.
You've got it wrong.
Huh?
Who's that?!
You're supposed to hit the solar plexus.
Tooru!
Sheesh, don't scare us!
It's Tooru-san!
Wonder what they're talking about?
Oh!
They're such good friends.
They sure are.
Wha-
We'll help!
Thank you.
Hup.
I'll take these.
You don't have to take them all.
You carried them by yourself all the way here.
Are we usually allowed to leave right now?
This way we're splitting the work evenly.
I'm sure it's fine.
She's totally embarrassed.
How heartwarming.
Yeah.
Huh?
Senpai's started chatting with a boy.
Toorun's disappeared.
Oh, she's back!
With a bat. Is she going to play baseball?
Whoa!
K's Poems
Safe and sound.
I'm leaving now!
Good morning!
G-Good morning, Kitou-sensei!
She caught me again...
Guess today's not your day.
Tell me about it.
Oh, speaking of which, Tooru hasn't come by today, has she?
Cleaning duty again?
No, we're in the middle of a fight.
What? For real?
Wha- Are you okay?
Yeah, it happens once in a while.
The two of them, in a fight! What do we do, Nagi?
This is no time for you to be getting upset!
Calm down!
But I mean-
I mean, a fight- I can't believe it!
I told you, calm down!
A-At any rate, let's ask why.
Right.
So? Why are you fighting?
Well, you see...
It's gotten late.
I'll walk you home.
I'll be fine.
But I heard there are perverts roaming the streets lately.
Then you'd be the one in danger on your way home alone from my place.
I said I'm fine.
You'd be in danger!
I'm the one who's safe!
What reason do you have for that?
What about you? What if something happens?
We're in the same neighborhood! It's fine!
Well, the same goes for me!
It's more the same for me!
... and we ended up arguing over it.
So what did you end up doing?
She slept over at my house.
While you were still fighting?!
Yeah.
Can you even call that fighting?
I can't believe Run and Tooru are fighting.
I'll bet Tooru's feeling depressed.
Tooru!
Run-chan, you jerk.
Wow. Drowning her sorrows in juice.
It's hard to butt in with this atmosphere.
Don't tell me she noticed me!
Bulls-eye each time!
Then I'll bring it sometime.
Thanks.
Fighting, huh?
Tooru's probably depressed,
but Run looks the same as usual.
It's rare to see you reading a book, Run.
Oh?
Really?
What are you reading?
Run...
That's upside-down.
Huh?
Oh!
In general, if we take y = ax + bx + c as equation 1,
and ax + bx + c = 0 as equation 2...
In the event of an injury due to an accident or a mishap,
first attend to those at the scene...
Wow, this is long.
Do the rest yourself! At least skim it all!
What should we do?
Hmm...
Nagi, aren't you worried?
Of course I am.
But I don't know what to do.
It hurts to see them like that.
Yeah...
Ah, what should we do? I'm so worried.
If you have any worries, I'll hear them!
Kitou-sensei!
Go on! Any sort of worry is fine!
N-No, I'm not really worried about anything.
Hold up!
The worst thing you could do is bottle up your worries inside!
Now, open up your heart!
L-Like I said, I'm not worried about anything.
Don't hide it!
Let me hear everything!
Go on! Go on, go on, go on! Go on!
What is there to be shy about?
N-No thank you!
You won't regret it! Come on!
Geez, I'm not worried about anything!
Wait up, Yuuko-san! Don't be shy, open your heart to me!
Today's really not your day.
Run-chan...
Ah.
Toorun looks down.
Yutaka's gotta go cheer her up!
What is it, Miporin?
We're heading back, Yutaka.
I don't think Tooru-san's in the mood right now.
Huh? But...
Come on, let's go.
Ack! Miporin! I can't breathe...
I got away...
Tooru?
Actually, it bothers me, so I'm going to make up with her!
To the school store!
Wha- Hang on! What's the school store have to do with this?
I'll need sweets to make up with her.
You're buying her back?
These, please!
That will be 200 yen.
Five Yen
Should I pay?
Oh!
Huh?
The clouds gently float off into the distance.
All I could do was gaze up at them from here.
She got ahead of me!
Where are you off to now? Hey!
Gosh...
If only I could fly, I could go with you
Was there something strange about this?
Sorry
Ah.
to the ends of the earth. What awaits us there?
You never realize how precious something is
Tooru!
until after you've lost it.
If I were more honest with myself, I'd have understood.
The rain clears, and beneath the rainbow,
will we be smiling? Right now, I want to walk this path
forever and ever, together with you.
Toorun looked down.
Yutaka's worried.
Yeah.
Ah!
But I get the feeling she's fine now.
Case closed, huh?
Honestly, that was bad for my heart.
I don't have a handkerchief...
What's this, Nagi? Moved to tears?
Huh?
How could you not be moved by this?
K-Kitou-sensei! When did you-
Hm?
Come on. Let's go home, Yutaka.
Right!
Toorun's gonna be cheerful tomorrow, right?
Probably.
That means she'll play with me, right?
Only for three minutes.
Whaaaat?
K's Poems
I'm heading out now.
'Kay.
Later.
Yes, good work today.
Drink it
The tall shadows
akane ni narabu
茜に並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kageboushi
背高かげぼうし
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　お喋り
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね　明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigato
いつもありがと
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれて　ヨカッタな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
ル・ル・ルン・
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風とココロ　ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
つぎの角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Next time
In the blink of an eye, fall is here.
What? But we haven't covered the important stories yet!
Like Toorun and Yutaka's moongazing, or Toorun and Yutaka's athletic festival!
Next time on A-Channel!
"Present"!
Naturally, those include me too, right?
See you next week!