Kanai Hidehiko-san.
Is that correct?
You're a Selector.
You too? Why do you know who I—
Have you heard of the Bookmaker?
Yeah, from some rumors here and there.
He books matches between Selectors based on their level.
If you form a contract with him, he can help you avoid the desperate search whenever your time limit approaches.
I'll gladly introduce you if you'd like.
What the heck is up with you?
And why would you ask me of all people?
Forget it. This is probably some sort of trap.
That's too bad.
I'll ask something else then.
Will you do it with me?
Born into memories everything is given life
born memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Pull me from this maze of fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Dive into memories, if only I could see you
dive memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurikaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Battle
Past and Present
Attack!
Guard.
Shit!
Attack! Attack! Attack!
Fuck! Turn End!
Mel, Grow.
Summon SIGNIs.
In addition, I bet a coin.
Berserk.
Full attack.
Turn End.
All right, let's attack with everything!
Calm down!
You're being controlled by her power!
We should use a coin—
Shut up!
I'll win if I can get just one more attack through!
I summon three SIGNI! All-out attack!
Arts: End of Heart.
Now you have only one coin remaining.
Think about what would happen if you hit your limit without finding an opponent.
Would you like an introduction?
To the Bookmaker.
Bravo!
I'm touched, Chinatsu-chan.
You scored this contract for me in record time.
I think you might be a natural at this job.
Did I perhaps draw out your latent abilities?
I simply did as you asked.
And being able to do that is what's amazing.
It's not as if I could've asked this job of anyone.
You must be strong in battle, and strong in here too.
Just for reference, why did you decide to take it up?
I wanted to settle on a new job quickly.
A new job, huh.
Don't worry, I'll make sure to pay your salary in full.
So, Chinatsu-chan.
This is the next person I'd like you to recruit.
Rio-chan, see you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
Hello.
You're the Selector girl...
Do you want to battle again?
Nope, I just wanted to play with you today, Rio-chan.
With me?
I see, so your mom...
Yeah, when I was in third grade.
I wished to see her again just one more time.
I prayed to God every night.
And then I became a Selector!
I named my LRIG Mama.
She kinda reminded me of her!
My, that makes me happy.
She even scolds me sometimes.
"Did you finish your homework?"
And like, "Eat all your green peppers!"
When I see Rio-chan's face, I just can't help it.
But it's the same for me! I listen to what you say.
But... she's not my real Mama.
That's why I'm gonna get back my real Mama with the battles!
You don't know, Onee-san?
If you get five coins, you can change
one memory any way you want!
I'm gonna erase the memory of
Mama dying after I win!
Then Mama never would've died, right?
You're so clever, Rio-chan.
I know!
I have an idea, Rio-chan.
You'll need to win a lot of battles
for that to happen, right?
Wouldn't it be bad if you couldn't find any Selectors to do that with?
Yeah, it would.
I have a friend called the Bookmaker.
If you ask him, he'll find an opponent for you.
Wouldn't it be useful to know someone like that?
Yeah, it would!
Where can I meet that person?
Hey, Ril.
What?
Do you think I'm dependent on you?
Have I just been relying on other people,
like Hanna-chan said?
I wonder if that's why Chii-chan hates me now.
Ril, you were created from my memories of Chii-chan, weren't you?
Yes.
Are you helping me because we're friends?
Or is it...
Sorry.
I don't even know what I'm saying.
I'm sorry.
Here, your paycheck.
I included a little bonus.
Here's to our future work.
Did that girl sign a contract?
That girl?
Oh, Rio-chan? She sure did, and it's all thanks to you.
Looks like you want to say something.
Was it really necessary to involve such a young child?
I'm not entirely sure what you mean.
Aren't you intending to force her into a corner
with battles and then enjoy her struggles?
She just wants to escape from the truth of losing her mother.
And she's free to do so.
It doesn't matter what you want as a reward for winning.
The important part is that you can't run away from battling.
We're simply lending her a helping hand.
Huh? What?
Chinatsu-chan, don't tell me you feel sorry for her!
Just because you're the same...
I'm not. I—
You're planning to discard her.
Suzuko-chan and your memories of her.
What are you implying?
Right, I remember now.
I believe it was... yes!
You'll live as freely as you wish, right?
"I can cut the chains that restrained me
and live as freely as I wish."
"For that purpose I will become strong, emerge victorious
from the Selector battles, and discard you."
Did I get it right?
You want to get rid of what restrained you.
But can you even do that?
What do you mean?
I just can't see someone who'd feel sympathy for a child actually throwing anything away.
Especially about Suzuko-chan.
Chii-chan.
Have no doubt.
I will discard Suzu for my own benefit.
That's the entire reason I'm here.
You know, I'm on the edge of my seat.
I can't wait to see the moment you molt into a truly strong and beautiful creature.
That doesn't matter to me.
I'm ridding myself of Suzuko for my own sake.
There's a good girl.
Then I've got some good news
for you, Chinatsu-chan.
Suzuko-chan just lost a battle and is down to only one coin left!
Don't betray my expectations, Chii-chan.
Hello.
Heya, it's Satomi.
Thanks so much for the other day.
Though it's too bad you lost the battle, Suzuko-chan.
Anyway, sorry to spring this on you so soon,
but you've been chosen.
Chii-chan.
You know, I...
I had so many things I wanted to talk with you about.
But all I could do was send the occasional letter.
And even those started to bounce back after a while.
The first thing I did after I moved back was visit your house.
I guess you moved. I was worried you didn't live in this city anymore.
So it made me really happy when I suddenly saw you here.
Suzu.
Do you think I lied and that we can go back to how we used to be?
You never change.
You never have, and you never will.
You are the chains that restrain me.
Now, let's battle.
You can't escape.
Open.
We get the first turn, Suzuko.
Grow.
Suzuko?
I waited.
Every day I waited for your letters.
You played basketball in middle school, right?
I thought that it was just like you.
Suzuko! The battle already started!
When I read that you were applying for a private prep school, I was hardly even surprised.
You know, it snows a lot in Hokkaido, but they
make sure that it's never blocking the streets.
Huh? What am I talking about?
Suzuko.
I never, ever stopped wanting to see you again.
There's so much I wanted to talk about... with you.
That's why—
Ending your turn?
Chii-chan?
Yeah.
Don't you understand? You only have one coin left!
If you lose this battle, you'll disappear!
Suzu!
Turn End.
In my last year of middle school, my father's company went bankrupt.
We lost our house, and I had no time to send you letters as we moved from place to place.
I saved up money working while attending high school.
Just one misstep, and you fall off the path.
Every single day, I tried to live up to your ideal.
I tried and tried... and what did that get me?
Chii-chan?
I can feel that who I am as a Selector is the real me.
Unrestrained by anyone, I'm free to grow strong.
I can finally make out the form of the revolting parasite that dug its way inside me.
Suzu, it's you!
Mel, Grow.
I summon Mayo.
Coin Bet.
Berserk.
She used a coin!
Suzuko will only be able to attack on her next turn.
Mel, attack!
Ril!
Turn End.
Ril...
Use a coin.
If we find out what's in her hand,
we might be able to counter it.
But...
You'll lose at this rate. Is that what you want?
But in a battle against Chii-chan...
N-No!
It's futile. You can't resist Berserk.
Full...
Attack.
Arts: End of Heart.
R-Ril, I...
Suzuko, look straight ahead.
If you have something you treasure,
a memory you don't want to lose, then fight!
But...
I see.
That LRIG is the one holding your hand now.
Ril.
Ril and Mel! Together forever!
No matter what, we'll be together forever!
I'm going to vomit.
Disappear from my life!
Another coin?!
Coin Bet!
Berserk.
No...
Stop! If I attack again, then Ril...
We already told you it's futile.
Summon Armile.
And attack...
Downwards!
Down?
What was that?
Did she attack a random place to avoid a counter?
Suzu's pretty funny.
Turn End.
Mel, Grow.
I accessorize with Teaksauce.
Steak gains Lancer.
Attack!
Goodbye, Suzu.
What?!
No way.
Don't tell me that was intentional.
She used Berserk to protect herself?
Ril, are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
I never would've come up with that.
That's how it always was.
Aw man, it's all wet.
Should we play at home today?
Hey, I just got a good idea!
It's so nice and cold!
Come on! You do it too, Chii-chan!
Okay!
Ah, it's Suzu-chan!
What're you doing?
If you do this, it feels really cold and nice!
Wow, you're right!
It feels nice!
I hated it.
Bye-bye, Suzu-chan!
Bye-bye! See you later!
Chii-chan?
I hated how you could get everything
I wanted without even trying.
That's no good.
If you don't clean up, you'll catch a cold.
Am I gonna get in trouble?
And I hated your smile.
Don't worry, I'll just say you tripped.
Really?
Thanks, Chii-chan!
There, you can put your rain boots back on.
I'll protect you from now on.
So don't ever leave my side, okay?
I hated it.
Sure!
I wanted your smile for myself.
I hated myself for trying to build such a warped relationship.
I don't need it! I'm going to make every memory of you disappear, Suzu!
Chii-chan, wait!
Mel, attack!
Hey!
What are you doing here? There's a sign right there saying it's dangerous.
What happened?
If a third party approaches a battle in progress,
it's forcibly cut short.
This battle is invalid.
Invalid?
If only you had disappeared.
Chii-chan was serious.
Disappear, Suzu!
If I disappear...
If I stop battling and lose all of my memories...
Will you discard her?
Isn't she your friend?
Yeah...
Is this all right with you?
You should just be the one to protect Chinatsu.
I should?
Remember it, Suzu.
That's so big!
I'm Homura Suzuko.
What's your name?
Morikawa Chinatsu.
Then you're Chii-chan!
Chii-chan, let's read together.
Okay.
Good morning, Chii-chan!
Good morning.
Ril.
But how?
All of your memories are inside of me, Suzuko.
Thank you, Ril.
We didn't start out this way.
A goal, or an ideal...
If only I were stronger, if only I could go back to that time...
I'm sure...
I'm done with running.
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
Someone pulls back their tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no ga
But I can no longer remember who
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
I thought I needed to get stronger.
Won't you join me?
I have a reason that I must battle.
Didn't you decide on this job?
Won't you do it?
Has Morikawa really...
Next time: Transformation / Pure White and Pitch Black.
Transformation
Pure White and Pitch Black