Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
I thought it was called "Miso"
or "Malt" or something like that.
To keep the nasty pests from staring,
we'll be quick and stealthy.
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Wow!
It's the ocean!
The beach is a must during summer!
It was worth waking up early for this.
Viewing the ocean from a train
like this is a first for me.
Ah, because you're a rich girl, huh?
She was one.
At the beach, we've got to...
Relax on the beach?
Make sandcastles?
And split a watermelon!
But...
Yeah...
We came here to work, huh?
"Veggies, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, and Fish"
Summer. Summer means the ocean!
The ocean means a beach hut.
This August, I present Himitsu
no Hanazono, beach hut version!
It's tough working there as it is...
And now she has a beach hut version.
Don't worry. Mitsugu found
this suitable place for me.
Yamaji...
Always there to serve.
Of course, the shop is temporarily closed today.
That's not what we were worried about.
Wait, I've been wondering since earlier,
but what's "Himitsu no Hanazono"?
--It's the name of my shop.
--What?!
Oh!
Secret Garden... is English for
"Himitsu no Hanazono!"
Did you know, Miss Yoko?
She would know the name of where she works.
Er... well, I thought it was called "Miso"
or "Malt" or something like that.
Those are totally wrong.
It's a western cake shop!
Well, if it were based on Miss Sonobe,
it should be called "Den of Thieves"...
...or "Shop of Chaos."
As I said, it's "Himitsu no Hanazono!"
Same difference.
Quite right.
It's completely different!
It's perfect for someone who reeks of the 80's.
Oh, Yamaji.
So you knew, Yamaji?
Yes. Every time I get a receipt,
I cringe with embarrassment.
Anyway, from today we'll be
Himitsu no Hanazono, beach hut version!
Oh, I have a question.
What is a beach hut?
Miss Yoko...
Are you serious?
Th-That's right. Of course
Miss Yoko wouldn't know.
You're a rich girl who knows
nothing of the world.
I-I have at least heard of it before!
I just do not know what it is exactly.
Sonobe! Explain to me what
a beach hut is in plain terms.
Huh?
With interpretive dance!
Waves.
Wind.
I do not understand. Not at all.
I do not think I can work then.
Sand! I am sand.
Uh, what is this?
Is it a ritual or something?
W-Well, we've come all the way out here.
And she said she would pay us, too.
I suppose there is no other choice.
Then, let's go change.
Yes, let us.
All right, let's go!
--Truthfully, I didn't approve of this beach hut thing.
--I'm getting excited!
There's nothing good about getting
sunburned and heat stroke.
To keep the nasty pests from staring,
we'll be quick and stealthy.
I see. Good luck.
"Shaved Ice"
And I was playing--
Yum! What is this? It's so good!
Wow, it's delicious!
I'll have the melon and orange one, too!
Oh, but I want to try all of them!
What's that? It sounds good.
I want to try it, too!
It's so obvious she's a fake customer!
Well, as usual, I'm forced to help out, too.
Thank you very much.
Please work hard so nasty pests
don't notice Miss Yoko.
I think it'll be fine.
What is it? You seem dissatisfied.
Well, you look different
from what I had imagined.
I do?
Yes. I had imagined...
Summer! Under the bright sun!
A summer time for girls bursting with youth!
The sweet lure of a flushed body.
A sweets paradise by the shore!
Himitsu no Hanazono. Open this
summer at the beach hut. Mwah!
Something like that.
Absolutely not.
Old-fashioned, as usual. And you could
get sued for that disguise at the end.
If you could at least wear
something like Hayama or Futaba...
I do not wish to get an unsightly tan.
How about working in a bikini to avoid that?
I'll make your uniform a bikini.
Miss Sonobe, you can wear a bikini.
This place is more like a
fancy café than a beach hut, huh?
That's true. We'll have a summer menu
with gelato, frappés, and gelatin desserts.
What about ramen?! Curry?! Fried noodles?!
We're a dessert shop.
Isn't fried noodles a dessert?
What? It's not a side dish?!
Himitsu no Hanazono!
"Beach Hut"
Open today. Himitsu no Hanazono!
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Man, the shop's name is embarrassing.
Should we move somewhere else?
What's that?
Big Sister! Big Sister!
Big Sister!
Big Sister.
Yu?
I heard that you were working at a
beach hut. I'll help with the sales.
I'll just have some of everything!
Oh? But the whole menu is ice cream and drinks.
Oh, really? What should I do?
Need some help there?
Maybe it's not a good idea.
I'm cold after eating so much.
You do not have to push yourself.
--But, you made this. I'll finish it all.
--Here's the peach lassi.
--What?
--Thank you for waiting!
Big Sister wasn't the one making them?
Hm?
So immature.
He's really immature.
Just because you're an adult doesn't necessarily
mean you're mature. I thought you were aware.
Yup.
It's true.
"Closed for the Day."
Today was our pre-opening, so I've closed the shop early.
Thank you for your work.
We were only open for half the day,
but sales were excellent.
It was harder than I expected. And very hot.
We're not used to it.
I've prepared a barbecue to restore our
energy since tomorrow will be a full day.
--Meat?!
--Meat!
I-I want some, too...
Are you all right, Yu?
I'm fine. That much food is nothing. I'm a man.
Especially if you'll cook the meat for me...
Everyone, the food's ready!
What?!
You really don't learn.
So immature.
Wow, so enthusiastic.
Apologies. Is my cooking not to your liking?
No, I don't feel like eating it.
Well, I'm actually glad...
Then, we'll have some.
Let's eat!
Food is so nourishing after hard work.
Yamaji! Grill with the ratio of veggies, meat,
meat, meat, meat, meat, meat, and fish!
Our profits today...
Teru!
Wow, it looks so yummy!
Big Sis!
You were up early for work
today, huh? I came to help...
What? We're done already.
Your sister is very kind.
--I'm jealous since I'm an only child.
--Would you like some, too?
--You've told me that before!
--Yeah, thanks!
Oh, it's the little boy!
H-Hello!
You're not going to eat any meat?
That's not good. You won't grow bigger.
I know! I'll make some for you.
--Oh... Thank you very much.
--Yu...
This might be the last straw.
Oh no, barbecue should be fine.
Raw meat has more vitamins, did you know?
I'll call an ambulance, just in case.
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Here's the mango frappé.
Phew. This is our last day working here.
We made it through, somehow.
But we didn't get to play at all,
even though we're at the beach!
We've been working this whole time.
Thank you both for accompanying
me this whole time.
Still...
You got tan, Futaba.
More like burnt.
Well, it's summer!
Even so!
Summer means curry! Aren't I kind of like curry?
You're okay with that?
Anyway, I have a farmer's tan now,
so I want to even it out.
We'll be done working, so let's go
all out and play tomorrow!
We haven't gone into the ocean,
so we need to take this chance now!
You are right.
I'm pretty much done with homework,
so let's have fun for the rest of summer.
H-Homewor--? I'm not sure I know that word.
Our modern Japanese homework is a
reflection essay. Will you be okay?
Then, I will prepare lunch for you as thanks.
Really?
Do you have any requests?
Barbecue!
We had that the first day.
What's the beach without barbecue?!
There's more to the beach than that!
How about curry?
It's enough just looking at you.
You can leave it up to me, then.
Aw!
Regardless, let us enjoy the beach tomorrow!
Yeah! The ocean is plentiful.
--You're going to catch stuff?!
--All right!
Let's make the most out of tomorrow!
"Shark Sighted
No Swimming"
It depends on the species,
freshness, and cooking preparation.
What are you talking about?!
Aw, man!
--What the heck? I can't swim!
--How disappointing.
It would have been nice if it were
a dolphin rather than a shark.
Yeah...
Big Sister!
Yu!
You're not working today, right?
You can play, right?
That's what we thought...
--There's a shark--
--Not to worry!
"Southern Sea Resort Hotel"
I brought tickets for the hotel pool.
So let's go here!
Oh, can we?
Yeah!
Can we barbecue there?
I said it was a hotel.
Wow!
A pool!
It's so pretty!
It is all thanks to you, Yu.
It was nothing.
Oh, it's been a while since
I've gone to a pool with you.
Y-Yeah...
Now, make sure to stretch. Here's a floatie.
It's like you came with your mom.
Oh yeah, where's Miss Sonobe?
The lunches are taking longer than expected.
She said she would meet us by lunch.
Big Sister, let's pla--
Futaba!
Sakura.
Usuda. Why are you here?
Oh, yeah.
He's not good at dealing with Sakura.
I just happened to come here with my family. Hm?
Oh!
Yu! I found you!
It was probably emotional
damage rather than physical.
I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Wait, Sakura went with him.
Oh...
Miss Yoko, be nice to him next time.
I should.
Now, let's enjoy this pool!
Yes!
We will enjoy it in Yu's place, too.
Wow, this is amazing! Hotel pools are great!
Stop, it's embarrassing.
But, it's so cool, Nishiyama!
Your bathing suit is pretty amazing, too.
Th-This is normal!
By the way, it's amazing you
got free tickets for this pool.
Someone gave them to me.
Really?
Hayama's sister gave them to me.
What?! How did that happen?
You see...
"First place"
It's so heavy!
Excuse me, I can help you.
Really?
So that was Hayama's...
Then, she gave me the tickets she won.
I can't really enjoy myself now that I know.
Well, it's not like Hayama is here.
Oh, it's Hayama and the others.
What?!
They're totally enjoying themselves.
Just... ignore them.
--They're totally enjoying themselves...
--I-Ignore them.
Got some turban shells!
What are you doing?!
Oh, Nishiyama.
I'm practicing catching
sea urchin or abalone and stuff.
Don't do that here!
Yeah. It's against the law
unless you're a fisherman.
That's not the problem here!
Oh, you are--
Oh, Nishiyama. Why do you always
follow me? No way, do you like me?
Don't make up gross things like that!
Oh, it's the nice girl from before.
Oh, Hayama's sister.
Even her sister's here.
Is she your friend, too?
She's just my classmate, Nishiyama.
Oh, right! Since we're all here,
let's all play together!
Wai--
I-I have some friends here...
Huh? You do?
Come on, let's go!
Nishiyama!
Now, I'll go finish my sandcastle--
Teru!
Ack!
You should swim, too!
Y-You should know. I can't--
Ah, you can't swim, huh.
Is that true?
It's pretty scary if something happens, huh.
Like if your boat sinks in the middle of the ocean.
That's true!
Let's practice swimming!
In case you really need to some day.
When I really need to...?
--There!
--Like now?!
--You can do it, Teru!
--Th-The sisters share a resemblance.
Come on, Teru. You need to try harder.
No, way! I can't!
Hayama, you don't like the water?
No, I just can't swim.
I've lasted this long not knowing
how to swim. I'm fine just the way I am.
Hayama.
Teru.
Then, let's go practice in the kiddie pool.
No!
--You can do it!
--Please try your best.
--Everyone! I brought lunch.
--Oh, Miss Sonobe.
I'm saved.
You took a while.
Sorry, it took me longer since there
were so many unfamiliar things.
This is your lunch.
I've been waiting for this!
Yeah, it really took a while
since it was a first for me, too.
By the way, why are you both beat up?
It was just harder than expected.
And it was wild.
But, we got a hold of a rare ingredient.
Rare ingredient?
Oh, I don't think the shark
will be bothering us anymore.
I still don't recommend swimming
since there are many jellyfish.
Oh my, is that so?
Don't tell me...
--Delish!
--You ate it?!
It's ground meat.
They seem like good friends.
You do get sleepy after swimming.
You can use me as a pillow, too.
N-No, thanks.
Go ahead, you can lean on me.
Th-That would be improper.
I can't eat another bite.
She would...
Was she sleep talking?
She's probably having a feast
in her dream right now.
I can have a feast if I sleep?
No, that's not...
Go to sleep. Go to sleep!
Sleep. Sleep.
--I don't think you can sleep if you try that hard.
--Go to sleep. Sleep.
--Sleep. Sleep.
--Miss Yoko...
Sleep. Go to sleep.
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
"Mumble mumble"
I can't eat another bite...
But I can. Probably.
Seriously?
I cannot. I cannot eat anymore.
I will take the rest to-go. I cannot?!
"Next time: Ten Yen Short" "Wah"
A nightmare.
"Next time: Ten Yen Short"