They're putting up the new class lists tomorrow, right?
You think classes will begin right away?
The cherry blossoms bloom in full glory, as does spring itself.
I hope we're in the same class this year too!
Yeah!
As flowers grow and unfold, so do our hearts flutter.
How can this be?
I'm this exhausted after the briefest of flights.
It's finally gotten warmer,
but how can I resume my journey if I cannot fly?
It's because you put on so much weight.
This mochi's delicious, my girl.
It carries the fresh flavor of spring.
It's cherry blossom mochi!
Oh?
You've turned into a whole different bird compared to when we first met, Dela.
It's like the difference between raw and baked mochi, so it's kinda nice!
You can go now, Tamako.
Okay. I'll leave the rest to you.
Fly!
I must fly!
What's that? A bird?
You think it'll fall?
Ah, it ran out of fuel.
It's falling!
You're way heavier than I thought you'd be...
The cherry blossoms bloom in full glory, as does spring itself.
That day I fell from the sky...
was the day I fell in love.
A bird?
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Found your name?
Not in class C.
Oh, I'm in class A.
So am I!
I'm in class B.
What?!
No way!
Why?
We've always been in the same class!
Well, that's life!
We're in different classes.
Tamako and I are in different classes again...
Oh, we're in the same class as Asagiri.
From Badminton Club?
Yup.
Oh!
Does she have something against us?
Episode 3
Gettin' Hot For That Cool Girl
I'm Yagi, your homeroom teacher.
I got married just last month,
so I'm in high spirits!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Whatever feelings the coming year may bring,
let's face them in high spirits!
Well then, let's begin introductions.
How about we start with Asagiri?
I'm Asagiri Shiori.
I'm in Badminton Club.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you.
Next up, Inoue!
Yes!
Next up, Kitashirakawa.
Yes! I'm Kitajiragawa—
Oops.
I'm Kitashirakawa Tamako.
My family runs a mochi shop, Tamaya, over at the Usagiyama Market.
Right now, I'd recommend the cherry blossom mochi.
Please try them out, if you'd like.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh, right.
I'm in Baton Club!
I'm Makino Kanna.
I'm good at measuring things by eye, love right angles,
and have great interest in structural supports.
Out of Order
Right now, I want to fix that locker in the back.
I'm also in Baton Club.
How's your new class?
I'm with Ooji.
How's yours?
Our teacher's really enthusiastic, so I think it's gonna be a fun class!
It'd be even better if that locker got fixed.
What the heck?
One of the lockers in the back is broken, and I want to fix it.
Huh?
Maybe I should come in early and do it.
Come on, stop that!
I wonder if it's possible to hammer a nail with a baton...
Nope. It's not.
This one. This movie.
Looks good.
Hey bird, what're you doing here?
Oh, it's you.
You know, this bird can turn into a projector!
Don't let him know that, though.
Huh? Say what?
Huh?
Are you by yourself, my lady?
Do you like birds, my lady?
M-My body's...
so h-heavy...
Nevertheless, I ought to be looking for my prince's bride,
so do I really have time for such pursuits?
Huh?
She's gone?
She's gone!
And...
Where the devil am I?
Thank you very much!
Calm down, me!
At times like these, all I need is a bird's eye view.
Timbiiird!
Oh, it's the bird from this morning.
Destiny!
How can you talk?
You're a bird.
I apologize, my lady.
You're a bird, right?
The name's Dela Mochidis Gusting.
And yours, my lady?
Shiori.
Usagiyama  Market
Asagiri Shiori.
Shiori, eh?
'Tis a wonderful name.
Usagiyama  Market
We're here.
Shiori.
Would you care for some tea at my place as a token of my gratitude, please?
No, thanks. I'll take my leave—
We have some delicious cherry blossom mochi, too!
Cherry blossom mochi?
I said "my place," but in truth 'tis but a temporary abode.
It is a mochi shop.
A mochi shop?
Welcome!
Huh?
Oh, I thought you were Tamako.
This is Asagiri Shiori.
You go to the same school as Tamako, right?
Hello.
This is Shiori.
Pleased to meet you. Here.
Hey there, Mr. Bird.
My girl calls me Dela these days.
Well, good for you.
Hello.
Oh, my. Are you a friend of Tamako's?
Uh, um...
Nice to meet you.
Oh, right! Hold on a second.
Tasty, is it not?
Yeah.
I have returned.
Welcome ba—
Huh?!
Ah!
Asagiri?!
This kind and beautiful girl, Shiori, found me when I had lost my way and walked me home.
Really?
Hey! Stop dawdling and show her inside!
Oh, right!
It's all right.
I'll take my leave now.
Wait!
Try some of our cherry blossom mochi before you leave!
Don't throw it away!
Dela's seat
H-Here you go.
Thank you.
G-Go ahead!
All right.
Delicious, is it not?
It's great!
Thank goodness!
I'm so happy you came over!
I'm home!
Aw geez, even our house reeks of cherry blossoms!
Welcome back.
A friend of yours from school?
Yup. Asagiri—
This is Asagiri Shiori.
Hello.
Anyway...
I'll be leaving now.
While you're here, why not join us for dinner?
But...
Who's that from? Your beau?
No, my mother.
Your mother. I see.
Did something happen?
She said she'd be home late tonight.
Oh.
You should definitely stay for dinner, then!
Excuse me!
Sorry. I'll be right back.
Coming!
Where's Dad and Grandpa?
At a neighborhood meeting.
Wanna try some pudding too, Shiori?
Huh?
ma              ya
Thank you very much!
Tamako, what's for dinner?
Grilled fish and croquettes.
Again?!
Can I cook?
I don't know. Can you?
Probably!
Um...
Here it is! Spaghetti carbonara with minestrone!
Wow!
This is so fancy, it dazzles the eyes!
Looks tasty.
Sorry. We should be serving you.
No, it's fine.
I helped out too!
This carbonara is delicious!
It's not for you, Dela.
Huh?
Who was that?
My father.
Usa Bath
Apparently our bath's broken.
Welcome!
Oh wow, Shiori. Your hair's so pretty!
What shampoo do you use?
Shampoo?!
I'm jealous. Your skin's so smooth!
Would you like a second opinion?
Get out, Dela!
You should just stay the night.
She's right.
No, I...
Asagiri.
Dinner was great!
Thanks!
Ah...
Don't mention it.
Shall we go, Shiori?
I hope I wasn't a bother.
See you tomorrow!
Take care!
The night breeze is still a tad chilly.
Are you not cold, Shiori?
Northern               Turnstiles
Um... I'll be all right from here.
Is that so? Then please, take care.
Thank you very much.
There's no need for thanks.
The train's almost here, so I should go.
Rather, it'd be wonderful if the two of us could take another stroll beneath the cherry blossoms one day.
Don't you agree, Shio—
Northern               Turnstiles
Guess I'll go home.
Tamako Market
Good morning!
Back in business!
Morning!
Oh, Asagiri.
Good morning!
Thanks for yesterday.
Morning, Tamako.
Morning.
Did something happen with Asagiri?
Yup.
She cooked dinner for us last night,
and we went to the bathhouse together, but...
Oh, wow.
Maybe I was being a bit too friendly there.
It was fun.
Thanks for yesterday.
Thanks for yesterday! It was fun!
Er,
I'd like to set some times to meet your parents at home,
so circle the days that are convenient for you and turn them in.
By the way, my home's currently in a state of complete and utter...
harmony!
What are you doing here, Dela?
I have arrived with the spring.
What the heck?
Sorry for the trouble.
Um...
Grr! Don't get in my way, my girl!
C'mon, get outta here!
Um, thanks for—
Oh, I get it.
Everyone would be too distracted by my glorious presence to practice, eh?
Off you go. Come on.
I apologize for not taking that into consideration.
How you've come to that conclusion is beyond me.
Can't we just leave it the way it is, Dad?
You know we can't.
When one is in love, mere anticipation sets the heart aflutter, I see.
Eek!
Oh no, I fell asleep!
Are you okay?
Destiny!
I'm perfectly fi—
Actually, no.
Ow, ow, ow!
You're too kind, Shiori.
You're also graceful, elegant, and wonderful.
What's wrong?
I'm not...
I'm none of those things.
And you're so beautifully modest too.
Will you stop by again today?
No.
Why not try some tasty mugwort mochi—
I'll pass.
Why is that?
I still haven't thanked them for the other...
Mochidis Gusting.
Please pass this on to Kitashirakawa.
Tell her I said thanks for the other day!
Wouldn't it be better for you to tell her that in person?
In person...
That's why you should stop b—
Hey!
Asagiri!
Usagiyama  Market
Thanks.
I just moved here, and I'm terrible with maps.
Why, if it isn't Tamako's friend.
Oh, my. So you're Tamako's...
...teacher?
Thanks for taking care of her!
Is she being a good girl at school?
Please take care of our Midori too.
Want a croquette?
You can have one too.
Wow. It's like everyone in the market came out to say hello.
Oh, Mr. Yagi!
And...
Asagiri?!
Thank you for looking after my daughter!
Don't mention it!
Please help yourself to some of our mochi.
All right, then. Thank you.
I'm going out for a bit.
What?!
Behold.
These are my very best feathers.
This part, right here.
I'm off, Grandpa!
Take care, okay?
Thanks for waiting, Asagiri.
Sorry for causing you trouble again.
It really wasn't...
Um...
Well, I'll be—
Let us retire to somewhere quieter.
Care to unwind over hot coffee, Shiori?
Good idea.
What?!
You're coming too?!
In fact, it might be better if you stayed back.
Huh?
You've been following Asagiri around too much as it is, right?
Er...
Right.
What?
I'm off!
Stars and Clowns
Stars and
Clowns
1F - Records
2F - Records
Coffee
Here you are, Asagiri.
As thanks for the other day.
Huh?
It's just a little something from our store.
Thanks.
Asagiri...
If Dela or I start to get on your nerves at all,
please let us know, all right?
I'm sorry I just blurted that stuff out in class.
There are times when music speaks louder than words.
Ah, if only all words were like music.
From time to time,
I wish they were.
Bitter!
Ki—
Kitashirakawa.
Yes?
You know, I had a lot of fun.
Huh?
I had a lot of fun the other day!
Loads and loads of fun!
Asagiri.
I did too!
You know, whenever I was in the gym,
you guys always seemed to be having a lot of fun.
So I'm glad we're in the same class now.
Bitter.
It's really bitter, huh?
Well then...
We're friends now. That okay?
O-Okay!
Let's have fun together from now on.
Sure.
See you tomorrow!
There's no way I could've been bothering her...
Usagiyama Market
is there?
No, don't worry about all that!
There are countless girls who have fallen for me!
Mochidis Gusting.
Huh?
Thank you.
Thanks to you,
I was able to become friends with Kitashirakawa.
It was nothing. I figured you two needed someone to break the ice for you.
Really?
Thank you very much.
It's fine!
No need to feel indebted to me!
I shall let you have this.
It's a symbol of love for you, my—
Um, it's not like I play badminton because I love feathers.
Well, goodbye.
Wow. You're friends with Asagiri?!
Yup. I was worried I was bothering her, but now we're friends!
That's great.
Oh, that reminds me.
I saw Asagiri in the bathroom the other day. She was standing in front of the mirror repeating to herself,
"Thanks for yesterday. It was fun."
I had lots of fun.
Tamako?
It's nothing.
What's with you?!
Words are sometimes difficult.
Words are sometimes vexing.
Trying to get your feelings across can feel like a fruitless endeavor.
However, your words and feelings will reach them someday.
It's so good.
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
Tamako here.
They say it's best to eat cherry blossom mochi while looking over a river.
Apparently, the beauty of the riverside cherry blossom trees makes the mochi taste even better.
Episode 4   A Tiny Little Love Blooms
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?