What could this be?!
What could it be that boils within my chest?
It's...
love.
Love shall disappear!
Stop it, Daddy!
I think King Selfish stopped mid-punch for a second!
I heard a heartbeat of love!
King Selfish isn't completely taken over by darkness!
The king's heart is still within him!
Please, Lovely Pad, show us the king!
Father!
That is King Selfish's heart!
He's trapped inside it!
That's my real Daddy...
Okay!
We'll go save the king!
What?!
By saving him, you mean...
We'll be going inside King Selfish?
That's too crazy, even for you!
But I guess there's no stopping you.
Can it truly be done?
Sure can!
Who the heck do you think I am?
I'm Oogai First Middle School's Student Council President!
Aida Mana!
Huh?!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Hearts Racing at Max Speed!
Precures vs. King Selfish!
No way!
That girl's the Student Council President?!
No wonder they looked so alike!
You can do it, Mana!
I'm right behind ya!
I'm rootin' too!
Me too!
Prez, you can do it!
I doubt even the entire Yotsuba Conglomerate's influence could cover this up...
There's no need to.
Sir!
And Madam!
The Precures are risking their lives to save the world.
Let's all root for them.
You can do it, Precures!
Hey, you shout too!
R-Right!
You can do it, Precures!
Precures!
Do it!
Don't lose!
Those voices...
Doit, Pwecure!
What irritating voices!
They make my stomach turn!
Those voices are the people who wish for happiness.
The people who love their friends, family, and everything else in the world!
Oh poor king who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Silence!
I shall extinguish every last one of those voices!
Mana, please save Daddy!
Roger Wilco!
Selfish!
I am King Selfish's faithful servant.
We'll eliminate all who stand before King Selfish with no mercy!
Ira!
Selfish!
Sword Hurricane!
Self!
Self?
Gather!
Self!
Heart Dynamite!
Head over heels...
Regina!
Ace Mirror Flash!
You two!
What're you trying to pull?!
Oh, you still think you call the shots?
We put up with your whining because we considered you King Selfish's daughter,
but that's all over now!
Regina!
You shall not lay a finger on my friend!
Regina, are you all right?
Now let's move on!
Please, Ira!
Just let us through!
King Selfish is concentrated Egogy!
Do you have any idea what could happen to you if you went inside?
I do.
But Cure Heart said she'd go, so I have to follow.
Mana's my best friend, after all!
Friend?
Friends lend a hand when you need it most.
I'm sure you know what that's like.
You and your stupid "friends"!
Go ahead, see if I care!
To enter King Selfish's body,
we must go through his mouth.
I shall create an opening!
Rosetta Balloon!
A one, two, and three!
Laaaaaaaance!
Huh?!
What's goin' on?!
L-Lance turned into...
A-A-A giant!
Wha...
What a surprise!
He's still here!
You dare stand before me?
Very well, come!
Laaaaaaance!
Get him!
Use that right hook!
He can't reach!
Laaaaaaaance!
Look at that!
It's a beam!
Not!
Don't bite the ears!
Now is your chance!
Thanks, Rosetta!
Ai!
Ai wants to save Daddy too, right?
After them!
Diamond Swirkle!
It's the swallow's duty to help the Happy Prince.
I'll handle this, so go on ahead!
Got it!
The king is that way!
Self...
Selfish!
We'll send you to Davy Jones' Locker!
Baaaaah.
This place is swarming with Selfishes too?
It shows how thoroughly Egogy has corrupted Father!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
You won't be the ones that got away!
We can't have them following us along!
I'll hold them off here.
Girls, find the king as quickly as you can!
Don't worry.
I swear I'll catch up!
Cure Sword...
Now hurry!
Girls, let's go!
Don't ink you'll get away!
You shall not pass...
one step beyond me!
This is...
King Selfish's heart...
Father!
Daddy!
The Egogy is growing stronger!
Be careful!
Who are they?
We are King Selfish's cells.
We eliminate all foreign bacteria that enters King Selfish's body!
Hey, who are you calling bacteria?
Return my father!
Ha! No chance!
Well, her stick packs a punch!
You've got no hope!
Do you really think you can beat us inside King Selfish when he's already reached maximum Egogy?
Cure Diamond!
I'm... fine...
I can't let them get to Mana!
Rachel!
Comin' right up!
I'll fight to the bitter end with you, Rikka!
I'll show you our final attack!
Precure Diamond Blizzard!
Mana... it's all up to you.
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Love love looooove!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Laaaaaance!
The Lovely Pad can't withstand...
No,
the world is at stake!
We cannot...
afford to lose!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Laaaaaance!
Mana...
Father!
Please, open your eyes!
He can't hear you!
The king's lost his soul!
That's not true!
I heard a heartbeat of love from him!
I know the king still has his soul!
The king sacrificed his soul to cure his daughter and gave his psyche to darkness!
Call for him all you want, but he'll never open his eyes...
again!
Do not... harm... my family.
The King of Trump awakened?
What a joke.
If only you had never voiced your selfish desire to save your daughter,
the citizens of Trump Kingdom would still be living in peace!
You obsessed over your family in spite of having a kingdom to run,
making you the most selfish human in the world!
You sowed the seeds of your own destruction!
You're wrong.
What parent wouldn't want to save his child?
That's not selfish at all!
What?!
Families are pretty great.
No matter how down you get, they'll stand by you and make your heart race!
That's why I want to let Regina, Aguri, and Ai see their father one more time!
And as long as I'm still breathing,
I won't let anyone stop me!
Because I'm...
Oh, I can feel it!
Cure Heart's heartstrings are tied like a knot!
Because I'm brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Now's your chance to reach the king!
Right!
Family love, huh?
Don't make me laugh.
You think a king who brings his kingdom to ruin over a single girl deserves no punishment?!
Love is not a crime.
The true criminals are the ones who abused that love:
you!
Daddy!
Daddaa!
Father!
Ange...
K-King... Selfish just...
They... really pulled it off...
What in the world happened?
The Precures rekindled King Selfish's heart!
Unbelievable!
That gigantic creature completely disappeared right before our very eyes!
You've fulfilled the duty that you've carried since birth...
Splendid, Aguri.
Mana! C'mon, Mana!
Mana!
Daddy!
Mommy!
Grandpa too?
Ya did good.
Mana...
we saw everything.
Mana!
Thank you for keeping your promise.
Mana, I love you!
Regina!
Regi—
Prez!
Guys!
Thank goodness you're safe!
You're not injured or anything, right?
Aw, I'm fine!
Man, you had us freakin' out!
Sorry.
Oh no!
Fools...
No darkness disappears forever.
My dear King Selfish,
you achieved a truly magnificent form after your ten thousand year slumber.
But worry not.
I would be glad to carry on your legacy.
This makes me Numero Uno!
The human world, Trump Kingdom,
and every other world will become mine!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
I've met so many people in this world, so I swear I'll protect it!
Girls, let's go!
Right!
Dokidoki Precure's final episode:
From Me to You!
My Sweet Heart!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!