[YOUNG ED] The sun is male,
representing masculinity.
[YOUNG AL] The moon is female,
representing femininity.
[YOUNG ED] When the sun
and the moon overlap,
then the two genders become one.
[YOUNG AL] In other words,
the union represents
a perfect being.
So then what's a perfect being?
Does that mean immortality?
Hmm... Or maybe
something even greater.
[YOUNG AL] But what
could be greater than that?
[YOUNG ED] I don't know,
maybe... maybe god or something.
[FATHER] Join me!
Yes! I will no longer be bound
to you or your consequences!
I'll force you down to this
earth and into my bowels!
You have no choice
but to be absorbed!
[WIND BLOWS]
[IZUMI COUGHS]
Is everyone all right...?
What happened?
You have done well...
my faithful sacrifices.
You mean you
actually did it?!
[FATHER] Yes... I have done what
I set out to do... Acquire God.
Acquire God...?!
That isn't possible!
Unfortunately, it is...
Given a great enough
amount of energy.
Wait, what energy?
The Philosopher's Stone?!
[AL] It can't be!
Does this mean everyone
was turned into
a Philosopher's Stone?
How many lives
were sacrificed for this?
[ROY]
Amestris is a large country...
at least fifty million people.
Bastard!
[ENERGY EXPULSION]
[ED] Damn you!
[FATHER] Your alchemy
will do you no good.
[FATHER]
Farewell, gentlemen.
[HOHENHEIM] What
are you--...? What's that?
The power of God
is now in my control...
With that I can do anything--
for instance, I can create a sun
right in the palm of my hand.
[FATHER] Shall I turn its
flame loose in here...?
What do you think?
[POUNDING SOUND]
[HOHENHEIM] Your plan for
binding God to this world
was a flawed one...
We've plotted against you since
the moment you set it in motion.
[POUNDING SOUND]
[HOHENHEIM]
Over the many long years,
I have performed
calculation after calculation...
[HOHENHEIM] I have arranged my
own Philosopher's Stones--
the friends who
long resided within me--
in preparation
for this very day.
[VOICE 1] The time has come.
[VOICE 2] He is
guilty of committing
the ultimate transgression.
[VOICE 3] We no longer
have bodies to return to...
but the people of Amestris
still have the chance to
resume their physical forms.
[VOICE 4] Yes...
we know what we must do.
Let us return their souls
back to their bodies.
[VOICE 5] It is what
Hohenheim asked of us.
[POUNDING SOUND]
So you've planted
your Philosopher's Stones,
what of it...?
They are merely points...
They will not activate,
without a circle...
That's a basic rule of alchemy.
We do have a circle.
It's one of enormous power...
And it can be self-activated...
Even if something should
happen to incapacitate me.
[HOHENHEIM] The moon's shadow,
cast on the world
by the eclipse!
[VOICE 5]
We're starting now, Hohenheim.
Even now, you still think
you can stop me...?
You're a fool, Hohenheim!
[HOHENHEIM] That's the very
reason I came back...
It's time you
remembered your place...
Dwarf in the Flask!
[FATHER GRUNTS]
[FATHER SCREAMS]
[WAILS AND CRIES OF SOULS]
[BABY CRIES]
[PIANKO] Winry...
are you all right?
[WINRY]
What... was that?
Was it just me...
or did we all lose
consciousness?
Did you guys
black out as well?
[PINAKO]
So it would seem.
What in the hell
just happened...?
I don't know how to
describe it... It was like...
It was like being trapped...
imprisoned in
a vortex of anguish.
[ED] Did it work?
[HOHENHEIM] Yes...
The people of Amestris
have had their souls
returned to their own bodies.
[HOHENHEIM] And with
nothing more than the souls
of the Xerxesians he already
had, I doubt he can
continue to control
that which he calls God.
[FATHER] I can always
create another stone...
I am not through...!
There are more!
[FATHER] A billion humans
I can draw energy from!
[FATHER BELLOWS]
[AL] May!
Detecting and using
the power that flows
within the ground
is what we alkahestrists do...
What's more,
the greater the power
the other side has
that I can use becomes.
[MAY CHANG] Look out...!
Behind you!
[BLAST]
[GROUP STRUGGLES]
[HOHENHEIM] Damn...
I don't have what it takes
to fight his energy.
[MAY CHANG] Try as hard
as you can, sir...
I can't hold on much longer!
[HOHENHEIM]
It's no use.
[AL] Come on, Dad...
Hang on!
[ED] Can't you
even do this...?
Just stay focused!
[HOHENHEIM] I can only
do so much, boys...
I'm just a decrepit old man...
but I'll give it everything
these old bones can do!
[HOHENHEIM ROARS]
[AL] This has to end soon
or Dad's Philosopher's
Stone will burn out.
You done yet, Scar!?
[BRADLEY] Ishvalan!
I guess I was mistaken...
I thought the
science of alchemy...
was abhorrent in
the eyes of Ishvala,
the one you believe
to be the creator of all things.
[BRADLEY] Have you
abandoned your god?
[BRADLEY] You would
leave him... so easily?
[BRADLEY] Is your god so
readily lost to your people...?
Is he?!
[BRADLEY]
During the Ishvalan Civil War...
...when you were surrounded
by nothing but despair...
[BRADLEY] Surely somewhere
in the darkest
depths of your heart...
you began to believe
that there was no
god in this world at all.
[SCAR BELLOWS]
[BRADLEY CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
I myself have never
believed in faith or God...
If they exist...
perhaps this is their way
of divine justice
and providence.
[BRADLEY]
And it seems they
have sent a visitor
to do the deed.
[BRADLEY] Here to avenge
your grandfather...?
Very well. Go ahead.
Any last words
you'd like to say?
[BRADLEY]
None.
[LAN FAN]
Such a sad life...
Tell me, Bradley... was there...
anyone who you loved...?
Any friends...?
Your wife?
[BRADLEY] My wife?
[LAN FAN] Are you saying
you have nothing...?
No message for her...?
When she finds
out what you are...
Your trivial words of sorrow...
of love, and guilt mean
nothing to me, young lady.
My wife understands...
she is the woman that
I chose to live by my side...
There are no more "words" that
need to pass between us now.
[BRADLEY] That's what it means
to be the wife of the Fuhrer.
[BRADLEY CHUCKLES]
[BRADLEY] And now you've
spent all your time asking
useless questions and lost your
opportunity for vengeance...
What a shame.
[BRADLEY] I lived my life
by forever following the path
that had been set for me.
Thanks to the
idiosyncrasies of humanity...
it was... at least...
a life worth living for...
and maybe even
a life worth dying for.
I sense something.
[SCAR]
A Philosopher's Stone.
This...?
[SCAR COUGHS]
[LAN FAN]
Are you all right?
[SCAR] I need you
to take me over there.
[LAN FAN] But the
circle's been broken.
[SCAR] I know...!
But over there is--...
The center.
[LAN FAN]
Very well.
[SCAR]
Brother...
I cannot lie...
The hatred within me
has not perished...
and yet I am about
to help Amestris...
the very object of my hatred.
[SCAR] You spoke
of positive streams
and negative streams...
Thanks to the life I have lived,
I carry both within me.
[SCAR] I wonder which
way I will flow.
[HOHENHEIM]
It's coming!
[MULTIPLE BLASTS OF ENERGY]
[ED]
How do you like that...?
Your little throne
has been reduced to rubble.
Now I think it's time
someone put an end
So I am gonna take you down,
and the 'truth' along with you!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
What was that...?
Did you use alkahestry?
[SCAR] No,
it's something else...
something my brother developed.
My brother researched
the science of alchemy...
From there, his interests
led him to begin looking
into the art of
alkahestry as well.
[SCAR] Alkahestry is
an art that uses the
flow chi through the ground.
[SCAR] In contrast,
this country's alchemy
uses tectonic energy...
However... my brother
realized something...
Alchemists weren't able to use
their power to its full measure.
[SCAR] There was an
inhibiting component interfering
with the connection between
the alchemist and that energy.
I sensed that when
I came to this country...
Like... like a mass of people
crawling beneath the earth.
[SCAR] That's right...
The sensation you felt was
the enormous Philosopher's Stone
that stretches underground
throughout this land.
How do you like this, huh?!
Is it really true?
[MAY CHANG] You made a circle
that returned everyone's souls?
[HOHENHEIM] That's right...
And it worked perfectly...
After that, Scar created
a reverse circle...
It will correct the corrupted
alchemy of this country.
It was Scar's brother...
Through tireless research...
he discovered
a secret long kept...
[HOHENHEIM] The existence of the
nationwide transmutation circle.
[HOHENHEIM]
Using that as a base,
he applied his
knowledge of alkahestry
and developed what
is known as a
reverse transmutation circle...
This circle would render the
Philosopher's Stone of Amestris
ineffective, thus enabling the
alchemists here to once again
harness tectonic energy
to its fullest extent.
[AL SHOUTS]
[HOHENHEIM] Keep it
coming with all you've got...
Make him use
his Philosopher's Stone.
[HOHENHEIM]
He'll run out of energy.
Yeah, and when
will that be?
I'm not sure...
but we have to keep on trying.
[IZUMI]
Here, take this!
The sweet memories...
That's exactly the
tub I took a bath in...
Now it's your turn, Daddy.
Get outta the way, Greed!
[BRIBIE]
Hold it!
Don't move...!
We've got you.
[ARMSTRONG]
Lieutenant Hawkeye?
Major Armstrong.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 2]
W-What the...?
That bastard...
He's going to try to make
another Philosopher's stone.
Go after him!
[AL] Right!
Let's move you...
Someplace safe.
I'm sorry... I didn't
expect to be so useless.
[AL] Brother!
[ED] Al...!
Go on ahead.
[ED] Seems our friend here
still wants me to stick around.
Come on Al, let's go...
Don't let that thing
beat you, Ed!
Right!
[IZUMI]
Darling!
[SIG] Izumi!
This is no time
for happy reunions...
Look after Mustang.
[SIG] Right.
[HAWKEYE] Colonel!
We still have some
business we need
to finish up above...
We'll be seeing you.
[HAWKEYE] Colonel,
are you injured?
What's wrong?
[ROY] My sight is gone.
[ROY] Lieutenant...
how are your injuries?
Don't think about me...
Just worry about
yourself for once...
Your eyes...
Lieutenant...
can you still fight?
Yes, sir!
Young Lord!
The name's Greed now...
jeez I can't believe you
bothered to tag along
all the way down here.
That's Wrath!
I see...
So they finally got 'im.
[GREED] Bastard dies with that
peaceful look on his face...
Pisses me off.
[PRIDE]
Damn you Greed...
Have you forgotten that you're
one of the Homunculi...?
Where's your honor?
[ED] So he should just
be a good boy like you
and do everything his
father tells him, is that it?
[PRIDE] Do you need to ask
such a ridiculous question...?
It's only natural that we
should want to obey our father,
no matter the order.
You're the one
who's ridiculous.
[ED] Only natural, huh?
So it's natural to be a
brainwashed punk who doesn't
even try to think for himself?!
Explain it to me...
Why are you so eager
to be his willing lapdog?
[ED] He's wearing you
ragged, breaking you down...
and he doesn't even care.
Why should I care
if Father doesn't...?
I'm not a puny
weakling like you are...
I am one of the Homunculi!
What do you know, human?!
[ED CRIES OUT]
This container
won't last much longer...
But still...
like my father is...
you are of
Hohenheim's bloodline...
so we're virtually brothers.
Which means, Edward Elric...
I can use your container...
Your body belongs to me!
What--?!
[WAILING SOULS]
[KIMBLEE]
You can't have it, Pride.
I won't let you
take this body...
It's not a good
fit for a Homunculus.
[PRIDE] Kimblee...!
There's no way...!
How could you maintain
your individuality among
this tempest of souls...?!
It's just not possible!
[KIMBLEE] You call
this a tempest...?
Oh, stop. You're going
to make me laugh...
The bitterness
that all of these
voices contain soothes
me... like a lullaby.
[PRIDE] Why are you
interfering...?
Kimblee, why?!
[KIMBLEE] Not by choice...
I was perfectly content,
but when you decided
to throw away your honor
as a Homunculus,
you forced me to step in.
[KIMBLEE] You speak of
your precious pride,
that quality for
which you were named.
But then suddenly you find
yourself in grave danger...
and you seek to escape
into the body of a human,
the lower life form
that you so despise...
It's Pathetic.
[KIMBLEE]
You're a disgrace.
[ED YELLS]
[PRIDE]
He'll kill me!
[KIMBLEE] If you think that,
then you still don't
understand Edward Elric.
[ED]
Selim!!
Impossible...!
He's turned himself
into a Philosopher's Stone
and now he's forcing
his way inside me?!
I've caught you... You are mine!
[PRIDE] Stop this.
[PRIDE] Stop this!
[PRIDE] Please stop!!
[ED] So this
is your real body.
[ED] Once this is all over,
I'm going to have to
apologize to Mrs. Bradley.
You can wait right there...
You foolish boy.
[SELIM] Mama... Mama...
[NARRATOR]
The strong arm reaches out...
The flame gushes
forth with a fiery roar...
With all lives at stake...
the people prepare
to give everything they
have to the fight...
The final battle has arrived.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 62:
"A Fierce Counterattack"
If one wishes
to obtain something,
something of
equal value must be given.