Where should I go?
I don't even know where I came from.
I don't have any memories.
How can I become free?
A freedom I can attain through murder...
What is it?
Smile.
Please smile, Elen.
Just give it to the police.
I'm counting on you.
Wait!
I'll be killed if I don't run.
I can't escape from those black eyes.
If you don't want to die...
...come at me with all you've got!
You were born with a talent.
A talent to kill people.
A talent to survive.
A talent for being an assassin.
You have to be reborn if you want to live.
Your existence is only allowed as long as you kill people.
What is the path that we must walk?
Being a tool.
Being an instrument.
We just need to function.
We can't think about anything unnecessary.
"I'll erase an inexperienced young man's memories and make him an assassin."
I agreed to Scythe's reckless plan.
Because it was necessary...
The power of Phantom.
Phantom. Inferno's ultimate assassin.
The title given to the best sniper in the organization.
My masterpiece...
Ein.
And Zwei.
He too.
But in the end I'm just being used by the organization.
Both Phantom and I have no other choice but to live like slaves.
We indeed have that in common.
But we're not slaves.
Even you have your freedom.
It's speed.
Speed?
Even if the course is predetermined,
as long as you wish and put in effort,
you can accelerate your speed.
You might even stand at the top of the organization.
You're free to decide how you'll go.
Say, Lizzie.
Would you comply with any order?
I won't work under someone I wouldn't follow.
That sounds like you.
Hey, Clau.
What?
I've been meaning to apologize for some time now.
Four years ago, I wholeheartedly joined your organization but wasn't of any use.
Your organization was crushed by Wisemel,
and even Romero was...
Back then, if I had been...
It's all in the past now.
The weak will be assimilated by the strong.
That's how nature works.
That's why I've joined Inferno.
Clau...
One day I just have to get back what I lost
and what was taken away from me...
I want you to do another job for me in Los Angeles soon.
You want to do an unexpected job,
to make the higher-ups owe you one?
Yes.
That's why we need to do this in a clandestine manner.
I'm not personally against such plotting.
He's no longer necessary to me.
I'll take Zwei...
Phantom...
It can't be...
Yes. This is your passport.
The real you... your past is written in it.
Try reading your name.
Azuma...
Reiji.
Right... I was on a trip.
And then...
Hello? This is the Azuma residence.
Hello?
There's no way I could go back there.
Which organization are they from?!
Phantom?!
Damn you, Scythe!
You idiot!
Why are you shooting your allies?!
This might be Scythe's order but stop acting like a puppet!
You can't escape!
Think about this.
Ein!
I have to do it.
Ein, I'm the only one who can protect you.
I won't forsake you.
I definitely won't hand you over to the organization.
Let's escape together...
From this city...
From Inferno.
Why are you so concerned about me?
You won't benefit from this in any way.
I don't want to let you die.
I don't want to leave you to your death.
This isn't for anyone.
I'm doing this on my own will.
You need a new name.
A name?
Not Phantom nor a number.
A name for you to live as yourself.
Elen. Your name is Elen.
From now on I'll call you Elen.
Why Elen?
Do you need a reason?
I've decided that.
A name to live as yourself. Not as a puppet or an assassin.
Elen.
Elen... It sounds kind of strange.
Let's look for your lost past, Elen.
Together with me.
That isn't like you, Ein.
Overcome your pain with your will.
Master.
She went back to Scythe.
No way.
Idiot. You assisted the traitor.
You're a suspect now.
You cannot return to Japan anymore.
But you still have an ideal choice left.
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back.
What is that?
You know how to use this, don't you?
I'll kill Scythe.
Scythe!
Reiji...
That's an interesting outcome.
How appropriate for the finale.
During the past three months,
we've successfully taken over one of the important organizations that control the east,
the Renato Family of Boston, as well as the Baldini Clan of Philadelphia.
We've also started negotiations with our rivals about them joining us.
Our policy won't change.
We'll give a backhand to those who play tough against us,
and death to those who dare to strike back.
Creation and destruction.
This country will change...
To our era... The era of Inferno.
Is it okay to leave everything to her?
She's doing an excellent job.
Her existence is vital to Inferno,
which needs a little rest from its expansion.
Besides...
...you have your subordinates called "Bloodies."
And I have you.
Because she doesn't have any backing,
she's unaffected by any interest conflicts.
She has Phantom.
Phantom is indeed very skilled.
But the organization won't bow down to Phantom alone.
Just as we saw with Scythe Master three months ago.
There's no mistake.
He's such a fool.
Now that he's lost Phantom...
He has no value.
Sorry for making you wait, Mr Giuseppe.
If Claudia should get arrogant, and repeat the same mistake,
we'll just dispose of her.
You can drive a bit longer.
Come back in about an hour.
Do you think this is too good to be true?
Ms McCunnen, I fail to see...
...what you would gain by offering such favorable terms to us.
I want the Godoh Group to owe me a favor.
Someone with a strong sense of duty like you would owe me a favor. That's all.
So you want someone to back you up?
Right.
I'll give you these 200 million dollars.
But I'll gain something even more valuable than that.
It certainly makes business sense.
We'll inform you later regarding the profit.
We'll win big.
It means we'll have a big debt to owe then.
This is the true beginning.
Right, Romero?
No way... Taking so many men alone...
Who is he?!
Zwei, I acknowledge your loyalty and contribution,
and bestow the title that you're worthy of.
I approve thy succession.
From now on, you'll stand at the top,
and live that name in the underground world.
Accompanied with fear.
Phantom.
From this moment, you are Inferno's Phantom.
I will obtain everything.
You're necessary for that.
Reiji, my Phantom.
Okay, Reiji.
From now on, the two of us are partners.