ToraDora! 10 Tl by KloneDesu
It's morning?
Yeah...
We couldn't sleep after all...
After something like that...
What are we going to do?
Today was our "Scare Minorin and Knight to the Rescue" plan.
Can we really scare Kushieda when we're this scared ourselves?
Oh shut up.
If we don't do it, we can't change the future.
Well yeah, but...
What should we do?
Something that Minorin would be afraid of...
What's something that Kushieda would be afraid of?
Ki—!
Y-You're early Kitamura.
What are you two plotting from early in the morning?
We're not plotting anything.
Could it be that...
Are you two responsible that fuss with Kushieda yesterday?
I thought so...
Sheesh.
Why would you do something like that?
Don't you feel sorry for Kushieda?
W-Well that's—
I-It's a present.
A present?
Minori actually likes horror stuff... more than her three-meals-a-day.
I wanted to give her a good summer time since she said she loved being frightened.
Hey, Kitamura.
I see.
That explains why Kushieda's eyes were glowing so brightly even though she was acting that scared.
Alright, count me in!
Let's work together and really scare the pants off of her!
Er... Um...
I know, I'll get Ami, too.
The stupid Chi, too?
She's pretty knowledgeable about the area around here.
Alright, let's start moving.
But I don't think Kawashima's going to do it.
Leave it to me; I'll convince her without avail!
Don't worry!
W-What are we going to do Ryuuji?
What are we...
There isn't much we can do is there?
Seaweed.
Oh my-my, I was planning on making breakfast...
Good morning Takasu-kun.
Y-Yeah.
Hmm, What are you making?
Oh, lunch.
Everyone said that we were going to spend the whole day at the beach.
You woke up earlier to prepare for it?
That won't do.
Chef Kushieda will lend you a hand!
Please, please, give me your demands.
R-Right.
Will you slice the onions then?
Right oni-slice, with pleasure.
What's the menu?
Egg Sandwich and Tuna Sandwich.
Also some potage made with left over curry, I think.
Good, that sounds good!
You move your hands pretty good Kushieda.
Oh, did you just compliment me?
Yay.
Also consider the dish washing from yesterday, you're at quite a high level.
Both my parents work at home, so I made my little brother his lunch while he was still living with us.
You have a little brother?
He's a strapping high school boy, Akechi-kun.
It stings!
Hey, are you okay?
I messed up.
Takasu-kun?
Oh yeah, I have to peel the apples.
You really are good at cooking Takasu-kun.
Yesterday's curry was awesome, too.
I didn't do anything so amazing.
I think those parts about you are really wonderful.
The girls at school don't know this side of you do they?
I might be going a bit over, but your future bride will be very happy.
Kushieda!
Whyat yis yit, Takyasu-kyun?
A-About yesterday...
About that...
Don't tell anyone okay?
I've never talked to anyone about something like that.
How do I put it...?
I let my guard down.
It was a slip of the tongue.
But I'm glad that you were the one that I was talking to.
Thanks for listening to me.
Uh-oh!
You klutz, you're so darn cute!
D-Don't say cute!
Just kidding!
More importantly Chef, what shall I do next?
Hm, let's see—
Should I stir it, should I stir the crap out of it?
Today's sun rays are strong, too!
Komachi-Angel!
Minorin's full of energy...
Well then, the rest will go as planned.
Huh, what about Kawashima?
She's going to help us right?
It's been decided that I'll set some traps at a nearby cave with Ami as a guide.
Then we can't get anything done without her.
What is she doing?
Don't know.
I'm going to go get her real quick.
Taiga, hold this for a sec.
H-Hey!
Here, I'll hold it for you.
Isn't it heavy for a girl?
N-No thanks.
I'm fine.
Kawashima, are you there?
I'm here.
Everyone went ahead you know.
Sheesh, what are d—o?!
I was being entranced by myself.
Do you want to look, too?
You're so...
Hey-hey, isn't this amazing?
What do you think of this cleavage?
Guess it's alright.
That's all?
Oh yeah, you already saw me in a bikini at school.
That's not it.
But this comes off you know.
See.
Put it on, put it back on!
What~? Then you put it on.
I refuse!
You're so cold.
If you're going to act like that; I'm not cooperating with you.
Wha—d-don't say that.
Hey.
Why do you want to help Minori have fun?
W-Why?
If you're not going to tell me, I'm not going to help you.
You have five seconds, okay?
Five,
Four,
Three.
Are you sure?
Two,
One,
Zero.
No cooperation.
Taiga!
Bring it on! Come on, with force!
Like ba-bam!
It's cold!
What in the world are they doing?
Come on, why?
'Cause, I feel kind of tired.
We won't know anything about the cave without you.
I wrote a map didn't I?
I'm sorry, but you can work hard by yourself.
Hey...
No complaints right?
It was your choice after all.
Sorry Takasu, Ami just suddenly...
That's okay, I'll go with you.
Wouldn't it be a big burden by yourself?
But if both of us left, they might get suspicious.
Don't worry, I'll do it by myself, somehow.
I've thought of three traps that are worthy of awards.
Kushieda's going to go crazy from fear without a doubt!
I-Is that so?
Hey, Kushieda, Aisaka.
What is it?
I'm going to use the toilet!
Wow, it's good! Takasu-kun, you're a genius at cooking!
Well, you helped me, too.
Huh, Minorin did?
Right-o!
I mixed the crap outta the eggs in that egg sandwich!
Eating lunch while I'm gone?
Sheesh Kitamura-kun!
What's with you?
Shouting out your potty announcement to us girls.
Oh, sorry.
And you took way too long. Where in the world did you go—
The preparations are complete.
R-Right.
What, what.
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, Kushieda, we're actually—
Hey, Minori-chan.
There's a really beautiful cave by the inlet.
A cave?!
It's one of my special places.
It's special?!
You want to take a walk there later?
A walk?!
That sounds great! Let's go, let's go!
I can't wait!
Oopsy-daisy.
Oh, is this it?
Amin's special—
Walking ground...
It's got quite an atmosphere...
Doesn't it?
Alright, let's go inside!
B-But it looks like something would be in there.
Oh, we might meet an unidentified creature!
No, its fine as along as it's among the living...
Right, we have to capture it alive!
I'm really getting into the mood!
I guess we were right for bringing him into our plans.
His slick talking is so cool.
Alright, let's go Kitamura Exploration Team!
We'll find the two-headed golden cobra!
It's dark, it's cramped, and it's scary!
Sound's like something I've heard before.
It's more spacious than I expected.
This area is.
Hey, stay focused.
We're not here for a simple courage test.
You understand?!
Y-Yeah.
It's going to get one step lower up ahead so watch out.
And now the first barrier.
What is it?
Something deep-fried...
That's right, Kitamura's really intelligent, but—
He's an idiot, too...
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun.
Hey, isn't it kind of cold?
It's because we're deep inside.
That's not what I'm talking about.
What's wrong?
I smell ketchup.
Hey, what are you doing?
This is...
Blood... writing?
It says, gyaaaa...
This is the second one?
He's definitely an idiot.
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun.
Stop sighing!
Huh, what the—
This is...
Hey, what's wrong?!
Ta-Ta-Ta-Ta-Takasu-kun!
T-That's—!
Oh-um—
It's a woman's hair!
It's the curse of a woman who broke her heart and died of unnatural causes when she wandered into this cave while looking for a place to die!
Let me out! Let me outta here!
Minorin, calm down.
Nice assistance, Takasu.
You set up some stuff, too, huh?
No-I—
My last trap is 50 meters ahead of here.
You can keep your hopes up.
R-Right.
Come on Kushieda.
Hold yourself together.
Kitamura-kun is capable after all.
Minorin was really scared.
It wasn't Kitamura.
Wha—?
Of course it wasn't me either.
T-Then—
It's not made up.
It's the same as last night.
It's real.
One, two, three, four—
Minorin!
It's dangerous by yourself so let's hold hands.
Really?!
Let's hold them! Let's hold them like crazy!
Alright!
Now that our bodies are warmed up, let's move forward!
Uh-Um—
Oh man, this is ridiculous.
I'm going to use a shortcut to get home early.
H-Hey, Kawashima, where are you going?!
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun, are we still going further?
The exit is this way, right Ami?
Where's Ami and Takasu?
Ryuuji?
Wait up Kawashima!
Do you really know where you're going?
Of course I do.
Are you that worried that you're separated from everyone?
I-I'm not very good... with dark places and stuff.
Then—what would you do if I left you behind?
Would you be scared?
Would it make you uneasy to be separated from me?
Would you be lonely?
Would you think that you wouldn't want to be away from me?
H-Hey.
Do you need me?
N-Now's not the time for this.
Do you want to hurry and go back to Minori-chan?
I already told—!
I don't think she would be a good match for you.
Wha-I-I-don't really...
Someone who would match you is—
What?
Huh?
Wha—?
Where am I?
No way, we're lost!
Hey-Hey, you've got to be kidding.
I wouldn't joke about something like this!
W-What should I do?
H-Hey.
Y-You'll be okay.
I'm sure Kitamura will come looking for us.
Don't be scared.
I'm here for you.
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to apologize.
That thing about being lost, that was a lie.
You really thought I would get lost?
Silly-little-boy.
Ow, ow.
Stop Takasu-kun, it's so sticky.
Now's not the time to laugh!
But you're like a little brat.
I was scared for real you know!
Takasu-kun, you're pretty useless aren't you?
There you go again and—
But I don't dislike that part of you.
I said earlier that you wouldn't match Minori-chan right?
I was serious about that.
Because you're like the moon.
What the heck?
Minori-chan is like the sun.
If you stay by her, you'll just get burnt away and vanish.
I mean, you would never be able to hit Minori-chan right?
You can't be on equal footing with just idolization.
You can only be equal with some one like m—
That was—
Kushieda's voice!
Wait, Takasu-kun!
Sorry—I...
It's alright.
Let's hurry.
Right!
Kushieda!
Ryuuji!
Takasu! Ami!
You guys were alright?
Kitamura, where's Kushieda?!
What happened?
Well you see...
Something got Kushieda...
Something? What was it?
I don't know.
But something is there.
Don't tell me Kushieda was...
It ran out of battery.
Takasu, lend me yours.
Right.
What's that sound?
Is it a voice?
Kushieda! I'm coming!
H-Hey, Kitamura!
K-Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun, Kitamura-kun, Kitamura-kun!
What the hell is going on?!
E-Everyone, stay together.
Let's start by calming down.
I don't care what it is...
All that's left is... for me to get him!
Wha—Taiga?!
Tai—
Kitamura-kun, an accident has occurred.
We must rescue Taiga!
Roger.
Are you okay Aisaka?
Kita-Kitamura-kun.
Kitamura?!
You're quite late, Akechi-kun.
Ku-Kushieda?
Yes, I am no other than Kushieda Minori.
A.K.A. Minorin.
I'm the culprit!
And the accomplice was this fella!
The hair in Takasu's room.
The messy clothes in Taiga's room.
That and all else was all done by us!
We're really sorry.
It's just that your methods of frightening me were way too weak.
It made me want to teach you guys the right way to scare people.
Does that mean you knew all along?
Yeah, since you guys were being so secretive together.
That's why I brought Kitamura-kun over to my side and made a counterattack.
But it was a lot of fun.
Thanks.
You're not going to get mad?
'Course not, I love horror after all.
Wha—?!
I acted afraid to lure you guys.
If you say you're afraid of horror or the occult, someone would eventually try to scare you.
I just deliciously enjoyed your attempts to scare me.
Well, now that we're done with the spoilers—
It lit up!
Isn't it beautiful?
Today was quite the day wasn't it?
Yeah, what a nuisance.
What you said earlier.
I didn't give you a proper answer.
Huh?
I would get lonely if you weren't around.
Actually, it's not a matter of whether I would get lonely or not.
It's whether you are or aren't lonely.
I've never even given thought to if I was lonely or not.
Then think about it.
Isn't that painful?
If it's painful, you should come out and show it.
Because we are-um—
On equal footing?
Hey.
Takasu-kun, you're—
kind sometimes.
What's wrong Takasu-kun?
It's the final night.
Are you having fun?
Kushieda.
Um, You know...
T-Thanks.
Huh?
I was totally tricked and scared for real, but—
It's fun being around you.
At any moment.
That's what I should be saying.
I really had fun, too.
And the curry was delicious.
You listened to me talking about strange things without laughing.
You were able to understand.
I'm really sorry for scaring you.
I went on my bad side when I wanted to show you a ghost.
Show me?
Yeah.
You said that you wanted to see a ghost.
Wha—?
Oh.
Why did you want to scare me Takasu-kun?
Huh? T-That's because…
Taiga told me that you didn't like horror stuff.
So you wanted to tease me?
Nope.
You would never do something to others that they don't like.
You're someone that's always thinking about making others happy.
Then why would you do such a thing?
I really want to know the reason.
I'm really full of wonder about it.
I wanted to show you a ghost.
I wanted you to believe that ghosts were real.
You shouldn't give up, just because you can't see them.
That's what I thought.
I see!
Takasu-kun, wanna look for a UFO next?
Not a satellite, but a real one.
Huh?
After a UFO, I would want to look for… a Tsuchinoko!
TL Note: A Tsuchinoko is a fabled creature in Japan, they look like snakes but they live in the ground.
If I kept finding things I want like that...
If I made changes to the world I lived in...
Then I—
Kushieda!
It exploded. A UFO...
It's like a dream.
I really saw one!
Are we repelling a galactic war?!
We're going to protect the earth!
It's still part of the trip until we reach our houses.
Don't let your guard down everyone.
Maybe I should just go to my parents' house.
See ya' later!
Want to shop at the supermarket on the way home?
I'm tired, don't talk to me about your housewife duties.
Alright, alright.
Hey, there's a special bargain sale today.
I told you to shut up...
The culture festival.
Raise your spirits with the band's music.
Get your heart fluttering at the cos-play café.
Warm up your friendship at the campfire.
Get crotch-locked at the pro-wrestling show!
What in the world are you plotting...?