Oh no! Mitsuki's pendant
has been stolen!
Gosh, I know you're excited about
seeing Eichi, but you can't be so careless!
Thanks to the stupidity of the thieves,
we ended up getting back the pendant.
Takuto... The thing you said to Mitsuki...
Did you really mean it?
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Takuto!
A-All right.
I'll give it back, so forgive me!
Here you go!
Damn it!
Takuto!
What an idiot.
What do I do?
Takuto is... Takuto is...
What're you crying for,
you little loser?
You're so stupid, Takuto!
Takuto?
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
What's that for?!
Aren't you happy?!
I am happy! But why did you
do such a reckless thing?!
Takuto?
Why? Why do you always act so tough?
You did such a dangerous thing!
Oh, enough, enough!
Answer me, Takuto!
Why should I, you little loser?
What did you say?!
Takuto!
I-It's... It's because I like you,
of course!
Takuto...
I like you too!
I like you a lot Takuto!
Mitsuki?
Because you're such
a precious friend of mine!
Huh?
That's why it's only natural that I worry when
you do something as reckless as that!
Don't ever do it again!
Th-That's not it!
What?
Takuto?
That's right!
We're your friends!
Yup!
Miss?
Are you all right?
Yes! Oh, and we found
the pendant we were looking for!
That's good.
By the way, I don't see your friend,
but where did he go?
Takuto said he was hungry,
and he went ahead.
Mitsuki!
Ms. Oshige, Dr. Wakaoji!
Mitsuki, are you all right?!
Are you okay?
You didn't get hurt, did you?
No, I'm all right.
We were really worried!
Don't do anything like this
ever again, okay?
I'll need more than one heart if I'm
gonna be this close to a heart attack!
I'm sorry, but I really wanted
to get this pendant back.
I know. It's from Eichi, isn't it?
But please don't ever do
anything like this again.
Got that?
Yes!
Takuto...
We had originally planned to stop by
yesterday, but it should be all right.
How close are we?
We're almost there.
Isn't it pretty?
The temperature is a lot different from
Eagle Valley, so you need to be careful.
I will!
We're finally here.
Eichi, I'm so close
to you right now.
So Takuto really
does like Mitsuki.
According to my notes, the person
who found a family for Eichi lives here.
I wonder if they're out.
No one seems to be here.
What?! We're only one day late.
Why?
No way...
It's all right. Why don't we
just find Eichi on our own?
Yeah! We've come
this close to finding Eichi.
Keep your head up!
Yes!
Hey, shouldn't we look
for him with them?
I'm tired!
Then why don't we go to that lake
we saw earlier? It was really pretty!
I don't wanna go.
Oh, then let's have
lunch or something.
I don't wanna eat.
Then...
Just leave me alone!
So Takuto laughed and played it off earlier,
but were those Takuto's true feelings?
It's because I like you,
of course!
No way! There's no way!
That can't be the case!
Because if it is,
that would mean...
Unrequited love for sure?!
N-No!
I can't think negatively!
Even if his confession
were true,
Takuto may have totally
given up after being rejected!
Meroko? What're you doing?
I've been watching you for a while,
but are you practicing your funny faces?
You really look like you're
having fun. I'm envious.
Wh-Whose fault do you think...
Huh?
You should talk. You know, nothing gets
done when you mope around.
Just because you got rejected.
H-Hey, Takuto, calm down.
I didn't see anything.
And I didn't hear anything either.
Yeah! You're totally right.
There's no use in thinking about it like this.
Instead of thinking
about what'll happen
when she sees Eichi
and getting depressed,
I should watch them seeing each other
to break my attachment.
You sometimes have good advice.
No way! Did he understand
a little bit of my feelings?
Takuto...
So, I'm gonna go!
Huh?
Takuto? Gosh!
He has no idea how I feel!
Hey, come on!
Wait, Takuto!
I said, wait!
This beats me.
I thought we'd find him easily
after coming all the way here.
But it's strange.
I wonder why we can't we find him?
Maybe it's not this town?
Ms. Oshige!
S-Sorry, Mitsuki,
I didn't mean to bring you down.
Yeah, I know.
One cappuccino and...
so what are you having?
Let me see...
E-Excuse me!
Excuse me, are you Japanese?
Huh? Yes, we are.
I-If so...
The boy in this photograph...
Oh, I'm sure he's bigger now,
but his name is Eichi Sakurai.
Do you know him?
I want to see him!
I've come from Japan to see Eichi!
Oh, no. We don't know.
I wonder what's with that girl.
Just because we're Japanese?
To be asked out of the blue like that...
Oh, there they are!
Huh?
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki! Mitsuki!
How is she, Dr. Wakaoji?
Well, it seems her fever
has gone down.
If she rests tonight,
there shouldn't be any problems.
We've suddenly come to a cold place,
and on top of that,
we searched around for Eichi, so her fatigue
has probably caught up with her.
So it's not that her throat
has gotten worse?
That's not the case.
Oh, thank goodness!
It's not good to worry so much.
Okay.
And you won't get better
on an empty stomach.
I'll go pick up something to eat.
Stay in bed now!
Yes.
Eichi, where are you?
I want to see you
as soon as possible.
Mitsuki, I've wanted
to see you too.
Eichi...
I like you.
It's because...
It's because I like you,
of course!
Why did you appear
in my thoughts, Takuto?
Jeez!
It's because you said that
so unexpectedly.
I like you too!
I like you a lot, Takuto!
I told him I liked him too.
Could it be that I can't find Eichi
because I said that to Takuto?
But, you're the only one I like, Eichi.
I can't see the stars or the moon.
It's only a little while before
I go back to Japan.
If I don't find Eichi...
She's really an easy girl
to figure out, isn't she?
Her heart is filled with
thoughts of Eichi.
So give it up, Takuto.
She's...
Hey!
You've gotta stay in bed!
But the sky looked
overcast from inside.
It's no different from out here!
But it made me feel like
I wouldn't see Eichi.
Just go back!
I don't want to!
I won't go back until
I can see the stars!
Enough already!
That's right! Keep arguing.
Get really upset at each other.
That way even Takuto
will give up completely.
But...
Don't give me that!
What if you catch a cold
and get stuck in bed?!
You won't be able to
look for Eichi!
But if I can't see
the stars and the moon,
I feel like I won't be
able to find Eichi either.
Huh?
To not be able to see even
a single one today of all days...
It's almost as if I'm being told
Eichi's not here.
No.
Maybe it's that Eichi
doesn't want to see me.
And that's why he's hiding
so he won't be found.
If so...
What are you saying?!
Meroko...
It's not like you to get
so discouraged!
But...
You believed in Eichi so much!
I bet Eichi still thinks about you!
You think so?
Yes!
How could you stop
believing in him?
Snow...
Huh?
It's as though the stars
are falling from the sky.
I do want to see Eichi!
That's the reason I came this far.
To tell him that I like him.
Mitsuki...
Takuto, Meroko, thank you.
I'll be all right.
I won't get depressed anymore
while we search for Eichi.
So your spirits are back up again.
If you stay here, you'll catch a cold
so let's go back to your room.
Okay.
Sorry, Takuto,
for persisting like that.
That's all right.
Did I do it again?!
Even though, at first, I was thinking
it'd be great if they got in a fight.
Hello?
Oh! Ms. Kazumi?!
What?!
Oh, yes! I understand!
Ms. Oshige?
Mitsuki! Get ready right away!
We might be able to see Eichi today!
Oh, Ms. Oshige, calm down.
You should drive a little slower.
Ms. Oshige! Faster!
Leave it to me!
Th-This is scary!
Now!
Okay!
Japan Festival?
Apparently the local Japanese club
holds this event once a year for everyone.
And the person that Ms. Kazumi
told us about apparently volunteers here.
Huh?
Yes, that would be me.
I'm so glad!
Well, Kazumi Franklin told us
to come see you.
Oh... So it was you guys!
I had heard you were arriving
the day before yesterday,
but you didn't come so was
wondering what happened.
- Umm...
- Yes?
The Sakurais...
Where do the Sakurais live?
Oh, the Sakurais live over there.
See that small town on the other shore?
It's a short distance by car from that town.
I've never been there,
but I've heard it's a house
with a large fir tree,
so I think you'll
recognize it right away.
Eichi... He lives here and
sees this scenery everyday.
So Mitsuki will finally
get to see Eichi!
Is that all right?
Is what all right?
When all's said and done,
all we can do is watch, right?
That's true,
we are Death Spirits after all.
I don't know much else
but to look in the handbook like this.
Oh no, Takuto! Look at this!
IARUKAS IHCIE
What?!
Eichi will make her death come sooner?!
What's that mean?!
I don't know!
But the handbook is absolute, you know!
We can't have her see Eichi!
Takuto!
For now, I'll go ahead and investigate!
Meroko, don't leave Mitsuki's side!
Got it?!
Yeah!
Gosh! Why's this happening
at a time like this?!
A huge fir tree.
That must be it!
So this is where Eichi lives?
This looks like Eichi's room.
What is this cold feeling?
A shadow filled with the smell of death
surrounds this house.
Why?
Is that the Sakurai husband and wife?
They look really old.
You need to put it out of your mind.
That was an unfortunate accident.
But...
N-No way!
Takuto! What's going on?!
Is Eichi really going to hasten her death?
I don't know! But his name appeared
backwards in the Death Spirit Handbook!
Is it okay...to let her see Eichi?!
She's been working so hard to
be able to see him! So... So...
Next time on Full Moon:
"Eternal Snow."
- Look forward to it!