Th-This can't be happening!
Groribas was defeated?
He was one of our best warriors!
What manner of creature is he?
And how'd he get aboard?
Dammit!
Melzargard was supposed to be guarding the ship!
Now he and I are the only elite fighters left!
I bet he's just mucking about…
I need him now!
Curse the bastard!
Geryuganshoop, what is the problem?
Lord Boros! I-I am terribly sorry.
One of the natives has
managed to infiltrate the ship.
In the mere four minutes since coming aboard,
he has damaged 23% of the ship.
It seems he is alone,
but he has managed to instantly kill every warrior sent to intercept him.
Do not panic.
As long as the power sphere is safe,
the ship will not go down.
The damage so far is limited to the crew's living quarters.
But minnows won't be enough.
Geryuganshoop…
You, Groribas, and Melzargard are my top lieutenants.
Eliminate this intruder.
Groribas has fallen, sir…
What?
L-Let me get Melzargard back here!
He and I together will wipe out
the intruder without fail!
The Dominator of the Universe
one punch
three, two, one, kill shot
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Are you talking to him? Frustration
nan datten da, frustration
He's not going to stop
ore wa tomaranai
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
power, get power
On to the very edge
girigiri genkai made
hero
There are voices praising him
ore o tataeru koe ya
but he's not doing this for acclaim
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
hero
So he just fight evil without end
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
hero
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
A fighting hero
tatakau hero
A lone hero
kodoku na hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
Mystery Craft In Skies Above A City
We have more information on the enormous flying object that has suddenly appeared
in the skies over A City.
I'm here at the scene.
As you can see, all the main roads
leading to A City have been closed,
and a state of emergency has been declared.
According to survivors,
A City has been almost entirely demolished.
Name:
Hammerhead
Employment Application
Mystery Craft In Skies Above A City
This image of the giant flying object was captured with a telephoto lens.
What are your thoughts?
Most likely, this is the act of an alien or extraterrestrial being.
Or perhaps it's an unidentified life-form that belongs to a highly advanced civilization unbeknownst to us.
Of course, other possibilities exist as well.
I see.
Also, there have been eyewitness accounts
of very powerful life-forms descending to the ground from the spacecraft.
Several S-class heroes are presently at ground zero dealing with the situation.
He pummeled that thing with nothing but his bare fists.
Truly S-class.
But even so…
It's no good!
It possesses incredible regenerative powers.
And don't let it hit any part of you.
A single blow instantly tore my arm off.
Avoid its attacks at all costs!
If I may cut in…
Shall we use a bombardment to finish them off?
That is good.
Contact the ship.
On my way.
Where do you think you're going?!
You scum!
Best mind your manners!
I hope ya like mincemeat, freak!
Melzargard! What are you doing?!
I'm in battle.
We have an intruder!
Ridiculous.
It's true.
Finish them off and get up here right now!
This one's locked too.
Hey, open up! You've got a visitor!
Oops… I broke it.
I've decided.
I'm going to rip your limbs off,
then keep you as the ship mascot.
That is good.
So ya put yourself back together again, eh?
I'm gonna keep ya for batting practice!
Friends, it seems that direct
physical attacks are ineffective!
Let's withdraw for now and think of a way
to destroy it, like heat or something!
Smashing is all I can do!
Forget it!
This is all I know, too.
Can't teach an old dog new tricks.
Me, too. Sorry, sweet Iairon!
Iai, don't you have faith in me?
There's nothing I can't cut down.
It's pointless…
These guys are stubborn to a fault.
Melzargard!
Look, I really need you on the ship.
Getting rid of the intruder takes priority.
I'd love to, but I'm busy.
These creatures are persistent.
What?!
The life-forms down there are proving tough to handle too?
Nothing tough about them.
What's with the ship? Is it going down?
It's not going down,
but more than half the crew have been killed.
What?!
Listen.
Begin cleansing my location with a bombardment from the ship!
I've got my hands full right now.
Besides, artillery bombardment is a grunt's job.
Well, I am currently unable to return to the ship.
All right.
I'll notify the artillery crews.
Don't get caught up in the barrage and die.
Hey, wait!
You should come down here and help me.
That'd be much faster.
Hey! Geryuganshoop!
Damn him.
How tough is this intruder?
How 'bout another one?!
More futile attacks.
Although you are exhausting yourself. That is good.
The hell is this?
A marble? Why've you got this?
G-Give it back!
Sure thing.
Damn!
That's nasty, ya nasty bastard!
You dead?
Hey, this guy's got marble-looking things inside him.
That's where ya hurt him!
Oh!
Nice work.
So I just have to keep slicing until I hit a vital marble!
Impossible!
I've been growing that head for a hundred years!
How could it die in a dump like this?
No matter.
You scum are all dead when the shells hit.
They're on their way!
Attention, intruder!
Cease your destruction and leave this instant.
Leave immediately.
Otherwise, we will unleash all our forces against you!
That's weird.
I hear a voice right inside my head.
Take one more step and you're dead!
I can't get out even if I wanted to!
I've lost my way!
Really? You'll leave?
All right, I will guide you.
Take a right, then go up the stairs there.
A right?
Exactly, a right.
Then I guess I'll go left!
No, wait! Not that way!
W-Wait… Hang on! You can't…!
All right, that was my fault!
I'll come to you.
Please stay right there.
Ah! No!
Now this place looks like a
control room or something.
You…
An octopus?
You dare go around busting up our ship?
Hey! The debris is all flying at me!
Now I, Geryuganshoop, the strongest telekinesis user in the universe,
will grind you into paste.
Just about there.
Lord Geryuganshoop, preparations for
the bombardment are nearly complete.
Shall I proceed?
Maybe he went to the bathroom.
Hey, Lord Geryuganshoop!
Telekinesis… like a psychic?
You leave me no choice.
Super Telekinetic Gravitational Wave!
Die, earthling!
My unparalleled telekinetic powers allow me
to manipulate even the forces of gravity!
Have you any idea what a black hole is, you ape?
Inside one, the gravitational effects are
so strong even light itself cannot esca—
Wait…
Now what?
Take this! Telekinetic Shower of Rubble!
I-I got him!
What a waste of psychic powers.
I mean, all you're doing is tossing pebbles around.
Anyone can do that.
H-How… could…
I… Geryuganshoop…
be…
Excuse me.
Can I ask…
where your boss is?
This looks bad.
Is that confirmed?
Yes, Child Emperor said that the energy level in the spaceship is rapidly rising.
But the civilians—
Recall the search and rescue teams for now.
Have everyone take cover.
They could fire at any moment!
Hop on!
There we go.
Lord Geryuganshoop still hasn't
gotten back to me, but whatever.
Let's see…
I believe the order was to concentrate fire around the enemies on the surface near Melzargard.
Two heads to go!
I'll bust 'em wide open!
Is it time?
Ship, bombardment, coming…
Ah, there they are.
All right, bombs away!
It's over.
Evasion, impossible. Instant death.
Huh? What happened?
What on earth?
They stopped.
All of you would be dead without me.
Can't you even finish one small fry?
Maybe try starting over from Class C.
You can have your shells back.
Th-This is…
I wanna go home.
I didn’t expect you to be here.
Thank you, Unlicensed Rider.
Which areas are likely to have survivors?
There must be more out there.
But you…
I'll go rescue them right away.
We want to know, too.
Yeah, can't let him hog the limelight.
Stinger, Lightning Max…
Mind if we borrow this?
You guys…
Nice catch.
Found it.
Smush.
One left!
Silverfang!
A-A direct hit…
Weak, weak!
You are all so very weak.
Dead after a single hit!
A change of tactics was all I needed.
If I forget defense and focus on attack,
this will all be over quickly.
And you're next!
I will spring past that sword and squeeze your skull till it pops.
Let's see you try.
So he's come.
This planet's finest warrior…
I sense no limit to his vast power.
You the boss of these invaders?
Wonderful!
Before we fight, let us introduce ourselves.
I am Boros, leader of the pirate band known as "Dark Matter" and Dominator of the Universe.
I'm your average hobby he—I mean,
a professional hero.
My name's Saitama.
Saitama…
Look, I don't know what the
Denominator of the Universe wants with Earth,
but you sure trashed A City.
What I want with Earth?
There exists a prophecy.
Prophecy? You mean…
Once, I traveled the universe, ravaging everything in sight.
But I was too strong.
Eventually, there were none left who could face me.
I came to know the torment of
utter, all-encompassing boredom.
Then one day, a seer told me…
On this faraway planet,
a being exists who is my match,
one who could rekindle my passion for battle.
That was nearly twenty years ago.
Have you any idea the distance I have traveled to get here?
My men thought the prophecy was a ruse,
made up to lure me away.
But now I am certain.
Come. Give stimulation to my existence.
That is why I am here!
Are you stupid?
You can't just go around attacking other planets
just to liven up your boring life.
Even telemarketers aren't that evil.
This set of armor, made to seal in my immeasurable, irresistible power,
has now been broken.
Okay.
Let us begin!
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
I close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you... I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope these feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you work all the time
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, but I'm still worried
tsuyokute shinpai
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before any stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come back home straight
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Next Time
The
Strongest
Hero
The
Strongest
Hero
The
Strongest
Hero
Next time, on the finale of One Punch Man :
"The Strongest Hero."
What does it mean to be "strongest," Saitama?
You must tell me too…