Summer vacation's just about to end.
And then school starts again!
It'll be so much fun!
Fun?
I'll get to see everyone in class again.
Everyone in class?
Toorun!
Wait right there, Yutaka!
Darn, I didn't win.
You know, Run-chan...
You always have boys around you. Why?
Really? I don't think so.
I wonder why.
Has anyone ever confessed to you?
Confessed?
Oh, right, a while ago...
Someone has?!
Satou-sensei gave me this.
What?
He said he likes things like this.
It's kind of weird for someone to like candles.
I don't think he likes candles like that.
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Summer Festival
Hey, look at this!
Why don't we all go?
What is it?
Oh, they have this fireworks show every year.
Really?
They have a lot of booths too. Very lively.
Oh, and it's this weekend.
It's the end of summer vacation.
I want to go with you all.
Yeah!
We could all wear yukata!
Let's do that!
I guess it's fine once in a while.
Then it's settled!
Hey, what do you want to do today?
I don't know.
It's hot. I don't want to move.
Hey, why don't we go for some karaoke?
Karaoke?
Karaoke? Sounds fun. I love it!
Oh? Yuuko, you like karaoke?
Yeah.
I can pretty much sing any of my ringtones!
What do you like, Run?
Well, at this place it has to be the jambalaya.
And then ramen for reinforcements.
And then their parfaits come with so much ice cream!
Um... Weren't we going for karaoke?
Yeah. Karaoke.
It's kind of small.
I'll order some food and drinks.
What do you want?
Melon soda for me.
Grapefruit juice.
Tooru? A drink?
I-Iced tea.
Of course!
Oh, hello. We'd like to order now.
Hey, they've got this month's new songs!
One iced tea, one melon soda, and one grapefruit juice.
I'll put mine in first.
And one jambalaya and french fries.
Yes. Yes.
Please.
Alright. Let's go.
Take me summer breeze
Take me away
My love is feeling the breeze
Catch me summer breeze
Gently now
A summer dream taking off with you
Yuuko's got a voice!
It sure is nice!
Taking off with you
Take me summer breeze
Thanks.
Oh, I'm next.
Tooru looks really serious.
Is she picky or something?
You can take your time picking a song.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Okay, it's my turn now!
A cute alarm clock, gravity pulling me back to sleep
Ring-ring, snore-snore, another day slipping out
Fighting with my best friend over the best scrunchie
Who gets in the last word? There, you just lost it
Let's tell everyone about this strange magic
Using words that people might spread around
(3, 2, 1, say!) Playful, melodical, beauty, bang-bang!
With a big smile
Tooru, finished your staring contest with the book?
Oh, you want this one?
I'll enter it.
There. Entered.
Nice song.
Come on.
It's starting.
Go for it, Tooru!
Uh... Um...
The mic! The mic!
What's wrong, Tooru?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
My jambalaya's here!
It's still hot, so please be careful.
Grapefruit juice over here!
Here you go, Nagi-chan.
Thanks.
The melon soda is mine.
Here.
Thanks.
Huh?
She didn't want to sing...
I'm sorry I entered it without asking...
Slowly fading away into the twilight
A young country girl's innocence
Be it a love never to be
I just want to see you one more time
You put some passion into that one.
Just two more songs.
Once I sing two more songs, I can eat eight fries.
Your diet?
Forget about it and eat.
Hey, Tooru, didn't you like that song?
Here, this one.
Right?
But... I've never sung it before.
I might not do it right.
It's okay!
Tooru, it's turned off.
I'll start.
Run-chan...
Let's hold hands together
On the other side of the hill
There's one, two, three
And even more fun things
A white blanket
A big-eyed puppet
A polka dot skirt
But I can't split that with you
Even if you fall, even if you cry
Everyone's here for you
As long as it's exciting
I'm sure we'll be happy
Let's hold hands together
And walk straight ahead
There's one, two, three
And even more fun things
Only three left?
It didn't really work out, huh?
Wait, no one's singing right now?
Then I'll sing one.
Finish eating before that.
Then my next song will be...
Next door?
No one was there before.
Maybe they just got here.
They're really good at this.
But the song is kind of stuffy.
Oh, it started.
Run-chan, don't sing.
Why not?
It doesn't matter.
What?
Tooru!
Don't tell me...
This voice...
What?
What? What?
I want to sing karaoke with Run-chan.
Karaoke sure was fun.
Let's do it again sometime.
I want to get better at singing.
Oh, that's right.
They were talking about how to get better on TV.
For next time
Part 1
It's been a long time since we wore yukata to a festival.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
I have a few yukata. Which do you want?
This purple one is nice. It looks very mature.
Let me see.
I don't remember having this one.
Oh!
Mold is growing on it. The color changed.
Hm...
I guess none of them work.
Maybe one of the older ones will.
I'll go get them.
These mules look really mature.
Maybe they're Run-chan's mom's.
With these, I might reach 1*0 centimeters.
I'll never grow up like this.
Mom!
Oh my!
Look! We took them back out.
How do we look?
The festival was today, wasn't it?
They're very nice and flowery.
They look good on you.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
But the festival is tonight, right?
It's still 10 a.m.
I got too excited.
There they are!
Oh.
Thanks for waiting.
Alright, we're all here.
Doesn't Yuuko-chan look lovely no matter what she wears?
And Nagi-chan...
Oh, she curled her hair!
Look at that.
Yeah, she did.
How cute!
Well, you know, sometimes.
The fireworks are still a long way off, so why don't we spend time at the booths?
Can we see the mask store first?
Sure, why not?
Oh, you like kids' cartoons, Tooru?
No.
If we pass any shopping district booths, they'll try to give me stuff.
I'd feel guilty.
Oh, really?
Oh! A candy apple!
Candy apple...
Yuuko-chan, can I have a bite?
Yeah, sure.
Here.
It's good!
What, Tooru, you want some too?
Not really.
You sure?
Run, can I have some cotton candy?
Sure.
Wow, that's good!
Huh?
Yuuko-chan's trying the ring toss?
I got a third prize!
Congratulations!
Here's your fireworks set.
We come to see fireworks, and the prize is fireworks?
Alright! I'm up next!
First prize, here I come!
What? I only have this much left?
Booths cost quite a bit.
You have to be careful.
If you don't, you might not have enough for a second round.
But when you see these kinds of things, you just have to do it.
That's why you choose things that you can enjoy for a long time.
Katanuki?
Nagi, these things don't happen too often. Why don't we do something we can all do?
Sounds like you've never tried katanuki. It's fun, you know.
Really?
Why don't we try, then?
It's my first time.
Then let's try some easy ones.
I broke it...
Hey, Mister, one more.
Right up.
This is pretty hard...
Yeah.
Come on, hurry up!
Yutaka is still eating yakisoba!
Thank you all for waiting.
The fireworks show will begin momentarily.
The fireworks started already?!
Come on, everyone!
It's too crowded.
I know a good spot!
Run to the platform! No one goes there!
Nagi, that's enough katanuki for now!
Wait! My gourd!
It's just up these stairs!
You know, I kind of don't care for fireworks anymore.
Nagi, we're going!
I can't make it!
Hang in there, Nagi-chan!
Keep going!
We're here!
It was a break!
Wow!
The fireworks show has now come to a close.
Please dispose of any trash in the marked bins or take it with you as you leave.
Is that it?
Come on...
Only seeing that last part just isn't enough.
It's kind of sad.
Oh!
That's right!
I got fireworks from that booth!
Oh, right! Good job, Yuuko!
But we don't have fire.
That's okay!
Matches?
A candle?
You brought it with you?
Why are there only senko hanabi in this thing?!
Kind of boring.
But I like senko hanabi, you know?
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Yeah. They're pretty.
Today was delicious.
You ate way too much.
Oh?
Satou-sensei? Why are you here?
You don't need to ask.
Get away from me!
I should say the same thing.
By the way, Sensei, did you come here alone?
What?! I didn't come here alone!
Barkeep, another pint.
But you're alone now.
I am not alone!
There you go again.
Summer vacation sure was fun.
Yeah.
Sure was.
We even went to the beach.
Let's see the fireworks next year too!
Yeah.
I'll finish my katanuki next time!
Still upset?
Hey, come on. It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah! We got hooked.
Right, Tooru?
It was fun.
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
Speaking of the end of August...
Summer vacation homework!
Copying it from someone who already finished.
I tried to rush my picture diary, but I don't know what the weather was like every day!
On the next A Channel: New Term
Wait, we're not in elementary school...