While preparing for
her school trip,
Mitsuki's illness takes a turn for the worse,
and she collapses!
She can't even go
on the trip anymore.
What's worse, her grandmother
wants her to get surgery!
But Mitsuki firmly refuses,
saying she doesn't want to lose her voice.
Things are going to be tense between
Mitsuki and her grandmother again!
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
It feels so good!
Yeah. The sky sure is high.
It was worth coming out early.
Right, Mitsuki?
Hey, you can't keep being so glum.
That old lady is always unpleasant, right?
Yeah, but...
Do as you like.
She hasn't talked to me
much since then.
Even so, it won't do any good
to be depressed.
Right. Nothing gets done
when you mope around.
Yeah. But...
Jeez!
Everyone will only worry if you
go to school with a look like that.
How about we take a different route
as a change of pace?
Wow, that's amazing!
How beautiful.
Yeah. I didn't know there was
such a lovely place nearby.
Oh, it's so romantic.
I'd like to come here with Takuto
sometime, just the two of us.
Wait, Meroko!
Over here!
Mitsuki, it's about time to go.
Yeah.
Oh wait! Takuto!
I wonder if he lives here.
Mitsuki.
What're you doing? Let's go!
O-Okay.
Oh, that place used to be the mansion
of someone named Sanada.
Sanada?
Yes, I heard that he's the head
of a large company
and that he lived alone in the mansion.
But he may have moved.
What?
If I recall, it's vacant now.
With nobody to succeed him,
it was probably donated somewhere.
That's enough.
It's despicable gossiping
so much about others.
I-I'm sorry.
Okay, I've got to get to work.
Does it bother you that much?
He was just an ordinary gentleman.
Well, his fine graying hair
made him seem refined and nice.
Anyway, I'm gonna go again.
After all...
I'm curious why he looked
so surprised when he saw me.
That gentleman isn't here.
Yeah.
You guys!
Sure enough, you're the ones
from this morning.
Sure enough, the two in back
are with that girl.
- Huh? The two in back?!
W-Why?
Why can someone else see us?
He's the second person after her!
There is someone other than me.
Someone who can see Death Spirits.
Mr. Sanada?
Then you lived in the mansion?
Yes. I wanted to be helpful
to people at the end at least,
so I donated all of the land.
And so I'm living here now.
Oh, sure enough,
it doesn't say anything.
How is it that you can see us?
It seems that Death Spirit
is cautious of me.
I'm sorry.
It seems Takuto is in a bad mood.
Meroko!
Don't say anything unnecessary!
Takuto and Meroko, huh?
Oh... Umm... I'm Mitsuki Koyama.
Mitsuki... That's a cute name.
Enough about that. Answer us!
Well, that's simple.
A Death Spirit appeared before me too.
I was told that I had one year to live.
I was shocked at first, but now it's
as if I'm just waiting for that day.
No way! What about your family?
They'll all be sad!
I don't have any family.
Huh?
They've all died.
I was successful in business and
had a wonderful family around me.
It was a happy life.
But I grew busier
with work day by day,
and I became unable to spend
enough time with my family.
One Sunday, I put work ahead of
a commitment with my son.
Shall we even out this area?
Okay.
It was an accident that
happened in an instant.
From then on, I became
more absorbed in work.
It was painful to think
about my dead son.
My wife and I stopped talking and
we became complete strangers.
And then three years ago,
even my wife...
I was left alone.
Why didn't I value my family?
Why couldn't I share my feelings
with my wife?
I agonized with regrets of that.
It made it painful to even live.
It was at that time when the Death Spirit
appeared before me.
At first I was shocked.
To be honest, all I thought
was that I didn't want to die.
But now, I'll finally be
able to see them again.
This time, I'll be able to
really listen to them.
Me too! I'm the same!
I have until next spring.
I knew it.
Aren't you guys ashamed to
take the life of such a little girl?!
Oh... Well...
Umm... It's our job.
Mr. Sanada, Takuto and Meroko
are dear friends of mine.
Friends?
Yes.
And if they weren't with me, I...
Takuto, turn me into Full Moon!
Huh?
I want Mr. Sanada to understand that
you two are my dear friends.
So...okay?
Got it.
This is...
Takuto and Meroko made
my dream come true.
My dream to get the songs I love
to resound within the heart
of the person I love.
Songs...
Yes!
That is what's most
important to me now.
I see. I've seen you on TV before.
I see. So Takuto and Meroko
were helping you, huh?
Yes.
It seems you're kind Death Spirits.
Well, not really.
You're so mean, Takuto!
Why are you being so
disrespectful to your senior?
I'm not.
They're quite lively, aren't they?
Yes.
Mr. Sanada!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Those two have totally
become friends.
I wonder if people who can see Death Spirits
have some kind of connection.
- At any rate,
- Was it a little scary?
- Mr. Sanada sure is cheerful, isn't he?
- No, it was a lot of fun!
- Despite having only a short time to live.
- That's good.
But why can only those two see us?
Yeah.
It's a mystery.
What? These roses...
Mr. Sanada.
When are these roses going to bloom?
Oh, I think they'll be blooming soon.
My wife took great care of them
until she died.
She was really looking
forward to them blooming.
Hey, are you okay?
Is it that bitter?
No, I'm fine.
Say, Takuto. I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
I'd like you guys to wait just a little longer
before collecting Mr. Sanada's life.
I bet Mr. Sanada wants
to see those roses.
You know, he looked very
lonesome back there.
But you know, Mitsuki...
Please! At the very least,
until his wife's precious roses bloom.
There's no way!
That's impossible.
If I could do such a thing,
I'd have long since...
I'd have long since
saved Mitsuki's life.
But... But you know, Takuto...
Anyway, we can't do
what we can't do!
Takuto...
You know, Mitsuki,
all we do is collect the soul
when the time limit of the life runs out.
Determining the length...
is outside of our jurisdiction.
I see.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're not gonna go with her today?
You don't have to be so angry.
I can't help but be angry!
Oh Takuto! Jeez.
Wait! Takuto!
Hey! Takuto and Meroko!
Well, I'm glad I could see you guys.
As a matter of fact, I have something
I want to consult you guys about.
What is it?
We're on our way to Mitsuki.
Takuto!
Actually, I wanted to talk
to you about Mitsuki.
Would you be able to
give my life to her?
It's unbearable to think that
she has such a fate.
There may not be much left,
but I want to give her my remaining life.
So can you guys...
There's no way.
It's impossible for us.
We can't... With our power,
we can't change fate.
I thought Mitsuki was an idiot,
but Mr. Sanada's just
as much an idiot, huh?
We're the bigger idiots.
We have no power...
Other than collecting souls.
We can't do anything!
We're useless!
Damn it!
Hello.
Jonathan!
If he's here, then...
Of course, I'm here too.
Izumi?!
What're you doing here?!
Well, well.
There's only one reason for a Death Spirit
to come to the human world, right?
What?!
Work, work!
Jeez!
Let me see,
Yuichiro Sanada, age 56.
His life span goes until today.
You guys are child specialists
from pediatrics, right? Why?
Beats me. It was the Division Chief
of Death Spirits' order.
Izumi, it's almost time.
Right. Shall we get this over with?
Hey! Wait!
Takuto!
There's nothing we can do!
The code is to not interfere
with a collection!
Even so...
I can't forget about that old guy like this.
The two of them didn't come today.
Takuto, Meroko.
How long has it been since
I fell in love with you?
My feelings keep getting...
I see. So you've come at last.
I've come to collect your soul by the order
of the Division Chief of Death Spirits.
- I'm Izumi.
- I'm Jonathan.
Oh, different Death Spirits than
the ones who came before.
I guess I'll miss them.
It's time. Is it okay?
Yeah. Please start.
Are you ready?
Yes. I have no more regrets.
Izumi! Wait!
I've been waiting. I'll show you how
a Death Spirit should work.
No!
Mitsuki?!
Please, Izumi! Please wait a little longer
before doing your work!
Umm... This is some kind of mistake.
There's no way that Mitsuki
can see Death Spirits!
You see, umm...
Did you really think we hadn't noticed?
You guys were lovely,
getting all worked up.
You little...
Oops, I'm in the middle of my work,
right now. Don't interfere, okay?
No! Stop, Izumi!
At least... At the very least, please
wait until his wife's roses bloom.
It's okay, Mitsuki.
Mr. Sanada.
It's all right.
Please don't say that.
I don't want you to die!
Listen to me.
Please live the rest
of your life to the fullest.
And live to the end without losing sight
of the things that are important to you.
Mr. Sanada.
Please don't look so tearful.
I'd like the last face I see on
this earth to be a smiling face.
Okay!
Huh?
What?
Okay, Mitsuki.
Please.
Gotcha.
Mission accomplished.
This will happen to you soon too.
At the hands of Takuto and Meroko.
Izumi! You piece of...
Takuto!
Whoa! You can't resort to violence, Takuto.
It's only the truth.
See you later.
Mr. Sanada...
Mr. Sanada.
Mr. Sanada!
Mr. Sanada...
Look, Mitsuki! They're blooming.
They're beautiful.
These are the roses
his wife treasured.
I'm sorry, Mitsuki.
About Mr. Sanada, well...
Well... There was simply
nothing we could do.
Mr. Sanada might've seen
the instant those roses bloomed.
Takuto! I'll sing with all my heart.
Until the end! With all my heart!
So from here on,
I hope for your support, okay?
Takuto? Meroko?
Okay!
Mitsuki!
Look, look, Takuto!
The romance! The drama!
Will you stop?! I already know!
She got an email from Eichi, right?
Gosh, what's with the attitude?
This is the greatest thing
that could happen to her.
You could be a little happier for her.
Okay, okay. Good for her.
Takuto's sulking now.
Next time on Full Moon:
"An E-mail from Eichi?"
- Look forward to it!