What on earth?!
Look at that!
It's closing in!
Who's available?
We have word that Lightning Max and Smile Man are on their way.
Get me that threat level assessment!
As you can see, massive explosions
are going off behind me!
The monster is wreaking destruction on an unprecedented scale!
Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
While the Association's assessment is still underway, it is already clea—
[Railroad news]
Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Live broadcast from A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Live broadcast from A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due o a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due o a blockade.
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Guess I'll go.
Justice
Enforcement
Daddy! Mommy!
And who do we have here?
Just your average hobby hero.
What kind…
of half-assed backstory is that?
I was formed from the constant stream of pollution with which you humans have suffused the earth.
I am Vaccine Man!
The Earth is a single living organism.
You humans are nothing but a disease-causing bacteria eating away at her lifeforce.
In order to obliterate the humans
and their evil civilization,
The Earth has given birth to me!
You say you do this as a hobby? A hobby?
How dare you confront me, Mother Earth's apostle,
for such an inane reason?!
Yet, what more could be expected from a hu—
Not again…
All it took was one punch!
God damn it!
one punch
three, two, one, kill shot
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Are you talking to him? Frustration
nan datten da, frustration
He's not going to stop
ore wa tomaranai
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
power, get power
On to the very edge
girigiri genkai made
hero
There are voices praising him
ore o tataeru koe ya
but he's not doing this for acclaim
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
hero
So he just fight evil without end
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
hero
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
A fighting hero
tatakau hero
A lone hero
kodoku na hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
THREE YEARS EARLIER
A monster!
Run!
Huh?
You sure you don't want to run away?
I bet you're a newly employed
businessman who's already jaded.
I ate too much crab and
transformed into this, Crabrante!
I'm impressed you're not running.
You've got a death wish.
Is that it?
Well, not quite.
I'm no businessman. I'm unemployed.
Right now, I'm looking for a job.
I had another interview today and got royally rejected.
I couldn't care less about anything.
So I'm in no mood to run just because
the "mighty Crabrante" has appeared.
So, what'll happen if I don't run?
Your eyes are lifeless, just like mine.
From one set of lifeless eyes to another, I'll let you go.
Besides, right now…
I'm hunting different prey.
A big-chinned brat.
And when I find him, I'm gonna rip his arms off!
What're you looking at?
A big-chinned brat…
If he's caught, he's dead!
Hey, kid.
Were you messing with a big crab monster?
Huh?
He was asleep in the park, so I drew
some nipples on him with my marker.
It's definitely him!
He has no idea what he's done.
What do I do? I could still help…
But man, this kid sure is ugly.
It's none of my business.
I should just walk away.
Right. I mean, who really cares?
I found you!
What the hell am I doing?
Kid, he's after you! Get outta here!
Don't worry about me. Just go!
B-But…
My soccer ball…
Your ball?!
Hey, what's the big idea?
Don't tell me you're gonna protect that stinkin' brat!
Come on, you're gonna kill him over some harmless prank?
Think about this!
I've already mutilated tons of people.
Anyone who makes fun of the way I look
pays the price. No exceptions.
By the way, that brat drew nipples on my body.
With a permanent marker!
Look at these claws!
I can't even use a towel to wipe it off!
Get out of my way, or I'll make sure you never go job hunting again!
It just came to me.
You look exactly like a villain
from this anime I used to watch!
Die.
Hold it right there.
In this age of declining birth rates,
I can't just let you kill a kid.
You know what?
When I was a little boy, I wanted to be a hero.
Not a businessman,
but a hero who could send rotten villains
like you flying with one punch.
Screw looking for a job!
Bring it on!
Some hero you are!
You're pathetic!
You don't stand a chance against me.
Your life…
ends now!
Has it really been three years since then?
After that day,
I trained so hard I went bald.
I became so powerful no one can beat me.
I'm the hero I dreamed of becoming.
So what is this feeling? What's missing?
Why does my heart feel so empty?
482 yen, please.
Okay.
Oh, hang on.
I have 82 yen.
Incredible…
This is incredible, little brother!
I never thought it would work so well.
Yes,
it's more than I ever imagined, big brother.
My goal was to become the strongest man in the world.
The strongest man.
That was my dream.
At last, the ultimate steroid, Biceps King, is complete!
Little brother!
Drink this and you will obtain
the power you've been seeking!
What? Drink that?
Indeed! I added strawberry flavoring
to make it go down easier.
Brother…
Yes,
th-this will do!
My brains and your brawn!
By combining the greatest of minds
and the strongest of bodies,
we brothers will conquer the
entire earth and rule as kings!
I-Incredible!
Well done, little brother.
Thousands have perished!
Now, on to the next town to destroy it as well!
This is it, big bro.
This is what I was looking for.
The power to be the strongest.
This is an emergency evacuation warning.
A giant creature has appeared in D City.
The creature is currently heading towards B City.
All residents of the area,
please evacuate immediately.
I repeat, the giant creature is currently heading for—
Yes, that's right! Scatter like rats!
Get them!
I'm the strongest man,
I'm the strongest man. I'm the strongest man.
What do you think, brother?
Yeah, how's it feel being the strongest?
What?!
There's someone on your shoulder!
Put some pants on.
That guy on your shoulder! Kill him!
Brother!
How did this happen?!
All I ever wanted was to be strong!
And just when I finally became the strongest…
I don't know who you are,
but it's your fault my brother is dead!
The strongest!
Behold our brotherly power!
I am the strongest.
But so what?
I feel empty.
Right?
Having overwhelming strength is…
pretty boring.
Oops.
B City Destroyed
There's no sign that the evils
of the world are disappearing.
That hasn't changed since before I became a hero.
In other words, you could
say that I've made no impact.
I'm not necessarily sad about that.
But something's been bothering me lately.
As the days pass, my emotions grow more distant.
Fear, tension, joy, anger…
I feel none of them anymore.
In exchange for power,
maybe I've lost something
that's essential to be human?
Vroom, vroom?
No sense hiding if you saw me.
I'm Super Custom YO649Z Mk. II!
I love building custom cars so much
I used to feel all kinds of emotions whirling inside me when I fought.
I decided to deck myself out.
Fear, panic, anger.
I'm a custom car-loving monster!
If you're thinking of getting in my way,
I'll put a shine on that big headlight of yours!
But now, all I need is one punch to end it.
Guess I'll have eggs over rice tonight.
Each day, I come home uninjured and wash my gloves.
When I'm out fighting monsters,
I never feel as if my heart's really in it.
I mean, I just do the hero thing as a hobby.
In other words,
as long as I get a kick out of it,
that's all I care about.
My house!
He's tough!
What the hell are you?
"What" am I? How rude.
We are the true earthlings.
We?
I believe you call us "Subterraneans."
We suffer from overpopulation.
Therefore, we must now claim the world aboveground.
I understand that there are
many people on the surface too.
As it stands, you are in our way.
That is why we have decided…
to eradicate you all.
Since our invasion commenced,
70% of the surface dwellers have been killed.
This is a battle for survival.
I hope you can understand that.
However, this is unexpected.
We have never encountered a surface dweller
whom our punches would not kill.
Same here.
It's been too long since I've come across such worthy opponents,
Subterraneans!
We are earthlings!
H-How?!
You bastard!
Die!
It's over.
Who on earth was that surface dweller?
I'm…
just your average hobby hero.
I will not lose.
And the surface…
is under my protection!
Big talk for a race of vermin!
What is this feeling?
This wild throbbing in my heart?!
This rush! This tension!
It's been so long that I forgot
the exhilaration of a real fight!
It's coming back to me.
This is it.
Well, well…
Looks like you've been taking good care of my children.
This is it!
I, the Subterranean King, will take you on.
This is the very feeling…
I've been looking for!
The surface is ours!
You surface dwellers must die!
I am the Subterranean King!
Surface dwellers, prepare yourselves for—
All right, bring it on!
Sorry
I've become too strong.
The Strongest Man
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
I close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you... I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope these feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you work all the time
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, but I'm still worried
tsuyokute shinpai
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before any stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come back home straight
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Next Time
The Lone
Cyborg
How'd you like seeing me get ripped apart this week?
Now it's time for me, the mighty Crabrante, to tell you what happens next week.
Huh? There are no visuals?
Well next week, this guy appears in Z City where Saitama lives!
What now? Time's up?
Well next time, on One Punch Man : Episode 2,
"The Lone Cyborg."
I hope you all—