Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Live broadcast from A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Live broadcast from A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due o a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Live broadcast from A City
Large explosion in A City
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due o a blockade.
[Traffic news]         Traffic on the road connecting cities A through J is backed up due to a blockade.
[Railroad news]
Large explosion in A City
Justice
Enforcement
one punch
three, two, one, kill shot
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Are you talking to him? Frustration
nan datten da, frustration
He's not going to stop
ore wa tomaranai
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
power, get power
On to the very edge
girigiri genkai made
hero
There are voices praising him
ore o tataeru koe ya
but he's not doing this for acclaim
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
hero
So he just fight evil without end
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
hero
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
A fighting hero
tatakau hero
A lone hero
kodoku na hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
THREE YEARS EARLIER
B City Destroyed
Sorry
The Strongest Man
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
I close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you... I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope these feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you work all the time
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, but I'm still worried
tsuyokute shinpai
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before any stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come back home straight
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Next Time
The Lone
Cyborg