This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to real people,
organizations, names, laws, or locations is purely coincidental.
Thank you for choosing the Tōkaidō Shinkansen.
Change here for Chūō Line, Yamanote Line,
Keihin-Tōhoku Line, Tōkaidō Line, Jōban Line,
Sōbu Line, Keiyō Line,
Tōhoku, Hokuriku and Jōetsu Shinkansen,
and Tokyo Metro lines.
This train will begin its journey back at 5:54 PM.
Hikari 519 will—
Miss.
Miss? Miss!
Are you awake now? You're in Tokyo.
Thank you.
I was told to get off at Shinagawa,
then take the blue line...
I ended up at Tokyo Station.
Let's see...
Blue... Blue?
There's both light blue and dark blue.
Towards Kamata and Kannai...
Towards Kamata and Kannai....
Towards Kamata and Kannai.....
Towards Kamata and Kannai......
Towards Kamata and Kannai...
Towards Kamata and Kannai....
Kabayaki, katsu sandwiches, katsu curry!
Towards Kamata and Kannai.....
Kabayaki, katsu sandwiches...
Kabayaki, katsu sandwiches, katsu curry...
Kabayaki, katsu sandwiches, katsu curry.
Woah...
So, uh...
Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama...
Age 17, March.
I've come to Tokyo.
'Cause I don't want to give in.
'Cause it's not me who's wrong.
It's snowing!
The dark of night hides away behind an unfinished beat
We take a single breath of its embrace before we're crushed beneath
Although you try and fail and try and fail again
You can seize your chosen future by your own hand
Nothing's set in stone until you make it, so reach your hands out
Trapped in an endless crowd
Crying out with a voice that can't make a sound
And by the break of day
Sounds of footsteps will smother all you can say
Time's march will carry on
But the silent calls remain
The cold, filthy water flows
Through a city full of raw pain
In a world where nothing ever changes
We still have to live to see tomorrow
Though the scorn pervades your voice, we've got no other choice
No other path to tread
We've only got the future ahead
I promise you it's real, this stupid dream I feel
It's like there's no hope left living in this city, but still I try
Looking out and seeing there's a future for me
Reaching out and seizing hold of what I can be
Look around and see
I've been saying it all along
This stupid-sounding song
We're shining a light through streets of hopeless darkness
It's not a dream
Though this town is full of rot and decay
There's no point in giving in to dismay
Even now, there's time, there's time!
The dark of night hides away behind an unfinished beat
We take a single breath of its embrace before we're crushed beneath
Although you try and fail and try and fail again
You can seize your chosen future by your own hand
Nothing's set in stone until you make it, so reach your hands out
Tokyo Hype
Excuse me!
Is anyone there?
Kawasaki Station Real Estate — Closed
My name is Iseri. I came to pick up the key...
No surprise. I'm way too late.
Totally dead.
Let's see...
Here, I guess?
Excuse me, is this—
Keep it down!
I'm sorry!
This is it.
What did I even expect?
Maybe... they could have hidden a spare key here...
Or not.
Um...
Ow!
Excuse me, I live here. Can I help you?
Um, I'm Iseri. I'm moving in next door.
O-Oh, is that so? Nice to meet you.
Th-thanks.
It's just... I don't have my keys...
I was supposed to pick them
up from the agency today,
but I got here very late...
Did you call them?
Unfortunately, my phone died...
Want to use mine?
Without my phone,
I don't know the number either...
I see. Wanna come in to charge it, then?
Come on. Don't be shy.
No, no, it's alright.
I'll manage somehow.
Thank you for the offer!
I'm sorry, if you could just look after my suitcase!
There!
9 missed calls from Mom
8 missed calls from Suzune
9 messages from Suzune
Not surprising.
9 missed calls from Mom
8 missed calls from Suzune
9 messages from Suzune
Incoming call: Suzune
Hello?
Oh, you finally picked up.
Mom, Nina picked up!
Sorry, I ran out of battery.
Where'd you go off to?
Uncle rang us earlier today, you know.
He waited ages for you.
I know.
I'll sort out the keys tomorrow.
Enough chit-chat. Let it go.
Bye.
Hey. Are you sure you're gonna manage on your own?
Sorry, my battery's running out.
@o4traveler
Went to a temple in Kyoto~
#Kyoto #Travel
@k4hvi_hyvaa
Haven't been to this shopping mall in ages
#daily_life #walking
@yuyaptpt
At the train depot.
What a find!
#what_year_is_it_from #kumamoto_trains
#quiz
@aaya229
Tried my hand at pottery! lol
#pottery_wheel #pottery #too_hard
#managed_somehow
@momokan_1209
I'll be performing here today
#kawasaki_station #momoka #music
#street_concert
Wait. That's right around here.
@momokan_1209
I'll be performing in front of the
East Exit at Kawasaki Station at 10 PM
#kawasaki_station #momoka
#street_concert
At 10 PM?
No way!
She's really here.
Excuse me...
E-Excuse me!
You're Kawaragi Momoka, right?
Yeah.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Of Diamond Dust,
and you personally.
Thanks.
Um...
I really, really like your songs.
I moved here to Tokyo from the countryside today.
Your songs gave me the strength to take this step.
I see.
I really mean it!
I really do.
I think I've listened to your songs over a thousand times by now.
I saw on the internet that you were going to perform here today...
Thought it was fate.
Wanna buy my CD, then?
Oh, of course!
One thousand yen...
There.
Thanks.
That ain't a thousand...
And that's your problem?
Huh? Did I say something dumb?
Not really.
I'm just happy to have a fan like you.
Warms my heart.
You there.
Didn't hear me last time?
This is our spot, little girl.
Should've put your name on it, then.
Point is: get out of here.
Come on.
O-Okay!
Hey!
You little...
Run!
You're dead!
Why me, though?
Oh, actually, you're right.
We just need to explain you're a random person who was passing by.
They'll probably...
Stop right there!
...not let you go, actually.
This way!
Damn it!
Jackass.
What does that gesture mean?
"Thank you."
Why were they so angry, then?
What's your name?
Nina.
Iseri Nina.
Kawasaki and Shin-Kawasaki?
Yeah. Normally you'd expect Kawasaki to be next after Shin-Kawasaki, right?
But turns out it wasn't...
Should've checked the map.
My phone battery died.
And that's how you missed getting the keys?
My uncle told me Kawasaki was the easiest to settle into if I wanted to live in Tokyo.
So much for that.
Tokyo?
Yeah?
Kawasaki isn't part of Tokyo.
Technically, it's in Kanagawa.
Same as Yokohama.
What? I was told it was on the edge of Tokyo.
Your uncle and the agency fooled you.
I bet they gave you a place no one else wanted.
So that's why the rent is so cheap…
I actually think Kawasaki is a nice place, though.
I agree.
I only met you because I came here.
I have a ticket for a Diamond Dust concert in my hometown that got canceled.
I carry it with me as a charm.
Could you maybe sign it for me?
Excuse me.
Here, your medium beef bowl.
So this is a... beef bowl!
What, never had it before?
What planet did you come from?
Kumamoto.
No beef bowl places there?
There are!
But my family rules included always eating all meals at home.
Family rules
— Dinner is eaten at home together as a family.
— No smartphones are allowed in the living room.
— Family meetings are every Sunday night.
Wait a sec...
Are you from a rich home?
I wouldn't really call my family rich...
It's so good!
How? How is it this good?!
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
Thank you!
It was delicious, thank you.
The last train'll be leaving soon.
What's your plan?
I'll figure something out.
So you don't have a plan.
Let's go.
Thank you!
I'm covering both meals, it's on the counter!
Thank you very much!
I might not seem like it, but I do care for my fans.
It was quite delicious.
Thank you so much!
You wanna fight?
Thank you very much!
You told me it meant "thank you"!
It's like, the complete opposite!
I'm sorry, really.
Here?
It'll be cold inside, just as a heads up.
The heating here doesn't work.
Do you live with family?
Nope, no one's here.
It'll take me a bit to take these off, so go on ahead.
It's the room at the end.
A-Alright.
The light switch's on your left!
You okay with cats?
Yeah.
Sit down.
I'll make us some coffee.
Thank you.
It's so cool!
What, can you play?
Absolutely not.
But I've always wanted to.
Wanna try holding it?
Can I?
There you go.
It's heavier than I thought.
Looking pretty awkward there.
Of course I am.
Come on, I was teasing you!
Just need to get used to it and you'll look super cool.
Aren't you still in high school?
Well, I'm seventeen.
I'd be in my last year if I actually went to school.
Sugar?
Yes, please.
I was exactly your age
when I quit school and came here with my friends.
It's already been three years, huh?
Wait, you're only twenty?
That doesn't really feel like a compliment.
You know, it might really be that fate brought us together.
Yeah! For real!
So...
You only came here today, right?
Yes.
Um, if you could...
I'm going back home tomorrow.
To Asahikawa.
Girls Band Cry.
What do you mean?
I'm moving out of here.
I'm going home
and quitting music.
But why?
Your songs are so good, why would you stop?
Thanks.
Try your coffee.
Momoka, please.
It's all settled already.
My music wasn't selling, y'know.
Can't live off concerts and music sales alone.
You end up working shift after shift after shift.
But you're the one that wrote Void, right?
It has so many views...
Wellll, it's not mine anymore.
What?
I don't have the rights to that song anymore.
Tell me more.
Details, please.
Nothing for you to worry about.
Tell me, please!
You wrote that song, Momoka. Am I wrong?
There's no way you can change that!
Of course you can!
No, you can't!
You can.
You cannot!
No, you can't!
You're so stubborn.
Just like the stereotype.
What else didya expect?
Stop that, please.
Don't.
Jeez.
What happened to the little lost lamb from before?
I don't get it.
It's because that song's...
Evening.
Good evening...
Don't make too much noise,
or the neighbors will complain again.
You're going out at this hour?
Who was that?
He's my...
B-Boyfriend?
Your boyfriend, right?
Y-Y-You're living toge—
Calm. The. Hell. Down.
Roommate.
He's my roommate.
I couldn't afford a place this big on my own.
But he's a guy!
Correct.
But, he's into guys.
He's probably heading over to his boyfriend's to stay the night.
Boyfriend's?
My gosh!
Tokyo's just insane!
Kawasaki.
We have our own rooms,
and rarely run into each other.
I barely notice that he lives here too.
But...
You should consider sharing
a place with someone too, you know.
In a city this big,
you'll end up working two jobs
to afford living alone.
What's your rent?
50,000 yen.
Your income?
I'll get a job, but haven't looked into it yet.
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
I have some savings.
And I did get some money from my parents.
Ah, you've got it easy, then.
You can do whatever you want.
In a city like this, having money lets you—
Sorry, but what do you know about me?
You say I've got it easy.
But you've got no idea what I struggle with!
Thank you for the coffee.
Sorry to bother you.
Nina, wait!
You're really fast.
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
You quit school at such a young age
and came here all alone.
No way you've got it easy.
Do you have a dream?
Nothing in particular, really.
Surely you do.
I didn't come here for a dream.
I just felt like there wasn't a place for me.
I didn't do anything wrong,
but it seemed like everyone thought otherwise.
I didn't want to lay down and take it.
I see.
All the more reason to apologize.
And what about you?
What's your story?
Why are you going back to Asahikawa?
It wasn't anything in particular.
We had a disagreement and disbanded.
You mean Diamond Dust did?
Yep. And as we were sorting out the details,
the problem of song ownership came up.
The other members said
they were gonna continue without me, so...
You just gave them the song?
I could write another one any time.
Or, that's what I thought back then.
What?
You're such a softie, Momoka.
But I think you're really cool, too.
Ah! Take it easy!
Oh, you're blushing.
I'm not!
You're gonna completely ruin my hair!
Wanna do some karaoke?
Like, right now?
You know some pretty old songs, huh?
My grandma listened to them a lot.
And you ended up liking Diamond Dust songs?
Yeah.
I found them while I was at rock bottom.
It felt like they were shouting
all the things I had bottled up.
They told me to stay strong.
To me, they're my life's soundtrack.
What I sang earlier today was the last of it, for me.
The last Diamond Dust song I'll ever sing.
I...
Okay, next!
Ow.
Oh, it's just the cat.
Good morning.
When you read this letter,
I'll probably be gone already.
The movers ought to be there, too.
I'm gonna pick up my paycheck,
wander around a bit, then take the train home.
Also,
I'm leaving you my guitar.
Enjoy your life in Tokyo!
I'm sorry!
I'll unlock it for you.
Yes! Thank you for bringing it all in.
Good luck!!
Flip 'em off!
I'll be right back!
Momoka...
Momoka.
Momoka!
Excuse me for a bit.
Hey, you can't just...
Momoka. Momoka!
Are you really okay with this?
Once you leave, there's no turning back!
It really doesn't have to be the end!
But if you give up now, it'll be truly over!
Are you okay?
I know I'm being stubborn right now!
Maybe I shouldn't be saying this, but who cares!
I came here because I didn't want to lay down and take it!
And I don't want you to have to take it either, Momoka!
Please.
Please...
flip 'em off with me!
You can sing, right?
Of course!
All the blank white pages that are set before me
Full of simple questions anyone could answer
It's form over function
But my fingers are trembling anxiously
Wandering alone, I find a crossroads looming ahead
There's no map here to guide me
How am I to know which way will lead to the best path
To walk down
They tell you that your textbooks have the answers that you need
They always seemed so difficult to read
And even as I grow, I'm just as clueless now as I've ever been
Will the answer that I'm searching for
Really scratch this itch, or lead me to more?
If you found yourself inside my shoes
How would you decide which path to ignore?
All the blank white pages that are set before me
Full of simple questions anyone could answer
It's form over function
But my fingers are trembling anxiously
There's no right answer
No one wins or loses
And it's all so simple
I can only march on
And carve out my own path
No more brooding
If I keep on debating, I'll waste my life
If I keep up this struggle, I'll waste my life
Next time: "Three Nocturnal Creatures".