To be honest, this snow is really annoying!
Especially on days when headquarters issues a close patrol order.
Yeah.
You haven't given up on Jacott-san, have you?
Not exactly...
Well, that's fine, isn't it?
You can just keep looking, and even if you can't find her...
...then you can still believe in the best, right?
What?
For a moment there, I thought you looked like Rio-senpai, Kureha-chan.
What's wrong?
Under that cliff, at eleven o'clock. Approximately 400 meters.
Hang in there!
Hang in there, please!
Even her clothes are frozen!
Kanata, remove her coat.
I'll switch coats with her.
Uh, right!
She's...
A Roman soldier!
You actually managed to restore this facility.
You really are the most impressive genius in the history of the academy.
With that, victory is ours!
And it's all because of you, Kannagi Noël-kun.
Noël-chan!
They found her during patrol.
It's a Roman soldier.
Her left leg looks broken.
Hey, her fingers are turning blue!
Frostbite. If we're not careful, she'll lose her fingers.
The Witch of Helvetia...
Leave her to me!
Looks like she'll make it through, somehow.
Her fingers are fine, too.
I'm so glad.
Where's Noël-chan?
She wants to stay with her for a while.
But I wonder why...
She's trying really hard...
...just like how she looks when she fixes the Takemakazuchi.
I see...
A bugle.
She could be scouting...
As I thought.
But, I was really surprised.
Of course you were.
No one thought we'd run into a Roman soldier ther-
No!
This is the first time I've seen a Roman.
Aren't they supposed to be our enemies?
So, I thought they would be scarier looking.
They probably think the same about us in Rome.
But I realized,
when I saw her,
that Romans... aren't so different from us.
Hey, Kanata, you-
Hey, Kana-chan.
It's almost time for the evening call.
They're still arguing over the peace talks, aren't they?
So it seems.
Are we reporting her?
If we do, she'll be taken to the Capital and interrogated.
That can't be helped!
She infiltrated enemy territory during such unstable times!
A soldier should be prepared for torture-
Interrogation.
I will decide how to deal with her.
Please give me some time, Kureha-chan.
Please do not forget, Commander.
We are soldiers.
Can I ask you one thing?
Did you meet anyone else... while carrying her here?
I don't know; I was so focused.
I understand. Thank you.
Tell me, Rio. What would you do?
A Helvetian soldier.
What are you doing?
Where am I?
Am I a prisoner of Helvatia?!
I don't speak Roman.
I see.
So I was caught-
What was that scream?
What's wrong?
She... woke up.
I'm glad.
Imperial Roman Army, Tank Division, 13th Batallion Company
Master Sergeant Aisha Aldola, serial number 1031021.
What did you come here for?
Imperial Roman Army, Officer Aisha Aldola...
What was your mission?
...serial number 1031021.
You have some nerve...
How did it go? Learn anything?
Nothing at all!
Seems like she doesn't understand Helvetian.
All we know is her serial number and that her name is Aisha.
I'm Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann, in charge of this fortress.
You have really nice breasts, my favorite type.
Can I suck and massage them for a bit?
Can I run my fingers all over your body?
W-W-What are you saying, Commander?
Seems like she really doesn't understand Helvetian.
But this is troubling. We can't interrogate her like this.
We need find someone who speaks Roman soon.
Until we can interrogate her and file a report, we'll hold her here.
But...
I thought I would make a gamble.
I don't care what happens.
Aisha-chan, welcome to Clocktower Fortress.
Clocktower fortress?
Yes, Clocktower Fortress.
I see... So I made it here!
Grandmother...
Here!
Oh, maybe it's too hot.
She ate it!
Delicious?
I'll eat your food because it will give me power to flee.
She must be saying it's delicious!
I wonder why.
Kanata's just being her usual self,
but for Noël to warm up to her is...
Perhaps it's her atonement.
Have you ever seen a fossil of an angel?
Angel?
I forgot, they don't understand me...
I should have studied Roman.
I guess you're right.
If we could communicate, we could...
You're working hard.
Oh, Yumina-chan.
Do you have enough help shoveling snow at the Church?
Yes.
The children are working really hard at it.
I'm glad to hear that.
I guess they're growing up, too.
Yes.
People grow as days go by.
Just like the sound of Kanata-san's trumpet...
Rio would say that she still has a long way to go, though.
Oh, weren't you going to Treize to stock up?
Things happened. That trip was a waste of time.
Sounds like you had it rough.
Oh, that reminds me.
I heard this terrible rumor about the Fortress...
Thank you for your audience!
The trumpet sounds wonderful.
I didn't know there were trumpets like that left.
Can I play it?
I think Rio-senpai would allow it, as well.
It's a good trumpet.
Really, it's rare to see such a nice-
Hey, that song was great!
This is wonderful!
Because Iliya-san's sound echoes in me,
and that sound echoes in Rio-senpai, as well.
That very same song!
Not only does it reverberate in Helvetia, but in Rome too!
Sound reverberates.
In Rome and Helvetia, the same way!
Temporary measures.
Danke.
"Dan...ke"?
Yeah, that's right. Danke.
What does "danke" mean?
It means "Thank you".
I knew they'd find out!
This town never bore the full brunt of the war,
but almost everyone here lost parents, siblings, family and friends in the war.
Even if they are nice people,
to the victimes, they are...
Do you remember Mikhail, the distillery owner?
I was at his place until yesterday.
Apparently, the majority of the Helvetian Army is on the move,
heading towards here.
If that's connected to why a Roman scout is here, then,
it would get blown out of proportion.
Either way, we should ask her.
Naomi-san, do you know anyone who speaks Roman?
Of course I do!
I am Yumina.
I am a servant of the Helvetian Orthodox Church.
May a thousands blessings be upon you.
So...
...you're a heretic.
There's only one God.
That greeting is blasphemous.
What did she say?
That was just a greeting.
Enough of that. Quick ask her!
Why are you here?
If you don't tell us, you put everyone here in danger.
If you care about them, then tell us the truth.
I can't tell you about my mission,
but I wanted to see the Angel Fossil located in this town.
She says she came to see the Angel Fossil.
Angel Fossil...
What?
My grandmother was a maiden here at this fortress.
"My grandmother was a maiden at this fortress."
She was captured at the Eastern Front and met my grandfather.
"She was captured at the Eastern Front and met my grandfather."
I listened to her stories as I grew up.
"I grew up listening to her stories."
So I wanted to see the Angel of the Apocalypse that brought judgment
to the world in the past, the one my grandmother spoke of.
That is a mistaken doctrine!
It was the demon that destroyed the world!
Leave that. Just tell us exactly what she said!
She wanted to see the Angel of the Apocalypse that destroyed the world.
That's why she came...
A call to advance?
That code is...
Royal Guard Platoon... 9th Independent Mobile Division...
The Ninth... It can't be!
Colonel Hopkins!
Is he famous?
He's known as the Demon of Vingt.
They say he revived the weapons from the ancient times,
and annihilated three towns in a single night.
It's all right. He doesn't know that you are here.
It's all right.
Regardless, you don't seem to have time to worry about it.
If you don't decide quickly, you'll all be in trouble.
You can either hand her over-
There's nothing to think about!
We are Helvetian Soldiers!
I lost the bet.
I didn't make it in time, Rio.
Please hold on!
Rio-senpai didn't want anyone else to suffer.
She said that that's why she's doing what she can.
Isn't that why she left?
Even then, I don't want this to happen!
We're all the same!
We're all in this together!
These are my orders as Commander of the 1121st Platoon.
This order is by my own judgment. I will take full responsibility for it.
Do you all understand?
I am Commander of the 1121st Platoon, Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann.
Several days ago, a Roman scout was captured in Treize.
Unfortunately, due to an accident during questioning... we couldn't confirm some details.
Coincidentally, we've received information from a witness that a Roman soldier is in Seize.
Does this ring a bell?
No, Colonel.
Understood.
As of this moment, the 1121st Fortress,
is under the control of the 9th Independent Mobile Division.
Don't raise your voice so suddenly.
I'm sorry.
Aisha-san just told me about the legend of the Flame Maidens.
It's strange... but according to her-
Search thoroughly!
Did you find her?
Search there, too!
Nothing over here!
Find her!
Open this door!
She has to be here somewhere!
Tighten security!
She said that she hasn't asked for your name yet.
Noël... Noël Kannagi?
Yeah...
You're the Invisible Reaper?
The Invisible Reaper?
A rat?
Noël-san?
H-Hello?
This is the 1121st Fortress.
A large contingent of Roman soldiers has appeared at the Seize's border, in Nomansland?
Next time: Resound in the Blue Skies