Wow, flowers!
So pretty!
Hey, Rikka.
Hm?
When you grow up,
what do you want to be?
I wanna be a doctor like Mommy!
I want to help sick people get better!
Hey, traveling the world as a photographer like me is pretty fun, too!
I wanna be like Mommy!
Thank you, that makes me happy.
But being a doctor takes looooooooooads of studying!
It's no cakewalk!
I can handle it!
I see...
I'm gonna study really hard!
And I'm gonna be a doctor!
Oh, the test results are out.
And Rikka's in first place, right?
Midterm Test Top 10 Scores
2nd    Ishikawa Rikka
2nd: Ishikawa Rikka
Huh?
Huuuuuuuh?!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
A Dream or a Promise?
Rikka's Numerous Woes!
Solitaire
I feel like I shouldn't say anything...
Rikka...
We should gently leave her be.
That's right...
This jewel may be mysterious,
but I feel like I've seen it in Trump Kingdom's castle.
Could it be a Royal Crystal?
What might that be?
It's a legendary jewel that only the royal family is allowed to possess.
There are five crystals in all,
and it's said that something amazing will happen when all are gathered together!
And this is a Royal Crystal...
Or it looks like it, at least.
I've only seen them once myself, so I can't say for sure.
Not much to do about that.
Sorry, I'm kinda hungry.
Oh yeah!
Mom said to get everyone together for dinner!
Oh, splendid!
How about you, Rikka?
Sorry...
I have things to do, so I'll leave early.
Wait for me!
I'm a tad worried.
diner
Pig's Tail
I'm home!
Oh, welcome home.
Who's this?
Rikka's mom!
Are you done with work today?
No.
When I get a break,
I need to go back home for a change of clothes and go right back to the hospital.
Sounds busy.
The hospital?
Rikka's mother works at a large hospital as a doctor.
Is Yuuzou doing well?
According to his letters, yes.
You don't need to worry about him.
But Rikka, on the other hand...
What happened to Rikka?!
Well, uh...
It's not anything... big, really.
I just hear her shouting suddenly from her room,
or sleep talking in some strange language,
so I wonder if she's all right.
Sorry, I've got stuff I need to do, so I'll go on ahead.
Wait, Rikka!
What's up with Rikka?
Is she that torn up about not being first on the exam?
It's more than that to Rikka.
She dreams of being a great doctor like her mom.
And to do that, you have to be smart enough to rank first in the school!
It's a real issue if her grades fall!
Is that so?
Rikka's mom is worried too,
so I wonder what the problem is.
There's only one answer!
Answer?
That is...
What is?
Rikka's gone bad!
Huh?
I've seen it on TV!
Kids her age go rotten at the smallest chances!
Whatchoo lookin' at?!
No way.
Bad news!
We saw Rikka walk into a big building earlier!
And we heard lots of loud, serious slapping sounds!
She's... fighting!
She's a bad apple!
It can't be true!
This is the place!
Your whole life's ahead of you, Rikka!
Huh?
It's you girls...
The tail feathers of the copper pheasant are long,
Competitive karuta?
What's that?
It's a game where you take cards based on the poems from the Hundred Poets.
long as the nights I spend alone
It's not just a game!
Sorry.
Competitive karuta is a full-fledged sport.
So, the shouting in your room was...
Me practicing with Rachel.
Who's a rotten apple, now?
But I did not know you had begun playing karuta.
I got interested when I read a book on the Hundred Poets.
I read it for my studies,
but all of the bittersweet love poems stole my heart!
I couldn't put it down!
And while I was researching it,
I learned about competitive karuta.
And she registered here before I knew it!
How very like you, Rikka.
So that's why your studies have been lacking.
Yeah, that's the thing.
I want to become a doctor,
so I don't have the time for distractions.
Rikka...
That was the plan, at least!
But it's so fun that I can't stop!
But... I'm planning to quit.
Nothing's more important to me than my promise with Mom.
In a week, they'll hold a match against the queen.
Match Against
the Queen
I'll test my strength there,
and then I'll quit!
Rikka, this queen...
She's the strongest female karuta player in the country.
The princess enjoyed karuta as well, and played it often...
There might be a clue there!
She was interested in karuta despite being from the Trump Kingdom?
We've got it.
After one week, then?
Match Against
the Queen
In that week,
we'll help you balance karuta and studying!
You girls!
The most valuable skills in competitive karuta...
are memorization, precision, and endurance.
I have crafted a training schedule for this week.
The rules of a match are simple.
Line up 25 cards on each player's sides.
The player who takes all of her cards first, wins.
You have fifteen minutes to memorize your arrangements.
That short?
I've got it.
Already?
Very well.
The drops from a light shower
That was fast!
Before wisps of fog
rise in the autumn dusk
That was a one-syllable card.
There's only one poem that fits that syllable!
Now, read the next one!
Perfect whiteness laid on Fuji's
lofty peak by a drift of falling snow
Good News For People Who Don't Get Math
Japanese for Dummies
Careful Selection Series    Math Problem Compilation
Math ~Unexplored Territory~
Careful Selection
Series
Japanese Problem
Compilation
Science    Let's Study Science!
The Easiest To Understand Math In The World (Probably)
Shine!    Second Year Middle      100 English Problems
Society
Fun English
Hello, Ishikawa speaking.
Oh?
Rub my shoulders.
Right away.
Where's my melon juice?
Get it yourself.
Right here, Madam Regina.
Don't be a brown-noser!
Really, King Selfish's daughter, here?
Nobody told me!
Hey, buy me some cream puffs.
Excuse me?
If that's how you'll be,
I'll tell Daddy on you.
Ira! Bring your stuff!
Where is he?!
Thank you.
I feel like I've improved because of your help.
She said "Good luck."
It's the queen!
Good day, everyone.
That woman is...
The queen.
Now then, we shall begin our matches against the queen.
It's rare to get the chance to battle against the most skilled woman in the country.
Treat it as a good experience.
Yes.
I can feel the tension from here.
The waves are gathered
The queen got one?
She's fast.
It drives the grass
Though I did not pray
As I wait for her
Thank you very much.
That's how the queen plays...
That was really intense!
It was just like a sport!
She wasn't just fast.
It's how she set up her cards, too.
She's on a whole different level!
I won't stand a chance against her!
Rikka...
That woman...
What about her?
I knew I felt something about her.
Can I get an autograph?
I'm sorry.
I decline such offers.
I see...
Because you said you were coming, I awaited you,
but only the moon came to greet me at the cold light of dawn!
Everyone praises and esteems me!
And yet, why?
Why am I a queen with no king to match me?
It's because every man in the world is too weak!
That's why I'll never find love!
No, it's because I'm too picky and set hurdles too high.
Aw, just be picky.
I will grant your desire.
Grant me your darkness!
I think I'll get serious.
What?
I felt a dark heartbeat!
It's you!
Let's go, everyone!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor karuta card who has lost her love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
There you are!
You insolent children dare challenge me?
Very well!
We shall battle in karuta!
Huh?
Hey, who said you could—
Come to me, my karuta cards!
Listen to me!
Now, we fight!
We're playing karuta?!
The only relief
Found it!
Aaaaaah!
Cure Heart!
Even the gaps in the shutters are too cruel to let the dawn's light in
We have to get the cards first!
Under a thatched roof of a makeshift hut in an autumn field
It's that one!
Get "My sleeves are wet, not just from the dew!"
This one?
Unfortunate.
That one is "My life passes by in vain as I watch the long rains fall."
It's the wrong card!
I'll give you one of mine!
Cure Sword!
For you, I head out
I know this one!
That's cheating!
This is known as covering!
It is a legitimate technique!
Soon I will cease to be
There!
Spring has passed
When I look up
Theeere!
Is it the same moon that rose on Mount Mikasa?
You're stealin' too much spotlight.
We can't put up a fight!
We're fighting the queen.
Of course I can't...
It's all right.
That's right.
You practiced hard.
We're rooting for you.
You girls...
Cure Diamond,
show us the fruits of your effort!
Got it!
Flower's colors have faded away
While in idle thought,
This one...
is the one I got wrong before!
I won't allow you!
Cure Diamond!
How could this be?
I got it!
Ouch!
Cure Heart!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Waaaah!
Drat!
Today's been a complete mess!
Thank you very much.
It's been a while since I've had such a fun match.
But you've got a long way to go before you can defeat me.
Here, take these.
They're my favorite cards.
Practice with these.
Thank you very much!
Goodbye, then.
The queen was really strong!
But you put up a good fight!
The cards?!
A Royal Crystal?
My, how pretty!
It's too bad.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Don't think you can pull the wool over your mother's eyes.
It's not what you think!
Rikka didn't mean anything bad...
There's a good explanation for this...
I'm sorry I lied to you.
But I'm done now.
I'll go back to studying to be a doctor!
Really, this girl.
I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at all.
It's good that you found something fun.
Mom?
You're still a child,
so do what you want.
If you like karuta, feel free to continue.
And if you find something else you like,
put everything you've got into it, too!
You can do anything you put your mind to.
That's right.
It's good to have a lot of dreams.
Like wanting to be a photographer over a doctor!
Dad!
I'm back.
Your father just called last night to say he'd be home the next day.
Doing what you want too much can be a real bother.
Aww, it's no problem.
I've got a lot of stories to tell.
Huh?
And I'd like to hear some of your stories, Rikka.
Wait, Dad!
Me too!
Mom, you too?
I'm gonna try a bunch of different things!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Makopi's starring in a movie?!
A Precure, an idol, and a student?
I can't help but worry!
Dokidoki Precure:
Super Busy!
Makoto's Idol Life!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!