I'm leaving now.
Morning!
Oh, good morning, Futa... ba?
Youko, good morning!
I Am Graduating
From Bread Crusts
Did you hear, Youko?
It's such a nice day,
but it's supposed to rain in the afternoon.
What a shame!
Wah, what are you doing?
Ow, that hurts!
Wh-What is the matter
with you, Futaba?
Wh-What do you mean?
What's the matter with you,
Youko?
What's the matter with me?
Morning...
Man, I couldn't peel myself
out of bed this morning.
I deserve an award
for going to school today.
Oh, good morning, Hayama!
You're so polite!
Oh, I see what's going on here.
What is it?
Is this some kind of surprise?
Like there's a hidden camera
recording my reaction?
Goodness gracious.
You can put an end
to this charade.
I'm not going to fall for it.
Oh, Youko is acting strangely!
She said "goodness gracious"!
This coming from you?!
I finished my
crocheted lace yesterday!
It took two whole months!
Crocheting lace?
Why don't you just buy it?
Aww, this is my hobby!
Look, isn't it just the cutest?
Oh man, what a girly hobby.
Hmm?
What's the matter, Youko?
They're even like this
when I'm not around.
What is the matter
with those two?
U-Um...
Hmm?
H-H-Hayama...
W-Well...
What's up, Nishiyama?
Y-You're the last one...
to turn in the worksheet.
I have to turn
them all in together, so...
Jeez, I haven't done it yet.
Why don't you do it for me,
Nishiyama?
You're class rep, right?
Huh? B-But...
Ah, I get it.
This is a dream.
You're making it difficult for Nishiyama
by not turning it in.
That won't do...
Huh?
Oh, fine.
I'll do it now.
What a terrible dream.
Hayama.
Darn that Hayama!
What a troublemaker! Curse her!
I'll show her what I'm like
when I'm not holding back.
Just watch me!
What's this?
Hey, Hayama!
Look how much trouble
you're causing Nishiyama!
Hurry up and turn it in!
I'm doing it now.
Nishiyama's not class representative
because she wants to be!
She was forced into the job because
nobody else wanted all the extra work!
Nishiyama's really timid,
so she couldn't say no.
Maybe they haven't changed
all that much, after all.
I'm bushed!
Maybe I'll ditch afternoon classes.
Goodness, no!
You should go to class.
So lazy...
I-I'm still not used to
these two acting like this.
But if this is a dream,
what is everybody else like?
Whoo! I'm so pissed off!
I hate this awful world!
Maybe I'll break
all the school windows!
If I steal a motorcycle and don't know
how to ride it, it's the world's fault!
Hayama's sister
is the school's top delinquent, isn't she?
Delinquent?
She even comes to school.
Talk about devoted.
Oh? Yamaji!
What, Nishikawa?
Address your teachers properly.
Wh-What's this?
Violence at school?
Youko, what are you doing?
You just punched a teacher!
Oh my, I couldn't help myself.
But he's a teacher!
And I didn't punch him.
I slapped him.
Honestly!
That's what you're clarifying?
What is this?!
It's an offense to hit a teacher!
Report to the faculty room
immediately!
If there's a problem,
they can come see me.
Why are you acting so rebellious?!
Youko! Stop it!
Now, now.
What's all the commotion?
School is starting soon.
Return to your classrooms.
Or maybe...
You want to be punished
by Ms. Shino?
And that's what happened
in the dream.
My dream!
That was your dream?!
Of course it was.
I'd never do such a thing.
R-Right...
Wasn't it interesting?
It's too bad I woke up
right when it was getting good.
Wasn't my personality
pretty terrible?
Well, it was a dream.
I wasn't too different
from the real me.
You weren't even there, Futaba.
Don't say that!
Central Shopping Plaza
It does seem pretty fun
to be a different you, though.
Especially since you're usually
hiding your true self, right?
Oh, there she is! Futaba!
Sakura!
Well, how do I look?
I tried changing up my image!
Oh, how cute.
Yeah, I think I nailed it!
I'm gonna be an idol
when I grow up, after all.
Ah, you mentioned that.
So could you listen to me sing?
I need to get used to singing
in front of people so I don't get nervous.
I'm in full bloom!
My charm is never-ending!
I won't let you
even glance at other girls!
Today and tomorrow,
forever and ever!
Ugh... A recital...
Unlike my sister, she's way off...
Sa... Sakura!
Why don't you practice before
performing in front of people?
Yeah, they say to wear a bucket
on your head to cure tone-deafness.
Try that!
Wh... What's this?
A bucket...
So I should sing like this?
Y-Yeah.
That's what I heard.
I'm in full bloom!
I'm in full bloo—
Sakura?
F-Futaba?
I might throw up.
Good thing we have a bucket!
Not quite right.
I tried doing it like Sakura.
Oh, then how about this?
Yeah?
Well, it doesn't get in the way...
Want to try on glasses too?
Hayama. Glasses.
You can't have braids
without glasses.
Maybe I should cut it shorter.
Why would you do that?!
How could you cut your hair?
I thought it would be
a nice change.
I've got split ends, anyway.
And long hair uses a lot of shampoo and water,
which can get expensive.
B-But...
It would be a waste
to cut your long hair.
You've been growing it out
since you were young.
Right?
It would be a waste.
You can't go back
once you've cut it, either.
Your normal hair style
fits you best, Miss Youko.
You think so?
A princess haircut is a must for a rich girl,
even if you aren't one anymore.
Not because it looks good on me?
Thank you very much!
I'm not just so-so anymore!
Don't you think I'm a pro
at working part-time?
You're amazing, Miss Youko.
Truly the best in the world
at everything you do.
What a professional!
At working part-time?
Well, at first I couldn't believe
she had a job at all.
This environment has probably been
good for her development.
Oh, found it!
Here it is!
This is the shop from the book.
Welcome!
Wow!
Which one should I get?
Miss Youko?
Ni...
Nishikawa?
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Huh? Who's that?
A school friend... from before.
Oh, Osakabe!
Hmm? You know her?
Huh? Um, well, we were in
the same grade at my old school.
Oh, Mannenrou Girls' Academy, right?
The rich girl school.
Even rich girls work part-time?
Oh, you're here learning
how the world works?
No, I can no longer
call myself a rich girl.
I'm working for the income.
Oh...
Strawberry
Tart
These two cakes are our
seasonal recommendations.
Oh. I'll have those, please.
Miss Youko!
Miss Youko's a real pro!
Um...
You can contact me here,
just in case.
Let me know if there's
anything I can do for you.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
M-Miss Youko!
You were amazing!
A total pro! You did great!
O-Of course.
I have leveled up.
This is nothing!
I'm a pro part-timer!
Oh, even though all you have is pride,
you tried so hard!
I-I'm going to take a short break.
I need a drink.
That's mayonnaise!
I heard you had it rough yesterday.
It was fine.
It's true that I don't want
to be seen like this.
But I can't go back to my old life.
Because who I am now
is the real me.
Miss Youko...
Morning!
What a wonderful day it is!
Teeheehee. Teehee!
Teeheehee, ow ow ow!
Same reaction as in the dream.
You don't have
enough feminine charm!
Wh-What do you mean?
Do you even have to ask
when you're eating like that?!
Even I'm trying my best
to become an idol by doing this!
Futaba, why don't you
try hard at something too?
That's what happened.
I see...
I was shocked to hear that I didn't
have enough feminine charm,
so I wanted to show people
that I'm a girl.
Teehee!
Miss Youko is trying her best,
so I thought I could try my best too!
Futaba!
Oh my! The birdies
are having a little chat!
Hayama is all polka-dotted!
Are those hives?!
Hey, these are good.
Aren't they?
Oh, do you want some, Odagiri?
It's okay. I'm satisfied
just by the offer!
Teehee!
Huh?! What's the matter, Odagiri?
Are you feeling sick?
It's almost lunchtime,
so I shouldn't eat sweets now.
Are you sure?!
They're burnt milk caramels!
Yup. I'm okay.
You're drooling!
Oh, so you're not very feminine?
You should've just
asked me for pointers.
I've got a health and beauty regimen.
You do?
I take rose supplements to smell better,
do stretches to maintain my figure,
and regularly do sit-ups
and use dumbbells.
I also do that and this and that.
Y-You do all that?
Amazing! You really give it your all!
Y-Yeah, I'm trying hard!
What's wrong with that?!
My lucky number's three.
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
My lucky color is yellow.
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
What are you looking at?
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
Lucky Number
Lucky Color
Your lucky number today is 3.
Your actions will make things better.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
My horoscope.
Girls like this kind of thing, right?
That's true.
Oh, Futaba Odagiri.
You're not
stopping by Mr. Stuffed's?
Huh?
There's a new curry challenge.
If you finish three kilos, it's free!
Three! Yellow!
No, that's not related.
Um, I-I can't.
What?!
I couldn't finish three kilos of food.
I am a girl, after all.
What are you saying?
Are you mocking me?
You're Futaba Odagiri!
Don't say you can't finish it.
That's rude to those
who've lost to you!
It's fine. Go ahead.
Yes.
You're at your best when
you're shining brilliantly.
Okay!
Stuffed Hut
Delicious!
Her feminine charm
is at absolute zero.
Stuffed Hut
Thanks for the food!
I won't lose next time!
Futaba!
I heard that you wanted
to increase your feminine charm.
Ahh... Err...
I made this for you.
Wait!
It's probably a special soup that'll
raise my feminine charm or something, right?
What?
Nope! It's a drink!
Doesn't make a difference!
Here.
The color! And the smell!
I brought some for everyone.
What happened to you?
You think...
...our feminine charm went up?
Anyway, what are you
doing here so early, Yuu?
Daddy has a job for your father!
Oh my, for my father?
That's great, Miss Youko!
Having connections is great, isn't it?
Thank you so much.
How can I repay you?
Huh?!
Um, maybe you could
sign a marriage application?
Huh?
Well, you know!
It'll be just for fun,
like playing pretend!
Jeez, I'd be okay with that
any time!
Let's go submit
our marriage application.
Let go of me!
I've been learning
how to sing, you know!
Aren't you head over heels?!
Well, looks like that's his fate.
I am the daughter
of the Nishikawa family.
My father is a company employee,
and I'm his only daughter.
Whoa!
Wow, that's so normal.
I'm just the same as you now.
I won't be so easily captivated
by food like I used to—
U-Um...
Nishikawa... Um...
This is thanks
for your Valentine's gift!
Dietary Supplement Cookies
Huh?
I thought I should get you cookies,
but I wanted them to be useful too.
A-A-Are these for me?
Miss Youko.
She's super happy.
Wait, isn't White Day next week?
What?!
Are you still thinking about it?
I'm truly pitiful.
I haven't changed a bit
since I met you two.
Huh?
You've definitely changed.
Really?
When we first met, you said,
"Why are you eating here too?
How bothersome!"
You were way more like a rich girl.
And I thought,
here is a protected species.
What?
What are you saying, Futaba?
You mean endangered species.
What? But you'd find a lot
if you looked in the right places.
When did we start
talking about animals? Um...
If they're an endangered species,
maybe they'll go extinct.
That's why we need to protect them.
Um, why are you
talking about animals?
Oh!
Found another endangered species!
Huh?!
Yeah, but it'd be annoying
if there were a lot of them.
What would be annoying?
Aren't they talking about you?
Hey!
Kondou is a different kind
of protected species.
Why are you wearing
that again, Sonobe?!
And that's a rare beast.
We shouldn't get too close.
Sonobe!
Let's go, Miss Youko.
Don't feed the animals.
And that's...
Pretty sure that one's poisonous.
Run away!
Huh? What?
Hayama! Futaba!
Wait for me!
saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
I am graduating from bread crusts!
Oh...
I'm trying instant food today.
Wow!
Yakisoba Noodles
She's done it!
She put the sauce in first!
What she said before...
It's all over!
Huh? What?
Oh, look.
She's sulking.
I don't even like instant noodles.
They're such a hassle anyway!
Bread crusts are more abundant
and taste delicious.
You brought some?!
Thank you very much!