Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Morning, Haruka!
Morning, Yuu-chan.
Another Sakura Colour
Here.
Thanks for letting me borrow your notebook.
Mathematics
Takayama Haruka
Geez.
Mathematics
Takayama Haruka
Do it yourself next time.
I only used it for the first half,
and then I did the rest myself.
Really?
Really!
I'll show you!
Huh?
It's not here.
Classics
Takayama H
Yuu-chan, you wrote your maths solutions in my classics notebook!
Man, I messed up!
Good morning.
Scooters
Bicycles
Haruka, Yuu, G'morn!
G'morn!
Ah, Shizuku-chan, morning!
Morning!
What's up with Shizuku-chan?
She's not acting like her usual self.
She was totally smiling!
Normally Shizuku-chan would be like...
M-Morning...
Ah, Kaede playing a pretty girl...
I can see Yuzu doing that, but if Haruka and Yuu also do it...
Mornin' girls!
Ah, Kotone-chan!
You scared me to death!
Hey, Kotone-chan,
Shizuku-chan's acting strange.
Did something happen?
We had a quarrel last night.
It seems she's angry.
How can they act like this after having a quarrel?
You know, I was freeloading at Shizuku-chan's home.
Shizuku-chan, go ahead and take your bath.
Did she fall asleep?
Time to doodle!
Of course she'd get angry!
I haven't finished yet.
She's sleeping soundly, huh?
Shizuku-chan, I like your home.
Even if it's a little small, it's cute and warm.
Your mother is kind too.
And most importantly,
it's close to school.
I'm really grateful.
Hey, what's going on?!
Suddenly kissing her cheek...
Were you drunk or something?
Kotone, she probably doesn't want someone she dislikes doing that.
But we're really close.
You know, just like those two.
Right?
Ah, that's-
No way.
I wouldn't do that either.
That was surprising.
I had no idea Kotone-chan and
Shizuku-chan had a secret just like ours.
Isn't it kind of different, though?
After all, it seems like Shizuku-chan got angry.
Yuu-chan, you don't like it either?
Why do you keep asking over and over again?
You're so persistent.
Because if you don't like it, I want you to say so...
Ah, that's what you meant by us being kind of different!
What are you assuming about us?
I'll go on ahead.
Wait, Yuu-chan!
Ah, Shizuku-chan!
Yuu-chan, Haruka-chan...
She really is angry.
Her eyebrows give it away.
H-How about this?
She's angry.
Look at her mouth.
You heard it from Kotone.
She's such a loudmouth.
I always look sour,
so I look even more so when I get angry.
Everyone is afraid of me, so I usually try to fake a smile.
Don't worry about it!
Shizuku-chan, since you're so cute, just act like your usual self!
Yuu-chan...
Close to Yuu-chan...
Close to Yuu-chan!
After all, some people's feelings are a lot more obvious.
I-I know that I'm also at fault for ignoring her.
But saying that she likes my home because it's close to school...
It's as if anyone's home would be okay as long as it's close to school!
You wouldn't kiss just anyone for letting you freeload, would you?
At least she's not angry because Kotone kissed her on the cheek!
However, I can't tell anyone about these thoughts.
She just told us, though.
Shizuku-chan, are you fine with fighting with Kotone-chan?
The situation won't change if you just keep running from it!
If that's the case, Sonoda,
it seems you haven't turned in your maths and classics homework.
Time for a scolding!
Sensei!
Haruka didn't turn in her classics assignment either!
Takayama come with me, too!
I would have turned it in if Yuu-chan had written in her own notebook!
Homework?
That's right, I have maths next.
I'll have to get my notebook back.
Hey, I went to the cafe in front of the station today-
Everyone!
I brought the maths notebooks!
Take them!
Of all people to be giving them out right now...
Huh, there's one left.
I wonder whose it is.
Go away, go away, go away, go away...
Go away
At least leave the notebook!
She's still going to tease me?
But maybe she took it with her because she wants to talk with me.
Maybe she wants to tell me that there's some other reason,
and that she actually thinks the same thing.
no
No.
I'm the one who wants to talk, not her.
You haven't talked to me since morning,
so I wondered if you'd follow me.
What is it?
I just want my notebook back already.
I'm sorry.
You didn't like me kissing you, did you?
I just wanted to say that.
After all, I want to be able to talk with you.
Shall we go back to the classroom-
That's not it!
I-I'm not angry because you kissed me.
Are you really staying at my house only because I'm close to school?
Or is it because my mum is kind?
Are we only living together for those reasons?!
It's as if you don't care about me at all!
Shuffle
Why are you backing away?
Fire Extinguisher
I don't know.
Shizuku-chan, behind you!
Why did I have to get yelled at too?
I wonder what happened to Shizuku-chan.
Don't change the subject!
That voice...
Shizuku-chan, what happen-
This is serious!
I caught you.
And now I know why you were angry, Shizuku-chan.
Should I correct what I did yesterday?
Wait!
I'm actually kind of glad that you like
my house because it's close to school,
so let's forget about that.
But let's do something different than yesterday.
On the mouth?
Shizuku-chan, even though it's small, I like it because you're there.
I like the warmth and your mother.
Shizuku-chan, I like your home because you are there.
S-Should we get out of here?
They'll get upset if they find out that they were seen.
This reminds me of when Yuu-chan and I kissed.
Why?
Why is she grabbing my hand?
Could it be she wants to kiss too?
No, that can't be it.
Yeah, unlike me, Yuu-chan isn't a girl who likes kissing.
But...
Ah, that's what you meant by us being a bit different!
What are you assuming about us?
I'll go on ahead.
Which is it?!
I imagined something strange.
If I bring my face closer to hers, I might find out.
She closed her eyes!
Hey, Yuu-chan!
If Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan turned out like that,
it means that right about now, Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan are...!
That looks delicious.
Want a taste?
Just having a taste may not be enough.
If it's you, Kaede...
Ohh!
I wouldn't expect that.
Hey!
Give my Pokitz back!
That was the last one!
I took it already.
See, they were!
Another Sakura Colour                              The End
Haruka!
Show me your notebook!
I'll copy your answers!
Again?!
We have a test next week, so do it yourself!
Please!
No!
High school is different from middle school.
If you fail, you will have to repeat the grade.
I don't mind repeating the grade.
Yuu-chan, then you'd be a year behind!
Then I could act like you are younger than me!
Why does that make you so happy?
1st Year Student                                                                                            2nd Year Student
Yuu-chan repeating a year.
Haruka!
Oh my.
Sonoda-san, my former classmate.
You're addressing a second-year student with just her name?
I'm sorry, Haruka-oneesama!
I thought I'd ask you to fix my necktie...
Bang
Calling me Onee-sama!
That's unfair!
What?
After School with Hari-chan
Since Yuu-chan's lonely, she visits me every time we have break.
Yuu, you have to hurry back.
No!
I don't want to leave Haruka-oneesama!
But our high school is closing in three years,
and we won't have any younger students,
so wouldn't she end up being a dropout?
Dropout
I wanted Yuu-chan to call me Onee-sama!
I wanted to fix her tie for her!
What's she going on about?
All of this will be in the test.
Neutralisation
Ionisation
Combination of hydrochloric acid and sodium hydroxide
That's everything.
Yuu-chan can't drop out!
I'll have to strengthen my resolve and make her study on her own!
If Yuu-chan drops out,
I'll no longer have a reason to go to this school.
Haruka!
Show me your notes!
Okay!
No!
Ah, I was so close!
Trying to trick me with your charm is cowardly.
What's so enjoyable about toying with people's hearts?
I wonder if Shizuku-chan and Kotone-chan will lend me theirs!
Angry
We'll be starting a study group for you after school today!
What?!
Let's begin the study group.
Everyone, let's study hard for the test!
Yeah!
Hey, Yuu-chan, wake up.
Mathematics
Yuu-chan, don't sleep!
Who do you think we're having this study group for?
Bump
She seems to be tired!
Wake her up!
Geez!
Yuu-chan, wake up!
Why are you sleeping?!
You don't want to be a dropout, do you?!
I know...
Harupoppo, how do you do this?
Ah, you use the thing we learned earlier.
The one on this page.
Use this formula for it.
I see! Thanks!
Not at all.
Yuu-chan, are you doing okay?
Yuzu-chan, what are you trying to pull while we're studying?
You're asking me?!
What can I do to keep Yuu-chan from falling asleep?
That's Hari-chan, which Yuu-chan said she likes.
I wonder what Hari-chan is.
Bear
A bear?
A raccoon dog?
Raccoon dog
What's that thing on its back?
Even though it's really popular these days,
I have no clue what it is.
Hey, Shizuku-chan.
That thing on your bag,
is it a bird?
A pig?
A cow?
A fox?
A raccoon dog?
Grumble
She answers with her stomach, huh?
So it's a raccoon dog?
It's a hedgehog!
So it's a hedgehog?!
I know!
Yuu-chan, wake up!
Yuu-chan, I drew Hari-chan to keep you from sleeping.
This makes it less boring, doesn't it?
Mathematics
Takayama Haruka
Hari-chan?!
Show me!
No!
What's this!
Doesn't look like it at all!
It's scary!
It didn't work.
Of course!
Yuu's still sleeping.
Should we start with a subject Yuu likes?
Uh, a subject that Yuu likes...
I know! I know!
Yuu-chan said she likes PE!
That won't be on the test.
I see! PE!
Let's go out and play volleyball!
I'll play volleyball!
What?
Weren't we supposed to be studying?
Also, the baseball club is playing outside.
The riding club may be running around too.
Don't they have practice grounds?
It'll be okay!
Club activities are suspended before tests!
But we won't be okay!
The tests are coming up!
Often: frequently; Understand...
Yuu-chan likes volleyball, so the plan is to
memorise chemical symbols while we play.
Oh, I see.
Nice, Haruka.
Here I go!
Hydrogen!
H.
Water!
H20.
Carbon dioxide!
No idea!
Let's start with easier questions!
Yeah!
Bring it on!
Yuu-chan, answer the next one properly!
You'll be yelled at if you can't answer!
Leave it to me!
Here it comes!
Hey!
What are you doing right before the tests?!
We're sorry.
Studying while playing sports was probably a bad idea.
We'll just have to study normally, huh?
That doesn't work, she'll just fall asleep.
In short, she'll just have to memorise everything,
so she'll have to study while doing something memorable.
For example?
Something embarrassing?
Just like what you're doing right now?
Yeah, you definitely won't forget that.
I have to think hard.
Something embarrassing for Yuu-chan...
Try translating this one.
You can use a dictionary.
If you can't do it, I'll do what the sentence says.
Erm...
She will...
...hit...
...three times...
What's "her hips"?
Her hi...
Hi?
Hi...
You don't know?
Do you want me to show you with my body?
What's this?!
Bang
Too embarrassing!
Haruka?!
I wonder what Harupoppo's thinking.
But if that prevents Yuu-chan from dropping out...
No, it's too strange.
That's right!
More! More!
It has to be something even more embarrassing...
Are you all right?
Are you breathing?
Embarrassing...
Why are you talking to her like she were dead?
With 2 H2 and O2, what will the coefficient be here?
Three!
Wrong!
Okay, take one off.
N-No way...
There's no way around the punishment.
It's for your own good.
O-Okay...
Should I help?
I'm... embarrassed.
Getting naked alone is embarrassing.
I'll get naked with you.
Okay...
What are you making me think?!
Yuzu-chan, you pervert!
Do you have something against me?!
It's this late already, huh?
It's almost time to go home, huh?
Let's go, everyone.
It's finally over!
Let's buy Pokitz on the way home!
Ah, Yuu-chan and I will stay behind.
I didn't hear that!
We'll go on ahead, then.
Bye bye!
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Y-Yuu-chan, you haven't forgotten our secret, have you?!
W-What's come over you?
Y-You know,
if you study while k-kissing,
I thought you might remember better.
What's with that reaction?!
I wouldn't have to do this if you'd study seriously in the first place!
Why are you moving away from me?!
Aren't you saying that just because you want to kiss?
You're wrong!
It's not because I want to pester you!
It's because I don't want you to drop out of school!
I'm telling you to study because I want to spend my high school life with you!
We'll actually study, right?
Y-Yeah.
I'll ask you a question, then answer after kissing.
Fill in the blank.
Translate "May I go with you?"
Got it?
Here I go!
It's so long I can't answer...
It's "go"?
Correct.
Next,
correct the word in the brackets.
Translate "I want one more piece of paper."
More.
Correct.
More, more!
You want more?
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yuu-chan, what's up?
Let's go home.
Thank you.
One week later
English
I've answered this question before!
I wonder if Yuu-chan did it without falling asleep.
She's thinking about it!
Bang
Takayama-san?!
Geez, that Yuu-chan!
After School with Hari-chan                        The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Sonoda Yuu here!
You're so cute, Yuu-chan.
Kotone-chan, why are you here?
Well, I didn't really get to talk last week.
It's because you keep saying the same thing over and over again.
But Shizuku-chan is so cute!
I know that already!
You're so cute when you're angry, Yuu-chan!
Next time, Trick 3.
The President is Onee-chan
Pool Cleaning Promise
"The President is Onee-chan" and "Pool Cleaning Promise".
Look forward to it!