Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Since it's the "Fall of Reading",
I've been getting my hands on a lot of books lately...
Whoa, how rare.
But the cost really adds up, even if it's for a good cause.
You don't have to buy them.
Can't you just borrow them at the library?
They might actually have some stuff you want to read.
Well, I doubt libraries have manga, though.
"Reading", right?
As in, reading books...
That Kind
of Feeling
Studying for Test
Ugh...
I can't concentrate.
Well, breaks are important, too...
Like now.
I think I'll play some games for a change of mood.
Ah!
It's Kuroi-sensei.
Hey!
Stop playing games and study!
If you get bad grades, I'm going to be mad!
Crap!
There are spying eyes everywhere!
How could you, Sensei!?
The game doesn't seem as fun with all the interruptions.
Sensei, when you were a student, how did you study for tests?
When I couldn't understand something, I played or slept.
Really nothing in particular.
You're just like me.
But now as a teacher, the tables have turned.
I kind of understand that, but it's so unfair!
I'm thinking about setting goals and...
...slowly working my way toward them this time.
Onee-chan, can you help me on the parts I don't understand?
Do you want to do it together, then?
So, in this case, the value of 'x' becomes...
What is it?
I was just thinking that the drama episode has already started.
Today is about how the protagonist gets mentioned in a weekly magazine,
and rumors of her pregnancy spread.
Hmm...
Do you want to watch TV, then?
No, it's okay.
I'm recording it.
*poke*
Um, uh...
I get sleepy when I see a lot of things in a row that I don't get...
So, you're always sleepy?
Ehehe...
Maybe I shouldn't go all-out from the beginning and just call it a night.
Okay.
And thus your motivation has gone down a few more levels.
Mm, I really can't focus!
All right!
Eh?
How to study for tests?
I was wondering what you did, Miyuki-san.
Let's see...
If you're overly conscious about it, you'll wear yourself out.
So for me, I try to stick to my regular routine.
I'm pretty confident about today.
Like, I feel so at ease.
Isn't your "daily routine" pretty bad?
You didn't do anything, did you?
Eh?
Even though she puts on such a cute face?
Yep.
And she's got poison on her claws, too.
So she has a pretty scary side, too...
Yo!
Oh, Kagami.
How did you do?
I didn't do too good this time, although I maintained my rank.
So this happens to Kagami, too...
Onee-chan stuck around to help me this time.
Thanks to that, I did better than usual this time.
How about you?
Surprisingly, I didn't do too well this time.
I was pretty confident, too.
It's not surprising at all...
Rather, it was expected.
I was under the impression that people are attracted to those similar to themselves.
Hm?
For example, Kagami and Miyuki-san are both class representatives.
And Kagami and I both like games.
Well, the genres differ.
You like gal-games and RPGs, while I like shooting games.
I thought Tsukasa and I were both stupid...
But the gap has definitely widened this time.
Eh?
Even if I did bad this time, it won't really bother me.
It should!
If you let your guard down because everyone else did bad, you might fall behind.
Hm...
Huh?
Rather...
I didn't make any bets with my dad this time, so I won't really be that sad.
You won't ever become an honest adult.
If you're going to copy Miyuki-san,
why don't you take notes all the time and not just during testing period?
Miyuki-san is really methodical.
She must be a type A person.
Ah...
People tell me that often, but I'm actually type O.
Eh?
You're type O?
You don't seem like it.
Yes, but...
BLOOD TYPE PRIMER
According to this book,
I have many qualities that are typical of type O people.
BLOOD TYPE PRIMER
For example, "Type O people are childish and straightforward."
That's pretty spot-on.
"Type O people are...
...forceful, overprotective when it comes to their possessions, and greedy."
Hm...
So Miyuki-san has a dark side as well, huh?
Konata, you're type A, right?
Yep, but people often think of me as type B.
"Type A people are considerate and pay a lot of attention to their surroundings.
And they seek peaceful relationships among people?"
Is this right?
I'm really considerate and I notice things, don't I?
Only things that you care about.
I'm calm and respect others.
Only when it involves homework.
So what blood type are you, Kagami?
Me?
I'm type B.
Easygoing, ill-mannered, gullible, contrarian,
and don't put a lot of thought into things...
Is that supposed to mean something?
Does that make Tsukasa type AB?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Why?
Just because...
Personality-wise, Tsukasa would be type A while Kagami would be type B.
We're both type B.
I mean, we're twins.
Oh, right...
Totally forgot.
We're not as easygoing as you are, though.
Speaking of fortune-telling, there are methods using animals or sushi.
Sushi         Horoscopes
What are your favourite things?
We'll use your answers to determine your personality.
Sushi?
Um, Miyuki-san is...
Oh, salmon roe?
She's still high-class, even here.
I love salmon roe.
And what about me and Tsukasa?
Cucumber rolls?
Cucumber rolls, huh?
I guess that could be considered sushi as well.
That's pretty close.
What about you?
Me?
Ginger?
You're ginger!
Don't make fun of ginger!
Well, it is essential to have when eating sushi...
And the content of the fortune itself isn't too bad.
You're right.
"Even cucumber rolls can be considered sushi."
Ah!
Hello...
Konata?
You know how we were talking about blood types today...
Just to clarify...
I guess fraternal twins can have different blood types.
So your impression wasn't entirely wrong.
I was afraid you would take it too seriously.
Why, thank you for being so considerate.
You're so honest.
I'm starting to see why you're a type A.
Speaking of which, they had a TV show on psychological tests.
But things like those get it right in some parts, but wrong in others,
so they're bound to be accurate some of the time.
Kagami...
If you keep looking at this so realistically, you're not going to enjoy life.
You should act more like your age.
Oh, Tsukasa.
You tried really hard this time.
Kagami slipped a little on this one.
But Kagami still received a better score.
Good job, both of you.
Um, how should I say this...
You both did your best and-
Oh!
Tsukasa, you really tried hard this time.
But Kagami still received a better grade.
Hey, Matsuri!
Try to be a little more tactful.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Kagami-chan and Tsukasa-chan,
I'm envious of how you two are such respectable young women.
No, no...
Not at all!
And I hear you're always top in the class standings at Ryouou High.
I wish my children were more like you.
It feels like she just threw my name in there with Onee-chan's.
Oh no...
It's nothing special.
So I can't really be happy.
Since the tests are over, we should go hang out somewhere!
Oh, good idea.
Do you want to go see a movie for a change?
I wonder what they're showing right now.
They're playing something amazing right now.
Like?
Some might call it a splatter film...
But at the same time, it has suspense and top-notch horror!
Oh!
Let's go to that, then!
We should go home and then meet up later.
Let's, let's!
I don't want to go...
I just don't!
We've got some spare time, so what do you want to do?
That Konata sure is taking her time.
Is she late again?
I wonder.
There's no way she could get here before we did...
Geez.
The movie's going to start.
When did you...?
I didn't recognize you without that thing...
Anyway, we don't have much time so let's get going.
Oh yeah...
Kagami, pretend that we're sisters.
Huh?
Why?
Well, it's less suspicious if I try to get in for the children's price that way.
You brat!
You're always complaining about your height.
But at times like this, you take full advantage of it!
Wasn't that scary, Takemi?
Aw, you're so cute.
I'm kind of hungry.
Yeah.
You must be hungry as well after screaming that much, Tsukasa.
Y-Yeah.
What do you want to eat?
Then, how about a cake buffet?
Sounds good.
The buffet...
A place where every girl's greed can be satisfied.
They have so many types of cakes and drinks.
Really?
I wonder if we can eat them all.
Easy for you, Kagami.
Our store is limited to 1 hour per customer.
Drinks are over there in the drink corner.
And the cakes are in the showcase over there.
So help yourselves.
Okay!
*bow*
Oh, and if you leave behind abnormal amounts of food...
...se will have to charge you separately.
Keep that in mind.
Then please, take your time.
Leaving behind abnormal amounts of food?
There are probably people that take a lot but don't finish it all.
All right, let's go.
You're getting a lot.
Can you eat all of that?
What about you, Kagami?
This is normal for cakes.
I can easily finish this.
Let's dig in!
That one...
And this one...
It's starting to get painful.
I think we took a little too much on our first round.
I retire.
*stare*
Ah, but if we don't eat it they'll charge us for it.
That, I can't allow.
It's painful.
I can't...
Our time's almost up!
Oh, Kagami's eating two at a time now!
Otherwise it would be a waste!
I can't...
No, no!
If you drink too much water, it'll be harder to eat.
You have to stuff yourself with as much as you can,
and then at the very end, wash it down with water.
Don't just sit there and watch us!
You eat some, too!
I can't eat anymore.
You can stuff yourself with more pudding and bavarois.
Here.
Why don't you eat it, Kagami?
I'm already at my limit.
I've already retired...
You can just swallow the pudding.
Eh!?
Here, hurry!
This doesn't feel right...
It doesn't feel right at all!
Since we're done with our tests, I went overboard and played so many games.
So thanks to that, I'm sleepy...
If you put that much effort into studying for your tests...
...I'm sure the results would have been different.
The recent bishoujo games have lots of save points,
but it's still so hard to stop playing.
I'm the type that likes to finish in one sitting.
I've been wondering, but you can't buy that kind of stuff as a student, can you?
How do you get them?
I get my dad to buy them for me.
No way!
This happens every time, but your house never ceases to amaze me.
So your dad goes and buys them?
And you, as a daughter, shouldn't be asking!
I'm so sleepy.
You don't seem like you play games, Miyuki-san.
Ah, I don't have a console, but I play a little on my PC.
Eh?
What kind of games do you play?
I'm so surprised.
Solitaire and Minesweeper...
Sometimes I get really into it.
You're not mistaken,
but that's just wrong, Miyuki-san.
But I understand.
You can really get absorbed into simple games like those.
Yuki-chan, how high do you score?
Solitaire depends on your luck, but my score is usually over ten thousand.
On Minesweeper, I just broke one hundred seconds on difficult.
I guess people like Miyuki-san really get into these games...
We've seen so many sports-related activities this year.
Yep.
That person even won the gold for figure skating at the Tokyo Olympics.
Even high school baseball was pretty intense.
There were so many games going into extra innings.
Yep, yep.
Yep, that Handkerchief Prince.
Speaking of baseball, that player went to America.
Oh!
Is the Japan Series over?
Long time ago.
No way!
Were there discounts this time?
The Japanese series was between two teams,
so the supermarket and department stores didn't do much.
But they had some commemorative sales.
They probably just discounted the ham and stuff, right?
Yep, yep.
I wonder...
I better keep a close eye on it next year.
Knowing you, you're probably just going to buy a bunch of snacks.
Not true.
I buy salt, sugar, soy sauce,
and other condiments you use around the house.
Eh?
You probably wouldn't understand though, right Kagami?
Well, excuse me!
I'm not good at household chores!
Eye drops?
Want some help?
Ah, thank you very much.
Okay, lie down.
Yes.
Now, relax.
Y-Yes...
Here it comes.
Loosen up.
Y-Yes.
Um, I'm sorry.
I'm not doing it on purpose.
Your face is... scary.
The bad thing about prizes is that it takes a while to get them.
Thus, I have discovered a way to enjoy sweepstakes like these.
What?
First, you mail your postcard in a festive mood.
And when you actually get the prize,
you've totally forgotten about it so you can be happy again!
Isn't that a good deal?
"One grain of rice tastes twice as good."
I don't like waiting for it in the first place.
When it comes to something you like, you're so positive.
Lucky Channel!
Oha-Lucky!
Hi!
I would like to cheerfully bring you this week's Lucky Channel.
Believe it or not, this is already the 9th one!
I'm the navigator, Kogami Akira.
And the person to whom the producer, Itou-san, is about to say,
"Hey Shiraishi, get over here."
Eh, is that so?
Giving 100% of my strength in supporting Akira-sama...
Shiraishi Minoru here.
Pleased to meet you.
Now, this is the third round of introducing characters!
What a surprise...
This time, Hiiragi Tsukasa!
Here we go.
You stupid, slow and bone-headed...
Hiiragi-
It's really starting to-
I-I'm sorry...
It's really starting to get interesting.
Yes!
Let's tie our loincloths and give this our all!
Right, Akira-sama?
Loincloths?
I'm an idol, so I'm not into those things.
You can take care of that part.
Oh, right...
Um...
So tie our loincloths until you get a wedgie!
Now listen here.
Let me advise you out of my concern for you.
C-Concern?
If an entertainer starts going downhill, it's over for them.
So, I was an entertainer?
And you've been stealing other people's material lately.
You do that a lot lately, so watch it.
Yes!
Let's see...
What were we doing today?
Introducing Hiiragi Tsukasa-san.
Oh, oh, oh!
That To Hear-
Mi-Miracle!
Kamigishi?
Minorun-run!
Right?
So you can say it, huh?
She reminds me of an idol-like character from a while back.
Um, do you think so?
Well, if you say Tsukasa-san is an idol, she does seem a bit like one...
Don't make me laugh!
Hiiragi Tsukasa, an idol?
Where did you get that from?
Since you work right next to me like this,
you should understand what a real idol is by now.
O-Okay.
Hiiragi Tsukasa is just the gentle type,
with that lame "looking for happiness" face.
I-I see...
"Looking for happiness"?
You know, who cares about Tsukasa anyway?
A-Ah, not even my parents hit me!
I'll show you how to be an idol.
First up is how to be photogenic.
Eh?
You know,
this is good information for you, so listen up!
Y-Yes!
You know how people suddenly take pictures of you on the street?
"Please, hit the shutter."
"Looking for... happiness?"
*fawn* * fawn * fawn*
Well, something like that.
Props are also appropriate.
Make sure you can carry them with you.
Where?
And, you can't let anyone take a picture of you when you walk around town...
So you always have to be on your toes.
And make sure your teeth are sparkling white.
Like a doll.
Passionate.
You also have to keep your eyes wide like acorns,
and only laugh with this part of your mouth.
Scary!
But your expression has to be natural.
So if someone suddenly points a camera at you,
be like, "I'm so surprised!"
Or something.
Oh, naturally...
And for some variation, if you walk with a guy to a ho-
Aww, it's time to say good-bye again!
So please send any questions, opinions,
and commentary you have about this show to us!
We accept them over the radio and homepage as well!
We'll see you again next time.
Bye-bii!
You just had a photo-shoot!
Yes, I did.
How was it?
The one with me in a cardigan, right?
Oh, it's so cute.
Thank you very much!
What now?
Was it cute?
Oh, everyone said it was cute.
I guess so.
Yes, it is.
Yes, I was.
You seem totally into it.
It looked like so much fun.
Oh, like using your eyelids and putting your hands on your chin like this.
It was fun.
Ah...
Yep.
Did it turn into a habit?
Yes, I think it has...
Including the cross-dressing.
Did you check the pictures?
No, I haven't.
The Manager-san...
Yes?
Checked the pictures...
And said, "Honestly, what do you think?"
Well, I have a bunch of mokkori pictures, too, so I think that's covered.
Sorry, sorry.
I made such a basic mistake.
I'll sing properly this time.
As you say that, you put another song in.
Give me that, too!
Here you go.
Did you decide, Tsukasa?
Give us a sec.
Because I don't know that many songs...
Don't worry about it.
I'll sing something to pass the time.
Hey, sing something other than anime songs.
This isn't an anime song.
Hey, I've heard this before.
What is it again?
It's by Koizumi Kyoko.
I used to sing this with my dad a lot.
If it's not an anime song, it's an oldie?
Eh?
Calling Kyon-Kyon an oldie doesn't do her justice.
Deai wa kaze no naka
出逢いは風の中
A new encounter is waiting in the wind,
Tsukasa, why don't you
sing something simple,
Koi ni ochita ano hi kara
恋に落ちたあの日から
Since that day I fell in love.
like a children's song?
Kizukanu uchi ni kokoro wa
気づかぬうちに心は
Before I knew it, my heart was
I'm looking for that, too, but...
I'm sorry.
Oh, take your time.
Anata wo motometeta
あなたを求めてた
Yearning for you.
We have plenty of it.
Nakanai de koigokoro yo negai ga kanau nara
泣かないで恋心よ　願いが叶うなら
Don't cry, lovelorn heart, if my wish can come true,
Namida no kawa wo koete subete wo wasuretai
涙の河を越えて　すべてを忘れたい
I'll cross this river of tears, and forget everything.
Setsunai kataomoi
せつない片想い
What a painful one-sided love.
Anata wa kizukanai
あなたは気づかない
You don't even notice me.
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Konata here.
Super ***** Brothers World 3-1.
At the stairs near the end you can jump on the falling turtle.
And if you spam the A button,
you can repeatedly jump the turtle, getting infinite lives!
Which is nice but...
If you do it too much...
And get more than 129 lives...
Dying just once will result in a game over.
I won't bother with the, "The lives aren't infinite then!" response.
I wonder if it's that...
A public service announcement from that company near Toufukuji Station...
...about doing everything in moderation.
Next week: "Desire"
「Desire」
Look forward to it!