When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Sixteen Years Ago
He'll be Hayate.
His name will be Hayate.
Let's name him Hayate.
My, what a wonderful name.
But why?
The reason's obvious, isn't it, Dear?
Because I want him to grow up strong,
so he can run like the gale
(hayate) away from bill collectors.
Wow, that a fantastic name!
It is, right? I'm a genius!
No matter when we have to
abandon our child to go on the run,
we'll have nothing to worry about now.
Dear, you really are something else!
Thus named Hayate,
the boy's destiny was thrust
upon him from the day he was born
to become absolutely perfect at everything.
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
All of America cried!
We'll make ya laugh 3 times in 5 minutes!
Already, no hope for the Academy Award!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naive and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Like a Dog, a Mouse, and a Bulldog
What's with this painting?
What do you think?
Is it not a fabulous portrait?
It's apparently a gift of sorts, but...
Just how much do you
think this is valued at?
And so... Open the price!
Ones, tens, hundreds, thousands,
ten thousands, hundred thousands,
millions, ten millions...
Two hundred million yen!
It's cheaper than I thought.
I have brought the milk tea.
Thank you for your hard work.
Though, well, in 10 years,
my autographed illustrations
will probably be worth 100 times
more than this thing.
Good grief.
It seems you still do not understand...
...what true quality is!
What did you say?!
Oh?
What's wrong, Hayate?
This is a fake.
What?
Wh-What are you saying?!
You should know that this august painting
is worth even more
than your debt, which you'll spend
the rest of your life repaying!
Please excuse me.
What do you think, sir?
It is a fake.
What?!
We actually received word just earlier
that this painting appears to be a fake.
There we go.
Well, please excuse us.
CRUSHED
Hey, where are you going?
Eep!
W-Well, it's been a while,
so I thought I'd go be a Giant
of Art in the storehouse or something...
See you!
B-But anyway, you have
a brilliantly discerning eye, Hayate.
How did you know that painting was fake?
Well, that's... uh...
This is from back when I was little,
but well, I used to help with my
father's business and sell art.
Oh, so your father was an art dealer?
Oh, no, that's not it.
Ah! Truly, you have a sharp eye!
You see, we would first
show them the real painting
and when the customer had made a purchase,
he would hand it over to me right
in front of the customer
to avoid suspicion.
The boy will package it up for you then,
so please wait one moment.
We were dealing with valuables,
so the customers are also wary, but...
They seemed to lower their guard,
knowing I was a child,
so I would make it look like
I was packaging up the real thing,
but I would switch it with a fake
that was hidden behind the real one
and sell the customer that one.
That's a crime, no two ways about it!
I was little, so I didn't
know it was a crime.
And that was when my father drummed into me
how to instantly recognize fakes
for all kinds of paintings.
How much worthless information
did you have drummed into you?
Hayate Ayasaki, protagonist of this manga
and occasionally its heroine.
He's not out to destroy the Andro Army,
but he possesses an invulnerable body.
The author loved the World
Masterpiece Theater too much
and before he realized it, he had
created an utterly unfortunate boy.
Um...
What have you been reading from, Nagi?
Um, excuse me...
Well, something's been bothering me,
so I'm reading the original manga
from the beginning.
Something that's bothering you?
Never mind that. I wish you
wouldn't rob me of my job...
You think Hayate's abilities
are amazing, too, right?
Yes, of course.
Too amazing.
He's deft, but he also
has great physical strength
and he accomplishes all
tasks perfectly and swiftly.
Now, on to the next room.
On top of which, he's got
incomprehensible special powers,
making him too good to be
the protagonist of a romantic comedy.
Well, we do occasionally get
the shoehorned battles, so...
So, here's a question I've got.
Doesn't he have any weaknesses or anything?
Huh?
Weaknesses! You know, weaknesses!
Doraemon has mice, Oba-Q has dogs,
and Goku has his tail.
For the heroes of manga and anime,
they tend to come with
weaknesses by default, you know?
I see... Is that how it works?
I don't know. Hayate's amazing,
but he's got a bit of this aura
that makes you want to be mean to him.
Please, stop this.
Well, I won't deny it...
Right?
As someone who shares Robocon's
weakness, you agree, right?
What does that have
anything to do with this?!
Or actually...
Oh, really! I wish you wouldn't
remind me of such unpleasantness!
So, I think Hayate needs a weakness!
Come on! Hinomaru Box!
Ru Ma No Hi
I've prepared items that could
possibly be weaknesses for Hayate
in the form of "Hinomaru" boxes.
Uh, then I'll take the "ma" from "Hinomaru".
Good. Open the box!
Um, Nagi?
Keep that creepy thing away from me!
Then you shouldn't have
prepared it in the first place.
Darn it!
I guess it really was stupid of us
to rely on Saito the announcer!
Uh, "us"? It's not like I really...
In the end, we'll just have to discover
his weaknesses through observation.
I see...
All right, that's correct, too.
I've finally overcome my math weakness.
Darn! Look at that!
One of Hayate's rare
weaknesses has been overcome!
Um, I don't think that's
necessarily a bad thing.
Does he have any other weaknesses
or things he doesn't like?
Time to observe carefully!
Oh, but look at him.
The Miss won't eat sardines like this,
so I'll mince it up a bit and get rid
of the fishiness with ginger.
And she doesn't like carrots
or green peppers, either.
Plus, she absolutely won't eat spicy things.
Oh, and she doesn't like
chicken skin, either.
It seems he's observed you carefully
on your weaknesses and dislikes.
Honestly, it's because she's
so picky that her growth is...
I swear! Hayate, you're really... I swear!
Since it's come to this,
we have no choice but to go after him
with standard weaknesses.
Pardon?
Ta-da!
What do you think? This'll scare him, right?
Yes, it's just scary in all sorts of ways...
Everyone gets scared when a ghost shows up.
This is the perfect plan.
But isn't that more like your own weakness?
All right! Now, I just have to wait
until night to catch Hayate sleeping...
I do not see the need to wait until night.
Look, if you just darken
the room like this...
N-N-Nah, Maria, i-isn't it still too early?
Do you think so?
But you'll have to go to these lengths,
or he won't be scared.
You don't have to be that scared...
Ya got a long way to go!
That voice!
Fermented soybeans, red miso soup,
savory monja pancakes!
If it's weaknesses,
I'll give ya a run for yer money!
Sakuya...
Where did you pop out from?!
The butler-in-debt's weakness, huh?
All right, leave it to me!
Guys like him sometimes have
the most unexpected weaknesses!
Unexpected?
Terrifyin' invaders who forced humanity
to the brink of extinction...
But their sinister plot's
destroyed by microorganisms!
Isn't that the weakness of aliens?
As I thought, I cannot leave this to Saku.
If only I could come up with a good idea...
I have a good idea.
Isumi!
What's this good idea?
My idea is...
We can simply ask him directly.
I hadn't thought of that!
Huh?
So, what is it that you
are afraid of, my dear Hayate?
What?
Um...
"This is about where
I'd be afraid of a cup of tea."
For those of you who don't get it,
please listen to the traditional rakugo
story called "Scared of Manju Sweets".
What's this, an Edo Era punchline?!
I'm scared of Dom Pérignon!
I got the feeling something just went by...
That was just your imagination.
Come to think of it,
what's yer weakness, Isumi?
What?
Just wonderin' if even the supreme
Ghost Sweeper's afraid of somethin'.
Something I am afraid of?
I do have something.
Ooh! What's that?
I am afraid of caterpillars.
Caterpillars?
What the heck? That's an awfully
normal thing to be afraid of.
With a body length of 180 meters
and weighing 20,000 tons,
it is the guardian deity of Infant Island.
It spun a giant cocoon on Tokyo Tower...
Even an atomic heat ray
attack had no effect on it
and once it became an imago,
it is said to have devastated
a certain country...
No, no, no, no!
I mean, that's no caterpillar!
Lame...
...brain...
If that'll be all...
Lame...
I won't let you sleep.
(Nekasanai yo.)
With pleasure.
(Yorokonde.)
I'm stuffed!
Thanks for the food!
I appreciate you treating us
to lunch as well.
You are quite welcome.
She certainly left them neatly uneaten.
You probably thought you
took advantage of my weakness,
but it won't be so easy!
Just you watch, Hayate!
Next, I'll be sure to uncover your weakness!
So you still haven't given up?
Maria.
Once everything's cleaned up,
would it be all right if I took a break?
Certainly, I won't mind.
What are you going to do, Hayate?
Oh, nothing much. I just thought
I'd get back to my studies.
Since the finals are coming up.
The finals?
I must work hard to advance
to the next grade with you, after all.
W-With me...
Th-That's true.
You two better not interfere
with Hayate's studies, got it?!
By no means are you to get any silly ideas,
such as being hell-bent
on discovering his weakness!
Ya know...
I shall be careful, Nagi.
Oh, yes, I have the math
problems from last year.
Would you like to look
at them for reference?
Yes, I would love to!
Um, this is math, and yet,
the problems aren't in Japanese...
Yeah, it's in German.
What?! German?!
But Germany is the land of sausages!
Well, they've got other
things like beer, too, though.
Never mind that! This is way
beyond the level of "hard"!
H-Hello there, Wataru. Welcome.
We're getting a great
number of guests today.
So what are you suddenly
storming in here for?
What am I here for?
I mean, what's up with this exam?!
Well, Hakuou is
a prestigious school, after all,
so it's only natural that it's hard.
There's hard and then there's this!
That's right! There's
no way we can read this.
What?
You guys can't read that?
Isumi Saginomiya: 4 Languages
Maria: 13 Languages
Nagi Sanzenin: 8 Languages
Wataru Tachibana: 2 Languages
Wait, you skipped grades
and you can't even read German?
I've got my hands full with just English!
But you could choose to have problems
in English as well on the exam.
Um, even English is kind of iffy for me...
Hayate Ayasaki: 1.5 Languages
J-Just for my own reference,
what will happen
if I should fail or something?
Please don't fall silent.
What should I do?
Goin' to a prestigious
school sure sounds tough.
I'm so glad I'm goin' to a normal school.
Saku...
Now, then, guess playtime's over.
Ya guys study hard.
C'mon, Isumi, let's go.
What? Me, too?
Yeah, 'cause Wataru won't be able to
focus on his studies with ya around.
What? Why would Wataru have problems...?
S-Saku, you bastard!
Oh! N-Nothing...
Well, Nagi, we'll leave the rest to ya.
C'mon, let's go, Isumi.
All right.
Sheesh.
Well, no helping it then.
In the meantime,
over at a normal high school...
Huh? What's with this quiz score?
Ayumu Nishizawa
This might be kind of bad...
Even with talk of love and romance,
the realities of high school life are harsh.
I have to study!
Newest Edition
Understandable German
That should do it.
What are you doing, Miss?
Oh, because there's a limit to how much
you can study on your own.
I figured I'd go look after my
less accomplished little brother.
I see.
I guess there really
are limits on your own...
Um, I also...
Because, you see,
unlike you, he's not the sort
who can do it just by working at it.
Huh?
Uh, um... Miss?
Well, I'm going to go
tutor Wataru over there.
I will not tolerate a Sanzenin
butler getting a failing grade.
Yes, Miss.
So, what are you going to do now, Hayate?
Um...
Please tutor me, Maria!
I thought you might say that.
Thank you very much!
I swear! You better be
at least a little grateful.
I am. Sheesh.
I'd feel bad for Saku
if you flunked or something,
so work hard.
R-Right.
But I had no idea that both Wataru
and Isumi had skipped grades.
Come to think of it,
I guess we never mentioned it.
Without friends, Nagi would probably
completely stop going to school,
so we had them skip grades with her.
Their grades were good, too, so...
Mind you, it was originally supposed to be
Isumi and Sakuya who went with her.
What?
The truth is, with Wataru, skipping
grades was a pretty big stretch.
But there was a reason Wataru
desperately wanted to go to Hakuou
and only 3 slots available
for skipping grades, so...
Mr. Wataru Tachibana
Enrollment Paperwork
Hakuou Academy Entrance Exam Center
Nagi tutored him at that time, too.
I see.
I guess they're close.
Yes.
So, if the Small Beauties
of Infant Island become lost,
the entire world will surely fall
into a panic once again...
Nah, enough 'bout that already.
By the way, how's school these days?
Is it still fun?
Yes, but Nagi does not come
to school much, so...
Then, Wataru's 'bout
the only playmate you got?
That is not entirely true, but...
I only say hello to Wataru
every one in a while anyway.
Good grief.
And here I thought maybe they
were slowly gettin' somewhere.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Nothin'.
So, what happened to King Ghidorah?
What? Um, King Ghidorah was...
But it is a little worrisome, isn't it?
Pardon?
I mean the Miss and Wataru.
They may still be children,
but for a young man and a young
woman to be alone is...
Oh, please, Hayate.
Perhaps we should figure out a nice timing
to bring them coffee or something.
You're thinking too much about this.
I mean, if we start talking
about a young man
and a young woman being alone,
we are also...
What?
The cliché romantic comedy mode!
Should we bring them coffee, after all?
Finding a nice timing for it...
P-Perhaps we should...
But I feel bad that you're
always tutoring me...
Huh?
What's with this creepy gracious attitude?
Y-You idiot! I'm always gracious!
You'd be more endearing
if you were always this gracious.
You... Stop that!
Miss!
We have brought you coffee!
Wait...
Nice timing!
Wh-Why are you holding hands
while you're studying?
You've got this wrong, Hayate!
Th-This just sort of happened...
It just sort of happened...
and you were trying to do what?
I wasn't trying to do anything!
That's right, Hayate!
This is a misunderstanding!
That's right! I wouldn't even want
to do anything to Nagi!
What?!
I mean...
I love Isumi!
What?
Uh, um...
I got lost while I was
chasing after Sakuya and...
Y-You got it all wrong, Isumi!
Th-Th-This is... You see...
J-Just kidding. I was trying to go
for a joke or something.
Oh, my, so it was a joke.
Don't ya have any desire
to make progress here?! Ya wuss!
At this rate, going to the same
school has been meaningless.
But you see now, don't you?
You don't have to worry about us.
S-So it seems.
Now I can rest easy and go study with Maria.
Yes. You can rest easy and...
Hold on a second. What did
you say you're going to do?
Oh, as I said, go study with Maria...
Go study with Maria, just the two of you?!
How dare you do such a thing
behind my back?!
Why you! This is unforgivable!
M-Miss?!
Miss, what are you so angry about?!
I don't want to hear your excuses!
In the end, it seems not
understanding a girl's feelings
is Hayate's greatest weakness.
Now, then, next time, even
Hollywood films will be shocked!
They'll fight against a luxury
passenger liner, terrorists,
and man-eating sharks.
Lame...
...brain...
You have to "go Isumi" on jokes.
Wait, that should've been
"go easy"! Just kidding!
You really love telling jokes,
don't you, Wataru?
Nah...
Even though they are not very funny.
But as a creature, I think
he might be kind of funny.
Looks like I'll hafta give him some lessons.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
The Katsura Sisters'
Lettering by Hitomi Nabatame
The Katsura sisters'...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Boom! It's Yukiji Katsura!
B-Boom! I am Hinagiku Katsura.
We are the much talked-about pair
of pretty girls, the Katsura sisters!
Ta-da!
Hey, are you sure about this, Sis?
I'm going along with this because you say
this is your moment in the spotlight,
but this is really embarrassing, okay?
Hina, your enthusiasm is lacking.
And we practiced this so many
times yesterday, too.
If this song sells, I can say goodbye
to my hard life of poverty!
I'll get to drink all
the Dom Pérignon I want!
Well, then, see you again next time!
Preview
I see! So that's what it was!
The reason I haven't won Hayate over...
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
The most important thing
when it comes to romance...
...is giving the cold shoulder!
But I want a situation where Hayate
will rely on me more somehow...
Nagi, you've been invited on
an ocean voyage on Sakuya's yacht.
Yes, that's it!
Next time, "The Poseidon
Advance Generator Gavas"!
But this ship's pretty well-built.
Ya think so? That's nice.
You can give me the cold shoulder
all you want! I'm not falling for you!
The Poseidon Advance Generator Gavas
Just In to "Hayate the Combat
Butler" again next time!