Mom!
Why are you posing like that? What's that cool pose for?
This is no cool pose.
Note: "Chikaeshi no Juhou" (道反之呪法) translates to
It's a spell technique called "Chikaeshi no Juhou".
"Incantation of the Reversing Path"
It's a meditation to seal away any apparition.
You look like a transforming hero!
Okay then, I'm going to be a monster.
I'm no transforming hero, but a Tsukuyomi priestess.
But the Tsukuyomi priestesses are Allies of Justice, right?
So you are a hero!
Well, that theory actually does make sense.
All right, here I come! "Chikaeshi no Juhou"!
You don't need to yell! The posture is wrong, too!
This looks better!
You look stronger and more intimidating to the enemy!
You think so?
I can't hear you, Mom!
Don't you underestimate me. Watch how I do it!
What's the matter, Sasami? What's so funny?
I love you, Mom!
Such a strange one...
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 7                                              Ganbaranai
"I FORGOT HOW TO SPEAK"
Everything was not always so fine and dandy.
Back then, Big Sister Tsurugi was even less enthusiastic.
She was tired-looking and spaced-out.
Big Sister Kagami never smiled or chatted with me.
She was afraid of the slightest noise
and seemed as though she was always
fighting something invisible.
So I was always smiling. I was forcing myself to smile.
I was struggling and in pain as I was teased
and got in trouble at school, too.
But I had to tell myself to smile.
I couldn't do anything,
so I pretended I was always happy and laughing,
so Tsurugi and Kagami would laugh with me.
No matter how much they scolded me
or told me to shut up,
I made sure that I did everything I could
to try and not hate this world.
You idiot!
Useless!
Slowly but surely the expressions
on their faces softened.
This is no time for crying!
Slowly but surely the expressions
on their faces softened.
They began smiling more and partying more
as they interacted with Mama-lin...
I thought the coldness which had been
making their hearts ache had disappeared,
but everything broke...
Tsurugi was cast into the Underworld.
Kagami was too beat up to move.
But I was just fine! I'm all about being just fine!
So I have to go.
I'm scared and can't stop my tears from falling,
but at least I'll keep on moving forward!
If my wish could come true,
God, let me grant everyone's wish!
Oh?
Don't move.
I'm just purifying your body.
I have no control over my body...
It looks like you've been neglecting your health.
If you don't put some meat on your bones
you'll be weak and die young.
What is this? My head feels hazy.
I dulled your consciousness with drugs.
It would be a problem if you were to exert
your Power of God upon me.
Why... Where am I...
This is where Tsukuyomi Shrine used to stand.
The shrine is gone, but it's still a good place
to be away from the world and train yourself.
I'm going to purify it and restore the barrier so
it could be a hideaway for the Tsukuyomi priestesses.
I'll ask the question again.
This is the biggest compromise.
Do you swear to follow through with your duty,
without thinking of escaping,
as a Tsukuyomi priestess for the people?
No.
Why not?
Did you not swear to me that you would
come back to be a Tsukuyomi priestess?
I said that to make you stop.
So you're telling me that was a lie.
I don't like this. You're forcing me to do this with drugs.
I don't want to follow through with
the stupid duty that ended up killing you.
I finally got out of there...
I finally made friends...
So you're going to abandon the duty
given you by Heaven?
That's not what I wished for!
As long as time allows, I'm going to re-educate you.
No... No... I'm not going to do my best anymore.
Then... that can't be helped.
You always tended to vomit easily since you were a child.
You might spit it up if I fed it to you by mouth,
so I delivered it into you directly.
I kept you conscious for questioning,
but once this drug takes effect
your thinking ability will be lost completely.
There's nothing more that I want to ask you.
There's nothing left for you to say.
I no longer have any expectation for someone like you.
It's a shame, Sasami. It's so very much a shame...
I'm absolutely disappointed with this one as well.
He's a spineless and ignorant man to begin with.
I guess watching the shrine getting mercilessly
destroyed wasn't bad enough for him.
He not only went on to do whatever he pleased
after that, but he also failed at the end...
He's hopeless.
You're of no worth if you're
not going to carry out your duty.
However... we can't allow the bloodline
of the Tsukuyomi to be eradicated.
Therefore, there's only one thing left that I want from you.
Bear a child, Sasami.
Let that child inherit the Power of God
and become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Once the power transfer is complete,
you're free to go anywhere you please.
There aren't many blood relatives because
I was too sickly to have many children.
This one will have to do.
No way...
No, no, no...
Don't be like that.
Be impregnated by him and give birth
to a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I'll educate her and return this world
to the way it should be.
No... No...
At least...
At least let it be my Big Brother...
I can't allow that.
He's been cut from the Tsukuyomi family.
He's a sinner who committed
the worst crime by taking you away.
He has no right to ever associate with the Tsukuyomi.
By the way, he came here earlier,
probably trying to rescue you.
He made a big scene, demanding to see you...
...so I took care of him.
Cleanse your body first.
Burn the incense, conduct the ceremony
and ask to be blessed with child.
Oh, you broke?
No matter. It's all right as long as you're physically intact.
I just explained to Sasami her final duty.
She fell quiet after I told her that you were dead.
She must care for you very much.
How disgusting! You're nothing but a monster.
I want nothing more than to kill you if I could.
Do you insist on using Sasami as a tool
to produce a Tsukuyomi priestess?
Have you any motherly love left at all?
The moment I left the Land of the Dead,
I ceased being human.
I'm a Tsukuyomi priestess first, and her mother second.
Sasami truly loved you.
I'm aware of that.
But that's an insignificant matter...
...Brother.
Compressed sleep. Now awakening.
Confirming outstanding damage:
38% restoration by self-repair.
Approximately 7 hours remaining
before reaching battle-ready condition.
Sasami...
Are you worried about me, Meat?
The opponent is the most powerful
Tsukuyomi priestess in history,
blessed by the King of the Underworld.
If you challenged her with no strategy,
even Tama would end up like us...
The King of the Underworld...
In other words, The Hero God,
the Embodiment of Chaos: Susanoo.
Susanoo is the Chaos and Rebellion
that directly opposes Amaterasu's Order and Control.
The worst enemy anyone could have.
I'm glad this has GPS-like functionality.
You may be a Tsukuyomi priestess
or the Hero God or whatever,
but you'd better not mess with the Yagami Sisters!
Please take care of the rest...
Tama...
Yawn...
I must go rescue Sasami somehow...
Whoa! That scared me!
This is Miss Tsurugi's...!
What a blessing this is!
Oh? This sword isn't as sharp as it looks.
Now I can get out of this room with this...
This is nothing!
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff,
I can smell Sasami from over there!
Sniff, sniff.
It's this room!
Sasami!
Sasami! It's me! I'm here to rescue you! Sasami!
You've got nothing to worry about now.
No matter what happens I'll protect you!
B...
Big Brother... You're alive...
Yes, I'm alive, Sasami! So please stop crying.
Big Brother!
Ouch! Oh?
I don't understand what's going on!
You're supposed to hug and kiss me
and say "I love you, Big Brother!" weren't you?
What took you so long to come rescue me?!
You frickin' idiot!
Dumbass! You ignorant, useless,
piece of trash! You bug!
It's okay now, Sasami. Big Brother is here to protect you.
Big Brother...
You think I'll let you go?
I never expected them to pierce
the barrier from a distance.
I expect no less from the Divine Sword
Ame no Murakumo,
the guardian sword that purifies any evil spirit...
But, still...
...considering that they send the weapon
and not show themselves...
I bet those evil gods still can't move.
Move, Mom! I'm not going to make a baby!
I'm going to be the one who eradicates the Tsukuyomi
bloodline, which has lasted this long for no reason!
I've already decided...
I'm going to return this world,
which humans have distorted forcefully,
to the Chaos that existed before myth!
That's the real world! The way it should be!
I'm not going to let my mind get distorted
no matter how much you beat me up,
put me through pain or try to brainwash me!
You ignored your happiness and pleasure
and tried your hardest in order to carry out your duty,
but what did the world give you in the end?
Only death and suffering!
There's no room for you to argue.
While you're fooling around and not trying hard at all,
others must take up your slack and work even harder.
I can't call you my daughter
when you refuse to recognize that,
when you instead always lean for the easy way out
and disregard the value of your life!
I used to love you so much...
You rarely smiled, but you were so sweet to me,
so cool, and always protected the world!
You were my hero!
But the Shrine used you to the core and killed you!
I'll never forgive the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
I don't care how dignified and important the duty is,
being a Tsukuyomi priestess is stupid!
We are humans, not gods!
We may not be able to do anything,
but we can still live our lives happily!
Know that none of your words can reach the dead.
It's too far! Darn it!
I know we've got to rescue Mama-lin,
but we have no idea where she is!
The last time I was here I was just
following Big Sister Kagami,
so I couldn't remember how to get here,
and I got lost...
I walked for a long time,
but I somehow circled back to school!
I asked the policeman for directions,
but all I remembered was "somewhere in Kyushu".
He got upset with me because he thought
I was playing. I did nothing wrong!
Tama will never forgive the person
who's done such awful things to my sisters!
I'm going to beat up that person and
go home with Mama-lin and everybody else!
You've quite the lifesaver on your side...
Mama-lin, let me borrow this!
Tama...! How?!
The gods are ubiquitous.
The higher gods exist in a wider and broader plane.
When a human acknowledges a god's existence,
that god becomes substantiated.
Through that gap between concept and reality,
the god can reconstruct itself
and move about instantaneously.
Tama is in elementary school,
so she doesn't get the complicated stuff!
But it's not about who's smarter!
It's about who's trying their hardest!
What?
She must've transported the Divine Sword and made it
emerge in the same space as the Demon Sword!
What's going on?
According to myth,
the Demon Sword Ame no Habakiri is weaker
than the Divine Sword Ame no Murakumo!
Here, Mama-lin.
Mama-lin was calling for her mom...
You idiot!
You know Mama-lin was crying!
You're her mother, so stop doing
mean things to your child!
She consumed me...!
She consumes gods... What in the world?!
I get it! You must be a new breed of god,
created for the handover of the new generation!
A New God!
Impossible!
Did our Sun intend to end this long-standing myth,
the most unrivaled beauty in the world?
I will not acknowledge such a thing as a New God!
This is...!
"Chikaeshi no Juhou"?!
The meditation technique to seal away any apparition.
Sasami... How dare you?
I gave you birth, but you consider me an apparition?!
I'm sorry, Mom...
Go back to the Underworld!
Hi, Mother!
I wanted to thank you for that thing the other day.
Got a minute to talk about your daughter's future?
Stop playing around, you evil gods!
Don't you care what's going to happen to this world?
I must make this world the way it should be!
Until then I can never die!
I'm sorry, Tama, but I won't be coming home for a while,
so take care of things while I'm gone.
Sasami! Sasami!
I don't want to talk right now...
Sasami, eat something at least.
Okay...
I'm going to eat it later. Just leave it.
All right.
He understood me?
Today's menu is my specialty! My special ramen!
If you don't hurry up and eat, it'll get soggy.
For dessert is my love!
I don't want that dessert. You can take that back.
Understood. Too bad.
He understood me again?
Oh, it looks like you got a package,
so I'll leave it here too.
I'll be downstairs, so call me if you need anything.
Tsurugi?!
Hello?
It's me! I was in an accident!
Beware of bank transfer scams!!
I need to pay them consolation money,
so send me about 500,000 yen!
Beware of bank transfer scams!!
Yen          Yen           Yen           Yen
What's with this bank transfer scam?!
I thought you went to the Underworld, Tsurugi.
I managed to Alter some things
so I'm sending you this signal.
It's going to drain me if I talk long, so I'll be quick.
O-okay.
I'll be home after I beat up my stupid brother,
so take care of my sisters for me for a while.
And about your mother...
When I dragged her into the Land of the Dead
she was on the verge of crumbling away
because Tama consumed her.
She's not completely gone, though.
She may be resurrected some day, but
she can't do anything for a while. That's all.
Phone in use
Tsurugi
Okay.
Don't worry too much!
Well, I guess that's not that easy, huh?
But you wanted to choose this path
even if that meant disobeying your mother.
If you stagger and stall, that would be
even more disrespectful to her.
So look forward and keep on moving.
Promise me that, okay?
Okay...
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best a little longer.
After I take a little break, I'll be at it again.
Phone in use
Good. Just don't strain yourself too much.
I wish you luck.
Oh yeah, on the way to the Land of the Dead
I found something that belongs to her.
I shipped it to you, so go ahead and keep it. Bye.
Phone in use
Call Ending
Call ended
Call has
ended
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
I'm back!
Yawn... Welcome back, Tama. I'm glad you're okay.
I'm so tired.
I'm not surprised.
You were lost for a long time. Anyway, good work.
You're a person who can do anything
if you put your mind to it.
Well, since you're here, I want you
to go ahead and sing this song, too.
Big Sister Trusugi has disappeared
into the Land of the Dead
and Sasami has been suffering from depression.
We don't have anyone to sing the song.
I'll sing with you, too.
Are you really sure?
Okay, Tama will do her best!
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You're looking fed up but still smiling
Yawn...
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You're looking fed up but still smiling
Yawn...
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together
Zzz... Zzz...
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomade mo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
I can't do this anymore! Tama is finished!
Hey, were you singing at all, Big Sister Kagami?
I was.
If you didn't hear me, turn up the volume
on your TV and watch it again.
It's nice and easy to let Tama do things.
Yay, you praised me!
She's truly convenient.
Next Episode
Preview
Ganbaranai
It's time for Ganbaranai@Ranking.
@Ranking
The ones who don't do their best: Number 3...
The ones who don't do their best
No. 3
The arm on the crane game.
The arm on the crane game
Work
Work harder!
Harder.
No. 2...
No. 2
The ball pen with plenty of ink
which suddenly stops writing.
You have no intention to work, do you?
You have no intention
to work, do you?
No. 1...
No. 1
This preview segment.
This preview segment
I don't even know what's going to happen
in the next episode!
Next time, Episode 8:
Next Time
Episode 8
"Strategic Solitude"
Strategic Solitude