So what did you do yesterday?
I went to Seibu-chichibu
I see. What's at Seibu-chichibu?
I wonder...
Yesterday I went to Najimi's store and she drew me a picture.
I see.
She's gotten a little better.
Must be all the practice.
Did you go somewhere yesterday, Tsuyurin?
Seibu-chichibu.
Later today, I'm gonna play with Justice at the park...
Would you like to come?
I'm shopping at akiba and...
I don't have time to play with kids.
What a coincidence, meeting you in a place like this.
Nidou-san, are you buying stuff?
Erotic games?
No! I am...
It's not that I especially like them...
Erm..
I've never experienced one before, so for educational value...
The way you said that sounds like you're coming out and saying you're a virgin.
No, that's not what I meant.
Well, I've never done it before, but...
Oh, but I know how it's supposed to go, of course.
Nidou-san, would you like to do something that's better than erotic games?
Eh? Nidou-san's assistant?
Wait a second, Tsuyuri!
Whose side are you on?
An enemy to both sides?
What are you saying?
Tsuyuri!
She hung up.
This is trouble.
Nidou-san's assistant...
Pay attention to the shape and angle.
What's going on here?
Softer!
But I'm not going to lose!
Yes!  Now that's an excellent boob!
What kind of assistant are you?
Eh?  An erotic manga?
Me?
It's ok. Besides, ero sells better.
We should give it a try.
I can give a lot of advice for ero manga, also.
Will I be able to sell more than Najimi-san?
Easily.
Let's give it a shot, shall we?
Let's!
Let's make a really erotic one.
Yes, a really erotic one.
Immoral...
Immoral!
Perverted...
Perverted!
Hello?
Ah, Najimi-san's friend.
How'd you get my number?
I asked Najimi for it.
Ah, I see.
So, What is it?
I'd like you to help Najimi's rival.
What do you mean?
There's a girl who's competing with najimi to sell doujinshi.
And I'd like you to help her improve her drawing ability.
That's no good!
It'll be like betraying Najimi-san.
No, it's more like helping her out.
Huh?
People only grow after they overcome a challenge.
Don't they say, a tiger challenges its cubs by making them find you at shibuya train station?
I think you're mixing quotes with a dog story...
I understand!  Najimi-san must overcome this challenge in order to grow.
With your effort, you may gain something amazing.
S-something amazing?
Najimi's heart.
I'll do it!
What do you want me to do?
I'd like you to buy some adult doujinshi marketed to girls.
Adult doujinshi for girls?
Whatever suits your taste.
Ok, see you in 2 hours at Nerima station.
Hey wait!
This is Hoshi-kun, this is Nidou Kaneru-san.
Nice to meet you.
You're najimi-san's rival?
Yes.
Now, before we start drawing H-manga...
Hoshi-kun, the books.
Ah, umm...
Here.
I was thinking nidou-san would draw for girls.
I had him choose these.
That's his preference.
I thought so.
They really do exist, don't they?
I'm going to draw something like this?
That's what these references are for.
What do you think?
Well, I think you're free to draw whatever you prefer.
I see, freedom of preference.
There's conviction when you say it, Hoshi-san.
You think so?
Ah, I'll pour us some tea.
No, I'll take care of it.
You need time to practice drawing, right?
Ah, yes.
Well, if you don't mind. Thank you.
He really is feminine and attentive, isn't he?
I suppose.
It explains why Justice won't leave him alone.
Justice-san, as well?
Now that you mention it...
Uhm...
Yes?
Hoshi-san, is there someone I know who you like very much?
How did you know?
Are you seeing that person?
Well, no...  I just need an opportunity.
What about Sora-chan?
Does Sora-chan know about this?
Oh, her...
I don't think she knows.
What do you mean, you don't think she knows?
Huh?
Her precious dream...
Eh?  Um, Nidou-san?
We have to go.
Huh?
You're going to confess your love, right now.
Right now?
She should be at the park right about now.
This is so sudden!
The longer you wait to tell her the truth, the more you'll hurt her!
I understand now...
She's been waiting to hear my words.
I understand.
I'm a man... I'll go!
I'm sorry, Sora-chan.
We're about to destroy your cute dream.
And I'm also... sorry...
For I actually wanted...  Just a little bit.  A really tiny bit.
To see the two of them... coupling.
Honey flavor.
Sora-chan.
Kaneru-chan?
Is this the one you want?
Yes.
The ribbon should be...
Yellow, please.
I said Hoshi-san is going to confess his love to Justice-san.
Why?
There are people like that in this world...
And Hoshi-san is one of them!
I don't get it.
I'm so sorry.
Ah! Justice!
Now's your chance, Hoshi-san!
I have something to tell you!
Huh?  Why?
They're staring at each other.
What is it?
Hurry up, I have a promise with Sora.
Eh, well... Erm...
What the hell does that mean?
Wait, she probably wants me to settle things with this guy before I confess to Najimi-san.
Got it!
Listen, Justice!
I need to tell you about Najimi-san and me.
I'm listening.
I want to get along with Najimi-san, so...
Could you kindly watch over us?
No can do!
There's no way I'll allow you near Najimi!
What have I done to deserve this?
I've done nothing to offend Najimi-san.
Even when we went to the hotel for research...
I was hoping to make a move if the mood was right...
But in the end, the mood never was right!
-Never was right! Never was right! Never was right!
Dear good children,
It is now 5:30pm.
If you're still playing outside,
What do you mean?
Be good and go home safely.
Um, well...
What I meant was...
Justice-san is making the first move? This can't be.
I'd like to hear more details.
Oh, no!
He's aggressively closing his lips in!
No, you can't!
Stop!
Justice!
Hey, stop!
This is also a form of love...
I'll use it in my manga.
Only with appropriate consent, you two.
In all of history, I wonder if there was an anime with a dirtier mind.
Eh? There is?
Let me borrow the DVD.