Hurts, doesn't it?
Magi carry the pain of that Crest for their entire lives.
Your dad really gave you the perfect name.
Your origin lies in cutting and tying, kid.
It's a little more nuanced than destruction and regeneration.
If you cut a thread and then tie it back together,
the thickness will be different, right?
In that sense, it means irreversible change.
"Kiritsugu," with the characters for "cut" and "tie."
I have the perfect Mystic Code for you.
I've ground some of your ribs into a powder and put it in these.
Your origin will materialize in anything shot by this.
If you fire when your target's Magic Circuits are active,
it will cut, then tie the circuits improperly.
One shot will incapacitate any magus.
I've made sixty-six, in total.
Don't waste them.
Natalia...
Can you hear me?
Just a bit further.
Roger.
Natalia, now.
In the end,
after leaving the island, I spent the next several years
with Natalia Kaminski, the woman who took me from there.
That meant choosing the same path as Natalia,
the path of a hunter.
Natalia belonged to no organization.
She was a total freelancer,
only in it for the money.
The Magus Association and the Church.
The rivalry between those two enormous organizations
kept her business booming.
Since that time,
I'd witnessed many tragedies like the one
at Arimago Island.
I'd learned that, across the world,
the same horrors happened every day.
Are you trying to be a hero?
Was there no meaning to it?
I thought
I killed my father to keep all this from happening again.
Killing one man isn't the solution.
Kill every single person who is like them, all over the world.
If you could do that,
maybe it would be possible.
I was kidding.
Don't take it seriously.
No matter what happens, do what you must to survive.
That's a rule I set for myself when I started doing this.
No matter what happens, prioritize your life above all else.
If you try to save one person and die,
it won't help anyone.
I don't think it's possible to save everyone.
I just want to save as many as I can.
Do as you like.
This target is gonna be hard.
Do you know him?
The magus Odd Vorzak.
He uses his bee familiars to raise his army of ghouls.
The Magus Association has offered a huge bounty for him.
You know a lot about him.
He causes a lot of destruction.
In the last town he visited, we lost the entire place.
A town...
Natalia,
can I have one?
How old do you need to be to smoke in your country?
I won't stop you, but they aren't good for you.
Where's he going?
A flight from Paris to New York leaving in four days.
Vorzak will be on board.
I'll be on it.
I missed him once.
You've gotta clean up your own mess, right?
So even you fail sometimes?
He's that tough.
What should I do?
Most likely, he has allies in New York.
I want you to eliminate them.
You'll fight Vorzak alone?
He can't stow his bees in an overhead compartment.
Then this time, we won't miss him.
Shut your mouth, kid.
Kid, do you copy?
Okay, all clear.
Good luck to both of us.
Easier than I expected...
The less that's required to neutralize him, the better,
Natalia.
All right, Kiritsugu, his body is still in the passenger cabin...
Are you ready to carry it out?
I've secured a vehicle.
All we need now is a doctor
to carry out the sick patient.
As long as you don't mind that I don't have a license.
Hey!
Natalia, what's wrong?
Ghouls!
We have a problem.
He was keeping the bees
inside his own body?
Natalia, get out.
What do you think my altitude is?
Unfortunately, I didn't prepare to skydive.
Not good...
Looks like the cockpit's down.
I have no choice.
Natalia, you can't...
I'm going home.
I'm going home alive,
carrying Vorzak's body.
For that to happen, I need to do something about this plane.
Anything you want to say?
Yeah...
Natalia, you can do this.
That will do...
Prepare a nice, warm bed for me, and wait.
Can you hear me, kid?
You didn't fall asleep, did you?
Loud and clear, Natalia.
We've both been up all night. It's a rough morning.
If you'd slept in a bed last night,
I really would have killed you.
Now, good news and bad. Which do you want first?
Don't you always start with the good news?
Okay.
First, the good news.
For the moment, I'm alive.
The plane is also undamaged.
I made it up to the cockpit fairly easily,
though repairing the comm array wasn't so easy.
And I think I can pilot it,
assuming it works similarly to a Cessna.
Have you contacted the control tower?
I have.
Initially, they assumed it was some joke.
But they said they'll be nice and give me an escort.
And the bad news?
I'm the only one who hasn't been bitten.
Three hundred passengers and crew.
They've all become ghouls now.
All that separates me from the night of the living, flying dead
is the cockpit door.
Spooky, right?
Given all that, will you be able to make it back alive?
Well, the door's pretty tough.
They're scratching at it as we speak.
But they won't get through.
It's the landing that concerns me.
This thing may be too large for me to handle.
I know you'll be able to manage it.
Were those words of encouragement?
Good to hear them.
I can handle the landing,
but what do I do with these monsters?
Don't think about it.
I have it all worked out, Natalia.
Good to know.
Fifty minutes to the airport.
Too long to spend praying.
Kid, talk to me for a while.
No problem.
When you said you wanted to help with my work,
I really didn't know how to respond.
You didn't look ready to relent, no matter what I said.
Did I seem like such an unpromising student?
No, not at all.
You had too much potential.
Far too much...
What does that mean?
The ability to cast aside your feelings and pull the trigger
is a skill most killers
take years to develop.
You've had it from the start.
It's a hell of a gift.
But basing your calling solely on your talents
won't always guarantee your happiness.
If you think only of what you should do,
and neglect what you want to do,
you're merely a machine.
A force of nature.
That isn't how a human being should live.
I always thought of you
as a much colder person.
What are you talking about? Am I not?
Have I ever gone easy on you, even once?
You're right.
You've always been a strict teacher.
You never held back.
You did whatever you could to teach me.
Normally, raising a boy
is the father's job.
Well...
Ah...
In your case, I basically took away your chance for that.
Well, anyway,
I did feel a little bad about it.
This was the only way of life I could teach you.
So you consider yourself my dad?
Don't get my gender wrong, idiot.
At least call me "mother."
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I spent a long time alone in this blood-stained business.
So long, I even forgot I was alone.
Well...
It's been pretty entertaining, in its own way...
Having something like a family.
For me, too.
I really did think of you as my mother.
I was glad not to be alone.
Hey, Kiritsugu...
Quit saying stuff that'll embarrass us next time we see each other.
Jeez.
You're throwing me off.
I land in twenty minutes or so.
If I'm smiling sweetly over old memories when I try to land this thing, I'll end up dead.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I'm getting too old for this...
Perhaps I screwed up so drastically
because playing family made me lower my guard.
If that's the case, this is goodbye to my job.
Maybe I'll retire.
If you quit your job,
what would you do then?
If I weren't working...
The only thing left would be acting like a mother.
You are
my real family...
Did you see that, Shirley?
I killed again...
Just like with my dad.
I didn't screw up, like I did with you.
I saved many people...
If Natalia had landed successfully,
there's no telling how many people
might have died.
Her sacrifice prevented that...
So... So...
Shirley...
I...
Shut up! Shut up!
You bastard!
Kerry,
What kind of adult do you want to be when you grow up?
I...
Quietly the falling stars shine in the night sky
and the prayers they won't answer fill the Heavens and the Earth
Episode 19
Where Justice is Found
On a fragile branch shows the budding future you abandoned
and reluctant at its passing the bud falls to the ground
Beware, the time is ripe, for if you but reach for the golden fruit
the world will come to an end
The white of unblemished snow when it falls
disappears as it learns of human warmth
A beautiful dream tore you apart
It was the truth and the tenderness in your cold eyes
Quietly the stars of our prayers shine in the night sky
until your will brings down the dream we live
Who are you?
That isn't funny.
How does the life you took from Sakura feel?
By my Command Seal, I order my puppet...
That's the expression you used to wear.
This is a battle I started.
You know, I really am happy.
Next Time:
Return of the Assassin