Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
We saw a shooting star the other day...
...but Kagami said something about the
wishing three times thing being unrealistic.
Shooting stars are so wonderful.
I haven't seen many of them.
It's difficult to see the stars from our house.
Right...
Since your house is in the city, right?
I would probably be too amazed...
...to have time to make a wish.
The sight of a dazzling, shining star...
...would fill you with feelings of joy.
That could explain the myth
that shooting stars grant wishes.
Your honesty is what dazzles me.
The Many Ways
to Spend
Christmas
Eve
The Many Ways
to Spend
Christmas
Eve
It's almost winter break.
But we have finals first.
Do you have any plans for winter break?
Nothing.
Reminds me...
We haven't taken a vacation in a while.
I went to Asakusa the other day.
When was that?
You know how you get sleepy
on the train during winter?
She missed her stop?!
Huh?
But isn't that the opposite direction?
The train reached the end of
the line and turned around...
...and then I missed my stop again...
By the time I was conscious, we were in Asakusa.
Hey now.
You can only miss your stop so many times.
But it wasn't entirely a bad thing.
Since I hadn't visited Asakusa in a while.
Shouldn't be doing that right before finals.
And I had a feeling I saw a girl in a
sailor uniform with a machine gun walk by...
What was that about?
Don't tell me someone was making a hit.
And you know...
Sleeping more helps you grow more!
You're growing?
I got an even better one.
My dad pulled an all-nighter
and then went to turn in a manuscript.
He got on an early-morning train but missed his stop...
...then it reached the end and made a U-turn...
...and when he woke up, he'd already missed his stop...
...and this happened a few more times.
He started to wake up when
he got close to his station...
Patrasche...
...but he still ended up missing it.
I'm so tired...
He was tired and wanted to get
home and sleep, but he couldn't get home.
In the end, he no longer knew...
...which direction he was going whenever he woke up.
Unbelievable...
I still wake up before my stop when I fall asleep.
That's amazing!
How do you know?
Maybe she has an internal alarm clock.
Though it doesn't work all the time.
What was that?
Since she's always snacking away.
Shut up!
But train seats are really warm...
...so you get really sleepy.
That's true.
It's all warm and fuzzy...
...like you're sitting next to
the window in the classroom...
...on a sunny winter afternoon.
What's this?
Covering for each other?
I-It's not like that!
The other day...
When I tried to wake you up on the ride home...
Hey, wake up!
We're there.
Just five more minutes...
I mean it...
She yelled out half-asleep.
Everyone around us was laughing.
One of my friends did that in class once.
Sheesh.
Birds of a feather.
You're grouping us together?!
But why five minutes?
Well, if you went to wake someone up
and they were like, give me another hour...
...wouldn't you be pissed?
Well, that's true...
...but five minutes comes up
in a lot of other situations.
Like, just wait five minutes!
You have a point.
Maybe 'cause it isn't too long or too short?
Though the five-minute wait
for a train feels really long.
Sure does!
Guess so.
But then again...
People who say to wait five minutes...
...tend to make you wait a lot longer.
You know how people say to not use
your cell or put on makeup on the train?
But it's a lot worse when the
person next to you leans on you.
They're so heavy.
And you end up wanting to
stand after managing to get a seat.
And when you're stuck with
the sticky head of an old person...
Sometimes, I try to shove them off...
...but they somehow manage to
keep returning to the same position.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a mystery.
When I fall asleep...
...and there's a man on one
side and an empty seat on the other...
...I try to lean myself towards the empty seat...
...but for some reason, I always
end up leaning the other way.
Guess your body feels more
comfortable leaning a certain way.
When I see someone leaning over...
...I shrink up like this...
...then their elbow hits my side.
Doesn't that mean they're actually awake?
Really?
Well...
Bye-bee!
Goodbye.
You know how...
...some people at our school
take the inbound train home...
...and some people take the outbound train home?
Don't the ones who take the
inbound train look more refined somehow?
Since Yuki-chan's an inbounder.
That's not...
Yeah, yeah.
Back to the farm, fellas.
Oh.
This is the stop before.
Yo!
I didn't get any studying done yesterday.
I actually put in a lot of effort this time.
If I do say so myself.
How much studying did you do?
Only four hours.
A whole four hours!
Huh?
You're good at everything, Kagami.
Well, I do a lot of studying.
Just between you and me.
You're definitely really competitive.
Well...
Maybe it's my pride as the older sister...
I feel like I have to be ahead of Tsukasa.
Though I usually say neither
of us is really older or younger.
I used to be pretty worried about that stuff.
But Tsukasa probably wasn't much competition.
Well, that's true...
Stupid Kona-chan thinks she's all that!
It's almost Christmas!
I wonder what my present will be this year.
You still get presents...
How long did you believe in Santa Claus?
Santa Claus isn't real?
Holy cow!
Santa never came to Konata's house...
...so her dad gave her presents in his stead.
That's why she thought he might be out there.
That old man...
He really wants to look good
in front of his daughter, huh?
Hey, Hiiragi!
Hiiragi-san.
Here's the handout from before.
Gotcha.
And then, Hiiragi-chan...
Hiiragi!
You dropped your pencil.
Thanks.
Hey, Kagami!
Kagami-san.
Here's the handout from earlier.
Got it.
Sebastian, like. stinks.
Kagami.
You dropped your handkerchief.
Holy cow?
Maybe I go to Tsukasa's class a little too much.
My cavity started hurting recently.
My, how dreadful.
I really can't stand dentists.
You went to see the dentist
for your cavity the other day.
Is it better now?
Dentists take a long time on each tooth...
...and they have to repeat
the procedure for every tooth...
...so it takes a long time, right?
So I ended up escaping...
...after making a number of excuses.
What to do?
She sounded all cutesy...
...but that's pretty crazy!
Konata!
Wanna go wild with everyone on Christmas?
Sorry.
I already have plans for Christmas.
Oh.
Is it a man?
Something like that.
Are you going somewhere with your dad?
Nope.
I told Dad that I'd be home late.
Don't tell.me...
You're really going on a date with your boyfriend?
When did you...
Sorry to disappoint you...
...but I'm just working.
Oh...
Almost all the customers are male so I wasn't lying.
Thought you'd managed to get ahead of us.
You got me.
There's a special event on Christmas.
We dress like Santa CIaus for that.
You really love that kind of stuff, huh?
But you know...
You guys also cosplay as
shrine maidens for New Year's.
At your temple.
Don't call it cosplay.
Anyway...
It's good that Santa Claus gives everyone presents...
...but ever since I was little,
I was like, he's totally trespassing.
You shouldn't look down on
something based on a holy man.
Spiteful brat.
Still...
Santa is supposed to give children dreams...
...so what's with the men who
turn to this squirt with their dreams?
What's this?
You just casually insulted a lot of people?
And is it okay for you guys to celebrate Christmas?
Oh, yeah.
We usually got Christmas presents, right?
We worship every god there is.
We regularly visit temples.
And we sang in a church choir once.
Sounds peaceful.
But...
Yes?
A shrine maiden said she wanted
to get married in a wedding dress...
Is that okay?
Wouldn't that be a little complicated?
Yo!
Getting chilly these days.
Cousin Yui, welcome!
Whatcha watching?
A detective show.
Any good?
Not really.
Nothing else to do.
Okay, I got it.
That man's the killer.
Please wait, Officer.
There's something odd about this case.
Nothing odd at all.
Case closed!
What's with you?
This has nothing to do with you.
This is why cops are useless.
Aren't you a cop yourself...
Why'd someone have to call now?
They're about to reveal the killer.
How can you tell?
Look.
I see.
You're the killer, huh?
No use in hiding it now.
I wonder why these two-hour
shows always end on the edge of a cliff.
Maybe cause people aren't willing to
act until their back's against the wall?
Yahoo!
How ya doing?
Cousin Yui, evenin'.
Whatcha watchin'?
A movie for a popular detective show.
Dad rented it.
Crimes don't happen in conference rooms!
They happen at the scene!
No, no, that's wrong.
Nobody ever gets that passionate.
Yet you reject that...
Pretty sure that...
...the receipts were stolen at the behest of the chief.
This is why he fails.
You know what's going on?
That's right...
They eat pork bowls a lot in police shows...
...but apparently, that isn't actually allowed.
Well, it's fiction...
...so a lot of it's probably made-up.
So police commissioners'
granddaughters aren't really like that?!
Police commissioners' granddaughters?
Well, I've never met one.
I'd at least want Mai-chan to exist...
To give me hope...
Empty dream.
There sure are a lot of cases
with adults going after children.
Indeed...
I've been thinking...
If you teach kids martial arts...
...wouldn't there be a decrease in that stuff?
After intensive training...
...Master Oyama was able to beat a
cow with his bare hands, with one blow.
And bears toppled like trees after a couple of hits!
I see.
But won't that come back to haunt you?
When those kids grow up...
...the adults will be strong, too.
U-Um...
You know...
People say training in the martial arts...
...helps you mature as a person.
I see.
But...
There's someone who does martial
arts and hasn't matured right here.
How rude!
Oh.
I have this cousin, Cousin Yui's little
sister, who's entering high school next year.
She's physically weak...
Cousin Konata!
...but she's sweet and pure and really adorable.
But when I start thinking about how a
healthy spirit leads to a healthy body...
....I start feeling like something dark
is lurking behind those shining eyes.
I doubt aphorisms are universal.
Look at you.
The year's almost over.
Once it's December, you always
feel like the year flew by so fast.
Are you going to help out at your
temple as shrine maidens again this year?
Probably.
Come draw your fortune again.
With fortunes...
If you get really bad luck, it's an unpleasant feeling.
But if you get really good luck...
...it feels like you already wasted
your luck for the year, doesn't it?
Well, that's why people say average luck is best.
Okay!
Then here's an early present from your teacher!
Here are your report cards!
How did you do, Kona-chan?
Here! Good work!
Teacher!
I don't want this present!
We give presents based on effort in my school of Santa.
Think on it.
Like a bonus to your winter homework.
I wonder what kind of Christmas
cakes will be good this year!
When you go to a bakery...
...there are so many cute cakes...
...that you can have fun just looking.
What happens to the cakes
that weren't sold before Christmas?
Perhaps the employees take them home.
But if nobody takes them,
they might throw them away.
They often compare marriage to Christmas.
Like how twenty-five is the end of the line.
Once you're past twenty-five,
a Christmas cake is just another cake.
After one night, it's just another decorated cake...
...that suddenly looks stale...
...so you lose your appetite.
I was talking about Santa Claus
with Kona-chan the other day.
How long did you believe in Santa, Yuki-chan?
It feels like you would have
been a true believer like me.
I also believed in Santa Claus.
When I was little, I tried to send a
letter of gratitude to Santa Claus...
...and did some research.
But I didn't learn much after asking my parents...
...so I did some thorough investigating...
...and learned of the people Santa Claus was based on...
...and once I saw the phrase
"origin of Santa Claus" pop up...
...my dreams were quickly shattered.
How'd you do, Miyuki-san?
Lemme see!
Just what you would expect from Yuki-chan.
I could never do so well.
I feel a little pissed about losing...
Yuki-chan's at the top of our class so it's hopeless...
We could never beat her.
No.
I don't care about grades...
...but stuff like bust size...
Look! Whoa!
I'm hungry.
I'll have a cup of ramen.
Not done yet?
These three minutes of waiting feel really long.
I'll use this to kill time today.
And then your noodles end up soggy, right?
Me too!
The extra broth for my cup fried soba dried up!
You people...
She told me she would be late...
But this is too late!
I can't let her make a habit of this.
Need to give her a stern
dressing down every now and then.
As the man of the house.
I'm home!
Konata!
Come here for a minute!
What time do you think it i—
Merry Christmas!
This is my Christmas present for you.
It must have been cold outside!
Want some hot tea?
Yay!
I do! I do!
I'm so happy I could die.
Yo!
G'day!
Cousin Yui's here to save the day!
You stink of alcohol!
It's dangerous to DUI!
I parked the car somewhere and had a drink nearby.
Listen to me!
It's Christmas Eve yet my husband's not here!
Our plans tonight are...
Cousin Yui...
Shouldn't you go to your parents'
place instead every once in a while?
Hello?
Yui?
It's me.
I was going to sneak in and surprise you...
...but it was locked.
Are you at your parents' place?
I'm coming home!
Right away at full speed!
Running every light on the way!
Seriously, you shouldn't be breaking the law.
I'll drive you.
I've got a little time.
I'll log in for a sec.
Huh?
Teacher's on.
Teacher.
Let's go crazy.
Until morning.
Please wait one moment.
Christmas
Cakes
Ain't a leftover.
Doesn't count as a leftover.
Nanako Kuroi
'Cause I bought one.
27years old
Single
I was here last Sunday to buy manga.
Don't get why you pay the fare to come here so much.
Even if it's for the points...
...this is pretty excessive.
You really love this stuff.
Besides, do you even use the prizes they give?
I don't.
Thought so.
That kind of stuff is hard to use.
Yep. Yep.
lt'd be a waste to use.
Their value would go down.
Oh, so that's how it is...
Whatever.
No!
Yes.
Didn't you get shocked by static electricity?
Nope.
Why's that?
Konata's always sitting in front of the computer...
...so her body's already full of weird waves?
Still, I really can't stand winter.
And I heard you can get shocked
just by touching someone's hand.
Ow!
Are you sure you two don't really hate each other?
Holy cow.
Ow!
Whatcha doing?
Oh, I wanted to try it again!
Stronger!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
We're already on the eleventh
episode of Lucky Channel!
And on this eleventh episode...
...I have some wonderful news
you've all been waiting for!
U-Uh...
Everybody's sent in...
She's really in it today.
...lots of passionate letters...
...asking for Akira to show up in the actual show!
H-Hello.
On the next episode, I, Akira Kogami...
I'm the assistant Minoru Shiraishi.
Zip it!
...will be showing up in the actual show!
But I need to introduce myself!
Thank you to Konata Izumi from
Saitama along with everyone else...
...who sent postcards to Newtype!
So Akira-sama's also making an appearance?
What's with the...
"Like, you're finally showing up
in the twelfth episode?
I've been in it for, like, forever!
Ho. Ho. Ho."
...attitude you've got?
A-Absolutely not!
It's an honor to appear with
Akira-sama in the actual show as well!
Appear?
All you did this week was
pick up a handkerchief, yeah?
You shouldn't be thinking you've got
what it takes to make it in this business!
Don't forget that you can just disappear like that!
I-I'll keep that in mind.
After that announcement...
...you can't wait for the next episode!
You want it now?
Everyone is probably trembling...
Er, shaking naked in their boots in anticipation!
Hey.
We should treat our fans with care...
...and air it right now!
We can grab a thirty minute slot, right?
Uh...
That'd be pushing it...
Pretty please?
Or forget it.
So send any messages to the
radio show or the home page!
Bye-bee!
What to do?
It'd be bad if I overshadowed
the main characters, right?
It would indeed.
But there's a tendency for the
main character's friends and rivals...
...to end up more popular than
the actual main characters!
What?
A-Akira-sama?
What's wrong?
Aren't you...
Yes?
...talking about yourself?
Don't get so full of yourself
'cause you're popular lately!
No, absolutely not!
Don't expect this to last!
No, never!
You won't be placing first in the poll
What are you talking about?!
Don't mess with me!
That's impossible.
Listen to m—
Next we have a duet from Tsukasa and Miyuki-san.
Yuki-chan.
Let's go up front to sing.
You chose a song for them to sing...
How bizarre.
I know all kinds of songs.
But it's still an anime song, huh?
Anime songs actually come
in handy in these situations.
Not even close!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Tsukasa.
Um...
I was really hungry one night...
...but it was really late...
...so I was wondering if I should eat something...
I finally decided a little bite would be okay.
And then I went to the kitchen...
...and I remembered I had some snacks left over...
...so I opened up the freezer...
I'm already out of time?!
Next time:
「Let's Go to the Festival」
Let's Go to the Festival.
Look forward to next time!