[Narrator] Alchemy:
the science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter;
however, it is not
an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange,
the basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[Radio Voice] God's children,
who live upon this land,
pray in faith and
ye shall be saved.
Those who have lost their way
the Sun God Leto shall...
So what are you guys, like,
street performers or somethin'?
Seriously?! Do we look like
street performers to you?!
Well, yeah. S'why I asked.
Let's go, Al.
[CLANG]
Hey! Easy! I didn't
mean nothin' by it!
Sorry! Accident!
We'll fix it!
How's that?
It's smashed ta' hell.
Watch and learn, gramps.
♪ Energetic Strings ♪
[Alphonse] Okay. Here it goes...
[gasps]
There. See? How's that?
Amazing!
It's a miracle...
You've been touched
by the Sun God,
just like
Father Cornello!
Touched by who now?
[Al] It's not a miracle.
It's alchemy.
Oh, so you two are alchemists.
Right, I've heard'a them.
Then maybe you've heard of us!
We're the Elric Brothers!
The Elric Brothers you say...
(hmmm)
Wait--I do know that name.
The "Fullmetal Alchemist"...
Edward Elric, is that right?
Wow, so you're the young prodigy
they tell all the stories about?
Well Of course he is!
Just look at that armor!
That must be how he got
the name "Fullmetal."
[Al] No, um. It's not me...
[crowd] Huh?
What? You mean it's
the little guy there?
Who's little?! Come here and
say that to my face, I dare ya!
[radio announcer speaking]
[Edward] So... what's with
this guy on the radio?
Th-That's our leader,
Father Cornello...
[radio voice continues]
[Man 1] We were lost until he
came to town and began teaching
us all the ways of
the Sun God Leto.
[Man 2] He grants eternal life
to the souls of the faithful,
[Man 3] He can even
resurrect the dead!
His miracles are proof that
what he says is true!
So this guy's claiming he can
bring the dead back to life?
Now that's something
I gotta see...
[cheering]
[Edward] So that's it, huh?
What do you think?
[Alphonse] There's
nothing to think.
That's alchemy.
No doubt about it.
[Ed] But somehow he's ignoring
the law of equivalent exchange.
He should've only been able
to transmute that flower
into an object of equal mass...
[Al] And he's changing organic
matter into inorganic matter...
He shouldn't be able
to do that, unless...
[Ed] Yeah, there's
just one way...
Bingo.
[bell ringing]
clang clang
[Rose] O, merciful God...
Please, hear me. Hear my prayer,
I beg of you...
Please bring him back--
[Edward] Huh... so this
is the almighty Leto?
[Rose] Welcome. Are you
interested in Letoism?
Nope, can't say I am - not
really the "religious" type.
Well, I'm sorry to hear
that... To know God is...
...to know hope. If we
believe in divine grace...
Then through him all
things are possible.
If you believed--
I'm sure Leto would bless you
and make you grow taller!
[Ed] What's that
supposed to mean?!
[Alphonse] Easy, brother.
She's just trying to help...
[Ed] What about bringing
the dead back to life?
Do you believe
that's possible, too?
Yes.
[sigh]
Water, 35 liters; carbon, 20
kilograms; ammonia, 4 liters;
lime, 1.5 kilograms;
Phosphorus, 800 grams;
salt, two-hundred
and fifty grams;
saltpeter, 100 grams; and
various other trace elements.
Uh...?
That list represents the
complete chemical make-up
of the human body for
the average adult...
It's been calculated to the
last microgram, but still...
there's never been
one reported case
of successfully
creating a human life.
And you're telling me something
modern science can't do,
you can do with prayer?!
"Lift thy voice to God...
...and the prayers of the
faithful shall be answered!"
Did I mention, all those
ingredients I read off...
Down at the market, a kid
could buy every one of them
for the spare change
in his pocket.
As it turns out,
humans are pretty cheap.
No, that's blasphemy!
People are--
We're all children of God...
created in his image!
Heh. You have to understand,
alchemists are scientists.
We don't believe in unprovable
concepts like creators or gods.
We observe the physical laws
that govern this world
to try and
learn the truth.
It's ironic, really.
That through the
application of science,
we have in many ways
been given the power
to play gods ourselves...
So you're putting yourself
on the same level as God?
That's just-- sheer arrogance!
[Ed] You know,
there's an old myth--
about a hero who
flew on wings made of wax.
He thought he could touch the
sun, but when he got too close,
his wings melted, and he came
crashing back down to earth...
Right Al?
[Al] Brother...
[Ed] I'm sorry, miss...
This is difficult for me to ask,
but do you think
your Father Cornello
could even save an
arrogant scientist like me?
Of course! That's wonderful!
If anyone can lead you to
the creator's light, he can!
[Cray] Father Cornello,
there are visitors here
who wish to see you.
A child, and a man
wearing a suit of armor...
They would only give their
names as "the Elric brothers."
I can't be bothered now.
Just send them away.
Wait, "the Elrics"?
You're sure that's what
they said. You're positive.
Yes, Father. That's what they
called themselves, no mistake.
Damn... then this
is a problem...
Edward Elric, the
Fullmetal Alchemist,
has come to call on us.
That's him?
The man in the armor?
Hmm. Dressing the part,
it would seem.
But, why would a State
Alchemist be here in Liore?
Surely they can't have found
out about our plans...
[Cornello] It's possible
this dog's nose
is too sharp for his own good.
[Cray] This way, please.
Father Cornello is a busy man,
as you can imagine.
But you're in luck.
He's decided to spare
a moment for you.
Yeah, thanks.
We understand.
We won't take too
much of his time.
Good, then it's agreed.
We'll make this quick.
Brother Cray, what is this?
What do you think you're doing?
[Cray] Rose, these heathens
have come to ensnare
and discredit the
Father. They're evil.
This is God's will!
Brother Cray...
Well, like you said.
Let's make this quick!
Oh yeah! Strike!
[Cornello]
What's this commotion?
Ah, the Fullmetal Alchemist.
Welcome to the home
of our sacred order.
Father Cornello!
[Cornello] I must apologize
for my disciples' behavior.
It would seem they've
been misguided...
[Ed] Okay, let's say I
believe you weren't the one
guiding them. What next?
Have you come to learn
the ways of Leto?
Well, there are a few things
I'm curious about...
Like how you've been
using second rate alchemy
to deceive your followers.
My dear boy, I don't
know what you mean.
What your doubting
eyes see as alchemy
are the miracles of
the Sun God Leto.
Look again. Could
mere alchemy create
something from
nothing in this way?
[gasp]
[Ed] Yeah, that's what
I didn't get at first...
How can you perform transmutations
that ignore the law of
equivalent exchange?
As I said,
because it isn't alchemy!
But then I started
thinking about it...
If you'd somehow managed to
acquire a certain object
to amplify your alchemy...
one that's said to make
the impossible possible.
That would
explain everything.
What...?
[Ed] I'm talking about
the Philosopher's Stone.
Your ring.
That's it, isn't it?
I've been looking for that.
[Cornello]
The ring is just a ring.
I am God's humble servant.
It is from He alone that
I derive my power.
Still tryin' to
sell that line, huh?
If that's the way
you want to play it,
I guess I'll have
to come up there
and beat some truth out of you.
My, you really are quite
the incorrigible heathen,
aren't you? Rose, dear.
Yes, Father...?
That gun there
beside you. Pick it up.
Uh... Okay...
Now child, I want you to
shoot the Fullmetal Alchemist.
No, I-- Father,
I can't do that!
I am the Sun God's
chosen emissary...
My word is the word
of Leto himself!
Shoot him rose.
It's God's will.
[Cornello] Why hesitate?
When you lost your fiancé
to that tragic
accident last year...
...who was it that saved you
from the very depths of despair?
Have you forgotten?
It was you, Father...
That's right...
It was I who took your hand
and led you into God's light.
And do you remember recall what
it was I promised you then?
You said if I had faith,
you'd bring him back to life!
[Al] No, wait!
It's not me! Honest!
Dammit, I'm the
Fullmetal Alchemist!
It's not him! It's me!
It's the short one?!
You're kidding!
I'm sorry, but I have to do
this. I don't have any choice.
[Ed] He's been
lying to you, Rose.
You're wrong!
I've seen his miracles!
Father Cornello will bring
him back to life. I have faith!
Fine. Then shoot.
[gun firing]
ba-ang!
[Al] Uagh!
[Ed] Al!
[helmet bouncing]
chk clang chk
[screaming]
Ooh-aaaahhahhha!
Good. God Leto is pleased.
You have done well, my child.
Now pick up the gun and
shoot the other as well.
[Al] Haven't you made
her do enough already?
[shock]
Uh-ahuh!
But... your head!
I thought you were--!
Don't worry 'bout it.
He's pretty solid.
[Al] Yeah, see?
No harm done.
♪ exciting strings ♪
[Cornello]
An empty suit of armor
that walks and speaks?!
Do you still doubt it, Rose?
This unholy thing
is an abomination!
Evil of this kind
must be purged!
[growling]
And I believe my chimera
should be up to the task.
So this is the sort of thing you
do with the Philosopher's Stone.
That's just twisted.
Anyway, looks like
I'll need a weapon.
[magical ringing]
♪ music swells ♪
No transmutation circle!
So the State Alchemist
title isn't just for show.
You truly are
gifted... However--!
[roaring]
Your little spear is no
match for chimera claws
that tear through iron!
Heh...
You shredded my pants!
[Ed] But I guess those claws
don't do so good
against steel...
Bite him, you stupid beast!
[roaring]
[Ed] You like that, kitty?
Go on. Get a good taste!
[magical whimper]
[shocked]
Ahhhh...
[Cornello] Your arm...
A brother trapped in armor...
I see...
It's all becoming clear now.
You did it, didn't
you? The one thing
even the most novice alchemist
knows is strictly forbidden!
Why don't you come
down here and try me?
I'll show you real quick
who the novice is!
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Why don't you come
down here and try me?
I'll show you real quick
who the novice is!
[Cornello] Rose... this
is the price of their sin.
These fools attempted
human transmutation--
the greatest taboo
for any alchemist!
In their arrogance,
they tried to bring
someone dead back to life!
[gasp]
hhhhuuuuuhhhh
He thought he could touch the
sun, but when he got too close,
his wings melted, and he came
crashing back down to earth...
Oh no...
[Ed] This is what happens
when you try to play "God,"
or whatever you want to call
it... Take a good look, Rose.
Is this what you want?
So this is the great Fullmetal
Alchemist, Edward Elric--
Not even half a man!
Hell, not even half a boy!
And what're you?!
You're just a phony
that can't do anything
without a Philosopher's Stone!
[Al] Father,
we just want you to hand over
the stone before you get hurt.
Don't be absurd! Why?!
So you can use it for yourself?!
Please... If you fools are
really so eager to play God,
then perhaps I should send
you to meet him instead!
[gun fire]
BRAT-TAT-TAT-TAT-TAT
Huh...?
[Ed] Nah... Me and god, we
don't get along too well.
Even if I went... he'd probably
just send me right back here.
[gun fire]
BRAT-TATAT-TAT--TAT
[Rose yelling]
Ouh-aaaaahhhhh!
This way!
[people chattering]
[magic ringing]
[Ed] Yaaahhhh.
Well, don't just stand
there! After them!
These heathens seek to harm
the order! They must be stopped!
[running]
That's far enough.
What're you gonna do boy?
You're unarmed and outnumbered.
Look, just come quietly.
We don't wanna have
to rough you up.
[laughing]
hahahaha-ha
[screaming]
uhwaaaaaaahhh
Don't go easy just 'cause
he's a kid, ya got that?!
[yelling]
oh-haaaahhahuhh
[Ed laughing]
Ha Ha ha haaaaaaa
[Alphonse] What do you think
of Cornello now, Rose?
He just opened fire. He didn't
care that you were in the way.
[Rose] But... that's because--
What he said back there,
is true, isn't it?
[Al] We're not evil.
All we wanted was to see
our mom's smile again.
But our transmutation failed...
What we made...
wasn't even human.
[wind gushing]
We learned our
mistake the hard way...
People don't come back
from the dead... Not ever.
That's not true... I mean--
[Al] Alchemy is based on the
law of equivalent exchange...
The price of even a failed human
transmutation was enormous...
It cost my brother
his left leg...
and it cost me my whole body.
Do you see it? My brother
drew that with his own blood.
His leg had been taken.
He was bleeding.
I can't imagine
the pain he was in.
But through all that,
he still gave up his right
arm to transmute my soul,
and bonded me to
this suit of armor.
Now, I just want to help him get
his body back to the way it was.
He wants to find a way to
get me back to normal, too.
It won't be easy. We might
even get killed along the way.
But that's the path we chose...
All we can do is keep moving.
[Rose] But... Father
Cornello said...
He said he could do
it. He promised me...
Just because you and
your brother failed,
that doesn't mean--
It doesn't mean he will!
[running footsteps]
There you are,
you infernal brat!
Look, can we just cut
the crap and talk here?
All I want are some straight
answers about the Stone.
Tell me what I need to know
and I'll be on my way...
...or we could get
the military involved...
[angry grunt]
Ask your questions.
You could do anything with
the Philosopher's Stone, right?
So why waste all of that power
performing phony "miracles"?
Because with each miracle,
I can attract new
believers to the order,
believers who would lay down
their lives for my sake.
I'm slowly building an army!
A legion of holy warriors,
unafraid to die!
In a few more more years,
I'll be ready to unleash this
mindless horde upon the world!
And I'll use the Philosopher's
Stone to tear this country apart
Who knows? I might even carve
you out a slice for you!
[evil laughter]
[childish laughter]
Wait, what are you
laughing about?
I knew it. You really
are a novice, aren't you?
[Cornello echoing]
You don't mean that--!
[Al] There were never
any miracles, Rose...
He lied to you.
He lied to everyone.
[Cornello echoing]
Why you...!
[Cornello through speakers]
How long?!
How long has that been on?!
[Edward through speakers]
From the start.
Your "believers"
heard every word.
[Cornello] How could you?!
You'll pay dearly for this!
[magical ringing]
Sorry... Not today!
[Ed] Just face it...
you're outclassed here.
I am without rival!
[magical laser lightning]
[explosion]
[gasping in pain]
ughh ukggg uh
It-It's a rebound!
No! I won't be
disgraced like this!
Now, boy... Behold...
...the chosen emissary
of the Sun God Leto!
[explosion]
[ground being crushed]
[Ed wincing in pain]
My word is the divine
word of god himself!
My fist is the almighty
fist of judgment!
Oh, yeah?
The fist of god, huh?
Well if that's what
you want, you can have it!
[magic electricity]
[yelling]
OUGHAAAAAAAH!
Shut up! Just give me
the Philosopher's Stone!
What the hell? The stone...
It's supposed to be
perfect material!
How did it just
break like that?!
[Cornello] I don't know!
I don't know anything about it!
Spare me! Please! I-I was
wrong! Please! I beg you!
It's a damn fake.
[Cornello] Please don't.
I'm helpless without the stone.
Spare me, please!
You mean, we went
through all this...
risked our lives just for
this one possible chance...
...and it's a fake.
So, uh...
What about me?
I don't care what you do!
Just get outta here!
Right!
[Alphonse] And what
about the Stone?
[Edward] A phony.
Just like him.
[Al] Oh.
I'm sorry, Al.
For a while there,
I thought we'd really found
a way to get your body back.
[Rose] Give me the
Philosopher's Stone!
[Al] Rose...
Like I was
just saying...
It was a fake.
It wasn't real.
And besides,
it's shattered now...
Liar!... You want to keep it
for yourself, don't you?!
So you can use it on your
bodies... that's right!
And so you can try to bring
your mother back again!
You shut up!
People don't come back from
the dead, Rose. Not ever...
Not ever...
[Rose] But he promised me...
He said if I prayed,
it would happen. A miracle...
That hope was all I had left!
What am I supposed
to believe in now?!
Tell me what to do... please...
I can't tell you that.
You have to figure it out.
[Ed] Stand up and walk...
Keep moving forward...
You've got two good
legs. So use them...
You're strong enough
to make your own path.
[angry mob yelling]
Bring him out here!
That damn brat.
It's all ruined--
everything I've worked for...!
[Lust] Yes, all that
hard work for nothing.
I knew we should have just
incited a little rebellion.
[Cornello] You--!
I'm hungry, Lust.
Can I eat the old man?
Please? He's big and fat.
Not this one, Gluttony...
We don't want you giving
yourself indigestion.
Now you, too?! Everyone is
mocking me! I won't stand fo--
[stabbing]
[Cornello] Urrgghhhuh
[Lust] I'd say this
concludes our business.
Just as things were beginning
to look promising, too...
Now I suppose we'll have to
start over from scratch...
[Lust] Father won't be
pleased. In any case,
it's time we started
thinking about our next move.
[chomp]
[Narrator] Following the
incident in Liore,
Ed and Al travel to the
Eastern Command Center
to report to Colonel
Mustang. Once there,
the brothers are taken to
the home of the Sewing
Life Alchemist, Shou Tucker
and his young daughter, Nina,
where they hope to learn more
about the field of bio-alchemy.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode 4.
An Alchemist's Anguish.
Some meetings in this life are
destined only for heartbreak.