TAKA-AMAHARA SHOPPING CENTER
This is a warning.
Due to the acts of foolish humans, a lethal virus has spread.
Hyakuya
Orphanage
As such, the human race will regrettably cease to exist.
Mika, the director's...
Yuu, keep watch over the others!
Director! Director!
However, it is known that children of thirteen years and younger are unaffected by the virus.
Yuu...
Henceforth, we, the direct unit
of Third Progenitor Krul Tepes,
will now proceed to place the children
of this district under our protective custody.
Four Years Later
Next.
Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
Clear. Next.
Hyakuya Mikaela.
You'll get sick if you keep
throwing those out, you know.
As if I can drink this disgusting crap!
You're such a gourmet.
And you just do whatever they tell you.
I don't think it's that bad here.
Are you serious?
As long as we stay here, we won't be killed,
and more importantly, we can live with our family.
Isn't that enough?
I won't let them treat me like livestock!
Jeez, you know being stubborn won't help at all—
Hey!
Yuu! Don't!
Apologize!
I said, apologize!
Um, I'm sorry! He's not the sharpest tool
in the shed and has a few screws loose,
Hey!
so, um, please excuse him!
Cut it out, Mika!
I'm gonna kick his—
Good evening.
Is he a noble?
Lord Ferid!
Hello, Mika.
What were you up to?
It's nothing big.
Just one of my family members stirring up a fuss.
That sounds rather worrisome on your end.
Putting that aside,
will you be coming to my mansion again tonight?
Yes, please!
Good boy.
Boys with exquisite blood
are always welcome in my house.
Will that boy be joining us?
What? You freaking wish—
He's really shy, so maybe next time.
Is that so?
What a shame.
Why did you apologize?
I was gonna kick his sorry ass!
There you go again with that nonsense.
Listen, there's just no way for a human to physically overpower a vampire.
You don't know that until you try!
Rather, how can you not know?
Just don't go overboard, Yuu.
That was a really close call.
Do you and that noble know each other?
Is that a problem?
Lord Ferid gives me anything I want in exchange for my blood.
He gives me proper food, too.
You have to use your head
to survive in a place like this.
Yuu, don't you also have something you wan—
No!
Here again?
What are you doing?
Aren't you supposed to be with Mika?
Why would I be with that idiot?
What? Did you guys have a fight or something?
Oh, be quiet already.
And don't get so close to me.
Why not? We're all one big family.
I don't have a family.
Of course you do!
The director told us that everyone
in the Hyakuya Orphanage is family.
Sounds dumb.
All right, kids.
We have a new family member today.
His name is Yuuichirou.
Make sure to get along, now.
Roger!
Hey, Yuu.
I'm Mikaela.
I'm an orphan just like you,
but I have a big family now!
And now you're a part of that fam—
Family? Don't give me that crap.
I came here because my father almost killed me.
My mother cursed my existence and called me a devil child,
and then she took her own life.
Do you get it now?
"Family" is nothing but a—
You've had it pretty rough, huh?
But as of today, we're your family.
Welcome,
Yuuichirou
C'mon, let's get going already.
We're all waiting on you for dinner.
Come straight home, okay?
Yuu!
You took so long, Yuu!
Me too.
I'm starving!
All right, I get it. Stop crowding around me.
Guess what? We're having curry tonight!
Akane's cooking us curry!
Curry?
How did you...
Surprised?
Mika just brought a whole bunch of ingredients.
It's my first time cooking a feast like this,
so I'm pretty excited.
That dumbass...
This is great!
What's wrong, Yuu?
Aren't you hungry?
Oh, yeah...
Carrots! There are carrots inside!
It's like it's my birthday today, you know?
And mine!
No fair! It's mine, too!
Me too!
All right, then. Today is officially everyone's birthday!
Yay!
Don't forget to thank Mika for this food.
Okay!
Where'd he go, anyway?
Why isn't he here?
Yuu, where's Mika?
Oh, Mika's actually...
Taichi took mine!
Then I'm taking away Taichi's curry!
No way!
Aw, my curry...
Hey. I'm home, Yuu.
Whatever.
What, no "welcome back" or anything?
Just to let you know,
I ate your portion of the curry too.
Seriously?!
Of course not.
The kids enjoyed it.
So? What did it take
to get the ingredients for that curry?
Jeez...
Next time, we're using my blood.
That horrid-tasting blood of yours isn't gonna get you very far.
Kidding.
Don't worry about it.
You're gonna teach those vampires a lesson, right?
So until then, I'll—
Stop it!
Stop trying to shoulder everything on your own.
I'm not... I'm not an idiot.
Even I know that defeating vampires is—
That's enough.
These kids really hang on to your every word.
"We will defeat the vampires."
"We won't lose."
Those words you keep saying.
All right, let's eat some curry.
Here. You never ate, did you?
Don't want it.
It's yours.
No can do.
This isn't a request. It's an order.
Why do I have to take orders from you?
Because you have to fight the vampires with this.
But you can't fight on an empty stomach, am I right?
You...
But that's not all.
Ta-da! A map of the city.
It even clearly marks the exit!
Did you steal these from that noble?
Ferid's mansion is huge,
so I was snooping around for a while.
As if Mikaela the Mighty would just give his blood away for free!
But that all ends today.
Let's run away together.
Don't worry. I've got this.
I have it all planned out.
Leave it to Mikaela the Mighty!
But what about the virus?
They say there's only death waiting outside.
It doesn't affect kids thirteen and younger, right?
How old are we now?
Twelve.
We'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
If the two of us stay together...
If the whole Hyakuya Orphanage family stays together,
then it'll all work out.
I can't tell if you're smart or just really optimistic,
but who said you could decide all this stuff on your own?
What are you guys doing up?
It's pretty late.
Oh, welcome back, Mika.
Yuu, you finally ate some curry?
All right, let's do it!
Yeah, let's go!
Akane, wake all the kids up.
Wh-What?
It's time to say our farewells to this world!
This way.
Hey, Mika, where are you taking us?
I don't like the dark!
Walking out at night is against the rules, you know.
It's fine. Don't worry.
We're going to say bye-bye to this world anyway.
Why?
Say bye-bye and go where?
Well...
Back to our world.
It'll be curry day, every day!
Really?!
We can really eat curry every day?
What about Salisbury steak?
Once we make it through here, we're free.
All right, we're at the final stretch!
Let's go.
Yeah.
I've been waiting for you.
My poor, pitiful little lambs.
Yes, those faces of yours.
The expression that humans make as all hope drains from their faces...
That's the reason why I can't stop playing this game.
Game...?
Oh, dear. Dead already?
Damn you!
Oh?
That's my gun, is it not?
Not only the map, but the gun, too?
That's rather commendable.
It seems the will to fight back still resides within you.
Worry not. There's still hope left.
That map is not a counterfeit.
The path back to your world lies straight ahead.
Once you escape, chasing you
would be quite difficult for me.
Caught between hope and despair,
I wonder how your cries will sound...
Run!
Now!
I told you, didn't I?
We gotta hold him back!
Please, stop it...
Stop!
Akane!
I want to see that face of yours in despair.
Don't forget, Yuu.
We're family.
Wait!
Mikaela, your blood was divine.
Thank you.
Yuu...
Run...
Die.
Mika!
Hey, Mika!
Go, Yuu.
Don't you dare say that!
We're supposed to leave together!
Don't let us die in vain...
No... No!
I don't want to...
I finally...
I finally had a family of my own!
I'm not leaving you behind!
Hurry up and go!
You idiot!
Yuu... That's the first time
you've ever called us family...
Good. He made it.
Just like the prophecy said:
one of the test subjects from those responsible for Japan's destruction, Hyakuya Laboratories, will appear.
Young boy.
We're going to use you to eradicate the vampires.
Fine by me.
If I can annihilate those vampires...
Four Years Later
A World Joined by
Blood
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Humanity
after the Fall
"Humanity after the Fall."