Cowboy Bebop Season 1
ASTEROID BLUES
Hey, Spike.
- It's ready.
- I'm just about done myself.
What's cooking?
Special beef with bell peppers.
Asimov Solensan. This is our next target.
Hey, Jet...
He's high up in the syndicate
that deals all around the asteroids.
About this beef with bell peppers...
The guy's name is Asimov Solensan.
Weren't you listening to me?
You don't call
a meatless beef with bell peppers
"beef with bell peppers," do you?
Yes, you do.
- No, you don't.
- You do when you're broke.
What happened to the million-woolong
bounty from that last guy?
The repair bill
for the plane you wrecked...
and the shop you trashed...
and the medical bill
of the cop you injured
killed the dough!
Three days ago, there was a shootout
between his group and an enemy syndicate.
He killed his own men and took off.
They say he's hiding
with his woman in Tijuana.
That's a place for nobodies to go.
Despite being a nobody,
he's worth 2.5 million.
Don't feel like it.
Tijuana... The beef there is really tasty.
Attention, please.
We will soon arrive at the gate.
We look forward to serving you again.
I'll head over
after hitting up the cops for clues.
Then I'll try seeing old man Bull.
Can you trust that old guy?
Such an easygoing song.
Thief!
This again? Goddamn son of a bitch.
Man, you're totally ripping me off,
but do you realize
the reason you can live here
is because I dug that gate
with all my might?
This again.
You always say that when you lose.
We all dug the gate together, remember?
That we did.
We dug like there was no tomorrow.
Goddamn idiot son of a bitch!
Give me a beer.
And I'll have a bloody mary.
I got vodka, but unfortunately,
I'm out of tomato juice.
I'm sure there's one can in the back room.
I'll take a look.
Top-notch Red-Eye.
You'd know, as a buyer, right?
Can it be... Bloody-Eye?
Prove to me that it's the real thing.
Keep those eyes open.
This is dandy,
but you got anything to eat?
I see.
The red-eyed coyote will appear
at the north end of town.
That is what I see.
A red-eyed coyote, huh?
You, Swimming Bird...
You shall meet a woman.
You shall be targeted by that woman.
And then death.
- Again. I see.
- Again?
I've already died once.
Got killed by a woman.
You take women too lightly.
Catch you later.
May he be blessed by Wakantanka.
Presidente?
I'll have a glass on the house.
Damn. Asimov sure lost his head.
No shit. We gotta do something
before the cops start moving.
You wanna leave it up to the cops?
He is using those eye drops.
There's no way we can win.
I'm telling you, we got nothing
if we don't get that Bloody-Eye back.
But, man...
Hey.
Can you give me the specifics?
Man, I'm hungry.
You, too?
It's better to leave the water running.
Or it'll clog.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I don't want that anymore.
You can have it.
I'm really sorry, honest.
Felt like my stomach was glued to my back.
Nice fighter.
It's an old model.
She's been with me for over ten years.
Looks like you've gotten a lot
of use out of it.
I travel around a lot.
I'm actually a wandering performer.
I can't tell if you're for real
or just joking.
A lot of people say that about me.
- Been to Mars yet?
- I was born on Mars.
They have everything there.
Unlike here, Mars has lots of people,
lots of things...
They must live happily there.
Only the rich.
Then I'm sure we'll be happy there.
You planning on escaping to Mars?
Running away... But how far can you go?
Who are you?
An old-fashioned cowboy.
A bounty hunter?
Good call.
You're not going to catch us?
Your buddy seems to be pretty ill.
I don't deal with weakened nobodies.
Wise decision.
You are the nobody.
Asimov. That's enough.
Adios, cowboy.
Why did you stop me?
I could have killed him in a second.
You're tired. If you do this anymore...
He was young and attractive.
I was waiting for so long
for you to come pick me up.
I can finally escape
the lowly life I've had here.
I can finally live happily on Mars.
A nap. How peaceful.
- I had a good dream.
- That's great.
You can see the rest of that dream
on the Bebop.
I'm giving up on this one.
It's impossible to catch him.
There's no way we can win.
When Asimov left his syndicate,
he snuck something out with him.
The top-end stuff of all the illegal
eye drops that the syndicate makes.
He took off with all of the drops,
so, the group is in a mess.
They wanna catch him,
but all they get back are corpses.
Because Asimov is using it...
The eye drops known as Bloody-Eye.
They're planning on going to Mars.
Mars?
But before that, they'll sell this off.
- That's...
- I grabbed it from his breast pocket.
You... met him?
A nightmare.
He got you?
The red-eyed coyote will supposedly appear
at the north end of town.
This again? Goddamn son of a bitch.
Man, you're totally ripping me off,
but do you realize the reason
you can eat well around here
is because I cultivated the land
with my buddies, you hear?
Yeah, and that's us.
That we did.
We planted seeds
like there was no tomorrow.
You were always planting seeds
of a different kind, though.
Do you have bloody marys?
I only got beer.
I've got tomato juice.
How much?
Three hundred thousand woolongs.
I got 50 packs.
Fifteen million Woolongs, eh?
I'm in a hurry.
I'll find others if you don't want it.
Show me.
Looking for this?
Hey, do you know what you are worth?
- What?
- Only 2.5 million woolongs.
You're such a cheap guy.
Long time, no see.
Since when are you a buyer?
Did you give up on bounty hunting?
No thrill in cheap bounties.
Looks like you do better as a thief.
Give it back.
Sure, I will.
I owe you one--
You trust your eyes too much.
You're not a chameleon.
You can't see everywhere at once.
Let's go!
That way!
What the hell are you--?!
Don't move!
All right, stay still.
Idiot!
We're doomed if these break.
Be more careful.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're late, Jet.
Shit.
Asimov.
Stop! Doing any more is insane.
Don't do it.
Don't!
We can't run anymore.
There's no way we can get away.
Hey, Spike, it's ready.
- It's ready.
- What's cooking?
Special beef with bell peppers.
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
COMING EPISODE
- This program is finally under way.
- What's the meaning of this?
Next week we're completely changing gears
to show an anime for all ages.
Cheerful animals wreak havoc all over.
- What?
- But an animal expert isn't coming.
From little kids to the elderly,
if you love animals...
Hold on, Spike.
- Everyone gather round and watch the show.
- Is it okay to say stuff like that?
But I ask one favor.
Good kids should sit far from the TV.
Stand back about a kilometer.
STRAY DOG STRUT
- Too far.
- Eight hundred meters, then?