[NARRATOR] Alchemy...
the science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter;
however, it is not
an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange,
the basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[NARRATOR]
Scar, the man who was
responsible for killing
a string of State Alchemists,
came after Edward Elric.
Ed was ready to accept
death at Scar's hand.
But thanks to the intervention
of Colonel Mustang
and the military,
Ed was able to
escape with his life.
Ed and Al, realizing
the joy of being alive,
were once again determined
to survive and move forward.
They decided to return to
their home in Resembool
to seek help in
repairing their bodies.
[KNOCKING]
[ED] Huh...?
Hey.
[ED] Lt. Colonel?
[HUGHES]
The folks at the Eastern
Command Center were
a little too busy to
make it down here today,
so I came to see
you off instead.
Great, but would
you mind telling me...
...what the major's
doing here?
For protection...
What would happen if
Scar came after you again?
You're in no shape
for a fight now, Ed.
The Major's
here to help.
Just try to grin
and bear it.
Children can
be so stubborn.
Hey shut up!
I'm no child!
Anyway... are you sure
Al made it on board?
Of course.
[SHEEP BLEAT]
I thought he might get
lonely without a little company.
My brother isn't some
kind of farm animal!
[HUGHES]
Oh... it's time.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
Okay, you boys have a safe trip.
Stop in and give me a shout
the next time you
make it to Central.
[ED SNORES]
[ED YAWNS]
[ED YELLLS]
[ARMSTRONG]
Doctor Marcoh!
Doctor Marcoh,
that is you, isn't it?
It's me! Alex Louis
Armstrong from Central.
[ED] Friend of yours?
[ARMSTRONG]
He's from Central...
A talented State Alchemist.
He was researching into
possible medical
applications of alchemy.
But after the
Ishvalan Civil War,
he went missing--
just disappeared.
[ED]
Let's go, major.
A guy like this
doctor might know
some useful things
about bio-alchemy.
[ARMSTRONG]
Excuse me, but do you know who
this person is by any chance?
Wow, major, you
can really draw.
The art of portraiture
has been passed down through
the Armstrong family
for generations.
[VILLAGER A]
That man looks like
Dr. Mauro to me.
Mauro?
All of our town's doctors
were drafted to help
on the battlefields
during the civil war...
Then Dr. Mauro came here.
He's really been a lifesaver.
He'll see any patient and
he never gives up on anybody.
We're lucky he's here.
You see this big,
bright flash of light,
and then you're cured,
just like that!
Hmm...
[ED]
This is it.
Um, hello!
[GUN FIRES]
[MARCOH]
All right... Tell me what
you two are doing here.
Have you come
to take me back?
[ARMSTRONG]
Please, Doctor...
calm down.
I don't ever want to go back!
Anything but that!
That's not it.
Please listen.
So you're here
to silence me, then?
No, nothing like that!
I won't be tricked by you!
[CRASHING SOUND]
I'll ask you one more time:
please, calm down!
Alphonse!
[ARMSTRONG]
So, you changed your name and
decided to live in hiding way
out here in the countryside.
If the rumors I've
heard can be believed,
when you disappeared...
You took top-secret
materials with you.
[MARCOH]
I couldn't handle it anymore.
Order or no order, to
have to dirty my hands
researching that
thing was too much.
What 'thing' is that?
It took so many lives...
During the Civil War,
so many innocent
died because of it.
I could spend my
whole life trying
and still never atone
for the things I've done.
But I had to do something,
so I came here to be a doctor,
to save lives instead
of taking them.
Doctor...
what exactly was it
you were ordered
to do research on?
What 'thing'?
The Philosopher's Stone.
[ED AND AL GASP]
The top-secret materials I took
were my research documents...
...and the stone itself.
Do you mean you
still have it? It's here?!
[ED] How can that be
the stone? It's a liquid.
[EVERYONE GASPS]
The Sage's Stone...
The Grand Elixir...
The Celestial Stone...
The Red Tincture...
The Fifth Element...
Just as the Philosopher's Stone
is called by many names,
so it can take on many forms...
It is not necessarily a stone.
This is an incomplete
product, however...
There's no way to know when
it will reach its limit
and become unusable.
[ED] Finished or not, it
demonstrated plenty of power
during the Ishvalan
Civil War, right?
Huh...?
[ED] It's just like the stone
that false priest had in Liore.
It was incomplete, but it still
amplified his
powers considerably.
If imitation stones this
powerful can be produced,
who's to say a complete
product can't be created?
[THUD]
Please, Dr. Marcoh,
I need access to your
research materials.
[MARCOH] Major...
Who exactly is this boy?
This boy is
a State Alchemist, doctor.
What?! But he's only a child!
[MARCOH GRUNTS]
[MARCOH]
After the war, there were
many State Alchemists
who turned in
their certifications
because they refused to serve
as human weapons any more.
And now a child...!
[ED] You think I don't know
what I've signed up for?!
I know what I'm doing,
but I don't have any choice.
If this is a mistake, then it's
a mistake I have to make.
There is no other way.
[MARCOH]
I see... So you've
committed the taboo?
Amazing...
the ability to transmute
a specific person's
soul like this.
Maybe one as talented
as you would be able
to produce a complete
Philosopher's Stone.
So...!
But I can't show
you my research.
Why not!?
You must not
seek after the stone.
Not even if it's to
get our bodies back?
Never!
This is the
devil's research.
If you chase the stone,
you will go through hell!
I've already
been through hell!
[MARCOH] Please...
Please, just leave.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ED]
I've already been through hell!
[ARMSTRONG]
Are you sure
about this, Ed?
Huh..?
Even an incomplete Philosopher's
Stone could be useful.
You could have taken it
from the doctor by force.
Yeah... I wanted it so badly,
I could almost taste it.
But, still...
But still, we don't want
it so badly that we'd be
willing to deprive this town of
their only doctor to get it.
We gained plenty just
by finding out that
the Philosopher's
Stone can be made.
Now we'll just have to look
for some other way to do it.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ED]
What about you, Major?
How do you feel about
not reporting back
to Central on Dr.
Marcoh's location?
I met a simple,
small-town doctor today.
I can't see any real
reason to report that.
[ED LAUGHS]
[MARCOH]
Wait!
[MARCOH BREATHES HEAVILY]
[ED]
Dr. Marcoh?
[MARCOH]
This is where
my materials are.
If you're certain
you won't regret
learning the truth
in the end,
start looking here.
Look closely...
maybe you'll find the truth
hidden within the truth.
But... I've said
too much already.
[MARCOH] I hope
the day will come
when you are able to
restore your bodies.
[AL] Brother...
What does the note say?
[ED] National Central
Library, First Branch.
I get it.
Like hiding a tree
in the forest...
Finding one book
in that giant library
will be
difficult indeed.
Finally, another clue
about the stone!
[DOOR CREAKS]
[MARCOH SIGHS]
[LUST]
I've been looking
for you, Marcoh.
[LUST LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[DOG BARKS]
[PINAKO]
Winry...! Winry!
Our best customer's here!
Huh..?
[ED]
Yo! Granny!
[AL]
We're home!
[PINAKO] Oh dear,
what have you done now?
[ED]
A lot has happened.
Can you fix us up?
[LOUD THUD]
This is Major Alex
Louis Armstrong.
I'm Pinako Rockbell.
I know I haven't seen
you for awhile, Ed...
But you've gone
and grown smaller!
Granny...
you've got it wrong.
You're supposed to say
"how big you've
grown lately, Ed."
But why would I say
something so clearly untrue?
I'm still taller than
you, you mini-hag!
[ED YELLS]
Edward, I thought
I told you to call first
when you're heading
back here for maintenance!
Winry! Are you
trying to kill me?!
[WINRY LAUGHS]
Welcome back!
Yeah...
[WINRY] Oh no!
[ED] Yeah, sorry.
It's a little smashed up.
"A little smashed up?"
"A little," Ed?!
Do you see what you've
done to my beautiful creation?!
I slaved over this!
It's basically the same;
it's just in smaller pieces.
[ED YELLS]
Don't tell me...
You a little
smashed up too, Al?
What kind of trouble
have you two been
getting yourselves into?
[AL YELLS]
You idiots!
All you ever do is worry me.
[PINAKO]
All right, I see.
In order to get this
information you need,
you want to go to Central
as soon as possible, am I right?
[ED] Yeah... this is
kind of a rush order.
[PINAKO]
Hmm... it's not just the arm.
Your leg needs adjusting too.
Guess you're growth's not
completely stunted after all.
Oh, shut up!
[PINAKO] The leg aside,
the shape the arm's in,
we'll have to build
it from scratch.
Is there any chance you
can have it done in a week?
[PINAKO]
Give us some credit, Ed.
Three days.
But you'll have to make do
with this spare for now.
It's a little difficult to walk
on a leg I'm not used to.
[PINAKO]
We'll be finished before
you get used to it.
Three days, huh...?
Between machining, assembly,
connecting, and finishing...
That's three all-nighters.
I'm sorry for
all the trouble.
Well, you want
to get to Central
as soon as possible, right?
Then I'll work
my butt off for you...
But you better
believe you're gonna
pay a fortune in
rush order fees!
[LOUD THUD]
[ARMSTRONG GRUNTS]
The wood
you requested.
Oh... thank you.
I haven't seen Edward anywhere
around the house in a while.
Yeah...
He said he was going off to
visit his mother's grave.
[PINAKO] Major.
What kind of lives are
the boys leading these days?
Hmm?
They have yet to send us
so much as a single letter.
Ed and Al are well known
for their alchemy,
even in a high-profile
place like Central...
Sometimes that gets
them into trouble.
They seem to have
a knack for finding it.
But don't worry.
They're all right...
The Elric Brothers
are strong boys.
[PINAKO]
Strong, huh...?
Yes... I think you
could call them that.
I'm curious,
Madam Rockbell...
You speak of
the Elrics as though
they were
your grandsons...
Of course.
I've been watching over
them since they were born.
I'm a friend of
the family, you see.
The boys' father is an
old drinking pal of mine.
One day he up
and left the village,
abandoning his
wife and sons.
I don't even know whether
he's alive now or not.
[ARMSTRONG]
Come to think of it, Madam,
where are young Winry's parents?
Gone, Major...
They both died
in the Civil War.
My son and his
wife were surgeons.
They went to the battlefield
to do what they could.
There were never enough doctors
for all the injured soldiers.
It was...
terrible... the war.
Yes, it was indeed.
Oh, looks like it's about time
for me to get supper started.
You look like
you could eat a lot,
but don't worry;
there's plenty.
Oh no, please don't trouble
yourself on my account.
[PINAKO]
Food always tastes better
with guests anyway...
We also have an
empty patient's cot
and some spare bedding
if you'd like.
The boys don't have anywhere
else to stay but here...
Adding one more guest won't
be any inconvenience to us.
What about the house
they grew up in?
[PINAKO]
It's gone now...
The brothers don't have
any home to return to.
The day they left,
after Ed had gotten
his state certification...
...they burned down
their own house.
My guess is they did it because
with no house to come home to...
...there could be
no turning back.
[DOG WHINES]
Yeah, you're right.
We should head back.
I'm back...
Oh, Edward Elric!
Gyaah!
What unyielding love
to try and bring
your mother back to life!
What a tremendous
sacrifice to give up
your arm in order to transmute
your brother's disembodied soul!
What determination to
burn down your own house...!
To make sure...
there was no retreat!
Come Edward...
Allow me to offer you
this comforting embrace!
[ED] Just stay back!
Don't rub your chest on me!
Aahhh!
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[BUZZING SOUND]
Look at you, working hard
so early in the morning.
Been up all night.
Heh, Heh, You're still
at it, busy as a bee.
At this rate,
you must be almost done.
One more all nighter.
Oh.
[THUD]
[WINRY]
Get out!
[DOOR SLAMS]
[BIRDS CHIRP]
[AL] They said it would
take three days, right?
So, give 'em three days.
[ED]
Yeah, I know, I know...
It's just when I think of
a clue to the stone sitting
in Central library somewhere,
I get so impatient!
[DOG BARKS]
Here you go!
It's all ready!
[WINRY LAUGHS]
[PINAKO] Ready?
Ah... yeah.
On one...
Two...
[PINAKO AND WINRY]
Three!
[ED GRUNTS IN AGONY]
That's the worst
part every time.
When the nerves have
to connect like that.
[ED] Once we have
the Philosopher's Stone,
I can kiss
that pain goodbye!
Our biggest
source of income...
I'll be sad to see you go.
[ED YELLS IN AGONY]
Hold still...
Ugh... Do you want me
to do this right or not?
It's just so lovely!
The smell of oil!
The hum of the ball bearings!
The rugged yet amazingly
beautiful form
created through
anatomical engineering!
Ah! How wonderful
you are! My automail!
Crazy gearhead...
You're lost without me,
alchemy freak.
[PINAKO]
All right. We're done.
Well?
Yeah...
It feels good.
I increased the percentage
of chrome this time,
so it should be
less prone to rusting.
The tradeoff is that it's
not quite as strong,
so don't try anything crazy--
Hey! Listen up!
[ED]
Al, it's your turn!
[ARMSTRONG]
You can fix him right here?
Yep... You have to know
the trick to it, though.
Major, you see that seal
on the inside of his back?
That's the medium between
Al's soul and the armor.
So I have to be
sure not to ruin it.
There you go!
You're good as new!
You ready to try it out?
Yeah!
[PINAKO]
It'll be quiet around
here without those boys.
Well, Brother?
Yep, it's time to head
to Central and find
Dr. Marcoh's documents.
We leave first thing
tomorrow morning.
[ED SNORES]
Sleeping with his
tummy out again.
What am I gonna do with him?
It's like you're
the older one...
Huh, Al?
He can be a handful.
Someone has to
look after him.
[PINAKO]
How old are the two
of you boys now?
[AL] I'm fourteen...
and Brother's fifteen.
To think someone as young
and as small as he is...
...could be used
as a human weapon.
It's almost funny...
especially watching him sleep.
[AL]
Thanks... both of you.
[WINRY]
What's this? Why so formal?
[AL]
Granny, Winry...
I'm so grateful to you for
always welcoming us
like we're really family.
He won't ever say it, but...
I know Brother
feels the same way.
[WINRY] Al...
[PINAKO]
Don't you worry, dear...
We know he feels
that way, too...
He doesn't have to say it.
[AL]
Granny... Winry...
...thank you.
Thank you again
for everything, Granny.
[PINAKO] Sure.
[AL] Hey... where's Winry?
[PINAKO]
Resting. She's stayed up
three nights in a row.
Want me to wake her?
No, that's okay...
She'd just nag me.
Make sure to do
maintenance or whatever...
[PINAKO]
Hold on a second, boys.
[ED] Hmm?
You should come back
once in a while
and have dinner with us.
[AL AND ED LAUGH]
You want us to
come all this way
into the mountains
just for some dinner?
[PINAKO LAUGHS]
[WINRY]
Edward...! Alphonse!
Come back soon, 'kay?
[ED] Yeah!
[AL LAUGHS]
[WINRY YAWNS]
I just about slept
through the entire day.
Whenever Ed comes over it's
like a tornado hit this place.
Huh?
Whoopsy...
[NARRATOR]
Doctor Marcoh's notes on
the Philosopher's Stone
were indeed in
the place he said.
But nothing is ever that easy.
Unfortunately for the Elrics,
the enemy is always
one step ahead,
leading the boys
ever deeper into
the maze of "truth
within the truth."
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Seven. "Hidden Truths."
The only way to
reach the destination
is to never turn away.