Bon, I'm sorry for lyin' to you.
Be good to Rikko.
Take care.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
Where are you going this early in the morning?
I thought you were acting odd last night.
Looks like the sneaking suspicion I had was spot on.
Hey, wait!
Wait, I said!
Let... go of me!
Move!
I'm not moving, you idiot!
If I do, you mean to go away for good, don't you?!
You're going to run off somewhere!
Are you planning on leaving everyone and everything behind?
Sorry. I can't be here anymore.
Since when did you become such a coward?!
Where's the guy who told me,
"Nothing good comes out of being afraid"?
What the hell are you guys doing this early in the morning?
Bon-ouji, are you okay?
Nii-chan?
Fighting about the festival?
I understand that you're really into it, but...
I couldn't sleep last night.
The truth is I was scared too.
Is something wrong?
Just for a minute,
even if it's just one, let me stay like this.
Ritsuko! Did you bring in today's paper?
Yeah! I left it by the phone.
Oh, I see it!
I'm home.
It's Dad!
Welcome home, Dad!
Welcome home!
Did you bring us anything?
Dad, your hair's turned gray.
Has it? I suppose it has.
Did you bring presents?
Yes, I bought you stuff.
Yay!
Let's have 'em!
Hey, at least let him set foot in the house first.
WELCOME
HOME
DAD
Everyone, I'm sorry for being away all this time.
You look cute!
Look, Nii-chan!
That's great, Taichi.
And this...
...is for you, Sentaro.
Um, I don't know if you'll like it or not, though.
It's a fountain pen!
You're lucky, Nii-chan!
Wow...
Something expensive like this is wasted on me.
A child doesn't go turning down a present from his parent.
Oh, looks like everyone got a present.
Sachiko, pass these out.
Okay!
A child and his parent...
Are you coming to practice today?
Yeah.
Startin' today, I'm gonna practice my ass off for the festival.
You mean it?
I mean it!
What the hell?
That was a weird way to greet each other.
MUKAE
RECORDS
JAZZ
POP
CLASSI
Me at the festival?
Yes, I was hoping that you would play bass for us.
You're asking me out of the blue.
Adults have a lot of things on their plate, you know.
And there'd be so much to prepare.
You can't do it?
You're totally prepared!
Ain't no way we can lose now!
Hey, hey!
How's it goin' for you guys?
Oh...
Right now, we're in the middle of getting our costumes fitted.
There's no way we're going to lose against you guys this year.
It's so flamboyant.
We, on the other hand...
...are plain. Way too plain.
We don't have any razzmatazz.
At this rate, we might not be able to beat them.
That stuff doesn't matter.
All we gotta' do is let our music do the fightin'.
I know! I know that,
but this is our last school festival.
I just don't want to have any regrets.
Easy to say.
But appealing to people who have no interest in jazz is a tall order.
W-What are you saying?
I can't sing!
Don't worry.
There are still ten days left. We'll work it out.
Rikko, if you're gonna refuse, now's the time.
'Cause if you decide to do it,
we're not gonna go easy on you.
If you don't wanna sing, tell us right now.
But I hope you don't turn us down.
Sen's got it right.
Would you help us out?
Alright. I'll give it a try.
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens...
Kit-tens...
No, you've got no swing!
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens
Bright copper kettles and warm woolen mittens
Brown paper packages tied up with strings
These are a few of my favorite things
Cream colored ponies and crisp apple strudels
Doorbells and sleigh bells and schnitzel with noodles
Wild geese that fly with the moon on their wings
These are a few of my favorite things
Girls in white dresses with blue satin sashes
Snowflakes that stay on my nose and eyelashes
Silver white winters that melt into springs
These are a few of my favorite things
I simply remember my favorite things
And then I don't feel so bad
"My Favorite Things"...
My favorite things are...
The footsteps of a certain person heading towards the house...
The sound of the piano and drums riffing in the basement...
The laughter of two boys...
Silly, I know.
Drums and watermelon and onigiri...
Those are a few of my favorite things...
What the heck is that, Sentaro?
Go on, Bon. Your turn!
Tell us your "favorite things."
I don't have any!
Even before Ricchan said hers, I had something in mind.
My "favorite thing" is this time right now.
Tomorrow's the day.
All that's left is playing our best at the festival.
Bon,
how about playin' "Moanin'" one more time?
Hmm...
Nah, let's save it for tomorrow.
If we started jamming now, we wouldn't stop.
I see. Yeah, you're right.
Well, see you tomorrow, then. Don't be late.
Yeah!
He forgot to take this.
Ah, well, you don't need a score for jazz.
An' I can just give it to him tomorrow.
Oh, where are you going?
I'm gonna run to deliver something he left behind.
Kaoru-san left a while ago.
You might not be able to catch up.
I know, I know.
19th School Festival
Sen's late.
Hey, hey!
It's almost time for our battle.
Huh? Where's your partner?
Don't tell me he's late.
No, uh...
Seiji, come on!
Okay!
Well, see you later!
Ricchan...
Sentaro...
He got into an accident on his motorbike last night
and was taken to the hospital.
S-So, how is he?
I don't know!
What should I do?
Kaoru-san...
Sentaro is... Sentaro is...
Ricchan, calm down!
I'll go to the hospital to see how he is.
Stay here until I get back.
Dammit!
I've dashed down this slope countless times, but it's never felt this long.
CITY
HOSPITAL
Um, excuse me!
I'm looking for...
I'll help you when it's your turn,
so please get in line.
Wait!
U-Um...
I heard there was an accident.
They've finished operating,
but it's serious head trauma.
He still hasn't regained consciousness.
No Visitors
He might never wake up again,
the doctor said.
Don't talk like that!
But...
That's right!
Even when Sen is all bloody from a fight, he just laughs it off!
Um... the one in there is Sachiko.
I don't know why, but Nee-chan was riding on the back of Nii-chan's motorbike last night.
They got hit by a car.
Then how is he?
He's hurt, but not too bad.
He was sitting over here earlier.
I see. Thanks!
That's right!
The place he's most likely to go...
...has gotta be...
I've seen this angel before somewhere.
If you're gonna take somebody to Heaven, could you make it me an' not Sachiko, angel?
Why do I end up hurting the ones I most want to protect?
Why... was I even born?
Bon? What's wrong?
Hey, what are you cryin' for?
This way, we don't have to see each other cry.
What do you mean "we"? I ain't...
It's okay to cry, Sen.
You've been keeping it bottled up all this time.
Sacchan!
Thank goodness,
Huh? Sen?
At the time, it looked like he was just stepping out...
...but he disappeared, and the festival was over before it even began.
And then...
It's Bon nii-chan.
Kaoru-san...
Um, here. If you're able to eat these...
Do you know where Sen nii-chan went?
Sen nii-chan would normally never give me a ride on his bike.
But I had a twisted ankle and kept complaining about it to him.
The accident was my fault.
I have to apologize to Sen nii-chan.
Sacchan, right now, if you focus on getting better,
Sentaro will come back soon!
You want to show him that you're healthy again, right?
Yeah.
I said all that to Sacchan, but the truth is...
Kaoru-san, what'll I do if Sentaro never comes back?
Ricchan...
We're talking about him.
I bet when we least expect it, he'll suddenly turn up.
Don't you have that feeling?
Yeah. You're right.
He will come back, won't he?
Sure.
Kaoru-san, don't go anywhere, okay?
Um...
Excuse me...
Oh. I remember you. Bon-kun, right?
Do I know where he might be?
Sorry, I'm afraid I don't.
Um... Father,
he left this behind.
He once told me the reason he always wore the rosary as a necklace was because
he was afraid that if he lost it,
he would be abandoned by the world.
Se—
I thought maybe Sen had come back.
Pops, he's not coming back.
I'll never be able to practice with him again.
W-What are you talkin' about, Bon?
Never again...
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.