Please...
Marry me!
You're pathetic.
But fine. If you insist, I'll marry you.
Takasu Ryuji's Doghouse
Quick, Ryu-chan, come see!
Taiga-chan's given birth!
Look at all these babies!
They're yours.
Just a dream...
A True Tale of Horror
~I Gave Birth to Puppies~
I'm supposed to be on vacation...
And here I'm having nightmares because
of some crappy movie I rented...
Dream or not, though, that's gotta
be the worst future ever.
Hey, Taiga.
I had a terrible dream....
You were a dog...
My husband was a dog...
In other words...
Worst dream ever.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
- A premonition?
- Yeah.
When You Go To The Sea
A warning that I have to do something,
or else that miserable future in my
dream is all I have to look forward to.
So, to prevent that, one of us has to
have the other's back on this trip.
I get all that, but why badminton?
Like I said...
We have to settle who gets to do what.
Are you listening?
Don't use the stove.
Stir the rice bran once a day.
Make sure to change Inko-chan's
water every morning.
The rest is in the note I left you.
Okay, I've gotta go.
Go? Where?
Told you, didn't I?
We're going on a trip.
Bye, Ya-chan.
What a lovely day!
You better follow through with
the plan, like we agreed.
Are you sure?
You win! You win! Get this thing off me!
If that stupid dog hadn't gotten
in my way, I would've won.
You were punished for challenging
me to something you're good at.
Seriously, nothing good happens
when dogs are involved...
Do you honestly think this'll work?
Just let me handle it.
By the time this trip is over,
you and Minorin will be...
What is it? Something wrong?
Good morning!
You're right on time!
Excellent! Well done!
What's wrong!?
Show some spunk, people!
Shout it out!
- The heck? They from the zoo?
- Y-Yay?
- So last century.
- What an absolutely fine day for a trip!
- Don't look!
- Uh-huh...
But Amin isn't here yet!
She still has time!
Yep! And I have an idea!
Huh?
Nobody's here yet.
Y-Yo...
You're two minutes late, Ami.
Morning, Amin!
You're late, dumb Chihuahua!
Wh-Where is everyone?
Don't run away, dumb Chihuahua!
Ami! We're right here!
Platform 3 Departures: Dancer #1 - 8:30
Izukyu-Shimoda - 10 cars
Wow! This tastes great!
The plum inside makes it super plummy!
You always deliver, Takasu.
Want to be my groom?
Not on your life.
Aw, you're such a meanie.
Huh?
Oh, hey...
I don't see Aisaka-san.
Is she running late?
Maybe you should give her a ca—
Ow!
What was that for!?
Oh, you're awake, Dumb-chi?
Thought you were sleeping
with your eyes open.
What!?
Could you please not fight
while we're on vacation?
So anyway, what've you done over
the break so far, Kawashima?
Me?
Just working.
Oh, you went back to work?
What about you, Minorin?
Softball, work, softball, work,
softball, softball, work,
- ...softball, work, softball, work, softball...
- A-And you, Taiga?
What have I been doing?
What's this, Taiga?
Something I made.
I-I heard a weird voice go "senpai"!
Could this be...!?
Uh-huh.
I made a collection of spooky voices
from some weird CDs I have.
I knew it!
Oh, no! They were calling to me!
Do you enjoy scary stuff like that?
U-Um, I guess.
I would never have guessed.
I'm also a bit surprised Kushieda
doesn't seem to enjoy it.
Understatement! I hate it!
Absolutely hate it!
Completely loathe and despise it!
Minorin is terrified of scary movies,
ghosts, and all that occult stuff.
Right...
So you and I are going to scare her to death.
And just when she feels overwhelmed
with fear, you'll swoop in to save her.
Shouting, "I'll protect you, Kushieda!"
It's Operation Scare Minorin,
Cue the White Knight!
So! No scary stories allowed!
It's the ocean!
Man, how far are you making us walk?
Can't you see it from here?
Let's circle around back.
We'll head straight to the porch.
This is your beach house!?
And we're staying here!?
That's right, Minori-chan.
Holy cow!
I'm impressed!
But first, we'll need to tidy up.
This place hasn't been used since last year.
L-Last year!?
Y-Yeah...
This should be an epic battle...
You're kidding!
But the beautiful ocean is right in front of us!
Save the cleaning for later!
- What!?
- Agreed!
We can clean later!
Hey, wait for me!
I'm going to join them.
Will you?
That's good!
Why am I cleaning by myself?
Feels so nice!
Hey.
What's up?
Look over there.
Isn't that a human head?
A floating corpse!
What should I do!? I've been
standing in corpse juice!
- They seem to be having fun.
- My bad, Minorin! I think it's just seaweed!
- I didn't expect you to come, Yusaku.
- Then it's a seaweed corpse!
- Of course.
- I've been standing in seaweed-corpse juice!
It's my duty as Takasu's friend
to go where he goes.
No problems with the student council?
What are you talking about?
Nothing...
Takasu!
Ami wants us to go shopping.
She says there's a moped in the shed.
A moped?
Oh.
You should take Taiga with you, then.
Aisaka?
N-Not a chance.
Mopeds freak me out.
What!?
Be careful.
Will do.
So long!
Man...
That was your chance to be alone with him.
I was using my head.
We need to find a good spot for
the plan before they get back.
Just admit you were too embarra—
Mosquito on your face!
Jeez...
What does she mean by "a good spot"?
This is...a bathroom?
Definitely needs a good scrubbing.
Wh-Who's there!?
Sorry! I didn't know!
Takasu-kun?
I-I'm leaving.
You've got balls to walk in
on a girl taking a shower.
I-I didn't do it on purpose!
It's okay.
I'll keep this a secret from the others, if...
Wh-What are you saying?
Well...wanna do it?
D-Do what!?
Clean the bathroom!
Please, what were you expecting?
That expression is priceless!
Taiga...
Dumb-chi did what?
Pretended like she was taking a shower?
Toyed with an innocent young man's heart?
So? You done checking the second floor?
You're so useless!
No wonder Dumb-chi tricked you so easily!
Fine.
I'll do it.
And I'll yell at Dumb-chi while I'm at it!
Come here, Dumb-chi!
Dumb-chi was actually taking a shower.
Dumb-chi was all...
Boom!
And boing!
And bam!
You don't need to tell him that!
We're back!
Quite the haul.
Where's Kitamura?
Putting the moped away.
I-I see.
Oh, I'll help carry it all in.
I-It's okay!
You did the shopping.
You sure?
Wh-What's wrong?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Something just brushed against my neck!
Must be your imagination.
Y-Yeah...
You're right!
No, I'm sure something just touched me!
Something slimy and seaweedy!
I-It even smells like it! So it must be!
A seaweed-wrapped animal ghost...
A sea otter?
Seaweed-wrapped sea otter corpses!?
A sea otter with its pocket
stuffed with scallops!?
I've been cursed by sea otters and seaweed!
No way!
I can't stand spicy food!
Well, I prefer curry that way!
Curry should be mild!
Hey! Ryuji!
I know.
I'll make sure yours is mild.
There you go, giving Aisaka-san
special treatment again.
You're gonna make all the
other girls hate you.
Including Minori-chan.
What!?
Howdy. You rang?
Wow, almost done? Mad skills.
Y-Yeah...
I just need to add the roux.
You all should get set up—
Oh, making dinner already?
I can help set the table.
Y-You're...
H-Hey! Taiga!
Yusaku...
Are you insane!?
Oops, sorry.
I heard Takasu talking.
Forgot you girls might be here too.
Are you a moron!?
Taiga!
Wake up!
Sorry about that.
- Hey! Hey!
- Uh, whoa...
You proud Adonis!
Give me a nude shot!
Oh, you. Stop that.
Your innocent act doesn't
work when you're naked!
- There's my shot!
- Aww, stop it...
I just saw something black and bushy...
I-It was probably a seaweed ghost.
Seaweed, huh...?
Kushieda!?
Yusaku, you're disgusting!
S-Sorry...
Just go!
Y-Yeah...
Watch out, guys...
This house is haunted by evil spirits...
Is there anything I can do?
Make the curry really spicy...
Got it.
Looks delicious!
Didn't have much to work with,
but as Kushieda requested,
I made it extra spicy.
Excellent!
Chow time!
Let's dig in!
Mmm, not bad at all.
It's quite good.
Not as spicy as I expected, though.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Want a bite?
You're right, it's not that—
Minorin?
Hot!
My throat is...!
Burning! On fire!
It hurts!
This is it!
The knockout punch!
Hells yeah!
- Here it comes again!
- You guys okay?
Takasu-kun!
You rock!
It's super spicy and totally delish!
Indeed.
It somehow keeps you craving more...
I feel kinda funny...
Uh, there's more, if you want.
Hit me!
Yikes...
Thought I was gonna die...
Done! I'll do the dishes.
I'll help you.
What is it?
Too much spicy food, I think...
I need stomach medicine...
Your stomach hurts?
I didn't bring anything...
You're not feeling well, Aisaka?
I brought medicine.
It's in my room. Wanna come get it?
Huh? U-Um, that's...
Great, take care of her!
What!? Wait...
It's a chance for you to be alone with him.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
She's all yours!
Right.
Hey.
My tummy hurts too!
Just kidding.
Wh-What's with you?
Nothing.
You were spacing out.
Never a dull moment when you're around.
Is that a compliment?
Maybe, maybe not.
What's that supposed to mean?
Whatever.
- How about we go down to the beach?
- Takasu-kun, can ya grab that glass for me?
Oh, I can wash it.
Sorry. You were saying?
Nothing.
Was that enough water?
Is it helping?
I think so...
Really? I'm glad.
It hurts me to see you in pain, you know.
Oh!
Perhaps you should lie down?
Your dish-cleaning technique
is really something.
I've gotten a lot of practice at work.
Your curry was a wonder to behold.
Nah, not really.
Oh, hey!
Let me treat you for helping me out.
Keep it a secret from the others.
Takasu-kun...
How's the green tea flavor?
Oh, it's fine.
The red bean one's kinda bleh.
Check out all those stars!
Y-Yeah, they're pretty...
We're alone.
Is this my chance?
Ku-Kushieda, do you have a b-boyfriend?
Do you think that seaweed
ghost is still around?
Takasu-kun...
Have you ever seen a ghost?
What? No, I haven't...
I believe ghosts exist, even though
I've never actually seen one.
But I don't believe any of the
people who claim they have.
Okay...
And, well, this applies to something else, too.
I believe I'll fall in love one day, get married,
and live happily ever after...
Even though I've never actually
felt that way about anyone.
It's like I live in a different world from the
people who fall in love so naturally.
And since I've never "seen" it before,
maybe those "ghosts" don't exist, either.
I've nearly given up on ever seeing one.
So...the answer to your question is no.
What about you?
Can you...see ghosts?
I think I'm interested in seeing them.
That's why I check out mystery
spots and watch scary movies.
The way I see it...
Even people who can easily see ghosts
are amazed by their first experience.
Then there are the people who've
seen them, but deny their existence...
And finally, those who have to work
really hard to see them at all.
But all in all, I see no reason to give up.
What's that?
A UFO?
No, that's a satellite.
A satellite, huh...?
Darn...
I thought it was a UFO...
You know, I hope you see a ghost one day.
I-I'm sure there's a ghost out there
who wants you to see it.
That must be why so much
weird stuff happened today!
What?
The seaweed ghost is trying
to get my attention!
Wh-Where did that come from?
Maybe I will see it someday...
Never mind.
You're so strange...
Hey, Ryuji.
My stomach feels better now.
Oh. And?
I really stuffed myself.
Why did I eat, too...?
So...
What should we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm obviously talking about the plan.
You haven't done a thing.
And you have?
I-I'm playing a support role right now!
Jeez...
Anyway, I'm tired.
I thought spending a whole day with
Kitamura-kun would be a thrill,
but I was such a nervous wreck,
it shortened my life expectancy.
Maybe.
But I'm dead calm when I'm with you.
The hell? That's not very nice.
This is dumb.
Why am I sitting so close to
you in such a huge room?
Guess I've gotten too used to being
in that cramped apartment.
Hey, now...
Ryuji, I've been thinking...
That dream wasn't so...
What was that?
Nothing.
I'm going to sleep.
Huh? All right...
Good night.
Huh? When did I put my bag here?
What the hell is this?
It's slimy...
Ryuji!
Look!
I found this dress in my bag, but when
I touched it, it was warm...
Like someone was just wearing it...
Th-There's something weird in my room too.
Long hairs on my pillow...
Wh-Who's there!?
I-It must be...
W-We're dreaming, right?
Y-Yeah, gotta be!
We're picking up from that dream
where you had puppies,
and I was living in a doghouse!
So if we close our eyes,
we'll eventually wake up, right?
We sure will!
Or will we?
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Scary! Scary! Scary!
Horror movies are scary!
Ghosts are scary!
Steamed buns are scary!
Stay calm, Kushieda!
But...
UFOs might be the scariest of all...