Mirage Dance!
Gotta hang in there!
All those trash monsters got cleaned up, you say?
These girls are surprisingly good.
Well, good timing.
I was just starting to feel a little bored.
I realized that I wanted to be protected by Sis forever.
So I was fine being weak.
That's what I was thinking.
But when I wished to change—
when I wished to become stronger...
You managed to transform?
That doesn't help me at all.
I've never once thought that I was fine being weak.
I-I suppose...
Okay. We're nearly there.
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
Sis!
Nepgear!
Rom...
Ram...
Uni...
I see you managed to transform, Nepgear.
Yup! I'll save you right away.
I wouldn't be so sure.
#05 The Goddesses' Resonance (Over Limit)
Good job making it this far, Candidates.
My name is Arfoire.
I'll be the one to bring joyous tidings of chaos
to this world ruled by those four young ladies—
Compa!
How I've missed you!
Huh?
Oh, hi.
Hey! Don't interrupt me!
Why would you do this?
What are you after?
Allow me to educate you.
What I seek is a new system that doesn't need CPUs—
a world where anyone can become a ruler.
You just want to rule the world yourself!
If someone stronger than me shows up, they're free to knock me off my throne.
That's how a world of equality works.
Am I wrong?
Stop trying to pretty up your own ambitions!
You're just envious of the goddesses' powers!
There may have been a time when I felt that way,
but not any longer.
Because...
I myself possess the power of a goddess!
She transformed?
But she's not a CPU!
Cross Combo!
No way!
That's my ultimate skill!
How can you use that move?
I have the ability to copy others.
And now I've even made the goddesses' techniques my own!
No way! That's impossible!
I made it possible!
Tanzerin Trombe!
Stop it!
Don't be mean to Nepgear!
Go suck on a pacifier or something, pipsqueak.
I... hate her.
Yeah, me too.
You and I...
Let's beat her up!
Rom...
Ram...
You won't get away with this!
Better prepare yourself!
Huh?
Well, what can two transforming toddlers do?
Ice Coffin!
Yay!
Lace Ribbon Dance!
Rom! Ram!
Now it's my turn.
I'm the only one who can't transform.
And Sis is watching all this, too.
Why do I keep worrying about her?
Right now, I need to...
Hit.
Hit!
Hit, dammit!
Uni...
All right!
That's it, Uni.
Focus on your target.
I see it!
EX Multi Blaster!
No doubt.
Only resolve!
Uni!
That's so cool!
H-Huh?
I transformed.
You did it, Uni!
Way to go!
B-But of course!
A hero always arrives fashionably late!
Yup. You're right!
Uni.
Bravo, ladies.
What's happening?
Wh-What's going on?
Right on time, I guess?
Do me a favor, Compa.
Talk to that mouse.
What should I say?
Let's see...
Something like, uh...
Time for me to leave.
U-Um...
Mister Mouse.
Uh, wanna have a nice, long chat?
Over there?
Huh?
Boing?!
A nice, boing chat, you say?
Yes!
C-C-Compa!
I'm freezing.
I've already stopped feeling anything.
What?!
Yeah, I'm starting to feel numb.
We need to do something before our bodies go into arrest!
Neppy!
Iffy!
I've got a message from Histoire.
O-Okay.
I have bad news, girls.
Anti-Crystals sever the link between you and your Share Crystals, but that's not all.
It also has the ability to convert Share Energy into something called Anti-Energy.
And it is said that concentrated Anti-Energy can take goddesses' lives.
So what can we do?!
As of now, we don't know how to counter it.
If I had three days—
Vert!
N-Neptune...
No!
Noire!
Huh?
Sis?
Let me help too!
Compa...
Sadly, you're wasting your energy.
What the heck is that?
I-I don't know!
That's how Anti-Energy kills goddesses.
Rainy Ratnapura!
No...
Nep... tune...
No—
S-Sis?
Nooooo!
Where... am I?
Am I... dead?
Nah, I'm not.
But... why?
Share Energy shouldn't be able to reach me in here.
So warm.
I see.
So that's how it is.
We are...
Your precious sisters are no more!
Everything you did came too late.
But don't let it get you down.
You'll be joining them soon enough!
In the dark abyss of despair, that is!
Sis...
They're all...
What?
They're all still fighting.
And we...
...refuse...
...to lose!
We're gonna take you down,
putting everything we have on the line, body and soul!
What is this?
The Share Energy's resonating?
Look at how...
...it's sparkling!
My Anti-Energy...
My miracle is being negated!
You're not getting away!
Begone!
Sis?
Where are you?
Hey...
Sis!
Right here, Nepgear.
I missed you so much!
Thank goodness!
Stop wailing like babies.
Sorry I made you worry.
Sorry I took so long, Sis.
What're you apologizing for?
Look at how you've grown.
Thanks.
Sis.
Sis!
You see...
I...
You did well, Nepgear.
From now on, I'll always be with you.
Sis!
Vert.
That must've been hard.
Thank you.
Good heavens.
You're only getting her for today, okay, Vert?
Good thing I prepared for this and made myself a loophole.
You should thank your lucky stars I'm such a capable mouse.
Why would you save me?
You were under no obligation to.
Villains have their own brand of friendship, you know.
I have to say, though. You're like a sack of potatoes, you old hag!
You could stand to cut down on those curves, you know.
Hmph.
I'll have you know my naked body's something else.
Too much information!
The Share Crystal's shining like blazes!
Sure is!
Looks like it hasn't changed much from before.
I was worried too,
but our Shares didn't go down all that much.
For real?!
Must be 'cause I'm such a wonderful person!
Actually, I think it's more that people had low expectations of you to begin with.
Either way,
all's well that ends well!
However, we're still facing a gradual downward trend.
Let's forget about that for now.
Not happening!
I'll have you work your stripy socks off, starting today.
What?!
I'd rather get tangled up in slippery-slimy tentacles!
So...
What about the other nations' shares?
Oh, they did go down a bit, as expected.
But Vert launched that VR interface for the general public.
I hear she got a lot of support that way.
Blanc Steamed Buns
And over at Lowee,
their Blanc Steamed Buns are selling like hotcakes.
Finally, Noire and Uni went monster hunting all over the place
and recovered more Shares than they'd lost.
So yeah,
it's almost like we're back to square one.
Delish!
And Neppy doesn't change at all, does she?
Hm?
Here I was, thinking you'd get a bit more serious after what you went through,
and you just take us on some random picnic?
You've got it the wrong way around!
It's precisely because I went through that
that I need to live every day like it's everyday!
I have no idea what you just said.
Heeeeeey!
Wh-Who in Gamindustri is that?!
N-No clue...
Compa!
IF!
Huh?
Who are you?
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
No doubt.
Only resolve!
Uni!
Your boobs!
Now they're as small as ours, Uni!
We're flat buddies!
I'm not too happy about being in that category.
Lastation's Secret (For Your Eyes Only)