Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, what would you do
if you had to do something super hard?
When everyone says that
you don't have a chance?
It's very tough.
But you want to at least
believe in yourself, you know?
So, even in a pinch, let's
change that into an opportunity!
Let's change it! Let's change it!
Yaritai koto wa nani
Sou kikareru tabi
Aoi sora miageta
Kotae wa only my heart
Honto ni daiji na kotoba
wa kantan ni wa iwanai
Hikari ga yubisasu
basho e to hashiridasu yo
Dakishimetai mono nara
nakitai hodo mune ni aru
Egakitsuzukete yuku kitto take it someday
Shiroi kumo ga nagareru
chiheisen no mukou ni
Naranderu mirai wa itsumo soba ni aru kara
A doll? A ghost? What is it?
My name is Fool. I am
the Spirit of the Stage.
Nothing to hear, nothing to hear,
I'm not hearing any weird voices.
Nothing to see, nothing to see,
I'm not seeing anything weird!
Oh, it's not there anymore. Thank goodness.
What are you doing?
Listen, if you can see me,
it means that you were chosen for the stage.
And it's still talking!
What is your name?
Sora Naegino. Wait, I'm talking back to it!
Sora Naegino...
Looks like another
interesting star will be born.
Tonight, a new era is about to begin.
I'll ask them to change my room.
Hey!
"My Amazing and Lonely Challenge!"
Excuse me, Dorm Supervisor, I'm coming in.
What was that just now?!
You!
Yes! I'm sorry!
Teach me that trick you just did!
What?
I just want you to teach
me the trick you just did!
Oh, I didn't know you were a new student.
Yes, I am Sora Naegino.
Sorry about that earlier.
It's just that you suddenly opened
the door during my karate practice.
Not at all. So, Dorm Supervisor...
Please call me Sarah.
Sarah? As in the diva of Kaleido Stage?
That's right.
So this is that gorgeous diva, Miss Sarah?
She's different from the
image I had in my mind.
Hey, you're Japanese, right?
Oh, yes.
I'm into karate now.
Can you be my sparring partner?
All Japanese are black belts, aren't they?
Oh, and teach me that trick
you just did too. And then...
I never knew Miss Sarah was like that.
In the end, I couldn't switch my room either.
That girl kissed up to the Boss
and cheated her way in, right?
She was late for the audition and
still passed. It like, makes me mad.
She kissed up to the Boss to join the troupe?
I heard she's even maneuvered
her way onto the stage already.
That's unforgivable.
I had to try three times
before I was accepted.
The third time's showbiz.
No?
No.
Then how about, "In the
nick of time's the charm"?
Not good.
Shoot. I screwed up again.
Oh, that expression! You look so cool!
Not here.
Looks like it was just my imagination.
Maybe I'm a little tired after all?
When you're tired, you should
take a shower and go to bed early.
You're right. I think I'll
do that. Take a shower and...
Now, take your clothes off
quickly and take a shower.
No one is here except for you and me.
So don't worry, take your clothes off.
Oh? You look pale.
Hurry up, take off your clothes and shower.
He's still here!
How dare you treat the
Spirit of the Stage this way?!
I demand you untie me right now.
At least take off the blindfold, please.
You're up early working hard.
Oh, Boss?
Newcomers shouldn't
be cleaning the stage yet.
I just happened to wake up early.
Oh, it's thanks to you that
I was able to join Kaleido Stage.
Thank you very much.
Wait. What are you looking at?
I was just thinking you still have nice legs.
He's weird.
Oh, everyone, good morning!
You're awfully early.
If you like cleaning that much,
can you do our share too?
What?
We want to go to our lessons early.
I have talent, but since
I'm not close to the Boss,
it's like the only way for me to
appear on stage is by working hard.
So take care of it for us.
I feel a little better now.
That's all right. I'll just
clean this place by myself.
Just what you'd expect from
Kaleido Stage... it's bigger than it looks.
Sora!
Ken.
You look tired. What's wrong?
It was just a lot of hard work
to clean the stage by myself.
What?! You did it by yourself?
Oh! No, I'm a slowpoke,
so it took me longer than the others.
By the way, if you don't hurry,
you'll be late for your lessons.
Oh, shoot. See you later!
Good luck, Sora.
You still have a long way to go.
Everyone, please listen carefully.
In these ballet lessons, you will master
how to move your body beautifully,
which is essential for grand ceremonies.
--A beautiful body movement, that is--
--I'm sorry I'm late!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry! I'm late because
I was cleaning the stage.
Really, you were also late for
the audition, too, weren't you?
I'll try harder and catch
up on the parts I missed.
All right, then. Now, we're
going to start the lesson.
Everyone, one row at a time, turn!
I have to work hard.
Next!
Oh, you!
Yes!
Don't you have any ballet experience?
No...
You must be joking.
You're the only one without any.
Because in order to show
a beautiful pose on the stage,
the knowledge of ballet is essential.
Fine then.
--I'll think about what you should do,
so take a short break for now.
--Why was someone like her
able to pass the audition?
--It's so unfair!
I agree.
She's making everyone laugh.
Oh, you mean that.
I can't believe you were on stage
when you couldn't even
do a simple turn like that.
Well, who cares?
She'll get to go on stage, even if she can't.
It's like, it must be nice.
Right now...
Right now, I may not be
able to even do a turn,
but someday, I will be able to do it.
Someday, I'll even be able to do
amazing routines like Miss Layla...
Miss Layla's big routine?
You mean the Golden Phoenix?
You're kidding me!
You seriously think the
Golden Phoenix is easy?
So, you think it's like a piece of cake?
Well, I didn't mean it like that.
Why don't you show us your Golden Phoenix?
Oh, no... Well...
Kalos has such confidence in you, after all.
The Golden Phoenix
should be easy for you, right?
I...
What's wrong? Can't you do it?
Just so you know, I don't
acknowledge your existence here.
All right then. I'll do it!
I'll show you that I can
do the Golden Phoenix!
Really? I'll be looking forward to it.
I'd like to see it in a week, then.
But if you can't do it after
stating so boldly that you would,
you will leave this place.
All right.
Yuri, let's go to the training room.
It isn't like you to say
something like that to a newcomer.
I just can't stand Kaleido Stage
having someone who can't do anything.
The Golden Phoenix?!
I'd like to borrow a video
of Miss Layla if you have one.
That is totally reckless!
The Golden Phoenix is
a trick that only a top star
like Miss Layla can do!
I know.
And it's a trick done on the trapeze.
Sora, have you ever worked on the trapeze?
No, but I have no choice.
I want everyone to acknowledge me.
And for that, I have no choice
but to do the Golden Phoenix!
Sora...
The Golden Phoenix is
performed by first swinging high
and spinning your body very fast.
Then, you release the bar,
spread your arms wide like a phoenix,
and catch your partner's bar.
Spinning your body using this
special bar makes it extremely difficult.
Miss Layla and Mr. Yuri are using
the training room for their new routine,
so you'll have to use the
actual trapeze on the stage.
There's a net, but it's still dangerous,
since the trapeze is pretty high.
I'll be all right.
So, what do I need to do?
Well...
First, you need to practice
swinging your body back and forth.
After gaining enough momentum,
you'll jump to the bar on the other side.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
If you fall, make sure you
land on your back. Okay?
You don't have enough
momentum! One more time!
I never knew just swinging
would be this hard.
But I will do it no matter what!
I'm sorry that I ended up
keeping you here until morning.
Oh, don't worry about it.
If it's for you, I don't...
Sora!
Oh! Mr. Policeman!
What are you doing so early in the morning?
I was practicing on the trapeze.
I see, good luck.
Tell me when you'll be on stage.
I'm your number one fan, got that?
Thank you, Mr. Policeman.
Hi...
I'm going to see if you're worthy
enough to be Sora's boyfriend!
You got it all wrong! He's not
my boyfriend or anything like that!
You sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Well then, Sora, good luck!
Not anything like that.
--I really have to work hard, though.
--Not anything like that.
Not anything like that.
--Or I'll end up leaving this place
before I even get to be on stage.
--Not anything like that.
--Ken, keep me company again tonight, okay?
Of course.
Oh...
Were you practicing all this time?
Yes, because if I don't work hard...
It's not something you
can do just by working hard.
Why don't you give up
and apologize to Miss Layla?
I gave up on joining Kaleido Stage earlier
because I missed the audition.
But somehow I managed to get in.
So I really want to stay here!
I don't ever want to give up again!
Ow...
If you think that hurts,
you still have a long way to go.
He's still here.
The reverse Chariot.
This card indicates that things will
end in failure and you will taste defeat.
However, even if the results
of a fortune telling are bad,
the future can be changed.
Depending on that person's efforts.
Thus, in order to gain the muscle
strength to perform various tricks,
you have to eat a low-fat
and high-protein diet.
Could it be...
She's working really hard?
I did it!
Okay, Sora. Next, you have
to do it while you're spinning.
Sora!
We brought you something to eat!
I know you haven't eaten anything yet.
Oh...
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'm glad you liked it. Please have all of it.
I will.
I recommend this.
Hot pepper drink?
It'll give you energy.
Anna, Mia, thank you.
I'm sorry, Sora. It's all because
I mentioned the Golden Phoenix...
No, don't worry about it.
Because now, I have a chance to prove myself.
At first, I thought you were accepted
because you kissed up to the Boss,
but I guess that wasn't the case.
Sorry for misunderstanding.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, the bandage on your hand is coming loose.
Let me fix it for you.
Good luck. We're rooting for you.
Thank you.
Swing the bar back and forth. Spin,
then jump.
Is Sora okay?
She's doing image training.
She's picturing the image of
the perfected routine in her mind.
I see.
Finish.
Therefore... Well, in other words...
I'm listening to the lecture.
Please don't mind me.
Easy for you to say...
Oh, Mr. Yuri!
What in the world were you
looking at when you jumped?
There is no Juliet who is not
always gazing at her Romeo.
That is why you are not Juliet.
Mr. Yuri...
I'm not completely in
the character of Juliet?
So close! She almost made it.
I can't believe she managed to
do all this in such a short time.
If she can just grab the bar now...
No, she still can't maintain
a beautiful pose in the air.
Before she catches the bar,
what she's doing can't be
called the Golden Phoenix.
Go, Sora!
By tomorrow...
I have to perfect it by tomorrow.
You couldn't perfect it after all,
but you did do your best.
There's no knowing yet.
The real test is tomorrow.
I haven't given up yet.
I can't wait to see what kind of
Golden Phoenix she'll show us.
Yeah.
Thank you for coming to see me.
I've got to do it. I need
to believe in myself.
The bar should not be my aim.
My aim should be my love, Romeo.
And then, I can be Juliet.
The Golden Phoenix!
She did it!
Sora, are you all right?
Yes. Thank you.
You're really something.
Oh, Miss Layla.
You didn't get the last part right,
but that was definitely the Golden Phoenix.
Huh?!
I guess I have to acknowledge you this time.
What?
Yuri, let's go.
Sora, you can stay at Kaleido Stage now!
Congratulations, Sora!
I'm glad for you, Sora!
I'm happy for you.
I can stay at Kaleido Stage?
Cheers!
Aren't you happy now that you
can stay at Kaleido Stage, Sora?
Yes, I am. Thank you.
You're still here?!
Sora, I think the three of you
should take a bath together.
They say that true friendship
starts with sharing a bath together.
If you are concerned about me, do not worry.
That's enough!
Ouch! What are you doing, Sora?!
Oh, well. This is...
Please stop it!
What?
That was a Japanese comedy
routine I've heard of called "tsukkomi."
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
Hey, you guys can't see him?
What are you talking about?
You're throwing a party? We can't have this.
Dorm Supervisor.
We're not allowed to have a party?
Of course not, unless you invite me as well.
That's the rule at this dormitory.
Miss Sarah...
Miss Sarah?!
No way!
Now, let's have some fun!
The image I had of her...
When you sabishii toki doushitemasuka
Never say sonna no wakannai
Nemuru asobu magazine mekuru
Sabishii toki wa sabishii yo
Mienai denpa ga kyou mo
tulututu machi ni tobikau
Anyway kokoro no bekutoru
so many reason hanashiteru
Jiyuu ni sora o tobitai keredo
Hane o hirogeru basho ga nai
Demo shinjiteru
Katachi no nai mirai ga aru yo
Katachi ni shitai watashi ga iru
Kanashikutemo machigai demo
Omou mama fly to the free
"Next Kaleido Star"
You don't have a role.
And so, Kaleido Stage's
next theme is Cinderella.
I heard that we newcomers
would also appear in it,
but I'm the only one who doesn't get a role?!
It can't be.
It must be some kind of mistake.
But according to orders from Boss Kalos,
I have to hand out candy
to children in the theater.
I just gotta do it this
time too! Gotta! Gotta!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Distant Stage."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...