Murdered?
But that's just...
Why the Father?
This cannot...
This cannot be permitted!
Why didn't you tell Tokiomi?
Tell him what?
Your poor father...
He left this world,
convinced his son was a man of God.
Or perhaps,
was that his salvation?
Do you even care that your father is dead?
He was murdered, after all.
Should you not, at least,
pretend to be upset?
I'm very frustrated, yes.
Are you?
Is it...
because you could not kill
him with your own hands?
Saber?
Irisviel, are you all right?
You must have been so worried.
I'm sorry.
As long as you're safe,
that is all that matters.
Still...
Don't worry.
I can sense it's just Maiya-san.
From Tohsaka?
Yes.
Tohsaka Tokiomi has proposed an alliance.
An alliance? At this stage?
Rider and Berserker are the
only other Servants left.
Tohsaka's probably uneasy about facing them.
He's reached out, thinking us the
easiest group to convince.
Essentially, he considers us weaker
than the other pairs.
He said he'd like
to meet with you at the
Fuyuki City church tonight.
In my view, Tohsaka Tokiomi has been
meticulous in his planning
for this Holy Grail War since the very start.
And there's evidence to suggest
that Assassin's Master,
Kotomine Kirei, is his pawn, as well.
If Tohsaka has Kotomine Kirei in his pocket,
I'm not sure we should ignore his offer.
Maybe not.
Kotomine Kirei...
Remember this, Saber.
If anyone in this Grail War
can defeat Kiritsugu, to win the Grail,
it is Kotomine Kirei.
Very well, we'll accept.
Father?
Father!
Rin,
your father wants to talk to you.
Rin...
As you grow up, always try to
keep the Church in your debt.
Beyond that, I trust your judgment.
I know you will succeed, even on your own.
Eventually, the Holy Grail will appear.
The Tohsaka are duty-bound to obtain it.
But more than that,
if you want to be a mage,
that is the path you must follow.
This is for you, Rin.
I have to go now.
You understand what to do, don't you?
Yes.
Goodbye, Father!
I, Tohsaka Tokiomi, offer you
my most humble gratitude
for accepting my invitation.
Allow me to introduce Kotomine Kirei.
My disciple,
and until recently, our fellow
competitor in the Holy Grail War.
But that is now in the past.
He has lost his Servant,
and has relinquished his rights as a Master.
The Holy Grail War has
entered its final stages.
We, of the three original families,
are the remaining Masters,
alongside one outsider.
What think you of the
current state of affairs?
We cannot, under any circumstances,
allow an outsider to claim the Grail.
I am sure you must agree on that.
The idea of an alliance is absurd.
However,
if you wish to decide on the order in which
we fight our remaining enemies,
we may be able to reach some consensus.
Meaning?
Meaning that we are
prepared to agree to wait
until the other two are defeated
before we turn our attention to the Tohsaka.
A temporary, conditional truce?
That is a fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
First,
that you give us any and all information
you've gathered on Rider and his Master.
Done.
Second,
that Kotomine Kirei be fully
removed from the Holy Grail War.
May I ask why?
There is substantial animosity
between the Einzberns
and the Executor.
If you intend to keep that man
under your protection,
it will be impossible for us to place
even a sliver of trust in you!
What is this about,
Kirei?
What do you think of Kiritsugu's gift?
This vehicle is similar to a horse,
so it will serve me better than the automobile.
I'll go on ahead,
and secure the route back.
We should go, too.
M-Madam?
What's wrong?
Go, Maiya-san...
But...
Tohsaka will suspect that something's wrong.
This is normal.
It would have always happened.
Actually, it's a miracle I've been able to
function as a human for this long.
I'm a homunculus created solely
for the Holy Grail War.
You knew that, didn't you?
Yes.
Grandfather Acht wanted
the Grail's vessel to have a survival instinct,
so that it could avoid danger
and ensure the Grail's completion.
He dressed the vessel in a
disguise called Irisviel.
That is what I am.
How... But then you...
Very soon,
I shall revert to what I was originally.
Next time we meet,
I doubt we'll even be able to converse like this.
That's why Kiritsugu left Saber's
scabbard with me.
Avalon...
Do you know about its effects?
I've been told it prevents aging
and has unlimited healing power.
Avalon has staved off the
collapse of the shell that is my body.
Naturally, things deteriorate quickly
when I'm separated from Saber.
Why tell me this?
Because, Hisau Maiya...
I knew that you wouldn't pity me.
You'd just accept me as I am.
That's why.
Madam,
I've always seen you as someone
quite distant from myself.
That's not true...
Do you understand?
I do.
Even if it costs my life,
Irisviel, I will protect you to the end.
So please...
When the time comes, die for Emiya Kiritsugu.
Die, for the sake of his dream.
Thank you.
I wish
you had informed me of your
dealings with Einzbern.
I'm afraid I have no other choice.
You must withdraw from the Grail War,
Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Who are you?
Must I leave, not even finding my answer?
Still considering options, at this late hour?
You couldn't possibly be so dense, Kirei.
The Grail beckons you still.
And in your heart of hearts,
you long to continue the fight.
As far back as I can recall,
I've spent my life searching for one thing.
I've squandered my time, endured great pain,
all for nothing.
But now, I feel as though
I am closer than ever before
to the answer I've sought for so long.
Then why, after all that introspection,
do you still hesitate?
I have a foreboding...
That when I learn that which I seek,
it will destroy me.
I see. Good work.
Did you receive some good news,
to lift your spirits?
We've finally learned where the Einzberns
have been hiding.
You really are a piece of work, Kirei!
You've planned to continue
all along, haven't you?
I was hesitant,
and I nearly retired.
But in the end,
it is as you've noted, King of Heroes.
I know of no other way
but to continue asking.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
JN 424.
The Gospel of John.
God is spirit.
And those who worship him must
worship in spirit and in truth.
But, Kirei...
You have quite a problem here.
If you were to enter the Holy
Grail War for yourself,
Tohsaka Tokiomi would be your enemy.
Meaning that you now stand in this room,
alone and helpless, before an enemy Servant.
Quite a dire situation, no?
I think not.
I'm not above begging for my life.
Oh?
Gilgamesh...
Allow me to tell you the truth
of this Holy Grail War.
What?
When it began, this ritual of Fuyuki
was an attempt to open a passage to the Root,
through the sacrifice of
seven Heroic Spirits' souls.
The deaths of these seven Servants
would activate the Great Grail.
Indeed, all seven.
Do you understand?
That is why my master has been so fixated
on conserving his Command Spells.
When the last battle has been fought,
he will need one to force his
Servant to commit suicide.
You claim the loyalty Tokiomi
has shown me was all a lie?
Ultimately,
my master is a mage, down to his core.
Even if he were to
admire a Heroic Spirit,
he would never hold even
the semblance of loyalty.
Tokiomi...
You have finally proven your worth.
At last, that boring, tiresome man
will provide me some entertainment.
It is your move, King of Heroes.
Will you remain loyal to my master,
and accuse me of having ulterior motives?
Indeed, what to do...
Ignoring his disloyalty,
Tokiomi remains my source of mana.
Completely turning my back on my Master
would hamper my ability
to remain materialized.
Oh... Of course,
I seem to remember a free Master
with Command Spells, searching for
a Servant unbound by contract.
I believe you're right.
But I wonder if the King of Heroes
would deem him a worthy Master.
He will suffice.
He is somewhat stiff,
but overall, I find him very promising.
Perhaps he'll even manage to entertain me.
I'm glad you came, Kirei.
I couldn't leave Fuyuki without saying goodbye.
I'm extremely proud to have
had you as my disciple.
In the years ahead,
I hope that you, like your late father,
will maintain close ties with the Tohsaka.
Can I count on you?
There is no need to ask.
And when the Holy Grail War ends, Kirei,
I would request that, as my senior student,
you will help in Rin's education.
This is brief, but consider it my will.
Just in case.
It seemed best to prepare,
even for remote possibilities.
It names Rin as successor to the Tohsaka Estate,
and you as her guardian until
she reaches adulthood.
I will not let you down.
I shall take full responsibility in
looking after your daughter.
Thank you, Kirei.
What's this?
A parting gift, from me to you.
Open it.
An Azoth dagger.
Proof that you have mastered
the Tohsaka family magic,
and graduated from student
to full-fledged mage.
I don't deserve such kindness.
I cannot thank you enough, my master.
It is I who should thank you, Kotomine Kirei.
Now I can focus completely on the final battle.
It's getting late.
I apologize for keeping you so long.
I hope you won't miss your flight.
No...
You needn't worry, my master.
I never booked a flight.
Master...
Just like my father,
you never truly understood me,
even at your end.
What a tedious demise.
Look at that ridiculous face.
Well, he had a dematerialized
Servant by his side.
Who can blame him
for being taken by surprise?
You're making jokes now, too?
You impress me with your progress.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel better about not
getting to kill your father?
You truly have no objections,
Gilgamesh, King of Heroes?
No, not as long as you keep my interest.
Otherwise, Kirei,
you're the one who will need
to prepare for death.
Thy body, born of my will.
My fate, resting on thy sword!
If thou wilt bend to my will, my justice,
heed the Grail's call...
I swear before you.
Thine offering shalt be my flesh and blood,
Kotomine Kirei.
My new Master.
Shall we get started, Kirei?
You may end this comedy
at your own discretion.
As a prize, I shall give you the Grail.
As you like, King of Heroes.
Please enjoy the show.
Until I find my answer,
I will gladly be your jester.
Episode 17:
The Eighth Contract
Kerry, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
Please don't go to that house.
What is this?
From now on, you must decide for yourself.
It's too early for you.
Someday, you'll have the power
to change the world.
Next Time:
Distant Memories