And then?
Ami-chan, you took it in?
That big one?
It was my job.
Big? They're about that size.
No, no, it was this...
Oh, I'm sorry...
It's just Yusaku.
What was big?
You mean a pe-
No way!
It was a big dog!
In a magazine shoot I was doing, they had me taking pictures with a big dog.
What were you thinking?
Is Maruo okay?
He seems kind of out of it.
Everyone to your seats.
We're going to start the end-of-day homeroom now.
Class representative, the greetings please.
Kitamura-kun?
Stand, bow, thanks for the meal.
What?
A joke?
It looks like there's a lot going on, but let's all cheer up.
Kitamura?
The weekend starts tomorrow.
And when you come back to school next week, it's time for the student council elections.
It's already that time of year?
Yeah! An event!
Kitamura-kun, you need to pull yourself together and work hard!
After all, you're the number one candidate for the next student council president.
Or rather, the only one.
Alright! Let's make it exciting!
But the next president is definitely going to be Kitamura.
Kitamura, good luck!
We'll help out too!
I...
I'm not going to run in the damn election.
I'm going to quit being vice president.
I'm going to quit being in the student council.
Quit...
Quit, quit...
Kitamura-kun?
I'm going to quit everything!
No response at all from Kitamura.
I wonder what happened to him.
He said something about quitting the student council.
The student council...
Did that damn student council president push you around?
What the heck?
Please, let me go!
What the hell are you thinking?
What's going on, Minorin?
Come with me!
Oh, it's you guys. It's terrible! Look!
Ki-Ki-
Kitamura-kun!
What is up with that hair?
No matter what I say, he won't tell me why.
That's why I asked you all, his close friends, to come.
Do you have any idea why he did this?
I have no idea!
How could I understand anything about a guy using such an obvious way to rebel in this day and age?
No, I don't really...
What about you, Kanou-san?
I neither know nor can I understand why.
Now that he has said that he would quit the student council, nothing he does has anything to do with me.
Kanou-san.
Sensei, you are just wasting your time on a big idiot like him.
Hey, wait...
Kanou-senpai, you've become pretty cold.
What if you were actually the reason why Yusaku decided to rebel?
Hey, Kawashima!
That might be true.
But if that's so...
Then I'm going to get even more disappointed in Kitamura.
Ami-chan, did you learn something about Maruo?
Who knows?
But the student council president seems to know something.
Kanou-senpai did?
Taiga?
Magistrate!
I have brought the criminal!
Taka-chan, save me!
Kushieda's being really mean!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything!
Kitamura just called me last night and asked me how to dye his hair blond. I just told him how to do it!
You saw what Kitamura-kun was like yesterday!
You didn't even think to wonder why he would want to do something like that?
But I didn't think he'd really do it!
Is Maruo really going to quit the student council?
Hey, Ami-chan.
Isn't there something we can do for Maruo?
He's just a sweet model student trying to get attention.
He just wants to say, "Someone, please notice poor troubled me!"
He may think he's trying to rebel just by dying his hair blond when he's in the 11th grade...
But it hurts too much to even...
Stupid Chihuahua!
You're not worried about Kitamura-kun?
What's the point? I'll just look stupid.
What?
Quit it, you two.
Hey, isn't that Kitamura?
Where, where?
Calm down please, Kitamura-kun!
I said I'm going home, so I'm going home!
Kitamura-kun!
Please wait!
Kitamura-kun.
It must be nice to think that if you just cry out, someone will save you.
Alright, everyone.
Class is going to start.
Hey, would you come with me to Kitamura-kun's house?
I don't have work or practice today and I'm kind of worried.
What about you, Taiga?
No...
It'd be easier to talk to him if there were fewer people.
I see.
Okay, Takasu-kun, wait for me by the school gate.
I'm going to stop by the clubroom and then meet you there.
Are you really sure?
I'm worried about Kitamura-kun.
But I won't be able to do a good job at it...
And...
To be honest, I'd rather he go on like this and cut off his relationship with the student council.
No matter what the cost, I need him to get away from that damn student council president.
Taiga?
So that's why you better pull it off, you dog.
Even if you tell me that...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I hope Kitamura-kun is at home.
I wonder what happened.
Yeah...
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
You're kind of quiet.
No, that is...
I was kind of wondering what Kawashima and Taiga are thinking...
Kawashima wouldn't say stuff like that about her childhood friend, right?
I'm sure Ami is really worried about Kitamura-kun.
Ami is someone who's been working in an adult's world, right?
She probably knows a lot more than brats like us.
About Kitamura-kun too.
She's been patiently hanging out with us even though she knows things we don't.
Is she really that great of a person?
But Ami didn't say anything that wasn't true.
There aren't many friends who will say things like that for you.
That's why I think, in her own way, she has a good reason for saying things the way she did.
Or rather, I really hope she does.
As for myself, and unfortunately you too, we both have things we don't really understand.
Even though we want to understand the other person, there are things we don't.
Yeah....
At times like that, I want to believe that Ami is the only one that really understands everything.
It's like a last hope to those of us who, in our inexperience, can't understand one another.
Something like that.
What am I saying?
I think Kitamura-kun's house is this way.
Kushieda is... How do I say it...
Kind.
Kind?
No!
That's not it!
I'm greedy and...
Sly...
Kushieda?
In the end, no one was at Kitamura's house.
We didn't get to see him.
I'm home!
You're here.
W-Welcome home, Ryuji-kun.
What's with you?
Did you eat something weird?
Hey!
I'm visiting.
Ki-Kitamura!?
Yasuko-san said to come in.
So, at her kind invitation...
Not that!
Actually, I ran away from home.
Do you come to Takasu's house often, Aisaka?
Yacchan said I can come here and eat whenever.
So, at her kind invitation...
I see!
Good for you, since Takasu is living next door.
Tatami really are great!
My house doesn't have any tatami rooms.
Me neither! It's all western style.
There's something really calming about Japanese style rooms, right?
Yes!
I think so too.
Nutmeg, nut...
Now then! I've got to help out.
What?
Alright! I'll peel for you!
I'm really good at it.
Good at it?
I see.
Anyway, you just want to show your good side, right?
Right.
Alright!
Then make those really good sunny side up eggs again.
I got it!
That's it. Put in the eggs like that and put on the lid.
Lid? What lid?
The frying pan lid of course!
Take that and add just a little water.
Water? What about water?
It's on fire!
Oh I got it!
Here's where you need the water!
No!
Kitamura...
This is...
Hey, Kitamura!
Don't eat it!
I've never really cooked before...
It tastes like a tougher version of sunny side up eggs!
Kitamura-kun.
Aisaka.
You wanted to cheer me up by making this, right?
Thanks.
It worked. I feel better.
Okay...
Takasu made this hamburger patty?
Yeah!
It's Takasu's Special Red Wine Sauce!
And of course it's delicious.
Maybe I should try to learn to make it...
Yeah! You can't go wrong with Takasu teaching you.
I'm full!
It was amazingly delicious.
Good for you.
And...
What's the reason for that hair?
Ryuji!
I didn't want to become the student council president...
I thought if I had hair like this, no one would expect something like that from me anymore.
That's all.
Just for that...
You don't have to become the student council president if you don't want to!
It's something you decided!
I think that's just fine.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, Ryuji, bring out the video games.
Great idea, let's do it!
There's no school tomorrow, let's play all night!
Yeah!
I fell asleep.
Huh?
Where's Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun?
Ryuji...
I wanna eat ice cream.
What, right now?
We don't have any.
Ice cream, ice cream.
Guess I'll go to a convenience store.
Want to come?
Where's Kitamura-kun?
What the heck? Pulling out his own futon and going to sleep all by himself.
Cheeky...
I get to see Kitamura-kun's sleeping face.
Hey...
It gets cold at night so wear this...
Taiga?
I'm...
No good after all.
What was I all happy about?
I just kept thinking only about me.
I wasn't able to see that Kitamura-kun was hurting, that he was sad...
Or what he was worried about.
Really, I'm useless.
I'm useless.
Useless!
You're not useless...
No!
I'm no good.
I can't help Kitamura-kun like this.
I can't do anything for him.
Whenever I was of no use, Kitamura-kun always reached out to me.
And at each time, I was reassured.
That it's okay for me to be here.
That I'm someone who can be here.
Kitamura-kun...
For me, Kitamura-kun...
The last hope?
Taiga, it's the Big Dipper.
And that's the North Star.
Orion's belt.
Which one is Orion's belt?
See, those three lined up...
I see it.
Those stars look really close together.
But they're actually really far apart.
We learned that in elementary school.
It's kind of like...
Kitamura-kun and I.
What you see with your eyes isn't the truth.
How much more do I need to see the truth that you can't see with your eyes?
How far apart is the distance...
Between me and Kitamura-kun?
It's because you don't know that you want to close that distance, right?
Because you like him, you want to understand...
All you can do is try and reach out and get closer little by little.
Yeah...
Morning, Takasu.
Morning.
I went ahead and drank the milk in the fridge.
Sorry.
But it looks like you guys partied last night.
You should've woken me up.
Sorry.
That's right...
Last night, I went along with Taiga's food binge...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's already this late?
I've got to hurry and make breakfast...
Taiga!
Hey, wake up, aren't you embarrassed?
Leave her be, she's sleeping so well!
What a happy sleeping face.
Stinks of... Milk!
What a fabulous slam when you just wake up!
Kitamura-kun!
No way!
Did you see me when I was sleeping?
Sorry! I did!
No! What should I do? Was I making a weird face?
No!
Calm down.
My hair is all messed up!
She kicked us out.
Nothing we can do. Let's go get some food...
Alright! Let's go have some fun!
I was always busy with the cultural festival and club stuff.
It's been a long time since I've gone out to have fun during the daytime.
I know of a good place!
Altogether, he's hit over a hundred balls.
There's really something wrong with Kitamura.
Sweaty exercise is the best kind of fun for students.
Looks a little abnormal to me.
Alright! Takasu, you're up!
No, I...
Kitamura-kun!
I'll go next!
Aisaka, you're all fired up!
Taiga?
Look at me.
I'm going to hit them!
Alright, Aisaka, keep your arms tight.
You hit it!
I may have just found a diamond in the rough.
Amazing, you're amazing, Aisaka!
Why didn't someone as amazing as you join the softball club?
I'm home.
That was an amazing homerun.
Aisaka, you're really talented.
Not really...
Welcome home, everyone.
Ryu-chan...
Could you hold Kitamura-kun down?
Like this?
That's right...
Hold him down just like that.
Taiga! Hold him!
Just now, when I called your father...
It seemed like he was really mad.
So I think you should fix your hair so you can go home.
I can't believe you were in contact with my parents!
In the end, a guardian is just a guardian!
Kitamura-kun's going to become the student council president, right?
In that case, you can't have blond hair, right?
I won't become the student council president!
No way!
I wonder if Kitamura-kun went home properly...
Dont't know...
I guess he really didn't want to do it.
I wonder...
Do you remember what Minorin said during the summer at Ami's house?
"I love horror, so I tell everyone I hate it."
Yeah...
Something about a "feast of horror."
Kitamura-kun keeps saying he's not going to become the student council president, right?
What if he really feels the opposite...
And he really wants to do it?
You don't think so?
Even if that were true, unless he wants to do it, our hands are tied.
But...
Then we just have get him to want to.
Are you really sure?
I'm okay!
It's something I decided to do!
Alright, put this on.
Let's go.
What kind of joke is this?
You've got to be kidding!
Seriously?
Silence!
I am announcing it here.
Once I, Aisaka Taiga, am elected as student council president...
I am going to take over this school, turn your high school memories into a sea of blood...
And send you all to the mo-mo-morgue!
Once I become student council president...
I'll send you all into a box of fear.
An abyss, right?
And then on the night of the crescent moon, and fresh blood mo-morg-
You're still on that...
Hey, you! Shake hands with me!