When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
I will show everyone what true culture is.
All that aside, do the inking on this.
What?!
Mistress Kuzuha!
I was getting rather tired
of the normal culture fests.
Besides...
Right about now, that kid who's totally
devoted to his Miss is probably...
Miss!
To think you would abandon me...
Hmm, that might be nice.
Mistress Kuzuha!
Do the inking on this, too!
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Just you watch! With the power of
my manga, I will make this world mine!
Hey, you, are you really hypnotized?!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Why Dead?! Academy Culture Fest – Part 2
Really, don't you think you're worrying
about this a bit too much?
We even received a phone call
from the Miss herself last evening.
But don't you think it's strange?!
That the Miss is participating
in a school event of her own free will
and she stayed the night
with the Superintendent
to liven up the culture fest!
Butlers must be manly!!
What part of your statement just
now contains any cause for worry?
Well, certainly, on the face of it,
there isn't any, but...
Well, Mr. Klaus doesn't know
the Superintendent's personality.
Or actually, there are a lot of issues
with Nagi's normal behavior, so...
Right...
But this is just what I expect
from you, Maria!
To think you are aware of the
personality of Hakuou's Superintendent!
Well, her talent for causing
trouble for others
is the one area where
she borders on the genius.
I see...
Oh, pardon me.
Incoming call
Miss Hinagiku Katsura
Hinagiku?
Um, hello? Good morning.
Hayate, this is no time
for leisurely greetings.
What?
What's happening, Hinagiku?!
Look.
Th-This is...!
Um, this is the Hakuou Academy, right?
Right? Don't you think
it's a weird building?
Uh, I think there are a lot of surprises
besides the shape of the building...
This is probably all Nagi's doing, right?
What? Why do you say that?
Because there were a ton
of cars parked out front
with manga characters and stuff on them.
All anime-lovers have cars like that, right?
W-Well, I imagine it's
only a fraction of them...
Whatever the case,
the spectacle before them
was an exact replica of the manga
festival at Tokyo Big Sight,
which will surely be held again
at the end of this year.
Numerous doujinshis changing hands.
Character merchandise, such as body pillows.
Doujin music CDs.
Limited Color
Limited Item
Limited to Event
At industry booths,
figures limited to this event.
DVDs with extras limited to this event.
Incidentally, at our Rondo Robe booth,
Following the trend of subsidized products,
they are distributing not-for-sale CDs.
we are distributing Ariake not-for-sale CDs!
Family members who think this sounds
vaguely familiar, not to worry.
Also, be sure you don't look
at the stuff your children buy.
Since it may cause them
to withdraw from society.
Wow, the people look like rubbish...
"There are not enough women's bathrooms."
"There are people changing
in places other than the locker rooms."
"Do something about the resellers."
"I wasn't able to buy Kagami merchandise."
There are also others about change...
I've heard enough already.
I mean, these complaints have nothing
to do with our culture fest.
How true.
Still, while it is impressive
of the Superintendent
to set up an event of this size overnight,
the visitors who got wind of it
and came are equally amazing.
Don't be impressed!
If we let this go, it'll end up
like this every year.
We may be able to make
an enormous amount of profit.
That's not it!
With this many people gathered here,
it's only a matter of time
before one of the guests
gets hurt, so it's dangerous!
We have to do something about this.
Um, I'm going to go look for the Miss.
I think the root cause
of this probably lies in the fact
that the Miss is helping
the Superintendent.
And when you get down to it,
that happened because
I left the Miss all alone...
To think your mistress has
washed her hands of you...
You've failed as a butler.
Poem person...
Nagi Sanzenin is being kept
hospitably under our care.
What?
Oh, I'm aware of that,
since we got the phone call.
Phone call?!
That is what you call "uncool".
One could also call him a "goof".
Or is it being a "bonehead"?
He's "spacey" is what he is.
That cowlick is also symbolic of that.
Why you!
Oh! "Spacey"!
Shut up!
Sheesh! What's with you people?!
To think I came all this way
to secretly guide you to where she is!
What?
Why?
Thanks to her, I'm being
hugely inconvenienced!
Hurry up and take her back already!
Wh-Why...?
I can hardly believe we're
on the same school grounds...
Superintendent's Office
Mistress Kuzuha is having
a snack in the cafeteria.
Now's our chance. Hurry.
This has turned out wonderfully!
Truly, the pinnacle of Japanese culture!
Honestly! What do you
think you're doing here?
Come on, we're going back.
Miss!
Who are you people?
What?
Wh-What are you saying?!
Oh, please. I am Hayate,
your butler, remember?
Don't lie to me. There's
no way you're Hayate.
You must be an imposter.
If you were the real Hayate...
If you were the real Hayate,
no matter how busy you were
with the culture fest,
you would never...
You would never have left me all alone.
Miss...
Hayate...
Hey, hurry!
If you keep dawdling,
Mistress Kuzuha will be back...
No mischief now, Sion.
P-Please forgive me!
Boy, you seem to have angered
your mistress considerably.
She is saying she will never return
to her residence, you know.
Surely not!
Sanzenin, you are going to show everyone
how wonderful your manga is, are you not?
That is right.
I will stay here and continue to write.
You could do that
at your own residence, too!
Sh-Shut up!
Keeping one's work and private life separate
is a basic part of being a manga artist!
You're a Hakuou student before
you're a manga artist, remember?!
And you, too, Superintendent!
Gathering all those people
just for the fun of it...
There will be big trouble
if someone gets injured!
Interesting.
Then let us take this
opportunity to compete!
Compete?
I'm not telling you
to cancel it or anything.
It's just sort of dangerous
the way things are now...
As of now, we will vend this doujinshi
at a specially prepared
booth in the Academy.
Ayasaki, if your doujinshi wins
against ours by selling better,
I will return your mistress
and also restore the culture fest.
What is with this "great
and cuteness" attitude?
This is like a plot development
out of Comic Party.
In other words, this is a
doujinshi sales competition?
Exactly.
There is no way my manga
will lose against an imposter!
Um, Superintendent,
are you listening to what I'm saying?
So you would flee, you coward?!
She is not listening, nor does
she seem interested in listening.
So it seems.
I understand! We will accept your challenge!
What?! H-Hinagiku?!
However, to make things fair,
the student council will also take
over the running of this whole circus
to make things fair and safe!
Fine.
However, if you lose,
you will open a maid café
with the entire student council dressed
in super-embarrassing maid outfits!
What?
If you cannot accept those conditions,
I have no intention of doing what you want.
What shall we do?
Even then...
Even then, the safety
of our guests is important!
Hinagiku...
You can win, right?
Or more like, you better win!
I won't forgive you if you lose!
What? Well...
A match between a mistress
and her butler, huh?
This is getting interesting.
I will be the one to win.
But Hinagiku, they're talking
about a doujinshi sales competition
and our class is set up as a butler café.
Oh, that's true. You're right...
Thus, both camps proceeded to do battle.
Get over here quick
And a one, two...
Cheerful, with a cute heart!
I'm a bit mad
Get over here quick
End of the Century Legend, Magical Destroy!
At mach speeds
Well-received and on sale now!
Socially reclusive Sunday
Those of you who wish to buy one,
please line up in 3 rows!
No, you have to come flying now
Hayate Ayasaki, get a taste
of how powerless you are...
No, no, you just have to
And in utter despair,
writhe about with tears in your eyes!
What?!
That was why you instigated
this competition?!
British-Style Cosplay Café
Lose with all your might, Hayata!
In fact, just forfeit, Hayata.
I want to see Hina
in an embarrassing maid outfit!
Wh-What?!
I'll have you know, if we lose,
you guys have to wear it, too.
What?!
What did you say?!
That would be bad.
Right?!
So we have to all support Hayate!
And Hayate, you, too.
What?
If we don't win this,
you can't get Nagi back.
You have to make her snap out of it. Got it?
Yes.
It's exactly like Hinagiku said.
I have to restore a smile
to the Miss's face, no matter what!
A night of bravo!
(Yoru mo appare!)
Combo string.
(Renzoku konbo.)
Top Secret Sales Chart
Nagi Sanzenin
Hayate Ayasaki
We've won!
I can just see Ayasaki crying pathetically.
Th-There's big trouble!
Their shop's sales are suddenly
growing for some reason!
What?!
Invigorating
Suginami Intelligence
Hakuou Academy Culture Fest Report
Once again, the season for the Hakuou
Academy Culture Fest has come,
Suginami Ward's special
attraction of the fall.
Among their shops,
it seems this shop's cake set
is particularly popular this year.
Now, let us go check out the kitchen.
Pardon me. Might I get a word with you?
Yes.
What is the secret to your flavor?
Oh, no, all I do is put every
ounce of my heart and soul into it.
Hayate's Recipe
Right now, along with the cake,
you also get this doujinshi,
which contains the recipe.
Wow, that's a great deal!
What is this?
Also, the cover is a Mr. Shiraishi original.
Well, Hayate can cook like a pro, so...
Wow! I want one, too!
One set comes out to 500 yen.
But why is Hayate baking cakes?
What?! That's so cheap!
Butler Cafe
End of Line
Miss Butler, I'd like a cake set.
I'll have the same.
Yes, please wait one moment, Misses.
I would like a cake set over here as well.
Yes, certainly.
I'd like service over here, too.
Excuse me, Mr. Butler, are you listening?
Young Master?
Um, Miss, how would you
like another cup of tea?
Oh, my! You called me "miss"!
Young Master,
I never expected Nonohara
and his master to come help, too.
you still do not know what a butler is.
Still...
I'm sorry, Nonohara! Oh, at least let me...
I wonder how the Miss is doing right now...
Hey, Hayata, you can't take a break.
P-Pardon me!
If you don't work hard,
we're the ones who'll end up suffering.
I swear, if it was just Hina,
we would have interfered...
Then how about we have her wear
a maid outfit in celebration if we win?
Nice idea!
I am not wearing it!
And Hayate, break time is over.
Hurry up with the cakes.
Right!
Now, I think I'll try the cake.
Cake?!
Whoops. Not good, not good.
The enemy must not be underestimated.
But there is nothing to fear!
We are going to widen
the lead in one fell swoop!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
If they are going throw in some cake,
then I have an idea of my own.
Sion!
Y-Yes, Mistress!
Oomf, oomf.
Pardon me for the wait!
Every customer who buys
Nagi Sanzenin's doujinshi
will receive a deluxe consolation prize!
Now, you may have already bought one,
but how about one more to take
advantage of this opportunity?!
Hayate...
Calling me from somewhere
With the end looming near,
the competition got even more heated!
O courage, o wind, sweep through
And...
Loser Park
Calling me from somewhere
I wonder what Hayate's doing...
I don't care if I'm covered with wounds
Calling me from somewhere
Car! Car! Car! Car!
Look, I'll become the most powerful hero
Oh, that was so close!
You got the consolation prize,
the super deluxe home theater set!
I'll be right there!
All right!
Because I belong only to you!
That was too bad. Here.
A catalogue and the doujinshi.
Thank you very much!
Sold Out
And with that, we have sold every last copy!
All right! In celebration of our victory,
But I'm amazed it sold so well.
This manga makes no sense.
I think I will treat myself
to a melt-in-your-mouth pudding party.
They all just wanted the prizes, right?
Yay! That's my Mistress Kuzuha!
I guess so.
He's not here...
Are you being more stubborn than usual,
because the hypnosis didn't quite wear off?
What?
In that case, getting back
to your old self is easy.
You are cleverer than I am, are you not?
I see. I got it.
Thank you, Haruko.
Hina...
Oh! Um... It looks like
we're still a bit behind them.
But they're out of ammo now,
so we just may be able to catch up to them.
But there aren't any more customers...
It's just a little more,
so let's do our best until the end!
That's right! It's exactly
as Miss Katsura says!
If we lose, we get to see Hina
in an embarrassing maid outfit.
Let's not give up...
and do our best and win!
Ooh, he won.
He won against something in his heart.
All right! Then let's do our best!
Yeah!
Then shall we go look for customers?
All right, I guess we'll go.
What's wrong, Hayate?
Nothing.
Just thinking how fun it is
to work hard together
on something with everyone.
You look rather glum for all that.
Well...
I was just thinking
that I would've liked the Miss
to experience how that feels, too.
Then shall we get her to experience it now?
What?
Miss...
Welcome. You came to have some cake, right?
I'm certain to win this anyway,
so I just came to see the bitter
disappointment on your faces!
Well, that's too bad.
We still have some cakes left,
so we wanted someone to come eat them.
Right, Hayate?
What?
W-Well...
If you're going to go that far,
I suppose I have no choice...
It just so happens that I used
my brain to write my manga,
so I need something sweet
to resupply my tired brain with sugars.
So...
Bring me this supposed cake
that Hayate has made...
Certainly!
Thank you for waiting.
This is...
This is our shop's signature dish.
It's a bit unseasonal,
but I made it with my affections
for a certain someone in mind.
This person told me
that she didn't know me...
So, I wanted her...
...to remember all the time that she
and I have spent together...
It's sweet...
Hayate?
Miss!
Where am I?
As I recall, I came to see you
and I remember up to the point when
a weird fortune teller talked to me, but...
Miss!
What is the matter, Hayate?!
If someone should see us like this...
Wait!
We're totally being seen!
Miss! Your hypnosis has worn
off completely, hasn't it?!
So what of it?!
Look at the clock!
Time is almost up!
Top Secret Sales Chart
But the difference in our sales
is already obvious!
Now, members of the student council...
You will wear these delightfully
embarrassing maid outfits
and I think I will have
you work in my service!
Hello?
Oh, Nagi?
I thought maybe it was time
the weird hypnosis would've worn off
and you'd be with Hayate about now...
Hm? Well, you're right,
but what do you want?
We're in the middle of a pretty
serious-looking scene right now...
Oh, I'm sorry, but I wanted to
have some of Hayate's cake, too.
Would you please buy enough
for the members of the SP as well?
About 2000 servings.
Okay, got it.
2000 servings of cake.
Maria asked me to buy them.
Thank you very much.
You'll want it to-go, correct?
I-It looks like we won.
And that was the story of how
the life-or-death doujinshi battle ended.
But I wonder how Nagi's
hypnosis came undone...
Who knows? I wonder how...
That's awfully sloppy.
Hey, hurry, Hayate!
If we don't hurry,
the closing party will end!
Wait! Please hold on!
Th-This is embarrassing, Miss!
Hayate, what's that outfit about?
It's his punishment for neglecting me.
What do you think?
It looks good on him, right?
Oh, it looks like the folk dance has begun!
All right! Hayate, come with me and...
Huh?
I just can't go out like this!
Oh! Hey! Hayate!
Good grief...
I guess it doesn't change
the difficulties that Hayate faces.
It must be tough to deal
with someone who hates to lose.
Wh-What's with the look you're giving me?!
Oh, no, it is nothing.
If there's something you want to
say, speak up, all right?
Cross-dressing, huh?
Hayate Ayasaki... I still want him!
Oh! Mistress Kuzuha!
Thus, Hayate ended up back
in the Superintendent's sights again.
Next time, they will fight
against a hip young town.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate...
Ayumu Nishizawa's
Lettering by Mikako Takahashi
and Ayumu Nishizawa's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Pipiruma, pipiruma, I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I'm Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Ayumu Nishizawa.
Wait, you're still here?!
You're supposed to swap out
every 3 weeks on this segment!
What? What's wrong with that?
Besides, I haven't heard
Hayate's opinion of my song yet.
So, what do you think of my song, Hayate?
Your singing the other day was 35 points,
but this gets a full 100 points.
These days, you can make tons
of adjustments with technology.
What a thing to say!
Next time, we'll have Wataru and Saki.
Bye-bye!
Preview
Why is it?! Why can't I, a genius, draw it?!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
What is the matter, Miss?
Nagi is writing a new manga right now.
So, Hayate, go immediately
and gather reference material
on the date spots that young
people favor these days.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Must-See! Complete Autumn 2007 Guide
of the Latest Fashionable Date Spots
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Must-See! Complete Autumn 2007 Guide
of the Latest Fashionable Date Spots for the Young and Hip
"for the Young and Hip"!
And so, I will be going out
with Hayate today.
Going out with me?!
Did you know?
An Asian straight-tusked elephant fossil
was once found in Harajuku.