I'll hold them back here!
You guys, go on ahead!
"Women's Bathing Room"
They changed the password!
What?!
You're betraying your friends.
Doesn't that pain you?
Humph! My friend is you, right?
Leave me here and run.
Shouko!
This is terrible! The shampoo
and conditioner have been switched!
Oh no! We can't use
bubbles to hide our stuff then!
Principal, please prepare to escape.
That damn probationary student!
Whoa! She's got a burn mark on her butt!
She's the culprit who blackmailed us!
What? Then it wasn't Akihisa
who set up the hidden camera?!
I'm sorry, Aki, for misunderstanding.
That's okay, so long
as you realize it now.
Okay, guys! You can peek on
bathing girls to your heart's content.
Yaaaay! We're coming in!
"Aggghhh"
It was all a dream, once again.
This is the third night of
academic training camp.
Damn! I never expected that even
Ms. Takahashi would participate in the war.
That level of strength is cheating.
But what're you gonna do?
As it stands, you'll continue to be
frightened by the blackmailer's shadow.
Of course, I have no intention of giving up.
But tomorrow night is the last bathing night.
I've already worked out a plan.
But the guys from Classes D,
E, and F alone won't be enough.
Muttsulini...
Leave the picture taking to me.
Akihisa, call Himeji and Shimada in here.
What're you gonna do?
Using their pictures as a bait,
we'll request help from
the guys in Classes A, B, and C.
I see.
So we'll excite their animal passions
with pictures of the girls in yukata
in order to get them to help us, huh?
In that case, Hideyoshi,
here, this is your yukata.
We're going to excite the guys'
animal passions, you know...
I have to send Himeji and Minami an email.
There's something I wanna talk to
you about. Could you come to my room?
Send.
"Mizuki Himeji"
Ah, I've got a reply from Himeji.
Okay. I'll bring some snack food.
I've got a reply from Minami this time.
Okay, but why at this late hour?
I wonder if she's being cautious...
How should I write back?
"Ryou Sugawa"
Hm? This is from... Sugawa?
Yoshii, why are you trying so
desperately to peek on girls?
"Why"? Geez, why is he
asking something so obvious?
Isn't it obvious? I like what I like.
Hm?
"Sent Message"
"Minami Shimada"
"Isn't it obvious? I like what I like."
Calm down, Akihisa Yoshii!
Sort out what just happened!
"To: Minami Shimada" "There's something I wanna talk
to you about. Could you come to my room?"
"From: Minami Shimada"
"Okay, but why at this late hour?"
"To: Minami Shimada"
"Isn't it obvious? I like what I like."
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Is there a problem, Akihisa?
What you just did created one...
Oh, sorry. I'll fix it and give it back to you.
More importantly, let me borrow your cell!
Here.
I have to send a message to
Minami to correct my mistake.
Hm? The contacts... Kirishima's
email address is the only one in here.
What?!
She screwed with it again, and
she's supposed to be bad with machines!
Anyway, do you remember
Minami's email address?
Do you remember
Shouko's email address then?
Well, I guess that's normally how it is.
Hey, what'd you just send?!
I can't send a correction now, you idiot!
That's right! That feeling!
That's the feeling I have towards you, Yuuji!
Be quiet!
Yes, Sir.
Dammit! I gotta send
an email to Shouko now!
Let me borrow your cell!
I haven't bought a new
one since I ditched my old one.
I don't want it ringing when I'm hiding.
It's over... My life is over...
Come in.
Good evening.
Thanks for coming, Himeji.
Hm? Didn't Iron Man try to stop you?
He let me through when
I gave him some snacks.
Farewell, Iron Man... Rest in peace.
By the way, Akihisa, what was
it that you wanted to talk about?
Oh, about that...
Thus, they got their pictures
and the night wore on... however...
Aki... Aki...
Are you asleep? Hey... wake up.
Wake up.
I said, wake up!
Shhh! Don't make so much noise.
Why are you going back to sleep?!
Huh? Why are you here, Minami?
This situation...
1. I sent a weird email.
2. Minami must be upset.
3. She snuck in late at night.
4. Her entire body is a
weapon. In other words...
At least make it so that I won't suffer.
What kind of thought
process do you have?
What? I got it wrong?
I mustered up the courage
to come and see you, you know.
What?
So... uhm...
...instead of by email...
I want you to tell me in person, so...
Does that mean she wants to
hear my last will and testament?
Is there something
I can use to my advantage?!
Hideyoshi's cute sleeping face...
Muttsulini, who's so
intent on taking pictures...
Kirishima, who's trying to take off
her yukata and get into Yuuji's bed...
No! None of that will help at all!
I came to rescue you, Honey!
Something else is here!
Miharu! Why are you here?!
I snuck into your bed earlier
only to find out that it was empty
so I thought you might be here.
I thought you learned
the hard way yesterday!
What? You snuck in yesterday, too?
Honey... let's go back
now and sleep together naked!
Of course, I won't let you sleep since
I'm gonna do all sorts of things to you!
--There! There!
--Nooooo!
I won't let you sleep, either.
What're you guys doing?
Everyone, be quiet!
If you make that much noise...
Hey!
What's all this fuss about?
This is bad, Akihisa!
If he finds out that there are
four half-naked girls in our room...
Are you counting me again?
Girls, get out of here while
Yuuji and I act as decoys!
Let's go!
Yeah!
You'd better be prepared, Yoshii.
I am not!
Then, get prepared!
It can't be helped. We'll escape
into a room Iron Man can't enter!
Where's that?!
The girls' room!
I see! Iron Man can't come in
to the girls' room since he's a guy!
If I run into a girls-only
room in my underwear...
I'm a goner for sure!
Let's go!
No frickin' way!
Well then, wear this!
Thanks!
All right, now we can escape in there!
Wait! In a sense, this is more
fatal than being buck-naked!
Well then, we'll split here!
I won't let you get away!
I have no intention of
acting together with a perv.
Then, give me your yukata!
Stop it!
Shut up! Take it off! I said, take it off!
No! I said no! Hey!
What in the world...
Hm?
...are you guys doing?
I know you two have no luck with girls,
but if you wanna do something
like that, do it privately.
Please let me explain!
That was the incident that took
place on a hot night. Woo hoo...
Sleepy...
Are you two okay? We have to
recover our scores by taking tests.
Iron Man's counseling three days in a row...
It was because of that unexpected incident.
But we did get something out of it.
Whoa! Good job, Muttsulini!
We'll circulate them among guys and
recruit participants for the operation!
The fourth day of academic training camp...
The final showdown kicks off tonight.
There's something I found out last time.
This is the record of those units
spread on the second floor of the inn.
This is showing the Class C girls
fighting in science and humanities lineups.
In addition, they had the teachers' Avatars,
who're capable of physical interference, huh?
That's an impregnable defense.
Ah! Mr. Takenaka's hairpiece is...
And look at this.
The teacher field disappeared...
When the fields of teachers from
different subjects come together,
they cancel each other out.
I see. So this is what
they call interference, huh?
This is our last fight.
I bet they'll construct a solid
and unbreakable line of defense.
While avoiding the field interference,
they'll put their main forces in
the passage that we'll certainly take.
This is the expected
formation of our enemy.
Our room is on the third floor
and our goal, the girls' bathing
room is in the basement.
In the basement, Ms. Takahashi, Mr. Ooshima,
and Iron Man are on the line of defense.
Our force is made up of
guys from Classes D, E, and F.
The rest will depend on the
help from Classes A, B and C.
Looks like it'll be a tough battle.
I'll do something about Ms. Takahashi.
Muttsulini, you hold back Ooshima,
the health and physical ed. teacher.
And, Akihisa, you take on Iron Man.
Me?
The only one who can bring him
down is you, a probationary student.
I'm asking you.
But...
In return...
...we'll cover you with all our might,
and send you to Iron Man unhurt.
We'll make any sacrifice necessary
so that no one can touch
you until you fight Iron Man.
Yuuji...
Will you do it, Akihisa?
Yeah!
It's time to launch our operation!
All right! Are you guys fired up?!
Yeah!
This is our last chance!
We will accept nothing less than victory!
Yeah!
It doesn't matter if it's girls or teachers!
Let's give them a good taste
of the latent power of men!
The fourth night of academic
training camp! The final showdown!
Let's go!
They're here! The four ringleaders!
We'll bring them down here!
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
Summon!
Know your place, Class F!
Come back after you study!
We have no time to waste on small fries!
Hold it, Sakamoto!
It's Hiraga, the Class D rep!
We'll deal with him here. Go on ahead!
Thanks! I'll see you in Valhalla!
What amazing morale...
That's because everyone's heart is united.
But our real battle begins here.
If we don't have any
support forces, this is it, though.
You never learn, do you?
Teacher! Please be prepared!
You, too? Why?!
Kurosaki from Class C!
Those yukata pictures
that Muttsulini showed us...
I've never seen anything that
aroused such passion within me!
I now desperately wish to see
what's beneath those yukata!
We appreciate your help!
We'll leave it to you to watch our backs!
I'll entrust my dream to you guys, too!
Class C guys! Create a path for them!
The glorious road to victory!
Yeah!
At this rate, all the
classes will help us, right?
Well, we don't know about Class A.
Those pictures don't work with Kubo.
What?! Don't tell me, he has a more
amazing collection than those pictures?
"Main Bathing Rooms"
"Women's Bathing Room"
What took you guys so long?!
So Class B came, too!
Yuuji... Your mischief ends here.
Shouko...
Himeji...
We're not gonna let you past here, Akihisa.
This is it... There's no way that
we can defeat Himeji and Kirishima.
Nemoto...
This was a lost cause from the start.
To start with, is it worth peeking
when Himeji and Kirishima aren't bathing?
Don't give up! Even if those
two aren't bathing, other girls are!
Yeah, but...
There are no bathing girls in this
world unworthy of being peeked on!
So... So...!
Akihisa, we are at such a disadvantage.
Why aren't you giving up?
Even if you go through all that
trouble to get your pictures back,
your reputation won't change anyway, right?
It's not that, Hideyoshi.
It's true that at first, I was
going to get back those pictures
and clear the suspicion of me
peeking by capturing the real culprit.
But as I moved forward while
gaining and losing comrades,
I noticed something for the first time.
Akihisa...
Even if it's an illicit action,
I can't lie about my feelings.
I'll be honest. Right now...
I want to peek on girls bathing
purely to satisfy my desire!
Just where does your stupidity end?
So you wanna peek on Minami
bathing, rather than me, huh?!
That does it! Peeking is a bad thing!
I don't care about society's rules!
I'll live true to my feelings!
Well said, Yoshii.
Who's there?!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Yoshii.
I surely heard your honest feelings.
Kubo! You came!
I was hesitant all this time, but I made
up my mind after I heard what you said.
Guys in Class A, a total of 24!
From here on, we'll help you, Akihisa Yoshii!
Everyone! Cover him!
Yeah!
Thanks, Kubo!
It is I who ought to be thanking you.
Like you said, I can't lie
about my feelings, either.
Even if it's not allowed
by society, I like what I like!
I'm punishing Akihisa! Don't interfere!
Summon!
I swore that I'll protect Yoshii!
I won't let you do as you please!
Now! Let's go!
I never thought that even Class A
would help you... but it's not a problem.
I won't let anyone past here. Summon!
No, we're gonna pass through!
Wha...?!
Go, Akihisa!
Summon!
We won't let you get in his way!
I was starting to think you
might not show up, Muttsulini.
Even Kudou, too?
No change in our plan. Go, Akihisa.
But...!
That's fine.
Out of respect for
Muttsulini, I'll let you pass.
Go.
Okay.
Don't die, Muttsulini.
I'm disappointed in you, Tsuchiya.
To think that you have the illusion
that a student can defeat a teacher...
...decided...
What?
Who decided that a student
can't defeat a teacher?!
Very well. I'll take you on.
Summon!
774?!
I've never heard of anyone
getting that high of a score!
Having faith makes the impossible possible.
When did you get that much power?
We don't have much time.
Come at me together!
I'm surprised that you
thought I'd come this far.
I don't underestimate my opponent.
You're an idiot, but your ability
to take action is extraordinary!
Well, thank you very much!
You're extraordinarily straitlaced, too!
Don't underestimate me!
If I get serious, my power is far beyond this.
Then...
...why don't you get serious?!
If your peeking is discovered,
you'll get suspended!
That won't happen.
With this many people, you can't
identify all the Peeping Toms.
You fool. You really think so?
What?
You lack concentration!
If that's the case,
we'll just have to beat you all up
and take our time identifying
each and every one of you, that's all!
This is it, Yoshii.
What can I do to defeat him?
The concentration for ulterior
motives can only go so far after all.
Concentration? But... Concent...
That's right! Yeah, concentrate.
Narrow down the aim...
...for all my and my Avatar's
attacks to just one spot.
We'll concentrate our
attacks on your crotch!
What? What a terrifying
idea to come up with...
Pass out in agony, Iron Man!
Shatter into pieces!
As if!
We did it! Ah!
I won't let you have my honey's virginity!
Shimizu?!
Back off...
...or I'll make this picture
public and socially wipe you out!
My picture?! Do you possibly have
a burn mark on your butt, Shimizu?
How do you know that?!
So you are the blackmailer.
Then the hidden camera in
the girls' bathing room is also...
If you figured out that much,
I can't let you live! Stop fighting and...
Good job, Akihisa.
Yuuji... Guys... You guys are all okay!
Of course.
With this many people, they can't
identify every participant, huh?
Right! If we all go, we
won't be punished! Let's go!
Yeah!
A hard, painful battle...
It has already become history.
There's no one who stands in their way.
The men just move forward
with pride in their hearts.
Wh-What're you guys doing?!
It was all for nothing!!
All Year 2 male students in
Fumizuki Academy, a total of 149,
are to be suspended from school for a week.
"Approved"
I'm eating rice with raw egg over it
alone in the restroom stall.
It's early afternoon.
The spice I use is solitude.
And then misfortune strikes.
I smell something alarming.
The guy in the next stall started
eating curry in a pouch. Is he serious?!
Hold on a sec! Eating curry in the restroom
is bad manners, right?
I wanna protect this
solitude since I have nothing else.
I'll lose everything, even this space.
I gathered my courage and banged
on the wall, then looked in the next stall
and found another me sitting there.
Idiot Test!
Akihisa!
It's been a while, Himeji.
How have you been?
Akihisa... I'm sorry.
What?! Wh-What is it?
I'm sorry for treating you as a Peeping Tom
on the first day of academic training camp.
Well, I did become that
very Peeping Tom, though.
Aki!
Hi, it's been a while, Mina--
Question 8.
What aspiration did you have
when you entered the academy?
I believed that I was special and
one day something would happen
to cause others to realize my talent.
Get real.
Next episode!
"Me, Japan, and Unknown Words!"
This will be on the test.