This won't do, this just will not do.
Look at this pudgy belly!
When did you get so jelly-like?
Hey, what are you doing?
Ami has put on weight lately, no doubt about it!
This simply will not do!
I don't really care if the stupid Chi gets fat.
Y-Yeah.
Leave me alone!
I'm going home!
You idiot!
Idiot!
Dammit, I'll remember this!
That's no good, no good at all.
As one who fights for dieting, this is a serious incident that I cannot overlook.
Oh, you're so strict Kushieda.
Ah Takasu-kun, you're here?
When did you get here?
His presence is like air so it's hard to see him.
Her reply is so magnificent.
I feel like I'm falling for you again, Kushieda!
Let's get going, punks!
Kushieda Detective Office is going to stalk Ami.
Yes, sir!
Hurray for Gluttons
Don't claim you don't like something before you try it  !
Love it and never stop, it's sweet
Pink marbling, corn beef.
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for gluttons!
Don't claim you don't like something before you try it!
Love it and never stop, it's sweet...
Pink marbling, corn beef!
W-Welcome!
Boss, the target has entered the convenience store.
She's buying lots of something and will eat all of it, good or not, like an idiot, over.
Got it, we'll apprehend the subject at her house, over.
Yes, sir!
Get her!
Huh, what?
What?
What are you doing?
Boss, take a look at this.
Unbelievable, for someone to eat this much corn beef...
Did you really search for a convenience store that sold corn beef?
Nothing less from a taste-deaf idiot.
I don't want to be told what to eat by
someone who can only eat sweet curry.
Corn beef usually comes in cans.
When the cans are sealed, they are heated and sterilised.
However, with surströmming, sterilisation is unnecessary as it ferments in the can.
Herrings caught in spring are used.
They are fermented in barrels of salt for one to two months, and then tinned.
Sales begin on the third Thursday of August. The contents may be runny depending on the product, so use caution when eating.
At any rate, it is a world...
There he goes again, trying to pretend he's a sommelier.
That's enough, stupid dog.
It's tasty and it doesn't matter what you do or say, idiot!
Now I'll show you the most delicious way of eating it.
Here we go.
Of course corn beef is great when used to make sandwiches or rice balls,
but when you think about it, this simple way of eating it is the best.
It's so good you'll die.
I want to sleep enveloped by a sea of corn beef.
Here you are, please have some of this corn beef tower.
As if!
A-a-a-ah.
It's not good to judge things before trying them.
Taste it! Then you'll know whether you like it or not.
Um, well, shall we try it?
It's great, it's tasty, I'm sorry, mama, mama!
Right? Only few people understand how tasty it really is.
Unlike you commoners.
Doesn't matter, it's bad.
It's uncommon, but I agree with you, stupid dog.
You're wrong about it!
On the subject of corn beef,
It's like you're taste buds are swimming in a pool of delight!
when I was a kid I thought corn beef contained corn and beef.
Isn't it the best?
Yes it is!
What a hoax!
Ugh, it feels like it's about to come back up!
Splendid! Bravo!
This is the worst!
Which is why this duel is a tie!
By the way, corn beef means "sea salted beef" in English.
How terrifying, corn beef!
My next job is in Mongolia. I'm doing a swimsuit shoot.
Oh, sounds fun. I'm sure you'll look great.
Winter there is minus 20 degrees, your nose hairs will freeze off.
Really?!
Today's Inko
The End
Tasty!
Dedicated to Nakanishi Gou