♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE, ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK. 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[SEAGULLS
CALLING IN DISTANCE]
[CLICKING]
[SCREAMS]
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, A WATERFALL.
HUH? DO YOU KNOW
THIS PLACE, ED?
I THINK I KNOW.
I DON'T THINK I KNOW.
I DON'T THINK I THINK I KNOW.
I DON'T THINK
I THINK... AH!
OH! WHICH IS IT?
[SNORING]
COME ON!
OH...
[GRUMBLES]
[KISSES]
[MUFFLED PROTESTS]
[CRASH]
HMM?
[EIN BARKING]
OH, DAMN IT, EIN!
HEY, SPIKE, WHERE
THE DEVIL ARE WE?
IT'S EARTH, ISN'T IT?
EARTH? THIS SHIP
WAS HEADED FOR MARS.
WHAT ARE WE DOING ON EARTH
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- DON'T KNOW.
- OH, DAMN!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
WHILE WE'RE WASTING TIME,
OUR BOUNTY HEAD'S GETTING AWAY.
[GARGLES]
THIS IS OUR BEST LEAD
IN MONTHS.
HOW DID WE JUST
GET OFF COURSE AND
- JET!
- HUH?
- THE GIRLS ARE GONE.
- WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, I PROMISE. IF YOU
LEAD ME TO THAT WATERFALL PLACE,
- I'LL GIVE YOU SOMETHING GOOD.
- OH, GOOD THING WHAT?
YOU'LL SEE IT'S SOMETHING
WONDERFULLY, TREMENDOUSLY GOOD.
HEE HEE! YOHOO!
IT'S SOMETHING WONDERFULLY,
TREMENDOUSLY GOOD! HURRAH!
[SPLASH]
♪ YOU GET... ♪
[ENGINE ROARS]
♪ THEY KNOW ALL ♪
♪ IT'S TOO LATE TO FIGHT ♪
♪ BITTERNESS ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
HOT! HOT, HOT, HOT!
♪ THEY DON'T CARE ♪
♪ THAT YOU
OH OH OH OH OH ♪
OVER HERE!
WATERFALL!
HA HA HA HA HA!
[SIGHS]
RIGHT, LISTEN TO ED.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
HUH? OH.
OH!
HEY, LOOK! I FOUND ED.
HUH? SO EDWARD IS FOUND?
DO YOU KNOW THESE KIDS?
[KIDS LAUGHING]
LOOK IT! COOL, HUH?
- CAN I PLEASE HAVE YOUR NAILS?
- NAILS?
I'M COLLECTING THEM.
CAN I?
JUST THE PINKY
WOULD BE ALL RIGHT
UH!
ANYTHING YOU COULD GIVE ME
HEY!
IT'S COOL, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
[KIDS HOLLERING]
CHILDREN!
OH! OH!
OH. OH!
EDWARD!
HA HA HA!
IS THAT REALLY...
IS IT YOU, EDWARD?
I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL THAT.
I'M AFRAID IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN GET THE KIDS
TO PAY ATTENTION SOMETIMES.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IS EDWARD
IS SHE FROM THIS PLACE?
SHE WANDERED IN
ABOUT 5 YEARS AGO.
BEFORE I KNEW IT,
SHE WAS EATING HERE
AS IF THAT'S THE WAY
IT ALWAYS WAS.
THEN, ABOUT 3 YEARS AGO,
SHE WANDERED AWAY AGAIN
LIKE A CAT, YOU KNOW?
I'VE OFTEN WONDERED
HOW SHE'S BEEN GETTING ALONG.
BUT I DIDN'T THINK THAT SHE
WOULD SUDDENLY APPEAR LIKE THIS.
CHILDREN! LET'S EAT!
[KIDS HOLLERING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
OUR FATHER IN HEAVEN,
YOU KNOW WE'RE HERE.
SO, I'LL LEAVE OFF THE REST.
EAT HEARTY, KIDS!
THANKS! AMEN!
[EATING NOISILY]
HEY, I CAN EAT FASTER
THAN YOU CAN!
[KIDS LAUGHING]
UH, I'M AFRAID
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
OH, WHY, DEAR?
YOU'RE WELCOME HERE.
ACTUALLY,
I'M LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
ED KNOWS WHERE IT IS.
HUH?
WE JUST CAME HERE BECAUSE
THERE'S GOOD FOOD, FAYEFAYE.
[GRUMBLES]
YOU LITTLE RAT!
YOU HAVE TO GIVE ME
SOMETHING GOOD!
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THERE'S SOMETHING GOOD
IN MY DESK DRAWER.
I'VE BEEN SAVING IT
FOR YOU, EDWARD.
SOMETHING GOOD?
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
OH! SOMETHING GOOD FOR ED?
IT'S IN THE TOP DRAWER.
OH, AH?
NO, NOT THAT ONE.
AH?
YES, THAT'S IT.
OPEN IT UP.
OH!
HMM.
IT'S YOUR FATHER.
OH! ED'S FATHER?
MMHMM. HE CAME HERE LOOKING
FOR ED ABOUT TWO MONTHS AGO.
HE SAID HE FORGOT THAT HE
PUT HER IN A DAY CARE CENTER
AND THAT HE'D BEEN
LOOKING FOR HER FOR 7 YEARS,
HOPPING AROUND THE WORLD.
OH, HE'S NOT YOUR
MODEL FATHER, I SUPPOSE.
STILL, I DO HOPE SHE FINDS HIM.
IN THIS WORLD, PEOPLE MUST
CHERISH WHATEVER TIES THEY HAVE.
[STONE CRUNCHING]
[BEEPING]
- AH!
- YES!
[WIND BLOWING]
[SIGHS]
ARE YOU FAYE?
YOU ARE!
IMPOSSIBLE!
IT'S ME, SALLY YOUNG.
I WAS IN YOUR GRADUATING
CLASS IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH!
[COUGHS]
ARE YOU OK?
[CONTINUES COUGHING]
I WAS SO SURPRISED. I THOUGHT
YOU WERE SOME KIND OF GHOST.
YOU LOOK JUST
THE SAME AS BEFORE.
THEY SAY THEY APPEAR IN PLACES
WHERE THEY HAVE REGRETS.
OF COURSE, I REMEMBER NOW,
THEY PUT YOU INTO CRYOGENIC
HIBERNATION AFTER THAT ACCIDENT.
THAT'S WHY YOU
STILL LOOK THE SAME.
- ACCIDENT?
- FAYE, DON'T YOU REMEMBER IT?
[SIGHS]
MAYBE.
GRANDMA! HEY, GRANDMA!
GRANDMA,
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK NOW.
- IS IT TIME ALREADY?
- OH! OH.
MM.
DO YOU KNOW WHO
THIS NICE LADY IS?
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE IT, DEAR.
BUT THE FACT IS THAT SHE'S
A GHOST FROM BEYOND.
- OH!
- HUH?
[LAUGHS SOFTLY]
GOODBYE! TAKE CARE!
[SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO!
CHANGING COURSE WITHOUT ASKING.
OUR PLANS HAVE BEEN COMPLETELY
SCREWED UP BECAUSE OF THIS.
I DON'T APPRECIATE
THESE KINDS OF STUNTS, FAYE.
UH...
HMM?
[KEYS CLICKING]
[EIN WHIMPERS]
HEY, EIN, I GOT US SOMETHING.
WANT TO SMELL?
[BARKS]
[SIGHS]
WHAT'S WITH THEM?
IT'S LIKE THEY'VE GOT
A BIG SECRET OR SOMETHING.
BETTER LET IT BE.
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST
TOO HUNGRY, YOU KNOW.
IT'S A KNOWN FACT THAT
HUMAN BEINGS GO INSANE
- IF THEY DON'T EAT.
- IT'S 50 MILLION.
HMM. OH, THAT'S PRETTY BIG.
"APPLEDELHI SINIZ HESAP LUFEN."
[SLURPS]
DO YOU WANT ONE? HUH?
McENROE?
IT'S McINTYRE, AND I'LL TAKE
A PASS MR. APPLEDELHI. THANKS.
YOU SURE?
SUCKING EGGS IS GOOD FOR YOU.
IT'LL GIVE YOU POWER, CHARGE.
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
TONE YOU, McINTOSH.
IT'S McINTYRE, ACTUALLY.
I KNOW I'M JUST YOUR ASSISTANT,
BUT YOU COULD REMEMBER MY NAME.
IT'S NOT HARD.
DON'T SWEAT THE SMALL STUFF,
MY FRIEND. HA HA HA HA!
- HURRY, McWHATEVER!
- McINTYRE!
[ENGINE STARTS]
[WATER RUNNING]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[BREATHING HARD]
OW!
HEY, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING!
AH... [OUT OF BREATH]
- AH...
- WHAT?
- I'M SORRY.
- YOU'RE... SORRY?
[SIGHS]
YES.
I HAVE TO GO.
ARE YOU GOING OUT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, HUH?
EDWARD, I FINALLY REMEMBER
WHERE IT IS THAT I BELONG.
YOU BELONG?
YES, ED. YOU HAVE
SOMEONE WAITING FOR YOU, TOO.
THERE'S SOMEWHERE THAT
YOU BELONG, EDWARD.
YOU SHOULD GO
AND FIND OUT WHERE.
HMM...
THAT'S THE BEST. BELONGING IS
THE VERY BEST THING THERE IS.
[ENGINE REVVING UP]
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A PIECE OF CAKE.
50 MILLION IN THE BAG.
IF THE GIRLS COULD EAT SOME
SUKIYAKI WITH ME, THEN THAT
- JET, FAYE TOOK OFF AGAIN.
- OH, SWELL.
WHERE DID SHE GO THIS TIME?
ARCTURUS?
[SIGHS]
A WOMAN'S HEART IS AS FICKLE
AS THE SKIES OF GANYMEDE.
APPLEDELHI?
WE'D LIKE YOU TO COME ALONG
WITH US, ALL RIGHT?
A LITTLE BASIC COOPERATION
HERE, AND YOU WON'T GET HURT.
WHO ARE YOU GUYS?
WE'VE GOT WORK TO DO,
AND YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
WORK TO DO?
SINCE THE GATE ACCIDENT,
CHAOS RULES THE EARTH.
NOW HOW DO YOU THINK WE CAN
REGAIN PEACEFUL PEACE AND
NON-CHAOS IN THE COSMIC SENSE?
HUH?
ONLY THROUGH MAPS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE EARTH HAS CHANGED,
SO WE MAP THOSE CHANGES
TO UNDERSTAND THEM.
WE'RE CREATING MAPS OF
THE NEWLY ALTERED PLANET EARTH
SO WE CAN SAVE IT.
THAT'S GREAT.
ONLY THE METEOR SHOWERS CHANGE
THE TERRAIN EVERY TWO DAYS,
SO WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
NAH, THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
WE TRAVEL AROUND SO MUCH.
WE CHASE DOWN
EVERY MAJOR METEOR.
THEN WE UPDATE THE MAPS,
THUS CHANGING CHAOS TO ORDER.
- HUH.
- ALL RIGHT, I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
OOF!
AHH!
OW!
I WASN'T EXPECTING A MATCH.
AH!
[ENGINE STARTS]
AAH!
AH!
- EDWARD!
- HEY, HOLD IT!
[LAUGHS]
FRANCOISE!
HEY!
YAY!
HA HA HA!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
ROUND AND ROUND WE GO!
[LAUGHING]
UPSYDAISY!
THIS IS THE FATHER PERSON.
- FA-FATHER?
- YOU MEAN, YOUR FATHER?
YOU HAVE A FATHER?
THIS IS SPIKE PERSON
AND JET PERSON, OK?
OK.
HEH HEH!
NO, THESE ARE ED'S FRIENDS.
I STAY WITH THEM, OK?
OH, THAT'S DIFFERENT. THANKS
FOR TAKING CARE OF MY SON.
HMM, OR WAS IT MY DAUGHTER?
WELL, EITHER WAY,
YOU GUYS ARE ALL RIGHT.
A LITTLE TOKEN OF
MY APPRECIATION.
DON'T TELL ME, DID YOU PUT
THAT BOUNTY IN THE COMPUTER OR
50 POINT 000 000...
ONLY 50 WOOLONGS.
SO, FRANCOISE,
WANT TO STAY WITH ME NOW?
HUH?
HEY!
WOW!
- WHOA! LET'S GO, McDINGLE!
- IT'S McINTYRE!
HEY, HOLD ON!
UUH!
FATHER PERSON GONE.
[BREATHING HARDER]
[WIND BLOWING]
♪ I CLOSE MY EYES,
AND I KEEP SEEING THINGS ♪
♪ RAINBOW WATERFALLS,
SUNNY LIQUID DREAMS ♪
♪ CONFUSION CREEPS INSIDE ME,
RAINING DOUBT ♪
♪ GOT TO GET TO YOU ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW ♪
♪ CALL ME, CALL ME ♪
♪ LET ME KNOW IT'S ALL RIGHT ♪
HEY! DINNER IS READY.
HUH?
♪ PLEASE WON'T YOU CALL
AND EASE MY MIND? ♪
SPIKE. FOOD.
♪ REASONS FOR ME TO FIND YOU ♪
♪ PEACE OF MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO ♪
♪ TO GET ME TO YOU? ♪
♪ I HAD YOUR NUMBER
QUITE SOME TIME AGO ♪
♪ BACK WHEN WE WERE YOUNG ♪
♪ BUT I HAD TO GROW ♪
♪ TEN THOUSAND YEARS
I'VE SEARCHED IT SEEMS AND NOW ♪
♪ GOT TO GET TO YOU ♪
♪ WON'T YOU TELL ME HOW? ♪
YOU CAN'T COME WITH ME, EIN.
[EIN WHIMPERS]
EDWARD IS GOING
SOMEPLACE FAR, FAR AWAY.
ED MIGHT NOT BE COMING BACK.
SO YOU BETTER GO BACK
TO THE SHIP, EIN.
OH.
DO YOU WANT TO COME WITH ED?
[EIN BARKS]
♪ COME ON, NOW WON'T YOU ♪
♪ EASE MY MIND? ♪
♪ REASONS FOR ME TO FIND YOU ♪
♪ PEACE OF MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO ♪
COME ON, LET'S GO!
[BARKS]
♪ TO GET ME TO YOU? ♪
EVERYTHING HAS A BEGINNING
AND AN END.
LIFE IS JUST A CYCLE
OF STOPS AND STARTS.
THERE ARE ENDS WE DON'T DESIRE,
BUT THEY ARE INEVITABLE.
WE HAVE TO FACE THEM. THAT'S
WHAT BEING HUMAN IS ALL ABOUT.
IT'S BEEN A FAST TRIP FOR BEBOP,
ONLY TWO EPISODES LEFT.
BUT MAKE SURE YOU PAY
CLOSE ATTENTION TO THE END.
NEXT EPISODE,
THE REAL FOLK BLUES, PART I.