It's true!
When we played classical music
to our shiitake mushrooms,
they grew positively huge.
Oh, yeah? You don't say.
If you hit them with electricity,
like artificial lightning,
they grow even more.
Electricity?
Mm-hm. When they're stimulated
by a strong current,
mushroom fungal filaments
feel a sense of danger,
and apparently actively grow
bigger to ensure they reproduce.
Whatever, just do your homework.
A helicopter?
Come to think of it...
Ogi liked helicopters.
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Ogi-san? Do you mean Ogi
Takahiro-san, of Class 2-B?
Is the Mountain Range Clear?
Who's that?
You know, the one in Class 2-B.
This is an Ogi you don't know.
He was our English teacher
in middle school.
Satoshi, that one.
Of course I know Ogi-sensei.
But I didn't know he liked helicopters.
I thought Ogi's liking of
helicopters was well-known.
Ibara, you knew, didn't you?
Not really.
That's strange. How is it that
I know about it, but they don't?
They both went to
Kaburaya Middle School, too,
and Ibara and I were
always in the same class.
There's no way she wouldn't know.
Um, is there something
the matter over this Ogi-san?
Oh, just a little bit.
Ibara, you remember, don't you?
One day, a helicopter flew over
Kaburaya Middle School, right?
Yeah, several dozen times.
I'm talking about just one time.
In the middle of class,
Ogi suddenly ran to the window,
and looked up into the sky.
He kept watching as the helicopter
flew off into the distance
and then said something about
how he liked helicopters,
trying to laugh it off, before
getting back to class, remember?
Hm, when you add in all
those details, I do remember it.
That did happen. Was that Ogi?
Yes, it was Ogi.
That's better. I wasn't misremembering it.
That is strange.
Strange or not, that's what happened.
But when JSDF helicopters
fly around in squadrons,
it's quite a sight to see, and yet,
I don't remember Ogi-sensei
ever reacting to them.
What's a "squadron"?
In formation.
How can you tell they were JSDF?
Because I can't think of
any other helicopter groups
that fly around in formation.
And you're sure that Ogi was
around when that would happen?
Yeah, I think so.
I do remember seeing those helicopters
and looking up the word "AGM"
in my English dictionary.
AGM?
What is that?
An abbreviation for
"air-to-ground missile."
You're right; if those were to fly over,
Ogi would probably run out onto
the school grounds and dance around.
I doubt he would actually dance.
I'm just saying.
Mm-hm, it was Ogi-sensei that
was thrilled by helicopters.
Seems like it was just after we
started going to middle school.
Now that you mention it,
I seem to remember thinking,
"There sure are some strange
teachers in middle school."
But, like Fuku-chan mentioned,
I never saw Ogi reacting
to helicopters after that.
Three years ago, huh?
My memories have grown fuzzy.
But now that she mentions it,
except for that one time,
I don't remember Ogi doing similar.
When you mention Ogi-sensei,
there's another legend that
has a major impact, too.
An astounding legend concerning Ogi!
Don't go making your own.
It's not that. This isn't one I made.
Ogi-sensei himself said so.
Yeah, Ogi-sensei... I kind of
find it hard to believe, myself.
I'm not sure you'll
believe me when I tell you.
I'm not saying it's
impossible either, but...
Hurry up and spill it.
According to Ogi-sensei himself,
he has been struck by lightning
three times in his life.
Huh?! By lightning, you mean lightning?
Mm-hm. As in "thunder!"
Three times? I'm surprised he's okay.
He was struck by it... sandodaa!
[sandodaa: three times/thunder]
Three times? I'm surprised he's okay.
It sounds like Chitanda has
figured out how to deal with Satoshi.
Apparently, it didn't hit him directly,
but even so, he didn't get away unscathed.
He said he was knocked
unconscious once,
and he has some burn marks on his body.
Is that right? But he is still alive,
so that's one consolation.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Come to think of it, he didn't
have any scars that stuck out.
Lightning... and three times, at that.
Is something like that possible?
The city of Kamiyama doesn't
get all that much lightning.
Despite which, Ogi alone has
been struck three times?
Satoshi doesn't seem to be lying to us.
Truth
Falsehood
He even said at
the outset that he didn't make it up.
If that's the case, could Ogi be lying?
It seems too incredible for it to be a lie.
Hold on a second!
Satoshi, they keep old newspapers
at the library, right?
Yes, they do. Some of them, anyway.
They have some in the
school library, too, actually.
But just articles that have
to do with Kami High.
That's not going to be good enough.
I'm leaving.
I'm heading to the library. Want to come?
Huh?!
Hotaro, it almost looks like you're
motivated about something!
You're wrong!
How can I put this? I'm just...
I'm curious.
Hotaro...?
It is you, right, Hotaro?
You're our energy-conservationist
Oreki Hotaro, right?!
Have you been taken over by an alien?
Or maybe you've been
possessed by Chitanda-san!
Knock it off!
Oreki, you should go home.
Warm yourself up and go right to bed.
I'm sure you'll be back at 100% tomorrow.
How rude. Is it really so unusual for
me to do something spontaneously?
Well, whatever. I'll wrap this up quickly.
Oreki-san!
What?
You're curious, aren't you?
Okay, yeah.
You're going to go investigate?
I might not even turn anything up.
Now I'm curious!
About what?
That there is something in this world
that can tickle your curiosity!
I'm curious to know just what
such a thing might be!
She's pretty rude, as well.
Satoshi said he had homework,
so he wouldn't be coming.
It would have helped to have Ibara,
the library staffer, come along,
but I didn't have any right to ask.
Thanks for waiting for me.
Okay, shall we go?
You go on ahead.
I can give you a lift.
No, that isn't right.
No, not right.
No, you go on ahead.
O-Okay. Bye, then.
Chitanda!
Yes?
If you're able to search through
old newspaper articles,
would you check out the name
Ogi Masakiyo for me?
Ogi Masakiyo is written like
"small tree that is correct and pure."
Very well. I'll see you later.
Kanro ('Cold Dews')
When the dews stiffen as they form
in keeping with the gray cold
Hyouka
From what my sister says,
having gone up into the Kamikakiuchi
mountain range several times,
in ranges where the mountains
are of the 3,000-meter class,
even the air currents are blocked
and the climate can be completely
different on the near and far sides.
It wouldn't be right to keep
Chitanda waiting for too long.
Kamiyama City Library
Ah, Oreki-san!
I found some information on Ogi-sensei.
"Mountain trail beautification efforts
in the Kamikakiuchi Range."
Ogi-sensei is someone who went
mountain climbing, huh?
"The Kamiyama Mountaineering
Association began sponsoring
beautification efforts on the
Abumidake mountain trail on the 26th.
11 volunteers took part,
picking up trash around the trail.
Kamiyama Mountaineering Association
captain, Ogi Masakiyo-san, 39, said,
'The climbing boom means more climbers
who don't know climbing manners.
I'd like them to know that breaches
of manners in the mountains
could cost someone their life.'"
Yeah, I was afraid of that.
Um, is something the matter?
Not really. Did you manage to
search all the old newspapers?
Um, we can have them look at
the counter on the second floor.
I'm kind of hoping this hunch
I have doesn't prove true.
Excuse me, I'd like to do a
search on newspaper articles.
Sure. What would you like to search?
Articles from April through May,
three years ago, please.
Do you have any keywords?
Yes...
"Stranded."
Huh?
There are 12 hits. Would you
like to narrow that down?
If that's all there are,
please let me see them.
Go ahead.
Found it.
Search for stranded party in
Kamikakiuchi Range faces difficulty
It's an article from May 9th.
Excuse me, but could we see
this newspaper article?
Chitanda sees where this is going.
Maruta-san, do you have a moment?
What is it?
Um, we'd like to see this news article
from May 9th, three years ago.
Three years ago? Just a moment.
Right. Thank you very much.
Oh, it will take about 30 minutes
to get that article, is that okay?
Understood.
I'll call you over when it's ready.
We appreciate it.
Oreki-san, as long as we're here,
would you like to look around?
Yeah, okay.
A special issue on Taira no
Kiyomorithis month, huh?
The cover is so pretty.
In this feature, Taira no Kiyomori
is presented as a child
of the Shirakawa-in, huh?
There is indeed that theory.
Wow, that's something else.
Miyajima... the Itsukashima Shrine.
I've always wanted to go see it.
Exciting Vegetable School
So many cabbages! The colors are so pretty!
And so many tomatoes on this page!
They all look so tasty.
Come to think of it, Oreki-san,
we have plenty of shiitake
mushrooms that we harvested.
Huh?
Would you like some?
Oh! Books about insects, Oreki-san!
Dung Beetles
Dung beetles, huh?
How cute!
Why would she choose that one?
Oreki-san, is there anything
you'd like to look at?
Castles
Well, let's see...
That's a huge, proper castle.
Your house is pretty big in its own right.
Our house isn't that big.
I'd say it's just a bit bigger than normal.
I'm not sure what standard
you're using for "normal."
So, how did it go?
It has been compiled within
this file, so check inside here.
Thank you very much.
Whoa, it's heavy.
There's a lot in here, huh?
Ah! It's the newspaper from May 9th!
When Ogi interrupted class to
express his affection for helicopters,
it was probably on this day.
Here it is.
Two members of Kamiyama
Mountaineering Association stranded
So in sum, what does this all mean?
In sum,
it wasn't the helicopters that Ogi liked.
Ogi was hit by lightning three times.
That's probably a true story.
But would anyone in this city
who works as an English teacher
typically get hit by lightning so much?
That's true... they wouldn't.
So then it hit me. Maybe Ogi
often went somewhere
that lightning does strike a lot.
That would be the mountains, right?
Did you have a hunch it would be this?
More or less.
I thought that while Ogi was a teacher,
maybe he was also a
mountain climber, too.
So I figured it could be possible
and came here to make sure.
Why, on that day alone, did Ogi
look up at the helicopter?
Because that helicopter had
some special significance.
Ogi was eagerly waiting for
that helicopter to fly that day.
How do you mean?
To take it a little further,
Ogi was desperately anxious
about whether or not the
helicopter would fly that day.
That's why, when he heard the sound,
he couldn't help but check
to make sure what it was.
Just saying that an English teacher
pays attention to helicopters
doesn't tell you anything.
But when you say a mountain
climber pays attention to them,
that's another story.
Kamiyama here is in the shadow
of the Kamikakiuchi Range,
a string of 3,000-meter class mountains.
The mountain climbers in this city
paid attention to helicopters.
Might have been aerial photography,
or transporting materials.
But if it wasn't...
If it wasn't...?
It was a rescue.
weather deteriorating...
A rescue?
In the article, it says that on
the 8th, the weather was bad,
and helicopters were unable to fly.
Yeah, I know.
Ogi was worried about whether
the police chopper could fly.
Even while he was teaching,
he was anxious about the weather
on the Kamikakiuchi Range improving.
If it was clear on the mountain range,
the helicopter would fly.
If it was clear, the stranded climbers'
odds of survival would improve.
Imagine what kind of feelings
Ogi-sensei was going through.
I can't tell you what he was feeling,
but I think he was smiling.
We skimmed through the
newspapers for a few days after.
The bodies of two stranded
climbers were discovered.
They were found by the police helicopter.
Um...
Hm?
Is it okay if I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Why were you curious about this?
Is it that outlandish that I'd
voluntarily investigate something?
Yes, it is. It didn't seem
like something you would do.
Well, that's true. I usually say,
"If I don't have to do
something, I don't do it."
No, I didn't mean it that way.
She simply brushed aside
my immutable motto.
Oreki-san, you do work hard
for others, in all kinds of ways.
I've had you help me out
any number of times.
She's got it completely wrong.
However, Oreki-san, you're complacent
when it comes to yourself.
So why is it that today, at least,
you looked into your own question?
Hm...
I'm sorry.
It's something I just have to know.
When I heard about the
lightning from Satoshi,
it evoked an unpleasant
association in my mind.
Yes, you mentioned that.
I wanted to make it clear whether
I was right about it or not.
That's why I decided to go investigate it.
So I went to the library.
If it had been some major investigation
that would keep me there a whole week,
then that's another matter,
but if it only meant flipping through
old newspapers, no big deal.
I had you to help, too.
And if it were true, it was something
I should be careful about.
Be careful, you say?
The truth is, with
everything that happened,
I shouldn't just casually say
"Ogi sure likes helicopters, huh?"
That would be insensitive.
And that's something that
I try to be careful about.
Hm?
Was that too hard for her to follow?
Maybe not insensitive, but, you know...
that feeling of "not knowing
how the other guy feels."
I'll probably never run into Ogi again,
so maybe how he feels
isn't a major concern.
Oreki-san...
Hm?
That's... very...
I can't really express it.
What was she trying to say? Oh, well.
If she can't express it well,
I won't be able to get it out of her.
Well, gotta go. Thanks for
helping me out today.
You're very welcome.
I'm glad I got to see such an
unexpected side of you today.
Jeez, give me a break.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay, see you later.
By the time Chitanda gets home,
night will have fallen.
Chitanda's the one who
offered to tag along.
It's not like I asked her
to come. Then again...
I guess I do owe her one for this.
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "Does Anyone Have Any Idea?"
Does Anyone Have Any Idea?