You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Is the Mountain Range Clear?
Truth    Falsehood
Kanro ('Cold Dews')
When the dews stiffen as they form
in keeping with the gray cold
Hyouka
When the dews stiffen as they form
in keeping with the gray cold
Kamiyama City Library
"Mountain trail beautification efforts
in the Kamikakiuchi Range"
"Search for stranded party in
Kamikakiuchi Range faces difficulty"
Exciting Vegetable School
Dung Beetles
Castles
"Two members of Kamiyama
Mountaineering Association stranded"
"...weather deteriorating..."
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having
antennas is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Does Anyone Have Any Idea?