WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the series director, 宮本幸裕(Miyamoto Yukihiro).
Many people know him by his handle name, おとこ祭り(otokomatsuri).
Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika has two "main directors:" Miyamoto Yukihiro, and 新房昭之(Shinbou Akiyuki).
It should be noted that while Shinbou-san is considered the director, Miyamoto-san is given the title series director.
Hello, everyone! Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magi–Magika episode 6 um,
(lol)
Something Like This Is Definitely Strange audio commentary, umm... we are now continuing,
With the role of Madoka, I'm Yuuki Aoi!
Yup! With the role of Akemi Homura, I'm Saitou Chiwa, and—
Series–Series director, Miyamoto.
Yaaay!
Miyamoto Yukihiro-san, I look forward to working with you!
I look forward to working with you!
I look forward to working with you.
Miyamoto-san, you seem like you want to go home.
Miyamoto-san, you seem like you want to go home!
(lol)
You're brimming with that feeling since "Hello".
That's right...
Right.
I look forward to working with you!
I look forward to working with you.
We haven't really talked that much, so first of all, right, um...
Ne?
What does a series director-san (lol) do? (lol)
(lol)
What're you doing? (lol)
It's probably a super basic question, but actually, we don't really know, so...
(lol)
Um, we've greeted Miyamoto-san plenty of times, so...
Right.
and I know a bit about Miyamoto-san, but it's like "What does he do?" (lol)
That's right.
(lol)
We'd just like to ask that a bit. (lol)
What do you do?
Really, this kind of question...
Excuse us (lol)
Well, I might just seem to be loitering around aimlessly every time we talk,
(lol)
and then it's like "Well, that's really it." (lol)
Somehow um, isn't it what you'd call "series composition"?
That's right, it's basically like the series composition, and talking about the composition.
That's right, ne.
Director-sans are more about an overall balance, then?
Well, it's things such as making decisions regarding cuts...
Well, "Here should be like this?" or "How is it like this?" or "Here would be better like this."
Okay.
Mm.
You're asked if a lot things are "okay."
I see.
Ahhh.
So it's like you give a consensus on the full thing?
Right... well, it is dealing with details too, but by nature, it's dealing with what you call "content" itself.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, that doesn't mean that's all there is to it, just...
I've done a lot of pieces of work with SHAFT,
it's not just limited to saying "That's okay" or "That's not okay."
Mmmmm.
Those time—
You decide things about scenes(/settings)?
Yes.
Like saying "It's night, so it should be dark," or a sunset...
It's doing things at those sort of times.
I see, but without that person, no one would decide anything! (lol)
I see! butwithout that person, no one would decide anything! (lol)
Ne? (lol)
It'd be like, the outcome [of scenes] is "What?"
(lol)
That's why you're like a thinking intelligent person!
I see!
On the entirety.
Ah~Ah
Ahh...
Miyamoto-san is finally here, so what do we ask?
(lol)
Actually, since long ago, I've always kind of thought "What does he do~?"
Still, we just didn't know exactly what you did!
(lol)
That's right, isn't it?
Right, so for us, we've had a long "fellowship," there are a lot of people we know, and faces we know...
Mm!
Mm, mm.
But when being introduced, it's like "What does this guy do?" "What does this guy do?"
(lol) Right.
There are a lot of people I just remember, though.
Mm!
I see!
Now then, for that kind of position...
I don't really have anything to ask.
(lol)
Mm!
I don't really have   nothing to ask!
Ne?
What should be asked? I'm not even sure what I'm going to ask.
That's right, isn't it?
Right, "What's going to happen to Homura after this?"
(lol)
What a thing...
No, no...
Ah, actually, this time's commentary... we've finally finished the full thing.
Now we just have commentary.
Our recording, you know.
Right, we've done up to the end of episode twelve now.
Ah, that's right, isn't it.
After recording—
This is our first time being done with after recording, we finally know the full series.
I see, ah.
Then, we can just commentate on episode twelve, right?
Ehhh?
EHHHH?
You see, this is still episode six, so we can't do any spoilers.
Ahh, I see.
Actually, speaking of that...
If anyone out there hasn't watched the original episode six yet, please listen to this, but go watch the original volume first.
Right, right, right, right.
(lol)
There will be some spoilers.
Thfere will be! some spoilers.
We'll try hard not to spoil the full thing.
Wef'll try hard! not to spoil the full thing.
Yup! Then, this time um, I was thinking "What to ask Miyamoto-san," but um...
Mm!
Um, up to this point...
This is a conversation I'd like to hear, but...
For this piece of work's "concept"-type thing, why was this work originally created? It's an original, right?
Yes, yes.
I'd like to ask something like that, yeah...
Ah, I do—
If it's something like "I don't know", I'll ask a different question.
(lol)
Ah, how troubling (lol)
Unexpectedly, we were slow with deciding the timing on this series.
Ah, is that right?
Ah, that's right.
Ah, is it no good to say other titles?
No, I think it'll be fine, surely.
If it's no good we'll add a "pii!"(censor)
Ah, it'll be added?
A–Arakawa Under The Bridge is a piece of work we were doing,
(lol)
Ah, yes.
then, we just couldn't really fit Madoka into our schedule.
When that was done, we were going to do Den—Denpa Onna. It was very close, you know.
That's why it wasn't really truly brought up until the last moment.
Suddenly it was slapped on the table, and then it was like "OK!"
(lol)
That's (lol)... you were entrusted with such a nice thing?
"Let's do it" "Kay~!" → "Ehhh!?"
(lol) Nah, it was like that. (lol)
Ah, I see...
Ehhh?
Then, when the rough version of this piece of work was decided upon, it was given to you, Miyamoto-kun?
Yes, and—
Like "Here you go."
Then I was told "Make atmosphere."
Ahh, is that so? That's amazing, you know.
Then you just said "Yeah"?
(lol)
Mm!
Mm, that's right.
Then, since Miyamoto-san entered, the parts that changed...
Yes, yes.
Or,
Really we had this conversation in the beginning, but were there parts that were like "Do this a little bit more like this?"
Ahhh, you could probably say I actually wasn't that type of director, instead I properly asked/listened to director Shinbou's opinions.
Then I persevered when I was entrusted with things.
Mmm!
I believe that not much was completely replaced.
Were there any times that "Eh? That's impossible!" were said?
Ah, that was said every day.
(lol)
What about times when you left your impression on things?
Eh? Ah. During the time when we were swapping the dubbing and BGM, well, and then the errors...
Yes.
On those days, we still have a bit of detail to add, but at that timing there are judgment decisions made...
The director will say they want a BG to be changed, or a character to be changed a bit... then, "Can we make it in time?"
Ohh!
Hohhh.
Yes.
(lol)
Well, I can't say anything except "Yes!"
Ahhh.
Somehow, for us on this commentary, we had one blunder... a regrettable time?
That was when we got Kyousuke's hair color wrong,
because it was different between on air and commentary...
Ah, Kyousuke's hair color.
(lol)
That's right, isn't it...
So for us watching commentary right now, could there be something different this time, too?
Since it's like, there are details and scenes that are changed between the DVD versions we do and the actual on-air version.
Like scene cuts and such, right?
Right, right.
Then there are angles which are changed slightly, too.
That's there, isn't it?
Just well, slight differences that were impossible on the TV presentation, simply—
Made just in time?
As for things to change, well, it came down to judgment decisions.
That enhances the fun of seeing it twice.
Ne?
Right, right, right.
Really, for what you call the "time this was made," corrections were made all the way up to the deadline,
that's something that you can't avoid doing...
But, I have a bit of familiarity with SHAFT-san,
so this time, I have a long fellowship with Miyamoto-san, even if I don't know what he does, but then...
"This time, aren't the drawings really bad? Ah—"
(lol)
Somehow, it's extremely... to be frank, when we were recording...
"Oh, I wonder what this'll become?" is what it was like.
(lol)
There was certainly passion, though.
For battle scenes and such, it was often a little bit like "...Mm?"
Like "What kind of feeling does this fight hold?"
But then seeing it on air, is like "Eh? The thing in that state came this far?"
"Eh? Is this okay? No one died doing this?"
Right, like their feet really moved that much?
That's right, isn't it...
That was surprising, but... what if Miyamoto-san was cracking his whip?
(lol)
"Everyone get to work!"
No, I–I didn't do such a thing, though...
Well, for making the action scenes vigorous, that was Nozomu-san's, um... amazing... right, he died.
阿部望(Abe Nozomu) - Action Director
(lol)
He died every time a cut's location was changed.
"Ah, here that person will die... ah, here, that other person will."
آسف ولكن ليس لدي أي فكرة
I see!
It's like SHAFT is full of mahou shoujo.
They really persevered hard to create this sort of version, didn't they?
Congratulations! *clapclapclap*
(lol)
For us, during the after recording stages, when we finished all of our work, we would entrust everything else to the people who draw.
What sort of cut will the art become? There was still molding of the cuts going on, and a lot of, um, unifying/combining of drawings...
Well, it was a lot of mutual trust, so it's like "I'll leave the rest to you"...
For Homura that was especially true...
There were a lot of drawings that were just "...", and in some drawings she was not present at all...
I thought if the drawings were going to make it for on-air time, they'd have to improve by degrees,
when I saw them on air I understood the level of completeness they had achieved, so saying "I leave it to you" was all right...
Well, this is a different question, but...
After you heard our recordings of lines, did the drawings change?
For example, "Change the movement here," or "Do this more like this."
There was a lot like that. Um...
In a normal piece of work, you don't really know how that will end up...
Normally, more is completed before you do voice-overs.
Yes.
Then...
In the case of SHAFT-san, there might be a lot that's sort of like a blank white board.
(lol) yes, yes.
People do the voice-overs on that sort of thing.
Then, when we heard all of those voices - artists, animators, and really just everyone...
Yes.
there were plenty of situations where we changed things based on the voicing.
I see! So, for this too, then?
Uwaaaah!
Yes, especially for Madoka, we weren't making drawings in time (lol), so things were changed.
I see!
I see...
Ahhhhh.
Amazing.
Somehow, for us this time, the "temperature" of a conversation has a gigantic importance.
Mm!
Ahhh, that's right.
When reading the script at home, there's obviously a big impact...
But really, especially for Homura and Madoka, and also for the scene right after this,
That's right...
when you hear the talking acted out, they change a lot.
Mm, mm!
I love the scene right here, too.
Hahhhh.
Having this kind of conversation with Mama!
Right?
There's really a lot of conversations where the temperature changes if you hear people actually talking...
Ne?
Mm. It's kind of nice, isn't it?
Perhaps they might not move around very much, but it still really moves my heart by a staggering amount...
That's why I believe that doing facial expressions would be extremely hard.
Right?
You need both voice and art, don't you? A mysterious mix.
And then, the characters are extremely cute,
Right, right, right.
so doing this kind of scene with these kinds of facial expressions must be extremely hard, I think.
Ne?
I can really feel it, though.
That's right, actually, there are many times when that makes things easier...
Well, if there's nothing to go off of and you just draw an impression—
or well, if artists are simply told an impression, then seiyuu-san talk based on that...
More than anyone else, if it's Seiyuu-san who gives guidance to a picture, then drawing becomes easier.
Ehhh, really?
HWAAU, Amazing.
That's one plus of drawing wherever.
Yes, yes, yes.
It helps the situation of arranging, too.
But when that's done, a better thing can be made, huh?
Ah, that's right, umm... yes.
This really has that, when I saw it on air, I was extremely thankful.
That's right!
"Ah I see, it turned into such a display..."
That's why, um...
This could be a presumptuous way of thinking, but...
Probably, after seeing the facial expressions added to scenes and hearing the voicing on air, we truly felt it as well. Mm.
Right?
Ah, I'm really thankful for that.
Okay... a bit of a question, then.
Okay.
What charas do you like?
(lol)
Ah, right... I like QB.
THERE IT IS!
There it is!
There it is...
QB-senpai...
Beh-san, is it?
Beh-san...
Right, what do you like about him?
Well, he's extremely goal oriented. He seems like he completely follows schedule.
(lol) That's right, he's the one eliminating everyone.
If you're doing work with him, girls will properly get their job done.
That's right, isn't it?
But you'll have to permit having a sort of evil boss.
But ysdfsdfsdfll have to permit it, I think.having a sort of evil b.
"That's why humans are no good."
It's all right.
Right, right.
"Everyone's keeping busy, right?"
(lol)
That's...
That's right...
The concept this time is a bit unique, isn't it?
Ne~
Hohhh.
Right.
We're still at the halfway point now, so...
mm, so I can't really say, but...
But even at this stage, Madoka still hasn't become a mahou shoujo, right?
Even though it's halfway through.
Yes.
Even though it's "Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika."
-Even though. it's "Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika."
(lol)
Somehow, umm, I think this is a really new approach...
Somehow, umm, I think this is a r  (lol) new approach...
(lol) When will she become a mahou shoujo?
Right, right, right.
Everyone thinks that.
"Huh? I thought it was in the title..."
The opening shows her transformed form every time.
That's right, isn't it?
That's right!
Like "Is that okay?"
(lol) It's a lie!
(lol)
In previous commentary, the seiyuu do say that there are a lot of characters for auditions multiple times. That is because they were able to choose from a large list themselves. The show overall doesn't have that many.
You know, there are very few characters, aren't there?
In recent anime, there are relatively many characters, and you have to constantly depict them, right?
Mm, mm.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
So in doing that, really, to stay aware of all the characters,
and to get a sense of "unity" across the cast... is actually fairly difficult, I think.
But if you see the same members every week,
the people who create them can "bundle them up" into a team, each of which has a proper foundation...
So how do you do that?
And then how do you how do you get the compilation editing done on time!? (lol)
بأعقاب ما هي هذه الكلمات على محمل الجد
Then, the people who do that, don't really get to watch(QC) until the last moments, right?
At that time, are there are moments like "HUH?", or anything like that?
Well, basically, a series director-san and producer-san have a conversation...
Well, the director and producer may also have a bit of a conversation...
Um, a conversation like "Let's do it like this," or "I want to do this in this method."
Are there any times where it's just like "Ah, crap!"?
Times like that, um... well, actually I feel that there aren't very many, you know.
Amazing!
Ahhh.
Teamwork.
Mm.
Right.
Well, each—Right, each and every cut's position was decided by me at one point.
Ahh.
When watching tha—
I see! Right!
Isn't that like an intense editor(/compiler)?
That's righ—
Doesn't it take forever?
It's a pain.
Then Miyamoto-san is the one with the most hardship!
It's like something that never ends!
Constantly until the end!
Constantly!
(lol)
But then it continues with a different piece of work constantly!
Ne?
(lol)
There's never a time when you're actually done...
That's right, the end will never come, though.
That's right, isn't it...
Are there any times when you do 2 scripts at once?
The basics would be 5 scripts simultaneously—
WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA Wowowowow
Whoa, amazing!
That's definitely work...
(lol)
Amazing...
Hahhh...
That's like reading 5 novels together!
(lol)
Amazing!
That's absolutely impossible, especially if there's a lot of katakana, that's absolutely impossible!
Ne?
そんなの絶対おかしいよ(sonna no zettai okashii yo) - That sort of thing is definitely strange.
This is episode 6's title. Actually the title is "Konna no (this sort of)" instead of "Sonna no(that sort of)."
Anyway, very similar to the "wake ga wakaranai nai yo" line that Urobuchi-san references in episode 4's commentary, this line also became famous in the JP net community as a sort of joke/meme.
That sort of thing is definitely strange!
Ah, right!
I wonder if it's no good to talk about the "Grief Seed" problem at this point...
Right!
Ah, mm.
Umm, what episode is that?
It's episode six, you know...
It's -episode six!, you know...
Episode six is this time!
At this point...
We already passed that scene, right?
That's right.
Umm, in this episode "Grief Seed" and "Soul Gem" had a—
Yes!
(lol)
Right.
had a, had a, had a...
Umm, the lengthy chat between Sayaka and QB earlier...
The very first scene where they talk, but...
It was like they're interchangeable items (lol)
The scene where they talk on the bed, right? Right, right, mm, mm.
At that part, on air, there was a bit of a mix-up between Grief Seed and Soul Gem.
Mm, that's right, isn't it?
So, umm really, (lol) certain viewers may have said "Ah!"
It's fixed now.
It's fixed!
Yup!
But you know, you can interpret it as either one!
Right!
Wait—I probably shouldn't say that now.
The fact that everyone noticed is actually pretty amazing!
Right! Somehow, I'm very happy that everyone watches with so much passion!
Yes!
Right~!
That's really true, you know. Somehow, this time it's extremel—
Mm.
...
Kyouko!♥
Kyouko-tan.
(lol)
You like her.
Kyouko has come!
Kyouko... !!!
Kyouko is cute.
Moe~♥!
Kyouko~!!
Ever since Kyouko entered the conversations, the dialogue got extremely, umm...
They have an extremely "active" feeling, don't they?
Ahh.
That's true, you know~
Mm!
Umm, Kyouko, you know...
Since she's a character who has obtained stability inside of herself, seeing her gives you a feeling of relief.
Right, right, right.
Mmm.
In this kind of world, she's an extremely feverish type of character...
Ne?
In that regard, Sayaka begins to rapidly disappear, so...
Right!
Right.
That's very nice, it gives an uprising feeling.
Ne?
Mm, it's really nice. I really like Ai-chan's play of her, as well.
Right?
Amazing!
Mm.
It's somehow nice, isn't it?
Are there any characters whose impressions on you changed after we began voicing them?
No, not really by a large margin.
Well, there are a very large number of attentive details, like "Ah, so this would be said like this?" though.
Well, as for how I perceived conversations...
"It's fine if QB just continues with a smile, huh?"
Really... he begins to stick one on, huh? Like right around here!
That's right!
"I don't get the problem~"
(lol)
Starting right here!
Right, around here, you know! He's QB-senpai now.
You know, starting from here, Katou Emiri-chan was really always like...
"I am sorry for burdening you with darkness."
Every time, she apologized.
That's right, huh?
But,
right after this, is it? Emiri-chan gradually burdened us with darkness, too.
"It's okay, I'm just burdening you all."
She'd say like, "Humans are no good!"
"I don't get what you guys are saying!"
"I -don't get! what you guys are saying!"
That was her fad during after recording.
When drawings were being done, were QB's finished quickly?
Ah, he was a very helpful character, you know.
Ahhh.
Since his mouth doesn't move.
Ah, it doesn't move, you know.
(lol) Really...
Right...
Ne?
The way he moves around his tail, like here, was enough to make him cute.
What moves around behind him sort of serves as a facial expression.
Yes.
At first, it was a bit fluffy and cute, though...
Even though he moves it around like a cat...
Right, right, right.
In the beginning, he had facial expressions included in his settei - like his mouth would go "Ah!"
Things like there were there, too.
When we first started recording, he did properly gape his mouth.
He gaped his mouth, right.
He'd gape his mouth when there was a disturbance, mm, he doesn't anymore, though.
disturbance, mm.
mou...
The director had those things taken out.
Mm!
Ohhhh.
But that way, it gives a sort of "frightening," mask feeling...
It gives you a feeling of being unable to understand what he's thinking.
That's right...
Ah, somehow, umm—
There it is...
Coming this far, there are really a lot of... what to call them... mm, mysteries!
Mm!
They've gradually built up, I think around this point is max...?
That's right!
Then,
A little bit after this, it's like "Huh? QB...? Huh?" isn't it?
The mysterious times are—
Right, right (lol)
That's something to be wary of...
Well, as you might think, obviously it's something that the writer had thought up.
Mm...
Mm.
Well, in the first stages you were supposed to have disbelief regarding it, though...
Ohh, amazing isn't it...?
Ne?
You know, for us too, every time... since this is an original... and we were always given the script at the last moment before acting...
Ah—sorry! Sorry!
I didn't mean that in a "Why didn't we get it earlier?" type of meaning... But you know,
we didn't know what was going to happen afterward.
Ne? Right.
It constantly stayed on my mind...
Every time, we all had a meeting like "What's going to happen next!?"
Starting from episode one, you know!
Ah, this cut...
That's right, another painful scene.
That's right, huh.
No, but you see... it's always painful.
(lol)
More than you can imagine. (lol)
Th–Th–That's right, it's more painful than you can imagine!
Basically, every time, it's more than you imagined.
Ah, Homura-chan really kept at it, though...
Right.
That's right!
Homura was, umm... really running while giving it her all, you know!
Concentrate on running! Running!
SUPER tired!
That's how it is!
And she was perspiring!
That's right!
That's right, in the very first test recording, I did a "*PANT*PANT*PANT*"
"Let's just stop that."
Th—
That might be a little bit uncool.
It's still episode six, so there's the "cool and calm" Homura-chan, you know.
Right, right, right.
Maybe around, um... episode eight, you know? That might change.
Ne?
Then, we're done with half the series now!
That's right, ne~
From your viewpoint, Miyamoto-san... with this work, what do you...
For example, seeing it up to this point, what part piques your interest the most?
That's right, well...
Well, this is my impression when watching too, but... it gives an impression like "This is an anime full of iniquity, huh?"
Well, Madoka does quite a bit. She thinks, cries... then, she amasses many wounds, and in the end,
the way she thinks of herself is degenerating.
Well, uhh...
Then uhh, I don't want to talk on the behalf of the animator-sans too much, but umm...
they'd say "I haven't seen up to here yet, so I kind of don't want to do this."
(lol)
Somehow,
It was troubling, because they hadn't seen it on TV yet.
"No, I'm happy about that... but I kind of want you to do your job, though."
(lol)
Everyone was very passionate about it!
The fact it piqued everyone's interest is amazing, isnt it?
What happens after this is amazing too, I would like to watch while having fun!
Well then, umm...
Ending episode 6, Yuuki Aoi and–Saitou Chiwa, and–Ah, Miyamoto.
Thank you very much!
See you again next time.
See ydou again~ next time.