This is the end!
Homura-chan...
You...?
What the hell did you do!?
I see, you're that rumored irregular one, aren't you?
You're using an unusual technique.
Don't be a hindrance!
Sayaka-chan!
It's all right, she has only fainted.
What's up with you?
Just whose ally are you?
I'm an ally of those who keep calm and an adversary of idiots who cause futile strife.
Which one are you?
Sakura Kyouko.
Wha—
Have we met somewhere?
I wonder about that... who knows?
I can't see what kind of cards you'll play at all, y'know...
For today, I'll back off for you.
That's wise.
You... gave us help?
Just how many times will you make me warn you?
To what extent of a fool are you?
I've already told you quite harshly to not carry any involvement in this, haven't I?
I'm...
If I'm in the company of a fool... then I won't choose my methods.
Homura-chan... why?
Whatever the case, the fact that she has some kind of scheme is certain.
Take sincere care.
Akemi Homura, you couldn't possibly be...
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 6
Something Like This Is Definitely Strange
Miki
With this, you should be all right again for a little while.
Wow, it's pitch black.
That is dangerous now.
A witch may hatch if it absorbs any impurity beyond this.
It's all right, lend it to me.
With this, it's safe now.
You ate it?
This is yet another one of my duties, after all.
Still, for the purpose of purifying your Soul Gem again next time, you have to quickly obtain a new Grief Seed.
Is keeping this thing pure such an important thing to do?
Sakura Kyouko was powerful, right?
If you have an overabundance of Grief Seeds, it enables you to use magic that you'd be otherwise unwilling to by squandering them.
That's Kyouko's forte.
Even so... to do something like sacrifice other people for the sake of Grief Seeds...
A Soul Gem will accumulate impurity if you're putting magical powers to a high level of use.
Sayaka, so long as you're going as far as possible to avoid collecting Grief Seeds,
you should consider your chance of success in a fight with Kyouko as nonexistent.
Somehow, you know...
Even Mami-san didn't have enough Grief Seeds, right?
But, she still fought properly, didn't she?
In the end, is there... a difference in talent or something?
That's certainly a fact.
How devious!
That's unfair!
This just can't be helped.
Above having the characteristics, Kyouko is a veteran.
Conversely, there's a natural who'd surpass Kyouko by talent alone, even with no experience, if she'd just become a magical girl.
Eh? Who's that?
It's Kaname Madoka.
Madoka would?
Is that true?
Yeah.
That's why if you want the battle power to oppose Kyouko by any means necessary,
you might as well try the method of relying on Madoka.
If she were to contract with me...
Uh-uh, no way!
This is my fight, after all.
I can't drag that girl into this.
A request to customers
「When playing, please do  not eat or drink.」
「We will refuse admission to those with goals such as flirting, sales,
or pulling customers away from this location.」
Yo! What's up this time?
I would like to entrust this city to you.
Why did the wind change direction?
Girls like you are more appropriate for being a magical girl.
Miki Sayaka is unsuitable.
Hmph. I had that intention from the beginning though, y'know.
What'll you do about that Sayaka person?
Leave her alone, and she's gonna come rushin' in again.
I would like to finish this as peacefully as possible.
Don't lay your hands on it.
I'll deal with it.
I still haven't heard the most essential part.
What's up with you?
Just what are ya aiming for, exactly?
In two weeks, a Walpurgis Night will come to this city.
Why do you know that?
That's a secret.
In any case, if that thing is defeated, I'll leave this city.
Afterward, you can do as you please.
A Walpurgis Night, is it?
For one person, it'd definitely be tough, but if there's two of us we might be able to win, huh?
Want a bite?
It's no good. Too much time has passed.
We have no way to chase the familiar from last night.
I see.
Hey, Sayaka-chan...
Won't you encounter another situation similar to yesterday's if you continue hunting witches like this?
Well... I guess that'd be natural, wouldn't it?
If that's the case, then shouldn't you try properly talking with that girl from before if you meet her again?
If not, you'll suddenly continue quarreling...
Quarreling, is it?
Did last night's event look like a normal quarrel to you, Madoka?
That was, you know... we were genuinely trying to kill each other.
We were only taking each other lightly in the beginning.
From the halfway point, she and I were seriously trying to put an end to our opponent.
That is... all the worse!
So I'd dare to talk to her?
Don't say idiotic things.
My opponent is a person who uses humans as bait for the sake of getting Grief Seeds, you know?
How do you think we could establish a compromise?
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl for the purpose of beating witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch. She's a magical girl just like you!
I think there's surely a way to get along if you look for it!
The way you do things is different, but your feelings on exterminating witches are the same, right?
The girl from yesterday, and...
then, Homura-chan too!
If only Mami-san had never quarreled with Homura-chan...
That's not how it is!
Madoka, even you saw it, right?
At that time, she... waited for Mami-san to suffer damage, then came to defeat the witch.
Because she wanted a Grief Seed, she watched as Mami-san helplessly died!
That's... not right...
That transfer student, and the Kyouko person from yesterday, are definitely the same!
They think about nothing but their own circumstances!
By now I understand.
Mami-san was the only special one.
All of the other magical girls... are just like those two.
That's...
The familiar last night was a small one, but even so, it'll kill people, right?
That thing's next target could be Madoka's papa or mama.
Or it could even be Takkun, too!
And yet you're fine with that, Madoka?
You'd forgive a person who would leave that alone?
You know, I'm... not just simply fighting witches.
I desired this power so I could protect people important to me.
That's why... if there's a person who's even worse than a witch...
I'll definitely fight.
Even if it's a magical girl.
Sayaka-chan...
Kyubey, say something too...
The only thing I can tell her... is that she's being too reckless.
The current Sayaka has no chance at winning against either Akemi Homura or Sakura Kyouko.
But you know... Sayaka won't let herself listen.
Menu
Time settings
Timer
Automatic
Reheat
Hot Water
Settings
Time settings
Automatic
Menu
Time settings
Automatic
Menu
Time settings
Timer
Automatic
Menu
Time settings
Timer
Reheat
Time settings
Timer
Reheat
Time settings
Timer
Reheat
Time settings
Hot Water
Timer
Time settings
You must be tired
In the fridge,
there is potato salad.
Tomo
Can't sleep?
Yeah... do you have a bit?
It's my friend, you know. She has it difficult.
What she does and says probably isn't ever a mistake...
Yet, when she tries her best to do the right thing, her circumstances steadily get worse.
That happens often.
Even though it's aggravating, you know... piling up righteous deeds doesn't mean you can obtain a happy ending.
Rather, if every single one of us all firmly believes that his or her way is righteous, to the point of becoming stubborn about it,
happiness would be a far-off thing, you know.
Being unable to have happiness, even though you aren't making any mistakes... something like that is awful.
Yeah.
I wonder... what should I do...
It wouldn't come to a clean and pretty conclusion if someone else just thrusts a speech onto them, right?
Do you still want a solution, even if it isn't with a clean and pretty method?
Yeah.
Then you should make mistakes.
Someone should make mistakes for the portion of that overly righteous girl.
Make mistakes?
Something like telling a cunning lie, or running away from a scary thing.
But there are times when you realize that those developed into the correct choice.
If you're truly lost at the end of the line with no other options, you might as well try something like boldly making a mistake.
I wonder if I could get that girl to understand that it was for her benefit?
There will be times when you can't get her to understand, too.
Especially right afterward, you know.
I said it before, right? "It won't be a clean and pretty conclusion."
Between giving up on that girl and having a misunderstanding, which is less objectionable?
Madoka, you grew up to be a good girl.
You don't tell lies or do anything bad.
You always try your best to do the right thing.
You're already a success as a child.
That's why, you know... before becoming an adult, you should properly study how to make mistakes now, too.
Study... you say?
Injuries heal faster while you're young.
If you learn how to fall down skillfully now, it will surely help you stand up much later on.
After becoming an adult, you know... it steadily becomes more difficult to make mistakes.
As the number of things you're carrying on your back increases, you can't afford to be careless.
Hmm...
Isn't that tough?
Being an adult is tough for everyone.
That's why it becomes okay to drink sake.
I sort of want to hurry up and have a cup of osake with you too, Mama.
Quickly become an adult, then!
In spite of the tough portions, being an adult is fun.
Oh, if it's Kamijou-san, he was discharged yesterday.
His rehabilitation results were already favorable, so his schedule was moved up.
I–Is that so...?
Kamijou
You're going home without meeting with him?
When you spent all day today chasing after him, too.
You're...
I already know. It's the boy in this house, right?
I know that he's the reason you formed a contract with Kyubey.
Really now, you used your one and only chance for a miracle on something stupid in the end.
Kamijou
What could someone like you understand!?
The one who doesn't understand is across from me, idiot.
Magic, you know, is absolutely the kind of thing you use for granting your own desires alone.
Nothing decent will come from using it for the sake of other people, y'know.
Tomoe Mami didn't teach you that either?
Kamijou
If you wanna make the guy you fell for a possession, isn't there a more clear-headed method?
Like with that long-awaited magic you got.
What?
March in there right now, and smash that boy's legs and hands till around the point where they'll never be usable again.
Give him a body that can't do anything without you.
If you do, this time for sure that boy will be your possession.
Kamijou
His body and his heart, everything, y'know.
If ya'd feel broken up over it, I'd be fine with taking on the task in your place.
Friendly courtesy between similar magical girls.
No problem, y'know.
I'll absolutely... you alone, I'll absolutely never forgive.
This time, I won't fail to...!
Shall we change our location?
People's eyes will accompany us here.
Someone should make mistakes for the portion of that overly righteous girl.
Even if you say that...
(Madoka.)
(Madoka!)
(Make haste. Sayaka is in danger!)
(Come with me!)
No need for restraint if we're here, y'know.
Shouldn't we do it flashy?
Wait, Sayaka-chan!
M–Madoka!
Don't get in the way!
You have nothing to do with this to begin with, Madoka!
No, something like this is definitely strange!
Hmph, annoying ones have annoying comrades, don't they?
Then, I wonder what that would make your comrade?
Tch.
This is different from our discussion.
I believe I told you not to lay your hands on Miki Sayaka.
Your way of doing things is too lukewarm.
Anyhow, the other side is willing to do it.
If that's the case, I'll be her opponent.
Don't interfere.
Then, I'll wait till I'm done eating this guy.
That's sufficient.
Don't take me lightly!
Sayaka-chan, sorry!
Madoka, what're you doing...?
But if I didn't...
Sayaka-chan?
What you did just now was bad, Madoka.
Of all things, for you to just feel like throwing your friend out like that, there must be something wrong with you!
What... what's going on?
Stop it!
What's the meaning of this, oi...
This girl's dead, isn't she!?
Sayaka-chan?
Hey, Sayaka-chan?
Wake up! Hey... Hey, come on! What's wrong!? Hey!
No way, this is...!
Sayaka-chan!!!
What the hell is happening?
Oi!
This is because you magical girls can only control your bodies within the bounds of a one-hundred-meter radius, you know.
One hundred meters!?
What's that about? What do you mean!?
However, ordinarily these incidents don't occur often, since you're naturally keeping it in your possession while walking about.
What are you saying, Kyubey!?
Save her! Don't let Sayaka-chan die!
Madoka... that isn't Sayaka. It's just a mere empty shell.
Didn't you just throw away Sayaka a minute ago?
Wha–
What...?
If you had the easily breakable body of a normal human, there's no way I could request something like fighting witches.
For you magical girls, there's no choice but to make your original bodies something like external hardware.
The actual substance of your souls is given a much more compact, safe figure, allowing you to perform magical powers efficiently.
It's my duty when concluding a contract with a magical girl, you know.
I pull out your souls, then change them into Soul Gems.
Why, you... such a thing...
Don't screw around! In that case, haven't we become something like zombies!?
It's actually convenient, right?
Even if your heart is torn apart, or if you lose every drop of blood you own,
if you repair that body with magic, you'll quickly be in operating shape again.
Unless your Soul Gem is crushed in the end, you girls are invincible.
Compared to a human body full of weaknesses, isn't that greatly advantageous when fighting?
That's awful... something like that is too much!
You girls are always like this.
When I convey the truth to you, it's always the same reaction.
I don't get the reason.
Why do humans make such a fuss over where their souls are located?
What?
What's going on?
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
You had a desire that you wanted fulfilled, even if it meant accepting a fate of battle, right?
And that unmistakably became reality, didn't it?
Episode 7
Can You Face Your True Feelings?
Can you face your true feelings?
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net