Charm magic.
My apologies.
It's a curse I was born with.
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do about it.
You can blame my birth or the fact that you were born a woman.
Surely you aren't expecting your pretty face to save you from my blade, spear-wielder.
It would be quite the killjoy if it did.
I see.
The anti-magic skill of a Saber-class Servant is no fairy tale.
Very well.
Cutting down a woman softened by my face would only soil my reputation, anyway.
I'm glad my very first opponent is one of mettle.
Oh? So you desire a fair fight.
I consider myself fortunate to encounter such a proud Heroic Spirit.
Well then...
...let us begin.
It begins.
Someone has put up a magic field.
It's probably the Master of the enemy Servant.
We can observe the entire battlefield from up there.
Indeed, that's a perfect vantage point.
But anyone who saw it would think so, too.
Maiya, you approach from the eastern wharf.
I'll take the west.
We'll find points where we can monitor both Saber's battle and that crane.
Understood.
Let's see what you can do, adorable King of Knights.
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Saber is looking out for both spears simultaneously.
She doesn't know which of Lancer's spears is his trump card.
The long spear in his right hand, and the short spear in his left.
Which of those is his Noble Phantasm?
If I can ascertain which, I can make my attack.
If only we knew his true name.
He's definitely a Heroic Spirit skilled in the use of spears.
But that will not suffice.
What's wrong, Saber? You're on the defensive!
He's good.
Curse that sword of hers.
I can't judge my distances without knowing that blade's length.
She must be a master swordsman to be able to repel my strikes like that.
Maiya.
Northeast of Saber and Lancer.
On the roof of that warehouse.
It's Lancer's Master. Can you see him?
Negative. Not from my position.
Okay. I'll take him out.
Assassin?
There's activity at the warehouses at the Mion River mouth.
The first battle has finally begun.
Not the first.
This is technically the second battle, Kirei.
It appears that Saber and Lancer are the combatants.
Can you read the Servants' statuses through Assassin's eyes?
Easily.
Saber's parameters are particularly high.
Most of them appear to be ranked A.
I see.
She is the strongest Servant class, after all.
Saber appears to be a bigger threat than Lancer.
Can you see either Master?
Other than the Servants, there's only one person who isn't concealed.
She's standing behind Saber.
A woman with silver hair.
Well, that means Lancer's Master has the wisdom to remain hidden.
He's no novice.
He understands the rules of the Holy Grail War.
Wait, a silver-haired woman?
Yes. Caucasian.
With silver hair and red eyes.
She almost doesn't look human.
An Einzbern homunculus?
So they created yet another artificial Master.
And I thought Emiya Kiritsugu was the
only pawn Jubstacheit had in store for us.
It appears I was wrong.
That woman is the Einzbern Master, then?
Either way, she'll heavily influence the outcome of the Grail War.
Kirei, keep an eye on her.
Understood.
I shall keep one of them on her at all times.
I can see him.
But shouldn't Assassin be dead?
I knew something was amiss.
Let's see how this plays out for now.
Continue to observe Assassin.
I'll watch Lancer.
I'll attack Assassin and draw his attention, so you can use the chance to take down Lancer's Master.
No, Maiya.
Not when it's Assassin we're dealing with.
We aren't prepared to fight Servants right now.
Understood.
While there is no honor in a battle
fought without an exchange of names,
allow me to offer my regards.
It is impressive for a woman to fight this much without even breaking a sweat.
You need not be so humble, Lancer.
Even without knowing your name, words from such a master of the spear do me honor.
I accept them gratefully.
That's enough fun, Lancer.
Lancer's Master?
Do not allow this battle to drag out.
Saber is a formidable opponent.
Defeat her with all haste.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
Understood, my lord.
So the long spear is his Noble Phantasm.
That's right.
I shall go for the kill now.
Saber, you're still using mana to conceal your blade with wind?
I see.
So you have a reason to hide your sword.
My guess is that the sword reveals your true name.
How unfortunate, Lancer.
You will never know the name of my blade.
I will finish this before then.
We'll see about that.
I shall expose your invisible sword, Saber.
Your cherished sword has been exposed.
The Invisible Air was dispelled?!
What's happening?
That red spear is chipping away at the Invisible Air!
I now know the exact length of your blade.
Now I won't misjudge my distances again!
I still have a way to counter that spear, however.
If I can just take advantage of...
...a brash attack...
Saber!
Thank you, Irisviel.
I'm fine. The healing was effective.
So, you just won't let me win that easily.
But why?
My armor should have easily deflected that strike.
So how did that blade...
The armor itself wasn't pierced.
What's going on here?
The only explanation is that Lancer's blade went through my magically woven armor.
So that's it.
I see the secret of your spear, Lancer.
That red spear cancels mana.
And your armor was created with mana.
You should just surrender if you're relying on it, Saber.
You're as good as naked before my spear.
Don't think that you've won simply by depriving me of my armor.
If I cannot defend against your blade, I only need to cut you down first.
Prepare yourself, Lancer!
So you're going all out.
You're betting everything on one strike.
You're converting the disadvantages of having the
armor to the advantages gained from abandoning it.
What courage. What a bold decision.
I like that.
But it is a foolish mistake in this case, Saber.
We shall see.
You can continue remonstrating after my next attack.
I'm telling you, that's a mistake.
Servants can have more than one Noble Phantasm...
A trap?!
This is bad. Very bad.
Wh-What is?
Lancer just unleashed his finishing move.
He wants to end the battle right there.
And isn't that better for us?
Fool! What are you talking about?
I wanted to keep watching until a few more Masters showed up,
but Saber might be defeated at this rate.
Then it will be too late.
T-Too late?
Wasn't the plan to attack after they've knocked each other out?
It's true that I was hoping other Servants would answer Lancer's challenge.
Isn't it obvious?
It would be faster to fight them all at once than have to find them one by one.
All at once?
Yes.
Rarely does one have the chance to exchange blows with heroes from another age.
And if six of them gathered in one place, I'd get to fight all of them.
Look at Saber and Lancer.
Both are valiant warriors I would love to duel with.
It'd be a pity to let either die.
But isn't that the point?!
You're supposed to kill each other in the Holy Grail War!
To win, but not destroy...
To conquer, but not humiliate...
That is what true conquest is!
We watch no longer!
We shall also participate, boy!
You idiot!
What you're doing is insane!
You can stay here and watch if you don't approve.
I'll go!
Take me, you idiot!
Good! Now that's my Master!
This is bad. He severed a tendon.
I can't move my thumb.
You just won't let me win.
Still, I admire your persistence!
What are you talking so much for, you fool?
You missed the chance to defeat her.
I apologize, my lord.
Irisviel.
Heal me as well.
But I have...
I have, and yet...
I healed you. It should've worked.
Saber, you should already be fully healed!
You did well to realize your armor
was useless before my Gae Dearg.
But it was rash of you to abandon your armor.
Had you not done so, you could've guarded against my Gae Buidhe.
I see.
A cursed spear that inflicts wounds that will not heal.
I should have realized this sooner.
A red spear that negates magic, a cursed yellow spear,
and a mole that enchants women beneath the right eye.
First of the knights of Fianna, Diarmuid of the Radiant Face.
I never dreamed that I would have the honor of facing you.
It's all thanks to the Holy Grail War.
But it is me who is honored here.
No Heroic Spirit summoned by the Holy Grail could ever mistake that golden blade.
To face the legendary King of Knights and land even a single blow...
I must be pretty skilled myself.
Now that we both know each other's names, we can duel honorably, as knights.
Or are you upset that this is happening after you've lost an arm, Saber?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's humiliating that you would be concerned over such a scratch.
Prepare yourself, Saber.
I'll get you this time.
Only if I don't get you first, Lancer.
A chariot?!
Both of you, sheathe your blades.
You are in the presence of a king!
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I am of the Rider class in this Grail War.
Episode 4
Blade of the Demonic Spear
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I can't read its status or anything else about it!
Irisviel, stand back!
That is his Noble Phantasm.
With this Command Spell, I order you...
Believe in your Master!
She has been revived at last!
Nothing will remain of your corpse!
Next Episode
Howl of a Mad Beast