Good morning, Yuuji.
The weather's beautiful today.
Do you want breakfast?
Yuuji...
Do you want to sleep for a while longer?
Shouko, pass me my cell phone.
Hello, is this the police?
There's someone trespassing on my property.
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Yuuji, what is this?
Sweat
I-I don't know.
I've never seen that before.
It was covered with a textbook cover and hidden under a secret compartment in the third drawer.
Hello? Can you hear me? Hello?
Sorry, my bad...
I shall forgive you if you burn it.
Wait, that doesn't sound right.
Fine, I won't forgive you even if you burn it.
Then does it even matter which one I pick!?
And what the hell are you even doing here this early?
This.
That's a premium ticket to Kisaragi Grand Park...
Shouko Vision
Yuuji Vision
Why do you have one of those...?
A kind soul gave it to me.
The only person I know who has one of those things is Akihisa.
They're holding a special mock-wedding event.
Akihisa Yoshii
Unknown Caller ID
Yo, who am I speaking to?
I'm going to kill your ass.
Uh, who the hell is this?
Akihisa Yoshii
Unknown Caller ID
What? Hello?
We should hurry up and leave, Yuuji.
No way.
You liar.
I don't remember agreeing to this.
You certainly agreed to go out with me if you lost the ESB.
Nope, don't remember that either.
All right, pick your poison.
You swore to me that if you broke your promise, we would get married immediately.
Hey, are you sure you're not just making this up?
Seventh Period
Me and Shouko and Kisaragi Grand Park
Akihisa, you bastard...
You are so going to regret thi-
Couples are supposed to lock arms.
You're the only person I know who would do that just to prevent someone from getting away!
Welcome to Kisaragi Grand Park!
Akihisa Yoshii
Sup, bro. Looks like you're having fun!
Run!
You've got the wrong guy!
Why the hell are you here?
And you too, Hideyoshi! Just what's going on here?
Who are you talking about?
I'm just an employee.
I do not believe we have met before.
If you wanna play dumb...
Hideyoshi Kinoshita
Whoops! I slipped!
Wow, seriously?
Do you have your invitation ticket?
Here.
Awesome! This is a premium ticket! You get to take part in our special event.
Bravo, this is Alpha. Locked on target.
Kouta
Crap, I can't move...
Kouta, shift to wedding stage.
Hideyoshi
You can't move? What's going-
oh! Did you set controller mode to something other than one?
We can't afford to make a mistake.
...Don't tell me you think your tactics against the Psycho Mantis
would work?
Hey, what's with you? Is this supposed to be a movie or something?
Do not worry about it. It is nothing you need to be concerned about.
You were obviously talking about us!
Moving along, let us take a
commemorative photograph.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Shouko!
I guess some habits are hard to break, right, Voyeur?
Yuuji, you pervert.
I won't do it again. Cut me some slack.
We'll continue in bed.
I said I wasn't going to do it again!
I'm not interested in whatever the hell you're wearing down there!
You will take that back.
Say cheese.
Cheese.
We're going to get married.
I can't believe this.
We provide the special effects free of charge.
We'll be hanging this up in the park's photo gallery.
Best wishes
from Kisaragi Grand Park's photo gallery!
Are you fucking crazy?!
Yuuji, are you embarrassed?
I'm not sure why I would be
embarrassed by this, exactly...
Look at that, Ryuuta!
Let's have them take our picture too!
Good idea, Riko.
Hey bros, mind taking a picture for us?
I beg your pardon, but this service is only for customers with a premium ticket.
Come on, it's just a picture.
Aren't we customers too, ya bastard?
I mean, come on. I'm way more suited to be an advertisement than that loser.
Exactly!
Ryuuta is a hundred times more handsome than that dork.
Hold it. Just where are you going?
Those two are speaking ill of you.
Just ignore them.
If you say so...
Spare me the bullshit! Just take our picture!
Very well, if you insist... Please follow me.
Okay, place your hand like this.
And put some force into it.
Owowowow!
Say cheese.
What the hell was that?!
You requested a picture like theirs.
Are you crusin' for a bruisin'?
Oh shit! He's pissed!
You piece of shit! Don't you dare make fun of me!
I can tell this is going to be one hell of a pain.
How the hell did those three sneak in?
Yuuji, are you embarrassed?
I can assure you that no man on Earth
would be embarrassed because of this!
But couples are supposed to lock arms.
Does this even make us look like a couple!?
You two, over there! The two lovebirds!
See? People can tell.
That's just because they're fucked in the head!
Hi, I'm Phi the Fox! Allow me to introduce our most amazing attraction!
Some college chick just hit on Akihisa and is taking him out on a date.
Yoshii?! Where are they?
So you're working here, Himeji.
Hi, I'm Phi the Fox! Allow me to introduce our most amazing attraction!
Fine. If you wanna play dumb, have it your way.
So what are you going to recommend?
I recommend the haunted house over there!
Oh, okay. Shouko, we're not going to the haunted house.
Wait!
Why?!
Isn't it obvious? I'm sure you guys laid a trap for me or something.
Please! Go to the haunted house!
In your dreams.
Hold it, Yuuji!
I'm Noin! I won't let you get away with bullying Phi!
Hey, Akihisa, why do you look so retarded?
How rude! I don't look retarded!
Yuuji, Noin is very clumsy.
I don't care how clumsy they are, foxes don't have their heads on backwards!
Yoshii, your head's on the wrong way around!
Oh crap!
And I was wondering why I couldn't see!
Hurry up and fix it or Sakamoto will find out who we ar-
Do they seriously think I haven't noticed yet?
Oh yeah, Akihisa. What happened to the date with that college chick?
So, Yoshii, I hear you're going on a date with some woman during our very important mission.
Mizuki
Minami
Sending
＀
Mail
What are you talking about, Himeji?
Mizuki
Minami
Incoming
＀
Mail
Minami is on her way.
Please explain everything very thoroughly.
Whoa, hold on! You can't spill blood at an amusement park!
What the hell, Aki?!
Explain yourself.
And you'd better not stretch the truth.
This is all just a mistake...
Now's our chance, Shouko!
Let's head to any attraction except the haunted house.
Shouko?
We're going to the haunted house.
What did Hideyoshi tell you?!
I can hug you as much as I want in the haunted house.
Scary Abandoned Hospital!!
Haunted House
Please sign this before you enter.
Sign?
This is a contract.
You must sign this before entering any attraction that may be dangerous.
What, is it really that bad in there?
Well, I guess that makes it sound more interesting.
Let's see...
Contract.
I, Yuuji Sakamoto, take you, Shouko Kirishima, to have and to hold, from this day forward,
for better, for worse, until death do us part.
You can use this pen.
Here's your stamp.
And here's some ink.
Is it just me? Am I the only one who finds something wrong with this situation?
This is carbon paper, so your stamp will go through to the other side.
We appreciate your concern.
Hell no we don't!
This way, please.
Please look after my bag.
Don't tilt it, please. The contents will spill out.
Certainly.
Okay, please enjoy your terrifying journey!
So they converted an abandoned hospital into a haunted house?
Yeah, this place ain't half bad.
What is this?
This is your voice.
What, is this a remix or something? Or
maybe Hideyoshi is imitating my voice...
Well, whatever it is, it's not exactly terrifying.
I like Himeji more than Shouko
because she has bigger breasts.
Yuuji, is this true?
Now I understand why it's supposed to be terrifying!
Yuuji, prepare yourself.
God damn it! Yeah, this is pretty damn terrifying, all right!
You're not getting away.
No! Don't fall for it! This is a trap!
Good work. Did you enjoy it?
Do you feel like getting married?
How the hell does marriage follow from this shit?
They say that a strong bond will be
formed between a man and a woman
who escape death together.
Yeah, sure. But what if the woman is the reason your life is in danger to begin with!?
Yuuji, it's about time for lunch.
Oh yeah.
I am pretty hungry after all that running around.
Excuse me, customers, but I'd like to announce that we're having a special at the park restaurant today.
Please come and try out our special menu for premium ticket holders.
Special menu?
Please follow me!
Please do.
What's the matter, Shouko?
I'm looking forward to the special menu.
Me too.
That was delicious.
Everything tastes fabulous when I'm with you, Yuuji.
I thank you all for joining us at our special lunch show!
We have here today a high school couple who are about to get married!
WHAT!?
We've prepared a special event with which to congratulate them.
It's called the Kisaragi Grand Park Mock-Wedding Present Quiz!
Shit! They locked me out!
If you can answer all five questions correctly,
you'll be able to participate in our gorgeous wedding ceremony.
If you so desire, you can be
registered immediately, no problem!
Oh, but there is a problem!
Would Mr. Sakamoto and Ms. Shouko please step up to the stage?
No thanks.
Mock-wedding... Must participate...
Calm down, Shouko!
Damn it.
I can't just go along with this.
All right, let us begin!
Wait, duh! I just need to get the questions wrong!
I used to be a child prodigy, so
answering incorrectly is no big deal!
Question number one.
Bring it on! There is nothing that I don't know!
When is is Mr. Sakamoto and Ms. Shouko's wedding anniversary?
What? What the hell kind of question is this?
Here.
Every day is our anniversary.
Correct!
No! I can't handle the shame!
Question number two.
Dammit! I'll just have to bullshit my way out!
Where will their wedding take place?
Miso mackerel!
Correct!
What the hell?
Their wedding will take place in
Kisaragi Grand Park's Phoenix Room,
also known as the "Miso Mackerel!"
That's BS! You just made that up on the spot!
Question number three.
I know what you guys are up to.
I'm going to answer the next one so fucking wrong you won't believe it.
Where did they first meet?
You're mine!
Here.
At their elementary school.
Correct!
I'll just have to answer before he even finishes asking the question!
Question number four.
When did-
I know the-
Correct.
It's useless. I can't compete
with these bastards...
Fin
It's over.
Hey, wait a second.
We're going to get married too,
so why aren't we getting a ceremony like these two?
We're joining in.
Excuse me, this round is still going on...
Can it, slave!
I'm a god-damned-customer!
You hear me!?
I want to participate in the
mock-wedding too! Just saying.
Just saying...
Shut the hell up, you retard!
When we say we're joining in, we're going to join in.
I've got an idea! We'll ask them questions.
If they answer it correctly, they win.
If they don't, we win.
You're out of your minds!
Oh hell yeah!
I can wash my hands of this crap with these idiots' help!
Listen to my question.
What's the capital of Europe!?
Congratulations to Mr. Yuuji Sakamoto and Ms. Shouko!
They've won the Kisaragi Grand Park's mock-wedding event!
Let's proceed to today's main event - the mock-wedding itself!
Please give a warm welcome to our groom!
You guys are so dead.
Let's introduce the groom first.
Actually, never mind. That's a huge pain in the ass, and this isn't a real wedding anyway.
Hey!
Okay, in comes the bride!
She's beautiful.
Yuuji...
Do I look like a bride?
Yeah, you do.
Well, you don't look like a groom, at least.
Yuuji...
What is it?
I'm really happy.
Hey, what's wrong?
This has always been my dream...
Your dream?
It's always been my dream to marry you, ever since I was a little girl...
I wanted to be your bride...
It's a dream that I never thought would come true...
So I'm overjoyed right now.
I'm overjoyed that it's with you, Yuuji...
Shouko, I...
This is boring!
Seriously. I'm about to fall asleep.
No one gives a shit about your soap opera.
Hurry up and get it over with.
We lead busy lives, you know?
We don't have time to listen to your crap. Skip to the important part.
And come on, your dream is to be a bride? Are you twelve?
Honestly, it's pretty creepy.
Oh, I've got it. This is just a big joke, isn't it?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Do you two not have any respect?
Get the hell out of here!
Stop it, Yoshii!
All our efforts will go to waste!
But...
Calm down, Yoshii!
But Kirishima-
Please!
Shouko...
Yoshii, did you find her?
Nope.
Yuuji, where's Kirishima?!
I don't know.
What?
Don't you have any idea where she might be?
If we don't find her...
Sorry, but I'm not interested in this crap.
It's a total pain in the ass.
Anyway, I need to go take a piss.
How could you?
I'm about to burst. See you guys later.
Man, that was so retarded.
Mock-wedding? Give me a break.
My dream is to be your bride.
How was that?
You sounded just like her! Hilarious!
Hey, you two.
You got something to say, kid?
Well, nothing too important.
I JUST WANT YOU TO TAKE YOUR SHIT BACK!
Hey.
You took your time, Shouko.
Why are you...?
I thought you'd come here.
Yuuji.
What?
Do you think my dream is weird?
Shouko, I'll say this now.
Your feelings for me are misplaced.
I got you involved in this because I was an idiot seven years ago.
I was just trying to take responsibility.
You've wasted this much time because of me.
I'm sorry.
Yuuji...
I won't laugh at your dream.
Even though you've got the wrong guy...
I think it's pretty awesome that you can stay faithful to one person for so long.
So take pride in your dream. Don't let anyone tell you it's worthless.
Still, though, you've got the wrong guy.
Well, it was supposed to help you gain experience, after all...
I don't think they'll mind if you take a souvenir or two.
Yuuji...
Oh, and...
Your cooking's great.
Let's go.
I don't want people to get the wrong idea if we're late.
Yuuji!
What is it?
I don't think my feelings are misplaced!
My first kiss had the flavor of strawberry milk.
The sun sets as I push my bike home.
My mind blanks out as I sink into delusion.
Life spins me around and watches me fall.
Every day is a day to remember.
Let's hold hands until we touch the sky.
I get the feeling our future is promising.
Tomorrow will bring the sun and smiles.
Question 8:
How would you say "computer" in Japanese?
Super electric brain!
That sounds powerful.
Next episode: Rampage and Maze and Beings Instrumentality Project.
This will be on your test.