Whenever we pray for someone's happiness, someone else must be cursed in exchange.
Turns out that's how we magical girls work.
I really was an idiot.
Oktavia von Seckendorff
Sayaka!
What the...
Who the hell are you?
What did you do to Sayaka?!
Stand back.
Take my hand.
What?
Just do it.
Is this...
If you let go of my hand,
you'll be frozen in time as well.
So hold on tight.
What the hell's going on?!
Where'd that witch come from?
That is what was once Miki Sayaka.
You saw it happen yourself, did you not?
Are we just gonna run away?
If you don't like it, toss that useless hunk of meat aside and we'll kill it here and now.
Can you do that?
Like hell I can!
You're nothing but a
burden to me right now.
We should withdraw.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 9
There's no way I'd allow that
Sayaka-chan?!
Sayaka-chan, what's wrong?!
Where's her Soul Gem?
Wh-What happened to Sayaka-chan?
Her Soul Gem turned into a Grief Seed, giving birth to a new witch, and was no more.
No... You're lying, right?
It's the truth.
That's the final secret of the Soul Gems.
When these gems darken and cloud over,
we turn into Grief Seeds
.and are reborn as witches.
That is the inescapable fate of all who become magical girls.
That's not true.
It can't be true.
Right?
But... how could that be?
Sayaka-chan just wanted to
.save people from the witches.
She just wanted to fight
for what was right.
That's the reason she
.became a magical girl.
So why...
She just ended up bearing a curse of equal magnitude to her wish.
From now on, she will live to curse as many people as she had saved.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Do you just get off on
acting like you know it all?
How can you stay so calm
at a time like this?
Sayaka was her...
Sayaka was her best friend.
I hope you understand now what it was that you aspired to become.
Now that you've brought her corpse along, you'll need to dispose of it carefully.
If you just dump it somewhere, you'll run into trouble later.
How can you even call yourself human?!
I can't, of course.
And neither can you.
May I come in?
I want to talk to you about something.
So, you're alive after all.
Was it true? What Homura-chan said.
There was nothing wrong
enough to require correction.
So you've been turning us into magical girls just so we'd become witches?
Please don't misunderstand.
We don't do this out of
.ill will toward mankind.
Everything we've done has been to
.extend the lifespan of the universe.
Madoka, do you know the term "entropy"?
To give a simple example,
the amount of energy released by a bonfire
is less than the amount it took
.to grow the wood it's made of.
In short, when energy changes form, some of it gets lost.
As a result, the amount of usable energy in the universe is constantly decreasing.
That's why we searched for a form of energy not bound by the laws of thermodynamics,
and what we discovered was
the energy generated by magical girls.
What... are you?
Our civilization developed technology
that could convert the emotions of sentient lifeforms into energy.
But unfortunately, we ourselves did not possess the capability for emotion.
So we studied various
species across the universe,
and eventually found mankind.
Given your population and reproductive rate,
it's clear that the amount of emotional energy generated by each individual
is greater than the amount expended during its birth and growth.
Your souls are energy sources capable of defying entropy.
And the most effective of all are girls in their second stage of development,
who experience the greatest fluctuations between hope and despair.
At the moment when your Soul Gems flare out and turn into Grief Seeds,
a tremendous amount of energy is produced.
As Incubators, it is our job
to collect that energy.
Are we just disposable
energy sources to you, then?
Are you saying we should just die for you?
Do you have any idea how many
civilizations coexist across the universe,
and how much energy they
consume in a single second?
Eventually, even you humans will be able to leave this planet and join us.
When that day comes,
you wouldn't want to venture out into an empty, desolate universe, right?
In the long run, this arrangement benefits mankind as well.
You can't be serious.
You're telling me that ridiculous reason
is why Mami-san had to die and
.Sayaka-chan had to suffer so much?
That isn't right.
It's just too cruel!
But we ask for and receive your consent for every contract we make.
If anything, we've been very
.accommodating in that respect.
But you do it by deceiving us!
The act of deception in itself
is incomprehensible to us.
Why is it that when humans regret a decision based on a misunderstanding,
they feel resentment
.toward the other party?
I can't even follow what you're saying.
I can't accept it at all.
We have a pretty hard time
understanding your value system too.
Your current population numbers over 6.9 billion and grows by ten every four seconds,
so why do you make such a fuss over the life or death of a few people?
If that's how you think,
then you really are our enemy.
Despite that, I did come here to try and explain our actions to you.
I wanted you to understand
how wonderful your sacrifices are,
but it doesn't look like that'll happen.
Of course not.
Madoka, someday you will
become the greatest of all magical girls,
and then the most terrible of all witches.
When that happens, I'm sure we will gain an unprecedented amount of energy.
So, if you ever feel like dying for the sake of the universe, just let me know.
I'll be waiting.
Why are you so obsessed with
keeping that body fresh?
Is there any way to get her Soul Gem back?
Not that I know of.
So there could be some way
you don't know of?
As magical girls, your existence already defies established logic.
I wouldn't be surprised no matter what
implausible feats you managed to accomplish.
So you're saying it's possible?
No one has ever done it before,
so I don't know how you'd go about it.
Unfortunately, I have no way of advising you on the matter.
I wouldn't need your advice anyway.
As if I'd ever accept help from you.
Yakisoba
Melon
Bread
You Win
You're looking a bit unwell
this morning, Madoka-san.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I just didn't get enough sleep.
Speaking of which, is Sayaka-san absent again today?
I was thinking of going to see her after school,
but I'm not sure if it'd be appropriate.
Things are a little awkward
between us right now.
Hitomi-chan, I—
How can you still go to school after
.everything that happened yesterday?
Madoka-san?
I need to talk to you.
Can you spare a moment?
Hitomi-chan, I'm sorry.
I'm not going to school today either!
Huh? Ma... Madoka-san, wait!
Um, what did you want to talk about?
Do you want to save Miki Sayaka?
Huh? We can save her?
If we couldn't, were you going to just leave her like that?
Sorry, that came out wrong.
This may sound foolish,
but I don't want to give up until we
know for sure that she can't be saved.
She may have turned into a witch,
but she might still be able to
.remember her friends' voices.
If you call out to her, she might regain her memories from when she was human.
If anyone could do it, it'd be you.
Do you think it'll work?
How would I know?
We're doing it because we don't know.
Maybe if we slice that witch in half,
Sayaka's Soul Gem might fall out instead of a Grief Seed.
Wouldn't that be something?
It'd be like one of those stories where love and courage triumph over all.
Come to think of it,
I probably became a magical girl in the first place because I loved stories like that.
I'd totally forgotten about it,
but Sayaka reminded me again.
If you don't wanna come, I won't force you.
It's gonna be pretty dangerous, after all.
I can't promise I'll be able to protect you no matter what.
No, I'll help you.
Please let me help.
I'm Kaname Madoka.
Jeez, you're so gonna cramp my style.
Huh?
I'm Sakura Kyouko. We're a team now.
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
Corn-soup Flavor
Unmai
Bo
O-Okay.
Excuse me.
I don't feel very well. May I
.head to the nurse's office?
Who's the health officer for this class?
Kaname-san is out today.
Well, the class rep should go with—
I wonder if Homura-chan will help us out.
She wouldn't do something like that.
Isn't she your friend?
No.
Well, I guess you could say
we have a common goal.
We just teamed up in order to take down
something neither of us could handle alone.
In a few days, the Walpurgisnacht will come to this city.
Walpurgis?
The mother lode of all witches.
I doubt either of us could beat it on our own.
That's why we teamed up, so to speak.
Well, that's how it is between us.
This is it.
I wonder if it really is Sayaka-chan.
Could it be another witch instead?
The magic patterns are the same as the one from yesterday.
It's definitely her.
I'm going to ask you this one more time.
Are you really sure about this?
I'm kind of used to this already.
I'm always trailing behind others, never useful for anything.
But please, take me with you.
You're one strange girl, aren't you?
Hey, Kyouko-chan?
Yeah?
Am I a coward for always leaving the fighting to others,
and never doing anything myself?
Why would you ever become a magical girl?
Why? Because...
Don't take this lightly.
This isn't a job just anyone can do.
But...
If you get to eat good food every day and live a happy life with your family,
why would you give it all up to become a magical girl on some stupid whim?
There's no way I'd allow that.
I'd kick your ass before anyone else.
The only people who should put their own lives in danger are those who've got no other choice.
Anyone else is just playing around.
It's beyond moronic.
Is that how it is?
Someday, you might end up having to fight for your life whether you want to or not.
You should think about it when that time comes.
Okay...
Kyouko-chan, why did you—
She knows we're here.
Here she comes!
Let's do this like we planned, okay?
Ri-Right...
Sayaka-chan, it's me.
It's Madoka.
Can you hear me?
Do you recognize my voice?
Stay strong.
Keep calling out to her!
Sayaka-chan, stop it.
Please remember.
I know you never wanted to hurt anyone!
You wanted to be a hero,
right, Sayaka-chan?
Please go back to your old self!
Being stubborn will only
get you so far, Sayaka!
Kyouko-chan!
I'm fine.
This is nothing.
Keep calling out... to Sayaka...
Stop it! Stop it!
Sayaka-chan, open your eyes!
So you finally got the chance
to pay me back, huh?
I guess we did try to kill each other at first.
I thought you'd be a wuss.
But no matter how much I beat on you, you always got right back up.
You're mad, aren't you?
You can't accept what's going on, right?
I know how you feel.
Come back to us when you feel better.
Okay?
Sayaka-chan...
Please...
Sayaka!
You said you believed this power could make people happy!
Please, God...
After all I've been through...
I deserve a lucky break,
even if it's just this one time.
Kyouko!
Hey.
Are you...
Take care of her.
I made her go along with my idiocy.
You should never fight with a burden, right?
It's fine. That's the right choice.
Just focus on the one thing you really want to protect and keep it safe 'til the end.
It's funny.
All this time, that's what I thought I was doing.
Go.
I'll take care of her.
Don't worry, Sayaka.
I know you don't want to be alone.
It's okay. I'll be here with you, Sayaka.
Kyouko...
Homura  Akemi
Was there really any chance for
Sakura Kyouko to save Miki Sayaka?
Of course not.
She should have known
that it was impossible.
Why didn't you stop her, then?
I would have stopped her from
needlessly sacrificing herself, of course.
But in this case, getting her out of the picture served an important purpose.
Now you're the only magical girl left to face the Walpurgisnacht.
And it goes without saying that
.there's no way you can win alone.
If this city is to be saved, Madoka has
.no choice but to become a magical girl.
I will never let that happen. I swear it.
Homura  Akemi
sabitsuita kokoro
錆び付いた心、
What does your heart, rusted to brown,
oto mo nai sekai nani wo miteru no
音もない世界、何を見てるの？
see in this world bereft of sounds?
mata ne wo ieru kao wo sagasu yo
またねを言える顔を探すよ
I try to find the courage to say goodbye
sore wo kurikaesu dake
それを繰り返すだけ
Always, never succeeding
kizukeba soko ni wa
気付けばそこには
When I came to
hitorikiri de naku ushiro sugata
ひとりきりで泣く後ろ姿
I saw you from afar, crying all alone
tsurai you na
辛いような、
How painful
sabishii you na basho
寂しいような、場所
and sad it felt there
te wo tsunaideitain da
手を繋いでいたいんだ
I want to link hands with you
nando demo namae wo yobu yo
何度でも名前を呼ぶよ
Call me by my name, again and again
futashika na mirai demo
不確かな未来でも
Whatever the future may hold for us
hanasenai mono omou dake kokoro ga itai yo
離せないもの、思うだけ心が痛いよ
I can't let go, and merely thinking of it pains my heart
koko ni iru yo
ここにいるよ
Here I am
koko ni iru yo
ここにいるよ
Here I am
kaeru basho wa koko da yo
帰る場所はここだよ？
Is this where I belong?
itsu datte kawaranai
いつだって変わらない
The feelings I leave behind
omoi wo nokosu no
思いを残すの
will never falter
Illustrated by   Namaniku ATK (nitro+)
No one will believe the future.
No one can accept the future.
Episode 10
I will never depend on anyone again
I will never depend on anyone again.