What's the matter, Mr. Kogure?
We have hearts too! We have feelings!
I refuse to let evil go unpunished!
I'll make sure you end up in prison!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we can drop
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where rules and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10
xXxTrIsTxXx
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find out fast we’re not alone
Mario only had ten days left in custody
until the public prosecutor would indict him.
Okay, guys.
We're in a race against time.
This plan calls for two teams.
Joe and cabbage, and Turtle and Soldier.
Written statements are the only way
we can improve the prosecutor's impression of him.
Either one will do. Just make it happen.
Soldier and Turtle plotted how to approach
Yoshitaka Kogure, the man Mario assaulted.
Cabbage and Joe made their way to the Shonan Women's College.
"Yokohama District Prosecutors' Office"
In July of 1955, you tenaciously assaulted your homeroom teacher
and left him with injuries that took three months to heal.
Is that correct?
Yes...
Why? Surely you beat him for a reason.
Or are you one of those pieces of scum
who beat people for no reason?!
Stop!
Minakami...
Mario Minakami!
Well?!
I... had no reason...
Apparently, Mario assaulted his teacher to save that Junko Yoshida girl.
Ask her about the incident and have her give a written statement.
That's what happened to him?
We want you to help him.
Me?
We want you to give a signed statement
about what happened that day.
That day...
Mario was forced to use violence
to keep the teacher from assaulting you.
That's... what he said?
No.
He's not the kind of man who talks about things like that.
We're only looking into it because we're his friends.  I'm sorry.
Still, why didn't Mario ever say anything about it?
I mean, he helped save someone.
--If he had just said something...
--Cabbage.
maybe they wouldn't have sent him to the reformatory.
Cabbage!
I haven't even told my parents...
St....
Stop...
Stop!
Minakami... Please stop...
Nothing... happened...
Nothing happened at all...!
I wasn't about to be assaulted...
I already had been.
I'm sorry.  I can't give you a written statement.
I'm sorry.
It was after she'd been assaulted.
That's why Mario didn't say anything
and went to the reformatory...
Damn, I can't believe how straight-laced he is...!
But that's exactly why we gotta help him somehow...
I'm going to try asking again.
Cabbage?
It's worth a shot!
It was unforgivable.
Both that filthy teacher and myself,
for not being able to help her...
That horrible incident should never be spoken of.
If that means I have to
spend seven years in prison, so be it.
Oh. I see...
But we haven't given up yet.
Cabbage said he's going to stay and try to convince her.
Yeah.
That just leaves Soldier's team.
Asshole!
I'm never coming back to this shithole!
Yoshitaka Kogure, correct?
We need to talk to you.
What do you want?
What?!
You want me to help that damn brat?!
Mario regrets what happened.
He regrets it?!
I ain't giving any written statement!
You aren't exactly blameless in the incident, though.
Screw you!  He left me seriously hurt!
Seriously hurt, my ass!  You look perfectly fine to me!
What?!
I beg you!
Unless we do something, he'll have to spend years in prison.
Please! Show him some sympathy!
Basically... all I gotta do is sign this!
Yes!
The hell with that. Like I'd really sign anything.
Asshole..!
Stop, Turtle!
I hear Mario let you hit him twice first.
Huh? What're you getting at?
If he gave you two punches, I'll give you three.
Do you really think you can knock me out with such weak punches?
Just so you know, I’m not as soft as Mario is...
If you don't knock me out, you'll get a lot more than just hurt.
Bastard...!
Now, then... One more punch!
Now you'll get it!  I really will kill you!
You bastard! That's not fair!
I see.
The only way you can beat me
is with a weapon, huh, Mr. Kogure?
Bring it on, coward!
Soldier!
Well? Do you give up now, kid?!
Bastard!
Wait, Turtle...
Tell me, Mr. Kogure.
What would happen to you if I filed a police report right now?
Let me remind you that I haven't even laid a single finger on you.
This won't be treated as a simple fight.
Even without your prior offenses,
you'll get two years behind bars.
Prison is hell, you know!
Now, sign it.
I will save Mario, whatever the cost.
If my body isn't enough, then
I'll use a bazooka, a carbine, or whatever it takes!
That's what I'm a soldier for!
Soldier...
I won't let this go to waste.
I leave Soldier in your hands.
Right.
"Prosecutors' Office"
You're a friend of Mario Minakami, right?
Yes! My name is Ryuji Nomoto!
Nomoto?
I have brought a signed, written statement.
Take a sit.
What is this?
It’s clear you threatened the victim into writing this.
No, that's not true!  It's--!
I should've expected a piece of scum's friend to be scum too!
That statement really is...!
Did you really think something that suspicious would be of use?!
Now get the hell out!
We didn't shed our blood in the
war to protect scum like you!
Yes, from society's viewpoint, we might be scum
but we didn't become this way by choice...
My old man died fighting in Manchuria.
My mom suffered in unspeakable
ways to raise her children...
It's all because of the war that you started!
At the very least... can you hear me out..?
A crime is still a crime, no matter how you try to put it.
I refuse to let evil go unpunished.
Mario is not the type of guy who
would use violence for no reason.
The same guy who escaped from
custody without serving his time?!
Do you even know why Mario broke out?
Of course you wouldn't know.
The conditions in that reformatory.
Those hellish times...
Guards beat us like we were punching bags
and the part-time doctor paid them to use the boys as his playthings...
Our dearest friend knew
the truth behind it, so they tried to get rid of him...
Our dear Anchan...!
He put his life on the line for his friends.
He gave us the hope and courage to live!
And they tried to kill him!
That’s why Mario escaped carrying Anchan on his back.
Where is the justice in that?!
Your so-called justice is what killed Anchan in the end!
I refuse to believe such a nonsensical story!
You can investigate it for yourself
to see if it's nonsense or not!
Goodbye.
What are you doing?!
Don’t make me call security.
Please! Help him!
The prosecutor's heart is turned away.
I need to make it face this way!
I’ll do whatever it takes to do that!
Adult society wasn’t the only thing ruined by the war!
So, please, hear me out!
Mario had a real reason for being sent to the reformatory!
What sort of reason?
It was because...
It was because...!
I will tell you why.
It sounds like it was a very difficult predicament.
Minakami sacrificed himself by not saying a word
about me and being sent to the reformatory...
I understand the situation now.
May I ask you something?
Yes?
What made you decide to talk?
That's a good question...
I guess I was just a little envious...
Envious?
I’ve never had any friends willing to go to such lengths for me.
But Minakami has five of them.
five wonderful friends...
Is that... good enough of a reason?
I, too, had an irreplaceable friend.
A friend who was with me for only
three months in Manchuria...
Junko Yoshida.
Thank you for talking with me.
Nomoto... I met your son today.
The son you were so proud of...
Takada.
My sons damn smart.
He’s gonna do great things.
His name’s Ryuji.
Ryuji Nomoto. Remember it!
"Day of indictment"
"Interrogation room"
Normally, your incident would
go to the court as a criminal case.
However, given the fact that the victim has submitted a written
statement and that the accused shows satisfactory regret for his actions,
I hereby make this a summary case.
A Summary?
You're free to go once you've paid your
800 yen fine to the clerk on the on the first floor.
That is all.
Wait! What do you mean?
Pay the fine and you're a free man! Get going!
Bye.
Minakami.
You have some good friends.
Money problems?
Turtle?
If you need a loan, I'm your man!
I'm having a special today! Only 1% interest per day!
What are you doing?!
Go pay and be a free man again.
Everyone's waiting.
Everyone?
Hey!
I brought him!
Man, I wish I could've seen
you begging on your knees, Scam!
Shut up!
Oh, yeah! Mario!
The bar owner asked if you'd
start working there again tomorrow!
Mario?
You idiots...
What am I supposed to do now?
Tell me, Scam.
I owe you guys so much now.
How can I pay you back?
Don't be stupid!
We're friends, aren’t we?!
Okay! Time to celebrate! Let's go drinking, guys!
Anchan...
"You can simply pay back your large debt over the course of your life.
You guys have bonds for life, after all," Mario felt he heard Anchan say.
What could I keep watching over
same ta manazashi
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on running
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it now
a far off distance
Youthful passion. Overflowing feelings.
They each take their next paths.