"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
"Recital ♪15 -Symphony ♪9
D minor, K .125"
Miyuki-san, do you have something
to do at the end of the year?
Oh, Izumi-san.
There's a festival going on,
so I was wondering if you wanted
to come with me, Miyuki-san.
A festival at the end of the year?
That sounds like fun.
Yeah, it's really fun.
Is it like the Snow Festival?
But I will be going to visit
my family in the country...
I seem to remember getting
an invitation like this last summer.
Kagami-san...
Translating Konata's words,
you're wanted as someone to
help her buy stuff at Comiket.
When I went last summer, I was
really surprised by everything.
I'm not lying. A festival is a festival.
Going all alone is tough,
and no fun at all.
"Let's Go to the Festival"
Hello, Izumi residence.
Oh, Konata?
I'm writing my New Year's
cards right now,
but are you guys in mourning?
I haven't received
a decline notice yet.
We aren't.
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
Well, didn't you take some
bereavement leave this year?
Well...
Oh, yeah. But we're fine now.
Don't tell me you're using such
comic-book methods to...
Shiny happy...
We're right in the middle of
our big clean-up right now.
I see.
Then I'd hate to hold you for
too long, so I'll be going now.
Oh...
Later.
Yeah...
Why is it...
When you have other
tedious stuff to do,
you really want to tidy up,
but when you decide you're
going to be cleaning and start,
it suddenly gets to be tedious...
Konata, take breaks
only in moderation!
Comiket, was it?
"First time attending"
I hear that it's a huge festival,
but it really starts early in the morning!
I'm looking forward to it!
"Second time"
Nobody told you anything about it, did they?
I feel sorry for you.
No, no, you'll get used to it in no time.
"Regular attendee"
Tsukasa, I'll tell you now that
this event will tire you out.
In all sorts of ways.
Are you going to be okay?
Then I'll do my best.
I wonder if she really understands...
People of that nature are starting
to increase in number now!
Yes, the light will soon
turn green over here!
--Sis, this place is rather scary...
--Please make rows of
five, and proceed slowly!
--That's why I told you so.
That's right. I have to explain
your share of the work.
Our share?
Here, take these.
They're your shopping lists.
When we enter, first, we'll split up,
and I want you to visit all the circles
in the order shown on the map.
Kagami and Tsukasa, you take
areas 1 to 3 in East Hall.
I'll go around areas 4 to 6.
But be careful. If you don't walk
the route written down in red ink,
you'll get separated by the lines
for the circles along the walls,
and you might not be able to
move at all from there.
Especially here and here.
If you get caught in the crowd
in these areas,
you'll lose more than thirty minutes.
Why do you have to
take this so seriously?
Don't sweat it.
The circles marked in green are those
that you can visit in the afternoon.
They usually stock up
on tons of copies,
so the danger of them
selling out is very low.
In the morning, concentrate only
on the places marked in red.
S is for new stuff, K is for
previously released stuff.
If you aren't sure, just buy
everything they're selling,
regardless of whether
it's new or reprinted.
Here's your ammunition.
Take this, because it's bad to fiddle
with your wallet during checkout.
The café au lait is to
maintain your sugar levels.
Drink some every thirty minutes.
We'll meet up again at the end
right here, at exactly 13:00.
I'll wait fifteen minutes for you,
but if you don't show up,
I'll go look in the infirmary
for you, so be careful.
That will be all. Questions?
These are the only times
that you really show
an amazing amount of
intellect and passion...
Please don't run!
Climax from the get-go!
We're currently limiting sales of
the new issue to four per person!
We ask for your cooperation!
Um, excuse me... This is A-92, right?
Yes, it is.
Oh, you want one copy of each
new issue? That will be 1000 yen.
Yes, and?
Um, which ones are your new issues?
Here, the new issues are
this one and this one.
They're both 500 yen each.
Oh, thanks for the hard work!
Were the sweets I brought in tasty?
I'm so glad!
Um, can I have three of each?
Yes. Thanks a lot!
Slippery Brigade Leader and
Naughty Captain, right?
That will be 3000 yen!
I'll just have these.
Okay, that's 4500 yen.
Here.
Thank you so much!
Tango down. Proceeding
to the next point.
Um, this is East Hall?
And north should be
this way, so let's see...
Wah... Wait a minute...
Excuse me... I want to go that way!
I've basically covered
all of the big ones...
Let's see, the next circle to go to...
"Spellbound ~captured~"
Just a little bit...
Gauron doing so much to Sousuke...
This is so...
How is it?
It's 500 yen.
Well, um...
It's too stimulating for me!
She's here! It's her!
It's Legendary Girl A!
Calm down!
If you're freaking out,
she'll think something is up!
Yeah, but the places
she buys stuff from...
The strange jinx, where most of them
suddenly grow into popular circles!
It's impossible to ask me
not to be excited about her!
I know that!
That's why we put so much effort
into putting this issue together!
Just for her to buy one!
That's right... It's the end of the year,
yet we took time off work
to do our best.
This year... We'll make sure
that this year...
Can I look?
Oh, go right ahead!
Um, what do you think?
We put lots of effort in drawing
that scene involving the live show.
Hmm... Needs some work.
Thanks a lot!
Don't cry... We'll make sure
that next summer...
Um, excuse me...
Yes, is something wrong?
Do you know where I can find Pu-61?
Pu? Wasn't the Pu section
in East Hall?
Where is East Hall?
This is West Hall.
If you want to go to East Hall,
you need to line up over there,
and go upstairs.
Do you know how long that will take?
Let's see... This time of day,
it should take about an hour.
"Network Busy"
Okay, that's all!
I'm sorry, Kona-chan.
I just got back, finally, from
this place called West Hall...
At this event, you totally get lost if
you get washed away by the crowds...
And I was in line to go to the
bathroom for an entire hour...
Well, I was thinking the
shopping menu I gave you
was too strenuous for
a first-time attendee, anyway.
We can take it easy and look around
together in the afternoon.
She's planning on seeing even more?!
But it's gotten much easier since they
started holding it here in Ariake.
Back when they held it in Harumi Hall,
there were only two
convenience stores in the area.
Harumi Hall?
I think the last one in Harumi Hall
was about twelve years ago.
Wait. How old were you?
About five years old?
Dad took me there.
We always spent two nights in
this place called Hotel Urashima.
My first time was a Summer Comiket,
but back in those days, the second
floor of the New Hall was amazing.
The huge amount of sweat from
the attendees turned into steam,
and a cloud fluffed up
in the air above them...
That's enough.
I don't want to hear it.
It's more convenient in a lot of ways,
now that they're holding it in Ariake.
But, maybe because the event
has gotten so big,
the young attendees nowadays think
like they're customers or something.
It makes me so sad.
In the beginning, it was an event
that everyone made together.
Sorry to interrupt when
you're reminiscing so much,
but I don't get it at all.
"Akira Kogami at Comic Market"
"Apology: Due to sudden illness,
will not be attending today."
There's a place like this too?
We didn't come here in the summer.
Yeah. Though I think all
the good stuff is all sold out.
Really?
Oh, it's Nagato, Nagato!
--The person behind
Naga-mon is selling stuff.
--Thank you so much!
--So who is she, anyway?
--It's a pleasure to meet
you. Please do your best!
--What do you mean, the Haruhi
goods are all sold out?!
Without those Nagato cards, there
was no point coming out here!
--Wow, that's the worst...
--Please calm down. You'll cause
trouble to our other customers...
--Like I was saying earlier...
--Like I care!
--There are more and more
people like that lately.
--This is past the level of selling stuff!
I'm terribly sorry
to inform our customers!
Unfortunately, our limited-edition
goods have already sold out!
Really?!
Really!
Well, coming by this late...
That's...
I'm sorry, but you have to
line up in the morning...
You idiot!
Asia...
What are you...
Doing your best to please
the customers that missed out!
If you've forgotten
that spirit, then what?!
Even so, we're down to
the leftover items here!
Did you say "leftover items"?
Good things come to those who wait!
Unaffected by the fad shows
and cheap moe!
Comiket is the prime opportunity
to see something at its true value!
Right now, after all the
limited-edition goods are gone,
is when the real battle begins for
the corporate booths, is it not?!
Got it, dude...
Then suggest something
to this customer here!
The finest hidden gem
that you can think of!
Something... Isn't there
a weapon somewhere?
How about this?
No! This one over here!
Well, Nagato sells so well,
but this is, you know...
Even Koizumi sells well...
Shut up! This was left over
from three years ago!
The ones for the captain
sold out on the first day, too!
And so, how about this Kyon here?
No, I recommend Sousuke!
I was looking for the
Coco Saikoubi card...
You idiots!
You are...
Mr. Takahashi,
the company president!
"Company"
That's right! I am the company
president, Takahashi!
"President"
I heard all you had to say!
--It's fine that you want to show our
customers a new sense of value!
--That place is always hyper.
--Really?
--However, trying to push unpopular
characters onto them...
--R-Really...
I can't abide such
mean-spirited behavior!
No, both of them are
main characters...
Lucky Star!
Sis, I'm sleepy...
I'm sleepy too.
Helping the family out right after
coming back from Ariake...
How can they have an event
like that right on New Year's Eve?
Kagami, Tsukasa, Happy New Year!
Kona-chan, Happy New Year!
You're full of spirit, as busy
as it was this morning.
As cold as it is, I thought
you might not bother coming.
Well, you have a point...
But since the sum of the year
rests on New Year's Day,
that first shrine visit helps you
gather strength for the coming year.
Oh, that's admirable of you.
No, that's what Dad said.
Hello!
I suddenly have a weird feeling...
The shrine maiden outfit
is a nice change!
Yup, yup.
Stuff like this, stuff like that.
I'm done praying.
Okay, good job.
Tsukasa, did you guys
pray and stuff already?
Come to think of it, Sis,
weren't you feverishly praying
for something earlier...
You id--You don't need
to mention those things!
I wasn't that feverish about it.
I just thought that
it would be nice if this year,
I could be in the same class as
you and Miyuki for once, Tsukasa.
Really?
Sis, what about Kona-chan?
Kagami, you actually
have a pretty cute side.
Shut up!
I didn't say anything because
I knew you'd tease me that way!
That resistance is just so...
What's wrong with that?!
Sis, you've always been the
only one in a different class...
I wonder if Miss Kuroi
doesn't like me...
I'll pray so that I can be in
the same class as you too, Sis.
Tsukasa!
No, no, Kagami needs to be
in a different class as us.
Why?!
I mean, we can borrow stuff
when we forget,
and we won't get caught
even if we copy her homework,
and with Kagami in the class,
my score ranking will drop!
Then you can be all alone
in a different class.
Not here!
The other day, Sebastian...
Schoolgirls are so great...
Would you like to buy
fortunes again this year?
Good idea, since we're out here.
"Unlucky" "Great blessings"
Looking good from the beginning
of the new year.
Really! I saw something
really nice too!
This year is looking to be a great year!
It's all right.
If it's the worst right now,
the only way for your
fortunes to go is up.
I'm sure good things will happen!
Yeah. How to put it... I guess
it's all in how you say it.
Thanks.
If that's the case, why don't you
tie it to a branch to lift the curse?
Yeah. I'll do that.
Wow, tons of them.
Whoa, over here too!
Here we go.
Is this what you call being unlucky?
I think so...
Whether or not good things happen,
in the end, all depends on yourself.
A fortune is nothing more
than a test of luck.
That may be true...
But that's not something someone
involved in selling them should say.
Might as well try to
get all the fortunes
from "Great Blessings" down to
"Terribly Unlucky"...
Are they trading cards?!
Maybe there are secret ones too!
Secret paper fortunes?!
What kind of fortune would that be?
Like "Ultra Super Unlucky"
or something.
Wait, an even worse one?!
I don't want one of those!
That's something where, you know,
collecting them all
gets you a special item.
No, there's nothing like that.
By the way, I was thinking,
as I was staring at that
giant "kagami" mochi...
Like, this big.
Kagami, is your name
derived from that?
Well, that's not totally wrong.
A "kagami" mochi is round,
like an old-fashioned mirror.
Long ago, mirrors were said
to harbor deities.
So they named me in hopes that I'd
have the blessings of such deities.
Also, the roundness is said to mean
a happy, well-rounded family.
The roots of the name are so mystical,
yet the actual person ended up
growing up to be such a realist!
Would you like one?
But there sure are a lot
of worshippers here!
Well, it is the New Year.
But this is nothing compared
to all the famous places.
I wonder, of all these people,
how many are like my Dad and
here for the shrine maidens?
Is that how you think?!
Most of them aren't like that!
Probably.
"January 1, 2007 (Mon)" "Happy New Year"
"Flight to the Future"
"First Sunrise at Mount Fuji"
Once again, I bid you
a happy New Year,
--and my best regards for this upcoming year.
--Now, as usual, we'll
call out for Do Ooshiba.
--Mr. Do?
--Yes. Best regards.
--Yes! Happy New Year! I'm Do!
Now look at this beautiful scenery!
It's so great! It's so fantastic!
Now look here, such
a pretty flower...
Many many are blooming here...
Dad, want some tea?
Yeah, I'll have some!
Here.
Why, thank you.
Dad, you want to play games?
Dad, you want rice cake soup?
Dad!
"New Year's Allowance"
And so...
I guess he was happy with
how I kept fussing over him
until I got my New Year's allowance.
I'm exhausted!
Well, you know...
You guys really get along well.
And, now that I've safely gotten
my New Year's allowance,
I think I'll head out
to Gamers right now.
I see...
It's really a pain that there's
no stores like that in the suburbs.
We're really strapped for cash
in the first place,
and taking the train costs money.
I wish there was a store
like that in our area.
But all sorts of shops are catering
to online shopping nowadays.
So don't those places have it as well?
You just don't get it.
I mean, you can get the points
just fine through online shopping,
but what's fun is actually
going to the stores yourself
and looking around to see if you
can make an unexpected find...
What's up with that?! You're
totally set on using your money!
And now, the daikon radish
will soon become transparent...
Why are these bags called
meager (pochi) bags?
That comes from a meager
amount (pochitto),
Or just this much (koreppocchi),
And it apparently means
a bag to put loose change in.
I see...
I believe "pochitto"
was in western Japan,
And "koreppocchi" was
how you say it in eastern Japan.
Happy New Year! This is Takara.
Oh, Miyuki-san? Happy New Year!
And anyway, I wanted to hear about
the etymology of "meager bags"...
--Meager bags? If I recall correctly...
--Konata... You can trust
your father every so often...
--It comes from "pochitto" or "koreppocchi",
--At the least, ask around
where I can't see you...
--and apparently it means a
bag to put loose change in.
Now, I guess I'll say my
New Year's greetings
to all of my gaming friends too.
"Yamanka : (T_T)"
"Gatongo: don't cry!"
"Friend Konakona has logged in."
"Gatongo: oh?"
"Konakona: happy new year!"
"Yamanka: oh! Happy
new year! (>w<)b"
"Gatongo: happy (rotf1)"
"Konakona: I'm finally able to log in!
The end of the year was so busy..."
"Friend Nanakon has logged in."
Oh, it's my teacher.
"Konakona: Ma'am, Happy New Year."
"Nanakon: Yo! Happy
New Year! (^w^)/~"
"Konakona: My best regards
for the upcoming year."
"Nanakon: yup yup, best regards
for this coming year! (>w<)b"
All in all, she's always online.
Doesn't she have anything else to do?
No wonder she doesn't
have a boyfriend.
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
M-Morning Luckies!
I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
assistant to Akira-sama!
Times pass by so quickly, and Lucky Channel
is already on episode twelve.
This ocean is hell!
Well, um, as you can see,
Akira-sama was slated to appear
in the main segment
as well as this episode,
but her health deteriorated
right before the filming...
Huh?
Yes, you have a cold, right?
But we left a life-size signboard
of you in its place, Akira-sama,
so if they all watched carefully,
I'm sure they...
Yes? Wait, Akira-sama!
So, as seen here, it seems that
Akira-sama is very tired this time,
so I'd like to end it right about here!
Then, everyone, bye-nee!
"Don't get so conceited"?
Of course I'm not!
What? Me?
"You'll hear the true version
of Take it! The Sailor Suit,
so look forward to it"?
"If you don't watch the next episode,
I'll lecture you in
the name of Mars"?!
Fumoff--
That was pretty lively.
That was fun!
Yes.
Nobody's entered a song.
Considering the order,
you would be up next, right?
This is when you need
to have a song in!
I hadn't decided!
What song should I pick?
I guess I'll look for one too.
Oh, there's a menu here.
Yeah.
You can eat here as well!
That's right.
I sang that song a while ago,
so the flow isn't good.
I should have saved it for later.
What do you mean, flow?
How to put it...
You know how there is one?
How to get yourself wound up
to sing a song and stuff.
I don't get it.
Can I sing this?
They have tambourines here as well.
You use these to liven the place up.
Oh, Yuki-chan, let's try using these, okay?
That sounds great.
All right, this song!
I don't care if it's a hardcore
anime song, just put something in!
I put in a song that would
generally liven up the audience.
Oh!
You know this song, right?
I know!
I think I know it.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Let's see...
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Miyuki here.
When describing something
going at the top of the field,
putting every opponent far behind,
there are times that the term
"no contest" (dantotsu) is used.
It is said that this is
actually an abbreviation of
"by far the top of the line"
(danzen TOP).
The first person to use this term
within written text was apparently,
literally, the man who
won the election
for the governor of Tokyo
with a "no contest."
Next episode: Delicious Day.
"Delicious Day"
Please look forward to it!