Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can, okay?
Well, everyone, it's May.
I was so depressed because I failed last time,
and I was moping about it all by myself.
But I realized something
after Meryl talked to me.
I've just been looking for excuses,
blaming things on somebody else.
My name is May Wong,
an athlete who never gives up.
I will not let anybody get in my way.
Sora, you're not the only one trying
to get to the place where Miss Layla is!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Congratulations!
Thank you...
But I wonder if this is okay?
I think it's okay.
Really?
Leon said you passed, after all.
It means he's acknowledged you.
I wonder...
He did, he did.
Congratulations for being
able to participate in the festival.
Sora, good luck.
Thanks. I'll do my best.
Are you concerned about May?
Because I'm useless...
I understand how you feel,
but just think about the
festival for right now.
He's right, Sora. Your goal is...
Okay, say it with me, everybody:
Victory!
Yeah, that's right.
Only one of us is able to
participate in the festival.
So, in order for me to participate
in the festival, I have to beat May.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hello.
Oh, Kalos.
What? Sora's here, but...
What?! The final test?
What?!
The final test?
"The Two Amazing Demons."
I'll have them prepare
for the final test right away.
Certainly, if she is going to participate
in the festival, she can't sidestep this test.
But if she missteps once,
her career on the stage may end.
Sora can pull through this. I believe that.
The final test...
If I can pass this, that
Phoenix Ticket will be mine.
I mustn't think about May.
It makes me nervous.
I wonder what kind of test it is?
No matter what kind of
test it is, she'll be okey-dokey.
Everyone is cheering for you.
Thank you. I will do my best.
Miss Layla...
Sora, I will ask you one more time.
Do you seriously want to participate in
the Circus Festival no matter what happens?
Yes!
I see. That's fine, then.
Please do your best.
Yes, I will.
I have to pass this test.
No matter how difficult
the maneuver is, I have to.
I have no other alternative.
I'm ready.
Climb up.
What do you want me to do?
Let's see.
I want you to do a layout somersault.
What?
--What did he say?
--What is this about?
What's a layout somersault?
Among the trapeze maneuvers, that's
the most basic among of all the basics.
The performer spins once,
and grabs the catcher's hands.
That's it?
That's right.
All right.
Wait.
Remove the safety net.
What?!
No way! You can't!
When you perform in the festival,
you have neither a safety net nor a lifeline.
That's true, but...
A maneuver as basic as
this should not require a net.
I will create a chance for you to show off.
That's what he said to May.
I will create a perfect chance
for you to show off in today's show.
Will you fail the final
test before you take it?
Please remove the net.
Hurry.
Yes.
A good attitude, Sora.
Show me how ready you are to be a real star.
Let's begin.
I'll jump next time.
Sora...
Jump like you mean it.
Hesitating can be dangerous, Sora.
It's perfect timing. I can do this!
I can't jump.
Sora!
I can't believe this.
When I thought of what
I'd do if he doesn't catch me...
I couldn't jump.
Please let me try one more time.
When you do it for real in the festival,
are you going to ask me
to do it one more time too?
But... Please let me try one more--
Sora!
It's unseemly.
Sorry.
The way it is now, we'll have no
participants in this year's festival.
I know.
I thought Leon Oswald must
want to participate in the festival
in order to wipe out his
shame from three years ago.
But it seems I was wrong.
What is his purpose in staying here?
I heard the rumor that he was looking
for a partner who can match his level.
But all the partners he
had in the past left the stage.
Because he treats them
all like he did May Wong.
But, if they can leave the
stage over something like that,
I think they'd be better off if
they quit and found another career.
Knowing that, and he still invited Sora.
It means Leon must have thought
that Sora could be his partner.
And he thought he could win in the festival.
Even now, Sora is still
trying to follow your footsteps.
In order for her to surpass Layla Hamilton,
she has no other choice
but to win in the festival.
I think that's the starting line.
So you haven't given up on your wish yet.
That's right, you're the one who
was first attracted to Sora's potential
and pressured her into appearing on stage.
I will do anything if I can make money.
Kalos, if you were capable of that,
Kaleido Stage would never wind up in a pinch.
That was meant as a compliment.
I wonder if Sora is all right.
It's impossible to do something like that.
Especially after she saw
what happened to May.
I think we should leave her alone right now.
Okay.
I even endured that special training.
I wasted everything.
I disappointed Miss Layla.
Sora, you're so stupid.
But I don't have the
confidence to pair with Mr. Leon.
What should I do?
You were able to perform even the
legendary great maneuver with Layla.
To think that you can't even
do a basic maneuver with Leon...
I can't trust Leon.
A real star doesn't change her
shine depending on who's there.
Are you saying that I can't be a real star?
I don't know.
But I know for sure that being a real
star is something very distant for you
because of the way you're acting right now.
It's far...
It's far, isn't it?
It is endlessly far away.
Sora!
Yes.
This is bad!
It seems that May hasn't been in
her room since before last night.
What? May?
Sorry, sorry...
Get the ball, Sis!
Hurry, hurry!
Pass, pass!
Watch what you're doing.
Okay...
She looks kinda depressed, huh?
Yeah.
Meryl...
As I thought, you're here.
I found her.
Sora...
Why did you come here?
Did you come here to laugh at me?
No... May, I have something
I want to talk to you about...
Stop it! What could you
have to say to me now?!
Leon chose you. You won.
Be more proud of your victory.
And laugh at me, the one who lost!
May, I won't laugh at...
That's the thing about
you that makes me sick!
As a newcomer, I picked
a fight with you, the top star,
and just when I was feeling like hot stuff,
thinking I grabbed away
the lead role away from you,
in the end I wasn't seen as
anything but a tool to train you...
He injured my shoulder, and I ran away.
Isn't that funny? Laugh at me.
Laugh at me... at least.
No way do I want your sympathy!
No, you're wrong, May.
I couldn't pass Leon's final test.
I'm afraid of Leon.
I was afraid of him, and I couldn't
release my hands from the swing.
What? Then, the partner has not...
No. It hasn't been decided yet.
You didn't come back to the dormitory,
so you didn't know what happened.
So, I thought I had to tell you this.
What exactly am I supposed to do about it?
That is... I don't know.
But I don't know what I should do either.
So, what I want to say is...
well, I'm not sure...
When did you get something like that?
You guys are so hesitant!
You're irritating me so much.
Sora!
Yes.
Did you come all the way here to find
May and tell her something like that?
Well... kind of...
May!
What?
When did you start giving up so easily?
I'm...
If you act like that, you should have
listened to what I said, and kept skating!
You can't do anything?
You don't know what to do?
To me, it looks like you
just don't want to do it.
Easy for you to say,
but I was abandoned by Leon!
You're wrong.
You were injured because
you didn't have the skills.
To think you can't
handle a little ad lib like that.
If you want to blame
something, blame your lack of skills.
Don't act like you're the victim.
The one who abandoned you is you, May!
Yourself!
The May I remember is:
when someone told you "no,"
you used to work so hard
so that the person would never
be able to say "no" to you again.
You never said you couldn't
do something, no matter what!
Ow!
Don't talk to my sis like that!
Sis?
Dammit! You dumb kids!
Come and get us!
Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, I know.
I may still have a chance too.
May...
Thank you, Meryl.
I remembered how bad I am at giving up.
I'll challenge Leon one more time.
It sounds like you've gotten motivated.
Yes. I also have to thank you too, Sora.
Thank you for taking the time
and coming all the way down here
to let me know that you were disqualified.
I'll be his real partner this time.
Aren't you afraid of him?
As if!
Once he sees my new maneuver,
I'm sure Leon will grab my hands this time.
And with that maneuver,
I'm going to participate in the festival!
I'll make the world acknowledge
me like they did Miss Layla!
A new maneuver...
That's right.
And that name is: Demon Spiral!
Demon Spiral... What kind
of maneuver is that?
Obviously I don't know yet.
As for the practice room,
I'm going to use it.
Guys, I'm going back to the dormitory again.
So, can you tell that to Mom and Dad?
Yes!
She's gone back to the sis we know!
Really, she's such trouble.
Well, Sora, what are you going to do?
Will you just stand there and watch her?
No, I don't want to. But...
Did you say you can't trust your partner?
Yes.
You're the same as May.
You're blaming your
lack of skill on your partner.
Before you say this and
that about your partner,
are you doing enough to
earn your partner's trust?
You can't be my partner the way you are now.
I'll reduce your part further tomorrow.
Instead of worrying about that,
improve your skills so that
you're good enough to satisfy me.
That is important,
but I think the Kids' Stage is important too.
You talk pretty, but aren't
you just running away?
Didn't you face Layla
Hamilton with all your might?
Why don't you do the same for this guy?
Because...
If you stay like this,
your path will stay blocked.
You're the only one who
can cut your way through it.
Get it together!
Yes.
Thank you very much.
It's true. I was facing
Miss Layla like a daredevil.
But I don't have the confidence
to act the same with Mr. Leon.
How on Earth can I...
First of all, I don't like his attitude!
That's right!
But, if you ask who else
could play his role...
There is nobody.
That's true.
If we want to have an eye
on winning in the festival...
Why can't Sora do it by herself?
Unfortunately, the rule is
that she has to be in a pair.
Aw...
That guy...
Just watch, I'll do all of his
maneuvers easily in three years.
Go, Rosetta!
Excuse me, but I asked everybody to gather
today because I wanted encourage Sora.
So, if you encourage someone,
could you please encourage Sora?
Oh... That's okay.
I'm more than thankful for
the way all of you care about me.
The rest of this is my own problem. Really...
Then, for Sora, I'll show
you amazing martial arts
which can't even be drawn by human hands!
--No, that's not necessary...
--Um...
Here I go!
You're right! It's amazing!
She's right. This certainly
couldn't be drawn by human hands.
Sora, was it helpful?
Oh, well... kind of...
Since nobody is in, the air is cool.
That's right, the cool space
where I'm alone is where I belong.
After I joined Kaleido Stage I decided that.
In order for someone like me
who just joined Kaleido Stage
to bring down a top star like Sora
even one minute or one second faster,
I could not afford to goof
around with those others.
If they don't like me,
they can just not like me.
If they hate me, they can just hate me.
I'm going to win by all means!
The movement that time...
Because he didn't have both hands on the bar,
that's why he was able to do
that kind of unexpected move.
If I can use that move
and create a new maneuver...
One more time...
I will perfect this maneuver by all means.
I have no other path forward.
In order to surpass Miss Layla,
and also in order to be a true Kaleido Star,
I want to participate in the
Circus Festival no matter what.
I want to! I want to!
But, I still don't know what I should do
even though May already found
something and started running toward it.
Taurus found its way out of the darkness.
However, Sagittarius is
still engulfed in the darkness.
Sora, if you exert yourself
haphazardly, you'll just spin in place.
Then tell me what I'm supposed to do.
Oh, here she is. Sora!
Oh, Rosetta, good morning.
This is no time to be
exchanging laid-back small talk!
May said she's going to challenge Leon again.
What?! She did?
Who knew you'd be the one
to ask me for another challenge.
So, this new maneuver is
supposed to be able to satisfy me?
Of course it will, Leon.
You're the only one who
can catch my Demon Spiral.
If you screw up, I will fall.
If you're the God of Death, I'll be a devil!
Demon Spiral is a challenge
from a devil to the God of Death!
I expect you to accept my challenge.
Here I go.
That's right. This is my duel with fate!
Demon Spiral!
Amazing!
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
When I was at Kaleido Stage,
I don't think I looked at
the audience's faces much.
And so, the Demon Spiral was amazing.
But no, I can't back down like this.
Being bad at giving up
is something I patented!
If it's with him...
All right! I will show them
what I'm like when I'm serious too!
I'll show them! I'll show them!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Angelic Counterattack."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...