This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
I wonder if the others are sleeping all right.
Tomorrow, huh?
This'll really liven up the whole school.
It's gotta work out well.
Let's see, the quizzes start at one...
I'm not so sure about the shogi tournament.
But I definitely need to check out the cooking contest.
It's finally tomorrow!
Tomorrow, huh?
1 day left until the Kan'ya fair
May we advance through these three days with good fortune!
May we have the determination to conquer that mountain!
Hyouka
It's the culture fair!
A Huge Pile of the Stuff
Morning!
Hey! You're up early, Sis.
You've got the culture fair today, right?
Yeah.
I get the feeling you might run into a few issues.
Where did you get that feeling?
Just a hunch.
It's a Classics Club tradition to run into trouble during the culture fair.
I could do without a tradition that's gonna cause me trouble.
The least you could do is give me a good-luck charm, Ms. Senio—
There. You can have that.
Am I supposed to say thanks?
By the way, it's out of ink and the tip is broken.
I don't recall becoming a trash can.
You'll be late.
I know.
I'll drop by if I feel bored enough!
Please don't!
It's the culture fair, Houtarou!
It would seem so.
You never change, do you?
And you still seem to be enjoying yourself.
Of course I am!
The culture fair is the one great constant of all club traditions!
Look, isn't that Mayaka?
She's probably dressed up for the Manga Lab.
From the looks of it, they're also scheduled to work at the festival.
Did you have something on your mind as well?
I'm in the Handicraft Club, after all.
Let me say hi.
Hey, Mayaka.
Good morning.
Those clothes look good on you.
Stop that.
And who are you cosp—
Don't use words like that in front of normal people.
Roger.
Then, who are you dressed as?
Frol.
Frol? Frolbericheri Frol?
Yeah.
I'll put on gloves later.
Nice!
What's in your bag?
This and that.
That sounds suspicious.
So are you gonna be at the Manga Lab the whole time?
Yeah.
I ended up having to work at the counter.
Today, of all days!
Don't worry about stuff like that.
You can't do anything about the past.
This is it! The culture fair!
Yeah.
I heard a lot about it, but this exceeds all my expectations!
Whoa, look at this!
It's so well done!
Yeah.
It's pretty lively.
A little too lively.
You're done?
Yeah, I'm done.
Amazing.
Okay, let's get this done!
I'll part with you here for now.
Going sewing?
Just for a bit.
I'll be right there!
It's awfully quiet.
Yeah.
Get over it.
If you keep dwelling on that,
you'll get Chitanda fixated on it as well as Satoshi.
I know.
Classics Club Anthology
"Hyouka" issue #46
On sale
Good morning, Oreki, Mayaka.
Morning, Chi.
The time is here!
It is.
Let's give it our best shot!
Yeah.
Though will that even help in this case?
The thing is,
there's no guarantee it'll work out even if we try our hardest,
but I can guarantee it won't work out unless we put effort into it!
If you say so.
Okay, I guess I will buy some!
That's not why I said that!
But I'm the one who ordered them...
How many did we plan on originally?
Thirty.
And how many have we got now?
Two hundred.
Galaxy!
Oh no, my Saturn!
I see you made it.
Good morning, Fukube.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay. We haven't started yet.
Guys, I'm so sorry!
It's my fault for not double-checking our order with the printing company.
Everyone makes mistakes.
You're saying that in those clothes?
You shouldn't take all the blame upon yourself.
We're friends, aren't we?
You're saying that in those clothes?
That's true!
As club president, it was my responsibility to check it too.
I just handed over the manuscript and didn't pay any further attention.
It's our collective responsibility as members of the Classics Club.
Yes! I agree!
Okay. I get it.
You finally got it.
Stop saying stuff like that in those clothes!
We have no time until the opening ceremony.
Does anyone have any idea how we could sell most of these?
How much does one cost?
200 yen.
That's quite cheap.
The problem is the Classics Club isn't well-known
and we're cursed with a bad location.
Yeah.
So first off we need to get the word out
and find a better place from which to sell.
Are we going to set up a new stall?
I've been trying to think of ways to lure customers here all this time!
This will turn the tables on them, Oreki!
I wouldn't really go that far.
But would we get permission to do that at this point?
Well...
You're in the council, so tell us.
It'd have to be a special exception,
so you'd need to ask the Student Council president
or our General Affairs president directly.
Who's handling General Affairs at the moment?
You could at least look at the guide, Houtarou.
Look, here.
President:
Tanabe Jirou
First time I've seen that name.
I hoped you'd notice my little trick.
Your what?
What do you think? Subtle, huh?
Just look at the end of the club list, and here's the Classics Club.
I pulled a few strings to get it in there.
This booklet was edited by those of us at General Affairs.
That's amazing!
More like you're abusing your authority.
Don't worry yourself.
If you want to talk to the president, go to the meeting room.
Can't you ask him for us?
Well, I could.
But I'm not really the diplomatic type.
Really?
Chitanda, you should go talk to him.
I'll be there to offer moral support.
Please help us!
I get it. Let's do it.
She doesn't seem all that enthusiastic about this.
But more importantly, I'll promote our club myself!
So that's why you're dressed like that?
That's one reason.
I have a special move!
So you have a new idea we can use?
We should enter the culture fair's events and contests under the club's name!
If we play our cards right, our club could gain fame and fortune!
You're just in this to have fun, aren't you?
That's a wonderful idea!
Right?
Yeah!
You're amazing, Fukube!
Wait a moment.
Just leave it to me!
That's a good idea. Let's make that our main approach.
Chitanda should negotiate for a better selling spot.
Satoshi's in charge of promotion.
Let's stick to that for now.
But... what about you, Oreki?
I'll...
Yes?
...hold the fort.
Well, someone does have to stay here.
That's right.
Let's get going then.
The opening ceremony's about to start.
Yeah.
Well then,
let's stick to the plan,
and sell as many as we can!
The goal is to sell all 200 copies of Hyouka!
Let's go!
Hey-hey-ho!
...Ho.
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
Without further ado,
the 54th Kamiyama High School Culture Fair
has begun!
Whoa!
He jumped!
He spun!
I don't have time for this!
How about trying some calligraphy?
Calligraphy! Calligraphy!
Excuse me?
You can't grow rice
without land
Chitanda Eru
You can take it if you want.
No! I don't have time!
From Tsukuba's peak...
Spring has passed...
Note that though...
Strike at once!
100 Poets Club
Beginners welcome
What do you think?
Wanna try?
For some...
Here, this is yours.
No! I really don't have time!
General Council Office
I finally made it.
Excuse me!
What a wonderful picture.
Um...
Can I help you?
Oh, sorry. I'm looking for the president of the General Council, Tanabe.
That's me.
Ah, I see!
Please give the Classics Club more stall space!
Global act! Global act!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm the Classics Club's president, Chitanda Eru.
And I have a huge favor to ask of to you.
Please give the Classics Club more stall space!
I can't just approve a request out of nowhere like that.
So it's not possible? Thank you.
No, wait!
That's just our general policy.
Please tell me your particular circumstances.
I see! Thank you very much!
Wasn't Fukube supposed to be around for this?
So I prepared to accelerate, and shouted—
Wait wait wait, that's not gonna cut it!
Are you senile or what?
But it works!
No it doesn't!
And that's how it is.
That's definitely a tough one.
I really would like to help,
but all clubs could cite such circumstances.
I can't make an exception just for you.
So it's not possible after all...
I'm sorry.
But...
If you wanted to ask other clubs to offer your anthology for sale,
that'd be perfectly fine with us.
That's a great idea! We'll definitely consider it!
Thank you very much!
Welcome to
the Manga Lab
Good morning!
Morning!
Oh, Ibara.
You made it.
Kawachi, good morning.
Wow, you even brought a sword?
Yeah, though it's just a plastic replica.
You should've done the shoes too.
So she dressed up after all?
She was totally against it to start with.
Should've just listened to Kawachi from the beginning.
Come on, don't put it like that.
Ah, good morning!
Morning, Yuasa.
Good morning, President.
Good morning.
Did you have to spend much on your outfit?
Just the belt.
I see.
Do you have your receipt?
No, don't worry about it.
But more importantly, President,
could we—
Ah...
Never mind.
Okay...
Yeah. Sorry.
It's hard to bring myself to ask if we can sell Hyouka here.
Zeamiz
Hey, who're you dressed as?
Me? Frol.
You know, from "They Were Eleven"?
I've never heard of that one.
It a really old sci-fi manga.
A real classic, in my opinion.
Could you lend it to me next time?
Sure.
What? What are you lending her?
Manga.
All right, girls! Let's do this thing!
Excuse me, are you open?
Welcome!
Everyone! It's our first customer!
Welcome to
the Manga Lab
Classics Club
Anthology
"Hyouka" issue #46
On sale
Target: Sell all 200!
Sure is quiet.
Hooray for shopkeeping.
Let's see, how many confirmed sales do we have?
Given the situation, the club members buy two each.
With those, and the ones for our advisor and the archive,
that's twelve right there.
I guess that counts as selling well.
Hey, have you seen my apple juice?
Nope.
Damn, I'd barely even taken a sip.
What's that paper?
Did something happen?
Damn, I'm sleepy.
Um...
Oh! A punk!
This guy's a punk, right?
Uh, whatcha doing here?
Nothin— I mean, we're selling an anthology.
All of those?
Yeah. Long story.
I'll take one.
A customer!
A customer? Gotta act friendly!
That'll be 200 yen.
I'm not smiling at all.
Thank you very much.
Y-You!
What is it?
Could I take a look at that for a moment?
This?
This is it!
This is great!
Is it now?
Sorry.
I'm in the Fashion Lab.
We're doing a fashion show,
but I forgot to bring something to use as a formal pocket accessory.
This is really wonderful!
You can have it.
Seriously? Can I really?
It's basically trash anyway, so feel free.
Then have this.
That's the winning number for our show,
Fashion Lab
so if you bring that to our changing room,
we'll get you into the spotlight!
Thanks...
This would be more Satoshi's style.
Actually, I think his style is a little beyond me.
So much for that.
But at least I managed to sell a copy.
Oops, I did it again!
Hey, you!
Yes?
Taking keepsake
photos!
Photography Club
How about a picture?
No, this won't do!
I can't do my job if I keep getting sidetracked by anything interesting!
Occult Seekers! We're the Occult Seekers!
Wanna watch UFOs together?
We have ghost photos as well!
The Enterprise is on exhibit!
The launching ceremony starts soon!
Global act!
Want a charm?
Hasn't anyone invented glasses that only let you look straight ahead?
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Quiz Trial
Next time: Dead at Dusk.
Dead at Dusk