Wow, it's more amazing than
Kamisakuramachi-Ginza.
I don't really know too
many details myself,
but there are lots of dangerous
people around.
Be careful.
By the way, I saw it today.
That black bike.
Our first good target in
a while, a teenage girl!
Thank god for that info broker.
Just then, I realized that
my body was shaking.
Right now, is this truly "reality"
you're looking at?
The things you see every day
are the same as always.
Congratulations, everyone,
on passing your examinations.
Japan presently faces many problems:
a declining birthrate and increasing
class stratification.
But when I look at your faces,
I can't help but feel that the future is
still bright, that Japan is still all right.
It makes me feel better.
Of course, today is a special
day for all of you.
But I realize once again, as I stand here,
Don't you find yourself thinking that
today's a day just like any other?
that it's a special day for us teachers, as well.
Ry-Ryuugamine Mikado.
A shy boy who'd just arrived in Tokyo.
Sonoharo Anri.
Nice to meet you all.
A girl who seemed a bit otherworldly.
Kida Masaomi!
I may seem older,
but I'm a fragile little fifteen-year old,
just like the rest of you!
One guy seemed to be enjoying
himself massively.
Kamichika Rio.
Nice to meet you.
A girl with a dark side.
You probably have a lot of people
like this around you.
Harima...
Harima Mika?
Absent...
The kind of scene you see every day.
Late on your first day?
We're in the middle of introductions.
Present yourself, right there.
Yagiri Seiji.
Nice to meet you.
But sometimes, for no apparent reason at all,
you can see the hint of another reality.
Then, Yagiri... Get to your seat.
No.
Huh?
I don't think I'll be able to come
to school for a while.
No, I may never come back.
Huh?
I just came to say that.
Goodbye.
Hey, Yagiri, what do you mean...
That's all.
This is an extremely important
matter to me.
I don't have time to spend
on you people.
Goodbye.
Hey, Yagiri, wait.
Wait!
A crack, suddenly appearing in your peaceful,
everyday life, throws you off guard,
making you rethink things.
And there's a girl here who
may have seen exactly such a crack.
Two days ago, she should have died.
Highly
Unpredictable
She was born in a normal household,
the kind you can find anywhere.
She led a typical life without problems,
without difficulties.
But when she started middle school,
it arrived at her doorstep,
suddenly and without warning.
Nakura's Profile
Nakura
Stuff just sucks.
I want
to disappear.
Nickname :
Nakura
Stuff just sucks.
I want
to disappear.
Location:
Tokyo
What was in it?
A photo.
I guess my dad's having an affair.
He was with another woman.
And there was a letter, like,
"Will you let him get away with this?"
It felt sent by someone
who knew the woman.
Your dad's in the wrong here,
but that guy's a jerk, too.
I didn't know what to do,
so I decided that, for the time
being, I'd just hide it.
Ever since then, all the regular,
everyday moments
of my life took on this awful tone.
Sounds like it was hard.
What's wrong, Rio?
I was only able to put up
with it for six months.
I figured that things would be
better if my mom found out.
If it's hard to talk about,
you don't have to force yourself.
There are things I don't
like talking about, too.
I'm fine.
I want you to know.
But how could you mistake a
cell phone for a remote control?
But nothing changed.
I don't know if my mom
was keeping quiet, or if they had
worked it out away from me.
Dad's dumb jokes, the overly
sweet taste of Mom's stew...
None of it changed at all.
So I figured maybe I'd just disappear...
Lately, that's all I've
been thinking about.
I'm kinda the same.
Not as bad as you, Mazenda-san.
To Nagura-san
Subject:
What happened?
This girl I was dating...
My dad got her pregnant.
That's awful.
But it was my mother who
made me the angriest.
What did she say?
She said it happens all the time,
and since we have to consider our reputation,
not to make it a big deal.
Not a word about how she felt.
I figured, maybe she was putting
the family's reputation above me...
But maybe she was just thinking
about my future and stuff.
I don't think so.
You may be right.
She doesn't care about you, Nakura-san!
She only cares about herself-
Dinner's ready.
OK.
Mazenda-san, would you
like to disappear with me?
Mazenda-san, would you like
to disappear with me?
If we die together,
maybe they'll understand...
Understand what they truly
should have cared about.
Thinking back, it was stupid.
But when she left,
the girl was pretty serious.
She felt a power in Nakura's words.
She wanted to see this person who felt
the same things she felt.
Even if it was a lie,
she had nothing to lose.
Or so she thought.
Yes?
Mazenda-san?
Yes.
Oh, are you Nakura-san?
The minute she saw his face,
she thought it might not be Nakura.
The reason she went with him was that
she thought she couldn't let herself run away.
So even when it happened...
Hey.
Hello.
We clear?
There's no one around at all.
OK, then... Sorry for tricking you!
Surprise, a desire to resist, regret...
All kinds of emotions came over her.
But right before she lost consciousness,
she thought to herself
that this was fate.
And why should she care what
happened to her any longer?
She would just vanish, without anyone
knowing what had happened to her.
But...
But there is someone here.
While she was unconscious,
the world was moving.
It doesn't seem like that hard a job.
Still, be careful.
Without regard to her feelings
or her will...
It's no good. I just can't get
the money together.
I'm not saying I won't pay!
But if anything happens to me,
all I'm saying is Shiki-san, of the
Awakusu, won't be happy-
Mister, I don't have time.
I'm not busy, mind you.
I bet I'm only capable of wasting another
two and a half minutes of my life on you!
And the other guy...
Yo.
I'm sure I don't need to tell a talented
transporter like you how to do your job,
but all you need do is what you're asked.
Just kick 'em around a bit.
Thanks!
The world was moving.
Things were changing, just a bit, from what
the girl had thought was her "fate."
Hey.
What are you?!
Are you OK?
It read, "I've been asked
to take you to a certain place."
I've been asked to take
you to a certain place.
The bike moved silently. Though once in a
while, it made a noise like a horse's neigh.
It felt like it wasn't real.
But what she felt was real.
The girl thought about the person
on the other side of this warmth.
What were they thinking, what did
they know, and how did they live?
When they looked at her,
what did they see?
Someone is waiting for you
on this building's rooftop.
Very well.
This is as far as
my job goes.
Mazenda-san.
Hello.
I'm Nakura.
Are you really Nakura-san?
The Nakura who wants to disappear.
Hi... Were you the one who saved me?
Yes, that was me.
Thank you.
Were you scared?
Yes.
It must have been hard.
Yes. But how did you know?
I'm the one who had them kidnap you.
And I had you rescued, as well.
What do you mean?
You were a bit angry at yourself
for being scared
when you were kidnapped, despite the
fact that you had decided to die.
But had you resisted, that would've denied
the part of you that wanted to die.
So you thought you'd maybe accept
it as fate and give up.
But now that you've been saved,
you find yourself relieved.
I wanted to see that look of yours.
In short,
I wanted to see the look on your face when
someone saw straight through you.
Why?
Let me see...
This will sound a tad philosophical to you,
but if I were to try to explain it,
I just love humans.
Humans are the most interesting
creatures there are.
Oh, when I say I love humans,
that means humans, not you.
Keep that in mind.
It was all a lie?
You understand your position?
Come here.
A lot of people have jumped from here.
Not so many as to call it really famous,
but it's high enough that
you're certain to die.
See that stain down there?
You think you're special, don't you?
You aren't.
Everyone's the same.
No one can live off simple honesty.
You've got a secret or two, right?
You ever think about why it's OK for you
to keep secrets, but not for your parents?
Well, I...
To get straight to the point,
I think everyone laughs at
dumb jokes and eats overly sweet stew,
regardless of if they're having
an affair or know their spouse is.
Look.
Whatever their worries may have been,
now they're just stains.
Stains. Without exception, all of them.
Equal before God...
Want me to let go of you?
See?
Well, I'm just happy
that I got to see your ugly feelings today.
It isn't your problems I'm
really interested in.
It's how you are when you
worry about them.
By the way, you were just as I pegged you.
Really quite boring.
I knew you never intended to die.
See you.
It was fun, Mazenda-san.
She hesitated for a moment.
Would she be able to hurt
him by doing this?
But she thought that maybe she'd just
been waiting for an opportunity.
Maybe those words the man said...
But without her knowledge...
Um...
Why?
Because the world isn't
as bad as you think.
And once again, she does
something extra.
The girl thought of her mom and dad.
Of her dad and his lover,
and her mom and dad...
Each of them had a part to their life
that she didn't know about.
Maybe they weren't as stained with evil, hatred,
and self-interest as she'd thought.
Maybe they weren't obscured by
compromise and weakness.
As she looked for the way home,
she thought of forgiving them.
Ever since then, the world
looked different.
Every single person had
their own emotions,
and every single person
had their own secrets.
She realized that this was normal.
Where you wanna go?
I'll take you wherever, so buy me food.
Let me see... OK, how about a bookstore?
There are a lot of bookstores around
here. What are you going to buy?
They seemed like the kind of
people you'd see anywhere,
Um, some manga to read when I get back.
but she was sure they had
secrets of their own.
Emotions they could never tell anyone.
Wait.
Yagiri-kun, something happened, didn't it?
Leave me alone.
B-But you were absent on the first day...
I said to leave me alone!
Wait!
Um...
Something wrong?
What's with her?
I'm such a lady-killer...
That chick with the glasses
is in love with me.
She's just nervous about the dangerous
and risky life she's about to lead.
Can you try to speak Japanese?
And he, too...
And she, too...
What they're seeing may not be reality.
The girl thought to herself that maybe
she'd also be able to tell someone,
"The world isn't as bad as you think."
I didn't hear you'd turned into
a defender of justice.
I just thought I'd asked
a talented transporter.
Were the others
who jumped
also your fault?
No way. The information broker,
Orihara Izaya, isn't that evil.
I'm not enough of a saint to stop
someone who wants to die, though.
It was fun, talented transporter.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Rampant
Evil
Ikebukuro...
He and she and I and you...
We've come to this town looking for
something, seeking something.
Trying to change something.
Next time:
Rampant Evil.
Want sushi? It's good.
Mister, long time no see.