W-Well, that one wasn't a joke!
Minami really does feel...
W-Well, that wasn't a joke!
We're seriously gonna kill you!
Minami...
She really...
does feel that way.
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Episode 9
Me, Romance, and Diplomacy!
A week after the training camp, the second year boys have returned from suspension.
Yuuji.
Hm?
What is—
Whoa, scary!
Don't dodge.
Of course I'm gonna dodge if you try to headbutt me!
It was a kiss, not a headbutt.
All right, don't move from there.
Put your hands behind your head and slowly explain.
Touching lips, smooching,
something that's only natural for two who have vowed to spend their future together.
Wait, I know all about kissing.
I'm asking why—
When, where, and with whom?
No, I'm saying I know the definition, not that I have experience.
I see. That's fine then.
I thought I'd die.
What brought this on?
Those two were kissing just now.
Seriously?!
Jeez, Akihisa's being an idiot, as always.
He should've known that's what a kiss would get him.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Actually, when you were asleep...
All right!
We've located another heretic!
All right, take him away.
Stop! I didn't do anything!
I'm sorry! Please, stop!
Though I could only kiss your cheek
because you rolled over in your sleep.
Brethren, where are we?
The courtroom where we deliver final judgment!
The heretics will face...
the Iron Hammer of Death!
Good. We now commence the heretic's hearing.
Huh? Yuuji, what are you doing here?
I got dragged in because of you!
Read them their charges.
Defendant, Yoshii Akihisa,
Yoshii Akihisa
will henceforth be referred to as The First Party,
First Party
Yoshii Akihisa
Shimada Minami
and in a similar fashion, Shimada, as Flat Chest.
Flat Chest
First Party
The defendant has been charged with an act of treason for opposing our doctrine.
Early this morning, The First Party performed a coercive act of indecency on Flat Chest,
First Party
Flat Chest
and one of our brethren secured him.
We intend to perform a thorough investigation of the relationship between The First Party and Flat Chest,
First Party
Flat Chest
Investigation
First Party
after which we will outline the proper measures to be taken against The First Party and the watch to place on Flat Chest...
Flat Chest
First Party
Conclusion
State the conclusions only.
First Party
Flat Chest
Conclusion
I'm jealous that they were kissing!
Verdict: death penalty.
Death Penalty
Wait, Akihisa, what's going on?
That's what I'd like to know.
Does anything ring a bell?
When was the last time you met Shimada?
The last night of the training camp, I guess.
Oh, back then.
Minami sneaked in when you were all fast asleep.
And you didn't think that was strange?
I thought for sure that she came to assassinate me.
Then what were you talking about before that?
Let's see...
Shimada Minami
I want to talk to you about something.
Can you come over to my room?
Yoshii Akihisa
I don't really mind.
Why this late at night, though?
Shimada Minami
Why? It's love of course!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
No, never mind.
So what were you talking about?
Something like a confession of love.
Shimada to you?
No... me to Shimada.
That should've totally set bells ringing!
Heretic Yoshii Akihisa, will you accept the sentence and repent for your sins?
The sentence?
Special bungee jump penalty.
What is that, exactly?
I can only give you a hint to save you unnecessary anxiety.
It's like skydiving without a parachute.
It's totally obvious! No bungee?! Will I be doing a bungee jump without the bungee?!
Oh, it's Himeji! Save me, Himeji!
Minami does love Akihisa...
Minami...
Eh, you're still on that?
Yoshii and Shimada made eye contact!
I thought I'd have a chance with Flat Chest!
If he took Shimada on top of Himeji and Kinoshita,
Miss Aki would be the only hope left!
Miss Aki
G-Good morning, Aki.
Y-Yeah, good morning.
Um, can I share your table?
Eh?
Mine broke.
Oh, no choice then.
Go ahead.
Thanks!
Why have you gone all quiet?
Well, aren't we a little close?
There isn't much room, though.
You're right.
Say, Aki, um... I'm not forcing you,
but do you want to have lunch together?
I packed a boxed lunch fo—
What are you doing, Darling?
Sh-Shimizu?!
I won't let this pig get close to you, Darling!
I-I've got no choice! My table broke, after all.
But you don't have to share with this pig!
Grumble grumble grumble
Minami does love Akihisa...
But Mizuki and the rest are hard at work studying.
I don't want to disturb them.
Aki's grades are going to be poor either way.
I feel like you just said something bad about me.
Unforgivable! Your handmade boxed lunch would be wasted on this disgusting pig!
The fries you seasoned with your handmade sauce at four in the morning!
The Salisbury steak made with the ground meat you bought especially for it!
The potato salad made with pesticide-free vegetables!
How do you know about all that?!
Not to mention the rice with the heart on it!
Miharu!
Um, Miharu, I've been putting off saying it, but you need to stop doing things like this.
I mean...
I'm going out with Aki.
Tatami Flip!
So, Miharu, please understand.
I don't want to! We'll get married and call our daughter Mirai, taking the "Mi" from your name!
Wait, Shimizu!
What will you do if you get a son?
"Namihei" would do for a boy!
Never mind all that, we couldn't have a child!
Class is about to begin.
Why are you here, Shimizu? Go back to your own class.
I have important business!
Please overlook me being here!
Important business?
Yes, the very important business of
annihilating all the pigs from this classroom!
You are forbidden from entering this classroom from now on.
That pig!
You're in trouble all the time.
Always the talk of the town.
Don't say that. It isn't really my fault.
Actually, thanks to you, this is
gonna be a real pain in the ass.
Huh?
There's been a movement within Class D to begin an ESB.
It doesn't really matter to us whether Class D
begins an ESB with another class, does it?
Even if they're coming after us?
What?!
But we have the worst facilities in the school!
They won't gain anything.
Don't tell me...
Yes. Shimizu's taking it out on us.
In order to get Shimada off of your table,
she's trying to force us back to using the orange boxes again.
But the whole of Class D won't just blindly follow Shimizu...
We were the main culprits in the group peeping;
all girls consider us their enemies.
Flat Chest
Class D's rep is Hiraga Genji,
but I doubt he can keep Shimizu's jealousy and the girls' thirst for revenge in check.
No way!
Because of last week's suspension, us guys still haven't recovered our points.
We'll be overpowered, even with Himeji on our side.
There's only one other way: to avoid the battle.
Is that really possible?
It's up to you and Shimada.
I want to confirm one thing.
What is it?
Are you and Shimada really going out?
As best as I can remember, probably not.
It's probably because of the mix-up with the texts.
The mix-up?
I see now.
Akihisa aside, you couldn't have
chosen worse timing, Yuuji.
I see.
My bad, Akihisa.
Then, clear that up with Shimada and get your relationship back to normal.
That'll settle down Shimizu as well.
That's...
Voyeur, is one of Shimizu's surveillance bugs here?
I did find one. I removed it, simulating device failure.
What did you want to talk about?
The thing is, that text I sent you
during the training camp...
That was actually... actually a misunderstanding.
Huh?
Well, misunderstanding as in
I sent it to the wrong person.
Who was it for?
Sugawa, I guess.
What?! You were going to confess to Sugawa?!
No way! I thought you were only interested in girls!
No, no, that's not it.
Yoshii Akihisa
Back
Accept
Yoshii, why are you trying so hard to peep?
Why? It's love of course!
Shimada Minami
Compose New SMS
That's awful on so many levels.
Sorry!
Anyway, like I said, I messed up.
I see! I thought something was
off, too. Now it makes sense!
Minami, you were a bit careless too.
Jeez, I don't want to hear that from someone who sends texts to the wrong people!
What are you going to do about my first kiss?!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Saying sorry isn't gonna cut it!
Th-Then...
What is it?
I-It was...
my first too, so we're even. Okay?
Of course it's not!
Eh? I-I see.
That's... Well... I guess since I took yours...
She's okay with it?!
Um, Minami, I want you to answer
me without getting angry.
What is it?
You told Shimizu we were going out, remember?
Does that mean you...
Th-That was...
That was, you know, because Miharu was too clingy. I thought she'd give up if I said I've got a boyfriend!
It seemed like the perfect time.
That's a pretty lame excuse.
She's not being honest.
You should've told me earlier.
I thought you were in love with me there.
O-Of course not!
I thought something was wrong, too.
You're never that sweet—
You're dislocating my arm!
That clears up the misunderstanding.
Once we tell Shimizu this,
everything will be resolved.
Thus a battle with Class D has been avoided.
However...
Question 9
Transliterate the following
phrase into English.
haatofuru rabusutoorii
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
heartful love story
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Although this is used quite
often as a catchphrase for books and
movies, some people mistake the
"heart" part. It's an example of a
familiar word that some find
unexpectedly difficult. On an
unrelated note, it's "ai ni michita
koimonogatari" when translated into
Japanese, and I wish all of you can
spend the days of your youth like in
a "heartful love story".
Shimada Minami's Answer
hurt full rough story
Teacher's Comment
"hurt" means injuries.
"full" means containing much of something.
"rough" means coarse or rude.
"story" means a tale.
You are so wrong that it seems as if you
purposely came up with this answer. I
think you're the only one whose life could
be described as a "hurt full rough story".
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
hurt full rough story
Teacher's Comment
Oh, I did not expect another one.
Listen to this.
The situation has worsened.
Beep
Um, is it true that you have
photos of Akihisa in a sailor suit?
They're 100 yen each. No unauthorized reproduction.
I'll take everything you've g—
Beep
Oops, wrong one.
What was that?! That sounded pretty bad for me!
Shut up, Akihisa. Don't sweat the small stuff.
It's not small stuff!
Why is there a black market for
my photos just like Hideyoshi's?
Stop right there, Akihisa!
In that case, things are even worse for me!
This is the right one.
How's it going in Class F?
They haven't noticed our moves at all.
Good. Let's use this chance to rebuild our points.
We'll declare an ESB against them
immediately if they find out about it.
Wait, I thought Class D wouldn't attack us!
You've got it wrong.
This ain't Class D.
It was the guys from...
Class B.
Damn that sneaky bastard Nemoto!
Why would they start a fight with us?
Nemoto's been in a pretty bad
situation since he lost to us.
He also got other boys to
participate in Operation Peep,
which failed miserably.
He's probably starting to lose authority in Class B.
That's why, to quell the dissatisfaction of his classmates,
Dissatisfaction
Cross-dresser
Enemy
he's going to create a new enemy.
That way he can direct all that dissatisfaction on to us by making us the enemy.
So he's just using us to sure up his own position, huh?
Eh?! If they attacked with our scores as low as they are, our loss would be a dead cert!
Guess we'll just have to create a situation where they can't start an ESB with us.
You can do that?
Yeah. We just need some other class to start one before they do.
Declaration of War
That means...
We're going to make Class D start an ESB with us.
You're kidding! Didn't we just clear things up with Shimizu to avoid a fight with them?
Declaration of War
We'll be given time to replenish
our scores once the battle starts.
Declaration of War
+Time
+Replenish
This way we can take it easy and use the time to build up our scores.
+Time
+Replenish
I see! Class B would hesitate to attack us when we're at full strength.
But Yuuji, as things are, we won't even win against Class D.
I have another plan to deal with that.
Anyway, for now, we'll provoke Class D
into starting a battle with us.
How do we do that?
Just do what you did this morning.
Cling onto Shimada and make Shimizu rage.
Eh?!
No way in hell!
Please!
You won't change my mind!
Asking me to act like this idiot's girlfriend isn't funny!
Shimada! You're the only person who can do this!
We'll go back to using orange boxes if Class B attacks us now!
Himeji's parents will start worrying again if that happens,
Mizuki
Parents
Worried
and this time she might really be transferred out.
Transfer
I need your help as well, Himeji.
Me too?
Yes. Shimada alone won't be convincing enough.
I want you to act green with envy at their relationship.
Is that... too much to ask for?
Um, Minami, Akihisa!
I know you're not thrilled about this, but please!
Mizuki...
I'm sorry for being so selfish,
but I still want to stay at this school.
So please...
I-I got it! I just have to act, right?
Thank you so much!
Now that's decided, let's get started!
Is this the script?
Hmm, let's see...
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly, Aki.
You know, I love you.
I always felt that way too, Minami.
Wait, what's with these lines?!
I can't read this!
I know it's an act, but still, it's just too embarrassing!
Oh well, then let me show you how it's done.
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly, Aki.
You know, I...
I love you, Aki.
I fell for you the moment I laid my eyes on you.
Being "just another friend" has
always been so painful for me.
I've always longed to be more than just friends.
Aki, sorry for being so forward,
but I want you to know that I love you.
Will you go out with me?
And that's how it's done.
I-Incredible.
That made my heart race.
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Will you leave me alone just a while longer?
Huh?
There are some dreams that you
just don't want to wake up from.
Jeez.
Voyeur, put that surveillance bug back on the roof.
Got it.
You three will stage your performance there.
I'm sure Shimizu will listen to the act and think exactly what we want.
The setting will be Shimada and Akihisa having a lovers' rendezvous on the roof.
You two need to go there arm-in-arm.
Arm-in-arm?!
But—
Good luck, and clean up your act.
F-Fine...
I'll send you straight to hell
if you touch anywhere strange.
It's hard to walk when you're holding on to me so tightly.
It's only normal; we're going out together!
But my elbow's touching your... there.
Eh?
Y-You pervert...
Your rib, I mean—
Bear it! I need to keep up the act!
Hey, Minami!
What is it, Aki?
Minami, what do you like about me?
Isn't that obvious?
From the top of your head...
From there to where?
...to your eyebrows.
Oh, my forehead.
What are you two doing?
Mizuki...
You're arm-in-arm, and so close...
It makes it look just like you two...
are going out together!
Huh?
Was there a line like that in the script?
I see! She's ad-libbing!
You're right, Mizuki.
I'm going out with Aki.
Is that really true?
Yes.
Sorry for keeping it from you, Mizuki.
Minami!
So you really do like him?
Sorry for keeping that from you, too.
I knew how you felt about him.
Sorry. You'll never forgive me, will you?
No, I sort of knew already how you felt.
Actually, I'm relieved now that it's out in the open.
So you'll forgive me?
It's not a matter of forgiveness.
I believe everyone's free to choose in love.
That's why I can't hold it against you.
Mizuki...
Thank you.
But...
I won't forgive that kiss you gave him this morning!
It was criminal!
And it was his first kiss!
Well, I got those texts from him,
and it just sort of happened...
Just happened?! Even if God forgives you, I won't!
Isn't that the surveillance bug?!
Minami... you idiot!
Oh no! It's all over if Himeji drops out of character with that thing on!
Himeji!
Wai— Hold it right there, Aki!
What are you doing, Aki?!
Are you choosing her over me?
I'm sorry! I need to do this!
Aki! Stay with me!
I...
Aki, I...
love you.
So that's... how it is.
Calm down, Shimada.
Don't say anything careless—
It's all right.
I'm done with the act.
Aki prefers proper girls like Mizuki anyway.
Himeji.
Akihisa!
Thank you.
I hadn't noticed it.
What's wrong, Himeji?
You don't look well.
You can tell?
Yeah, you look kinda lonely.
Lonely, huh?
That must be the sadness
from having someone you love taken away from you,
even if it was just an act.
Don't worry about it. It was just pretend.
You're right.
It was pretend.
I'd get a little jealous too.
Eh?
That is, if there were some other guy you two fell in love with, even if it was just an act.
Huh?
If that really were to happen,
what would you do, Akihisa?
Eh?
Let's see...
I guess I'd just think as hard as I could.
I guess I'd think real hard about what to do.
You'd... think hard?
Yeah. I'd think hard, in my own way.
And then I'd lay it all bare.
What I meant was who you'd choose...
Eh?
It's nothing! Don't worry about it!
But boy was I surprised!
By what?
It really didn't seem like an act just now!
Don't tell me, you...
Eh?
Eh?!
...have some acting experience?
Oh.
Ah.
Himeji...?
Idiot.
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
shinten shinai yo
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Question 10
Answer the following question.
Give examples of ingredients
that are added to miso soup
as a supplement for the
nutrients that miso lacks.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Green onions
Teacher's Comment
Correct. Other vegetables
that contain vitamin C such
as onions and crown daisies
would also be good answers.
Miso is very good for your
body as it is rich in Vitamin
B and contains soy protein.
On the other hand, it has
high salt content, so be
careful not to consume
too much sodium.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 10: Give examples of ingredients that are added to
miso soup as a supplement for the nutrients that miso lacks.
Vitamin C - Oranges,
Vitamin C - Oranges, hydrochloric acid.
hydrochloric acid
Would that still be food?
Next episode: Me, Romance, and the Art of Love!
Me, Romance, and the Art of Love!
This will be on your test.