kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
being at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
we may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings go deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
at this rate
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
won’t you kiss me? it’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
with our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
Wake up, sis!
Where’d you put those hairpieces you bought?
I need them!
Geez!
Did you seriously wear your glasses to bed again?
I keep telling you the frame will get bent…
Ouch…
My Sister’s the President
I can’t believe you!
Those glasses were like a part of me, y’know?
Sorry, sis…
Haruka told me she knows an eyeglass store owner.
I’ll ask her if they can fix them for you.
Again with this Haruka-san?
You seem to mention her daily.
Especially ever since your started high school.
I mean, it’s not like you’re lovers.
W
h
o
I’m a human-powered stove…
Oh, how lovely. Heat up my cup as well, won’t you?
She’s definitely hiding something.
Something suspicious…
You’re dropping crumbs all over the place!
I know she’s been coming over a lot ever since Yuu’s second year of middle school…
Flashback
You might catch her cold, so maybe some other time.
O-Okay…
That time I caught a cold…
When I got sick
When I went on a
high school trip
…and when I had that high school trip…
Mental Image
Come to think of it, I’ve never once had a look at her face.
The only thing I  have seen are her shoes…
What could you possibly look like, Takayama Haruka?!
What the heck are you doing?!
Afterwards, the staff tried this for themselves.
Sakura Trick
Misato West High School
Ah, our class rep finally returns.
What’d the teacher say?
It seems we gotta elect a member for the ball sports meet committee.
A ball sports meet?
Apparently, since there’s only three first-year classes…
…and the school’s strapped for funds, there won’t be a full sports festival.
For real?! We're not having a sports festival?!
Taian
Bukumetsu
Shakkou
Senshou
This day must be cursed!
First I broke my sister’s glasses, now this?!
Sorry to pour salt on your wound, but…
…you also have a make-up class after school.
Yuu-chan…
Sports… festival…
You wanted a sports festival this  much, Yuu-chan?
A ball sports meet could be just as fun!
But… I can’t do it at a ball sports meet…
Lead a cheer squad.
I agree! What a shame indeed!
Yeah! Yeah!
That reminds me, isn’t Yuu’s sister the student council president?
She said she’d be counting on me to help out her sister’s class.
For real?!
She sure is.
I don’t think I’ve ever seen her in person…
Didn’t you see her give the welcoming speech at the entrance ceremony?
I kinda fell asleep…
What? C’mon, Haruka…
You guys were all watching, right?
Sorry, we dozed off too…
Seriously?!
There you are!
Sonoda! It’s time for your lesson!
Coming!
She’s been stolen.
Yuu-chan…
One got away…
From what?
I’ve got a favor to ask,
would one of you mind being on the committee?
Huh? No way!
That’s it, Harupoppo!
You should take on the role and propose Yuu-chan’s cheer squad idea to the committee.
Ah
Ah, I see!
That’s a great idea!
The teacher might  have also mentioned some extra PE credit for taking the role…
Sign me up!
Me too!
If Kotone’s doing it, then…
Wha-?!
After school
Student Council Meeting Room
It sure was nice  of Yuzu-chan to let me go in her place.
Yeah! We both need to work hard for Yuu-chan’s sake too!
Sure, she let  you go…
First year… class A…
Ball Sports Meet
Committee Members by Class
First Year, Class A
First Year, Class B
Class Representative: Ikeno Kaede
Commitee Member(s): Takayama Haruka, Noda Kotone
Takayama… Haruka?
Could it be  that Haruka?!
Hey, Rina.
Y-Yes?
Where might this Takayama Haruka-san be sitting?
“Takayama-san,” you said?
Over there, I think…
The one with semi-long hair.
If only I had my glasses on…
Who is it? Who could it be?!
Ball Sports Meet Committee Meeting
Secretary
President
Vice-President
I’m Sonoda Mitsuki, your student council president from class 3-C.
Also from class 3-C, I’m your vice president, Sakai Rina.
Class 2-B. I’m your secretary, Otokawa Sumi.
Vice-President
President
Secretary
First off, I’d like to thank you all for volunteering your time.
As you all have heard, we will not be holding a sports festival this year.
That’s Yuu-chan’s big sister…
She seems way more mature than Yuu-chan…
Just being around her is making me nervous.
Kotone-chan… She's trying to cheer me up?
Ooh, shaky, shaky!
shake
She's just messing with me!
Soccer
Basketball
Volleyball
Dodgeball
Softball
Secretary
President
Vice-President
I think we’ve agreed on the events. Is there anything anyone would like to add?
“What about including a cheer squad for the event as well?”
Alright, I can do this!
That would be…
First year, class A.
Thank you.
She looks super angry at me!
I can’t see…
What should I do?!
How dare  you defile the purity of my only little sister.
Uh… I…
Harupoppo, leave it to me.
Just follow my lead.
S-Sure.
President Mitsuki.
President Mitsuki!
Yes?
Would you please…
give your sister…
…to me?
What?!
Sister?
We’re in the middle of discussing the ball sports meet.
Would you please save irrelevant topics for after the meeting?
T-That’s not what I meant!
Whoa… She’s so mad at me!
No… I can’t be afraid!
Fight, Haruppo!
I’ve gotta lighten the mood, and face her with impact!
snap
P-President Mitsuki, how would you like to be cheered on by cute girls?!
Wouldn’t a cheer squad be a perfect fit for the ball sports meet?!
President
Secretary
A cheer squad, huh? It sounds interesting, but…
…not really possible.
Our school has three years left before it’s shut down,
so the city’s not eager to provide funding.
That’s why we’re having this cheaper ball sports meet in the first place.
It’s a shame you current first-years won’t ever get to have a sports festival.
But we simply don’t have the power to change what’s been decided.
But, but, Mitsuki negotiated with the staff for a whole month to see if it was at all possible!
Please acknowledge all the effort she’s put into this!
Alright, meeting adjourned.
Here.
Kotone-chan…
Why’d I even bother joining the committee?
Just so I could embarrass myself like that?
Harupoppo…
There won’t be a sports festival next year, or the year after, either.
And certainly not after we graduate.
If you just give up now, Yuu-chan will never be able to lead a cheer squad.
I know, but I’ve tried everything.
You know…
…when I said I wanted to move in with Shizuku-chan, my parents were against the whole thing.
But… I convinced them.
This’ll be your only chance for these three years.
You don’t want to regret this later, right?
President Mitsuki!
sink!
Wha-What is it with you…?
Um, I…
I really  want there to be a cheering squad!
My friend was so sad that she couldn’t be in one,
so I thought I’d try to make her dream a reality!
What’s with you?
That friend has always helped me ever since middle school…
I want to return the favor for once!
Please let us have a cheer squad!
I won’t let go until you say we can!
What an odd girl… To think she’d go this far for that friend.
…I understand.
I’ll try to negotiate a cheer squad with the school.
Thank you so much!
What might your name be?
Class 1-A, Takayama Haruka.
Taka—?!
What’ll we do?!
S-She’s frozen in place!
P-President Mitsuki?!
Sakura Trick
A Few
Days Later
Is President Mitsuki home?
Yup, but she’s studying for exams right now.
She gets pretty mad if she’s bothered.
What a shame… I even bought an extra matcha cream puff for her…
Matcha?!
I’ll leave hers in the fridge!
Haruka-san?
The strawberry one looks good too! Let’s split it!
Split it! Split it!
I wanna try some!
You leave me no choice.
I think I’ll pass.
You sure? I guess I’ll eat it all then!
So sweet!
This was a limited-time flavor ending today.
Looks like you won’t get to try one until next year.
Ah, but there’s no guarantee it’ll even be out next year… too bad.
Yuu-chan, that hurts!
Haruka.
I heard from Kaede-chan…
…that you’re the reason we’re having a cheer squad.
I know you usually wouldn’t put yourself out there like that.
In fact, you get really shy sometimes…
You make me happy.
Lemme see… what the strawberry one tastes like…
I’ll just have a bit…
I’m gonna melt…
Just like this cream.
It is  sweet.
More…
I wanna melt with Yuu-chan…
This tastes way better…
Now that I can see clearly, I need to see Haruka-san’s face again…
I might not get another chance like this!
Sis
She even had my glasses fixed…
I’ve got to show my gratitude!
Calm down, stay composed…
I wonder what they’re chatting about…
Huh? What’s that sound?!
Hold on… that’s my heartbeat!
Geez. I’m just getting a look at her face.
There's nothing to it.
Yuu, Haruka-san, would you like something to drink?
I’m coming…
… in.
thump
Rising
My Sister’s the President
End
A Promise Made by the Pool
Haruka, I forgot my swimsuit…
Oh?
I was sure I packed it this morning…
Ta-da!
I had a feeling this would happen,
so I brought a spare!
Haruka
Thanks, Haruka!
Yuu
Haruka
What is  this?!
I stayed up late making it!
No thanks, I’ll pass!
But why?
What if I’m seen wearing this…
Yuu
Haruka
…and rumors start spreading?
No worries!
It’ll look cute on you!
That’s not what I’m worried about!
Are you fine with people knowing?!
Yuu
Haruka
Geez, you’re always over-reacting…
How about we switch, then?
We should  be the same size…
Fine, I’ll just rip it off!
No! Stop that!
What’re you doing?!
Here, I’ll do yours too!
Give it here!
No one’s gonna notice!
But if they do,  we can’t go back to the way things are!
That won’t matter!
They’re taking it to a whole new level today…
Anyway, why are we  stuck with cleaning the pool?
At least our class will be the first ones to use the pool.
Huh? When’s that?
Starting tomorrow.
Really?!
Really, really.
Well, no point in complaining!
Okay guys,
let’s make this pool squeaky clean!
Yeah!
I’m serious!
Sakura Trick
Did you really all come to goof off?!
Why not have some fun?
We won’t get a chance like this again.
We’ve got volleyball!
This ain’t a beach…
We can bury each other!
There’s no sand here!
We can sit back and relax!
I told you, we’re not at a beach!
Yuu-chan!
Look over here.
See?
So pretty!
I bet it’ll get bigger if you pinch the hose.
Should I?
Yuzu-chan, I’m sorry!
I’ll have my revenge.
Take this!
Prepare to get soaked…
Take that!
Haruka, cover it up!
It’s see-through!
What’s wrong, Yuu?
See-through!
What’s going on?
Oh, it’s nothing!
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan!
Check this out!
Why’d you reveal it?!
So big…
That’s not what I was showing you…
Take a look…
Right here, see?
I don’t get it.
J-Just forget it! There’s nothing for you guys to see here!
Haruka’s a D-cup?!
No, she’s a C!
L-Look over there!
Whoa, we’ve got another vacation queen here!
How long's she been there?
Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan look so mature when they’re together…
Fried chicken for supper would be great.
How much chicken did we buy yesterday?
Even though they’re just discussing tonight's dinner.
I wonder if Yuu-chan and I could be like that…
Haruka!
I saw a water strider over there!
She’s such a blockhead!
We’re not gonna finish, the way we’re going.
Yuzu, it looks like your thighs have gotten a bit chubby.
Don’t you think you should tone them a bit with the summer coming up?
Scrubbing the whole pool length might do the trick…
From here
To here
Alright, go get ‘em!
From here
Rock, paper, scissors!
I guess five papers settles it!
Looks like you’re cleaning the shed, Yuu-chan.
What? But I wanted to play in the pool more…
Hold on, everyone!
I actually chose scissors and made it look like paper.
So let’s have a redo.
Well, as the paper minority…
Good luck with the shed cleaning!
Not what I meant!
Pool Equipment Shed
Wow, this looks about right for a school with its days numbered.
This could take a while…
Here Haruka, I brought a broom and dustpan.
Thanks! At least one of us is prepared.
Wait, I’m  doing the sweeping?
What will you do?
I’m in charge of wetting the floor!
We’re not in the pool anymore…
It’s so dusty in here…
We should air this place out.
There’s gotta be a window…
Up there!
Y-Yuu-chan?!
Wha—?
Yuu-chan!
Now, onward and upward!
S-So heavy…
I can’t…
My swimsuit’s getting wet…
Just a little further…
I can’t do it!
Got it!
Cherry petals?
How can they still be falling now?
No, no, look a little closer. They’re not real.
Really?
It looks like the old swimming club did a lot of stuff here.
Even though summer’s around the corner…
…there are petals falling around us.
It feels strange.
Just like that time…
Yuu-chan, you’ve got a petal.
Yeah, they’re all around us.
No, there’s a petal right there.
Right where?
Seriously, where do you think?
Everywhere?
She doesn’t even have a clue…
Okay, I’ll take care of this.
Yuu-chan…
No, that’s not what I meant!
Sorry…
It’s gone!
You had a petal on you. On your nose.
You just didn’t seem to notice.
Yuu-chan?
Hello?
She looks upset…
There’s another one, actually.
Turn this way.
Where?
I’ll brush it off myself, so tell me.
Right here.
You gotta do it properly!
We are!
Spray some more water here.
Don’t spray it there!
I heard they were staying behind to clean the pool, but…
Take this!
You can’t get me.
You’re dragging this out, guys.
I don’t see Yuu-chan with them.
Just give up, Kaede…
Haruka-san’s missing as well…
Sis
Don’t tell me they’re off on their own doing  that again!
shake
No, that can’t be the case!
Sis
There must be something wrong with me.
I bet she just has an after-school lesson.
I’m such a worrywart.
I should get going.
Oh, there’s some trash here…
Yuu
Haruka
A Promise Made by the Pool
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
the time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we share
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
if we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
if we split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
memories to come… let’s make them
ippai ni shichaou ne
we’ll make lots and lots
love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
the miracle of us meeting in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
it had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
it’s something we can’t do alone
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Iizuka Yuzu here!
And Ikeno Kaede.
Do my thighs really  look that chubby?
Well, there are people who are into that.
wiggle
stare
I don’t want someone liking me just for my thighs!
At least you’ve got that, Yuzu.
I’ve got nothing…
W-Well, Haruka and Kotone are just exceptional, that’s all!
I don’t need your pity!
Next time, Trick 4.
A Plan Gone Sour
Dare I Say it's a Dare?!
“A Plan Gone Sour?” and “Dare I Say it’s a Dare?!”
See you then!
You’re such a faker!