Haruka's Room
Number 4
Haruka's Room...
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
"My knowledge is as huge as a giant if you need to know something about Gulliver's Travels!"
The little giant!
He's the vice president of the ESP Research Society at Midorigaoka High School.
Please welcome Muroto Daichi!
I'm a second-year student at Midorigaoka High School.
I'm Muroto Daichi, the vice president of the ESP Research Society.
Nice to meet you.
Muroto, only the top of your head is on-screen!
Well, I'd be surprised if I was actually shown fully. It's fine.
I'm used to this. I really don't mind.
This is fine.
I'd expect nothing less of you.
You don't get flustered at any time!
But could we still adjust the camera to fit him on screen properly?
He's playing a game!
Um... Where was I...
I'm Muroto Daichi!
Nice to meet you.
Do you really mean that? You're playing a game!
Do you always do this? Even when you're not on camera?
Not all the time.
I use my computer and sleep too.
Were you always this hollow, Muroto?
When I'm not on screen, it's like I'm backstage.
What's wrong with relaxing there?
He got serious!
The End