Takamatsu-kun, your report, please.
Ma'am.
According to the armory, we will run out of ammo soon.
We will need to replenish before we have our next fight.
Since we have a new addition to the force, shouldn't we get new guns, too?
You're right.
Okay, today's operation will be Operation Guild Parachute.
P-Parachute operation...
What's wrong, Otonashi?
I'm not so good with heights, I guess...
What are you saying?
We're not parachuting down from the sky, just going down to the basement from here.
Oh, it's just the basement.
What?!  "Basement"?!
We call it the Guild.
Far below the surface, our allies are creating weapons.
Is that to keep it from Tenshi's notice?
That's right.
If she terrorizes the Guild, we'll lose our weapons support and, with that, any chance we have to win.
Hey!
It's me.
We'll meet up down there tonight.
Disarm the traps.
Gotcha!  Tonight it is, then.  We'll be waiting.
Okay.
This time, we'll go with the members we have here now.
What?  What about Noda-kun?
That idiot's off doing his own thing again, isn't he?
All right, let's go.
Ready... pull!
Okay, let's go.
Come on, don't just stand there.  Move it!
Y-You mean in here?
This is the entrance?
It's been a while since we came to the Guild.
It's pretty dark.
Hey, someone's there.
Crap, it's the idiot.
Otonashi, I have yet to accept you.
What's the point of ambushing him here?
Noda-kun has the tendency to take situations seriously.
Makes no sense.
I don't care if I'm "accepted" by you.
You bastard...  How about I kill you 1,000 times, this ti—
Everyone, be on your guard!
The traps weren't disarmed?!
What's going on?
It's just as you see.
There are numerous death traps along the Guild's passage designed to repel Tenshi.
And every one of them is active right now.
So that means...
Maybe they forgot to disarm the traps?
Are they tryin' to kill us all?!
No.  The Guild reset the traps on purpose.
Why?
There's only one answer.
Tenshi came here.
Here?!
Just wild, man.
An oversight.
Did the Guild really do this knowing that we're here?
It seems you still do not understand.
No matter what happens, we won't die.
Of course, we'll feel the mortiferous pain.
That's exactly what I don't want...
But if the location of the Guild were to be discovered and taken over,
then we couldn't replenish ammo or replace any broken weapons.
How would you propose we fight against Tenshi in that state?
The Guild made the right choice.
Should we chase after Tenshi?
You wanna walk through all them traps?
Won't the traps take care of Tenshi?
Let's just head back!
A trap is only a momentary stall for her.
We'll follow.
March on!
So, what kind of traps are there?
We've got a great variety, actually.  There's no fun in ruining the surprise.
Look out!  Incoming!
What is?
Run for it!
Oh, God... crazy!
This way!
Hurry!
Sorry, Takamatsu.  Damn, looks like he's down.
I guess everyone except Takamatsu-kun made it out.  Let's move on.
Shouldn't we go help him?
It's not like he's dead.  He'll get up and find his way to the surface without anyone's help.
Really?
Here.
Ah, thanks.
You saved me back there.
No sweat.  I kinda like you, you know.
You swing like that?
That's not what I meant!
Will it open?
'Course not.
Shoot, I forgot!
The trap here is designed to lock you in!
How could you forget something so important?!
How unwise.
Here comes the dangerous part!
Get out of the way!
Get down!
What was that?
What happens if you touch that?
It'll slice you in half with laser sharpness.
The second one's coming!
What do we do?
Go under it!
The third one's coming!
What was the third one?!
It's an X!
How are we gonna deal with that?!
Everyone deals with it their own way!
Hurry and open it!
Don't look!
You shouldn't look.
What?
Got it open!  Hurry up!
So Matsushita-kun became the next victim.
I guess he couldn't do too much with his size.
He oughta lose some weight.
He must've seen something truly awful.
I'm glad you're alive.
Oh, by the way, you'll be back in one piece after a while, even if you're minced into bits.
The trap's moving!
Shoot, I forgot!  The trap here is a falling ceiling!
I keep telling you, don't forget important stuff like that!
T.K.!
Hurry up!
You can still make it!  Whoa... Fly high and hug him!
Thanks.
See ya.
Take care.
Sorry.
Even T.K. had to be sacrificed...
You guys are the ones who sacrificed him.
He's fine, really.  No worries, no worries.
Don't let their sacrifices be in vain.
Let's move on.
What's wrong?
I hear...
Shoot!  I forgot about this!
This trap here is...
T-That's why you should stop forgetting!
It's too heavy...!  I can't hold up...!
Should we fall, too, Otonashi?
Don't make decisions for me!
It's most unwise to lose so many people here!
I know that!  Hurry and climb up!
Otonashi, can you?
Don't really have a choice, do I?
You're such a sadist.
Shut up!
I'm grabbing your shoulders now.
What are you doing?!  Don't just rest there, get moving!
Where exactly am I supposed to grab?!
Wherever!  Do as you like!
Hurry up, already!
Fine...
You'll fall if you do it like that!
Of course...
Whoa, why does she smell so good?
Crap...
No, I'd better climb.
Man, why are you facing this way?
Like I have a choice!
C-Could you possibly finish climbing now?
R-Right...
What do you think you're grabbing?!
Stupid!
S-So um, Hinata was—
He's become an unfortunate victim.
I see...
So, we're finally down to four...
I'm amazed to see this new punk's still alive.
Yeah.
You're gonna be next.
A drowning trap, this time.
Guess he's a lead weight in water.
The exit's over here.
Follow me!
Here.
Thank you.
Yuri!  This way!
Shiina-san?
Let's go.
What's that doing here?
That's...
That puppy is drifting away!
Shiina-san, don't!
What an oversight!  It's a doll!
Even Shiina-san fell to a trap.
That's a trap for Tenshi, too?!
More like, wouldn't she have figured it out?
Adorable things are her weakness.
Wow.  So she's got a cute side.
But she'll be fine, too, right?
So you're the last one surviving.
Seems that way.
If this had been a real platoon, and I just let everyone die, it'd be over soon...
Some leader I am...
What could you do?  They were traps against Tenshi.  They had to be this strong.
Why don't we rest a while?
Yeah.  I want our clothes to dry, too.
I'm amazed how you can organize that bunch.
Why were you chosen as the leader?
Because I was the first to rebel.
That's all.
You mean against Tenshi?
Yeah.
I had siblings.
I'm talking about memories, like the ones you lack.
You mean things from before coming here, when you were alive?
Yeah.
There were four of us, including myself.
I was the oldest, and had two younger sisters and a younger brother.
Thanks to our parents' successful careers, we led a very wealthy life.
We lived in a house surrounded by nature, like a sort of summer home.
It was during summer vacation.
One afternoon when our parents were out, some unfamiliar men entered the house.
They were wearing hot-looking hats despite the scorching heat.
I could tell instantly that they were up to no good.
As the eldest, I felt I absolutely had to protect the little ones.
Yeah, but like I had a chance.
They were obviously after money.
But they couldn't find any.
They started to break windows and whatnot, only getting more irritated.
And then, they came up with the worst concept ever, regarding me and my siblings.
You're the oldest girl here.
You know where the important things are in this house, doncha?
Stuff you were told to pick up to hold safe if there's an earthquake, or to give to a robber to make 'em leave.
You got told where those things are, right?
I don't know...
I don't know of anything like that!
Go and find some, then.
If we don't like it, it's a shame, but you'll be saying goodbye to them one by one.
We'll wait ten minutes per person.
Bring one object every ten minutes.
I started to search all over the house.
I remember my head hurting so badly.
I felt nauseous.
I felt like collapsing.
"Their lives are at stake!  I have to find something!"
But I didn't know what they wanted.
I'm running out of time!
I need to hurry!  I need to hurry!
I'll take the biggest vase!
I-It's heavy...
It's this heavy, so it's gotta be worth a lot!
The police came 30 minutes later.
I was the only one left alive.
It's not about worrying if I'll become a water flea.
If God really exists, I want to fight against Him.
I mean, that's too unfair!
I had done nothing wrong...
Until that day, I was confident that I'd been a good older sister, too.
I had everything I wanted to protect taken from me in a matter of 30 minutes.
I just can't accept something so unreasonable.
I can't forgive being given such a life.
You're so strong, Yuri.
If my memory turns out to be something like that, I'll probably want to be obliterated right away.
But instead, you've chosen to fight.
That's right.
Hey, can I ask one thing?
What?
How did you die?
You moron!  It wasn't suicide!
Why would anyone who committed suicide fight?!
Besides, no one who's killed themselves is in this world.
Come on, let's go.
I will protect you.
This is the Guild?!
It's Yurippe!
She came!  She's safe!
So they make the weapons here...
You actually made it here through all those traps!
You're amazing.
That aside, where's Tenshi?
She was stalled until a while ago, but it looks like she's started moving again.
She was caught again.
She's close...
Yurippe...
We'll abandon this place.
What?!   Have you lost it, Yurippe?
Yeah!  How would it be okay if you don't get more weapons?
What's important isn't the place or the tool.  It's the knowledge.
Have you all forgotten that?
No...
What do you mean, Yuri?
In this world, new life is never created.  But we can create things.
As long as one knows the theory and the method, you don't need any materials.
We can make things from even a pile of dirt.
But at some point, we decided to prioritize efficiency and began regularly making replicas at a factory like this.
Cha-san.
He's in high school, too?
We used to give life to things based on our memory, didn't we?
In this case, let's move to the Old Guild.  We've left it untouched for too long.
There's nothing there, but we do have all the dirt we'd ever want.
We can return to the surface as necessary from there.
What about this place?
We'll blow it up.
We can't let Tenshi reach the Old Guild.
That's the only place we can return to.
But—!
She's right above us!
The only things you'll bring with you are your memories and pride as a craftsman.
That's all you need.  Isn't that right, fellas?!
Sir!
All right, plant the bombs.
Show me your teamwork!
There aren't any more traps.
Hurry up!
Yuri, where are you going?
To buy time!
Oh, you came?
You're not scared?
There's nothing to do even if I'm down there.
Here she comes.
Let's go!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
She's reacting too fast!
Wow.  She can even fight at close range.
Load the round!
Are you sure we want to use this?
Just do it!
Push!  Push!
Take it up now!  Show your strength!
Guard Skill:  Delay.
Damn it...
Otonashi-kun!
Move it, you two!
I knew you guys could pull it off!
I know that's not easy to make!
Otonashi-kun, this way!
Here she goes!
Everyone take shelter!
Fire!!
Did it work?
The cannon self-destructed...
Damn.  Guess we can't make things up for stuff we don't know about...
Don't wing things like that!
Tenshi's getting up!
You guys!
Handle her with these!
Hurry to the shelter!
Everyone has evacuated!
Okay, I'm detonating the Guild.
Ready?
Do it.
Ignition!
How many years has it been?  There really is nothing here.
Hilarious.
Kick the wall, and you'll get all the dirt you'd ever need.
What a horrible hideout.
I look forward to working with you again.
Yeah.
All right, let's get to work, fellas!
Are you awake, morons?
We've abandoned the Guild.
We blew it up, along with Tenshi.
Everyone, gather at the Old Guild.
The weapons are now being made there.
Before Tenshi gets back on her feet, everyone make your way to the Old Guild!
I repeat: Hurry up, you morons!
I saved her without thinking much.
What the heck am I doing?
If God really exists, I want to fight against Him.
I mean, that's too unfair!
Too frustrating!
You're really amazing.
It's no wonder why everyone follows you.
You're being a great leader.
Why is the new song a ballad?
Call me Christ.
I couldn't sing the song I like...
It's where Tenshi lives.
That was some heat in there.
Another great high-tempo song is "Alchemy."  "Alchemy" is—
Hey, amnesia boy.
Then what do you say happened?
I was just starting to think better of you guys!
We're in the worst possible setup.
Tenshi has arrived.
I guess this is it.
Don't touch that!