so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice
Someone was there singing for you, the happiness they sang about
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this gentle light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
Here.
Come on.
And that's the way we'll do it.
Roger.
As for where we condu-
Heading out, Kanata?
Good morning.
Already planning to use your first paycheck?
Not all of it.
I'm sending some home,
and I thought I'd send some souvenirs back, and...
A little treat for yourself?
Yes.
The first month was just training so you didn't get anything.
Excited, aren't you?
Yes. But I'm surprised.
I heard that we were usually paid late, and then in military scrip.
Here you are. Good work this month.
Thank you very much!
I didn't think I would get real money.
Of course you do. Why do you think we have our other busine-
Kanata, um... Er... There's a flea market in town today.
It's your first time, right?
Your first paycheck and your first day off.
A first time for everything and right on time.
Forget about your day job and take a good look at everything.
Okay!
Kanata's Day Off - Hair Ties
I'll be going then!
I told you not to say anything suspicious around Kanata.
But just think about it!
Getting paid in the middle of nowhere and without even a late supply shipment?
And... she actually believed you...
She accepts what she gets. That's Kanata.
Right.
Unlike you two. You found out where we got the money.
And how.
Well then.
Why don't we forget about our day jobs, too?
It's got character.
Don't you think?
But there's just one fault.
The price isn't going any lower.
I'm sorry, I didn't notice you there.
Looks like you're ready.
Yeah. We haven't run into any trouble.
But I've run into some.
I've got an idea to take care of it.
You in?
Tell me more about this idea.
This one is nice too.
So you're the fine shopkeeper. You selling these?
I hope you like our goods.
They're not bad.
But, there's just one fault.
Oh? What would that be?
You've got this many. It would take some work and a few connections to sell them.
And we don't have the resources for that, you get what I'm saying?
So-
We have a no-discount policy here.
The price is part of the taste.
We won't ask you to lower the price.
We'll just take them.
Don't even think about it.
Go ahead and shoot. If you can.
'Cause before you can,
this gun in my hand would blow your head clean off, just like your hat.
Then-
Not very smart, are you?
This is what you get for taking me lightly.
Good night, boys.
I warned you.
Punk.
You one of their friends?
Mishio!
The car!
Boss!
We're out of here!
But the souvenirs for the Don?
Worthless if we're dead!
Boss!
No one said anything about maniacs!
We're never coming back again!
They're gone.
Good.
You can get up now, everyone!
Man, I was scared for a moment.
But it looks like we fooled them.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Not at all. If the mob got a foothold here, our business would go kaput.
Just a little give-and-take.
But...
You will be giving us our fee for this little play.
Oh my. Mikhail, you do have a sense of humor.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not joking.
Now we talk business.
Why don't I take those?
Did you bust their car there?
You didn't do it?
What happened?
I don't know.
It looked like someone busted their car.
And there were some goods that they bought at the flea market.
Why don't I say I bought those and we split the profits?
It seems we've reached an agreement.
Yes.
So the play's finally over.
But that was quite a surprise.
What was?
You were completely in character, Rio.
If anyone discovered that we're distilling this, we'd have more than a court-martial on our hands.
Direct violations of the anti-trust laws and tax laws.
At worst, charges of treason.
That's right. We picked up this business after the ones before us.
And Rio's never been against it.
I was a bit surprised too.
Well, I was surprised myself at first.
This calvados was my mother's favorite.
And it was made here at the fortress.
Then maybe your mother was responsible for your station here.
Sound of the Sky
I'll be going then!
Sister Yumina!
I'm done! Look!
It's wonderful, Seiya.
Mishio.
Today is their first visit to the church.
The priest will be there today. So, just for today...
No!
Don't start causing her problems now. At least let her do your hair.
No! I won't let her!
Why not? You always tell me to do it!
Shut up, Seiya!
You can't do that, Mishio.
Mishio!
¥10.25.
Look where you're going, girl.
I'm sorry, I didn't notice you there.
Seriously, these bumpkins.
They're the problem.
It seems they've heard about our business.
Are you okay?
Yes.
But Miss Naomi, tell me, what should I do?
This is the first time I've had enough money in my purse to buy it!
If I ask for it, I could just buy it.
What if someone came in and wanted to buy that dolphin?
Did someone say they wanted to buy it?
No, just a hypothetical question.
Let's see... I would...
Right! I would tell them that dolphins were really scary people-eating animals and make sure they didn't buy it!
Oh! You're a genius!
Oh, and that dolphin.
I'll keep it until you say you don't want it anymore, so relax and worry all you want.
Then I'll buy everyone's souvenirs first.
Let's see... Dad, Mom, Grandpa, Grandma,
Grandma and Grandpa Warren, Great-grandma,
and Grandma Nanae next door!
Wow!
There's so much stuff to choose!
Like this!
Sorry, but no.
Oh, Mishio?
Are you out shopping?
It looks like she's looking for a box.
A box?
Like this. Did you see one?
Sorry.
Should I help you look for it?
What are you doing here, Kanata?
I'm here to buy souvenirs.
I was looking for something wonderful to send to my family back home.
But I'm not in a hurry-
I don't need your help!
I wonder why Mishio said that...
This is a bit...
Oh, that's quite nice.
This one is nice too.
Sister Yumina?
Excuse me, Miss Kanata.
Have you seen Mishio?
A box?
Yes. She said it was important.
Did she...
When her mother died, all of her family's belonging's were taken from her.
It's supposed to be a memento that her mother left her.
Whenever there's a flea market, she always goes to look.
I said something wrong.
I received my first paycheck yesterday.
And I told her I was sending presents back home.
That's okay.
I am...
We are trying to be her family.
If she were still jealous of you,
then it's because I'm not good enough.
Mama, which is more important to you, me or your treasure box?
You.
Mama...
Mishio...
Mishio!
These are Treize's famous firecrackers! They'll crack like thunder! How about 'em?
Sister... Sister Yumina...
Sister!
Mishio!
The car!
Sorry, but I'm not Yumina.
Sister! Sister Yumina!
Thank you.
Keep up the good work.
Now then.
Um...
Oh, what is it?
Was that car... yours, Miss Naomi?
Don't tell me you two did that?
I'm so sorry! There's ¥150 in here, so
I'll pay-
Good job, you two.
You can keep that. I already got my payment.
Miss Naomi! That box!
These ideographs mean "beautiful rice stalk".
Carve them into her seal and I assure you she will have a life as full of happiness as a bountiful field of rice.
My...
Miho, aren't you so happy to receive such a great fortune?
Did you find Mishio?
I thought I had done everything to be her family,
but I'm still not good enough.
No, you are trying hard.
Mishio!
Wonderful! You found it!
Take good care of it.
It's an irreplaceable memento from your mother.
No.
This box...
I want you to have this.
Mishio was taken in by the church after she lost her mother.
Her father was sent to the front lines and never returned.
And her mother?
Mishio's family lived in the Eastern region of Binnenland.
Not that...
Yes, the town stricken by the Invisible Death.
When they arrived here in Seize, her mother was already showing symptoms, and soon after...
Mama told me.
She said, "Sorry I can't do your hair anymore."
And she told me... to have the person who cares about me most tie my hair.
Can you tie it, Yumina?
Man lives on.
Even after being separated from those we love and suffer as though dying.
We still live on. We can live on.
That strength is our sorrow. Our love.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
My sister.
Everyone's already in there.
Yes. I'll go soon.
You had a long day.
Yeah. I didn't really want to wash my hair,
but things happen.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Let me dry your hair for you, Rio!
I've always wanted to touch it!
So you didn't buy the dolphin?
I thought that would be your little treat.
Rio, do you believe in destiny?
Why do you ask?
Well, something that felt like it happened today.
That was enough of a treat for me.
I don't believe in it. I don't like the idea that anything's already decided for you before you even get a chance.
But I do believe
that one small thing someone does
can work its way up and up
and change someone's life in an amazing way.
If that's destiny,
then maybe...
I...
D-flat.
It looks like Rio had a wonderful day today, too.
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: Chirping Crickets - Floating Lights on the River