2500 YEN PER T-SHIRT, ONE SIZE ONLY!
T-shirts! Get your T-shirts here!
We have towels too!
Thank you for your patronage!
Thank you for your...
I told you no one's going to buy this.
Why make them when we haven't
even decided on our band name?
Well y'know, I just thought it could help with our funds and stuff...
What are we, a football team?
Well, if we become famous maybe we can
sell those as an ultra-rare item.
You're being a bit too optimistic there.
Hey.
What're you spacing out for?
Thanks for coming!
I'll be cheering for you!
Do your best.
I'll definitely come to your next concert!
Thank you, I hope to see you there.
Rupa-san's so popular...
That's great and all, but we
really need to decide on our name.
- True.
- You got a moment?
Of course.
I'LL GIVE YOU A NAME
TL Note : The title is a reference to the song of the same name (Namae wo Tsuketeyaru) by Spitz.
- A concert?
- Yep.
Someone who helped me when I was just starting out
was asking if we wanted to play.
Where's the venue?
In Suwa, Nagano.
The plan is to arrive the night before the concert and rehearse right before it.
We're supposed to go back right after,
but I can play alone if you guys are busy.
Nina has studying to do, after all.
We're going!
Right?
Are you serious? We still sound like a
bunch of bickering instruments.
It's fine, the more we'll play the better we'll get.
Well, if you say so...
Which means we’re in.
Alright, alright.
Hmmm...
What is it?
What are we going to do about our name?
THE NEXT DAY
I’m warning you, if we're gonna call ourselves
Shin-Kawasaki, I'm seriously gonna quit.
I get it already.
We are trying to go pro...
Did Momoka-san say anything after last time?
Nothing.
She didn't give me an answer
and never brought it up again.
The Cold War treatment, huh?
What are you so happy about?
Weird, you'd think she'd be bickering
with Nina like always if she was against it.
What happened to the lizard?
It’s a gecko.
I moved him because he wasn't feeling well.
She's pissing me off!
If she has something to say,
she should just say it!
And you're pissing off the neighbors!
Well, she definitely has a right to be mad.
Because Nina keeps doing
stuff behind her back.
That was your idea.
Oopsie~
Just saying, if you're constantly going
to fight, Rupa and I are out.
We don’t have time for this.
I get it, but...
So, does anyone have ideas
on how to name our chaotic little band?
Do you have one?
- Wait, why am I starting?
You should go first.
Yeah, you're the one who brought it up!
Eh? It's embarrassing...
How about you just say it at the same time?
If you say so...
Alright, on three then.
Got it.
One, two, three...
- Chocolate.
- Undine.
One, two, three...
- Chocolate!
- Undine!
Hey, what's wrong with Chocolate?
It's...something alright.
As expected from a country bumpkin.
Your naming sense is gonna give me cavities.
Hey, that's mean!
What the heck was yours anyway? "Undine"?
Well…
That's way more embarrassing than mine.
Huh? Like hell it is.
They both suck.
Let's hear yours then!
Yeah, say it again.
Dream Girl.
Anything new?
I never thought it'd be this hard...
That's because Subaru's so picky.
I'll have to take your words and
throw them right back in your face.
"Did you decide on a name?"
She's pissing me off.
We ended up wasting the entire day.
She’s late...
Onee-chan?
You could've sent me a message, you know.
I wanted to surprise you.
But I didn’t expect you’d come home this late.
I usually come home earlier.
Something came up today.
Like what? You got a boyfriend?
Wait, you're not working at
some shady place are you?
Then what is it?
A band.
I'm in a band.
A band?
Yeah.
You, in a band? Seriously?
Got any pictures?
Here.
Woah, you were serious. You're the vocalist?
What's...with this outfit?
It’s a...
rock outfit.
A rock outfit!
The heck does that mean?
Just drop it.
I guess that explains your
grades dropping off a cliff.
How did you know?
Well, schools tend to contact the family if a
student's grades drop and they start playing hooky.
So they snitched on me...
Be thankful I stopped your dad from coming.
So, what will it be?
I'm not coming back.
That's fine and all,
but that means you won't be able
to come back in the future either.
You know, I do think it was Dad's fault.
100 TIPS FOR RAISING A CHILD WELL
He's a teacher who's well-known for his books on education.
He couldn’t accept that his
own daughter started skipping school.
I'm sure you were plenty hurt yourself,
but I try to put myself in his shoes too.
If you kept quiet about the bullying,
the school would have owed you one.
Combining that with your grades, getting a
college recommendation would be a given.
Maybe, but that's not
how I want to do things.
So you ran away, saying you'll get
into college through your own efforts.
And now, you're neglecting your studies.
Sorry, but I can't exactly
take your side on this one.
A FEW DAYS LATER
Let’s get moving. We're starting rehearsals tomorrow morning.
Got it.
Sorry I'm late.
What's with the baggage?
Is it too much?
Show me that for a sec.
This, this and this...
and some clothes.
Everything else stays.
Always travel light.
Alright then...
The Chuo Expressway, right? You can-
Quiet.
A manual gearbox? That’s rare.
It's the only thing I could find to borrow on a short notice. Let's see...
I think it went like this...
Or like this?
Those in favor of a driver change,
please raise your hands.
Rupa-san, you're a really good driver.
I used to drive a lot for my part-time job.
Do you think you can drive the whole way? We can take breaks if you want.
Was my driving that bad?
I’ll stop at a gas station if I
get tired, so you all can rest for now.
Eh, that's a waste of a road trip...
Wanna play a game then?
We'll ask yes or no questions in turn,
and if everyone raises their hands you win.
For example…who prefers cats over dogs?
Tomo-chan, you're a dog person? Didn't see that coming.
Well, they say cat-like people prefer dogs.
Your turn, Nina.
Umm…
Who doesn't have many friends?
Easy peasy.
Don't just go straight for the easy ones.
Momoka-san, you’re up.
Eh, I don't feel like it.
Fine, who thinks my driving sucks?
REST AREA
Let's take a short break.
Alright, I'll be back in a bit.
- Whoa, it's cold!
- Come on, stop it.
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- How much time do we have?
Excuse me.
You sure took your time...
What is this?
Did I get the wrong one?
It's fine, but...
TL Note : Nina got her expensive luxury brand water.
Phew.
Tomo-chan, why did you drop out of school?
Why are you asking?
Because I don't have anyone else to ask.
Let’s just say I had better things to do
than waste my time in that place.
My parents might as well have
not existed at that point,
so I realized I'll be completely
on my own after graduating.
Mom?
She was like a completely different
person when she was with that man.
Seeing her like that triggered something in me.
People trying to become indie musicians
right after graduating are dime a dozen.
The sooner I start, the better.
So I came to Tokyo to find
people to make music with.
As for school, it just took up too much time.
That's all there is to it.
You're amazing.
I could never think that far ahead.
When you suddenly lose all the people
you used to rely on, it happens naturally.
When Rupa lost her family in an accident, she...
also said something similar.
I was...nowhere near as serious.
I always wanted to do something like this!
Alright, smile everyone!
Momoka-san, Tomo-chan, that goes for you too.
Say cheese!
It's like we're idols...
Please shut up.
WELCOME TO THE FIREWORKS FESTIVAL LAND SUWA
I know our budget's pretty
tight, but this is kinda...
Ugh, it's hot.
And heavy.
Good morning.
Good morning to you too.
Girls Band Cry.
That was pretty good, wasn't it?
Are you crazy? We're all over the place.
The only ones all over the place are you two.
I'm playing just fine, thank you!
We're all a mess.
Forget that for a sec, Subaru-chan,
what's up with your head?...
You saw how I slept!
So, that’s your new band, Momo?
"Momo"?
It sure is!
"It sure is"?
Oh, my neck unsnapped itself.
Well, I can't say you're perfect, but I like the vibe.
It's better than being good but without
any chemistry, at the very least.
We’ll do our best today.
That guitar…
Yes, it's the same one.
Your sticker's still on it too.
DIAMOND DUST
Isn't she acting a bit...different?
Or maybe this is the real Momoka-san.
I’d like us to play a song together at the end.
- Does that sound good?
- Really?
Like, with us?
Wanting to play with you is
the main reason I invited you all.
Are you up for it, girls?
Uh, yes.
How about a little session then?
- Session?
- She means singing together.
You’re the vocalist, right?
Yes, I am.
Farewell, melody of the past
Until we meet again
As we become adults
Just once more
As our memories fade
- What do you think?
- Huh?
- Can you sing it?
- I think so.
Probably.
I’ll do my best.
That's settled then. I’ll tell the manager.
- Great song, wasn't it?
- Yes!
I saw Mine's concert not long after I
came to Tokyo for the first time.
She was just a no-name supporting act like us, an afterthought.
And yet she didn't let that faze her one bit,
singing with all she had as if she was fighting.
"This is true rock", I thought to myself back then.
It's the perfect scenario for my final concert.
I decided to leave the band.
Tomorrow's concert is the end for me.
I'm out.
What are you saying?
Sorry, but I don’t have it in me to go pro again.
Why?
My songs aren't made for the big world.
I'm truly happy that you grew to like them,
and even more so that they sparked a fire
in you. Seriously, thank you.
Are you really okay with this?
Yep.
This is my answer.
NICHOME
Wow, I didn't expect you to drink that much!
Rupa-san, you sure can hold your liquor!
She loves drinking people under the table...
Don't tell me we have to carry her again…
She's pretty damn heavy, for how she looks at least.
You better not mess up tomorrow.
We owe the audience that much.
- I know that.
- What's with the surly faces?
What is it? Are we fighting?
Uh, that aside! Mine-san, what kind of music do you like?
Mine-san, have you ever
thought about quitting music?
Oh come on, where did that come from?
Cut it out, will ya?
No one likes having to
make these kinds of decisions.
The longer you keep at something, the clearer your prospects at it become.
If you fail the first time around, you can chalk it up to bad luck.
But the second time, you
start questioning your ability.
So...she lost the ability to believe that things will go well?
She wants to believe.
But the more you believe in your success,
the more painful it will be when you fail.
She's scared.
She's scared, because music is everything to her.
Well, I'll be counting on you tomorrow.
Excuse me!
Are you...not scared of the same thing?
Me?
Yes.
Of course I am.
Sometimes to the point where I can't even eat or sleep.
Even now?
Of course.
But that's what it means to turn
your passion into your profession.
When I was studying music at college,
I thought about becoming a teacher and singing as an amateur.
I thought it was the smartest choice.
What made you change your mind?
Good question.
I don't even remember anymore.
Really?
Anyway, for me the stage is a place where I can express myself wholeheartedly.
A place I truly love.
So I must've thought
something along the lines of
"It doesn't matter how difficult
or painful it might be sometimes".
Oi!
Ew, you reek of alcohol!
What're you babblin' about?
I haven't had a single drop!
How does that lie even come out of your mouth?!
You're a real pain, you know...
You're always, always...
See you.
Oi, you listenin' to me?
I'm leaving her to you!
Huh? Hey, what am I supposed
to do with this?!
Nina! This isn't fair!
Excuse me, do you know how I can get to the lake?
Thank you very much!
That's it.
I know what to do now.
I've made my decision!
I'm going to do it.
KAMISUWA KAICHO
Thank you!
The next band is my personal favorite,
so give them a warm welcome alright?
Ready?
Ready.
By the way, what about our name?
Did you decide on one in the end?
We were supposed to come up with
something while eating, but no luck.
If we're gonna call ourselves Shin-Kawasaki,
I'm gonna...oh whatever.
Huh?
Good evening!
- We are…
- That little...
Uh, we are…
**TOGENASHI TOGEARI**
We're TOGENASHI TOGEARI!
They have the same name as my T-shirt.
What a coincidence, wow.
Nice to meet you all.
I joined the band this spring.
I don't know what pushed me to do it,
or why I wanted to sing in the first place.
But I love it.
For the first time in my life, I could lose myself in something.
Let's hurry.
You know, there's a song that changed my life.
That song became my drive to move forward.
And I want to prove to the world that it has value,
that it can touch people's hearts.
I want to tell everyone how amazing it is.
Subaru-chan, Rupa-san, Tomo-chan, and Momoka-san
I'm sure all of them feel
that way about something too.
That's why we're giving it everything we have.
We're scared, but we don't give up.
And that's why I…
I-
People might get annoyed, you know.
If you keep going on about yourself.
Sorry.
Geez.
That's one hell of an entrance.
Well, whatever!
I am a mass of wounds, body and mind fragmented by wear and tear
A chimeric passion in tatters in my ribcage
A trip to a deceptive city, like a lost soul, I wander
In a spiral of stench and noise, I cry
How to overcome today when everything is darkness?
Stop losing yourself in trivialities
This voice resonates in me as my tears keep flowing
"Conquer your fear and stop hiding"
"Join me so we can dance"
I want to leave this disgusting world
To scatter violently
To scatter, scatter slowly
But don't abandon me to my fate
As one vomits their sadness into the measures of a chorus
Forever, again and again
Until love is stronger
I refuse to believe it is just an emotion
To the point of losing my mind
Rupa-san.
Tomo-chan.
Subaru-chan.
Momoka-san.
I'm...
I'm dropping out of school.
To be continued: "If You Needed to Cry."