Hurts, doesn't it?
Mages bear the pain of that Crest
for their entire lives.
Your father gave you quite
an appropriate name.
Your origin lies in severing and binding, kiddo.
The nuance is a bit different from
destroying and regenerating.
If you cut a thread and
tie the ends together again,
the thread will be thicker
where you tied it, right?
In other words, the change is irreversible.
"Kiritsugu," with the characters
for "sever" and "bind."
I have the perfect Mystic Code for you.
I ground up part of your ribs,
and put some in this bullet.
Your origin will manifest in
anything you shoot with it.
If you land a shot against someone using magic,
your origin will cut their Magic Circuits,
then haphazardly tie them.
You could take out a
capable mage with one shot.
I made sixty-six rounds.
Use them wisely.
Natalia, do you read me?
Almost there.
Roger.
Natalia, now.
As it turned out,
after fleeing the island,
I spent the next several years with
that woman, Natalia Kaminski.
That meant following the same path,
the path of the hunter.
Natalia worked for no one but herself.
She only cared about getting paid.
She was a true freelancer.
The Mages Association and the Holy Church...
Natalia's business was supported
by the conflict between those
two massive organizations.
Since that night,
I've seen many tragedies
like what happened on Arimago Island.
And I learned
that similar things happened
all over the world, on a daily basis.
You want to be a hero?
Was it all pointless?
I thought
I killed my father so no one else would
be victimized like this anymore.
Offing one guy won't be enough.
If you killed every single person in the
world who was like these guys,
then maybe your wish
would come true.
I'm joking.
Forget it.
I've found there's only
one rule in this business.
Survive, by any means necessary.
No matter what happens,
put your own life first.
If you sacrifice yourself to save another,
that won't help anyone.
I know I can't save everyone.
I just want to save as many people as I can.
Do what you want.
This is gonna be a tough one.
You know him?
Odd Vořák, mage.
He uses bee familiars to turn
people into his ghouls.
The Mages Association has offered
a hell of a bounty for him.
You know a lot about him.
He brings devastation with him.
We completely lost the last town he was in.
A whole town...
Natalia, can I have one?
In your country, how old do
you have to be to smoke?
Well, I won't say no,
but they're bad for you.
Where's he headed?
In four days, Vořák will be on this flight,
traveling from Paris to New York.
I'll be on it, too.
He got away from me once.
I should be the one to finish the job.
Even you actually fail?
That would show how good he is.
What should I do?
Vořák probably has an ally in New York.
I'd like you to take him out.
You'll deal with Vořák alone?
He can't bring his bees into the cabin.
Then this time, he won't be
able to give you the slip.
Very funny, kiddo.
Kiddo, you read me?
Loud and clear.
Good luck to us both.
That was easier than I expected.
The less effort needed,
the better, Natalia.
All right, Kiritsugu.
Ready to get his corpse off the plane?
Everything's taken care of.
We just need a doctor to carry out
an incapacitated passenger.
As long as I don't need a license.
Hey!
What is it, Natalia?
Ghouls!
We've got trouble.
He had bees inside his own body?
Natalia, get out of there.
Do you know how high up I am?
And I'm not equipped for skydiving.
Oh, wonderful.
Looks like they're in the cockpit.
Only one option.
Natalia, you can't...
I'll come back alive.
I'll come back alive, with Vořák's corpse.
To accomplish that, I just need to
do something about the plane.
You wanna say something?
Yeah, I know you'll be fine.
Thanks.
Get a nice, comfy bed ready
for me, and sit tight.
You read me, kiddo?
Not napping, are you?
Loud and clear, Natalia.
It'll be a tough morning,
after our all-nighter, huh?
If you'd spent the night in a bed,
I'd have strangled you.
Now, do you want the good news or the bad?
Aren't you supposed to start with the good?
Okay.
First, the good news...
Well, I'm still alive.
And the plane's still in the air.
It was surprisingly easy to reach the cockpit,
but I had my hands full, trying to fix the radio.
Looks like I'll be able to fly this,
assuming it handles like a Cessna.
Have you contacted air traffic control?
Sure have.
At first, they thought it was some kind of joke.
But I've secured myself a nice escort.
Then, the bad news?
I've managed to avoid being bitten,
but the three hundred passengers
and crew are all ghouls.
It's an airborne city of the undead
beyond the cockpit door.
Scary, huh?
Will you be able
to make it back alive?
That door's pretty sturdy.
As we speak, they're scratching at it.
But there's no way they'll get through.
I'm more worried about the landing.
This thing may be too big for me to handle.
I'm sure you'll manage.
You're cheering me on?
I appreciate it.
I'll figure out a way to land the plane,
but what do I do about the monsters?
Don't sweat it.
I have it worked out, Natalia.
That's a relief.
I'll be at the airport
in just over fifty minutes.
That's too long to spend praying.
Talk to me, kiddo.
Sure.
When you originally told me
you wanted to help with my work,
I had no idea what to tell you.
It didn't seem like you'd back down,
no matter what I said.
You saw such little skill in me?
Just the opposite.
I saw too much skill.
Far too much...
What do you mean?
It takes most assassins years
before they learn the ability
to disconnect their feelings
from their trigger fingers.
But you had it from the start.
You had a real talent.
But even if you find a job
that suits your abilities,
that doesn't guarantee you'll find happiness in it.
If you only focus on what you should do,
without thinking about what you want to do,
then you're just a machine.
Just a phenomenon.
That's not how a human should live.
You know, I always took you
for a colder woman.
What? How am I not?
Have I ever once taken it easy on you?
No, you were strict
and you never held back.
You really did whatever it took to teach me.
It's usually the father who teaches the son.
Well...
It was me, more or less,
who took that chance away from you.
I guess I felt guilty.
I didn't have any other way of life
I could teach you.
So you consider yourself my father?
Don't get my gender mixed up, idiot.
At least say I'm your mother.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I spent every day alone,
covered in blood, for so long...
So long, I even forgot I was alone.
But...
This thing has been pretty fun,
in its own way...
Becoming something like a family.
For me, too.
I really did think of you as a mother.
I was happy that I wasn't alone.
All right, Kiritsugu...
It's gonna be really embarrassing
when we see each other again,
so that's enough.
Jeez, you're throwing me off.
I have to land in twenty minutes.
If I sit here laughing over old memories,
I'm gonna crash.
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
Maybe I'm just losing my edge.
Maybe playing house has made me soft,
and that's why I got into this mess.
If so, that's it...
Maybe I should retire.
What would you do if you quit?
Without this job...
My only option left would be to
keep acting as your mom.
You are
my real family.
Did you see that, Shirley?
I did it again.
I killed again, just like with my dad.
I didn't screw up, like I did with you.
I saved a lot of people...
If Natalia had landed that plane,
there's no telling how many
might have died.
Her sacrifice saved them...
That's why...
That's why, Shirley...
I...
Damn it! Damn it!
You bastard!
Kerry,
what do you want to be
when you grow up?
I...
Episode 19
Where Justice Dwells
Who are you?!
That isn't funny.
How are you enjoying the life
you took from Sakura?
By my Command Spell,
I order you, my puppet...
You finally look like your old self.
I started this fight.
I really am happy, you know.
Next Time:
The Assassin Returns