Seeing as you are apparently
incapable of capturing the third fairy,
you have a lot of nerve showing your faces here.
That little fairy really slighted us!
Next time, we shall defeat it!
This isn't the type of problem
that can be solved by numbers.
Please allow me to deal with this alone.
If you're so confident, then very well.
I thank you for this opportunity.
I won't forgive you.
I'll make you regret scarring my beautiful face!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Who'd have thought there'd be another fairy born so soon?
Nish to meet you! My name'sh Potpourri!
Apparently, we collected enough Heart Seeds
that the Great Heart Tree recovered enough to create a new fairy.
You really are so cute!
What's this?
Handsh off!
Is that something important to you, Potpourri?
I'm sure it's something of great use to you Precure.
It's proof that the Great Heart
Tree is recovering its strength.
That's right!
It's all because Tsubomi and Erika have worked so hard!
Oh, while I remember, I should introduce myself, shouldn't I?
I'm Tsubomi's grandmother, Hanasaki Kaoruko.
And this...
...is Lord Coupe!
He's sho c...
C?
Sho cool!
A Fairy Adventure!
The Hunt for the Next Precure!
The third Precure?
That'sh right.
If we don't find her shoon, then the
Great Heart Tree will be in great danger!
Huh?!
The Great Heart Tree is under attack by the
Desert Aposhtles, and is hiding itshelf away...
But my powersh alone weren't enough to protect it...
Potpourri...
So before the Desert Aposhtles find it,
I want to ushe the third Precure's
shtrength to protect the Great Heart Tree!
Potpourri is a fairy with strong protective powers.
Potpourri's partner Precure would surely have amazing protective abilities!
Then we have to hurry and
find the third Precure quickly.
There'sh no need!
I've already found the third Precure!
Wh-Who is it?!
Who is it?!
It'sh...
her!
Whaaaaat?!
I can feel really shtrong power within you!
I'm shure you're the third Precure!
Oh, I'm sorry, but my partner fairy is Coupe, you see.
Ish that how it ish?
Please cheer up!
We'll help you find the third Precure together!
How are we meant to find them in the first place, anyway?
Just leave it...
...to us!
Huh?
We're used to this world now, so with us at your side finding the third Precure will be a piece of cake!
Will you really be able to do it?
We have a plan!
Just leave it to us!
Precure! Precure! Precure! Precure! Pre—
I'm really not sure about this...
Now who should we chooshe to be our Precure?
Hunting?
Hunting is what you call it when you're looking for something!
Whoever the third Precure is, they'll have seen the messages sent by the Great Heart Tree in their dreams!
We'll look around Tsubomi and Erika's school first!
It's the school where we found Blossom and Marine, so the third Precure is bound to be there too!
We call it "The Hunt for the Next Precure!"
Thanks to my perfect dishguise, no one will find me shuspicioush at all!
With this, we'll be able to search for the third Precure without any trouble!
I am a cat.
As yet I have no name.
That'sh some tough shtudying they're doing.
I've no idea where I was born.
Erika! Masato! Kyouko! Akira!
Very well.
Sometimes, I get kids who ask me,
"Once I grow up, is the stuff I learn in school really going to help me?"
As your teacher, I promise you that
learning new things is never pointless.
Some day, it'll help you, in one way or another.
So keep your heads down and focus on the lesson.
Yes, ma'am!
Ms. Tsurusaki really is a wonderful teacher, isn't she?
Yeah!
She's sho cool...
Could she be the third Precure?
You really think so?!
I'd like to see that!
I can't see!
Hrm?
Is there somebody outside?
I must be imagining things...
I must be a little tired...
It's a... a... gh-ghost!
M-Ms. Tsurusaki, there's no one there...
Huh? What?
Could Ms. Tsurusaki be scared of ghosts or something?
No way! She's an adult.
Acting sho frightened of poor little me is jusht mean!
There'sh no way she could be the third Precure!
What do you think, Potpourri?
How about the girl over there doing shomething with the flowers?
Excuse me...
Whoa! A weirdo!
It's rude to call people weirdos, you know!
Well, if you're not a weirdo, what the heck's with you?!
Well, um... um...
We're... I mean, I'm...
trying to scout out a Precure!
Scouting a Precure?
That'sh right!
Is being a Precure something you're scouted for?
Well, we have our reasons!
I take it from the way you were
photographing them that you like flowers?
I do like flowers. As much as any girl would.
In that case, I'd like to shcout you as a Precure!
Me, a Precure?
Then again, that'd mean I could get an up-close
and personal scoop on them whenever I wanted...
All right then, I've made up my mind! I'll become a Precure!
I find her motives distasteful.
Let me confirm one thing: Have you had any dreams about a large tree?
A tree?
Of course I have!
She's lying!
That'sh no good! Let's go find shomeone else.
H-He's floating...
She's amashing.
Oh, that's Sayaka!
Being athletic is a good selling point if you want to become a Precure.
Excushe me.
Whoa! A weirdo!
I'm not a weirdo! I'm a scout for the Precures.
A scout for the Precures?
Mish, I want you to become a Precure!
Th-This is so sudden! I mean,
I'm only really good at soccer...
There's no reason a Precure
couldn't fight with a soccer ball!
What?!
Mish, have you ever had any dreamsh about a large tree?
N-No, I haven't...
That'sh too bad!
Hey, you from the girls' soccer team! Help me catch him!
I dunno if it's an alien or a ghost or what, but in any case, it's a huge scoop!
I think they're onto us!
Let's get out of here!
That was scary...
We'll have to search for the third
Precure without Kanae finding us.
Huh?
A lone flower, swaying in the burning winds!
Cure Fire!
Surely there has to be a cuter pose I can use.
Meow.
You saw me, huh?
Who are you? You're rather suspicious.
I-I'm a scout for the Precures!
What?!
That's perfect!
There's something I have to ask you!
Wh-What is it?
I'm making a comic book about Precure at the moment,
and I wanted to design my own, original, third Precure.
A third Precure?!
Yeah. But I just can't decide on a climactic pose.
I see a strong and beautiful hero, fighting to protect everyone!
That's the kind of Precure I want to convey in my work.
You must know a lot about them, right?
Tell me what the third Precure's pose should be!
I'm shure that you're the third Precure!
Whaaaaat?!
What?! Me, a Precure?!
What are you saying, Potpourri?!
Just imagine what he would look like if he became a Precure!
I'm... a Precure!
This is a new twist...
That mushtn't happen!
Me as a Precure, huh?
Boss! Are you all right?
So that's the trespasser!
It's a scoop! An honest-to-goodness scoop!
This is a huge, huge, huge, huge scoop!
Is he an alien, or some kind of ghost?!
This mysterious figure who prowls the school grounds in search of the third Precure!
Huh?!
That couldn't be...
It's not just "could be," it is! It's totally the fairies!
All right, everyone. Settle down and take your seats, please.
Kanae, take that down.
You really shouldn't be
scaremongering like that, you know?
All right then...
Right now, the teachers are searching the grounds for this trespasser.
I have to go and join them, so none of you leave this room, all right?
Yes, ma'am...
O-Oh, it's just the tree's branches.
I'm so pathetic.
I can hardly lecture my students if I'm freaked out by something like this.
Yeah, that's right! There's no way ghosts could actually exist.
Non, non!
I know I am rather beautiful, but that's no reason to be so scared, mademoiselle.
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
We need to find shomeone to
become the third Precure shoon!
Don't worry!
I'm sure we'll find them soon!
They're lost to you, forevermore!
Wha—?!
Why, you ask? Because I shall eliminate the third fairy here and now!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
That's far enough!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
We'll take back the Flower of our teacher's Heart!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
I'm scared of ghoooosts!
Huh?
Huh?!
They're scary!
Shtop iiiiiiiiit!
Potpourri!
I can't be a good teacher to those kids if
I'm scared of something as silly as ghosts!
I just want to be composed in front of my students.
But I'm just so scared of ghosts!
So that is what made the Flower of your Heart wilt so?
How laughable.
It's because she has that ideal that she's suffering so much right now!
You're just making a joke out of her,
and I've had it up to here with this!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
This isn't over yet!
Accursed third fairy... I shall remember this!
Now then, let's give the Flower of her Heart back!
Tsubomi? Erika?
Are you all right?
Y-Yes...
I think I saw a ghost, then passed out.
A ghost?
Yeah...
You probably won't believe me, but he was a long-haired man with the most terrible face.
And then I had a dream where I turned into a ghost...
I'm so pathetic, aren't I?
I'm supposed to be an adult.
You're not pathetic at all!
That's right, Ms. Tsurusaki!
I don't think it matters if you're
scared of ghosts, even as an adult.
You're really amazing, Ms. Tsurusaki!
Everyone in our class loves you too!
That so?
Thank you.
I love you all too, you know? Every last student who's in my care.
We know!
Well then, shall we head back to the classroom?
She's a really fantastic teacher.
Everyone in this school is connected by the trust they have in each other.
Trust?
Trust...
Trust!
That's sho beautiful.
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
So that's what happened.
Sounds like it was a lot of trouble.
In the language of flowers, a
hymenanthes means "dignity."
She might be afraid of ghosts, but Ms. Tsurusaki really is brilliant!
But still, pretending to be a scout for the Precures...
It's not something to laugh about!
It caused us a ton of trouble!
It really did.
The high school's been in an uproar over it too.
But I wouldn't have believed it was the work of a new fairy.
I feel really shtrong powers from inshide you!
You musht be the third Precure!
That's right! It could be Yuri!
With Potpourri's help, you can become a Precure again!
Pleashe, I'm begging you!
You should find someone else.
I can't become your partner.
She shaid no...
Potpourri,
your destined partner isn't someone you can find by just scouting them out.
Once you and your partner are connected by a
strong bond of trust, the third Precure will be born.
Shure!
But just who could the third Precure be?
Hrm...
I hope I can meet the third Precure shoon...
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Jusht where could my Precure be?
A Precure and their fairy...
...are connected by their bond!
And that lets them stand up to any foe!
From the day they find each other...
...it'll be the start of a thrilling and heart-pounding Precure legend!
The third Precure is right in front of our eyes!
It's now or never!
I'm shure I can find them!
HeartCatch Precure:
We've Finally Found You!
The Third Precure!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!