[AL]
This place couldn't
get any creepier, huh?
[GLUTTONY]
Hello, Father...!
I brought you a
human sacrifice!
Your father? Where?!
This is happening too fast.
[FATHER]
And who is this?
[AL]
Dad?
[FATHER]
Envy?
[AL]
That thing?
Brother!
Brother?
Al?
You're back
in your armor...
So that means...
[AL GIGGLES]
We're back in
the real world.
Guess so.
[AL]
Brother!
Ow! Ouch!
- [ED] You're hurting me!
- [AL] You're safe!
[AL]
I'm so happy you're alive!
[ED]
Your spike is poking my ribs!
[AL]
I'm sorry.
But I thought...
I thought you were dead.
But I'm okay, Al.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
I worried you.
Where exactly did
we wind up though?
[FATHER]
This is
somewhat surprising.
People emerging
from his stomach.
What the-- Hohenheim?!
Steel appendages, hm...
And an armored body...
Are you two
the Elric brothers?
So you're... you're not...?
Have you mistaken me
for someone else...?
Well, hold on...
HooHennn...
The name you said...
By any chance, do you
mean Van Hohenheim?
And how is it
the two of you
are acquainted
with him?
[AL]
Well, he's our father.
He's your father...?!
This is
indeed surprising!
I had no idea
he had children.
[FATHER LAUGHING]
If you are
indeed his progeny,
then why is it that your
family name is "Elric"?
Elric is our
mother's last name!
Oh, is that so...
So, where has he been
spending his time?
Who cares...?!
Just forget him,
who the hell are you?!
And why do you look
exactly like him?!
I know that he
can't be dead...
Listen!
- [FATHER] But to think that he
- [AL] Brother!
- [FATHER] has children now...
- [AL] This guy's the one who--
It would appear
that you're injured...
And you're missing
your left hand, aren't you?
[FATHER]
There. How is
that for you?
Your arm's broken.
It... it's not
broken anymore.
Hey!
Uh... Ow!
A few broken
ribs as well.
I consider
the two of you
to be vital resources...
You must both remain
alive and healthy.
This isn't right, Al...
He performed a transmutation
without any movement at all.
[AL]
And he didn't even
thin out my armor.
[ED AND AL]
There isn't any
equivalent exchange.
[LING]
You aren't human.
What are you?!
What the hell's
inside you?!
I would ask
who you are,
but I honestly
don't care...
[FATHER]
You can go
ahead and eat him.
[GLUTTONY]
Okay!
[ED]
What?! No, hold on!
Don't!
This guy's our friend
and you want to keep
us happy, right...?
So don't kill him, please.
[FATHER]
But I have no
need for him...
Your friendship
doesn't make
him any less
useless to me.
[ED]
What did you say?
[AL]
Brother...
The Homunculi
keep calling
this guy
their father...
I think he's the one
who created them.
What?
He did heal our
wounds, though.
[LING]
He didn't heal mine.
I don't like him.
I can tell he
looks down on humans
and calls us fools.
When you notice an
insect on the ground,
do you stop to
consider it a fool?
[FATHER]
The life of an insect
is so beneath you
that it would be a
waste of your time
to even consider judging it.
That would be an
accurate summation
on my feelings
towards you humans.
Look, you might've
healed our wounds
but that does not
mean we're friends...
It's pretty apparent
that you're the root
of all this evil!
I'm taking you down...
I don't care how many
cronies you've got!
And just who are you
callin' a crony, Pipsqueak.
Pipsqueak?!
Got ya now, boss man!
[AL]
Ling!
What's going
on here?!
How does he do that?
[ED]
It's like he can transmute,
just by thinking about it!
This is a
waste of time.
[ED AND AL]
What's going on?
I can't transmute!
[LING]
Ed! Al!
What the hell
did he do to us?!
[AL]
I don't know!
Why can't we
use our alchemy?!
[ENVY LAUGHS]
You lower lifeforms
never cease to amuse me...
You get a speck of power
and you think
you own the world...
And you don't even
know what that power is.
[ENVY]
And then you have
the arrogance to assume
that you're the one who's
in control of this power...
You're like a bad joke
that keeps getting dumber.
What are you
bastards planning...?
[ED]
You promised to
tell me everything
if I got you out!
Huh?
Why, I would
never stoop so low
as to make a deal
with a worm like you.
[ED]
Liar!
[FATHER]
You talk far
too much, Envy.
Oh, sorry.
You may prove to be
rather useful to me after all.
I could always use a new
pawn in the rotation.
[AL]
Is that... a
Philosopher's Stone?!
[LING]
A what?
You're really
gonna do that?
[ED]
Do what?
He's going to make
a new Homunculus.
[ENVY]
The Stone is added
into the bloodstream...
If it's able to merge,
then a human based
Homunculus is created.
But it's more
common for the Stone
to overpower the
subject and kill them.
[ED]
I'm not gonna let
you do this to him!
[ED AND AL GRIMACING]
What is this...?!
What's going on?
Why the hell aren't
we able to transmute?!
[ED]
You bearded bastard...!
Let him go!
He's got people waiting
for him to come back...!
Get off of me!
[ENVY]
Can you really shoot
such a sad face?
Can you, boy?
[ED]
Damn you...
[LING]
Don't shoot, Ed!
This is exactly
what I want...
So you just
stay out of it!
[ED]
Are you serious?
[LING]
I came to
your land to find
a Philosopher's Stone...
And now this guy wants
to give me one...!
I'm not gonna
turn this down!
Think about
what you're doing!
[FATHER]
Well, now this is new.
But we'll see
if your body
is as willing
as your mind.
No, don't!
[LING SCREAMING]
Ling!
[LING]
I told you... to
keep out of this...
Don't you dare interfere!
[LING SCREAMING]
Stay back...
I promise that I
know what I'm doing.
They're dealing with the
future leader of Xing...
Ling... Yao--
[LING SCREAMING]
[GREED]
Am I really supposed to
use this little brat...?
Oh well... Just hand
over your body...
I guess I'll have
to make do with it.
Fine with me...
Consider it yours...
You can have it!
Huh?
I said come!
I freely accept you!
Y'know, people
normally reject me.
You're talking
to the future
emperor of Xing, monster!
I am no normal man...!
My heart is large enough
to hold twenty
or thirty or you!
[GREED LAUGHS]
Well I do like how
ambitious you are...
Just don't try
and change your mind.
I'll never
change my mind.
My vassal lost her arm
helping me search for this!
I couldn't face her again
if I came home empty-handed!
I need this power...
I need it to protect!
To provide
for my people...!
And to take my
place as ruler...!
And I accept
all of the risks!
Your avarice is
certainly appealing...
But let's see if your stomach
matches your appetite...!
Can you handle this?
[ED]
Ling?
What...? Ohh...
You mean the guy I
took this body from...?
Sorry. But your friend
just checked out
and left Greed this body.
[AL]
So... You're not Ling?
Did he say "Greed"?
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
So then... Are you...
the Greed from before?
Huh...? What are
you talkin' about?
[ED]
You don't remember us?
[AL]
From Dublith?
You must've met
some different Greed.
[FATHER]
He was my
avarice before you.
Ahh... I gotcha.
That makes sense...
But if you wanna
hear it from me,
no, I'm not the
Greed you knew.
But... Ling...
Well he was an
interesting kid.
He gave up his body
without any fight at all.
You're lying...!
Ling would never give up
and surrender
himself so easily...!
Answer me, Ling!
Ling...! Ling!
What's the matter?
[MAY CHANG]
That feeling...
It's coming from that man.
He's a human...
but also not.
No, he's not.
It doesn't look like
any of them are human.
It's Shao May...!
Oh thank goodness...!
You're okay!
I've been so
worried about you!
Ohhh...
Now that is a touching
reunion right there.
[SCAR THINKING]
So the armored boy's
not with the Homunculi.
And they've
also got Fullmetal.
Where is he?
Where is Mr. Edward?
He's right there.
He's not really here, is he?
I told you
that's him right there.
That little guy is
the Fullmetal Alchemist.
Huh?
How dare you toy
with the feelings
of a maiden,
you human microbe?!
What'd you call me,
micro-girl?!
- [AL] Brother!
- [GLUTTONY] That's the Ishvalen
- Did you do something
to this little girl!
- that I never got to eat.
- [ED] Of course not...!
- [FATHER] Another human
with his own plans.
This is the insubordinate
who's been using his destructive
alchemy to carelessly
interfere with our operation.
Go ahead
and eat him...
He doesn't
have his alchemy
to stop
you right now.
Okay!
What?!
[MAY CHANG]
You'll pay for this!
You deceived an
innocent girl...!
And you kidnapped Shao May!
You'll suffer for
what you've done...!
All of you!
'Bout time!
[AL]
It still
isn't working!
But why is theirs?!
How can you use
your alchemy here?
What do you mean?
[AL]
This doesn't
make any sense...
How can they
still transmute?
[ED]
I don't know...
I have no idea...
But I think this is our chance
to turn things around... Scar!
You wanna know the truth
about what started
the war in Ishval?
In Ishval?
[ED]
The truth about
who shot that child
and started the uprising?
He's standing right there...!
It was Envy,
disguised as a soldier!
These guys orchestrated
the entire war!
[SCAR]
I'd like to hear
more details about this.
In between your screaming.
[GLUTTONY YELLING]
Now tell me...
For what purpose did you choose
to slaughter all of my people?
Depending on your answer...
I'll send you to join God...!
No... You don't
deserve to stand by God
alongside my fallen brothers...
Your only solace from my wrath
will be damnation!
Whoa, nice...!
He's got some pretty
good moves for a human.
Greed...
Take care of
the outsiders.
Sure.
I know you're
still in there, Ling.
Nope. Just Greed.
[GREED CHUCKLES]
[MAY CHANG]
I know him.
That's Ling Yao...
Of the Yao Clan... Right?
[MAY CHANG GASPS AND SCREAMS]
A little girl!
[GLUTTONY]
You'll make a
perfect appetizer!
Let's talk a moment.
How are you able
to use your alchemy?
Hmm...
Well, you are clearly
still transmuting.
Physical destruction...
no, decomposition, is it?
[SCAR THINKING]
If I had jumped
one second later...
I'd be a dead man.
Mr. Scar!
No, Shao May...
You need to run!
Time to eat you!
[AL]
You alright?
I never asked
you to help me.
Save the stubborn
pride for later...!
These people kill anyone
they don't have a use for.
We're getting you out of here!
There's too many of them.
You two?
I thought you'd
made it outside.
[AL]
Scar...
Can you make it to the
surface with this girl?
You would allow
me to escape...?
Even though I'm
the one responsible
for the deaths of
your friend's parents?
Yeah, well...
I'd rather beat
you senseless...
And it makes me sick
to have to ask
you for help.
But right now...
we need to save
this girl's life.
What do you
plan on doing?
I don't understand it...
but for some reason
I'm important to them.
They're not
gonna kill me...
They said they
need me alive.
I doubt that I'd be able
to get her safely
to the surface
with the condition
I'm in right now...
And I have no intention
of turning my back
on this place just yet!
Wait, what
are you doing?
Geez...! Couldn't you
have warned me first...?
What a rude thing to do.
[ENVY]
I guess you
think it was clever,
igniting the
hydrogen like that?
Where did he go?
You better tell me now!
[AL]
I have no idea!
[ENVY]
Get up and track
his scent, Gluttony!
You've used up your
regenerative power...!
Your body's dying.
That was a good solid kick...
This should be more
entertaining than I expected!
You idiot prince!
Wake up, Ling!
The name's Greed.
Shut up...
Give Ling his body back!
[GREED]
Sorry,
can't do that!
[FIGHTING NOISES]
Give up already, you idiot!
What about your country...?!
Have you forgotten
all about Lan Fan?!
[GREED]
Hey, Pops...!
I caught 'im for you.
Upstairs... I want him
taken directly to Wrath.
Man... you guys
really made a mess
of things,
didn't you...
[ENVY]
If you had simply
behaved yourselves,
then we would've let
you go a long time ago.
[AL]
Brother.
He's in there...
I know it.
Ling's alive.
[FATHER]
I see that you've exhausted
the regenerative
powers of the Stone.
There's no need to worry...
Fear not, my son.
I'll recreate you
when the time is right.
With all of your
memories intact.
[NARRATOR]
Humans will always be
drawn to create chaos
around them and they
will always choose
to spend their days in pain.
This is what reminds
them that they are alive.
But if this is the
reminder that you need,
kneel before me
and I'll show you
just how alive you are.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Twenty-nine...
Struggle of the Fool.
Is a man still
capable of standing
if his arms and legs
have been taken from him?