What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby at Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappea
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
I hate everything about this.
This sunshine, beating down on you all day,
these completely empty-headed students,
and having to hike up this steep slope every single day
just to get to school.
It all makes me want to puke.
Nishimi Kaoru
Joining us starting today is Nishimi Kaoru, all the way from Yokosuka.
It seems he was at the top of his class at his previous school.
I hope all of you study just as hard.
Nishimi Kaoru
I'm Nishimi. Nice to meet you.
Yokosuka?
Isn't that far?
I'm used to this routine. But...
He looks like a real nerd...
Spoiled rich kid...
Their unreserved stares...
Their Kyushu dialect that I can't follow...
This is the most memorable welcome I've received to date.
Nishimi. Nishimi!
Have you decided what club you're gonna join?
Are you interested in radios at all?
Look at that weirdo, Maruo!
Two four-eyed bookworm runts!
It's like they're made for each other!
S-Sorry. Because of me, they picked on you, too...
Infantile creeps like that can't do anything unless they're in a pack.
I'm not interested in them.
Nishimi...
I've no interest in radios, either.
Nishimi, one thing...
Whatever you do, don't mess with the guy who sits behind me.
He's a notorious thug that even the teacher can't manage.
His name is Kawabuchi and if he zeros in on you,
it's all over.
Oh, no.
Just thinking about it makes me feel nauseous...
Nishimi...
Nishimi?
I'm Mukae Ritsuko, the class representative.
I was instructed to show you around the school during lunch.
Nice to meet you.
Suddenly... I don't feel so bad.
So, the gym is back there.
And the infirmary is in this building...
A-Are you okay, Nishimi?!
What d'you think you're doin'?!
Whoops! Guess it just slipped!
Sorry 'bout that!
What is it?
Who's that?
Never saw 'im before...
Um... Mukae, where's the roof?
I've moved from school to school ever since first grade...
Any time something unexpected happened, I would lose my equilibrium,
and even minor stress would make me sick.
After losing my bearings so many times,
I finally found one place I could get them back.
Right. If I can just get to the roof...
What's this?
You finally...
came for me?
Who the hell are you?
Why you holdin' my hand?
You're the one that grabbed my hand!
I get it...
You're the key burglar, huh?
In that case, I ain't gonna hold back.
Are you Sentaro?
Lookin' for something?
Then you goons are the thieves, eh?
The roof belongs to the senior smokers!
W-Wait!
I want the key to the roof.
Get the hell outta here you candyass!
You want the key that badly?
I-I do!
Hold this for me.
H-Hey! Are you all right?!
Hey, come on, wake up!
How reckless can you be?
Going up against three seniors...
This is what you wanted, right?
Can I really have it?
Yeah, here.
For 100,000.
Don't tell me you thought I'd give it to you for nothin'?
I just put my ass on the line.
100,000 is nothin'.
Dammit!
Well, I'm goin' home.
Come to think of it, I didn't even go to class once today, though...
City boy like that's got no common ground with us country boys.
I can't believe you, Sentaro! You got in another fight?!
It's just some scratches...
You... Hey!
Riko, who's this guy?
I ain't gonna answer a guy who does nothin' but fight.
Maruo! You tell me.
H-He's Nishimi Kaoru. He just transferred in today,
supposed to be rich, a real brainiac...
Oh?
Later, Maruo!
Hi there, rich boy.
From now on, your name is "Richie."
Let's be pals, eh?
Sentaro's got a new target.
It's curtains for him.
I feel sorry for him.
Oh, no... I feel sick again...
Sorry. I've got a favor to ask...
Huh?
I can't pay 100,000, but could you lend me the key just this once?
Oh, this?
But right now it's—
Hey! It's raining out!
Then I'll take an umbrella!
It sounds like fun! I'll go, too!
What the hell? This ain't much fun at all.
Of course not. I'm not up here to have fun.
Then why bother comin' up here?
If you're bored, you can always go back.
Nah.
Class ain't my style.
D-Don't follow me!
You're creepin' me out!
This feels good...
Richie, you take a shower, too!
Leave me alone!
What're you scared of, huh?
Nothin' good ever comes outta fear.
Let yourself get a little wet!
What on earth?!
The both of you...
I swear...
Causing me all this grief...
We're going straight to the infirmary to get a towel!
Oh, that's right. I'll get your gym clothes!
I'll meet you there!
Is this jazz?
What, you can tell?
Well, sort of...
I play piano.
Just classical music though...
Classical, huh?
What a drag...
Okay, I'm here.
Huh? Where's the nurse?
Looks like she's out...
I didn't notice with your glasses on,
but you have a really pretty face, Nishimi.
W-What?
Oh, is it rude to call a man pretty?
Handsome maybe?
N-No, I'm not...
W-What are you doing?!
I'm a human hair dryer, is all!
Sentaro!
There he goes again, bein' scared.
Scaredy-cat!
I'm not scared!
Oh?
What's there to be afraid of?
And actually, the rain felt great.
Way better than I thought...
It's strange.
Even with everyone staring at me, I can breathe normally...
What kind of magic is this?
That's great, Dad!
Being able to play the piano, even while being a sailor?
Kaoru, I'm going to be away again for quite a while.
Be a good boy while I'm gone, okay?
When I play the piano, I can forget all the sadness
and loneliness from Dad being away.
Don't worry, Kaoru.
Your uncle in Kyushu has a huge grand piano.
But Dad, I don't want a grand piano...
What I want is...
Oh, Kaoru.
You're up really early today, huh?
You wanna play the piano?
Go for it.
Mariko wants to hear a tune that'll wake her right up.
But playing this early in the morning would be—
But I wanna hear it right now!
Mariko will take responsibility, so please!
Please please please!
All right, fine.
Dad...
Excuse me? What do you think you're doing?
Playing the piano at this hour...
What's the matter with you?!
I'm sorry, Auntie.
Mariko wanted—
See?
This is why I told you to stop it...
Putting the blame on someone else...
I guess it's difficult for a father to raise a child all alone...
Although it's your mother's fault for abandoning the both of you...
Nishimi!
Mukae...
Sentaro didn't come today, huh?
Maybe you're lonely without him here?
Sorry. I don't get what you mean.
I'll be quite pleased if he sees fit to extend his absence.
I-I see...
Looked to me like you two were hitting it off...
Everyone else is afraid of Sentaro, but you act normally in front of him.
I bet you two could become buddies, Nishimi.
Mukae... Cut it out with that smile...
Really, as his childhood friend, I can guarantee it.
Childhood friend?
So that's why you two are on a first name basis.
Oh, you can call me by my first name too, Nishimi.
And then maybe I'll call you Kaoru.
Kaoru, Kaoru, Kaoru...
W-What's with the echo?
Sorry, I probably shoulda asked first. If you don't like it...
No, it's fine! I don't mind it at all...
Oh, that's right... Ritsu...
Yes?
Do you happen to know of a record shop in town that sells classical music?
Records? We've got tons of records at my place!
You should come over!
You know what I really mean, don't you... Kaoru?
I-I think things are moving too fast...
Is this how Kyushu girls are?
This is our shop...
And this is my father!
Fath—
M-My name is Nishimi Kaoru.
Your daughter has been wonderful...
The classical records are over on that shelf, Kaoru.
Right.
What sorta records are you lookin' for?
Well, like piano music...
I play the piano myself, you see...
You play the piano?!
Oh, it's not a big deal...
C'mere!
Ritsuko! Outsiders aren't allowed in there.
Dad, Kaoru is a good friend of mine and Sentaro.
Sen's friend?
No, I'm not his friend, just a—
Come on, go in.
Go ahead.
What is this?
What the hell are you doin' here?!
Th-That's what I should ask you!
Ri'ko! We got an intruder!
Listen to this, Sentaro! Kaoru says he can play piano!
Yeah, I know, I know.
But I bet you anything it's just rich kid, stuffed shirt, classical stuff.
Jazz is the only music for me.
Kaoru... Kaoru?
Say, Kaoru, go on and play the piano!
Oh, I don't...
Ri'ko, only jazz is allowed in here!
If it's the piano you want, I'll play it.
Oh, I know this piece...
I can't hear any more. It's like this.
Wrong! That ain't even close!
What're you talking about?! I played it exactly right!
There wasn't any swing!
If you aren't feelin' it, it just ain't jazz to me!
Say, I'd love to hear you two do a session together!
What?!
Nah, Ri'ko. That's a no-go.
This guy don't get jazz and he's got no sense for it.
A little practice and playing it'll be a cinch!
Hmph!
Thank you for having me over.
Um, Kaoru!
Come back again, okay?
Ritsu, do you know the name of the tune he was playing on the piano?
Um...
The only thing Sen can play on the piano is the intro to this.
"Moanin'," by Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers.
I'd like this, please.
Wasn't he here to buy classical music?
Yeah...
I don't know why,
but his drums just won't stop thundering in my head.
Kaoru?
W-What?
Aren't you walking strange?
Really? This is how I always walk.
Ow!
Ri'ko! Richie! See ya!
You're running down this slope that I hate so much like it's nothing...
What can you see beyond the hill?
Is it an outlook that I've been blind to?
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change