When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right
Hey, Nagi Sanzenin! Come quietly
and fall prey to this robot!
Don't be ridiculous! Why should I?!
Naritasan
Ah! That's because there's someone who
will profit greatly by your death!
Impossible, for five reasons!
What?
Firstly, you are stupid!
Secondly, you are incredibly stupid!
Thirdly, you are infinitely stupid!
Fourthly, you are cosmically
and revolutionarily stupid!
And fifthly...
I've heard enough! Die!
HAYATE!
Wha?!
You called, Miss?
Hayate!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Who? Me? Well...
Hurry! The opening sequence
is about to start!
What? Oh! Uh, um, I came to
the Sanzenin household to...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal
guardian, who is there to
support his mistress in
all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Wait, the narration's too early!
I'm, um...
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Tell me, Mr. Santa, why
don't you bring me presents?
Ah, that's because your family is poor.
What?! B-But then, what am I supposed to do?!
Work, lad!
If a man will not work, he shall not eat!
If there's something you want, do something about it yourself.
B-But...
But have faith.
The one to have the last laugh will surely...
...be he, who is honest and hard-working.
Mr. Santa!
But well, I'm still not
bringing you any presents.
What?! Wait! What's that supposed to mean?!
Wait a minute!
Hey!
That last thing he said bothered me,
but even so, I decided to believe
in Santa's words and live by them.
That is, until today!
What are we going to do?!
Five more minutes!
If we don't get the manuscript
in five more minutes...!
Oh, this week's edition is doomed!
Please relax!
The fastest bike messenger in the
industry will be here shortly!
The fastest?
Here he comes! That's him!
Thank you for waiting!
I am the bike messenger Hayate Ayasaki
Your signature, please.
In English, "Unmei" Means "Destiny"
Thank you, fastest bike
messenger in the industry,
with the tremendously sturdy
and superhuman body!
But kid, are you really all right?
Please don't worry.
I work out.
Well, then, we look forward
to being of service again.
Oh, wait, kid!
I'm fine!
Really.
No! In front! In front of you!
Be Careful You Damn Bicycles
Suginami Ward
Sorry! Are you all right?!
Poor kid. And he's such an admirable boy.
Yes,
that boy is horribly unlucky.
Ow, that hurt.
Sheesh.
And it's Christmas Eve, too.
Yes! At around this time,
the boy was still...
...a totally unremarkable
high school student,
who attended a totally unremarkable
public high school.
Hey there, Hayate.
Why hello!
My totally unremarkable classmates,
who attend the totally unremarkable
public high school!
Well, sorry for being unremarkable.
So what's up? You're all together.
Oh, let me guess. A Christmas party?
Yeah, come if you're not busy.
I'm really looking forward to the party.
It's all you can eat and
drink for just 3000 yen.
Yeah.
We gotta eat a lot, 3000 yen's worth.
Uh, but I don't have any money, and
I'm still working my part-time job.
Better bring your A-game!
As unsociable as ever, aren't you?
Hayate, you're athletic,
so you should join a
sports team at school or something.
But that would cut into my time for work.
Darn you! All you talk about is work!
What are you, money-mad?!
You can't buy friendship with money!
Why do you need so much money anyway?
That's because... uh...
My parents are unemployed...?
S-Sorry, I think we got
kind of carried away there.
Later!
Yes, for example,
if they were laid off
because of the bad economy,
there would be some room for sympathy.
However, with Hayate's father...
Father
Yeah! Ever heard of self-realization?!
I think there's a much more suitable
job for me out there somewhere!
With his head in the clouds, he's an
insanely unproductive member of society.
Mother
Woohoo! It's not as if I'm
frittering our money away!
I'm investing in my dreams!
And his mother also neglects the housework,
throwing away money left and right.
If a man will not work, he shall not eat!
But I have faith!
The one to have the last laugh will surely...
Surely, it'll be he, who's
honest and hard-working!
Ayasaki, you're fired.
You've been lying about
your age, haven't you?
I hear you're still in high school.
H-How did you know that?!
Your parents came by earlier and told me.
I thought you were a serious
and capable young man.
You let me down.
I turned over the 170,000 yen you
earned so far this month to them.
Y-You gave it to them?
Hand over that kind of
money to those parents,
and they're bound to fritter it all
away, investing in their dreams!
That's absurd. What parents would do that?
My parents! That's why I lied
about my age to work part-time!
This can't be happening...
But even they must know that this
money need to be spent carefully...
Dad! Mom!
Where are my wages?!
Wages
Thank goodness! They haven't spent it yet!
Sorry! I tried "investing in my
dream", but it didn't work out.
Teehee. Mom.
H-How are we supposed to make
it to next year on this?
We don't even have any savings left.
To Hayate.
A Christmas Present for you.
What's this?
Ones, tens, hundreds,
thousands, ten thousands,
hundred thousands, millions,
ten millions, hundred million?!
An IOU for 156,804,000 yen?!
We borrowed money from
some very generous people.
Mother
Father
So, we'll be counting on you to pay it off.
You idiots!
To Hayate
Sorry, I got carried away gambling... no real helping it.
But well, what's done is done.
D-Don't just brush it off!
But it'll be tedious to work if off
and our family has no money left.
Mommy and Daddy gave it a lot of thought,
and we came up with a brilliant idea.
Brilliant idea?
We know!!
We'll give Hayate as a present by way of an apology!!!
It's Christmas, after all.
D-Dad! Mom!
Hey! Mr. Ayasaki, are you here?
We've come for your boy!
Could it be that you're the
"very generous people"?
You bet.
We're the "very generous people"
folk who lent your parents money.
C-Come on, Mr. Very Generous People,
my parents, who owe you the
debt, aren't here anymore.
Besides, there's no way I can
pay back 156,804,000 yen...
You ain't got nothin' to worry 'bout.
We're pros here, too.
If ya just come with us...
For example, ya could go
to a tropical paradise
and devote yerself to free volunteer work.
Or ya could find employment
with a global courier service.
Oh, becomin' a consultant,
who teaches the value of traffic
etiquette, could be good, too.
Well, we'll be able to help
ya out in a lotta ways.
Hey! Hold it right there, sonny boy!
I've managed to get away somehow, but...
I never thought they'd go so far.
My parents are unbelievable.
No matter how many times I look at it,
I guess it's still 156,804,000 yen.
I guess I've been abandoned for real.
But have faith.
The one to have the last laugh will surely...
NO!
In the end, it's the dishonest
guys who win in this world!
There's nothing to gain from
working hard at honest jobs!
Nello from "A Dog of Flanders" stayed
a nice guy and he wound up dead!
What is wrong with this machine?!
Does it not take credit cards?!
It was the fateful encounter of boy and girl.
Hayate the Combat Butler
(Hayate no Gotoku)
Christmas.
(Kurisumasu)
We lost him.
Spry kid, that one.
Find him, even if you have to
search every nook and cranny.
And you two, this isn't
even close to being enough.
If you don't bring it all by tomorrow,
you know what's coming, right?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Debt collectors of their kind...
They'll never let me get away, no matter what.
That's exactly right.
You're finished!
Don't fight it, just turn
yourself over to those guys...
O Hayate, you mustn't ever give up.
You were born a man and thus,
you must continue to strive to the very end.
Hah! What the hell can he do now?
Let us kidnap that girl.
Huh?
We shall kidnap her and gratefully
accept 150 million yen in ransom.
Good idea.
H-Hey, don't you think that's a bad
idea, no matter what the situation?
But my very life's in danger because
of those worthless parents of mine!
That is right. A modicum of
villainy should be permitted.
No, it ought to be permitted!
Don't do it!
Even Nello and Patrasche are
surely in Heaven right now,
exhorting you to avenge them.
Yeah, and even if I get caught, I'll
have warm meals and a bed in prison.
See here! Do not touch me!
Hey, hey, you're cute!
All alone on the night of Christmas Eve?
Come someplace fun with us.
Don't go hitting on girls on the
anniversary of Nello's death!
Go look at a Rubens painting
and observe it in mourning!
You fools!
H-Hey...
I've never even been hit by my dad!
Sorry about that!
Sh-Shoot, I automatically leapt
out at them without thinking...
Thank you.
I don't really get it, but you saved me.
By the way, do you understand how this works?
Huh?
Warm
I want this thing labeled "warm",
but it will not come out,
even when I press the button.
Well, you need to put in a
100 yen coin or something...
Without this "warm" thing,
I will freeze to death!
It's not good for a girl to
catch a chill, so wear that.
What a cheap-looking coat.
The craftsmanship is shoddy
and the fabric is heavy.
On top of which, it's too baggy for me.
But it's warm. I like it.
Yes, I shall do something for you
in thanks for this "warm" thing.
In thanks?
It can be anything. Just name it.
Anything... Really?
Yes!
I know! Since it's come to this,
I have no choice but to go for it!
In that moment, the boy found his resolve.
In thanks for his help, he would ask her...
...to be his hostage, so
he could demand ransom.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
Sure, sure.
Won't you go with me?
What?
I want you!
His questionable choice of words...
...was to thoroughly complicate
their relationship!
Idio... It may be Christmas Eve, but
to make a sudden confession like that?!
D-Do you know exactly what it
is that you're asking here?!
I could never joke about something like this.
This is life or death.
From the moment I first
laid eyes on you, I...
I decided that I would take you away with me!
His earnestness is conveyed.
However, whether it is
conveyed accurately or not...
...is a different story.
A-All right.
But in exchange...
Absolutely no cheating or anything, got it?!
Huh? Uh...
Sure.
Cheating?
Well, whatever.
Then, would you tell me your
guardian's phone number?
Okay.
Then wait here for a sec.
My heart's still pounding.
But that boy is strong and kind.
He's just so cool!
To Hayate
Hayate... Is that his name?
Haya...
Now, to make an anonymous ransom demand.
No one can stop me now!
Yes, hello?
Oh, hello? This is Ayasaki.
What's a kidnapper doing introducing himself?
It's over. My perfect plan...
And it hadn't even begun.
Daddy, Mommy, why isn't he wearing
a coat when it's so cold out?
Shh!
Yeah, in the end, this is pretty
much how it goes for me.
Whether I try to do honest
work or commit a crime,
it's never going to work out.
I feel so tired somehow.
If I just fell asleep now, would I die?
But that'd be fine, too.
There's nothing but pain, even
if I were to stay alive...
No one would care if I died anyway...
Are you all right?
This is terrible! You're so cold!
You will catch a cold if you sleep out here.
He was blindsided.
This kind smile...
To the boy's heart, frozen
in life's pit of despair,
it apparently made quite an impact.
What? Um, wait...
Patrasche, I was wrong.
There are incredibly kind people
in this world, like her.
And yet, I was going to do something
foolish like kidnapping...
What are you doing?!
Don't make a fuss!
That's right! What am I doing?!
Quit dragging your feet!
Hey!
Get in there already!
What?
Oh, dear! That child! She's
getting kidnapped again!
Are you an acquaintance of hers?
Yes. What shall I do? And
Himegami isn't here, either.
I'm going to borrow this.
You call the police.
I will rescue her!
Rescue her? But they're in a car!
That's right! This anime will
never condone brutal crimes!
Kidnapping is not cool!
All right, the kidnapping's a success!
Now, we'll be able to rustle up a
fat ransom and pay off our debt!
Hey, you two idiots.
You're polluting the air, so would
you do me a favor and stop breathing?
You're destroying the environment.
You have to take good care of Earth.
Y-You damn brat!
If you make us mad...
I told you not to breathe, didn't I, baldy?!
You keep that up and you're
seriously gonna get hurt!
Stay away from me, pervert!
Come any closer and I'm
calling for help, you fool!
You're the fool, little girl!
You think there's anyone who can
catch up to a car going this fast?!
Sure there is!
He said he would risk his
life to take me away!
So if I call for him, he'll come!
Then why don't you try calling
him right this minute?
HAYATE!
What?!
Hayate...
You scoundrels! Give that
girl back without a fuss!
B-Bro!
Shuddup! H-He suddenly jumped in front of me!
How dare you two...!
Would you please return that girl to me?
Y-Yes, sir!
Hayate!
Hey, shut up and walk.
What the hell was that guy?
Come on.
Hey, are you all right?
Please don't worry. I work out.
I'm really glad that you're all right.
It seems I must thank you again.
You don't have to thank me.
I very nearly...
Huh? What is it? No need to hold back.
Tell me whatever you want.
Then, this time, could you
maybe find me... a new job...
H-Hey!
A-Are you really all right?!
There's some kind of red
liquid coming out of you!
This is nothing... Just a bit too
much to put on the airwaves...
These scrapes on my head,
abdomen, and four limbs...
Hayate!
Hey, Hayate!
Nagi!
Ah! Maria!
Perfect timing! We need to treat him quickly!
I did contact Mr. Klaus and
ask him to come pick us up...
But this is...
Where in the world did
you get that shabby coat?
Uh, this is certainly a
pitifully cheaply-made coat,
but it's a coat that my savior
was kind enough to give to me.
I would disgrace the Sanzenin name
if I didn't wear it with care, right?
Your... savior?
That reminds me! We had yet to find
a replacement for Himegami, right?
Let's make it him!
Pardon?
We'll transport the injured in this car!
No need! Everything is taken care of!
I promised that I would find him a new job.
And I owe him.
So I will make him Nagi
Sanzenin's new butler!
Yes, it was truly a fateful encounter.
As of this night, the boy's fate
begins to change greatly, but...
Check back with us for more details.
We will continue to fight the broadcast
regulations again next time!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Preview
Hayate, you were looking
for live-in work, right?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Y-Yes.
Then why don't you work as
my butler at this house?
B-But Hayate doesn't even
know what a butler does...
I'll do it! No matter what happens,
I, Hayate Ayasaki, will put my life
on the line and protect you, Miss!
What am I going to do with
these two clueless people?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"A New Beginning with
Nagi Sanzenin's Estate"!
So we finally meet again, sonny boy.
A New Beginning with
Nagi Sanzenin's Estate
Frankly, the next episode's
going to be funny-cool, too!
Please watch "Hayate the Combat
Butler" again next time.