What was that all about, Inaba?
Iori is mine!
Stay away from her!
There's no reason for you to complain.
I made it clear that you and Fujishima are rivals.
If you work hard enough,
you can rescue Iori from Fujishima's clutches.
I set the stage for you.
I don't want to make an enemy out of a classmate.
Everyone but you yourself is an enemy.
Huh?
Hey, Taichi.
Do you have a crush on Iori?
What?!
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
What if you laugh more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
The comic I read just now was cool.
I want to eat curry now.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry, you gotta
drink more milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Cooks curry
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
me yui
AAAAA
We should get married
I love you
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to eat a
pot of curry.
Wonder if I should.
The whole world
Let's go
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry
I can't go out with you
It'd be bad
I don't have the homework
for tomorrow
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Every month
on the 25th
Deadline
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
I have a crush on Nagase?
Why would you think that?
You've been overreacting to everything recently.
As I recall, you used to be more of a stoic lump.
My reactions have been fairly reasonable considering the situation we're in.
I'm telling you to bag Iori before Fujishima beats you to it.
Why do you keep pushing me in that direction?
And Fujishima's a girl!
The white knight facing adversity to save someone fits you perfectly, don't you think?
Right?
Selfless freak.
Jobber and Low Blow
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what I said.
Why did you volunteer for this painful exercise?
Nobody else wanted to participate, so I had to volunteer
to make sure no one else would have to suffer.
Hence, selfless freak.
Why do you like pro wrestling?
It's the art of enduring.
In pro wrestling,
it's not about who can perform stronger and flashier moves.
Special moves can only be performed on opponents who are able to endure them.
I'm a big fan of the ones who let themselves get beat up.
Shut the hell up, wrestling freak.
You're the one who asked!
So, back to Iori.
Haven't you noticed yet?
She's the weakest link in the SCS.
I've never seen anyone so close to completely breaking down.
Isn't that what you're looking for?
She needs someone to shield her from the pain and suffering.
Sounds like a job for the white knight, don't you think?
Don't put words in my mouth.
I've never thought that way about her.
I should probably mention that Iori has a crush on you.
Yeah, right...
Weak reaction.
She needs someone to cling to.
Someone who will be there to unconditionally support her.
Besides, you and Iori come alive when you're together.
Really?
Well, it's your problem to work out.
Do whatever you want.
But...
I have a feeling that Iori's in the most danger.
Danger?
This personality swapping business could break any one of us eventually,
but she's the one who's taking the brunt of the adverse effects.
Adverse effects?
But so far, we've only had to deal with a few minor hiccups.
You don't have to be so serious about it—
Are you retarded?!
How can you be so optimistic?!
There's no question about it.
You're the most clueless one in our group!
Do you realize how serious our current situation is?!
It's only a matter of time until one of us gets seriously hurt!
Don't you understand?
Sorry...
Yeah...
Well, I was too harsh.
I've been feeling like shit after everything that's happened.
Sorry.
Can you forgive me?
There's nothing to forgive.
You're absolutely right.
It's okay.
W-Well, let's get back to work.
We'll never finish at this rate.
You're completely clueless.
Huh?
Your trash bag was blown away by the wind.
Wh-Why didn't you say something?!
Where'd it go?
Ah, there it is!
It was more entertaining this way.
Y-You see...
Student Cultural Society
I'm always yelling at you
because I don't want to admit how I truly feel,
Student Cultural Society
but deep down...
Deep down, I truly love you, Aoki.
I'm sorry about springing this on you now.
But I can't continue lying to myself.
Please go out with me!
Did you get all that?
I did.
Okay, switch!
Y-Yeah...
W-Well, I kinda...
U-Um...
I like you!
So would you please go out with me?
Yeah, that was good!
I felt a real twinge seeing the usually manly Inaba confess like a girl!
The first recording was probably taken from one of your fantasies.
I know, right?
Man,
I hope I can get her to say those words one day.
Well, that should be enough for now.
I'll delete the video.
Hey, we're just getting started.
Let's take a few more shots before the girls get back from shopping.
We may never get a chance like this again.
Right?
Say what?
Yui! Grab the cell phones!
I'm on it!
Burnable
It's hard to move around in this body!
Taichi, you need to exercise more!
W-Well, I kinda...
U-Um...
I like you!
So would you please go out with me?
I see that you boys were having fun.
Um, Inaba? What are you doing?
I'm getting ready to go streaking across campus.
P-Please stop, Inaba!
If you do that, you'll be killing any chance I have of leading
a normal life!
Then die.
Wait, Inaba!
Inaba!
If you do this, I might kill myself for real!
You want that blood on your hands?!
Shut the hell up! This is justice!
Don't expect to survive if you try that again.
Yes, ma'am!
We're very sorry.
I'm just as mad as she is.
I'll beat the crap out of you if you try that again.
Pizza Chips
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Iori isn't here yet?
Yeah, she had to leave early for something.
Oh, hey.
I've been wondering about something.
Yui, are you scared of us?
Every time I'm Yui,
I start to shake whenever there's a man around.
That's nonsense.
Why would I be scared of a couple of weaklings...
...like you?
U-Uh, Yui...
After all, I'm way stronger than you guys are.
So...
So men don't scare me.
Pizza
Chips
Sorry!
I kept telling you how I loved you,
but I never realized that you were hurting.
I'm...
such an idiot!
Yui!
Forget it.
I'll go help her calm down.
Inaba...
You knew?
Yeah...
She was good at concealing her fear,
so I can't blame you for not noticing.
But she's got it pretty bad.
I can help her get back on her feet.
You guys will have to take it from there.
I hate myself now.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Her acting was good enough to impress Inaba.
I mean, I didn't notice anything when I was Kiriyama...
But in retrospect, the signs were there.
When you look at the SCS,
Inaba is always mad and beats us up all the time.
Iori is all touchy-feely.
Yui is an active girl,
so it seemed odd that she never joined in.
You're pretty perceptive, Aoki.
We're talking about the girl I love.
You're still the same person you were,
even after this whole personality swapping mess.
I like to live in the moment and enjoy life.
That's my philosophy,
and it'll never change.
I'm hoping that we'll be able to look back on this body swapping business one day and laugh.
But that doesn't seem likely anymore
now that I've hurt Yui.
Pizza Chips
Why am I getting all serious?!
This isn't me!
I'm starting to think that you could really go places.
I know.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
Inaba
I'm going to walk Yui home.
I'm leaving my bag in the club room.
If you touch it...
You can guess what will happen.
You know,
I think you have a better chance with Yui than I do.
You said all those nice things about me earlier,
but you have way more potential than I do.
What kind of potential are we talking about?
Well, you're pretty clueless, so you haven't realized how incredible you are.
I have no idea where to go from here.
Yeah, how can we help Kiriyama?
See?
That's what makes you incredible!
You're thinking about how to help her.
You think on a higher level.
Well, it's not like I have any great ideas.
It's scary because I can see you pulling it off.
But if that happens,
would Yui fall for you?
What are you...
I need to call Yui and apologize!
Taichi, I won't let you beat me!
Really?
Sure.
If that's what you want, Mom.
Do you like this group?
Yeah, they're okay.
Actually, there's a pro wrestling special on tonight!
After this show is over.
Right...
Kiriyama...
Yeah, is this Kiriyama?
U-Um, I was probably crying,
but don't let it concern you.
Just forget it ever happened.
Kiriyama,
can we meet up somewhere?
Sorry, I kinda panicked and freaked out your sister.
She's been confused by my behavior.
Anyway...
Aoki called me right before we switched.
He kept apologizing.
Over and over.
I realized that you and Aoki would probably start tiptoeing around me,
and we wouldn't be able to have fun the way we used to.
The thought alone made me feel sorry for myself.
Kiriyama, do you suffer from androphobia?
Yes.
Something must've triggered it.
Could you tell me what?
I should've known you'd get straight to the point.
You're the second person besides Inaba I've talked to about this.
Back when I was in middle school,
I was almost raped.
Nothing happened, though.
I fought back and managed to escape.
Still, this was back when I practiced karate every day.
I won against every guy I faced.
I was convinced that I could fend off anyone who attacked me.
But when it really happened,
I barely managed to escape.
Do you realize...
how physically imposing men can be?
That's when I realized that I wouldn't be able to fight off a man.
Hey, Kiriyama.
What do you want to do?
I'd rather not say.
I want to help.
That's the problem.
If I say anything to you,
I'll be asking for help.
Is that so wrong?
I don't want to cause other people trouble.
Personally, I think you'll be more trouble as long as you have androphobia.
How can you say that?!
I don't want to live like this!
But...
Then let me help you!
You don't want to live like this, right?
Isn't that what you said?
I'm going to teach you the way to defeat any man.
Y-You're kinda scaring me.
Just watch and learn.
Grab me.
Th-That hurts just to watch.
What's wrong with you?
But now you know.
One blow is all it takes to...
I'm back!
Serves you right.
I've never been in more pain in my life.
I thought I was gonna die.
Huh?
Taichi, someone's coming this way.
Hey, shouldn't we hide?
This could get out of hand if anyone saw us.
Go on without me.
I'm finished...
Stop trying to play hero!
Uh, that wasn't my intention.
Um, excuse me?
Shoot!
Geez!
Hurry up!
Ki-Kiriyama, this should be far enough.
Huh? I guess.
No way.
When did I...
You didn't seem to have a problem that time.
That's because I was desperate.
Besides, it's just you.
Anyway, what was that about?
Why should a girl have to experience the pain of a man?
But it worked, right?
I guess it did...
Does that work on every man?
Yeah, it's not just me.
Really...
That kind of pain would leave them paralyzed.
One blow is all I need to win.
I'll practice at home.
What terrible weapon have I unleashed upon the world?
Hey,
why did you do that for me?
You even hurt yourself in the process.
That's what friends do.
That's so you.
Thanks, Taichi.
Yaegashi...
Were you with a girl in the District 5 park last night?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Were you the person I saw struggling
with a small girl with long hair?
I always pass by that park when I walk my dog.
Y-You've got the wrong person.
Very well.
I may have been seeing things.
I apologize for the false accusation.
And here I thought I caught you in the act of cheating.
'Sup, Taichi!
Hey, Kiriyama...
Hey, hey, hey.
C-Could you stop that?
Guess what, Taichi?
I might get back into martial arts and pro wrestling,
so tell me what you know.
Yeah, you bet.
How about right now?
Not right now. Not right now.
Maybe later.
I need to get going.
You can move on, Kiriyama.
What was that about?
Huh?
Whoa!
Did something happen between the two of you last night?!
That must be it!
I-It wasn't anything special.
I just gave her a little advice.
Well, it's none of my business.
It's definitely my business!
How are you guys so close after one conversation?!
Hey, let's have a strategy meeting, Iori!
What? But it's none of my business!
Well?
No, it really wasn't anything special.
I just gave Kiriyama a little push.
I guess this personality swapping business
can actually do some good.
I was convinced that it would destroy us...
Inaba?
Inaba!
Inaba, what's wrong?
Hey, Inaba!
Inaba!
Next Time
Twin Feelings
Do you want to know more about me, Taichi?
You need to take care of your own body.
I thought he might've been responsible.
Am I your enemy?
It's stupid that I'm actually touched.
My daily life, gone with the flow of time
seemed like a dream beyond what my senses could appreciate
I don't understand, I don't understand
So I mumble, still little more than a child, and dream
Maybe I'm a coward
It shouldn't matter
I wish I could be stronger
Onto that sort of facade,
my weak cries,
scattered feelings,
and changing intentions
the sun shone
You were the only one that mattered to me
I knew that
Maybe
.              .
hi       to
ra        n
do      m
.               .
.              .
If we do our best
me yui
I love my sister
Tune in next time!
Inaba
Let's go!