Haruka's Room
Number 2
Haruka's Room!
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
"All the women of the world belong to me. Inside my mind, that is!"
Please welcome the famous lecher, Manabe Yoshihisa!
I'm Manabe Yoshihisa. Nice to meet you!
We're both first-year students and are in the same class at Midorigaoka High School.
We are also in love with each other!
I always have Kotoura on my mind!
We're lovey-dovey!
Yahoo!
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
Manabe, what do you think about your habit of
having more than a normal amount of erotic fantasies
and troubling those around you?
Excuse me?
I know you were fantasizing about big-breasted women just now.
If you like big breasts so much, go to some country full of big-breasted women.
A country full of... big-breasted women?!
Stop it! Stop imagining a country full of big-breasted women!
We're on camera!
That's not... My breasts aren't that big...
S-Stop it!
The End