I'm sorry
I'm hungry
I hope everyone's okay
I hope I can see them again
Yuki
Kurumi                                         Ri
School Living Club
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Issho ni (Hai!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Houkago nara atarimae no koto
Saa sa, atsumare!
Kossori kaeruna! (Kora!)
Bukatsu dou dane? Katsudou shichau ne!
Asonderu nja arimasen
Tadaima tte ano ko ga iu yo (Okaeri!)
Minna de ireba daijoubu (Bu!)
Everybody say: tomodachi de iyou ne
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Daisuki (Hai!)
Watachitachi wa tanoshinderu
24 jikan hashaideru
Okujou ni wa akana taiyou
Kanari sakendemita (Genki desu!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Future
It's not for here, either.
Staff #2
What does this key open?
Hold it!
Totally                                                       Dirty
Looks like the end of the line
for you, Taromaru-kun!
So accept your fate!
Huh?
Splat
Oh?
My, you two, don't you know running in the halls...
Rumble
...is a no-no?
Now's my chance!
I finally caught you!
You're filthy. What happened?
Taromaru somehow got out of his collar,
and when I found him, he was
swimming in the pond on the roof.
Pond?
Oh, the water tank.
He was swimming in that filthy place?
That's why I was gonna give him a bath, but...
So you chased after him,
and that's how you ended up like this.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Well, it can't be helped.
I'll take care of the hallway,
so you and Taromaru go get cleaned up.
Okay!
Jeez, the hallway's all dirty,
and it's all your fault, Taromaru!
Yuki-chan.
Huh?
Oh, shoot! I forgot to take off my boots!
How does the water feel?
Stay still now.
It'll be over real quick if you don't move!
Hey, hold on, you're almost done!
Whoa there, you're totally soaked.
Oh, Kurumi-chan!
Want me to help?
Oh, thanks...
I-I'm okay, it's my job, after all!
Huh, okay.
Hey, I just saved you from a lotta trouble, okay?!
Show some gratitude!
Don't jump on my face!
Kurumi-chan!
Sorry, but I think I really do need your help!
Okay, leave it to me!
Uh, but leave the shovel.
Aww.
Okay, what should I do?
Could you hold him down?
Okay.
Alright, round two!
Staff
Hey, wa... Mii-kun, hold on, hold on!
Please hold still.
It'll be over quickly if you don't move.
W-well yeah, but...
Mii-kun, could you be a little more gentle?
You'll catch a cold if I don't dry you off all the way.
Then let's use the hair dryer!
We can't. Taromaru's using it right now.
Awww!
C'mon, Taromaru,
that's not for you.
Don't play with Yuki's hat.
Oh, thanks, Kurumi-chan!
You'd get sick if you ate this dirty thing.
Kurumi-chan?!
Hey, I washed it, it's not dirty!
I'm glad all of your laundry dried quickly.
Yeah!
The sun's really shining down on us today!
Which means it's really hot, too.
You think so?
What's wrong, Mii-kun?
You're embarrassing me, Senpai!
Huh?
Stop lounging around in that and put on your clothes!
Okay, thanks.
Let's all graduate!
Everyone write 100 pages!
I can't write that many!
You can't be lazy like this all the time, Senpai.
I mean, you're all graduating high school next year, right?
Graduation Album
It's okay!
Worry about tomorrow tomorrow!
Senpai...
You have to do the things you can today.
We're so lucky to have all the equipment
we need here at this school.
We should make the most of them right now!
For our future!
There are a lot of things we can do before graduation,
and lots of things we have to do
before we can graduate,
so let's make sure they get done!
You're right.
There sure are lots of things we can start preparing for.
Plus we've gotta study.
In the meantime, we should ask Megu-nee for advice!
Are you going to go to college, Senpai?
Well, lately I've been thinking
I'd just start working.
I mean, I wouldn't have to take any tests, right?
There are employment exams you'd have to take.
Huh?
I hear finding a job's really tough.
Huh?!
Well maybe I'll just stay a
high school student forever.
You really are hopeless.
Okay, I'll drop down to your class, Mii-kun!
No, thank you!
College or finding a job...
What are you going to do, Ri-san?
Huh?
I don't know what to say, I...
What are you going to do, Kurumi?
Eh, maybe go for a job.
So you want a job you can do
with Mr. Shovel, huh?
Could you be a little more imaginative?!
And in this recession, they'd be
looking for more men than women.
Hey, come on!
There are other opportunities!
L-like finding a permanent job,
or g-getting married...
Getting married?
To Mr. Shovel?
Why are you so fixated on my shovel?!
What do you want to do, Miki-san?
In the future?
It's still hazy, so I don't really have a solid idea...
I see.
I hope one day, we all will find something.
A club!
That's a great idea!
Let's start a club!
Yes, I think we'll be more motivated
having goals to pursue,
rather than just living out our days normally.
Yes. I thought about having classes,
but a club is much more fun.
What club will it be?
I'm not sure.
It's a club about living at school, so...
The School Living Club.
How wonderful, we came up with something
without needing to brainstorm!
I already know what kind of things you like, Sensei.
Since your taste is the same as mine.
Thanks.
Here.
Club Application Form
What is this?
Alright, I'm counting on you,
School Living Club President!
I-I'm the president?!
I think you're the best one for the job.
Alright. I'll work hard.
Student Council Room
School Living Club
Perfect!
Alright, everyone line up in front of the door.
Let's take a commemorative picture!
Okay, one, two, three!
Oh, Sensei!
Wakasa-san?
Let me take it.
Huh?
We've got to get a picture with our advisor.
Megu-nee, come stand over here!
Takeya-san?!
Alright, here we go!
Say cheese!
You scared me there, Takeya-san.
Sorry!
Ah, the picture's coming out!
Did I blink?
Should we take another?
Oh, you're right!
You're in there just fine, Megu-nee!
Staff #2
Yuri-senpai, you're still awake?
I just can't sleep.
What are you doing up?
I can't sleep either.
Something's bothering me.
Something's bothering you?
Staff
Here.
Thank you.
Remember what I said earlier?
How we're so lucky to have all the equipment
we need here at this school?
Yes, I remember.
It made me realize something.
Don't you think it's a little too lucky?
I went around the school again to take a look.
The solar panels,
the rainwater collection tank
and the water purifier,
the vegetable garden on the roof
and emergency food stores...
It's like the school was built specifically
to allow people to live in its walls indefinitely.
That's just-
I know!
It's a silly thought.
But I just can't stop thinking about it.
And I'm not sure what to do.
Yuri-senpai?
I understand.
I was thinking the same thing.
The equipment and facilities
on their own aren't that rare.
I'd expect a brand-new office building
to have at least one.
But for all of them to be together in one place,
it's a completely different story.
Staff #2
Is that the same key from before?
Sakura
Yes.
I have a feeling this key is a clue
to solving some of the mystery.
I was going to talk to everyone about it tomorrow.
Could you come with me for a little bit?
I thought we'd already looked in
the teacher's office?
Yes, we checked here first,
since the key said "staff" on it.
So what's the point of coming here again?
We'd only taken a look around Megu-nee's desk.
We'll do a more thorough search tomorrow.
For tonight, we can stop when we get sleepy.
Alright.
I couldn't sleep, anyway.
Let's split the room and see what we can find.
Alright.
Is this Megu-nee?
What're you girls doing?
Yuki-chan?
What's wrong, Senpai?
I woke up 'cause I had a nightmare.
Then I noticed you two weren't there
and I kinda panicked.
Oh my, I'm sorry, Yuki-chan.
Sakura-sensei asked us to look for something.
Th-that's right.
She wanted us to find out what this key goes to.
Oh, a treasure hunt!
I'll help!
Oh, is this it?
Did you find something?
Look at this!
That's not it.
Where did that stuffed animal come from?
Isn't it cute?
I don't really know what to say about it.
Please put it back where you found it.
Aww!
Oh, is this it?
What is it this time?
Look, look at this!
Yuki-chan...
Have you completely forgotten about the key?
This sleeping bag is awesome!
You can walk around in it!
Oh, I got it this time!
Is this it?
I don't think so.
That's not it!
Ah!
Mii-kun! Shoot me with that camera!
Hurry up and record, yo, yo!
Mic check, mic check, one two, one two!
Hello, all you at home!
Can ya hear me?
What are you doing?
You realize this isn't a video camera, right?
What? Really?
I'm gonna take your picture, then.
Huh? Wha...?
Say cheese.
Hey, Mii-kun, you gotta give me some warning!
You told me to get a shot of you.
Slap!
It's just paper!
Senpai, calm down. Look.
Huh?
Wow!
This is awesome! Super awesome!
Let's call it "The Awesome Camera"!
It's already called an instant camera.
Look, Ri-san, isn't it awesome?!
Huh? Ri-san?
Do you remember?
Huh?
Remember when we took a picture
of all of us with this camera?
And what happened after?
Ri-san, what are you...
J-jeez, Yuki-senpai!
Huh?
Yuri-senpai's mad at you
because you're playing around.
Oh, I get it!
It's getting late, so let's hurry up and
find something this key might unlock.
Roger that!
Yuri-senpai, that wasn't like you.
Are you okay?
It happened right after.
Right after we took this picture,
Megu-nee...
There are more of them lately.
Just as I thought, there wasn't anything here.
I see.
Shall we leave things here for today and get to bed?
Yes.
Oh, is this it?
What is it this time?
I think we already looked there.
That's what you think!
There was a hidden compartment!
And there's a safe inside.
What a surprise, right?
Yes, a big surprise.
Thank you, Yuki-chan.
You really are amazing, Yuki-senpai.
Oh, no, you're welcome, really!
Yuri-senpai, here.
Hey, what is it?
A DVD to use in class and a list.
Huh?
Is this all Megu-nee wanted?
Y-yes.
Then I'm gonna go tell Megu-nee we got it!
Guess it was nothing after all.
Yuri-senpai?
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
CONFIDENTIAL
Faculty Emergency Evacuation
Manual
Only open this manual when:
-  The principal or other official has ordered it
-  An A-1 warning has been issued
-  No outside communication has been received for more than 10 days
Um, is this...
Could you hurry and go wake up Kurumi?
A biological weapon can potentially cause more
damage than anticipated depending on its composition.
A pandemic, where the biological agent
spreads rapidly and uncontrollably,
can result in the event that
containment measures fail.
Complete isolation is the key to survival.
Those in contact with infected must also be isolated.
Sustaining the means of propagating the human race
is an act much more important
than the lives of individuals.
Hundreds of thousands of lives are in your hands.
Generosity and sympathy are
no longer virtues in this world.
A biological weapon...
Hold on a damn sec!
What the hell is this?!
What the hell?!
We found what you were looking for, Megu-nee!
It was really hard to find!
Oh, yeah!
And we found this really cute stuffed animal!
I shoulda brought it with me!
I'll show it to you next time!
Akaneiro ni kimi wa
Nani o kangaeteita no
Mabuta ippai namida o tamete
Gomakashiteita kirei da ne to
Utagai mo naku
Konna hibi ga tsuzuite ikunda tte
Zutto omotteita
Miageta sora wa tooku tooku
Bokura mitsumeteiru
Tada shizuka ni kawaranai mama
Maigo no te to te nigirishimeta
Mou samishiku wa nai yo
Owaru sekai mukou gishi eto
Bokura no yoake ga mieru kara
Mieru kara
Waratte
Next Time!
'Cause it's hot...
If it's hot...
When it's hot...!
Hey, calm down, Senpai!
But it's so hot!
Days like this, you just gotta-
Tell horror stories?
No!
Vacation Day
Next time on School-Live, episode 9:
"Vacation Day!"