Fall is special.
I eat five times as much!
Will you be getting
the extra large today, too?
Odagiri Futaba!
Odagiri Futaba, you stupiiiiid!
What is this all about?
Oh, poor me!
It feels like fall is here.
It's a little chilly at this time of day, huh?
Grape picking.
Chestnut hunting, mushroom picking!
Maple leaf hunting!
Maple leaf hunting...?
I wonder if maple leaves are tasty!
Well, they are all natural,
so maybe they taste good.
It's the autumn of eating.
You eat all year long, spring,
summer, winter, and fall.
Fall is special.
I eat five times as much!
How about you two?
What kind of autumn is it?
The autumn of reading?
The autumn of thriftiness!
Same as usual, then.
Yeah, I guess.
Odagiri Futaba!
Huh?
Wh-What was that?
Ten Yen Short
Stuffed Hut
What was that all about?
You do not know him?
No idea.
Oh, my.
In that case, how impolite of him!
He did not even put a "Ms."
in front of your name.
As your friend, I cannot accept
such rude behavior!
He must pay the penalty.
It's fine.
He's just a kid.
He was wearing East High's uniform, though.
No way, he's a high schooler?!
I thought he was in
seventh grade or something.
He said my first and last name, though.
How does he know my whole name?
All right, here you go!
Special Bucket o' Almond Jello!
Yay!
Let’s eat!
Miss Youko, your face looks like
you're looking at something disgusting.
You won't finish this one!
Done!
Thanks for a treat!
You finished...
More like you drank it all.
That was amazing, Futaba!
But honestly, it was so
amazing that it put me off.
Jumbo Dumplings
Finished!
50 pcs.
Fried
Chicken
Finished!
100 pcs.
1000 pcs.
Challenge Menu
Extra Large Ramen
If you don't finish, penalty
5000 yen
When did she do so many challenges?
This shop might not be able
to handle her much longer.
It's okay.
I do food challenges at other shops, too.
Ugh...
Take a commemorative photo for your first time
completing the Bucket o' Almond Jello challenge.
Okay.
Like this?
Or maybe like this?
No matter how cute she looks, she still
finished a whole bucket of almond jello.
Odagiri Futaba
300 bowls
finished
And these photos have her name on them.
Huh?
Odagiri Futaba
300 bowls
finished
My name?
I thought about it, and the only thing it could be
is that he saw my name on the shop photos.
But, why was he acting like that?
Right?
I would understand if he looked up to me.
Normal people would be a little put off.
Odagiri Futaba!
What is this?
Déjà vu?
But this one is a girl...
Unforgivable!
Not once, but twice!
No, they were two different people.
They were two different people, right?
I said, it was a girl.
Though they really did look exactly alike...
A cross-dresser?
For what reason?!
What is this all about?
Maybe I should get Yamaji to look into this.
They must pay the penalty!
Hey, you wanna go karaoke after school?
Oh, I do apologize!
Yeah, sounds good!
S-Sorry.
I wasn't paying attention.
Oh!
She must be the girl Futaba
and Hayama were talking about.
What?
Sh-She's staring at me!
Ca—
Can you meet me after school?
What?!
I wonder what Nishikawa
wants to talk about...
Nishikawa is pretty,
has a great figure, and is athletic.
She's so cool!
I've never been able to approach her,
but now she wants to talk to me!
Ah, there she is.
Wow, now seeing you again,
you two really look exactly the same.
Yeah, they look like twins.
Looks like we made her mad.
Tsuji Sasame from Class 2.
Does that sound right?
I do not know the names
of everyone in my class yet.
I have not talked to them yet.
Why is Odagiri Futaba here with you?!
'Cause we're friends.
What?!
Today was the first time
Nishikawa talked to me, though!
Perfect timing!
Odagiri Futaba, I have
something to say to you!
Huh?
Don't get in my brothers way anymore!
Your brother?!
They must be twins!
He's a year older than me!
Really?
You look like twins, though.
Why am I in his way?
I haven't done anything...
You have!
I'm talking about his big-eater challenges!
Big-eater challenges?
Ah, so he's the same type as Futaba.
He's failed the challenges
at Stuffed Hut so many times.
I see.
My brother... is stubborn...
...and hates to lose,
so he'll overdo it again.
Not to worry.
I'll beat him so bad...
...that he'll never be able to
overdo himself again!
Odagiri Futaba, you stupiiiiid!
I just...
...want to eat...
Oh, poor me!
No way, no way.
No more
big-eater challenge.
—The Meat House
We reserve the right to
refuse Odagiri Futaba.
—Challenge Restaurant
Banned!!
Odagiri Futaba.
—Surprise Lunch
Banned!
Odagiri Futaba.
—Surprise Lunch
Maybe I overdid it.
But I'm still hungry if I order normally.
And I don't have money.
Welcome!
Stuffed Hut
Welcome, Futaba!
Will you be getting
the extra large today, too?
Mr. Stuffed!
I'll have a normal size today.
I don't want to be banned from here, too!
What, a normal size?!
Yup.
I'll have a large helping of curry topped with egg,
corn, cheese, croquette, cutlet, and sausage.
That's not normal-sized!
Oh! Huh?
You're one of the Tsuji's?
Mister!
I'll have the same thing as Odagiri Futaba!
I won't lose, Odagiri Futaba!
You're my rival!
All right, here ya go.
Thanks!
Thank you!
Extra Large Challenge
Extra Large
Parfait
Rice Bowl
Extra Large
Buckwheat
Noodle
Extra Large
Meat
Delicious!
I won't lose, Odagiri Futaba!
I won.
I won!
I won!!
I beat her!!!
I finished it faster than you, Odagiri Futaba!
Now you're no longer a—
Hey, Mr. Stuffed.
Did you change your ingredients?
I knew you'd be able to tell.
I changed the seasonal vegetables.
I finished first!
There's no point in racing
if it's not a competition.
I want to savor it.
Wh—
Dang it!
I'll remember this, Odagiri Futaba!
I won't forgive you...
...Odagiri Futaba!
Those are delicious!
Oh, she's here!
Teru!
Big Sis?
Come on, let's go home together.
Odagiri Futaba...
If she's going to make a stop to do
a challenge somewhere, I have to stop her!
But if I do, then Nishikawa
might not like me anymore...
What should I dooooo?
I see, so that boy is Futaba's rival.
It's a one-sided rivalry.
Now that I think about it,
Big Sis eats a lot, too.
Is that so?
You know how she's a little spacey.
So she eats while spaced out, too.
So it takes a while for her
to realize that she's full.
She's that spacey, huh?
Something...
...is there.
Right there!
Huh?
Apologies.
Did you know I was here?
Oh my, Yamaji.
What?
It was just Yamaji?
You came from behind this time, so it scared me.
Maybe I was imagining it, then...
I thought there was somebody else...
I'm pretty confident in my stealth skills.
All right, let's go.
Huh?
What's that?
One, two, pull!
Oh.
Tsuji?
Is that rival's little sister?
Oh no!
How did you know?
"How"?
There aren't many people who would
fall for a trap like that these days...
I catch my brother like this!
Wait, don't put me on his level.
I needed to stop Odagiri Futaba from
doing more big-eater challenges!
But, I didn't want Nishikawa to get
mad at me, so I tried to keep undercover.
She can hear you loud and clear...
I can't believe you would set up
a foul trap in the middle of the road...!
How atrocious!
It's all your fault, Odagiri Futaba!
She runs away just like her brother.
She set a trap!
Futaba, she's after your life!
Be careful!
"My life"?
But, are you okay with it, Youko?
Huh? Me?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you have had a real conversation with?
She's right!
Before her, you hadn't talked
to anyone in your class.
Usually, you're a loner in class
who still doesn't have any friends.
She's a valuable—
Yamaji!
How to say it, Tsuji's brother
sure is determined, too.
It feels like we'll be seeing
him a lot from now on.
Don't worry, I'll beat him
so bad he'll never recover!
No, no, no, no...
Maybe you can be a little nicer to him?
You do both like to eat a lot.
Is that so...?
Hey, can you keep it down?!
I'm trying to read here.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
What are you reading, Nishiyama?
Hey!
Come Forth★
Murder Mystery!!
Oh.
N-No!
So you like these types of books?
It doesn't fit your image.
I-I... borrowed this...
Oh, that's the book!
I lent it to her.
S-See?
I buy most of them, but bot of us,
especially Nishiyama,
have been huge fans
since elementary school!
Y-You didn't need to say that!
It's all right.
We all have... our own tastes...
Why are you smirking like that?!
It's fine.
It's not weird or anything.
It's kind of cute and easy to read.
It's still a book.
I-I won't forget this!
I've seen this a lot recently...
Which is why...
...I think you should be a little
nicer to Tsuji's brother.
You're telling it to me now, Hayama?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you have had a real conversation with?
That is true...
But, she was so rude to Futaba!
E-Excuse me.
Er, um...
I-I'm... so—
I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Ouch...
Ah!
My money...
Oh my, how terrible!
Let's see.
Oh, there's one here, too!
Nishikawa...
I'm ten yen short.
What?!
I wanted to buy strawberry milk...
I wonder where it went.
We must find it!
Oh, I-It's okay, it's just ten yen.
Just ten yen?!
I'm sorry!
Oh, Miss Youko.
What are you doing?
Odagiri Futaba's friend.
Umm...
I'm Hayama from Class 3.
You see, Tsuji dropped some money...
Did you drop them around here?
Ah!
I just realized.
It was my fault.
I'm surrounded by Odagiri Futaba's friends!
Oh no.
What should I do?!
What, was it a lot?!
Yes, her precious ten yen.
Ten yen...?
Here, you can have it.
But if you'd rather,
you can also just borrow it.
See you.
I am very sorry!
Eh?
Um...
Now what?
I owe one of Odagiri Futaba's friends now.
But...
...I got to talk to Nishikawa a little...
...and Hayama... was nice.
I'm just going to return this.
Really?
That sounds just like Miss Youko.
She had that determined look
that said "every yen counts!"
But, that's what's so good about her.
She's been working for while now, too.
Nishikawa works part-time?!
Huh?
The little sister?
Is Nishikawa working part-time?
I can't believe it...
Yup, at a cake shop at the outskirts
of the Central Shopping Arcade.
They gave out fliers our school before.
Oh.
This is it, huh?
Oh, wow!
There's a maid!
And someone who looks like a butler!
A shop where Nishikawa would
work really is on another level.
Tsuji?
Oh, you came already.
Oh, er...
What are you waiting for?!
Let's go in!
Wh—
Oh, this is good.
What a wonderful fragrance.
Hey, where's the new cake?
Wh-Wh-What is this?!
H-How it turned out into this situation?!
What's wrong?
Drink it while it's still hot.
Smells nice...
It's good!
Right?
This is one of my favorites.
Yup.
Sorry for the wait.
I've been waiting!
Huh?
We came to try the new cake.
I-Is it okay for me to try, too?
What, you don't like cake?
Then, I'll have it.
Ah!
I'll eat it, I'll eat it!
You don't have to force yourself.
I'm not!
Really?
Yes.
Good for you, Miss Youko.
I like cake!
Hm?
Then I'll feed you.
You have made another friend.
Here, open wide.
Friend?
I can feed myself!
I guess if you think about it...
It was a miracle just to have
Hayama and Odagiri.
Personally, having another high school girl
here will make things more fun for me.
You can make friends even without money!
It's a good thing that you became poor.
When you were rich and aloof...
Q-Quiet, you mongrels!
I cannot believe that Tsuji
actually came to the shop.
I wonder...
Is she a friend?
I am not sure...
All right.
Find a partner.
I need to find a partner...?
N-Nishikawa!
She called out to me!
Until now, after told to find a partner,
I just paired with the last person,
or in worst case with the teacher.
She wants to pair up with me?!
U-Um...!
Hm?
Are you all right?
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Next week
Now, next week's Three Colors,
Three Leaves will be...
Next week
Now,
next week's
Three Colors,
Three Leaves
will be...
It's
Sasame.
It's Sasame.
Um...
How
was it...?
Hmm...
Um... How was it...? Hmm...
Ah,
next
time...
Ah, next time...
The Cursed Sword
Place of Death
Red Spider Lily
...will be these three: "The Cursed Sword,"
"Place of Death," and "Red Spider Lily."
...will
be these
three.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Next time: I Caught A Lot
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Dyu
fu
fu!