SERN will take the time machine.
SERN? What do you mean?
Makise Kurisu.
Okabe Rintarou.
Hashida Itaru.
The three of you will come with me.
What about Mayuri?
Shiina Mayuri is...
...not necessary.
Don't.
Don't do it.
For FB... FB... FB...
Mayuri?
Mayuri!
What the hell is this?!
Get away from her.
Okabe, get away from her!
She'll kill you too!
You'll pay for this.
I'll make her pay for this!
Forty-two.
CRT.
It's on.
Hurry!
Okabe!
I'll go!
But if it fails...
Do it now!
Okabe!
Leap!
Metaphysics
Necrosis
Mayuri was still in elementary school
when her grandmother died.
She went to her grave every day.
Even six months after her grandmother's death,
she kept going.
She always had her grandmother's
pocket watch in her hand,
and she was always, always looking up at the sky...
...like she was waiting for
her grandmother to come and get her.
And then one day, there was a ray of light.
It was the kind called Rembrandt lighting...
...or an angel's ladder.
It felt like the light was drawing her up...
...like she was going to disappear...
Mayuri!
Okarin...
I won't let it take you.
You're going to be my hostage.
I'll use you for human experimentation.
The words that came out of my mouth
were from some show I'd seen as a little kid.
Mayuri and I had watched it together.
Some mad scientist, screaming like an idiot...
I see.
So Mayushii is your hostage, right?
Then I guess I can't go, huh?
What's wrong?
Were you napping?
What time is it?
What time is it?!
What?
It's almost five.
You're going shopping, right?
Shopping...
I'll order pizza.
Thanks.
Just don't get the tropical special.
I hate that thing.
Agreed.
The time leap worked?
Okabe?
Where's Mayuri? Where is she?!
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
Mayushii said she was going to Miss Ruka's
to invite her to the party, remember?
Are you going shopping?
The development conference is canceled.
Canceled?
Why?
Did something happen?
We're done here for today.
Both of you, go home now!
What's going on?
Just go home!
Okay? Just do it!
What's with him?
His phone starts ringing, and then...
Phone?
This is Mayushii.
I can't answer the phone right now!
If you'd like to leave a message—
There's nothing to indicate
that the world line changed.
It's different from a D-mail.
I really am back at 5:00 PM.
It's the bullet train!
No, the bullet train is white.
After this, Mayuri will return with Suzuha.
Should I go to the police?
No, who would believe me?
That I've come from the future?
Three hours left...
I have to do something!
Mayuri!
Mayuri?!
O-Oka... No, Kyouma—
Where's Mayuri?!
Sh-She already left.
Left?
When?
Th-Thirty minutes ago, I guess.
She said she was going back to the lab.
Didn't she get back?
Um, I'm sorry.
It was so nice of you to
invite me to the party, but—
Did she say she was stopping anywhere?
Mayuri?
No...
If you see her, tell her to call me right away!
O-Okay.
If the world line hasn't changed...
If I don't do anything differently,
she should do what she did before.
Where is she?
Meow-meow!
Faris can't answer the phone right now.
If you need something—
Where are you, Mayuri?
Mayuri?
Too bad.
Assistant...
I told you that we were done for the day.
Go home—
Be honest.
You time leaped from the future, didn't you?
How could you tell?
The second you answered the phone,
you seemed to change.
From the way you're acting,
I can guess that something happened.
Yeah...
...but I don't have time to give you the details.
Just run.
Run? Where?
Anywhere.
Just get away from the lab.
Got it?
Tell me later, okay?
Yeah. Tell Daru too.
Got it.
Okabe...
What is it?
Don't do anything stupid.
I know.
Okabe Rintarou!
Hey, where's Ochanomizu—
Have you seen Mayuri?!
Shiina Mayuri?
She just invited me to your party—
Where is she?
Turn right, up there...
Hey, which way is Ochanomizu?
I have to take Nae shopping...
Ask at the police substation!
And once you've taken her, don't come back!
What do you mean?
I'll tell you later.
Mayuri...
Mayuri!
Okarin!
Look! It's the first star!
What?
Just come with me!
What about the party?
It was canceled. I told Kurisu and Daru.
Why?
I'll tell you later!
But I asked Suzu to come too,
and Daru was ordering pizza...
Just listen to me!
Okarin...
I'm sorry.
Mayushii doesn't understand...
You always do things I don't understand,
but today, I really don't understand you.
Did you really want to
do the experiment, after all?
Mayuri...
That's not it.
But just for now, can you listen to me?
There's no time.
I'll explain the details later. I promise.
Okay.
Sorry. Mayushii just got scared.
Don't apologize.
It's not your fault.
There are so many people here.
It's rush hour.
Huh?
But no one's on the platform...
Once again,
the following lines have been shut down due to a bomb threat.
They said they don't know when
the trains will start again.
How stupid of me!
Not now...
Okarin?
Mayuri, get to the subway now!
Okabe Rintarou, right?
What's wrong?
You're coming with me.
What are you standing there for?
Move!
Run!
Run as fast as you can!
Who are they?
Okarin!
Go, quickly!
Run, Mayuri!
Shiina Mayuri was the one who died.
Okabe...
I mean, Okabe Rintarou has been captured.
Mayuri!
Damn it!
I won't let you kill her!
Mayuri, I will save you!
I'll save you...
...no matter what!
Canceled?
Why?
Did something happen?
Yeah. Actually...
I got word
that Mr. Braun is planning to return tonight.
Okarin, did you do something again?
Yeah, I suppose so.
But what about Mayuri?
I'll talk to her.
It's dangerous to be here.
We're done here for today.
Was I too forceful?
No...
It doesn't matter if I was acting weird.
For now, I just need them away from the lab!
This is Mayushii.
I can't answer the phone right now!
Why is it taking so long?
It's going to end up like last time!
I need to find Mayuri.
Rukako
Hello?
Rukako! It's me! Okabe!
Oka... I'm sorry, Kyouma—
Where's Mayuri?!
Is Mayuri there?
Mayuri?
Yes.
She's just heading bac—
Stop her!
Tell her not to move until I get there!
She said she was going back to the lab.
Just do as I say!
O-Okay.
Mayuri!
It's the bullet train!
No, the bullet train is white.
Mayuri!
Okarin!
Are you okay?
I was about to go fix Fubuki's costume
and then go to the lab.
Fubuki?
A cosplay friend of yours?
Yeah!
She said a thread on the costume
I made came undone.
I just got a message from her.
So that's it.
Once it's fixed, I'll go right to the lab,
so I'll make it to the party.
Wait. The party...
The party was cancel—
I mean, it was postponed.
Why?
We can't use the lab...
...due to unforeseen consequences.
I see...
So I wanted you to come with me for a bit.
Right now.
What about Fubuki?
I'm sorry, but save it for later.
This is an emergency.
Um, did something happen?
Yeah, we're going away for a while.
On a trip.
Together?
Um, well...
I can put Fubuki off until tomorrow,
but this is very sudden.
Where are we going?
I'll tell you later.
We don't have much time to catch the train.
But Mayushii isn't ready at all, and—
Don't worry about it.
Come on, let's go.
Wait, Okarin!
Um...
Huh?
G-Goodbye.
Yeah, bye-bye!
Isn't Akihabara Station that way?
We're taking the subway.
I see.
It's been a really long time
since you dragged me along like this.
Yeah.
We're heading back.
Huh?
Okay.
Let's go.
Assistant
Did something happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Kurisu, huh?
My watch isn't working...
That's strange.
I just wound it.
There are so many people here.
The Sobu line shut down.
Shut down?
Yeah.
A bomb threat was called in.
I see...
Hey, Okarin.
Um, well...
Mayushii has a lot of questions she wants to ask,
but it's okay for now.
In exchange,
when this is over,
I want you to tell me everything.
Yeah.
I promise.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I can't help you.
Let's have that party sometime.
Yeah...
Sometime.
Sometime...
For sure.
Big sis Mayuri!
It wasn't...
I didn't mean to...
I just wanted to surprise her...
I won't let you kill her!
Mayuri, I will...
...save you!