If I show you my real self, what will you do?
Will you fall for me?
Hey...
H-Hold it...
I-I...
Taiga, are Takasu-kun and the others here?
Taiga?
Umm...
This looks bad.
Was my timing bad?
This isn't what you-
Ta-i-ga!
Minorin!
I don't think anyone's here!
Where did they go?
My, my...
Why are you lying?
Perhaps...
You don't want to acknowledge that there's another female allowed in this room apart from you?
Idi-
Stop talking nonsense!
Hmm? But...
No "buts", tell the truth...
Truth?
Oh dear, seriously...
T-Taiga?
Taiga!
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
Pool Opening
Good morning!
Taiga-chan, did something happen?
Nothing that concerns me.
I wonder what's for dinner tonight...
Rice medley, you're in for it, right?
Why not red rice and beans...
Right, ugly bird?
Ugly...
You know, Taiga, about what happened just then...
Kawashima was just joking around.
How should I put it?
She wasn't feeling well...
I'm sorry.
My, why are you apologizing?
You're really weird, Ryuuji.
I-Inko-chan?!
Get a hold of yourself, Inko-chan!
Don't faint!
Taiga, wake up!
There's no time lef-
Ouch... huh?
S-Sorry.
What?
Speaking of which, we've overslept!
Anyway, just hurry up and get ready!
What's for breakfast?
Why are you waking me up like this today?
There's no breakfast, nor lunch!
We'll be late if we don't leave within five minutes!
God... If we don't go to the convenience store, we won't have any lunch!
Hey, are you listening, Taiga...
I am listening, you perverted dog!
The convenience store, right?
What are you doing?
Just because you didn't have brea-
Ow!
Made it!
You're finally here!
Thank you very much for what you did yesterday!
No, uh...
What's up with you?
My summer uniform looks really hot, doesn't it?
Just kidding-
You're in my way, Stupid Chihuahua.
Oh, I didn't see you, Aisaka-san.
Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san.
Thanks for being turned on so early in the morning.
Hey, you guys...
I see. Oh my gosh...
Don't be jealous because of something small like that.
You're just misunderstanding what's going on.
You're really a dumb bitch.
What happened yesterda-
Good morning, everyone!
Oh, this might make my biceps stronger!
Minorin, don't use me for working out!
Regarding the pool day
All right, tomorrow is the long awaited pool day!
Now, let me clarify some things.
Summer is an adventure of love.
This is my last chance because I'm in my twenties.
This is bad, my tummy is...
I have big thighs.
My arms are worse.
What are you all talking about?
Just your ages are good enough!
Do we have mixed swimming classes in this school?
Oh dear, it'll be so embarrassing!
What the hell...
I thought you're a super-cute model...
What's there to be embarrassed about?
Regarding the pool day
You can only wear dark purple or black
Your arms can
What is it, eh?
What are you.... What are you...
What are you talking about?!
Sensei, homeroom is going to end soon!
Fine, we're done!
Stand!
Taiga, hurry up and come!
No, I'm not going to buy a swimsuit!
You don't have a choice since your old one broke last year.
Swimsuits should be washed and dried as soon as possible!
I said I don't want to!
Moreover, why is she here?
That's because this is the only shop that sells them.
I-I didn't invite her.
Hey, this will fit Aisaka-san perfectly!
Maybe it's a bit too perfect...
Calm down, Taiga! There are other people looking.
Takasu-kun, what do you think about this?
Well, it looks pretty go-
Hey!
How do I look?
Does it look weird?
Is it too flashy?
What's with those long legs?!
They're too flashy!
Really?
I just picked a simple one...
K-Kawashima-san.
What brand is that swimsuit?
Where did you find it?
Over there.
Oh, let's get the same one.
Only that... Spare me!
Kushieda...
Hey.
Even though I'm super-super-super cute, isn't this a bit scary?
This is just a normal swimsuit!
I wonder how far I can go with my cuteness, beauty and body!
Wouldn't hiding it be the same as committing a crime?
Hey Takasu-kun, you feel the same way, right?
Huh?
Hey, are you all right, Tai-
What are you doing?
I don't know what I should do anymore!
What is it?
What's wrong?
I just can't make a decision!
Is there something you're not happy about?
The only choices are dark purple or black.
That's not it, it's about the size!
Umm, how about children's size?
I'd rather die!
Don't say the same thing as the Stupid Chihuahua!
Isn't this small enough?
The price and quality is fine, you can even put it in a dryer!
Did you try it on yet?
That one...
I tried it already...
But it still wasn't quite right...
How should I put it...? Well...
Then this is fine, isn't it?
I guess...
Taiga, what do you want for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want.
Oh yeah, did you prepare for the pool?
Don't forget your bath towel.
Shut up.
Is there something bothering you?
Is it the swimsuit? Or are you still mad about yesterday?
No!
Then what is it?!
I don't know how to swim.
I hate it!
I can tell that's not the real reason.
I'm late!
Wait.
Drink this first.
Thanks, Ryuu-chan!
What is that?
Ryuu-chan's special soy milk!
It seems like soybeans contain some iso... vonvon thing which can make breasts bigger.
It's isoflavone.
I'd be in trouble if they shrink, so I can't let that happen.
I'm smart!
Taiga-chan is so naughty!
Stop sexually harassing my mother!
I'm going!
Seriously, that was messed up.
What's wrong?
You're acting strange.
Beans...
Hey!
I'll have one more even though it tastes bad!
What are you doing?
I need more isoflavone!
Huh?
What would you need-
Swimsuit size and isoflavone...
Taiga, don't tell me you're....
No, don't say it!
Don't say any more!
Are you...
...flat?
Seriously, are breast sizes something to be concerned about?
Sorry for making you wait.
How is it?
It's flat, isn't it?
It's really flat, isn't it?
No, well...
What about breast-pads?
I used them already, but...
It collapsed.
That's why I don't want to go to the pool.
Anyway, put something on, or you'll catch a cold.
What is this?
After you see it, you'll understand how I feel.
Note: Flat!
This is...
...really mean.
Pitiful breasts, pitiful...
I'm pitied because of my flat chest.
No, well...
These are just the thoughts of the person who wrote this...
Of course, I've already delivered a bloodbath to the photography club.
Oh, so that's why the photography club was suddenly shut down.
I don't want to show my pitiful side in front of Kitamura-kun...
I don't want to...
Hey, Taiga.
All right, I'll think up of something.
For the sake of allowing you to face Kitamura.
I'll do it.
I'm fine, you should go back and sleep.
No, I'll wait until you're done.
I'll stay up until you're done.
Hey...
Well, umm...
I'm sorry...
...for being spiteful.
How is it?
I will bring this with me for sure when I get married.
Maruo!
You look better without your glasses!
Start wearing contacts!
Really?
Totally!
I don't even have glasses.
Note: Female Changing Room
Bye, Aisaka-san!
I'll be leaving first.
Taiga?
Hurry up, I'll do your hair afterwards.
Okay.
Maaya-chan, I'm sorry!
My hair is a pain to do!
I'm sorry for making you wait!
Ami-chan!
Wow, as expected of a model!
You're body is amazing.
How should I put it...
I'm touched!
She's a goddess!
You're really different from us.
That again...
Of course!
I'm cute as hell today!
I'll let you peasants celebrate the arrival of an angel!
Now, lick my shadow!
This will be like the best thing you lowly scums have ever experienced!
Stop joking around, Maaya-chan.
Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run!
My hair will get messed up!
All right, our warm up will be a lap of running...
...feints!
Minorin?
Kushieda!
I've finally realized it!
No one can see your tummy when you're in the water!
And so, I'll be swimming.
Later!
Minorin...
Oh, Aisaka-san, you finally came out.
I was thinking that you might not show up because you were too embarrassed about your swimsuit being loose.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Are you still asleep?
Seriously...
I don't want to get sunburned...
Perfect!
She grew so much in just a year!
I'm all for Taiga!
Oh, how normal.
Your proportions are wrong as usual.
I did it!
Yeah!
Fake breasts special ops.
She found out...
As expected of Minorin.
Aisaka?
You're Aisaka, aren't you?
Although I can't see well without my glasses, you're the same size as Aisaka.
Why are you hiding?
Your hair is like a mouse, it's good.
Go away!
What?
Did I say something wrong?
I don't know...
Hey, flex your arms!
Like this?
Wow!
Just by himself...
He's so popular...
We're going to question this caste system!
This is a summer back flip!
Maruo!
Hey...
Want to do it?
Even though the whole period is just free time, isn't this a bit dangerous?
Hey, Tai-
Kitamura-kun said my hair is cute...
No, he just said it's good...
Prey spotted!
Let's go, my baseball bud!
All right, next!
Okay, captain!
Yikes, you got thrown in.
You must be having fun, Aisaka-san.
You...
Let's play!
I'll seriously get mad if you don't!
Here I go!
Hey, that's a bit over the top!
I was just playing...
Hey, Taiga, are you all right?
Taiga?
She...
I don't know how to swim.
Don't tell me she really can't swim...
You're kidding!
Leave me alone!
Taiga!
Sensei!
No!
Calm down, Tai-
No, a breast pad fell out!
I only have one left on me!
Wha-
Hey, something wrong is going on.
Aisaka...
Taiga!
Aisaka!
I'm coming now!
Don't come!
Taiga!
Shit, if this is the case...
This is humiliation...
I told you that I'm sorry!
I didn't know that you couldn't swim!
See, everyone is gone.
Change back to your old-
This isn't something that can be settled with an apology.
All because you did something so stupid...
My b-b-breasts were...
Anyway, apologize, apologize, apologize...
Besides, if you can't swim, you'll never be able to go to the sea or to the pool.
Hey, Takasu-kun, my villa is near the sea.
If you want, let's spend our summer holidays together.
What?
Wait, weren't you apologizing to Taiga?
Then I'll ask Yuusaku, too.
Huh?
What's wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you continue to make decisions by yourself,
I'll leak the video of the medley of 100 different imitations.
Oh, it was 150.
If you do that, you'll be breaking the permission laws of photography.
I'm sure even the Palmtop Tiger cannot win against the law.
Hey, you guys.
Stop it!
Even fists can get hurt.
But you see, Minori-chan, Aisaka-san wants to...
It's all the Stupid Chihuahua's fault!
What are you talking about?
After all...
Shut up!
Unless you want to increase our friendship with our fists, don't argue!
Let's decide this with a sports contest!
S-Sports?
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
For Whose Sake
The fight for Takasu.
Ami-tan VS Taiga?
Why does the good stuff only happen to Takasu?!
Please punish me after you win the fight for me!