It's been a year and a half since then.
Bro is dead.
Even now, it's still hard to accept that.
Still... I'm glad that I met you.
You made me happy.
If I hadn't met you that day...
I met Bro two years ago.
It was July of 1955.
Back then, I was full of desperation.
So...
what do we need to do?
Hey, senior.
Why don't you introduce yourself instead of showing us your back?
I don't speak with kids or monkeys.
Say that again?
You're all just fucking kids full of pride,
even though you've already fallen so low.
Or...
are you indeed just monkeys?
You better shut that mouth.
What about you?
Aren't you also a shithead who's fallen so low?
Well?
Then as fellow shitheads, no one would mind any of us killing each other, right?
True.
No matter how many of you shitheads die...
no one's gonna give a damn.
You idiots...
seem to need a good fight to learn a thing or two.
Come and get me.
I'll fucking kill you!
Here.
You're the last guy.
I'll keep watch, so make it quick.
You think you're our boss now?
What the hell do I gain from bossing you dumb kids around?
Don't you think...
that I know what you've gone through outside?
It's good...
Let's hope that by summer, two years from now...
we'll be out on the streets.
Bro was strong.
Even though he beat me to pulp, his fists were filled with warmth.
His words were filled with kindness.
Hey!
You idiots!
Stop slacking and defend!
Sorry about that.
Is it our turn to bat next?
Within a month, we were close enough to call each other by our nicknames.
Except for Uncovered, that is...
So...
do you even know why Sakuragi's in here?
You see...
he killed his own parents.
His own parents!
Thanks.
Cabbage!
Don't put that in your mouth.
You can't fall any lower than eating something a murderer gave you.
Why don't you tell us all about it right here?
That you were sent here for killing your parents.
Who told you something like that?
It was all a lie concocted by Ishihara,
but... it soon turned into a serious incident.
What's going on?
What's the alarm for?
A fire!
A fire?
It started in the library.
The library?!
Hey.
Sakuragi's in cell 2-6, right?
What did you do?!
What to do...
I don't have the key to your cell.
Here, Nomoto.
You double check too.
Do I have the key for cell 2-6?
I don't, do I?
I can't unlock the cell, now can I?
We were trapped inside our cell.
The one who came to save us...
was Bro.
Sorry, guys!
I'm late.
Bro!
You can't, Bro!
Is he trying to force it open?
It won't work.
We tried to break it down, and we couldn't do it!
Shut up, you fucking kids!
You're gonna give up just like that?
No way...
our lives could be worth so little!
Bro!
Bro, your leg...
It's... over.
Not yet.
Don't give up yet!
He'll come.
I know it!
He'll come... for sure!
I gave up hope completely...
because I didn't have faith in Uncovered.
I was pathetic.
Guys! Listen.
You see, the fire the other day.
I don't want to hear it.
So don't tell me.
You saved us.
That's all there is to it.
After that fire incident, our bond became impenetrable.
And then, we all carved our dreams into a tree on a hill.
We made a promise to reunite under this tree the summer after next.
Ishihara!
Sakuragi Rokurouta. Step out of the cell.
You're being moved.
Even after that, Ishihara and Sasaki continued their assault on him.
I confidently went out of my way to help Bro,
but wound up having my right hand shattered.
Here we go.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero!
They antagonized Bro because...
a year earlier...
his cell mate, Hagino Ei'ichi supposedly died in an accident.
But it wasn't an accident.
It was suicide.
"Inspector Ishihara was selling me to Sasaki...
as a sex slave.
Ishihara broke his promise to release me early.
So I'll wait for my mother in heaven."
He left Bro a suicide note.
I was certain...
that Bro was gonna be killed.
Instructor Kumagai was the only person we could depend on,
but Ishihara eliminated him.
Our only option was to protect Bro ourselves...
so we set an escape plan in motion.
Just a little more patience, Bro.
We'll get you out for sure.
Uncovered's plan was brilliant.
Dr. Sasaki, I'm coming in!
This is Yokosuka Jou from cell 2-6.
He's come down with a stomach ache.
If it's nothing serious, we can just give him some medicine and send him back.
Okay, Doctor.
Now!
I'm gonna strangle you!
Joe stole the cell key from Sasaki.
And Soldier and I rescued Bro from solitary confinement.
Bro!
We came for you, Bro.
Let's go, Bro.
We're all busting out of here!
But, things didn't work out as planned.
So, Uncovered...
Cabbage...
and Soldier...
I broke the key.
all risked their lives to protect Bro.
They won't be able to get out the front gate for a while.
And finally, Bro was free.
Setsuko!
Where are you going, Maeda?
If you don't stay out of sight, you'll get caught.
I brought medicine and food, plus more clothing for you.
I want to help out too.
Setsuko played a big part.
How did you get so thin? What happened to you?
I will not die.
If it hadn't been for Setsuko, Bro wouldn't have survived through those days.
He's awake, everyone! Sakuragi's awake!
Go back to the school.
Bro...
Please!
Save Soldier, Uncovered, and Cabbage!
Please.
He always cared for his friends, first and foremost.
Joe gladly returned to the reformatory after winning at rock-paper-scissors.
Our new life at the hideout relied entirely on Setsuko,
so to help her out a little, we got involved in the black market.
This boy's a boxer?
Are you strong?
What are you talking about, lady?
This here's the boss of Shonan Special Disciplinary School!
What?
Nobody there was a match for him!
Shonan Special Disciplinary School...
Why are you telling her that?!
Okay! It's all right!
I wound up inside a boxing ring
for the first time in my life.
Mario! Mario!
I was utterly defeated.
Get stronger, then come back and try again.
Damn it!
I'd felt plenty of frustration before then,
but I'd never been so mad at myself in all my life.
Still, Bro understood how I felt.
It's already late.
Get some rest.
We'll start training tomorrow.
You can't stop with just a loss, can you, Mario?
Bro wasn't fully healed, but he still held the sandbag for me.
Hey, Mario! Bro!
I just set up your next match.
It'll be on January 28, a Saturday.
Bro.
Yeah.
Let's win for sure next time.
And then, that fateful day arrived.
Well, be safe.
Yeah, I'll see you later.
Now that I think about it, Setsuko looked awfully lonely that day.
Maybe that's why I asked him a question.
Hey, Bro.
It's about Setsuko.
Do you like her?
Why are you asking so suddenly?
You're thinking of getting married, right?
I don't know.
I don't think I can do anything.
Still, I do want to make her happy.
That's how I feel.
She went through a lot of trouble for someone like me.
I want her to be happy no matter what.
Bro, watch me fight.
I'll definitely win.
But just before the match, we heard that Turtle got caught by the police.
Please go, Bro.
He must have something important to say.
He wouldn't call here otherwise.
You'd better win, Mario.
You bet I will.
Bro...
Bro, what exactly happened after that?
Before the MPs shot you, you received a fatal stab wound in your abdomen.
I learned that Sasaki had also been there.
Ishihara must be the one who stabbed you.
There's no mistake about it.
I'm heading out to confirm that now.
Until I settle this matter, none of us, including me, can move forward.
Please understand, Bro.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Settling the business of men.
Each of the six takes steps to move forward.