What am I supposed to do?
What's wrong with her?
Yuri-chan, 29 years old.
She cooked curry and brought it to a guy she'd been crushing on.
Sorry for the wait!
It's me!
But he turned her away at the door and didn't even try a single bite.
Was she thinking of an 80s movie?
That idea won't work nowadays.
He said you don't call a curry "curry" if the potatoes aren't in big chunks.
But it's so much better when they're mushed!
Why is this 29-year-old so particular about stuff when she's desperate?
Curry is prepared different in every family.
Indian style, Southeast Asian style,
British style... They all taste different!
Some people use fishcake, natto, or pig innards for ingredients.
Okay, Mr. Know-It-All, why don't you wear a turban while you're at it?
Aw, come on, you 29-year-old! Stop crying!
Well, shall we go have some yummy curry?
Yeah!
Keep Dragging On, The Way of Curry!
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for Foodies (India Edition)
Right Hand for Curry, Left for the Bathroom
This place is the best!
Welcome.
Yummy!
The taste of apples and honey really stands out!
Seconds, please!
I don't think either one is in there.
Ooh, 29-year-old Ms. Yuri-chan is here with us today, too!
- 29, I say!
- Kushieda...
- Hey, can you stop repeating my age?
- She 's so cute today...
It really makes me sad...
So being old makes you sad. That sucks.
Your skin's dry, your butt's saggy,
and there are days you can't walk outside without a parasol.
And you're dying to make future plans with your boyfriend. That's how it is, right?
Oh, so you get it! That's right!
The 29th year is when we finally hit a wall after thinking really hard.
Makes me wonder if my life is really at the right place.
We don't really get it now, since we're still teenagers.
Of course, I'll dream of marriage!
Yeah, men tell me I'm intimidating!
I love it when I'm being ignored!
So what's up today?
Takasu-kun said we're having curry.
I-Isn't it good here?
Even Indians are shocked!
You...fool!
Yeah, she's right!
You don't know nothin' 'bout no curry.
True curry's deep n' rich like the 4,000 years of Chinese history!
We're gonna have a throwdown!
I don't like spicy food.
Well, I'll have both.
Me too!
Let's start with my choice...
Super sweet, Jonny's Prince Curry!
Big Sis! I'm so glad I'm alive!
Too sweet. Can't eat it.
Way too kiddy...
Can't eat anymore.
Curry has long been one of the staple menu items for school lunches.
In the 1970s, people followed a practice called Triangular Eating Order.
It refers to eating in the order of bread, side dish, milk, bread, side dish, and milk.
Bread works, but when it was rice instead,
kids often experienced the horrid combo of milk and rice.
People push the practice of
Nutrition Education nowadays,
but this has been a practice followed since the Meiji era.
In 2005, a Standard Nutrition
Education was established.
It was aimed to have the citizens nurture a rich and healthy lifestyle.
The Balanced Food Guide is a part of that system.
To make healthy eating habits happen, the combination of food intake and...
It's way too long to listen.
What does he think he is?
Nutrition Education is really important!
Who listens to that seriously?
That's nothing but a lie to tell kids!
Devour my special, Spicy Jonny's "D" Curry!
The smell...
The spiciness is stinging my eyes...!
It's so red. Where is this color coming from?
Learn and die... It's too spicy to eat...!
Isn't there anything in between?
Curry advertisements tend to aim for a family audience,
but women are getting married at later years in their lives.
However! Don't you worry!
That's something we've observed happening all over the world!
Perhaps it's due to the implementation of individualism,
higher educations, and political unrest caused by uneven supply and demand.
You can expect the problem to worsen.
Basically, get married if you want to,
don't get married if you don't want to,
and if you can't, you just suck!
Freedom for us!
- We are free!
- What's with her speech?
Trying to be something?
I'm gonna cry. I feel so defeated...
I said not to take it seriously.
By the way, which curry are we picking?
No! He'll break up with me if I make him eat either one of those.
You two aren't even going out.
Our hearts just aren't ready yet!
Shazam!
Piranhas are known for their aggressiveness,
but Amazon natives use their sharp teeth to cut hair!
They're not just good for eating water buffalo!
That said...
This battle is a tie!
Curry is spicy!
It's a pun joke!
I hope he falls into the water!
There is no curry mix in India!
What!? Are you serious!?
Inko Today
Tuna.
Chestnut manju.
To be continued...