“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
I'll rely on strength in numbers!
It's here!
This is... the Dollars?
What is this? You don't mean, all these people?
For example,
you should marry me.
We've also been keeping your little secret safe.
Certy.
There are more than I thought. What fun.
I'm screaming!
Right now, my purpose is...
Give back Certy!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Harmony of Opposites
I suppose I should be grateful.
If it weren't for you, Nee-san would have locked her up in that tiny research room again.
Yagiri-kun.
Are you okay?!
Anyway, give Certy back to me. I have to get her out of here before the police arrive.
Is that why you're...
What do you know?
I've been looking after her since I was a child.
I wanted to free her, and I'm going to set her free into this vast world,
then I'm going to live together with her.
I've always, always, always, always, always, always thought about it, and nothing else.
There's no way. Nobody can stop the power of love, right?
Conversely, what about you?
Back there, and even now, you've been relying on strength in numbers.
You can't crush my love that easily!
That won't work! It may hurt, but I'll ignore the pain!
Pain isn't necessary in Certy's life, nor in mine!
So even with the pain that's inflicted on me now, I won't feel it at all!
It's useless!
Stop!
Please stop! Seji-san can be mean and violent, and is different from most people,
but he's not a bad person! Even so, he has someone else whom he loves...
No.
It can't be. It can't be, can't be, can't be...
No, this girl is...
This is not my head.
This girl... This girl's name is...
Harima Mika-san.
That's right. You're the Harima Mika-san who was supposedly killed by Yagiri-kun.
You're kidding.
Right?
I'm sorry!
Hey! Hey! Hey! You're home, right, Seji-san?
I'm here today, too!
Oh no! You forgot to leave the door unlocked!
I can't get in like this!
Are you asleep or something?
Don't you remember?
I sat next to you during the exams.
The person sitting to my right had an amazing name like Ryugamine,
so instead I turned to my left to see what type of person was sitting there,
and the moment I saw you I had a crush on you.
Then you looked back at me and smiled...
Therefore Seji-san, please let me see your face.
I'm begging you, I'm begging you.
Maybe you're not feeling well?
Is that why you can't come out?
In that case, I'll open it for you.
Wait just a second! I'm coming in now.
You know, since the day of the exam, I've looked up a lot of stuff about you.
Seji-san's birthday and family...
S-Seji-san...
You saw it.
W-Well, I... I w-won't tell anyone.
It's all right. Whatever tastes you have, I'll try to make them my own as well.
So please...
It's okay.
Seji-san!
Seji-san?
It's okay.
I'm sorry! I wasn't dead yet!
After that, your sister...
You want Seji to love you?
What a good girl.
And then... And then this doctor came,
and said that with just a little cosmetic surgery and makeup,
I'd look just like that head... the head that Seji-san loved so much.
He said, "Your name is Certy. That's the name of the head, after all."
That's why I tried to become Certy for you, Seji-san.
Yet Namie-san said it still wasn't enough.
She said we should erase my emotions and memories with medicine,
or a surgery of some sort, to make sure I didn't give away my true identity.
Still, I didn't want to forget my feelings for you,
Someone who knows my name...
Someone who knows that I'm a Dullahan...
so I tried to remember everything throughout the treatment.
That's why I've been hiding my true feelings this whole time.
There's only one person like that in this city!
It's because I want to be with you, Seji-san! That's why I haven't given up!
You must... be kidding.
You mean I...
Well, you couldn't tell the difference between the real thing and a fake,
so that's how far your love really goes.
Way to go.
Seji-san!
I think it's great that you put your life on the line to try and get her back.
I think I've understood you all along, Harima-san.
Sure, you may have some personality flaws, but you aren't a stalker.
After all, you risked your life for Yagiri-kun.
I doubt that's something you could have done on a mere whim.
I think the fact that you still love someone who almost killed you is amazing,
in more ways than one.
I think you and Seji-san make a good match, Harima-san.
Welcome back.
I bet you're going to say, "What are you trying to do?"
Then you'll say: "You knew, didn't you, that my head was at that research facility?"
"You and your father have both been working for Yagiri Drug Manufacturing from the start, haven't you?"
"Could it be that it was your father who stole my head from me?!"
"And despite that, you've been hiding it from me,"
"and you also cut up the face of a girl who almost died!"
"I'm a monster, but you, who truly devour people, are the real monster here!"
Or something like that.
Oh, and just so you don't take it the wrong way,
let me say that I don't know if my father took your head or not, nor do I care.
And that little surgery was something I did because the girl wanted it.
Perhaps Yagiri guided her opinion, but that's not something I'd know for sure about.
"Do you really know what I'm thinking," you ask?
Yeah. I do.
I've liked you for twenty years, so I know this much about you.
Why are you telling me this now?!
If that's true, then why have you been lying to me about the whereabouts of my head?!
Because I like you. That's why I haven't told you where your head is.
If you had found your head, you would have left.
I can't stand the thought of that.
If it means making you happy, then I'll never give up.
This is a battle over our love.
I will never let you go.
For that reason, I'm willing to use other people's love, death, myself
and although it may seem like I'm contradicting myself, even your feelings.
Even if I got my head back, I wouldn't just leave you alone.
Though that is what you think, it isn't necessarily what your head thinks.
I've given it a lot of thought.
Why have you, a fairy, appeared in this world before humans?
Isn't it because you've lost your head the reason why you're physically embodied in this world?
If that's the case, then if you got your head back and regained your memories,
wouldn't you disappear in a puff of smoke,
as if everything up until now were a mere illusion?
That's what I'm afraid of.
Will you believe what I tell you?
I believe you.
In fact, I don't believe anyone but you.
I'm afraid too. I'm afraid to die.
I understand that right now there's no one who can kill me.
It's not arrogance. I've accepted it as a fact.
I don't get any joy or emotion from it. Still...
No, because of that, I'm afraid.
The core that governs death doesn't reside inside of me.
My head is that core.
Someone could destroy my head.
And then, regardless of my will, or of my situation...
Would you believe that I, who have no eyes or brain tissue, get nightmares?
Do you believe that I tremble in fear when I get those nightmares?
It is because I'm afraid of them, and because I want to control my own death,
that I've kept looking for my head...
Do you believe me when I say that?
I said it before, didn't I? I don't trust anyone but you.
We're totally lost, aren't we?
We both have our reasons for our thoughts, neither of which are beyond the bounds of reason.
We must both look foolish.
Yeah.
Hey, Shinra.
What?
Let me hit you just once.
Okay.
Well then, let me hit you too.
Look, Certy. Your uncovered face is the most beautiful.
We just threw those punches in place of a kiss, right?
Are you crying?
It really is amazing, though.
Yo, Izaya.
Hey, Dotachin. It's been a while.
Quit calling me that.
By the way, do you know the origin of the name "Dollars"?
Is it like "Fork over the Dollars" or something like that?
No, that's not it. This organization genuinely does absolutely nothing.
We're "Dollars" because we're all "daradara."
Sluggish and lazy.
Dotachin, did you see that back there? The black biker just...
My, my. Did that really happen? Or was it a figment of my imagination?
It's like, "Was that rendered in CG?"
That "CG" character is one of the Dollars.
That's amazing! That's amazing! That's amazing!
Is that true?
To be honest, I'm surprised.
I knew there were quite a few people calling themselves Dollars on the Internet.
However, I had no idea that when you called a meeting
that this many people would show up.
Humans are more amazing than I thought.
Still, you seem to be dreaming of ridding yourself of the normal, everyday life, Mikado-kun.
Have you ever thought that if you spend half a year living the Tokyo lifestyle,
it'll become your normal, everyday life again?
After that, if it's the normal, everyday life you want to avoid, you'd have to move somewhere else,
or get involved in something more underground.
And even then...
it won't be longer than three days before that becomes your normal, everyday life again.
If you truly want to escape your normal, everyday life, you'll have to be constantly changing,
whether you're aiming for something of higher or lower standards.
Enjoy your normal, everyday life.
Out of respect for you, though,
I will give Yagiri Namie's phone number to you for free,
and I won't sell any information about you being the founder of the Dollars.
It's your organization. You should be able to take advantage of it any time you want.
Izaya.
Looks like it's time to go home at last.
Well, keep it up, Tanaka Taro-kun!
You bastard, stop right there! Izaya!
You don't mean...
The next day, everyday life returned to normal, as if nothing had happened at all.
For him, and for him,
and for that boy.
Hey, Mikado. I saw on the Net the other day that there was a Dollars meeting!
Simon and Shizuo are both Dollars!
And the black rider had no head, came riding down a wall, and took out a scythe!
It was all like, "Whoa!" I hear it was crazy!
I don't understand that one bit.
And for them, too.
I don't love you.
However, as long as I look at you, I can't forget my love for her.
Therefore, I will accept your love.
Until the day I get her back.
Good evening.
Evening. I've been awaiting orders.
Thank you.
I'm pretty sleepy today, so let's finish up early.
Ah, lack of sleep? Were you up all last night?
Yeah, kinda.
Looks like Kanra isn't here yet.
Kanra-san...
is coming, right?
Apparently he had some kind of emergency.
Is that so?
Excuse me, I have to go.
Thanks for the hard work.
Sorry to interrupt your fun. It's a last-minute job.
Not a problem.
And, my own normal, everyday life is still the same as always.
Like always, I still come across people I don't want to meet.
Looks like you lost your temper.
I mean, spirits are always supposed to be sneaky and then suddenly show up out of nowhere,
but you made quite the entrance.
Nobody's afraid of you anymore.
Speaking of which, you didn't kill anyone either.
What is that scythe, anyway? Can't you cut anything down with it?
Could it be that you're following that girl?
If you need me, I'm here to help. Gimme a call.
Later.
Yagiri Namie's whereabouts are unknown.
But that doesn't matter. I am me. I have nothing to be dissatisfied about.
These days are just like always.
Normal days without excessive hope, or despair. Nothing's different.
But what a feeling of complete fulfillment!
I am here. You are there.
If I'm your salvation, then you're my salvation too.
Also, the young man thinks about what Orihara Izaya has told him.
Can he, who aspires to an impossible reality, really seek eternity for his new reality?
Or will the new reality eventually go back to being mundane?
I'm sorry... for everything.
Thank you.
Hey, that's my seat!
There's a seat open behind the class rep.
What the heck?
You just got here, and now this?
No doubt she will stop doing things together with Harima Mika like before.
Whether that is a good thing is something only she can know.
But is that really true? Are people unable to know each other's hearts?
"You have to be constantly changing." That man's words echo in his head.
After doing something as daring as he did, he felt like he could do anything.
And yet the boy never would have imagined that asking a girl from his class out would take this much courage.
30 seconds after the boy finds the girl.
35 seconds after the boy finds his best friend courting the same girl.
45 seconds after the boy kicks his best friend across the roof.
74 seconds after that the boy's offer for tea is rejected.
78 seconds after the girl invites him to have lunch together on the roof instead.
Until the boy falls in love with the girl. Until the boy confesses his love to the girl.
However, you did something rather foolish too.
Messing everything up just for your brother's twisted heart.
Or rather, your own twisted heart for your brother.
And now, aren't you in trouble? You're about to get taken over by Nebula.
On top of it all, if you bring this up to anyone,
you'll probably get the mafia or some sniper aiming right between your eyes... bang! Checkmate.
A garbage truck?
Yeah. Same collection team as always.
Got it.
Hello? It looks like things are getting pretty complicated.
Can you get out of there right now?
You can't play one-on-one with two kings, can you?
I think your uncle must've been just like me.
Doubting the existence of the afterlife more than anyone,
fearing death more than anyone, longing for Heaven more than anyone.
However, I am convinced. There is an afterlife. Let's assume there is.
It's said that there are only females among the Dullahan. Do you know why that is?
No. Some of my subordinates have done research on the legends,
but I had thought it useless.
Now there's rationality for you.
Well, putting that aside, there's a Heaven called Valhalla...
Well technically, it's not quite the same,
but there's a story in northern European mythology about armored angels called Valkyries,
who guide the souls of brave warriors to Valhalla.
The women go to greet the dead... Don't you think you've heard that somewhere?
There's a theory that the Valkyries who roam the earth are really Dullahan.
If we assume that to be true, then this thing is just waiting.
For the time to awaken; for the time to fight.
So that she can look for a sacred warrior to bring to Valhalla.
The fact that she's alive but not awake means that this is not the battlefield.
If I could, I'd want to be chosen as that warrior.
If there's a place called Valhalla waiting for us after death, what should I do?
I don't think I can go to some conflict-ridden region and start fighting.
Therefore, all I can do is start fights that only I can win.
Am I right? What good luck I have.
That I, who don't believe in Heaven and have lived a life far from Heaven,
should happen upon an angel of death who has fallen to the earth.
You... all of that is nothing but guesswork.
Those who believe will be saved. Plus, I'm saying that this is insurance.
Even if it's hell, or suffering, as long as I'm there, I don't care.
Although, if possible, I'd like it to be Heaven.
Hey, Namie-san, let's all go to Heaven.
I'll keep this in my custody as a member of the Dollars.
It'll be hiding in plain sight.
Even Certy would never think that her head is with the very organization she's a part of.
That's right. You should join the Dollars, too.
Our boss has a policy of dragging in anyone who comes along.
Of course, I'm the one who's been gathering people the most lately.
Shall we make this fallen angel flap its wings with our own hands?
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara!!
A Sudden Turn
Her everyday life. There, nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
Although they say that in this town,
things are born and then disappear.
Next time: A Sudden Turn.