SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
That someone sung for you is happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Even if you shed tears, you cannot stop here
We're seperated a long way from tomorrow in the lights that rain without end
Let's practice with just the mouthpiece for now.
What?
Is there a problem?
No! Um...
I was just thinking that I want to be able to play music like you as soon as possible, Rio-senpai.
It'll be rough.
Yes ma'am! Please guide me!
We'll have breakfast now.
The dining room's that way. I'll head there first.
Yes, ma'am!
It's rocky and rough.
We'll be together from now on.
Good morning!
You suck!
FIRST CAMPAIGN
A STORY OF THE CHAIR
This was originally prepared to welcome you last night.
A token of kindness from us.
Thank you very much!
By the way, Rio, did you take the fish I was drying upstairs?
No, I didn't.
That's weird...
Come on, Noel.
If you want to sleep, do it after breakfast.
I'll try...
Didn't you just say you'd try?
I'm trying...
That's Rio-senpai's...
Hurry up. The food's getting cold.
Well then, let me formally introduce you to the members of Platoon 1121.
First would be the commanding officer.
I'm Second Lieutenant Felicia Heideman,
the tank commander.
Let's have a good time together.
Nice to meet you!
Over here is...
Hey, Noel...
Kannagi Noel...
She's Corporal Kannagi, the pilot.
She's in charge of the maintenance as well.
Pleased to meet you!
And finally...
Private Suminoya Kureha,
the gunner.
Listen here,
I may be younger, but I've been serving longer than you.
So you'd better do as I sa-
She overworked herself, huh?
Thanks for the hard work, Noel-chan.
Well then, let's start eating.
But...
Whatever!
Okay, help yourself.
Thanks for the food!
This is happiness.
The bacon's hand-made,
so eat a lot, okay?
I will!
Stamina is important to both soldier and trumpeter.
So eat well and grow your body.
I'll do my best.
Kureha.
Y-Yes!
Give her a tour of the base after breakfast.
Roger that...
Atten-tion!
I'm really busy right now,
but since it's an order, I'll have to show you around.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Thank you for your time, Kureha-san!
Don't act familiar with me, Private Sorami!
I'm sorry! Um...
Private Suminoya-dono!
Very well.
Let's begin. Before the platoon and national flag...
Salute!
Our Tank Platoon 1121 currently consists of five people.
They are: one Second Lieutenant, one Sergeant Major, one Corporal and two Privates.
That's five.
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono!
It's the bare minimum for a unit, so basically...
You could say we're elites.
Understood!
Our unit deploys the following ordnance:
One tank, one heavy machine gun, two light machine guns,
four rifles, and... five handguns...
Maintaining the national border of Trois, Seize with these ordnance,
is our mission!
Um...
P-Private Suminoya-dono, I have a question!
Very well.
Permission granted, Private Sorami.
Isn't-
I mean, if I remember correctly, beyond the borders of Seize is...
Indeed, beyond those mountains is No Man's Land.
But, our Helvetia Republic extends to this point.
So this is a border fort! The front line!
It's an important base!
Therefore, guard duty is critical. We perform the night watch in five shifts.
Sleeping on duty is forbidden.
And this is the one and only hotline in this town that connects to the government center.
In other words!
If it rings, it's important!
So when it does, wake everyone up and we will enter high alert.
You got that?
Yes, Private Suminoya-dono!
The CO's room and briefing room are on the second floor!
Unauthorized entry is...
Well, it's allowed.
But be sure to knock before entering!
This is the bathroom.
Heating the water and cleaning are done in turns.
And also...
Bathing order is based on rank, right?
Well, no.
Isn't taking a bath together much more fun?
Captain, what are you doing?!
I'm cleaning the bath.
Isn't it Noel's turn today?
But she seemed very tired.
You're not setting a good example as the commanding officer!
I'll do it later.
Please act with dignity appropriate for a commanding officer!
Now...
Look closely.
This is the battle tank our Platoon 1121 deploys.
The Vector-Zero Automated Walker Tank, Takemikazuchi.
It's much bigger than the one on the training grounds!
That's because she's what people call a "zero-generation" tank.
As a legacy of the old era, fewer than ten are left in this country.
I've heard of them.
They say these were amazing tanks.
But, the legs...
It's still undergoing repairs since we're short on parts.
W-Well yeah, there's not even a repair-manual,
and parts are scarce as it is.
But, Noel will do something about it, so it'll be okay!
I'm won't let you call it a mere decoration.
I'm sure she'll...
Someday...
I'm sure...
Don't take us for fools.
We slack off.
Of course, our unit slacks off.
We're even called "Seize's baggage" or "decorations" sometimes.
We're part of the Pink Corps, yet we don't have a working tank.
But...
Kureha-chan.
The tour ends here! Dismissed!
They're getting along right away, I see.
You sure?
They're just like us when we first met.
I suppose.
There's only one thing that worries me.
Last night, after you left to put Kana-chan to sleep...
Captain, why is she a signaller?!
Weren't reservists supposed to be either loaders or a pilots?
I can't help it. Heaquarters sent her to us.
Things don't always work out the way we want.
But...
Calm down, it'll be okay.
Rio will look out for you.
Just like always.
Of course, I'll do the same.
She doesn't look like it, but she's perceptive. She might have guessed what's going on.
I see.
We'll have to do something about it.
It showed up.
What did?
A ghost?!
Yeah.
That's just foolish.
You must've been daydreaming like always.
I thought so.
What do you mean, "thought so"?
I saw a ghost, too.
At the barracks, right?
Yeah.
Hey, what are you saying?!
But, aren't ghosts common?
I told you to stop saying that!
Noel, you're not any better.
As an engineer, you should report after properly and scientifically investigating it yourself!
No way.
Why?
It's scary.
What are you talking about?!
There's no such thing as ghosts!
There's none! There's none! I refuse to believe it!
I agree with you.
Right?
Of course.
Ghosts don't exist!
They don't!
They absolutely don't!
It's absolutely absolute!
Okay!
Investigate the perimeter thoroughly!
Just blow your trumpet if you encounter the enemy!
I'll send reinforcements right away!
Why?
Um, Private-dono.
What do you want, Kana- Private!
This is a little... exciting, isn't it?
The thunder sounds like a marching drum.
This is a mission!
We're not here to play around.
Listen up, Kana- Private Sorami.
You take point, I'll cover you.
Yes, ma'am!
Then, move out!
They say this wing remains as it was before this building became a fortress.
What was it used for before?
How would I know?
Just go!
Okay.
Ideographs.
I wonder what's written in it.
Don't just randomly look at stuff you can't even read.
It would be great if I could read it.
It's just some silly nonsense from long ago.
Let's keep moving.
Aren't you scared?
Nope.
You're dense.
But, aren't ghosts supposed to protect us?
What?
Well, in my hometown, we held an annual festival to thank the ghosts.
What kind of backwater place is that?
What you call a "ghost",
is something that possesses people, sucks blood, moves corpses,
and does all sorts of bad things.
That was a close call.
They say rats carry all sorts of disease...
What? So you do get scared after-
Are they gone?
Seems like it.
Hey, Kureha.
Private-dono.
I was thinking, this place could have been a school.
There's no school building this big, even in the government center.
But, long ago there were more people, right?
So back then, there must have been lots of kids our age gathering in this building,
studying together.
What, what? What is it?
They must have studied music in here.
Without being in the military?
Just look at this.
Nothing changed.
Even if I can't read it -
D-sharp.
- these notes...
...never change.
What are you getting lost in thought for?
Now what?!
Hey, Kureha-chan, isn't it lovely?
What is?
Everything!
Huh?
This town of Seize, this fortress,
and everyone in this unit!
We're just a small and insignificant unit in the countryside.
The tank isn't working, and they often forget to resupply us.
We're assigned useless missions.
We always slack off.
But you love it here.
No way! Stay away!
What, what? What?!
It appeared!
No! Wait for me, Kureha!
Kanata!
Amazing.
Of course!
I'm the gunner of this very wonderful Platoon 1121 that I love so much, after all!
So this is the true form of the ghost, huh?
What's so ghostly about it anyway?
Hey, you. You look exactly like yesterday's thief.
I'll put you on a spit!
You can't scare an injured animal like that, Rio.
But...
It must've had nowhere else to go, either.
Also, why don't you tell me what our unit's symbol is.
We'd be punished if we tried to barbecue it.
Right, Shuko-chan?
It has a name already?
But, I think this is wonderful.
You almost died yesterday because of this thing, you know?
But, thanks to it, I had a great adventure today.
Right, Kureha-chan?
What are you saying?
That doesn't even qualify as an adventure!
My, my. I guess this is majority rule, huh?
No, it's a commanding officer's order.
But the next time you steal food, I'll punish you.
Okay?
You did the morning call today, Rio?
If Kanata were to do it every day, we'd get complaints from the townspeople.
I'm sorry.
That's your seat, Kana-chan.
Kureha-chan?
I just happened to find a matching chair.
It's not like I did it for you...
Thank you!
Hey, stop it! Jeez!
What are you doing?
That's dangerous.
Seriously, what are you doing?
The food...
Pile up the feelings of love and friendship
Performing is also important
I cried happily
I laughed eagerly
But all of them make me alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me why we dance
you just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I want them to echo forever
Speaking endless words touched by love
Our harmony
I can hear our harmony
THE SQUAD'S DAY - RIO RUNS
Next episode: The Squad`s Day: Rio Runs
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.