"11 Years Ago, The Day Reia Died・(History)"
Mom? Where are you?
"Dear Kureha, I'm going to send her back
through the door. Don't worry, okay?"
Who's "her"? What's the door?
You found Kureha that day.
I can't let Kureha's precious friend be excluded.
Growl?
Someday, the time will come when
bears and people can be friends forever.
Take this pendant with you.
It's a love charm. I know it will help you.
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become
true friends with you. To cross the wall...
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"THE DOOR TO FRIENDSHIP"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
Don't move!
Rowr?
I came way close to taking you
for a bear and shooting you.
Don't do things that'll confuse people!
Growl... I thought I was way busted...
Did you say something?
N-N-No, growl! U-Um... what's that truck?
A special vehicle developed
just for bear annihilation.
"Bear-Killing Beam Truck・(Weapon of Destruction)"
Shock!
Bear shock!
Nasty!
Buzz buzz! Nasty nasty!
We cyborgized the dead bear,
and we're using her to generate electricity.
Fight fire with fire! And bears with bears.
Eco-kumagical! Nasty!
So, have you seen any bears in this area?
We have reports of another bear
sighting near the school this morning.
I-I know nothing, growl.
Oh.
R-Really! I haven't seen one single bear, growl!
The bears will get you, too,
if you hang out here all alone.
You should watch out.
Growl... That was close!
Anyway, if it's not here either,
where should I look next?
I don't understand it. Why did
Lulu Yurigasaki betray Ginko Yurishiro?
I thought she wished for Ginko
Yurishiro's love to be returned.
Her actions are inconsistent.
You're so dense. It's because
Lulu Yurigasaki loves Ginko Yurishiro.
Sparkle!
Love comes in many forms.
Perhaps that's why Kumaria questions
everyone who tries to go beyond severance:
"Is your love the real thing?"
Then she laid down a ladder for the girls,
connecting the two worlds.
A single, vast mirror stood
like a wall in their path.
Each girl saw her own reflection in the mirror.
--They heard Kumaria's voice say,
--Everyone, our friendship
--"Now, your friend is waiting on the other side of that door.
--is now being put to the test!
--The Wall of Severance has broken down,
--If you smash the 'you' in the mirror to bits,
--thanks to evil's way unfair betrayal.
--I if you tear it apart,
--There's nothing protecting us now!
--she shall grant you a Promise Kiss.
--Which is exactly why we must fight!
--Let's exclude the bear lurking among us
--But beware: this may cost you your life.
--with our own hands,
--and take back our invisible lives!
--I will ask you one more time: Is your love the real thing?"
Here it is!
All right!
The girls stared at themselves in the mirror.
This is the rest of the book...
The future Mom wanted to tell me about.
"The Moon Girl and the Forest Girl"
The moon girl summoned up all her courage.
"I want to cross the sky.
So I will smash myself."
The forest girl steeled herself as well.
"I want to cross the sky.
So I will tear myself apart."
"My love is true!"
The mirror shattered in an instant.
And they each found their friend
standing on the other side.
The two girls walked slowly up to each other
and simply, wordlessly gave
each other their Promise Kisses.
And so, having completed their Promise Kiss,
the two began a journey beyond
severance, guided by the star of love.
This is our destiny? Our rightful future?
She and I... Ginko and I
will go beyond severance?
A bear and a human?
That future just isn't possible.
Yes?
A prank?
Wait.
That's Mom's!
I came to give it back, growl.
Okay, I'll go now.
Wait!
Um... well...
Um... want a bath before you go?
Mom used to wash my hair
like this, way back when.
It was Miss Yuriika who killed my mother.
She was a bear, like you two.
But she died.
May I ask you something?
What?
I know that Mitsuko Yurizono
was the one who killed Sumika.
So why did Ginko tell me she did it?
Because...
That's what Ginko thinks, growl.
She knew that Mitsuko was after Sumika.
But she didn't save her. She couldn't.
What do you mean?
She loves you, Kure-chin,
so she wanted your love.
But with Sumika around,
she wouldn't be able to get that love.
Ginko was jealous of Sumika.
But I'm no better.
I was jealous of you.
That's why I said those things...
"Flashback"
Ginko was Sumika's killer's accomplice!
I felt like you'd stolen Ginko's love from me...
Isn't that weird,
after I wished all this time for
you two to do your Promise Kiss?
I'm sorry, Kure-chin.
So this really was the key.
See, that proves you were friends, right?
Ginko won't lie to you. She can't, growl.
Because you're her precious friend.
Precious friend...
--Growl...
Growl!
That was...
Did you remember something, Kure-chin?
It's no good. I still can't remember.
Growl...
But...
My mom told me. Ginko was my friend.
The girl I loved, who sang the love song
with me when I was little, was Ginko.
And yet I forgot her.
I can't even remember her now.
Why? Why are my only missing
memories the ones of Ginko?
What happened between us?
Ginko loves you anyway, you know.
Then and now...
Ginko doesn't back down on love.
Kure-chin, will you forgive her?
Growl... Will you please be her friend again?
Will you please love her again?
I... can't.
Humans and bears...
we have severance between us.
No one can overcome it.
I guess you're right...
Lost love never comes back.
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Tsubaki, you're in trouble!
You have a bear targeting you!
What?
Ginko Yurishiro and Lulu Yurigasaki
are really bears in disguise!
We just found evidence. One of them
must be the bear you missed on the roof!
Which means you're way in danger!
She's bound to come for her revenge!
Call us the second you
sense a bear nearby, got it?
Yes, I understand.
It's there.
Charge!
"Flashback"
I don't want to be alone.
Who's that?
She must've caught on.
But we won't let her escape.
Growl... Why are you helping me?
I don't know. But I'm sure
it's the right thing to do!
Search every corner of the neighborhood.
It's time for our final sprint.
Say, Kure-chin... I think I might know
the reason you lost your memory.
What?
For a bear to become a girl,
she has to make a deal.
A deal? With whom?
With what stands between humans
and bears--the Wall of Severance.
The Wall... You mean the men on the phone?!
Yeah. If they grant a bear yuri
approval in court, she can become a girl.
But to do that, you have to let go
of whatever you care about most.
What do you mean?
This is just my theory, but I bet in
Ginko's trial, she let go of your love.
My love...?
Right, the love you gave
her all those years ago.
That's why Ginko disappeared from your memory.
That's awful!
Muahaha! I'm so clever--right?
Yeah...
So I'm sure you can get it back.
Get what back?
Your love for Ginko.
Because you didn't really give up on love.
That's what I believe. And now this
really is goodbye, huh, Kure-chin?
Lulu?!
Lulu Yurigasaki has revealed the secret
of transformation to a third party.
Her yuri approval is terminated,
effective immediately.
Aw! Can't we do something?
No, we cannot. Rules are cool.
Lulu, is that you?
Growl...
Sorry, Kure-chin. I told you the truth,
so I can't be a girl anymore.
We can't be together anymore.
Goodbye, Kure-chin!
Found you!
Fire!
Firing!
Nasty.
Nasty, nasty!
This is a way different bear!
Kure... chin...?
I won't let a friend be excluded!
"Flashback"
"The Day They Met・(History)"
Who's that? Who's calling me?
Where are you?
"There is one way to make your wish come true.
In the center of the sky, there is
a place called the Door to Friendship.
If your love is true,
your friend will be waiting for you...
...on the other side."
That's the "Door to Friendship"
that was in the picture book!
I met Ginko on the other side!
Kure-chin?
It is! I know it!
"Flashback"
Who is it? Who's calling me?
Why are you calling me?
Growl...
Are you the one who called me?
It's okay, you're not alone. I'm your friend!
That's right. This is where it all began.
I crossed the Wall of Severance
that day and met Ginko.
Ginko, you're my friend.
And I...
I love you!
You can get to the other side
of the wall through here.
You can go safely back to the bear world.
Kure-chin...
Growl... Did I manage to become your friend?
No. You are not my friend.
I told you, I won't forgive bears.
The next time I see you, I'll shoot.
I know I'll kill you.
Kure-chin...
Go. Get out of here, now. Never come back!
Not to this stupid world.
This was the right thing to do.
I knew the evil was you.
"Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
The lily opens!
I way saw what you did. Who knew this
was a secret passage through severance?
You're the one who brought
bears into our school.
You joined the bears, and you've been
taking revenge on us for excluding you!
No!
Kureha Tsubaki, you're going to pay
for taking our friends' lives.
All right, the hunt's just beginning!
I found her.
I'm going to eat her, growl.
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love
We now begin the Yuri Trial.