Nice to meet you all! We are-
Diamond Dust.
We're releasing our debut single-
Time's ticking. This place isn't free, you know.
I still think we should try finding a bassist.
Would be nice if we could.
But I think we're doing pretty well
with just the three of us for now.
What is it?
Who was that girl talking just now?
No clue. Probably their new vocalist.
Never saw her before.
Did something about her catch your eye?
...It can't be, right?
Nevermind, it was nothing.
RAISE YOUR VOICE
Yo.
If it isn't Momo-chan! How many years has it been?
Come on, less than two probably.
I see this place hasn't changed much.
Sure it has, we're a hair away from going under here!
You're our only hope.
Is that you?
No way, you were so cute!
Oh shut it.
They just look alike...right?
Nina.
Uh, yes?
You can take a look inside if you want.
We're coming in.
It's much smaller than the stage we played on.
We're supposed to fit in here, huh?
Most live houses are about this size.
Though this one's been around for a while,
so it has its regulars.
And they won't go easy on us.
The boss said he'd like us to give it a shot.
What do you think?
A concert?
Don't push yourself if you're not feeling up to it.
We should probably practice some mo-
I'll do it.
At least hesitate a little.
She's totally hooked now...you'd never think
she was freaking out so much last time.
Well, we're talking about a 20-minute performance here.
So it shouldn't be that big a deal.
Let's try it.
And here are your tickets.
By the way, you're not allowed to advertise me
as a former Diamond Dust member, got it?
I'm in a new band with these two, and-
Here.
No turning back now.
What?
THE NEXT DAY
I didn't think we'd have to sell those ourselves...
DID YOU SELL ANY?
THERE'S NO WAY I DID
I ONLY HAVE TWO LEFT
NO WAY!?
TRY YOUR PREP SCHOOL, THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMEONE THERE
IT'S NOT YOUR HOMETOWN, SO IT'S NOT LIKE ANYONE WILL RECOGNIZE YOU
What do you want?
Well, uh, I'm doing a concert with my band...
You...interested?
You're in a band?
Yes.
I'm more into heavy metal...
That's totally cool, we're uhhh...
sort of something like that.
And you just gave it to her for free?
Customers over profits!
It's not like we're doing this for money.
The point is to get lots of
people to come, isn't it?
They won't come.
Here's a life lesson for you.
People hate it when something they paid for goes to waste.
But if it was something they got
for free, they won't care.
Also, giving out tickets for free
means we're the ones paying for them.
-You really don't know anything, huh?
-Know what?
Technically, we're the ones
buying those tickets.
We paid the live house for them.
Here you go.
The minimum amount of tickets you need
to sell is lower these days,
but in general, if you want to perform,
you need to pay performing fees
and for a minimum amount of tickets.
That way even if no one comes to your concert,
the live house is guaranteed at least the bare minimum profit.
That's not fair!
That's how the business works!
Oh really...
Huh?
Here.
Sorry for bothering you during your break.
What do you want?
I wish Momoka-san told us she was
paying for those tickets...
Well, we're basically kids to her.
How come?
We're younger, and we're not exactly
functioning members of society yet.
Hmm?
Hey, Momo-chan's friends!
Hi there!
Is this a new thing?
Uhh, where was it again...
Is he trying to sell us tickets again?
I don't think so.
Oh, there they are.
Here you go.
What are these?
Diamond Dust, that band that's getting their big break now,
they used to play here a lot.
So they paid a visit earlier and left these.
And you're giving them to us?
They have this big agency backing them now,
So I kind of lost interest.
Do you know why Momoka-san left Diamond Dust?
She didn't tell you?
No.
I don't know the details myself,
but apparently the agency started making
a lot of changes to the band.
Their look, songs and all that.
She hated the idea and left.
I have a ticket for her too if you want.
So, are you gonna give it to her?
No. I feel like we'll get into a fight if I do.
But I...I want to see them for myself.
Wanna go together then?
I'm kinda curious myself.
Subaru-chan...
THE NEXT DAY
You're the girl that gave me
concert tickets before, right?
Yes.
Do you still have some left?
Three of my friends want to come.
That'll be 7500 yen in total.
Eh, you were charging for them?
You don't have to buy if you don't want to.
You can't just flip it on her like that.
Well what was I supposed to do?
Something like "We were told to give them away at first so I did,
but then the live house suddenly changed their mind!
But since you're already a valuable customer,
I'll cut you a deal -
Three for 2500 each instead of 3000 each. Sound good?"
- That's called lying.
- That's called working hard.
Numbers 500 to 550, please enter the venue.
What is it?
A full house, huh.
Stationary at a crossroads
that doesn't appear on any map
What can I rely on
to find my way?
It's your own fault, you know.
No way.
It can't be.
Everything is so white
Everything is so slow
All the answers are
void of substance
Don't you dare sing that song.
Wait!
I said wait! It's barely been 5 minutes
since the concert started, what's gotten into-
- Subaru-chan.
- What?
I'm this close to saying some
really nasty things right now.
Just give me a sec.
I need to let everything out.
*indistinguishable gremlin noises*
Damn it,
JUST DIE!
I think I understood that last part.
What is this, what is this, WHAT IS GOING ON??
Don't ask me.
And it just had to be Diamond Dust.
The one thing that's as precious to me as my life. My treasure.
Are you going to explain what's going on?
Their new singer.
I know her.
We used to be friends, but not anymore.
Not anymore!
Girls Band Cry.
Nice to meet you all! We are-
Diamond Dust!
It's gonna break, you know.
I don't want to listen to that.
You barge into their concert, get pissed,
and now you're acting like this.
Do you know what they call people like that?
Toxic fans.
You can't possibly understand how I'm feeling right now.
Good, because I don't want to.
How is this even possible?
How did that girl even become Diamond Dust's vocalist?!
That shallow little-
Well, if she's there, it means she
stood out enough to pass the auditions.
So what if she-
Oh shut it already.
This is your problem, not theirs.
Maybe it is, but I love and listen to Diamond Dust
more than anyone else in that audience!
This is exactly what makes you a toxic fan.
Diamond Dust doesn't exist just for you.
Then what about you,
are you really okay with this?
Why wouldn't I be?
They seem to be more popular than when I was there.
So you're fine as long as they're popular?
It's better than them not being popular.
That's not what I'm asking!
You're always sticking your nose
into other people's business.
Like I said before, wasting time here
means wasting money.
Subaru.
This is pointless.
We can't practice with you two like this.
If you have steam to blow off,
better do it sooner than later.
IZAKAYA
- Well?
- Hold on a sec.
That was not necessary.
Also, who comes to a bar
in their school uniform?
It's not like I'm drinking alcohol.
Why are you always in your uniform anyway?
Saves me the pain of choosing outfits.
Also, high school girls get a lot of perks.
Liar.
Anyway, enough about me, have at it you two.
Why are you always sticking up for them?
I'm not sticking up for them or anything.
Yes you are. Think about it,
the current Diamond Dust has nothing
to do with the Diamond Dust you were in.
So?
Then why are you defending them? It makes no sense.
I don't get the problem here.
I'm not involved with them anymore. They can do whatever they want.
Whatever path they choose,
I don't have the right to complain.
I'm not asking for the right answer.
I want to know how you actually feel about this.
Whatever.
I don't really care.
But it was your band.
The band you put your soul into.
Don't just make your own assumptions about me.
Fine, then I was wrong.
I guess Diamond Dust was
completely meaningless to you.
Oh, give me a break.
It's the new singer that's actually bothering you, isn't it?
That's not it!
I'm asking if you're really okay with the new Diamond Dust!
Sorry everyone, please don't pay us any mind.
Guys, turn down the volume a bit.
Listen,
Bands grow and change, just like people.
It's an inevitable process.
Then why did you leave?
You left because you didn't like
that change you're talking about.
Because they were becoming something
different from the Diamond Dust you knew.
Because you were sure you weren't in the wrong.
Because you hate what they're doing now!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Was the song I always listened to meaningless?
I always thought that song was the heart and soul of DD.
Just admit they changed!
That whatever that was
isn't the real Diamond Dust anymore!
That they're-
Ugh...
Shut up.
I won't.
I loved your Diamond Dust
more than anything.
Everything is so white
Everything is so slow
All the answers
I loved your Diamond Dust
more than anything.
That song changed my life.
You can't just abandon it like that!
You hate it, and you still tell yourself that
you're in the wrong and they're not.
I don't want you to lie to yourself.
Do you know what the original
Diamond Dust's dream was?
What was it?
To stay as a band together, with the
original members, until we were all wrinkled.
To never quit no matter what.
That was it. None of us cared about music style
or anything like that at first.
That's why it's my fault.
"Grit your teeth for now."
"Once we make it big, we'll be
able to play the way we want to."
They did everything they
could to make me stay.
But it didn't work. I left them behind.
Here you go. Oolong tea.
Thank you very much.
Nina.
Sorry for the commotion everyone!
Even so...
I'm still a fan of yours.
Because I love your music.
Because the original Diamond Dust is the
only thing that touched my heart back then.
And you were the heart of it.
Idiot.
You're making a mess of yourself.
I know I'm an idiot.
I wouldn't be here if I wasn't one.
Keep the drinks coming!
Subaru-chan...
Huh? Hey, wai-
Sorry, your face pissed me off.
Momoka-san, I thought you could hold your liquor...
Well, she did go at it pretty hard today.
She reeks of alcohol...
Hold up, you're dragging her!
- Subaru-chan, grab the legs!
- Yessir!
Like this?
I don't think that's gonna work...
Momoka-san? We're going to
put you down for a second...
I'm sorry.
Maybe she was happy, you know.
No...
I don't think that's it.
You should be the one to
choose our stage outfits.
Having a friend you had a falling out with
become the singer of your favorite group
isn't exactly a common experience.
You should make something out of it.
How?
Letting your anger, joy,
and sadness run free,
that's the great thing about being in a band.
What's this?
The poster for our concert.
"Featuring Momoka, former member of Diamond Dust"?
He's got some nerve!
But you know, a good chunk of the people
that went to DD's debut live
will definitely come thanks to this.
Try to think about what kind of
impact you'd want to make on them.
You're right.
Outfits, huh...
It's not like we have much money to spend...
It's been three years already.
Yeah, we were thinking
we'll have to make a big impact
at the next competition.
Ah, Momo-chan!
Yo.
Sorry!
I told them not to write your name, but I guess
the staff couldn't pass up the opportunity.
But you see, we got a full house thanks to that.
Huh, what?
So, do we have our outfits?
Yes. I was thinking these would be good.
Here.
Did you make them together?
We're open to criticism.
Though you'll still have to wear them.
Let's bare it all together.
I see.
I like it.
You're supposed to be Momoka?
Yeah, what of it?
Sorry, but girly music's not my thing.
Mind if I shake the atmosphere up a bit before you're up?
We don't really care...
Don't worry about us, we'll shake it ourselves.
If you say so.
Nice one.
Momo-san!
Momoka!
Momoka! We love you!
Wanna start?
Impact...it's a nice word, don't you think?
We struggle, we exhaust ourselves...
we want to stick it to someone, even
at the cost of getting hurt ourselves.
Yeah.
You know, your song...
it pierced through my heart.
It had an impact on me.
It's as if it was telling me,
"Don't give up, even if you die trying".
Let's make that impact!
Scream out everything you're feeling.
Leave nothing out.
Let out all your frustrations, your shame,
yout anger, your sadness,
your pathetic self, that past you hate
so much you want to
crawl into a bed and die, and all those regrets that haunt you.
Lay them all bare!
Here we go!
LIAR
COWARD
This is everything I've got!
DROPOUT
What we found
at this tumultuous crossroads
Hollow words
that end up crumbling
A shooting star could
sweep everything away
And yet, nothing seems to change
We lie
to keep our hands clean
Our dreams falling apart in the distance
We pretend nothing
we hear nothing
Watch the storm pass by
The city is caught
in a whirlwind of truth
Where should we
let ourselves be carried?
If we can smile at the end
May our hands be tied
It's reality
But we will only understand
once our dreams are abandoned
Our wishes are never heard
In a distorted world
What can we do?
What can we improve?
Will you finally be discovered?
Before everything collapses
Let's shape in the shadows
The vision that drives us