What is this?
I'll be joining the battle, too!
You'd better entertain me, at least a little.
Open.
A battle has begun. It's close.
Is it Chi-chan?
I don't know.
Emergency.
Let's hurry.
We're back!
Taiyaki!
Wh-What is this?
What's going on?
That's right.
I fought Selector battles here, too...
Chi-chan...
I'll go first.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
Hello!
It's Aya, everyone's little sister!
Really? I'm doing support again?
Turn end.
You know how to use a key card, right?
A second LRIG already...
Kiyoi!
I know.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
It feels strange...
It's my own body, but it feels
like it's been so long...
Donor.
I'm going to ask for your help right away.
Okay!
Wh-What do we do?
Don't panic.
We're just equal now.
Aya.
Coin bet.
Yes!
Holograph!
I'm sorry!
Magical WIXOSS, Slow-ko!
Now, attack. Go!
I'm sorry!
Get yer butt in gear and go!
They're coming!
Donor, coin bet.
Escape!
Tch! What the hell are you doing, idiot?
I'm sorry!
She's strong...
You can tell, Chi-chan?
I still can't really remember
the rules in detail,
but I can feel it...
She has a strong desire
to win, no matter what.
By the way, I want to check something.
Are you fighting to beat me?
What do you mean?
I mean you can't win like this.
You need to work a little harder,
little bitch!
No, Kiyoi!
Don't let him provoke you!
It's what he wants!
Don't worry. I know.
But what Carnival is saying makes sense.
I can't win like this.
Kiyoi, you're not planning to
become the third LRIG, are you?
Don't! It's too dangerous!
If I want to win, I need to gamble.
Okay.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
Wh-What?
Donor?
Kiyoi, Donor just...
So you can only have two
LRIGs on the field at once?
Too bad.
Looks like your plan didn't work out.
It's not really a problem.
I know the rules now.
Piruluk.
Right.
Coin bet.
Catharsis.
Mizushima Kiyoi...
This power is a problem.
I guess it's time.
If I decide to crush you,
I'm going to crush you hard.
So you can never stand up again.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
No way...
Why can Carnival use three LRIGs at once?
I'm special!
Now, let's end this.
Slow-ko, Aya.
Summon Hurricane, Tsunawata.
Now, how will you stop me?
What happens to a Selector when
they run out of coins, I wonder?
I can't want to find out, Mizushima Kiyoi.
H-Hey, what's wrong? Let's finish it.
Now, of all times...
What just happened?
A forced ending to the game
without someone else interfering?
And Carnival is gone?
Are we... saved? I guess?
If that battle had gone on...
I would've lost.
Chi-chan!
Suzu?
Are you okay?
You haven't fought yet, have you?
Y-Yeah.
Carnival came after her,
but Kiyoi came in at the last second.
Kiyoi-chan did?
Wait... Huh?
Donor-san?
Shock.
Why did you become an LRIG again?
Oh, well, um...
What do you plan to do with all these LRIGs?
Your style is to become an LRIG
yourself and fight, right?
You don't even need other LRIGs.
At least give back Midoriko and Hanayo-san.
I can't.
The rule is you can't give someone
an LRIG unless you lose a battle.
Are you telling me to lose deliberately?
That girl with the glasses
just needs to get stronger.
Strong enough to beat me.
The weak don't have the
right to say anything.
What is it you're after?
I want to defeat that monster.
Just do it already!
Um, I'm with Pizza Hattori.
I have the pizza you ordered.
Thanks.
Right on time.
Th-Thanks.
Eat. You passed.
What? Are you screwing with me?
I like the self-destructive way you fight.
You want to fight strong opponents, right?
If you help me, I'll set up
as many fights as you want.
What are you about to do?
Make the Selector battles more exciting.
Make them fun and cheerful,
the way I like them.
I can't beat him like this.
I'm going to fight more battles
and beat him, no matter what.
What are you thinking?
I don't want you interfering in my battles.
You're messing up my plans.
It won't open.
The door won't open.
The door? What do you mean?
Don't you just need enough
keys to open the door?
It's broken.
The keyhole is broken.
The keyhole? What do you mean?
A new keyhole will appear soon.
The first door was...
The door to the outside.
The door to the girls.
They opened the door and left.
The girls left.
The girls?
Bring the keyhole here.
The keyhole. Bring it here.
Understanding.
It seems Carnival is indeed a unique being.
Chi-chan...
I really don't want you getting
involved in these Selector battles.
Suzu...
I don't know what will happen
if you lose your memories,
but I know you won't escape
unscathed this time.
I don't want you to get involved
in something so dangerous.
Thank you, Suzu.
But I feel the same way.
If the battles are that dangerous,
I don't want you to get involved.
Especially if you're saying it's for me...
I couldn't take that.
Chi-chan...
You're both very kind.
Suggestion.
If you both want the same thing,
why not settle it with a battle?
A battle?
If you can't avoid the battles,
the best thing to do is
minimize the risk of defeat
and maximize your chance of winning.
You two can battle, and the stronger
is entrusted with the other's LRIG
to maximize their chance
of getting what they want.
Entrust your LRIG...
...to the stronger?
But if you battle,
one of you will lose a coin.
Naturally.
But if you fight someone you can trust,
you can fight them again
to get the coin back.
That's the neverending draw plan
that Shou-chan talked about.
It carries some risk,
but I think it's a very effective
method of buying some time.
But Chi-chan, you've lost most of your
memories about the battles, right?
If you fight Suzu right now...
But I still need to win,
or Suzu will fight.
So I have to win, right?
Help me, Meru.
Chi-chan...
Right.
Chi-chan, hold up your card.
Open!
We don't want to lose any coins,
so neither of us should do a coin bet.
A coin bet?
The technique Mizushima-san
and her opponent used.
If there's anything you
don't understand, ask me.
Thanks, Meru.
Here I go, Chi-chan.
Grow.
Play Arm, Kukuri, Nunchaku.
Turn end.
It's my turn... Um...
I'll place some ENER and attack.
Chi-chan, you haven't grown yet.
Chi-chan?
Suzuko...
I know.
It's my turn.
Full attack.
Riru, attack!
Meru! I'm sorry... I...
It's okay.
Do you remember a little now?
You and I fought together.
Meru...
Yeah.
You were always there for me.
And you still are.
You fight with your LRIG.
That's what WIXOSS is.
Yeah.
Meru, grow!
Elegant Moonlit Evening!
Three Orders, Five Explanations!
It's my third time battling Chi-chan.
The first time, Chi-chan was
trying to get rid of me.
The second, I was trying to protect her.
And the third...
Chi-chan, for the first time,
I'm having fun battling!
ARTS: Grab the Chestnut from the Fire!
I'm having fun, too, Suzu!
Guard!
They both look so happy...
Envy.
This is what a battle should be, right?
Chi-chan, are you okay?
Yeah.
It's a little strange.
I've lost all my memories of the
previous Selector battles, but...
I want to keep going.
But...
Thank you, Suzu.
Chi-chan...
Once these Selector battles are over,
let's play WIXOSS again!
See Through the Fiery Ambition!
I'm sorry, Meru.
I lost.
No, it was fun fighting with you.
Leave the rest to us.
Yeah. Thanks.
Suzu, take care of Meru, okay?
Chi-chan...
Can you still tell me that Suzuko-san
should get her memories back?
Leave it to me.
But I'm not planning on sitting this out.
I lost my LRIG,
but I think I can help you with
things other than the battles.
I want to help you as you fight.
Then you're one of us now.
One of you?
Acknowledgement.
I welcome you.
Glad to have you, Morikawa Chinatsu-san.
Yeah!
Panties, panties!
Hey, fold them up!
Jeez.
I knew it! It's you, Hitoe!
I saw you from the veranda.
Did you need something?
Huh? Why do you have two bags?
Hitoe? Wait! Hitoe!
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
I'm about to have some hot milk with Tama.
Want to join me?
Help me...
Help me, Ruuko...
Hitoe...
Huh? You and Yuzuki were chosen as Selectors?
A new series of Selector battles has begun.
With the new rules, Selectors become LRIGs,
and if you lose, your LRIG is taken away...
You mean Yuzuki became an LRIG,
and her opponent took her?
Why didn't you tell me?
You can't just not tell me!
I didn't want to get you involved...
You or Tama-chan...
That voice... I know it.
Hitoe...
Yuzuki...
Ruu...
I...
Ruu, I'll...
Tama!
I'll help you!
Tama-chan?
I want to help Yuzuki!
And you, too!
Because you're my dear friends!
But...
Do you know what you're saying, Tama?
Yeah.
I heard a voice.
Again and again...
A voice calling me.
If I can save everyone, I'll fight!
I'll do the battles!
But...
It'll be okay!
Everyone is with me!
Ruu, and Hitoe, and Yuzuki!
Tama...
We're together... together forever...
So I'll fight with you.
Let's fight together, Tama!
Yeah!
Tama!
Tama-chan?
Tama...
Ruuko, you were chosen to be a Selector?
Let's do our best, Ruu!
Let's save everyone together!
Yeah!
Just as planned.
Now, at last, all the pieces are in place.
And...
the keyhole, too.
Determination / Warmth and Pain
Everything went well because
Kiyoi-chan was here.
Let's play with Kiyoi-chan!
I want to see Mizushima
Kiyoi-chan, no matter what!
I want to see her, no matter what!
If I do, I can become happy!
Let's hide!
Attachment / Trick and Trap
Attachment / Trick and Trap.