Everything went splendidly.
These games of yours squander my time,
Tokiomi.
I am very grateful, king amongst kings...
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh.
Your actions will establish your prowess as the King of Heroes.
And they will reveal which of our foes we must hunt.
I ask only that you stay your hand,
just for a short while longer.
Very well.
For the time being, I shall amuse myself with simple reconnaissance.
This era is fascinating.
The modern world is to your liking?
It's unspeakably ugly.
But in its own way, it pleases me.
The important thing is whether any treasures here are worthy of me.
If there is nothing here that deserves my adoration,
you will pay dearly for summoning me,
Tokiomi.
Worry not.
The Holy Grail is without doubt an item worthy of the King of Heroes.
That is for me to determine.
Let's leave that aside for now.
I'll go along with your schemes for the time being.
Everything of value in this world belongs to me.
No matter how precious a treasure this Grail of yours may be,
I'll never let anyone have it without my permission.
Tokiomi, I'll leave the details to you.
My, my...
Honestly...
I'm still amazed that Gilgamesh was summoned
as a member of the Archer class, considering their Independent Action class skill.
Well, I can let Kirei handle things from here.
Everything is proceeding as planned for now.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
Assassin was killed?
Hey, Rider... This is a big deal.
One of the seven masters has already lost.
Hey...
Hey! Do you not understand?
Assassin was killed!
The Holy Grail War has started!
I've been out, gathering information,
and you do the same thing day after day after day... Every single day!
You just sit around eating cookies and watching stuff on the VCR!
You're worse than a familiar... Worse than a rat!
And I told you to take spirit form when you're not needed!
I've given you all the necessary prana.
Kid, no one cares about Assassin.
He's only good at cowering in the shadows.
He could never pose a threat to me.
Anyway, boy...
Here, this is what matters!
This... The big black B-2 thing.
It's wonderful!
I'm thinking of buying ten or so. What do you think?
With that much money, you might as well just well just buy the whole country.
Oh... I see!
So, the question is where to acquire the funds.
Were there some major capital like Persepolis nearby,
we could simply go forth and raid it...
For now, it seems our biggest obstacle will be this "Clinton" guy!
He might prove to be a more formidable opponent than even Darius III.
R-Regardless...
It's good that Assassin was eliminated first.
Aren't you the type who always faces the enemy head-on?
So it's best for us that the guy who'd use smoke and mirrors is out.
We could get some good use from this Tomahawk thing, too!
Saber, Lancer, Archer, the three great Knight classes...
And Berserker, whose sole skill is to wreak havoc.
They're gonna be toast when you use that Noble Phantasm of yours!
Which just leaves Caster...
If only we knew Caster's identity—
How did Assassin fall?
Who was it that defeated him?
You saw it, right?
I think it was Tohsaka's Servant.
His appearance, his attacks,
everything was golden and flashy.
It all happened so fast, I couldn't tell—
Fool!
If I am to fight someone, it will of course be the victor!
Why weren't you paying closer attention to him?
Well, it matters not.
Did you observe anything else about the flashy gold guy?
It was the middle of the night...
And it was over in an instant...
Hey, Rider... Normally, a Servant only has one Noble Phantasm, right?
That's the rule.
But do not linger on the number of Noble Phantasms.
As you know, a Noble Phantasm
is the physical manifestation of a hero's legend or tale.
Sometimes, it may be a specific ability or method of attack.
Then is there a Noble Phantasm that consists of throwing dozens of swords at an opponent?
A sword that splits into infinite copies?
It's possible...
That could still qualify as a single Noble Phantasm.
But those weren't copies. Each sword had a different shape.
Ah, whatever.
We'll learn its true identity when we encounter him.
I-Is that really wise?
It is!
Actually, it's more fun this way!
Food, sex, sleep and war...
Whatever you do, enjoy it thoroughly.
That is the secret of life.
Now, let's go find some entertainment outside.
We're heading out, boy! Prepare yourself.
H-Heading out? To where?
Somewhere... Anywhere.
Oh, come on...
You weren't the only one watching Tohsaka.
Meaning that everyone else must also know of Assassin's death.
Things are going to start happening all at once.
But we shall destroy those that come across us.
Search and destroy...
It won't be that easy.
I am Rider.
My speed far exceeds that of any other Servant.
Wait.. Wait, wait! Not here...
You'll blow up the house!
My Servant has been lost.
I have forfeited my right as a Master,
and cannot continue the Holy Grail War.
In accordance with the treaty, I, Kotomine Kirei,
request that the Church shelter and protect me.
Your request is granted.
In my role as supervisor, I, Kotomine Risei, will guarantee your safety.
Enter.
Father... Isn't anyone surveilling this church?
No one.
This place has been declared a neutral sanctuary.
The Holy Church will censure any Master who defies the decree.
Then it's safe...
Yes.
Keep watch, just in case.
Post one guard here at all times, just to be sure.
Yes. Understood.
Who was watching the battle?
I detected the presence of familiars from four separate Masters.
Two days ago, I confirmed the summoning of the final Servant, Caster.
All the Holy Grail War Servants have now arrived.
One unaccounted for, huh?
I was hoping all the Masters would bear witness to it.
At this point, any self-respecting Master
would be observing the three main families' estates.
If they can't even think to do that,
they would never even suspect us Assassins.
We Heroic Spirits of the shadows shall sneak up behind those Masters
who believe Assassin to be dead.
And this time, we shall become true shadow.
The battle has commenced.
At last, it's time for the Fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
These old eyes of mine will finally see a miracle incarnate.
So, this is where Kiritsugu was born.
Well, Saber?
How did you enjoy your journey through the sky?
No comment in particular.
Far simpler than I'd anticipated.
I suppose flying is nothing of note for a Heroic Spirit.
That's not it.
Upon materialization, Servants receive knowledge of the modern world.
If required, I could even ascend this aircraft.
You mean you could pilot it?
My Riding skill allows me to command any beast or vehicle,
bar divine and phantasmal beasts.
If I can ride on a saddle and hold the reins, instinct will take care of the rest.
Ride on a saddle and hold the reins...
Did I say something amusing?
This place is so lively...
Kiritsugu arrived before us, yes?
Yes. He flew in half a day ago.
But he'll find us. Don't worry.
For the moment, we'll keep our eyes peeled,
so we can act when the time comes.
I don't get many chances to visit Japan.
I'd like to enjoy it before the fighting starts.
That's dangerous.
We should secure our base of operations, and then discuss plans with Kiritsugu.
I suppose you're right...
But it's such a waste. We've come all this way.
And...
It's my first time.
Eh?
This is the first time I've ventured into the outside world.
Then you've spent your entire life in that castle?
I am a puppet, created for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it isn't as though I'm wholly ignorant about the world.
Kiritsugu brought me movies and pictures,
and he's taught me all about the outdoor world.
But this is the first time I've seen it for myself.
So...
Forgive me. I got overly excited.
Please stop the car.
Walking through the city will be a new experience for me, as well.
But it is a knight's duty to serve as escort.
I shall do my best.
Then, if you please.
The equipment you requested has arrived.
The mistress and Saber have arrived as well.
The other Masters will likely assume that she is Saber's Master.
Understood.
There was an incident last night, at the Tohsaka estate.
Here is the footage I recorded.
What do you make of this?
It seems too good to be true.
The time lag between Assassin's attack
and Tohsaka's Servant's response was too short.
Assassin has a skill that masks his presence,
making it highly improbable that he was detected in advance.
I believe Tohsaka was expecting an intruder.
In a battle among Servants, learning their identities is critical.
Why would Tohsaka expose his Servant this way?
He must have had a reason to...
I suppose.
Maiya, what became of Assassin's Master?
He escaped to the church last night.
The judge decreed him under their protection.
Assassin's Master is Kotomine Kirei.
Maiya, set a familiar to watch the Fuyuki City church.
Are you certain?
Within the neutral zone that surrounds the church,
Masters are forbidden to operate.
Keep it at a reasonable distance so that the priest will be unable to locate it.
Very well. Understood.
Where is the thing I gave you?
Right here.
Two seconds to reload, huh?
I've become dull.
Indeed.
Ilya weighs less than that the Walther.
And...
She's eight years old already.
Focus on what matters now.
Think of nothing else...
It's wonderful, like a mirror that reflects the night sky.
It's fun to walk around a new town, accompanied by a gentleman.
Did I make an acceptable gentleman?
You were perfect.
You were a wonderful knight today.
You honor me, princess.
Saber, do you like the sea?
I don't really know, to tell the truth.
In my day and place,
beyond the sea laid the enemy.
Sometimes, I hated it. But not once did I ever love it.
I feel kind of bad.
You're a girl, just as I am...
But when you were King Arthur,
you had no opportunity to enjoy anything like this.
What of you?
Surely, you would have preferred Kiritsugu to escort you, right?
He couldn't...
It would only cause him grief.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy the time he spends with you?
Happiness pains him.
A hostile Servant...
Yes.
Making its presence known from the shadows, one hundred meters ahead.
It appears to be inviting us to go see it.
How thoughtful.
It wishes to determine the battlefield.
Shall we take it up on its invitation?
My thoughts exactly.
Rider... Let's go back down.
Right now!
Why? This is the perfect vantage point.
I'm gonna fall...
Take me back down!
I-I can't handle any more of this...
Calm down.
Waiting is a part of war.
I wanna go home. I wanna return to England...
I told you not to be in such a hurry.
See? Things begin to unfold.
This will be fun.
Welcome.
I have spent the whole day roaming the city.
Everyone else cowered away in fear.
You brave souls are the only ones to accept my offer.
That pure aura surrounding you...
Saber, I presume?
Indeed.
And you must be Lancer.
I must bear the shame of withholding my name from one I face in combat.
I dislike these rules.
Saber... Be careful.
I can only use healing magic to support you.
Beyond that I cannot contribute more.
Leave Lancer to me.
But it worries me that the other Master has not yet made an appearance.
Perhaps they plot something.
Watch yourself.
Irisviel, guard my back.
Very well, Saber.
Grant me victory!
Yes, certain victory.
Episode 3
Land of Winter Trees
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
Let's see what you can do, my lovely King of Knights.
Saber class's anti-magic ability is as powerful as rumored.
He's impressive!
That's enough fun for now, Lancer.
What's happening?
I'll go... Take me, damn it!
Next Time
Blade of the Demon Spear