I kill people with this hand, and I also eat with this hand...
There's no difference.
I do these things... in order to live.
That's how it is, right?
Yo.
That was unfortunate, hardhead.
Gant, you bastard! Is that all you can say on a day like this?
You've got a nice look in your eyes, Tony.
What are you talking about, old man Gant?
Don't play dumb.
I've known you guys since you were snotty brats.
So I can tell...
That look in your eyes is telling me you're about to start a bloodbath.
Don't do anything dumb, all right?
I'm always watching you.
Are we going to do it, Tony?
Yeah. We're going to crush Inferno.
It's not for revenge. It's to protect our town.
But Gant is keeping a close eye on us.
We can't make any careless moves.
I've got an idea.
There's a way to give them the coup de grâce without dirtying our hands.
Inferno is basically a bunch of traitors...
...who go against their bosses,
and join hands with their families' rivals.
Among the organizations on the West Coast,
these fifteen would benefit from joining Inferno.
Richard Harrington. Carlo Mendoza.
Are you saying that big shots like them are joining hands behind the scenes?
If we obtain evidence of that and reveal it to the public, they're done for.
Any organization would take care of misconduct by people in their own group.
Those who spit on the code of conduct...
...will bite the dust because of their own misdeeds.
Amazing... That's the most intelligent way.
Anton, I'll leave the arrangements to you.
Stay close to them and reveal their true colors.
However... be cautious.
Good morning, Ms. McCunnen.
You look stunningly beautiful as always.
Why are you here?
I called him here.
He offers his opinions based on his unique insights.
We can gain a lot from them.
I plan to have him participate in future executive meetings as a regular.
Any objections?
No sir.
The reason I called for an urgent meeting today...
...is to inform you of Tony Stone's latest actions.
Tony? That hardhead is still trying to do something?
I've obtained information that he's using spies.
I did think that there was an annoying fly buzzing around lately.
So he was sent by Tony of all people.
Seems like the message we sent him the other day had the opposite effect.
If they had come at us in a frenzy,
that would have actually been convenient for us.
But I didn't expect that he'd try to strike our weak point.
I suppose we should get rid of him immediately.
However, our goal at the beginning was to gain
the Stone Family's turf without turning it into a battlefield.
You have some sort of plan?
I can't help but to think...
...that Tony Stone's careless action is a once-in-a-million chance.
Oh? Sounds interesting.
Let us hear it.
Ein's been gone for a while now.
That's reckless. A daring plan like that can't possibly...
It's possible if we use Phantom.
I think she's proven her ability many times by now.
True. Although the scale is bigger,
it's not that much more reckless than her previous missions.
This might even work out.
I'd like to hear your decision, Mr. McGuire.
You sure know the right timing to promote your talent.
Thank you very much.
Fine.
Why don't we take a chance on that confidence of yours, Scythe Master.
Good, Ein. Wonderful.
You're really the best subject.
This meaningless world filled with confusion will be completely transformed by my will.
A new order... A new balance...
I will build it all.
In this program, even God is just an audience member watching from the upper gallery!
You are the lead... Ein.
My precious prima donna.
Did the meeting drag on?
These are the instructions for our next operation. Look through them later.
This one is a series of missions. Our targets consist of...
...twelve people.
Twelve? Don't tell me we're killing all of them in one night?
Our individual missions aren't hard.
We have to time things carefully and aim to be perfectly in-sync.
These are all executives of Inferno's rivals.
If this succeeds, the power balance on the West Coast will change considerably.
Is this okay? Isn't it too hasty?
That's not something you should be worrying about.
It's natural to think about the meaning of the mission, right?
Did someone tell you that?
You shouldn't bother.
It doesn't suit our way of existing.
So what's our way of existing?
Being a tool... Being a device...
All we need to do is function.
Don't think about unnecessary things.
How can you say that so firmly?
Does thinking harm us?
We'll break...
Both me...
...and you...
Looks like everything is ready, yes?
Take that stupid smile off your face, you snaky bastard.
Your plan isn't even an operation. It's acrobatics.
It's the same as walking a tightrope or jumping through a flaming hoop.
I only planned it because I have confidence in your abilities.
And anyways, why are you running this all by yourself as if you own the place?
Where's Clau?
She said she couldn't come because she had something else to attend to.
What are we going to do with her?
If Clau orders it, I'll go out on a limb no matter how dangerous it is.
But I have no reason to risk my life on your orders.
We'll have more and more of this kind of operations.
You may want to rethink how you decide to treat me...
...Ms. Garland.
Lizzie, it's time.
Don't just stand there! Let's go!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Well then. I'll see you later.
Phase one, complete.
Roger. Initiating Phase two.
The back! He escaped to the back!
Search over there!
I got him! Over here!
Who the hell is this guy?
I feel like I've seen him before.
I think he was working as a bouncer on Tony's turf.
The Stone Family?! Why did they come after the old man?
Those bastards!
There haven't been any suspicious actions from Carlos tonight.
He's having dinner at one of his usual restaurants right now.
What a carefree guy.
Yes. Okay.
Well then, I'll talk to you on the next scheduled call.
What's going on?!
With regards to Allen Construction's bidding,
there was a rumor that the local mafia was involved.
So it's possible that this is a gang war.
I see.
Ah, yes.
According to the information we've just received,
there was a gunfight and car accident on the Pacific Coast Highway.
We have a relay from the scene.
They're all overreacting.
The night has just begun.
You mean there's going to be more of that?!
Tonight's bloodshed is only the beginning.
From here on, it will truly be an era dominated by survival of the fittest.
It's a world where any dream is possible so long as you have power.
Mr. Godoh... would that way of life... appeal to you?
Anton, what the hell is going on?!
Abel, Bark... No one's reporting!
When things have gotten this serious!
All of them are probably dead by now.
Like a bullet, they left their mark.
I'm sure they're satisfied.
What do you mean?!
Are you saying that it was Bark and the others?!
Who killed Don Ronny and Hugo?!
That's what everyone will assume...
...since no one will go interview them in their tombs.
Anton... Why...?
Don't you get it? I guess you don't...
...since you're hardheaded.
Well done, kid.
Yeah. Now I can say goodbye to this filthy town.
It took me twenty-five years to get out of this cesspool.
I'm sick and tired of it.
You're retiring at such a young age?
I've received enough compensation from Inferno.
I'll buy a cottage or something on a Caribbean beach.
What's your cut?
My first promotion in fifteen years.
I did end a mafia war, after all.
Looks like both of us will live a long life.
An era came to an end yesterday.
The six old men who had controlled the underworld on the West Coast for a long time...
...died tragically.
Tony Stone was considered the mastermind of it all,
and the law brought him to justice.
Having lost their leaders,
each organization will be led to the new era by our compatriots...
...under one name: Inferno.
Outstanding. Another miracle performed by your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
Lieutenant Cyrus Gant, who resolved the mafia war that shook the entire city,
received an award from the mayor for his deeds.
Tony Stone, who was known as gang leader and boss of Melanie Square,
I wonder if everyone actually believes what's being said here.
simultaneously attacked six West Coast-based criminal organizations, and succeeded in every attempt.
No one cares about the truth... nor are they interested.
However, his ambitions were suddenly crushed by Lieutenant Gant's heroic actions.
I wonder who'll pray for the people who died that day.
I wonder who'll atone for those sins.
There's neither prayer nor atonement.
Death is the end of everything.
No matter what you do after that...
...it's meaningless.
There is nothing.
Dreams are just illusions.
All they do is get in the way of reality.