Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Konata.
Can I use your computer?
I want to type up something...
...for the meeting next week.
Sure.
Let's see...
I've been having difficulties lately...
[This segment is referring to the autocomplete settings on Konata's computer.]
I've been a head nurse recently,
...but I should have it finished in time...
I've been having difficulties lately, but it's a maniac transfer,
...so I intend to speed things up...
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to cross dress more.
...but without rushing...
...while keeping the committee mood in mind...
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood (← won't convert for some reason) in mind.
...and managing to work out all the details.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind, and dying to not work out the NSFW details.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind, and dying to not work out the NSFW details.
Hey.
Can we talk about your PC for a sec?
It's hard to use other people's computers, Kagami.
A
Fine
Line
I didn't check my inbox for two or three days...
...and now it's mega full!
You don't look like someone who'd get a lot of mail.
Cousin Yui...
Doesn't even bat an eye...
Of course I get mail.
Maybe it's 'cause I visit all the right sites...
...but over 90% of these are junk or spam.
It's hard for me to respond...
...so don't admit those things to a cop, okay?
Still, I've been thinking...
It's impressive how they can come up with all these interesting titles.
That's true.
Preparing to copy files
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
2 Hours remaining
90 Minutes remaining
58 Minutes remaining
It's going pretty fast.
Maybe it'll finish sooner than expected.
Antenna
Ponytail
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
41 Minutes remaining
38 Minutes remaining
60 Minutes remaining
It happens every time...
The way it goes up and down makes it useless!
Guess I'll have a cup of ramen for a snack.
Played me like a fool...
Hello.
Welcome.
I heard Konata and Yutaka are sick?
Whew...
You okay, Yutaka?
This hasn't happened in a while.
Yo, Konata!
You ok—
Cousin Yui.
Welcome!
You don't have the strength to go to class...
...but you have enough to play games.
Well...
You know...
You should understand, Cousin Yui.
Hello!
Minami and friends.
You came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed...
...but this is the first time she's had so much energy.
I really appreciate it, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school...
Maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you.
She must be having so much fun at school.
You know how they say that sickness comes from the mind.
And it looks like people forget they're sick when they're having fun.
Hello!
Minami and friends.
You came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed...
...but this is the first time she's had so much energy.
I really appreciate it, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school...
Maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you.
She must be having so much fun at school.
Minami-chan, Tamura-san, and Patty-chan.
Welcome.
Are you okay?
Get well soon!
But...
I wonder why I'm so weak...
I don't like how I make other people worry.
Nah.
That ends up making people want to protect you.
Well, it may sound good in theory...
...but it's usually hard on the person.
You could say that...
...it's like how people who actually have little sisters...
...don't feel the charm of little sisters.
That's it!
Here it comes!
The normal folks are shunning us!
So this is the "no idea what you're talking about" aura!
It can't be helped!
We're outlaws!
Speaking of weaknesses...
...you're sensitive about how you have no breasts, right, Minami-chan?
Really?
U-Um, well...
They say that they get bigger if you massage them, right?
I've heard about that.
I-Is it really okay...
...Minami-chan?
You're the only one...
...I can ask to do this...
I-I'm going to touch you...
Control yourself...
Control yourself, girl!
So you're a member of that circle.
Yes.
I participated in the last Summer Comiket.
I have a few of your books.
Man...
That's very kind of you.
Really.
I want to see the manga you draw, Tamura-san.
Let me read some, Big Sister.
Sure thi—
I-I don't think that's...
Nah, Hiyorin.
Doujin works are meant to be seen.
Please have mercy!
Not to the normal people!
That's bad manners, Hiyorin.
Anyone but them!
That's incredible.
Then let's go over the answers.
Xylitol gum...
Yes.
Has the ability to reduce cavities.
That's because...
When Xylitol...
...is absorbed by bacteria...
...the bacteria's...
...ATP...
...is depleted and at the same time...
...the bacteria in the cavity...
...is broken down.
If they're so good for your teeth...
...I'll give it a try.
I was chewing gum to help my teeth...
...and a filling fell out.
Now I have to visit the dentist...
The assiduous, yet slightly unlucky Miyuki-san is so moe.
There, there.
And so...
...Miyuki-san was crying today.
It was so moe.
R-Really...
That's what Big Sister said.
So that's why Miyuki-san looked so down.
I feel bad for this Miyuki-san...
...but I'm going to use that material!
Well...
I haven't been able to come up with ideas...
How do you come up with ideas for manga?
There really isn't a single method to it...
...but I use a lot of stuff from personal experience.
P-Personal experience...?
You read them, didn't you?!
Um, well...
Well...
After I begged her not to show you...
S-Sorry...
Those aren't based on personal experience...
B-But there were a lot of good stories...
...that I really enjoyed.
Thanks...
I think it's called déjà vu.
I felt like I'd experienced some parts.
I would also like to read them.
Sorry!
So sorry...
That was probably the one based on you two...
Teacher, good morning.
What's wrong, Izumi?
Up all night playing games again?
Or watching late-night anime?
Man...
They sure air a lot more late-night anime these days.
Great time to be alive...
Can't you just lie and say you were studying?
Really...
I was considering splurging on a DVD recorder or something.
Nah.
Don't do it.
You'll never get around to watching it.
Like how games pile up, huh?
What are you talking about?!
Hey!
Cut that out!
That's not funny!
Just so you know...
...it's none of my business what happens!
Hello?
You didn't hang up just now, did you?
Well...
I had three bars, but I still got cut off...
Well, I guess I was a little immature there.
Sorry.
It's not like I hung up on you.
Machida Dentistry
I've returned to this place again...
Okay...
Let's see which one fell out.
We can just stick it back in.
It'll be over soon.
But you've got another cavity developing in the back...
...so let's start treating that.
What's wrong?
I just realized that...
...strawberries smell like shortcake!
Er, don't you mean shortcake smells like strawberries?
Since it has strawberries inside.
H-H-Huh?
Well...
People mix stuff up like that every now and then.
Uncle.
Big Sister.
Good morning!
Yu-chan, good morning!
Today's Bow-Wow.
So many animals!
They're doing a special on pets.
First, we have...
...a Welsh corgi, Ku-chan.
It's a corgi!
So cute!
The owner's not too bad either.
She scores high for the thigh-highs.
And she has a nicely balanced absolute territory.
She'd look good in a gothic maid outfit.
Next, we have the Siberian husky, Silviana-chan.
It's a husky!
You don't see many of them these days.
I really like them.
This girl's gotta be a tsundere!
So moe.
Every girl with pigtails looks like a tsundere.
So you also play games, Kusakabe.
I like them, but I suck.
Wanna play a bit?
You're good, Hiiragi.
Wow!
Whoa, what was that?
Look!
Isn't Hiiragi amazing?
She really is.
Is this for real?!
When I see how much fun she's having...
Out of my league!
...I feel like a loser for caring so much about winning.
Total classic, right?
You go for the stink, huh?
Patricia-san.
Hello.
You've been visiting a lot recently.
Patty's a studious foreign student.
Which is why I've been teaching her
about the soul of Japanese culture every day.
The stuff you teach her...
...is only a tiny fraction of Japanese culture.
Otakus are the pride of Japanese culture!
My critical mission is...
...to absorb as much as I can...
...and take it back to America!
That's right!
I admire your passion...
Say, Patricia-san...
What kind of music do you listen to?
Let's see...
Orange Ran**.
Chemis***.
Suneoha**.
Porno Graffi**.
L'Arc~en~Ci**.
*inn.
Night****.
And many others.
I'm listening to many different Japanese artists!
That's a surprise.
But you know...
They all did anime songs, right?
Man.
You're so sharp, Konata.
And you only listen to their anime songs, right?
I'd like a maid.
A maid.
A maid, huh?
You live by yourself instead of in a dorm?
Yes.
I'm so busy with cooking, cleaning, manga, and anime!
I guess it'd be hard if you're not used to it...
You'd want to hire a housekeeper.
No, no.
Not a housekeeper.
A maid.
Aren't they the same thing?
Geez!
They're totally different!
What do they teach you in this country?!
Um...
Isn't your impression of Japan a little off?
I-I can't let you have this.
It's fried.
He won't give up because he knows you're soft.
It's hopeless.
Come here, I'll give you this.
Eat slowly now.
But now I feel a little lonely.
The class thinks that she's quiet and scary...
...but she's really kind, calm, and cool!
She's really admired by Kobayakawa-san, a relative of Izumi-san.
My...
Is that so?
Minami-chan!
Circular notice!
Minami-chan is calm and cool, huh?
Which reminds me...
Izumi-san also said...
She looks all cool and flawless...
...but when you see her with
Yu-chan, you can tell she's a good person.
That's what she said.
I'm sorry.
This is on sale...
...so it's limited to one per customer.
My...
Minami-chan is cool and flawless.
Also...
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san...
Minami-chan looks like she can do everything quickly to perfection.
Minami-chan looks like...
...she could do anything.
I admire how she's so cool!
Minami-san...
...is also admired by...
...Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san.
Mom?
The item you wanted is limited to one per customer.
Oh?
Oh...
Minami-chan does everything quickly to perfection...
Yo!
Welcome!
What'cha watching?
A mecha anime I rented.
Sure looks cool.
You still like this stuff, huh?
I'm not really interested in mecha.
You're not interested in mecha?
So why are you watching?
In order to grab a wider audience...
...recent mecha anime almost always...
...features a cute boy or girl.
Can you really call that a mecha anime?
Okay?
Hiiragi?
Got it?
It's a promise!
I'm counting on you tomorrow!
Yeah, yeah.
I'll take care of it.
Come on, Misa-chan.
Hiiragi-chan said okay.
You shouldn't keep bothering her.
But based on past experience...
People who say they'll take care of it never intend to.
Bah.
She's sharp about the oddest things...
Kagami-sama!
Let's stop by Gamers on the way home!
I don't need to buy anything...
..and I have something to do, so I'll pass.
C'mon...
Just for a bit...
No!
C'mon...
Don't play with my hair.
Besides...
You have bookstores in your town, don't you?
You know how once you've gone to a specialty store...
...a normal bookstore feels lacking in some way?
They might not have everything you want.
That's 'cause the stuff you want is too unique.
So?
What are you getting?
I'm getting this today!
You sure watch a lot of stuff...
I haven't watched the anime.
But the second I saw this cover...
...I felt a connection somehow.
It's been on my mind for a while.
I don't get it.
But you know...
I finally understand the concept of buying albums for their cover.
You know?
You choose light novels based on their cover, right?
Well, I can't deny it...
When it turns out to be good...
...you feel like you got a great deal.
And if it's not good...
...you don't regret it since you just bought it on a whim.
In other words...
...a once-in-a-lifetime encounter!
You might think that you're making sense there...
...but that's a stretch.
Let's take it easy.
Is this another once-in-a-lifetime encounter?
That was grandiose.
Cover your face.
Well...
You can't really control when you sneeze.
This is the first time I've heard
someone actually go "achoo" when they sneeze.
For some reason...
There's a world of difference between us after one sneeze...
No fair!
It's no fair how cute your sneeze is!
Don't tease her.
After a round, it actually smells good now.
But it's already over.
You two sure are close.
Do you guys ever fight?
Sure have!
Believe it or not...
...Ayano's really scary when she's mad.
It's true that some people are like that!
Geez...
Even Hiiragi-chan says so...
By the way...
You're always scary, Hiiragi.
So that's...
...my position in life?
Minami-chan runs the same time as you in the 100-meter dash.
Really...
But...
I bet if we actually raced...
...I'd win by the difference in our chests!
As if!
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
W-Wouldn't Minami-chan win because of her height?
Flat chest...
Everyone just ignored that, huh?
Don't you agree, Hiiragi?
Isn't it fun, Hiiragi?
What do you think, Hiiragi?
Misa-chan's "don't respond to everything so dully"...
...and Hiiragi-chan's "don't talk to me when I'm reading" attitudes...
...are really electrifying the air.
Man...
The characters in Japanese anime and games are really moe.
Yep.
Huh?
Isn't this image bugged?
That's okay.
This is how it's supposed to look.
But it's still pretty naughty...
What kind of game are you playing there, high schoolers?
What are you all doing?
Yu-chan doesn't need to know!
It's done.
I haven't written a long blog entry in a while.
And submit...
This page cannot be displayed
B-Back!
Back!
Warning: Page has expired
Hey there!
I'm not gonna read you The Riot Act...
Depressed.
It doesn't matter what's happened...
The two of you...
You know?
Worked together to build this corner up from nothing, right?
And look at this.
Why destroy it all at the end?
Disappointed.
I've done some things to make people call me dark and gloomy...
...but I've never had to mediate a pathetic fight like this!
Understand?
If we don't resolve this immediately, boys and girls...
...it's gonna make me look bad, too.
Yeah, Shiraishi?
I-I'm terribly sorry.
Gotouther-sama.
What do you think, Akira?
I'm sorry, Goto—
I'm sorry, Gotouther-sama!
In that case...
Why don't you just kiss and make up?
Okay?
One more episode.
Why don't you find your original
conviction and finish Lucky Channel?
Well?
How does that sound?
Underst—
Louder!
Understood!
Okay.
That's that.
I'll let you two handle the rest.
Do your best to survive in the anime industry.
Then I'll go home first.
I'll talk to the producer.
Call me if anything else happens.
I could lend you some help, if you want.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Shut up already!
Hey, people!
Can't you do a proper job on the last one?!
Are you listening?
Hey!
Forget it.
I'll do it myself!
Next time:
「TBA」
TBA.
Wait, what? They didn't name it yet?!