The conflict between Angela-sama and Lilia-sama has finally become a duel...
Who will end up with control over the academy, I wonder?
Angela, I will not hand this academy to you!
Stop this, Lilia!
Both of you, stop!
Educational Institution of Rebellion and Revolution
ARMAGEDDON
"Please do not stop me, Charles-sama!"
Angela, that which the academy needs is not the sword!
Love. It is love!
And there you have it!
We'll be performing a play based on this work for the cultural festival.
Uh... well...
That does sound interesting!
It's like this work is overflowing with passion!
I'll be going home now.
Please wait!
What are you going to do?
Join your hearts with ours, and let us revolutionise this academy!
Nope.
Oi, Amahara!
It's all right. We'll definitely make the underwear part.
That's our Hayama-san!
You are a goddess, descended from the heavens!
Our victory is now in sight!
Let us proceed forth, to a rainbow paradise!
Nayu seems to be faking her enthusiasm for this...
I just have to do my best.
This will be the last thing I can do with everyone.
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
An Afternoon With Her
Thank you for working with us!
We'll be making these six costumes, okay?
For this one, you'll need a strapless bra and a waist-covering corset.
You might also need a petticoat to increase the volume of the skirt.
With the bondage costume, a stick-on bra and satin panties...
The bunny costume is thin satin fabric,
so cover the nipples and wear a T-back...
This one could work well with bikini-style underwear I think.
Now to begin-
Why would you have me tied up?!
She's just measuring your sizes...
Enough with the exaggerated reactions.
Hmm... Bust, 84.
I'll step outside for now.
Ah, one more thing...
We'd appreciate it if the Underwear Society can appear in the play.
Eh? Us, too?
Yes. To be honest, we had a lot of members during spring,
but the sad truth is that we're now down to three.
This president and vice-president, huh?
We'd only be giving you a few lines, so please!
Then the one who should play the rabbit is... Mizuno-sensei!
M-Me?!
You'd fit perfectly!
Nobody else but Mizuno-sensei could fill this role!
R-Really...?
Hold it, it's obvious that I can't do this!
Then I'll do it!
But with this costume, a lack of chest would...
What?!
I... wouldn't mind doing it.
Even if it's only a little bit,
I want to be useful to Nayu-chan and the Underwear Society.
Haruka-chan...
Thank you most kindly!
Then this will be Amahara-san.
This would be Komachi-kun, maybe.
Komachi-kun would be cross-dressing?
That would probably look nice on him.
I had a really bad feeling just now.
Jinguuji-san, you're in the Kendo Club, right?
Can you please help us with our stage fights?
I certainly can!
Then let's face the culture festival and do our best!
Are you serious?
I'm going to be in it, too?!
It's perfectly fine.
It's a girl's role, so nobody will realise that it's you.
That's not the problem here.
I absolutely refuse to do it!
You can't...?
No, um...
Then we have our decision, eh?
Wait a moment!
See you!
Nayu-chan, try not to work yourself too hard!
I won't!
Amahara-san!
Late, aren't we?
I never thought that Amahara-san would come over to play!
I'm not really here "to play".
Was there something you wanted to talk about?
Or maybe something you want advice with!
Even if there was, I wouldn't ask you for advice.
Then why?
Kyoto...
Have you ever been there?
Never, not yet... Why?
There's no real reason.
Also, moving... must be tough.
Yeah, I'd guess so.
And changing schools...
Just what are you doing?
Sorry! I wonder if it'll come out...
Don't surprise me like that.
Is that Polaris' new product?
Can you show it to me?!
What?!
Please!
Just a bit.
It's cute, but it's really mature!
How about the bottom? How is it?
You're really...!
I'm home!
Wait, there was just a bit more to-
You wait!
Nayu.
Oh, welcome.
Sorry to have intruded!
Amahara-san! Thank you for coming over.
You're pushing yourself too hard.
Ah, right!
Can you lend me the bra you wore on the camping trip?
I want to use it for one of the Acting Club's costumes!
Yeah, sure.
Don't forget! The bra!
I get it, okay?!
So that girl was the daughter of Amahara-san from Polaris?
Yup, that's right.
This fried chicken is delicious.
Nayu.
Are you really okay with going to Kyoto?
Of course I am!
I'm really looking forward to it.
It looks like I'll learn a lot from it-
Japanese patterned underwear could be great.
That really went down well!
Hayama-san!
We've got a favour to ask of you.
What is it?
For the culture festival, our class is doing a cafe, right?
And so, do you think you could make some maid-like clothes for us?
But I'm not from the Handicrafts Club.
I'm from the Underwear Society.
The girls from the Handicrafts Club scoffed at the idea of maid clothes.
That's why we want you to make them!
The underwear you made for that magazine a while back had a great sense of style.
Hey now, we don't possibly have the time for that.
Our group is helping the Acting Club.
No, it's fine! I'll make them.
Nayu-chan!
I don't think I can make a whole bunch of them, though.
Really? Thank you!
We'll leave the design up to you, okay?
Nayu...
Are you really fine with that?
Yeah, I can do it.
I'm just happy that everyone seems to
have accepted the Underwear Society.
Class representative, why does it look like you're being forced to stand out here?
They're all changing.
So you don't know, either.
K-Know what?
It's nothing really.
Tell me. It's going to bug me.
Hayama-san... is going to transfer.
Transfer? Why?
To make it easier for her older brother to work.
Komachi-kun, it's okay now!
Amahara-san, perfect timing!
Your costume's done, too!
Why do I have a costume?
There weren't enough members,
so they wanted us to be in the performance.
I didn't hear anything about this!
Please? Come on...
Everyone's costumes looked great, didn't they?
Yeah, they did.
Hayama's transferring...
Do Shiraishi or Jinguuji know?
Cat-Eyes' costume was cute, too.
Komachi-kun, how did it feel when you wore it?
You needed my bra for this?
Yup!
Komachi-kun?
Was the shock too big for you?
Well, see you tomorrow!
Yeah!
Hayama!
Um...
I'll walk you home.
It's raining.
I wonder if it will let up...?
Is it true that you're going to transfer?
I guess that you'll be going with Keigo-san.
T-That's...
...It's true, as I thought.
Yeah.
I...
Why didn't you tell anyone?!
H-Hayama?
Don't tell anyone yet.
I'll come out and tell everyone after the Culture Festival.
I understand.
Thanks.
Today's our turn to do school lunch.
It's tough, but with the three of us,
it's very fun!
It would be nice if
we could continue
like this forever.
-Nayu
Sign: Culture Festival
I'll have one frankfurter.
One frankfurter!
Yeah, yeah.
Maid
Cafe
W-Welcome to our shop.
Oh, maids!
Those outfits are so cute.
Nayu-chan made them for us.
Hayama-san's played a huge role in this.
It's true.
Mizuno-sensei!
Yes?
This! Were you aware of this?!
Coordination Team!!
Members of the Underwear Appreciation Society
Thank you very much
Send for Hayama-san immediately.
What on Earth is this?
Come now, Tsukamoto-sensei...
Even the school's name appears here.
And now you're calling yourselves the Underwear Appreciation Society...
Without permission, it would appear that you are participating in the Culture Festival...
...by helping the Acting Club with their costumes.
Yes...
The play is cancelled.
You needn't go that far!
A club of delinquents cannot be allowed to participate in the Culture Festival.
Excuse me, but...
What is it, Mizuno-sensei?
The members of the Acting Club, as well as the Underwear Society,
have worked very hard for the Culture Festival.
It would be too harsh to make them suddenly quit!
These girls have tried their best to make the costumes and underwear, and they've done a great job.
I believe that the Culture Festival is a chance for the students to show off their true abilities.
Please, at least make your decision after you've seen what these girls have managed to make!
Please!
Sensei...
I agree with Mizuno-sensei about this.
Me too.
Sorry! We just got dismissed from our class' shop.
What's wrong? It's all gloomy in here.
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
Our Angel of Salvation has fallen into the hands of a demon!
Excellent. You're all here.
Did something happen?
The play... might be cancelled.
Amahara-san, I have something to speak to you about as well.
About my appearance in a magazine, right?
If so, wouldn't it be enough to punish me only?
Amahara-san!
Serves you all right.
It's because they got carried away.
You guys.
Tanihara-sensei!
You came!
I haven't seen you since graduation. How've you been?
What's wrong?
Actually, Hayama-san's...
Hayama?
Tsukamoto-sensei, these are the costumes the girls made.
What's going on?
She said a club of delinquents wouldn't be allowed to participate.
What?
But Mizuno-sensei asked her to look at the costumes first,
and then decide on whether or not to cancel the play.
This has some beautiful curves.
This lace has been layered very skillfully.
It spreads apart perfectly.
How is it, Tsukamoto-sensei?
Excuse me!
Is Hayama here?
Sensei?
This is my homeroom teacher from elementary school.
I must apologise for having one of my graduates cause such trouble.
Hayama, you apologise too!
I heard you're running an Underwear Appreciation Society...
What are these dirty things?!
I had such high hopes with your excellent grades!
I can't believe you've already started chasing boys at this age.
Is this what fills your head?
You're an embarrassment to our elementary school!
Is underwear really something that shameful?
Are you saying you don't wear underwear?!
What?!
The Underwear Society studies, and only studies, underwear.
Its activities are nothing to be ashamed about!
That's right!
We've learned a lot about underwear,
and it's a serious topic of study for us!
I also used to think underwear was dirty, but...
I've come to understand how important wearing proper underwear is for the developing body!
I am discussing something with Hayama.
It has nothing to do with you.
That is certainly true.
Underwear is something everyone wears.
There's nothing dirty about it.
Furthermore, aren't you the one who has nothing to do with this?
Please take your leave!
Geez, there's something wrong with the teachers in this school!
Tanihara-sensei!
Tsukamoto-sensei, thank you very much.
Even so, I have no intention of recognising the Underwear Appreciation Society.
But I will overlook the matter of the magazine this time.
I shall allow the play.
Yes!
Tsukamoto-sensei, thank you very much!
So from now on, these kids can continue their activities, right?
The school has no right to stop them from
studying underwear on their own, after all.
Nayu-chan, isn't it great?!
Yeah!
Our discussion has not yet ended!
Amahara-san, when doing off-campus activities like these,
do try to get permission!
And this goes for the rest of you, as well!
Please do not stop me, Charles-sama!
Angela, the academy needs not the sword!
Love- it is love!
Warriors from another academy have come to invade us!
That's right! Go ahead and fight amongst yourselves!
We'll take advantage of this, and take the academy now!
I'm sure glad Jinguuji took my spot.
Her acting's a bit lacking, though.
What?
I'm glad that we got to co-star with them.
For a while, I was wondering if it would work out.
Everyone, thank you!
The Culture Festival has truly been fun!
Amahara-san, thank you too!
It looks like we can keep the Underwear Society running!
I wonder what we'll do next year?
Next year...
Nayu-chan?
What's wrong?
Next year, I...
Make it clear already!
What?
You can't keep quiet about it forever!
Nayu-chan?
Sorry for keeping it to myself...
I'll...
Kyoto? Really?
It seems like Nayu really didn't tell anyone about it.
I don't think the others in the Underwear Society know, either.
I discussed this a few years ago too, but I refused back then.
Nayu learnt about it later and seemed fairly worried about it.
Then when will you be going?
Next month.
I'm transferring.
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
I'm also sad about Nayu leaving us!
I'll always treasure the time we spent together.
I got tear stains on some of my favourite underwear...!
Even now you're talking about underwear?!
Until
I
Met
You
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra.