Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star, I want
you to keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Do you have something you
want to be in the future?
A school teacher? A doctor?
You must have all kinds of
dreams of what you want to be.
Doing something you want
to do is very difficult.
But let's have a good attitude and
never give up on what we want to do.
Let's! Let's!
The dream everyone is looking
for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
Remember how I used to say
I could make it to the end?
I must have been pretending to be tough
Everything I did was reckless
and it never got me anywhere
But you alone were always beside me
The dream everyone is looking
for must be somewhere
You can start going forward
From this moment, something will start
I want to believe that
The light I haven't seen yet is
beaming toward the promised place
Until your dream comes true
someday, you're not alone
"An Amazing Sinister Rumor."
And now, I present to you my home page!
Wow, it's so cute.
But don't you think this picture
of Kaleido Stage is kinda skewed?
Don't worry.
I already got permission from the Boss.
It's amazing.
I'm planning on putting up everyone's
pictures in the gallery.
In particular, Anna's pictures
have special features.
When did you take these pictures?
When Anna flubs a gag,
that's the best time to take a picture.
So, are you going to post
everyone's pictures?
Well... That was my plan, but...
What?
Lately, someone quits every day. So...
Didn't you hear?
The other day, three people quit at once.
I'll be very disappointed if someone quits
as soon as I post the picture on the website.
So,
lately I'm concentrating my energies
on writing original stories.
Original stories?
That's right.
Cute stories, scary stories,
etcetera, etcetera.
How about something funny?
Nope!
Sora, you have a guest.
Oh, yes.
She looks Japanese.
Japanese? I wonder who she could be.
She said she would wait for you in the lobby.
Okay. Thank you.
I wonder if she was in the
rhythmic gymnastics club.
Well...
Oh!
Excuse me...
You're late.
I got tired of waiting for you.
Manami...
What? Did I bother you by showing up here?
No, no. Not at all.
I'm glad you came.
It isn't comfortable standing here,
so why don't we have a
cup of coffee somewhere?
Yes, yes.
You just need to be back here before
the evening performance starts. Right?
Yes, yes.
Sora...
Huh?
You should go change your clothes quickly.
Oh, that's right. Excuse me...
Why did you come here, Manami?
I was chosen as an exchange student,
and I'm going to stay in
Boston for three months.
Really?
As usual, you're doing well at school.
Of course. I've been studying hard.
When it comes to studying, I stand
no chance against you, Manami.
Well, maybe it's because
you were the only one going
to English Conversation School
while everybody else was in cram school.
You can't expect to keep
your grades up doing that.
Yeah... That's what you'd
tell me all the time.
But I was a little surprised today.
What?
I never expected you to play a lead role.
When you said that you'd be a Kaleido Star,
I thought it was ridiculous.
Who ever thought that you'd really do it?
Well... I'm not exactly at the
point where you can call me a star.
This time,
I just happened to be lucky enough
to co-star with Miss Layla, and...
Oh, so that's it.
Don't you have any regrets?
What?
No, I don't have any regrets.
I think I would have regretted it
more if I'd just stayed in Japan.
I see...
Did something happen?
What do you mean, "something"?
Well, I just wondered if you're having
a hard time deciding what you should do.
'Cause someone who's always
confident like you...
Don't you think that sounds rude?
You think so?
You're treating me like an idiot
who has nothing to worry about.
Oh... I never meant it like that.
Well, never mind.
Well, it's almost the time to go.
During your evening performance,
I will wait for you backstage.
What? Wait for me?
Yes.
I'm going to stay in your room tonight.
What?
I didn't make a hotel reservation.
Oh. Really...
This is our backstage.
You and I can't even hold
each other in our arms!
I don't care if you're a
ghost or anything else.
Please stay beside me.
What are you doing?
Oh, Sora...
Well... Who is that...?
Oh, she's my friend, Manami.
How do you do?
It's nice to meet you.
We were acting out a script
that Mia put on her website.
You want to give it a try too, Sora?
What? Me?
For Sora, I think this role is perfect.
Which one?
A mysterious comical loco girl.
What's that?
That sounds like a choice role.
It's perfect! It's perfect!
On the other hand, my lines
are embarrassing to read.
But I think girls will love it.
Right? Right?
It was a great show.
It was great.
Wait, Sora.
Ken...
Is your body not feeling well?
What? Not really...
Please tell me the truth.
If you overwork yourself too
much, you'll hurt yourself.
What?
You've already noticed
it yourself, haven't you?
You're not as trained as Miss Layla.
And you're doing the same performance
as her every single day.
What do you expect?
I know...
Hey, do you mind if I give you support?
You?
That is, if you don't mind.
Just in case, I already got
permission from the Boss.
What I'm going to do is
design your training menu,
give you advice about what
to eat... that kind of stuff.
In short, I'll be like a trainer.
If it's not too much trouble for you...
How can it be trouble?
So...
The reason why my body is hurting is because
it cannot keep up with my performance.
Hey, did you hear?
Karen is also going to quit.
That rumor could really be true.
As I suspected, he's headhunting everyone.
Kaleido Stage is, like, in trouble.
What?
Excuse me...
The story you were just talking about...
I think everyone's quitting because
they don't like you playing the lead.
Yes, that's right.
If I were playing the leading role,
like, everything would be much better.
Huh? Where is Manami?
When we got back, she wasn't here.
Really?
Hey, the rumor is that everyone is leaving
because I'm playing the leading role...
I wonder if it's true.
How could it be true? Are you kidding?
It's not like you to take
their words seriously, Sora.
I know...
I also heard the rumor that there
will be another theatrical company.
Kaleido Stage's rival?
So, they're headhunting everybody?
It's not a big deal. 'Cause we have
Sora, Miss Layla and Mr. Yuri.
All these things she has to deal with...
Sora!
Oh, Manami, you're still here.
You don't want me to stay here?
Oh... No... I didn't mean like that.
One, two... One, two...
One, two... One, two... One, two...
One, two...
Good, good. You can do it slowly, okay?
Yes...
I have to work hard and build my muscles.
Besides muscles, you ended up with
a boyfriend before I knew it.
A boyfriend? Oh, you mean...
No, Ken is not anything like that at all.
Not at all...
I've brought some protein juice.
If you drink it one hour after you work out,
it will help your muscles to recover faster.
I'll go get it for you!
Thank you, Ken.
Was he crying?
No way...
Too many things happened today.
Manami, you want to take a bath, don't you?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Oh, don't bother...
I'm doing this for crime prevention.
I've not done anything...
I've not done anything yet.
Sora, you haven't cut your
hair in a while, have you?
Oh, yeah, come to think of it...
I'll cut your hair for you.
Come to think of it,
I used to be forced to play
hairdressers and customers.
I was a customer and...
Forced?
Oh, well... I didn't mean like that.
Huh?
You belong at Kaleido Stage now, don't you?
I've been watching you all day long, Sora.
You pretend to be tough, acting
like everything is cool.
But I wonder if, in reality, you
might be crying behind that look.
So, you were concerned about me?
Not really...
To tell you the truth, I came
here to see your regretful face.
What?
Yes.
Everything is going smoothly.
"After I see your show one more time,
I'll be taking an evening flight to Boston.
Manami."
Manami...
One, two... One, two...
Okay, with a light step!
Quietly, like a feather.
So, the girl you were with yesterday...
Now, one, two... One, two...
She's leaving for Boston this evening.
Yes, that's good.
She's your friend, right?
Yes.
But, you're acting nervously around her.
Well, somehow, I can't act against Manami.
Miss Sora Naegino!
Do you think you're allowed
to speak during my class?!
Sorry. I'm sorry. I won't do it anymore.
It's a big mistake if you think you
can get away from being punished
just because you're playing a leading role!
Oh!
Mr. Yuri.
Excuse me, sir; I would like
to invite Sora to lunch.
May I have your permission?
Mr. Yuri...
With Sora?
Of course. I will allow you anything you ask.
Thank you.
I'm going to have lunch with Mr. Yuri?
Oh, shoot...
Don't be so nervous.
Well... I wish I could not be nervous.
But, I can't.
You're the one I've admired since
even before I joined Kaleido Stage.
I'm flattered.
In that case, then,
you wouldn't mind joining me, would you?
What? What do you mean?
I want you to come to my place
after you quit Kaleido Stage.
What... what did you just say?
I'm going to withdraw from
Kaleido Stage as of today.
I want you to create a new troupe with me.
Mr. Yuri...
In the new troupe, you, not
Layla, will be the top star.
You're... kidding, right?
You would never say that...
You're kidding, aren't you?
I'm not kidding.
Kaleido Stage is not as
great a place as you think.
Kalos has misled everyone.
I'm not asking you to make
up your mind right away,
but I think it'll be to your own benefit
if you decide what you want to do fast.
We're in trouble.
After today, 25 people are
going to quit at once.
What are we going to do starting tomorrow?
We have no choice but to
suspend our performances.
I guess we have to...
but I feel sorry for all
those kids who are left here.
I cannot believe this.
Even Mr. Yuri...
Sora, we're in trouble.
What?
Starting tomorrow, we
won't be able to perform.
What? We won't?
I don't believe this.
After today's show, 25
people are going to quit.
Even Mr. Yuri and the
directors are leaving...
We're finished.
No way...
I'm going to withdraw from
Kaleido Stage after today.
I want you to create a new troupe with me.
Mr. Yuri really meant it when he said that...
I beat Kalos.
Fight!
Today is the last.
Kaleido Stage...
...will be gone?
I'm sorry for what happened today.
That's okay. The audience was happy.
Yuri tried to win you over, didn't he?
Yes.
So, are you going?
No.
I see...
It seems that someone offered to buy
out my father's stake in Kaleido Stage.
I heard he was a businessman in Las Vegas.
I was aware that Yuri was up
to something for a long time.
But I was not able to change his mind.
I guess we have no chance to
use this "Pirates" anymore.
It could be...
Losing over 20 people changes everything.
I have to go.
Have a nice evening.
Thank you for everything, for all this time.
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
Just being able to see you look
like that really gratifies me.
Sora.
I saw your mistake.
Manami...
Sorry for showing you my goof.
Not at all.
I came here to apologize.
What?
I said something cruel yesterday,
saying that I came here to
see your regretful face.
Because I said that, you...
No. It's not like that.
I didn't make a mistake because of you.
Kaleido Stage is in serious trouble now,
and we won't be able to perform for a while.
After I was finally able to
co-star with Miss Layla too...
Will Kaleido Stage be gone?
I don't know.
Will you still not regret coming here,
even if Kaleido Stage disappears?
No. No regrets.
Why?
Because it was my dream.
I've always thought you were pretty dumb...
But you really are dumb.
But... I envy you.
I wanted to be a hairdresser.
Really?
But I always got good grades.
So my parents expected me to
do something more than that.
The reason why I decided to study overseas
was because it was getting stifling.
A hairstylist? That's nice.
I support you.
That's why you're dumb.
Usually, things are not that simple.
Oh... really?
I can't be like you, Sora.
That's why I think I wanted to feel relieved
by looking at your regretful face.
I'm not strong at all.
Please cut my hair again.
I'm your first customer.
No matter what kind of career you choose,
I support you.
I will try to do something
about Kaleido Stage.
I can keep worrying about it,
wondering if it'll just be gone,
but that won't change anything.
Instead, I should do something so
that Kaleido Stage will not go away.
Right?
I guess even you can give serious
thought to things like that.
In my own way...
Well, I need to be going.
All right.
Well, see you later.
Oh, by the way,
don't sleep without covering your stomach.
Okay.
So what do you think about Mia's story, Boss?
I knew it! He doesn't like it.
Sora, it's impossible!
No.
See? As I thought...
But, Boss, if we use this story,
we may be able to put on a fun show
even though we don't have many people.
One week...
Make it so you can perform
this on stage in one week.
Yes!
"Next Kaleido Star"
I might have gone beyond Shakespeare.
And so, Mia played a great active role
by directing the script she wrote.
While Mr. Yuri's headhunting continues,
the only thing we can do is do our best.
Miss Layla is against what we're doing,
but I positively know Mia can pull it
off. I know she can! I know she can!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Fire It Up!
Amazing Mia."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
I'm here between the sky and the
roads, and facing against the wind
And I'm facing forward so the sorrow
doesn't rain down ever again
I came all the way here after
I jumped over that wall
There are many times when
I just want to run away
But I'm still here, so,
I'm not daunted that much
The poem I scribbled down, I can just
start writing over from the beginning
Unable to write it well, I'm laughing