Bye!
I'm so sleepy today...
You are.
You don't look sleepy at all, Tooru.
I'm a morning person, so I'm fine.
I'm kind of jealous. I'm so bad with mornings...
Isn't that...
What is it, Run-chan?
That bird is acting kind of weird. Did something happen to it?
Hey, Tooru, that bird keeps flying in circles. Is it okay?
Run-chan, that's a weather vane.
Worried...
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Kilograms
That silky long hair!
That tight, slim waist!
Those arms as long as a giraffe's neck!
Oh? Are they fighting?
You have to have something even better about her!
Those smooth, long legs!
Something even better!
Those proudly puffed E-cups!
Even better!
That skin, whiter than powder sugar!
Even better! Even better! Even better! Even better!
What's wrong, you two?
I'm telling her how great you are!
Why are they talking about that?
Those pores you can't see without a microscope!
That face, smaller than a water flea!
It feels like they've only been talking about how you look.
I wish they'd talk about my personality or something...
Even better!
Let's see...
She always looks absolutely stunning!
What's wrong, Tooru?
Run-chan...
Run-chan only ever says good things about you.
And I put the noose on myself...
There are lots of great things about you, too, Tooru.
Like what?
Um...
Oh, right!
There are those people... who are into flat chests?
That "slender boom" thing?
You're right in their strike zone!
What?
Stop that!
What about your nice body?
You do look like a model, Yuuko-chan.
Crap...
I forgot!
My goal for this year!
Lose two or three kilograms by summer and have a supermodel body!
Wait, no.
I still have time.
The real summer starts in August.
This high school girl's summer has yet to start.
One more month.
With one more month, I can do it!
Today
School Cleaning!
POOL
What is wrong with me?
I completely forgot!
This high school girl's summer starts today!
Having to change into a swimsuit to clean the pool is such a hassle.
But cleaning in a swimsuit sounds fun!
Right, Nagi-chan? Don't you think so?
What's wrong, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing.
It's tight...
Did I gain weight?
I couldn't have...
I wonder if swimsuits shrink.
It feels a bit tight.
You're still growing!
A lot!
Stop that! Come on!
That's it! The swimsuit shrank!
Don't you think Nagi's acting weird today?
Hm? She's always this way.
Our job
The Yard
No!
Tooru-san!
Making progress?
Oh, Yutaka's friend.
Call me Miho.
Actually, I'm a fan of yours, like Yutaka.
Fan?
And you know, I always wanted to ask you, but I never got a chance.
Wow! It's so soft!
Do you set it? Or is it natural?
It's natural.
Toorun!
No fair, Miporin!
You're bothering Toorun, too!
I'm not stalking her like you do.
It's no fair if only Miporin gets to!
Yutaka will touch it, too!
Oh, you...
Toorun! Toorun!
You two look like you know each other well. Did you go to the same middle school?
Yes. Though, it's more like we can't get rid of each other.
She's been glancing at her watch for a while now.
Okay. Three minutes.
Get away from Tooru-san right now, Yutaka.
What? Already?
Miporin, don't be mean!
I'm used to this, so if Yutaka causes you any trouble, just tell me.
Speaking of middle school, Miporin's nickname was "remote control".
Isn't that lame?
Do you know why they called me that?
Not at all!
Yutaka!
So sorry, really.
As long as you understand.
Tooru-san, I'll take that trash bag for you.
No! Yutaka will take it!
Well, have fun with that.
Wait for Yutaka! It's heavy!
Miporin!
Remote control.
The sunlight beating down!
The poolside!
Feels like a resort?
No.
It's too hot...
It's hot inside the pool...
Well, there's nothing to absorb the sunlight...
Let's get this over with quick!
Look out!
What's she doing?
No idea.
Yuuko-chan, Nagi-chan! You can slide around here really easily!
You're right.
That's dangerous!
What if you slipped and hit your head?
That won't happen!
Come on!
Nagi, why don't you say someth—
Nagi!
What?!
You were just asking for it, Yuuko-chan!
You're all wet!
I see. That's how we're playing.
Run!
Got you!
Hey!
Take that!
Water flying through the air, splash, splash, splash
Nagi!
Almost like an unending summer poolside
Sizzling, the sky filled with sun
All the girls lightly sweating
Just a swimsuit? Borderline
They just want to play, nothing else
Loving being wet so much, just like kids
That paradise I saw in my dreams, as long as I'm with you, it's a resort
That secret I saw on my tiptoes
Falling back and landing on my butt, whoops!
Being clumsy every day!
Crying and laughing together
Teasing each other and getting along
Exciting times we all love are a precious treasure
That girl's skin looks so smooth
Let's play around and splash water on her
It'll splash right back off
Hey, hey, hey!
I want to hug her, that girl all soaking wet
Um... Toorun, what are you watching?
Got you!
Paradise.
Paradise, this ain't.
Didn't finish,
had to stay behind.
I'm home.
Man, I'm tired.
I should've put on more sunscreen.
It's okay.
I moved around a lot today.
I must have lost at least one.
No, I might have even lost two or three!
Work with me here, scale!
1 kilogram gained
Wait, wearing clothes counts as an extra kilogram.
Come on, it hasn't changed!
What a waste of excitement!
Guess I'll start a one month plan.
The fundamentals are exercise and restraints on eating.
No snacks between meals.
Have dinner early, and less.
Focus on vegetables and avoid oily foods.
Be sure to exercise daily.
Jogging, jumping rope, and stretching are very effective.
Dang, that's sadistic.
Alright, I'm done.
I can't tell anyone about this diet.
They'd all be on my case.
If Run found out...
It's not good for you! Don't!
And if Yuuko did...
You're fine the way you are!
You're enough already!
They'd totally say that.
And Tooru...
Man, that's good. Yeah, good.
Want some? Eat all you want.
Just the thought makes me hungry...
Nagi.
Crap! I showed fear!
Have to be careful. Tooru can read people.
Hey, what's up?
Diet.
What? What diet?
Hey. You're on a diet, right?
What could you be talking about?
Where are Run and Yuuko?
They went to the bathroom.
How did you know?
In the spring, you said you could easily lose three kilograms by summer.
And you remembered when we were talking yesterday.
Why can't you forget something so useless?
You going to tell everyone?
I won't.
Don't tell me you want something to keep quiet!
I don't.
What are you doing?
They're not here.
You eat so many snacks, but you're still slim.
Probably because I run around.
As a result, not enough nutrition here.
I see. They say, "If it moves, it goes."
Then I don't need to jog or jump rope, since my boobs'll go!
Alright!
If you're so concerned, you could ask Yuuko.
She might be doing a lot for herself.
There has to be some secret behind that nice body.
Yeah. You're right.
Alright.
They're not here either?
Maybe we missed each other somewhere?
Tooru, you're all sweaty.
These are tears of sadness from not seeing Run-chan.
Don't make excuses. You're hot after all that walking.
Not hot.
And why are you wearing long sleeves in the summer?
I don't want to show my arms.
You'll get heatstroke! Take it off!
You don't want to that much?!
Okay. Then open your textbooks to page 52.
What? Am I doing anything to stay in shape?
Nothing major. I just wanted to ask.
Hm... Let's see...
Maybe eating whatever I want, whenever I want,
and sleeping enough?
Well, guess I'm not doing anything.
What are you, some sort of supermodel?!
Man, you're mean! Useless!
What?
Staying in shape?
You mean a diet?
Oh, you were talking about a diet?
Did you start one, Nagi?
Well, yeah.
No point keeping quiet if you know.
Run, have you ever gone on a diet?
Never a real one.
I don't want to restrict what I eat.
You haven't either, right, Yuuko-chan?
Right, but why?
I mean, you have a pet, right?
Pet? What do you mean?
What was it? It sounded like a last name.
Tapeworms!
It's because of tapeworms!
I'm not raising any, and they're not pets!
Computer.
You can find a good diet on the Internet.
Oh, right.
Why do we need to go to the library?
Can't we use one in the classroom?
Looking this up in the classroom is kind of...
There are a lot of different diets out there.
I drank this and lost 60 kilograms?
That's way too much. Sounds fake.
If you lost that much, you'd have negative weight.
Then you could fly!
Yeah.
As a ghost.
Alright, I'm done.
Nagi-chan, is that all you're eating?
Yeah. Eating restraints are a fundamental of dieting.
Don't push yourself, Nagi.
Don't worry!
This is just right.
Pushing yourself.
That didn't happen! You didn't hear it!
I can't do that. I heard it.
Forget that you did!
Man, I always get hungry about now.
You know, Nagi.
Starting a harsh diet just like this is bad for you. Won't you stop?
Why not take it slow, or make it a goal for next year?
That's right, Nagi-chan! Let's take it slow!
I guess. Guess I shouldn't push myself.
I'll try doing it at my own pace.
Good, good!
Hey, then let's go get some ice cream!
Sounds good!
Wait! Why would you bring up ice cream after that?!
I want chocolate chip and strawberry!
Vanilla and cheese and yogurt.
They're all white!
I said—
Maybe I'll get mint and raspberry.
What about you, Nagi?
Rum raisin.
Guess I'll never get a diet.
Come on, let's go, Nagi!
Wait—
You're fine the way you are.
You're enough already.
Cute enough already.
Don't say things like that! It's embarrassing!
Wait right there, Yuuko!
Come on, come on! Let's go!
Wait!
Look at these.
New socks.
Wow! Neon yellow! They sure stand out!
Nice, right?
Morning!
Morning.
Tooru?!
Why are you wearing them loose?! In this decade?!
No, these are just a new pair of knee socks.
They just sag easily.
How thin are you?!
I put stoppers on them, but they still sag.
Want to try some Sock Touch?
I wish I were fatter.
Hey! You just said something unforgivable!
I didn't say anything.
Okay. Done.
Thanks.
I want to get fatter.
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
Alright! It's the heat of summer!
When you say summer, you think of the pool and the beach!
Let's go to the beach!
And the beach is all about swimsuits and cutting loose!
Oh, Yutaka can't get enough.
Are you really a high school girl?
Yutaka is sure everyone would love to see Yutaka in a swimsuit!
I don't think so.
On the next A Channel: Beach.
The only thing Yutaka wants is to see Toorun in a swimsuit!
Me, too! Me, too!
You're not going to make fun of that?