Attention, please!
I'm sick of all your smiling!
There it is!
Standing in heels makes my feet sore!
What is this Selfish?
Perhaps it's supposed to be a flight attendant?
Is there a princess among our passengers today?
It's looking for the princess!
Indeed it is.
Where did you hide her?
We wouldn't tell you even if we knew!
Then it seems I have no use for you.
Selfish!
Attention, please!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Self!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Self!
Love loove looooove!
Have a memento!
I'm deeply sorry!
I put everyone in danger because my barrier was too weak...
That's not it, really!
It's not your fault, Rosetta.
We all share the blame.
However...
I have nothing to add.
You realize your own shortcomings.
Do your best to overcome them.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
A Gorgeous Transformation!
A New Heroine Arrives?!
Alice, you've been sighing a lot lately.
Perhaps you should take a respite, Madam.
Thank you, Sebastian.
Through Cure Ace's guidance,
Mana and Makoto have reached new heights and strengthened their powers.
I must better myself as those two have.
Madam, you spare no effort in your pursuits.
Yet it is still not enough.
I must try harder...
Adversity
If you'd please.
Your fists are clouded!
I could never protect the others if I gave in here!
One more round!
Madam...
It seems the time has come to use this...
Created using the most cutting edge technology,
this artificial Commune was modeled after the genuine article!
Now is the time for me to serve Madam.
Precure Love Link!
If it is for Madam's sake, then I, Sebastian,
will stoop to any evil I must!
Now, begin the trial run!
Its speed is excellent!
Everything feels perfect!
This will certainly let me be of use to Madam!
Precure Sebastian Attack!
The princess ain't here.
Say that once you've put some effort into looking.
Oh, like you're one to talk?
And what's with the hat? Should I be callin' you Madam?
Sunburns are bad for my skin!
Oh, right!
I'll go relax in some negative ions!
Hey, you ain't got time for a spa day!
Clear one's mind, and become refreshed.
Come here, my ions!
My, look at the time!
I must hurry!
Oh, where'd it go?
I swear on my title of head butler of the Yotsuba family that I shall support Madam!
What?!
Oh no, I need my sunscreen!
What's this?
I feel like I've seen this before...
Precure Love Link!
Precure Love Link?
Huh?!
What is this?
You do this!
Oh, I see...
Wait.
Its manner of usage matters not.
What does matter is how the artificial Commune transformed into all of this.
Artificial Commune?
Ah!
There it is!
The artificial Commune is gone!
Gone!
Sebastian?
Madam!
Is something the matter?
What's all this "artificial Commune" stuff about?
Artificial Commune?
Oh, well...
Oh, incoming call!
Alice, there's a Selfish going berserk in the Yotsuba Mall!
I'll be there immediately!
I must defend everyone this time!
Um-yay!
Um-yay um-yay um-yay um-yay um-yay!
Eat yer fill!
Everyone, please escape!
Um-yay um-yay um-yay um-yay um-yay!
It's eating all the free samples!
If I fill up on free samples, I don't have to pay any money!
What a small-minded Selfish!
Don't call me small!
Your attacks sure are.
You gonna take that, Selfish?
Time to get big!
Self!
They grow up so fast!
Who might you be?
I can't simply hide my identity after being asked, can I?
My name is... uh...
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Yeah, just like that!
Brimming with beauty,
Cu—
—tie Madam!
Tea Madam?
It's Cutie Madam!
So, you're married?
No, she's no Madam, she's just Mammo!
Hey, did you eat something you found on the ground?
What a turn of events!
She undoubtedly transformed using the artificial Commune!
To think it would fall into the hands of the enemy...
So, what?
There's so much wrong here, I don't know where to begin.
What are you up to?
This is a grave matter!
I could get used to this.
Nobody can take their eyes off of my new look!
Shaddup!
You almost messed up my hair!
Have some table scraps!
Seeeeelf!
Girls, let's go!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow
Love love loooooove!
Enjoy your just desserts!
Hey!
Whose side are you on?
Curious...
What was that?
Did Mammo have a change of heart?
I must recover the artificial Commune at all costs!
Look at this article.
"The Black Beauty, Cutie Madam, Appears!!"
It seems she's been appearing here and there to help people.
Oopsie!
Hey, look up there!
Oh no!
S-Someone help me!
Not yet.
I need a full audience.
A male construction worker is in a dire situation!
Here's my chance!
The hero saves the day again!
My name is Cutie Madam!
I'm a strong, beautiful lady!
I'm open for autographs!
What's Mammo after?
It's hard to think she's had a change of heart...
But she's saving people, so something in her had to change, right?
Her look sure changed, though.
I think she's gotten cuter!
I hear she's even getting a lot of female fans!
I am so not into her.
Regardless, we need to investigate what her plans are and what power she used to transform.
We should split up and search for her.
Yeah.
Alice, is something wrong?
Oh no, nothing at all.
Where? Where are you, Cutie Madam?
I mean, Mammo!
There?
Wow, it's Cutie Madam!
You're gorgeous!
Could you put that visit on the house?
Of course!
I've been looking for you.
Who... er, what are you?
You may call me the Steel Butler.
The Steel what?
Enough! Return the artificial Commune at once!
Oh, so that was yours...
Now, return it!
And if I refuse?
I shall retrieve it by force.
Feel free to try!
My apologies in advance!
This is nothing!
I must not lose.
I must not be defeated!
Now, if you'll excuse me!
Sebastian!
I'm deeply sorry, Madam.
I'm the one who should apologize.
You developed the artificial Commune out of your wholehearted desire to protect my powerless self.
I apologize for being an unfit master.
That's absurd!
Madam, you are the greatest master a servant could ask for!
Come to think of it, you always did protect me.
You'd break my fall when I tripped on a stone,
scare off the monsters in a haunted house when I got scared,
and make me laugh on lonely, sleepless nights.
It is now my turn to protect you.
Heroger Show
This is the end, Heroger!
Your grave shall be dug here!
I shall protect Earth's peace!
Out of the way!
You...
My name is Cutie Madam!
I'm a strong, beautiful lady!
Not bad.
I think I'll join in on the fun.
Hey, you! Your grave shall be dug here!
Huh?
Farewell, Heroger!
I am justice!
I am the strongest!
Stop this foolishness!
You're only making the children cry!
I'm the hero today.
And I won't have anyone upstage me!
This power exists to make my wildest dreams come true!
Then I shall stoop to any evil I must to stop you!
For the children, and for the butler who loves me so!
Madam...
Sebastian, protect the children!
Right!
Now, we must escape!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
Prepare yourself, false hero, Cutie Madam!
You're the one who should watch out!
You're really into it today.
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Return the artificial Commune!
That's mine now.
I already wrote my name on it.
Then I shall retrieve it by force!
For Sebastian, who has protected me all this time!
You've discovered your love, Cure Rosetta.
Cure Ace...
You protect, and are protected.
The Precure's Five Vows!
First!
To love is to defend one another!
Protect each other at all times to protect your love!
Right!
Now Ai, let's go!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
How'd you do that?
Now, Cure Rosetta!
I won't lose to you!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
She reflected it!
Amazing!
She powered up!
What was that for?!
I liked that alter ego!
Well done, Cure Rosetta.
You're a warm, yet strong girl.
Cure Ace...
I'm sorry, Sebastian.
I broke the artificial Commune...
Think nothing of it.
You needed no such thing.
The tea you make truly is the best.
I hope you can make it for a long time to come.
As do I.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
What do I want in life?
Didn't you want to be a doctor?
Yeah, but I don't know if that's really my dream anymore...
Uncertainty of the heart leads to weakness!
This is an excellent chance to sort out your feelings!
And when you're troubled, you go to the beach!
Who knows where this could lead us?
Let's hope it's nowhere weird...
Dokidoki Precure:
How Do You Really Feel?
Rikka's Troubled Yet Again!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!