I call that phenomenon "Revival."
Current Temp
Drive Safe
I go back in time, usually one to five minutes before, and watch the same scene play out again.
Current Temp
Drive Safe
Each time, it's right before something bad happens.
As a result, I've prevented several disasters from occurring.
Welcome back, Satoru.
Ma.
Are you Fujinuma Satoru?
We'd like to talk with you at the station.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Mikoto Municipal
Grade School
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Did you watch Maskman?
Apparently next week is the last episode.
I forgot to watch Masked Rider Black!
1988...
February 15th
(Mon)
February the 15th?
Good morning, class.
February 15th
(Mon)
Good morning!
February 15th
(Mon)
What's wrong, Satoru?
Take your seat already.
Huh? Uh...
Right.
Where was my seat, again?
Wake up, Fujinuma.
That's Hinazuki's desk.
Monday...
Kayo's starting the week late again, huh?
D'you like Kayo, Fujinuma?
Ya two weirdos'd make a perfect couple.
I'm taking attendance.
Is this real life?
Azuma.
Here.
Abiko.
How did I end up here?
Abe.
Here.
Ikuta.
What is going on?
It's 18 whole years ago!
How far did you get in DQ3?
I'm level 15 now.
Damn, you slow!
Just kidding. I'm actually level 25.
Pull the other one!
What's up, Satoru?
My head kinda hurts, so I'm going to the nurse's office.
With your bag?
Whatever.
I'll let Teach know.
What the hell's going on?
Is this a Revival?
But why like this?
It makes no sense.
Ma!
Fujinuma
H...
Hello.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, just some stranger.
That's right.
She must be at work.
Ma...
I'm back.
Ma!
"Ma"?
Huh?
I said "Mom."
You silly boy.
What d'you want for dinner? Hamburg steak or meatballs?
H-Hamburg steak.
Hang on. I'll be done in a bit.
Just this mornin', you threw a tantrum 'cause your recorder was missin',
but you're over it already?
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's not worth cryin' over.
I had times like these too, huh?
I'd forgotten all about them.
No, I just hadn't realized.
Times I'd never given a second thought to.
And times I lost forever.
This is definitely a Revival.
A second chance.
I won't ever let go of these times again.
Mom.
That was great.
Thank you.
What's gotten into you, Satoru?
Thanks for the food!
My pleasure.
Morning!
Am I going to repeat 18 years of my life this way?
Mornin', Satoru.
Y-Yo, Osamu.
If this actually is a Revival, then I'm not here by mere chance.
It must be to prevent something bad from happening.
Does that mean I'll have to start here to save Ma?
But why this time period?
1988 National
Hockey Champions
I don't see an anomaly anywhere.
Hinazuki Kayo.
She lived with her mother, if my memory serves.
Wow...
That's perfect.
A blunt force trauma?
This group really is weird.
I can't discuss DQ with any of you.
Y-Yeah...
I mean, Hiro's more into FF, and Kazu only plays shooters.
Hiro...
Kazu...
I'm starting to remember.
And Satoru doesn't even have an NES!
Was that so?
But, Osamu, you can't talk to DQ buddies about anything but DQ, right?
I like this group because we're all into different things.
Kenya.
He's a smart guy, just like I thought he was.
By the way, Satoru.
Mind if I ask you something?
What is it?
Do you like Hinazuki?
You were staring at her the whole time during class.
Really?!
Come to think of it, he stopped and
stared at Hinazuki this mornin', too.
What's this, Satoru?
Why didn't you talk to us about it?
Leave it all to me!
Wha—
I'll get you a chance to talk to Hinazuki!
K-Keep it down.
U-Uh...
I don't know if I like her,
but she has been on my mind a little.
He said it!
Satoru, you got guts!
Well said, my boy!
I'll set things up so you can meet her after school!
What are you, stupid?
Not pulling any punches, eh?
That's the first thing you've got to say?!
I said that out loud...
Damn that Kazu.
He went and told her straight up that I liked her.
L-Look...
I thought that maybe we could be friends.
We go home the same way, after all.
What about me gave you that idea?
This brat is a pain in the ass.
But I kinda get it.
Because, Fujinuma,
you're a fake, just like me.
What's with her?
What is she saying?
I saw you runnin' back home yesterday.
Are mothers really that important?
Yeah.
Oh.
Hey, Hinazuki!
Wait!
I wanna be friends with you!
You wanna be my friend?
Then...
Could you kill someone for me?
I could've saved her!
Hinazuki was going through something bad even before she was murdered.
If I can resolve this huge anomaly, then maybe...
Episode 2
Palms
Because, Fujinuma,
you're a fake, just like me.
It's not like she realized I'm posing as my past self.
True, I was kind of playing it by ear today,
but I was the same my first time through grade school, too.
I was playing the role of my ideal self so I could get along with people.
Don't be embarrassed. Show some courage.
It was all so I could fit into this cramped society.
Sorry about that!
What was it, number two?
No!
You took long enough in there.
She must've seen through that.
I thought you'd fallen in or something!
I bet you filled the bowl!
She said "just like me,"
which means she's probably the same.
Can't take your eyes off her, huh, Satoru?
So, how'd it go with Hinazuki?
Did you manage to ask her to walk home together?
N-Nah, we just chatted a bit.
You chatted? Alone?
Yeah.
That means you've got a chance!
No way she'd talk to you alone otherwise!
So should I give her another message on your behalf?
So annoying.
How am I supposed to deal with these morons?
Quit fooling around, you guys.
What if you rush it and ruin things for him?
Good point.
He's still way off, but I appreciate it.
Satoru.
We'll all still be in the same class in sixth grade,
so take it slow and steady.
Got it.
School will be closing shortly.
February 17th
Come to think of it, when did Hinazuki disappear?
Time could be running out.
Students who are still in the building,
please turn off the lights and close the windows.
Let's bounce, Satoru.
Please be careful around traffic on your way home.
C-Coming.
Huh?
Didn't you just buy a pair of McGregor gloves?
Oh yeah, I did have those.
I wonder if I forgot them somewhere.
Probably at the hideout.
Hey, guys.
Can we stop by the hideout?
What are you talkin' about?
We decided we wouldn't go right after snowfall since we'd leave footprints.
I-Is that so?
See you tomorrow!
Ta-ta!
Yeah.
Kenya!
Thanks for earlier.
Honestly, it puts me off when
people kick up a fuss around me.
No kidding.
Well, don't worry about it.
Hey, Satoru...
I don't know why, but I get this feeling that Hinazuki being on your mind is something really important.
This might not be any of my business,
but talk to us if you need anything.
I'm sure the guys wanna help you out.
Sure. Thanks.
I get that they don't mean any harm.
And it was thanks to Kazu that I got to meet with Hinazuki in the first place.
So, how'd it really go?
With Hinazuki.
Did you manage to talk to her?
Yeah.
I think she spoke to me from the heart a little.
That so?
By the way, Satoru.
Lately, have you...
read the student anthology?
N-No, I haven't.
It's actually pretty interesting.
Go through it sometime.
Ta-ta. See you tomorrow.
Ta-ta.
Class 5-4 Student
Anthology
Ripples and Waves
Kenya was probably referring to Hinazuki's essay.
"The Town With Only Me Erased," by Hinazuki Kayo.
When I grow older, old enough to go wherever I want by myself,
I want to go a faraway country.
I want to go a faraway island.
I want to go to an island with nobody around.
I want to go to an island with no sorrow or suffering.
An island without adults, children, classmates, teachers, or Mom.
On that island, I'll climb trees when I want,
swim in the ocean when I want,
and sleep when I want.
And on that island, I'll think about the
town from which only I've been erased.
Kids will go to school as always,
adults will go to work as always,
and Mom will eat as always.
When I think about the town from which I've been erased, I feel lighthearted.
I want to go far, far away.
Hinazuki's essay is most definitely a cry for help.
I'm home!
Thank you for this meal.
Kenya probably thinks I took an interest in Hinazuki not because I have a crush on her, but because I read her essay.
Mom.
What?
On my birthday, can I call my
friends over and throw a party?
Y-Yeah, sure.
But we can't fit too many in this tiny apartment.
Don't worry. I'll only ask around five.
This is the first time you've ever asked for anything like this.
Wanna get a big cake?
Yeah. Thanks.
What I'm supposed to do now
is dig deep and get closer to Hinazuki.
I'll do things I never did in the past,
change Hinazuki's actions that way,
and prevent all the accidents that occur around me in the future.
If I keep that up...
Satoru, you awake?
Five, you said?
Did you get a girlfriend?
What, you're asleep?
She's a devil.
That reminds me.
I never showed Mom my essay because I
was scared of her devilish perceptiveness.
What did I write about, again?
1988 National
Hockey Champions
All right! I'm gonna go home and play DQ!
Me too!
It's snowing again?
Then we can't go to the hideout.
Satoru, Hinazuki's leaving.
Shouldn't you go after her?
Osamu...
It's fine, Kenya.
I'll catch up with her.
Thanks, Osamu.
Ta-ta!
Satoru really does have guts!
There's no need to run.
I know just where to find Hinazuki.
I'm guessing that her mother abuses her,
which is why she doesn't want to go home
and loiters at that park until nightfall.
And I used to think she was just a weird girl...
Hinazuki.
Fujinuma?
What're you doin' here?
Right back at you.
I said I wanna be friends with you, remember?
I can't murder anyone for you, though.
I was obviously kiddin'.
Yikes. She's the type of girl I have trouble dealing with.
You're, like, putting on an act, aren't you?
Pretending to smile. Pretending to be nice.
Pretending to be worried.
I don't think that's a bad thing.
Not that I'm one to talk,
but I can't see the real you.
You're probably right.
I am putting on an act.
I want people to like me.
I want friends.
I suck at interacting with people,
so I thought about what I could do to achieve that.
And I figured I could get to like everyone.
When I did, putting on that act got a little easier.
Yeah,
I feel like playing a part eventually makes it a part of you, too.
I feel like saying something aloud eventually makes it come true.
It's just like those nostalgic-sounding words Airi said.
In order to obtain what they want, everyone puts up with things, puts in effort, and picks up skills.
When they fall, they pick themselves back up.
Hinazuki must be the same.
I bet she's enduring something right now.
Unlike me, she's putting on a stoic act.
She's trying to pretend she feels nothing.
But there's no way a girl who's only ten years old could be that strong.
Hinazuki.
Take this.
I'm throwing a birthday party.
Fujinuma Satoru's Birthday Party
You should come.
A-Are you sure you want me to?
There'll be a lot of other people, right?
I don't know yet.
I decided to ask you first.
It's on March 2nd.
You'll come, won't you?
S-Sure.
Fujinuma, aren't your hands cold?
Y-Yeah, they are.
It looks like I left my gloves somewhere.
Hey. You're 29 years old. Get a hold of yourself.
What are you blushing for?
Fujinuma, I'm done.
My hand's a little bigger than yours, huh?
What are you, stupid?
But you know what?
You're kinda easy to talk to these days.
Well...
I did decide not to lie to you.
I said that out loud.
H-Hinazuki!
Ta-ta!
See you tomorrow!
She wasn't wearing gloves either.
This is where Hinazuki was last seen, 18 years ago.
I think her body was only found after the snow melted.
Girl
Isolation
Disappearance
Abduction
Death
I won't leave Hinazuki alone in this park.
I...
Hinazuki
I want to change the future!
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory