Within the infinitely vast universe,
Fumizuki Academy is a high school established for promoting victory in exam score battles.
Rage Meter
In other words, it is a breeding ground for warriors who use academic scores as weapons.
This did
not really happen.
With the dignity of their class at stake,
they fight in the subjects that they excel at
and attempt to obtain the more advanced setups of opposing classes.
Capable people will receive honor
and a fantastic and elegant school environment.
Those without abilities will descend into a pitiful bottomless pit
and live a hellish life.
This is the story of the student warriors who fought against their cruel fate.
And here, one can discover the fates of those who have failed the Summoned Being Exam War.
Although they have student discounts,
each ticket is still 1000 yen.
A medium coke is 300 yen.
Small popcorn is 400 yen.
Is this really the cost for only two hours?
Movie theaters are horrifying.
Yoshii-kun.
W-What is it, Himeji-san?
Want to see that?
Sign:  My First Love in the Center of the World 2
Oh. Looks good.
Let's watch it, Aki.
O-Oh.
I'll pass. You two can go watch it by yourselves.
Eh? Why?
Then you want to watch an anime?
That's not what I'm saying.
Just give up, Akihisa.
Men are powerless.
Y-Yuuji...
Yuuji, which one do you want to see?
I want freedom, and quickly.
Then let's watch the complete edition of Revelation of Hell.
Wait a minute—that's three hours and twenty five minutes long!
Times two.
Isn't that longer than school!?
This is to compensate for not being able to see each other during school.
I'm just going to go back.
I'm not letting you leave today.
What are you doing, Shouko? That's dangerous!
Two student tickets for two runs.
One student ticket and one pointless unconscious student ticket for two runs, right?
What a perfectly matched couple!
I'm so jealous.
Yoshii Akihisa.
Both of his parents are working outside the country.
His sister is also studying abroad and is not home.
He happily lives a life full of freedom.
Breakfasts should be...
...made simple. Dinners can be more fancy.
This side is for breakfast.
The bigger side can be saved for dinner.
Happily.
Good morning, Fukuhara-sensei.
Good morning.
You're Yoshii-kun from Class F.
Aren't you Class A's Kubo-kun?
That's right. Salutatorian of the year, Kubo Toshimitsu.
Crap. If I don't hurry, I won't be able to review for first period.
Later.
Hey!
What is it?
You aren't eating that?
I guess not.
It can't be eaten anymore.
Can I have it?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
He wants... what I've bitten before.
If I go by the thirty-second rule, it should be fine.
I'll be troubled...
Eh? Why?
You're too bold.
Isn't everyone watching?
I see...
You're right.
Okay, see you.
It's mine!
Eh? Did I step on something?
Yeah, it's my lifeline...
Good mornin', Himeji-san!
Good morning, Yoshii-kun!
So that is the love letter for Yuuji.
But Yuuji already has Kirishima-san.
Yo, it's rare for you to show up so early, Akihisa.
How'd it go yesterday?
The food budget for this month quickly disappeared in the darkness of the movie theater.
What about you?
When I awoken,
I saw a bounded cow getting killed.
When I tried to escape at the right moment,
I got knocked out by the stun gun again.
When I woke up, I saw the cow once more...
You guys really did watch it twice.
When I tried to escape, I'd be knocked out.
I had the terrible feeling that I would see the cow being slaughtered every time I opened my eyes.
So I gave up on running away.
You could never see the beginning of the film.
That's nothing. What am I going to do until my next allowance?
Can't you just sell off your mountain of games?
The hell are you saying?
How can I trade those unmatchable, brilliant works for food?
You ever heard of the phrase "to fry in one's own grease?"
It's only 'cause you're well-off that you can say such things.
This is a life-and-death matter to me!
Akihisa, you think my life isn't in danger?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I can't believe that our setup is even crappier than before.
The reason for that is...
It's all your fault, you bastard!
This is the result of everyone's hard work; you're so heartless to complain.
It's because you lost!
Why are you talking, Aki?
You don't have the right to talk about others.
We're the same. Neither of us could be of use.
I guess that's true.
Minami-sama, in her carelessness, was completely crushed by Hideyoshi's sister...
What's with "Minami-sama?" You screwing with me?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
You're the one who told me to call you that!
Just call me Minami!
Yes ma'am!
Minami, in her carelessness...
Ow! Ow! Ow! My temples are going to pop!
This attack is pretty boring.
This guy was the key to the battle!
And yet he couldn't even get full score on an elementary-level test.
You can't blame it on Sakamoto-kun.
There's nothing wrong with the result. I like this room.
So it is true that Himeji-san likes Yuuji...
Because I can sit wherever I want in this classroom...
Okay! Time to start homeroom.
Everyone sit—oh, everyone's already seated.
Eh? Why is it Nishimura-sensei?
Because you guys are hopeless idiots, I'm here to raise your scores!
From today on, I, the one in charge of make-ups, will be replacing Fukuhara-sensei as your homeroom teacher!
What!?
And I'll be doing narrations from now on.
Iron Man is going to be our homeroom teacher?
I will properly educate you guys with an iron fist! Prepare yourselves!
Now we'll have to go through hell every single day.
That's true. I wonder if there's anything we can do.
Oh, right. We'll just have another Summoned Being War and win it.
Can't do that.
Why not?
According to the rules, the losing class cannot declare war for 3 months.
Three...
Sign: 3 months
It's nothing. Three months pass pretty quickly.
We can develop new battle plans with this time, as well.
Why is it so bleak?!
There're also good things.
500 yen per picture.
I'm buying it! How beautiful!
Thanks for shopping.
Your meal money...
What are you worried about?
Sign: Secret Photo Collection vol.3
2-F Yoshii Akihisa
If I'm a man, I should have no regrets!
How brave.
After this, I'll really have to live on one pack of instant noodles a day until my allowance arrives.
Akihisa, aren't you forgetting something?
So you guys were here!
Hey, Aki, where are we meeting up this weekend?
Meeting up?
Don't say you forgot! You promised to buy crepes for me.
D-Does that mean that yesterday wasn't enough?
Yesterday was yesterday. A promise is a promise.
Sign: Yesterday
Sign: Promise.
Can I go too?
Eh! Himeji-san too?
There's actually another movie I want to watch with Yoshii-kun.
My food budget...
With the narrator switched out, it is the weekend.
Ramen man always wakes up earlier than others.
I'll use that for dinner. That for—oh!
I can cut it in half again and eat half.
Then cut the remaining into half and eating that half.
If I continuously repeat eating half,
one pack can last forever.
I might actually be a genius.
He's enjoying life in many ways.
I still can't afford to waste anything.
Hold on, now that I think about it...
Going to the movies and eating crepes with girls...
Is it a date?
Yeah! This is a date! It's not some punishment game!
It's fine to lose some blood for this!
Ah! Himeji-san!
That's...
So it's still a punishment game.
What are you zoning out for, Aki?
I've been beaten by this cruel and uncaring life.
Yoshii-kun!
Morning, Mizuki. That outfit is so cute!
Thank you. I was almost late because it took so long for me to pick it out.
Yeah, I spent a while thinking about what to wear, too.
Thankfully, I could still fit into my blouse from last year.
Eh? So that means since last year you haven't grown at—
Ow, ow! I haven't even said anything yet!
I know what you were going to say!
Rope!
Almost... Almost...
Why is Ninja Pervert here?
Self-training.
What do you want to see, Yoshii-kun?
We'll let you choose the movie today.
Me?
The price is still the same for each movie.
Then it's more worth it to watch longer films.
Yuuji, what do you want to watch?
Can my wants be fulfilled?
Then we'll watch War and Peace.
Hey! That's seven hours and four minutes!
Times two.
Fourteen hours and eight minutes... Who the hell can sit for that long!?
If you feel bored, you can sleep by my side.
That's not sleeping!
It's fine.
It's the same, as long as we're together.
No... No more!
Two student tickets for two runs.
One student ticket and one pointless unconscious student ticket for two runs again, right?
Her bluntness is so admirable.
I'm jealous.
Let's just pick a shorter film.
Are you really not going to have any, Aki?
It's delicious.
It's all right. I'm actually really picky when it comes to food.
I don't really like crepes.
If I don't start saving now, my food budget for tomorrow will...
I see. I was going to give you some of my banana crepe, since it's too big.
Eh?
I wanted you to taste some of my strawberry crepe, too.
Eh?!
Too bad you don't like them.
Yeah. What a shame.
I'm really an idiot! Look what I've done to myself!
It's a rare occasion for Himeji-san to feed me crepes with her mouth.
That single bite would give me more calories than my breakfast!
You want to try some?
It's good.
Oh, there's no helping you.
Y-Yoshii-kun, taste mine too, please.
I said it first.
It isn't a matter of who's first.
Here...
You can't, onee-sama!
Preposterous! Onee-sama was going to give some of her already-bitten sweet crepe to that filthy swine!
Miharu will not allow this!
I won't you let you get what you want, swine!
Swine?
I'll destroy you right now!
Eh? Me?!
Ah! Move aside, Move aside!
My crepes!
30 second rule.
Stand still! You swine!
Stop it, Miharu!
Wait for me guys!
Yoshii-kun... You dare dirty my face...
Why do I have to go through this kind of punishment?!
That child isn't normal.
Not normal?
Hey, Akihisa, what are you doing?
Hideyoshi, this way!
What is it?!
You swine!
Where the hell did they go?
If you get that filthy smell of yours on onee-sama,
I'll incinerate you, right down to the bone!
Where the hell are you hiding!?
Why are we hiding?
No... because she said she'll incinerate...
I'm just guessing, but are you guys running from her?
Yep. Do you have any ideas on how to get away?
If only I could summon my summoned being...
The Summon System doesn't work outside of school.
Yeah.
Oh, right! I happen to have some costumes from the theater club with me.
How about you wear this disguise?
Disguise?
Hey... I thought these were supposed to be for guys.
The members gave them to me.
I thought they were for guys.
How can it be for guys if it's for you?!
It's bizarrely cute...
What is this sudden sense of submission...
This is annoying!
I've found you!
Be good and—
What's with that outfit?
Don't ask! It's embarrassing!
Too filthy and impure!
If you think that cross-dressing can win onee-sama's heart, you're way off!
No. You're the one that's totally wrong.
I'm a normal girl who likes guys.
How dare you try to interfere with the pure relationship between Miharu and onee-sama, you swine!
I won't let you get away!
Why did it turn out like this?!
Seems like it backfired...
Nope, it's fine like this.
What should we do now? She's still right on our tail.
There's no other way; let's split up into three.
Wouldn't she just end up chasing me?
Oh! I have a good idea.
Let's go to Fumizuki.
Go to school?
I get it!
I found one!
Takeuchi-sensei teaches modern Japanese.
I'm completely useless when it comes to that.
There's no time to pick and choose.
Takeuchi-sensei, we want to have a Summoned Being War simulation.
Okay, I'll permit it.
Okay! Summoned Being,
summon!
Summoned Being,
Eh? How mean! Are you trying to obstruct my love?
Summon!
There's nothing to be afraid of as long as we have Himeji-san's Summoned Being.
This is our win!
I'm sorry, Shimizu-san!
I'm not going to let you have your way!
Attacking me?!
Seriously!?
Tutorials for those who have no points!
Eh? There's no school today, though!
As long as Miharu is with onee-sama, the hellish supplementary lesson will be just like heaven.
Together with onee-sama.
I don't want to do work!
Yoshii, have you finally come out?
You're mistaken!
Sign: Misunderstanding
I'm worn out.
Yeah. I hope Minami-chan and Shimizu-san are fine.
Shimizu-san must be happy to be with Minami.
Yoshii-kun, I'm sorry for today.
I forced you to run around with me.
Though, it was really fun.
It's all right. I had a good time too, Himeji-san.
You've really been kind since elementary school.
When I had to leave in the middle of the Placement Exam, you tried to reason with the teacher.
You argued that it wasn't right to give a zero on the exam because of illness.
But the teacher said that being physically prepared for the exam is also part of it.
He didn't even listen to me.
The Summoned Being Exam War earlier was also started for me, right?
I heard from Sakamoto-kun already.
From Yuuji?
I really am very happy.
I see.
Himeji-san.
Yes?
Um... About that letter that you wrote a few days ago...
Was that really a...
You mean this?
This letter is a chain letter.
Didn't you know?
If you don't give out the chain letter within three days, you'll be very unlucky.
But I didn't have the courage to give it out, so it went over three days.
It's so unbearable.
It's just like you said; it's a chain letter.
Himeji-san...
If you don't mind...
I'll...
No need.
One day, I will give it to someone with my own will and power.
I see.
One day... Definitely.
Will you support me?
Yup. I wish you success.
Thank you!
Breakfast.
Anyhow, he was enjoying it.
Oh, what's this?
Let's see.
Dear Yoshii-kun,
You're probably surprised to receive a letter like this all of a sudden.
However, I wanted to tell you my true feelings and wrote this.
This must be a love letter!
When I see the bright and cheerful Yoshii-kun,
I realized that my heart was being healed.
Someday, I hope that you'll be able to understand these feelings I have for you.
Please accept this.
To my beloved Yoshii-kun.
Wait, "boku?"
TL Note: Boku - Commonly used by boys, as in I, to indicate themselves.
A guy?!
Hey, Akihisa, who's the letter from?
It's gone! The letter is gone!
I even had the photo I just bought in it, too!
Well, it should be fine.
I didn't write my name on it.
This is...
Good luck.
No!!!
It even comes with a photo.
Someday for sure!
The fourth question.
Based on Mother Goose nursery rhymes, what is created from "sugar and spice and everything nice?"
Curry with rice!
Girls are not food.
Next week:  Love, Spice, and Bento.
This will be on the test.