What good is it if you don't deflect all of them?!
You're leaving too much distance!
Yessir!
Your actions are too routine!
I can tell what your next move is!
Right!
Hey, Yagyu!
It's my fault! Yagyu was just—
Stop it, Hibari.
B-But...
You're making a mistake if you think you're doing Hibari a favor, Yagyu!
All right, that's all for today.
You two, stay behind for extra training.
Eh?
Extra training? I feel sorry for them.
Mr. Kiriya has been really strict lately.
Hibari's a ninja.
Sorry. It didn't hurt, did it, Yagyu?
She can't rely on Yagyu forever.
I'm so sorry!
That was some pretty intense training.
You were watching?
They all have unique potential. With the right effort,
they'll definitely blossom into great talents.
It's because headquarters were able to recruit such fine candidates for us.
I can't imagine what it would be like without you all.
Those who have the makings of a true ninja are rare.
Without talent...
there's nothing we can do.
Well, it was awfully hard for us at first.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
A Ninja Classroom Retrospective
From now on, you are ninja.
Two Years Ago
Forget everything you knew about normal school life.
I'm Ikaruga. It's a pleasure to meet you.
The name's Katsuragi. My pleasure.
Looks like we're the only ones in ninja school, huh?
It may just be the two of us,
but let's have a good time of it.
Nice to meet you!
Huh?
We already exchanged greetings earlier.
So that's how you wanna play it? Fine.
First, let me see what kind of skills you have.
Right!
Right.
Sure. Nothing beats showing off my skills!
Begin!
Wh-Why, you!
That's enough!
Dammit.
I didn't even land a single a hit... Lame!
Oh well! No use getting bummed out on day one!
How else am I ever gonna make my dream come true?!
I'll beat her, no matter what.
I win!
Does it hurt for you to smile at me or what?
Smile, she says?
I have no right to smile.
Katsuragi, tell me the five fundamental elements.
L-Let's see...
Wood, fire, earth, metal, and water,
and a ninja needs these five elements to master their techniques.
Good.
Damn! Rubbing it in, huh?
Well, I have to admit, you've got skill.
It's true that right now, you're going to be better at anything we do.
Th-That jerk!
'Sup!
That's a nice greeting, first thing in the morning.
Sure, you may be better at training than I am,
but let's see about when things get serious.
If you don't like me,
say something!
Wha—
I simply do not wish to get involved with anyone else.
Is that right? Then like it or not, I'm involving myself!
Oh, whoops! Pardon me.
See you later!
You've got some nice legs there.
Your breasts are shapely, too... size not withstanding.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Hmph, you finally feel like taking me on now?
If you want my attention that badly...
Battle sphere!
What?!
No one will interfere with us in here.
H-Hold on! Mr. Kiriya said we weren't allowed to use battle spheres without permission yet!
Oh, so now you care about what he says?
Guess you're just a loser who's all talk after all.
Bring it on then, why don't you?!
You really push my buttons!
The feeling's mutual!
What?!
I never did care for how rudely you tried to butt into my affairs right from the start!
Hmph, glad to hear it.
I've been wanting to see your true colors!
What kind of person takes delight in being told they're disliked?
Better than havin' you say you like me when you actually hate me, no?
Don't go thinking you have any place here.
You are hardly family, after all.
I won't let myself be beaten.
What do you even know about me?
That's right, nothing! Only thing I know's that you piss me off!
Another fight?
Did you hear?
That girl's family pulled a disappearing act.
Like hell I'm gonna be beaten!
The sphere's breaking down? It can't be...
Whoa, this isn't good, is it?
I can't release it.
You made it. You can release it, can't you?
I can't! I really can't!
What happens if you can't release it?
W-We'll be stuck in here, like this, trapped inside forever.
That ain't good!
Trapped inside here... like this, from now on... until we die...
Wh-What have I done?!
First, calm down.
Katsuragi...
Let's just think of a way out of this together.
Together?
Why don't we start by kicking all over the place?
Aren't you scared?
How can I be a ninja if I'm afraid to die?
I'm just saying, is all...
Why don't you blame me?
Ikaruga, you really are a funny girl.
Huh?
When you think you made a mistake, you usually apologize first, right?
You've got the order wrong, asking me to blame you.
But I did figure out one thing...
We're a lot alike in one way.
Alike?
We're both kinda awkward.
That's why we get on each other's nerves.
You might say we confront each other with what we don't want others to see in us.
So we lash out, act goofy, and become evasive.
And we end up so afraid of getting to know each other that we build up a wall, like this.
Katsuragi... you're...
Phew... It's no use. Won't budge.
Ikaruga?
We're doomed if we give up, aren't we?
Yeah. I came here because I didn't want to be beaten.
So did I.
I'll bet.
Ouchies...
M-Mr. Kiriya!
Normally, only the one who raises a sphere can bring it down again.
You dissipated the sphere from the outside?
Be grateful your technique is so shoddy.
As punishment, you'll wait out in the hall until morning.
M-Morning? It's still evening.
This is crazy.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Well, I get to see the honor student in this embarrassing pose.
Okay, I forgive you!
How arrogant!
I hope we get some new students next year.
Yeah. The more friends we have, the more fun it'll be.
Yes, you're right.
Friends...
I hope we'll get someone I can grope better!
What do you mean, "better"?
I mean just what you think, of course!
Senran Kagura
One Year Ago
Ninja Morph!
A unleashes their power by morphing.
This power materializes in a form that the self wishes to be.
Wishes to be, huh?
Wh-What is it?
Katsuragi, it's your turn.
I've been waiting for this.
Time for your shot.
Wh-What kind of getup is that?
I've always wanted to cosplay as a nurse.
This is not a game.
Well, there are no rules regarding the clothing style, but—
Mr. Kiriya!
Katsuragi, this clothing is for fighting in.
That outfit is not suited for strenuous activity, is it?
Okay, one more try.
Ninja Morph!
How's this? This is easy to move around in!
Objection! I can't fight alongside someone dressed like that!
You sure are picky.
Well, I guess this should do it.
You two have gained enough power in training during this year
to finally be able to morph yourselves.
I want you to lead your underclassman, as well.
Underclassman?
I'm going to be late on the first day!
Ah, here it is.
Let's see, I go in through... the tea room... hold on...
Ow...
You're here.
This is Asuka. She's a first year who's just enrolled in Hanzo Academy.
I'm Asuka.
Oh yeah, she's stacked!
Just the newbie I was hoping for!
What exactly were you hoping for?
Incidentally, Asuka here is
Master Hanzo's granddaughter.
Master Hanzo's?
You mean the legendary ninja?!
I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
That is the legendary ninja's granddaughter, right?
Yes.
All things considered...
Something you don't like about her?
Not especially.
Ninja Baths
Ow ow...
Are you all right?
Are you bruised all over?
I'm okay. This is nothing.
All right, that's the spirit, that's the spirit!
What are you doing?!
I'm treating your injuries.
Huh?!
I've never heard of a treatment like this before.
Excuse me, I'm getting out now.
Things are even more fun now, huh?
It takes all kinds.
Hmm?
She probably enrolled with the best wishes of her loving family.
She's nothing like us at all.
Do I sense a little jealousy?
Don't fall behind the others, Asuka!
Yessir!
I came to be resented for whatever little talent I showed.
She has no such resentment to deal with, so why not show off her talent?
Asuka!
Asuka, don't!
You only got off that easy because this is training.
I'm sorry.
Hmm? Asuka, why do you look like that?
Huh? How come? My clothes are different.
This looks like those nice uniforms I saw earlier.
Ninja Morph?
Why?
She triggered it unconsciously?
Aw, I messed up again.
You're amazing, huh?
Eh?
It took us a whole year before we could morph.
It just happened by itself.
I doubt I could do it again.
You do seem to have the capability, don't you?
She's the legendary ninja's granddaughter after all!
I'm completely not living up to my name, am I?
But I cannot bring dishonor upong Grandpa's... I mean, upon my grandfather's name.
So I'll just keep on trying my hardest.
Asuka...
If you find yourself lagging behind someone, just think "gotta catch you!".
"Gotta catch you!"?
I see. You're like us after all.
"Catch you"...
I know! Can I call you Katsu?
Say what?
I thought that "Katsuragi" sounds so formal, so maybe I could call you "Katsu"!
Oh, I kind of like the sound of that.
You do?
Spring of This Year
A squid?
Not just any squid.
It's a Todarodes pacificus.
Huh? Oh, you don't say.
These are this year's new students, Yagyu and Hibari.
I'm Yagyu.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
So cute! So this is what being an upperclassman feels like.
All right, good.
Amazing. And she hasn't had any training yet either.
She is indeed gifted.
Come on!
But the other one...
Well, at least she's avoiding them!
You don't run away! You dodge them!
I-I don't understand the difference!
I can't take any more!
You're incredible, huh?
Yagyu!
Didn't I tell you underclassmen to clean up before leaving?
Yagyu...
Sheesh, she's got some nerve.
Skill is the only measure of a ninja.
Huh?
Class, rank, and age have no meaning.
Now just a moment!
What do you think rules are for?!
Take it easy, Ikaruga.
Just a minute! Yagyu!
As class rep, I cannot tolerate such insubordination!
Man, what are we gonna do about her?
I don't think she's a bad girl.
I mean, she's nice to Hibari.
Even Yagyu, who had been a problem child,
appears to be fitting in with the others now.
Well, if I'm gonna say "problem child", that could go for all of them.
Including you, Daidoji.
Hmph. You know better than anyone why I haven't graduated.
You still have a ways to go, Daidoji.
I'll definitely score a hit against you before I graduate, Rin.
Well, good luck. I'll look forward to it.
I won't hold back either.
Of course!
However, before I could graduate, she...
The mission was a difficult one. I was against it.
Mr. Kiriya, you're the one who said that it was an important mission for the state, right?
And that it was something I could take on?
But you have just barely graduated.
This mission is too dangerous.
I'll do it! I'm going to be a super-ninja!
At the time...
I should have stopped her, even if by force.
And as a result, my graduation has been postponed indefinitely.
This is no simple struggle against the dark ninjas.
I will settle this.
It's up to me to save her.
My graduation... as well as...
the end of my journey may be close at hand.
I'm sorry, Yagyu. This is my fault again.
I should be the one apologizing.
Huh?
You're making a mistake if you think you're doing Hibari a favor, Yagyu!
Yagyu...
I'm done. I'm leaving now.
Huh? O-Okay.
So, you ignored your commander and gave instructions to Haruka?
Seizing the top-secret ninja art scroll is the primary objective.
The top-secret ninja art scroll is
meaningless without its chosen one,
so we allow a Hanzo Academy student to develop as the chosen one,
and after that, we turn them to our side.
That is the best strategy.
We could always train a chosen one ourselves after we've taken it.
The chosen one for your own scroll has yet to come forward.
I want results. Something tangible. Besides...
It's already too late.
Shower Room
Huh?
I thought I left that on my desk.
Yagyu seemed like she was angry.
I got her in trouble again.
Of course she'd be angry.
I wonder if I'll always be lagging behind like this.
It's time for me to ask a favor of you.
Is that all right, my dear little puppet?
I decided on this path
and now I won't hesitate anymore
I have the passion to go forward
and courage to match it
The feelings I accepted
might all be the result of fate
And yet now I stand perplexed
With courage
With pride
And with beauty we will go forth
Let's go according to our dreams
Let's take it all on
They're my guiding light, honest as I am
Every day a kiss
Just like lovers
You looked forward to a real fight, right?
I decided I would believe
Now I try to make it real
Let's go according to our dreams
Next Episode Preview
Hibari's Room
We did it, Hikage! It's finally our turn to do the preview!
Yeah, it is.
I'd like to take this opportunity to express how wonderful sprouts are!
Sprouts are so—
Yomi...
Yes?
There's no time.
No?
Next time, "Serpentine Academy for Girls."
Serpentine Academy for Girls
Come get it like your life depended on it.