Armin, I'm glad I could be a good person to you.
You made the right gamble.
But!
This is where my gamble begins!
We have identified a person of interest in the Eoten Fatale Incident.
Her name is...
Annie!
O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel
We will kill
The enemy is huge
We will jump
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
Mercy
Raid on Stohess District ( 2 )
Several Days Ago
Bastards are keeping me waiting.
Erwin and his people need to learn some punctuality.
At this rate those Gendarmerie escorts will beat them here.
Bet Erwin's got a gutfull of shit he just can't squeeze out.
You sure are talkative today, Corporal.
Fuckwit.
I'm always a garrulous guy.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't made the wrong call,
this never would've happened.
I told you.
No one ever knows how it'd turn out.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all, sir.
You guys!
S-So...
We have identified a person of interest in the Eoten Fatale Incident.
This time, we will capture her.
The operation commences in two days.
The location is Stohess District, a town on our route to Central.
This is our one and only chance.
Once past Stohess, Eren will be remanded to the capital.
Without him, our quest to stop those who would destroy the walls will become insuperable.
Ultimately, Mankind itself may go extinct.
We will place all our hopes on this operation.
Here is your mission.
Upon reaching Stohess, Eren will act as a decoy,
drawing the target into this underground complex.
If we can lead her to the lowest level,
its size and complexity will allow us to restrain her even if she transforms.
But should she become an Eoten before then...
Well, Eren, we'd need your help.
Yes, sir.
About this target.
Are we completely sure she's in Stohess?
Yes. Our target is a gendarme.
A gendarme?
It was Armin who reached that conclusion.
He believes the target is also responsible for the two captured Eotena's deaths.
He suspects a former member of your own 104th Cadet Corps.
J-Just a minute here. The 104th?
The name of that person of interest is...
Wait. Wait!
Annie Leonhardt.
Oh... no...
Damn it! That ring!
She really did know I was bluffing from the get-go.
She knew it was a trap.
Of course she'd come prepared!
The self-reprobation can wait.
What do we need to do right now?
We need to make contact with Squad 3 and get above ground.
We've moved to plan B.
Combat with Annie, the Eoten Fatale!
Eren transforms as planned, and assists in her capture!
Will you do it?
Of course!
Hey!
There's Squad 3!
Did plan A fail?
It failed!
Time for plan B!
She smashed straight through the ground?!
We've gotta help them!
Eren!
Get back!
Hey! Mikasa!
She's actually willing to let Eren die?
She's gambling.
Gambling on Eren's ability to survive her Eotenes stomp.
It's crazy, but it also makes her almost impossible to beat!
Annie's willing to take any risk to capture Eren!
What's our next move?
The main exit is gone.
Even if we use our Gear to get out through one of the new holes,
Annie'll be right there waiting for us.
Conversely,
if we stay here, she could randomly crush us at any moment.
I'm sure I can do something!
Like when I blocked that cannon shell.
C'mere!
Hey!
Let's go!
Stay close.
Not again!
No.
Not now.
It hurts!
You need a specific goal to transform successfully, right?
Picture it in your mind clearly. Clearly!
I'm trying!
But...
Pathetic.
You can't bring yourself to fight Annie.
Eren?
After everything you've seen her do,
can you really believe that Annie isn't a ruthless Eoten?
What happened just now?
She murdered our fellow soldiers!
How can you harbor any doubts?
Shut the fuck up!
I'm trying, aren't I?!
Annie's this "Eoten Fatale"?
Why?
Why would you think that, Armin?
From the very beginning, the Eoten Fatale knew your face.
She also recognized your nickname, "Death Drive,"
which was used only by members of the 104th.
But the most important reason
is that I'm certain Annie killed the test subjects, Sawney and Bean.
How do you know?
Only a very skilled soldier could have pulled it off.
They'd have to use their own MMG to achieve such precision.
Yeah, wasn't that why they inspected everyone's Gear?
But they found nothing suspicious about Annie's.
Annie brought Marco's Multiaxial Maneuver Gear to the inspection.
That's how she avoided getting caught.
What?
What are you blathering about?
What does Marco have to do with this?
I don't know.
You're totally sure it was his?
Yes. I know what I—
Look, brat.
We get it.
You have any hard evidence?
No, I don't.
I think Annie looks like the Eoten Fatale.
Huh?
Are you serious?!
That isn't evidence—
So you have no proof, but you'll do this anyway.
No proof?
What is this?
Then why do it?
What if it isn't her?
Then we'll know she's innocent. That's all.
And I'd feel pretty badly for her.
On the other hand, if we do nothing,
we'll have to give you up to those bastards in the capital!
You're crazy if you think Annie's an Eoten.
Eren, now that you know it's possible,
aren't you getting suspicious too?
You fought that Eotenes bitch.
Didn't it remind you of hand-to-hand combat with Annie?
You actually know, don't you?
You know Annie is the Eoten Fatale.
If so, isn't it our duty to fight her?
Or could it be that your feelings for her are stopping you?
Huh?
I've got a plan!
Mikasa and I will escape simultaneously, one fleeing that way and one the other.
Annie will attack one of us.
Use that opportunity to get out through another exit!
Wait!
That means one of you will die!
And if we stay here, we all die!
Mikasa, take your position!
Right.
I'll take that side.
Mikasa!
Armin!
How?
How can you fight her?
How?!
We have no choice.
This is a world of cruelty.
Wall Sina ( 1 )
Wall Sina encloses the capital and holds around 200,000 people.
Residency requires special dispensation, being technically
restricted to the royal family and its relatives.
Wall Sina ( 1 )
Wall Sina encloses the capital and holds around 200,000 people.
Residency requires special dispensation, being technically
restricted to the royal family and its relatives.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Wall Sina ( 2 )
One may also earn Sina residency through meritorious service in
the Garrison or the Gendarmerie. This is generally considered the
sole means for commoners to become citizens and gain safe refuge.
Wall Sina ( 2 )
One may also earn Sina residency through meritorious service in
the Garrison or the Gendarmerie. This is generally considered the
sole means for commoners to become citizens and gain safe refuge.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Eren!
Annie, I'm not letting you have Eren!
Eren.
I'll get you out right away!
Open your eyes!
Don't let that Eotenes bitch get away!
We must keep her within the Walls!
What's this?
Escort team, leave the train to us!
Go see what's happening!
Roger!
Something's really wrong.
That explosion was...
Niall.
Deploy every troop.
We should assume an Eoten has appeared.
Wh-What?!
This is Wall Sina.
There's no way an Eoten could be here!
Wait! Stay put, Jaeger!
This fuckin' disguise is done!
Call me that name again and you'll be shittin' teeth, asswipe!
Commander, I'll go too.
Retrieve your equipment from Squad 4.
Roger!
Glad you've got the spunk to go,
but please do remember to fucking survive.
Yes, sir.
Erwin, what is this?
Commander, as requested!
Good work.
Hey, Erwin!
Everyone who's mobile, follow me!
We're rendezvousing with the capture teams.
Erwin, wait.
Your actions clearly constitute treason against the Crown!
Niall, seems your brains are even skimpier than those pubes you call a beard.
'Cause you don't have a fucking clue what's going on.
Take off your Gear, Erwin!
Ai, ai! An Eoten! An Eoten is come!
What's it doing here?
Run away!
Woah, isn't that an Eoten?
I think so. But how?
Move your asses!
Goddamn slackers!
I coulda been one of 'em.
What the hell happened to me?
Fuckshit!
Don't even try to kill it.
Just do your best to slow it down!
No use! It knows how our MMG works!
Don't think this is gonna be easy, bitch!
Eren!
Answer me! Eren!
Hey! What are you doing here?
Jean!
Eren's trapped!
The plan was for him to transform!
He couldn't do it.
I think the fact that it's Annie is stopping him.
Annie?
At any rate, we have to save him!
Jean, help me!
He couldn't transform?
Eren, what in the name of fuck is wrong with you?!
Didn't I once tell you that we're really depending on you?
We entrust the world, Mankind, and our very lives to you,
and this shit is how you repay us?
And Marco. Marco...!
Fuckshit!
Eren.
This is pointless.
We gotta do somethin' about her first!
Eren, I once told Jean...
that people unwilling to sacrifice everything
can never change anything.
That for the sake of fighting monsters,
one must throw aside his humanity!
Annie is certainly capable of that sacrifice.
Although I've no idea what's driving her.
But in this battle,
those who can make that sacrifice will prevail!
Annie!
If you're too soft to kill me this time,
no bullshit "gambling on Armin" excuses!
Armin, this way!
Understood!
Aw yeah...
Almost there...
Ma'am?
Your expression. It's disturbing.
Aw yeah!
Didn't count on needin' a plan C, but nope!
Commander Erwin figures everythin'.
Alrighty then.
There's a good lass.
Just stay put.
'Fraid you can't ask your Eotena friends to eat you up here.
But fret not.
You'll be devoured, all right... by me.
I'll digest every last piece of information we can worry out of you.
She broke free?
I knew we needed more traps!
Don't let her escape! After her!
People unwilling to sacrifice everything
can never change anything!
I know that.
That's why I've failed.
I put my faith in my companions and in our bonds, and I failed.
Remember...
I'll... exterminate you...
No.
I'll fucking kill you!
There's no time to think about morality!
Just move.
No time to keep your hands clean!
That's right.
Mikasa!
This is a world of cruelty!
Now what?
Eren!
Eren.
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
"I'll exterminate every single Eoten."
The same rage that led Eren to make that fateful vow
now spurs him on...
to destroy the entire world.
The Wall
Raid on Stohess District ( 3 )