When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Looks like it's going to be a hot day.
Oh, good morning, Miss.
Yes, I am going to school.
Yes, Miss! Then I shall
accompany you as well.
Wait, what?!
What has gotten into you, Miss?!
Getting up this early
in the morning all on your own?!
Not to mention, heading off
to school of your own volition?!
I mean, to begin with,
summer break started today...
Just kidding!
Huh?
Surprised? That was a great joke of mine.
A joke?
Oh, I see, so that's what it was.
Knowing it's summer break,
I feel too restless.
How could I sleep?!
All right!
Starting today, I'm going to play
online games, watch anime, draw manga,
and have all the fun I want every day!
I feel like her life is pretty similar,
even when she has school...
But I guess she must be really happy,
considering how excited she is.
Starting today, I can spend all my time
with Hayate every day.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
But wait, I just transferred
and it's already summer break...
Other than greet my classmates
and duel at the kendo club,
did I do anything?
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
I Like Books, But Sing It
Great Palace of the Dragon King
Hakuou Academy
Man, summer break is pure bliss!
I can drink all the sake
I want all day long!
On top of which, I can do
stuff like this all I want, too!
I swear, doing nothing
is the ultimate form of luxury!
Katsy!
Let's play!
What are you guys, grade school
kids from the Showa Era?
We figured you would have time to kill,
so we came to invite you along.
Sorry! I appreciate the thought,
but I'm busy right now...
Let's go catch rhinoceros beetles!
How about a tour on foot
of the thick woods around Fuji?!
Hey! What are you doing?! Let me go!
Um, Maria, do you know
any lethal techniques?
Err... This is out of the blue.
What is this about?
Well, I met some people I believe to be
first-rate butlers at Hakuou Academy
and according to them,
it seems first-rate butlers need
to know a lethal technique or two.
Uh-huh...
So I'm thinking of learning some
kind of lethal technique, too!
I see, so that's what this is about.
Uh, but why ask me?
Why? Well...
This is just a hunch of mine,
but you look like someone
who might know the Art of Assassination.
I do not know it!
But based on my hunch...
Please toss your useless hunches
in the trash this instant!
What?! You know it, don't you?!
Nagi, not you, too.
I thought you'd at least know the Five
Point Palm Exploding Heart Technique!
Right?!
Yes...
Honestly! Don't turn me into
a master of some fanboy technique.
Besides, lethal techniques
cannot be learned so easily.
I'm sure that's true, but...
Summer break is a great opportunity
and I'd like to master one.
I was hoping there might be a book
to help me master a lethal technique...
A book...
Wow!
I would expect nothing
less of a Sanzenin library.
What an amazing number of books!
Which makes cleaning a real chore.
But books are great.
When you immerse yourself in a book,
surrounded by all these books,
it truly makes you feel intellectual.
I see. That's my Miss.
Oh, these must be the shelves
stocked exclusively for you, Miss.
Hm? How did you know?
Because this is the one
area littered with manga.
Y-You're wrong, you know!
I read other books, too!
Yes, I know that.
Look at all these video game guides.
Like I said!
Reading really does
make you feel intellectual.
Quit mocking me!
I don't see any...
To be so fixated on lethal techniques...
I cannot comprehend it.
I can.
What?
Hayate must want to
show me how cool he can be.
I shall protect you with this
elegant technique of mine, Miss.
Ah! This is impressive, Hayate!
What is it?
N-Nothing.
All right, Hayate! I'll help you, too.
I'll look for books with clues
about lethal techniques with you.
Oh, thank you very much, Miss.
Honestly! Lethal techniques!
Lethal Techniques in a Nutshell
Book of Secret Sanzenin Techniques
It's not like online karate classes
or like learning to draw manga
at a technical school.
As if there would be a book
that could teach it to you so easily...
Lethal Techniques in a Nutshell
Book of Secret Sanzenin Techniques
Funnily enough, there actually might be.
"Lethal Techniques in a Nutshell
with Colored Charts"!
I never imagined there would be
such a useful sounding book!
Yes!
Book of Secret Sanzenin Techniques
But what do you suppose these
Secret Sanzenin Techniques are?
Oh, come to think of it,
Himegami used to use them.
Mr. Himegami?
Um, I hear his name come up
every so often, but...
Oh, did I never tell you about him?
He was Nagi's butler before you came along.
Though, various things happened
and he ended up leaving...
I see.
And this butler named Mr. Himegami
also knew lethal techniques?
Does that mean that perhaps
Mr. Klaus also knows such techniques?
Would you like to know
what my lethal technique is?
No, no, not really right now...
Quit playing around and go do work!
Anyway, if other butlers can do it,
there's no way you couldn't, either!
Miss!
Hayate, we're going to do special
training based on this book!
What? Y-Yes, Master!
I'll do my best!
Don't call me "Master"!
Call me Undefeated of the North,
South, East, West, and Middle!
Huh? That's a little too long...
Quiet!
Now, follow me!
A-Are you all right?!
I scraped up my knee a little.
There goes the myth of being undefeated,
north, south, east, west, and middle.
It sure is hot outside.
Miss, perhaps you shouldn't
strain yourself too much
and take it easy in an air conditioned room.
No, this is for the sake
of your lethal technique!
Then let's get started.
Yes! Please instruct me!
Rarrr!
Well, let's start with something basic.
Yes, ma'am!
"Case 1 – the secret technique
for when you're engulfed in flames."
What's it say? Let's see...
Uh, um, aren't there any secret techniques
for defeating the enemy before
you become engulfed in flames?
Hmm, there doesn't seem
to be anything in particular.
Starting with a technique
for such a dire situation is a bit...
Well, shall we give it a try anyway, Tama?
Let's see... "First, like
the Conqueror of Century's End,
"command a body that does
not burn, even in flames..."
Raoooh!
No, no, the entire premise is wrong!
But if you can't do this,
Case 2 – the secret technique
for when you get shoved off a cliff...
As I said, let us do something about it
before getting shoved off a cliff!
Then...
The Secret Technique for Becoming
More Lovey-Dovey with the Guy You Like
What is it, Miss?
What?! It's n-n-n-nothing! It's nothing!
Wh-What kind of secret
technique is this in here?
But I would love to master it!
You want to master it, do you?
Miss?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What is it?!
Oh, no,
I'd like to skim through the whole book
to see if there's anything useful,
so would you mind letting me see it?
Y-You can't! I decline! I absolutely refuse!
What? Wh-Why not?
It's too soon for you!
Please!
I wanna see!
At any rate, I can't show you
what I can't show you!
Oh, Miss, it's dangerous to go that way!
Miss?!
So, how do I get to be more lovey-dovey?
Get Naked!
R-Ridiculous!
The entire premise...
The entire premise is wrong!
Miss! In front! In front of you!
Rarrr!
If I could do something so embarrassing...
Miss!
Rarrr!
Hayate!
H-Hey, Hayate, are you alive?
Are you all right, Miss?
What? Oh... I am...
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad I was able to save you.
Oh, right. I don't need
to rely on any secret techniques.
Hayate and I are...
Th-Thank you.
Most of this book is useless,
but it's got some serious stuff,
too, like things to watch out for.
What? Really?
Yes! If you work hard,
you should be able to master these.
Yes!
All right! I'm going to learn
a lethal technique this summer!
Yes!
I better work hard for Hinagiku, too.
Yeah, you're right.
For Hinagiku, too...
Wait, what?
For whom, did you say?
Well, Hinagiku is always
helping me out in various ways.
Besides, I also promised her
that I would show it to her
once I mastered a super lethal technique!
Promised? Oh, I see...
Oh! The book of secret techniques!
Miss, why...?!
Ha... Ha... Hayate, you...
Hayate, you jerk!
Maria.
Oh, my! What happened?!
Won't you please teach me a surefire
technique to soothe the Miss's temper.
Uh, that would require
quite a bit of training...
It would still be a long way off
before Hayate mastered a lethal technique.
So, please continue to watch every
episode of "Hayate the Combat Butler"!
Watermelon seeds. Ptewy!
(Suika no tane. Peh!)
Fight, Pero!
(Pero-san, faito!)
What?!
The Miss has run away from home?!
Yes.
Members of the SP are following her,
so there's no need to worry...
But it still makes me feel uneasy.
Since everything the Miss does
is so incredibly abrupt
and the reasons for her actions
are never that clear.
I wonder what happened.
No... I think the reason is undoubtedly you.
All right! As the Miss's butler,
and also to get to the bottom
of her reasoning,
I must go after her!
I swear! That Hayate!
What's this about it being for Hinagiku?!
Does he mean to say that Hinagiku's
more important to him than me?!
If...
If Hayate comes to love
Hinagiku more than me...
You can't. You just can't!
This is wrong, Hayate.
You have Nagi, your precious girlfriend!
What are you saying, Hinagiku?
You're the only woman I can think of
that I'm destined to be with.
Hayate!
Hinagiku!
Humph! What's with you?!
Hayate, you stupid jerk!
What about Hinagiku's so great anyway?!
Hinagiku's just a little cute, that's all!
And she's good-natured and smart and...
On top of which, she's an all-around
athlete, everyone trusts her,
and even I wish I could
be a little like her...
H-Humph!
When it comes to our bust sizes,
we're about the same!
What did you say?!
And my grades are no worse than hers!
Aw, man, summer break's here,
but I don't feel very happy somehow.
I wonder what Hayate's doing...
Or actually...
I wonder what Hayate was doing
at such an incredible mansion.
And...
Who in the world is that girl?
I have so many things I want to talk
to Hayate about and ask about.
Oh, honestly!
I'm going to hurry home and go to bed!
Oh?
It's all Hayate's fault to begin with!
You're...
Oh, you're that...
...thieving hamster.
Wha?!
Wh-Who are you calling a thieving hamster?!
Then, the trespassing hamster.
The lock-picking hamster.
For starters, I think I'd like
for you to drop the "hamster" bit.
Well, for starters,
it was a fateful reunion.
I'm glad that we've finally
caught up with her, but...
Yes...
What is the Miss doing with Miss Nishizawa?
Never mind that. Is there any point
to this camouflage?
Well, I thought it might be
better to have than not...
By the way, Hayate,
I've been meaning to ask you, but...
What is your relationship
with that Miss Nishizawa?
What?! No, uh...
I love you, Hayate!
What?!
W-We're friends.
She was my classmate at my old school...
I see, that makes sense...
What could those two be talking about?
I would imagine it's about you...
What?! You're the owner of that mansion
and you took Hayate in when
he was rendered homeless?!
On top of which, as a butler,
he's living with you under one roof?!
Yes, that's right. You have
a problem with that?
Urk... What an envious...
No, no, that's not it. I feel so defeated!
Dear God, you're so mean.
This is way unfair!
So long, hamster. Don't ever
come near my property again.
Hold, you!
What?
If I back down now,
I'll remain the miserable defeated!
And my pride won't allow for that!
Fight me! Fight me for Hayate!
Very well. I just happen
to be in a bad mood anyway.
I'll turn the tables on you!
Karaoke BOX
What's this place?
What's this place? As you
can see, it's a karaoke booth.
Don't you know?
Ah! I've heard of these places...
This is the first time I've ever
set foot in such an odd place.
Huh...
But this is smaller than our bathroom.
What?!
If you spend hours and hours
in this cramped, dimly lit box,
even if you're not the heir
to the Mendou Zaibatsu,
I feel like you'd still become
afraid of the dark and claustrophobic.
Anyway, once we've ordered drinks,
we're getting right to the battle.
What do you want to drink?
Oh, I won't mind ordering for you
if it's like just one item.
An infinitely pointless attempt to show off.
Then, I'll have a Shiun matcha green tea
and a tureen of foie gras from Périgord.
I-I doubt they have those things...
I don't really understand, but...
It seems they're going to karaoke.
What shall we do, Maria?
Maria?
Wh-What? Oh, uh, p-pardon me.
For the time being, I've paid for
the booth over here, so let's go in.
Yes.
But why did Miss Nishizawa bring
the Miss to a place like this?
Hayate! Hayate!
Yes?
Wh-What is this device?
Well, you use it to punch in
numbers to pick songs.
I see, so that's how it works.
My! How amazing!
You can even adjust the pitch.
Oh, can you search
for them in this book, too?
Wow, it's so thick!
Um, since we're here anyway,
would you like to try singing?
What?!
Wh-What are you saying,
Hayate? I could never.
I don't know any of the
songs that are popular.
Besides, I'm worried about Nagi.
It'll be fine.
We can see their room from here,
and besides, I'd like to hear you sing.
But...
Th-Then, if you go first,
I'll sing at least one song.
What?!
A-All right. Then I shall go first.
I Belong to You
Calling me from somewhere
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Yay!
Now, to see the score
we've been waiting for!
Ta-da! 35 points...
You suck! Go home!
Why?
Not surprising, considering
how off key you were.
Okay, it's your turn next!
Right.
She's never karaoked in her life.
There's no way she'll sing well, right?
Earlier, I was just warming up
and I didn't give it my best shot,
but once I get serious, I'll be sure to win!
Just watch me, Hayate!
I'll save you with my singing for sure!
Get over here quick
I'm a bit mad
Wh-What?!
Get over here quick
At mach speeds
What's with this sparkly aura?!
Socially reclusive Sunday
She looks like Kirari Tsukishima to me!
No, you have to come flying right away
I mean, she's really good!
No, no, you just have to
Of course, she is.
Why? Because she's received education
for the gifted since she was little.
No
and naturally, included in that
curriculum was voice training
I hope you'll be here soon
from super top notch instructors,
and singing lessons.
You may have forgotten, but Nagi
is technically a hyper refined young lady.
This may be her first time at karaoke,
but there's no way she'd lose
to a run-of-the-mill high school girl.
Actually, was that earlier singer Igant?
How about that?
Looks like this fight is over.
Oh, no! We're only getting started here!
Singing is love! There's
no way I'm going to lose!
Interesting! I'll pound you into the ground!
That's my line!
Karaoke BOX
Their karaoke match got heated up even more
Bring it on!
and continued late
into the night. And then...
I sang a lot and I feel better now somehow.
Sniff. I can't believe I lose every round.
Oh, you want to use my credit card to pay?
It's fine! I'll treat you
for something small like this!
I don't want to be indebted
to a rival anyway!
A rival?
Isn't that a term for when two
opponents are evenly matched?
Welcome
Miss, we have come to take you home.
Ah, thanks. I'm surprised
you knew where to find me.
We received a call from your butler.
From Hayate? I see.
So long, hamster.
Hold it right there!
Next time, we'll compete
in something different!
Whenever you like.
I'll turn the tables on you again.
Now, then...
Time to hurry home
and play games with Hayate.
Summer break has only just begun.
But at that moment,
the maid and the butler were...
Lie to me, I'll see right through it
I'm not blind
Maria, why don't we stop around there...
...still singing.
Romance, into your two hearts
And thus, this was
the first day of summer break...
What should we do tomorrow for fun?
Don't tell me you guys plan
to keep staying here...
...and the various people
enjoying it in their own way.
Strait is the Gate
Oh, incidentally...
That should do it for the book report
and English composition.
...we have one formidable
character like her, too.
Kids at home, make sure you
plan out your homework well, too.
Next time, we'll be battling
minimum height restrictions.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Isumi's...
SIGN: Butler Report
...Butler Report.
Hello, I am Isumi Saginomiya.
Um, I was unable to make it
into the main episode,
but they have decided that
I could be in this segment, at least.
Um... What should I talk about?
What? Talk about this song?
Oh, dear
Um... This song is...
Hey, Isumi, keep talking that slow
and you're going to run out of time!
Nagi... Oh.
Preview
As I thought, the butler
uniform just won't do.
Huh? What's this?
Am I cross-dressing again?!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
No, I was thinking you can't be dressed
like that for the amusement park.
Amusement park?
I've been reborn into this invincible body!
That debt-ridden butler's
no match for me now!
Hey, you there, robot!
Whose industrial spy are you?!
Miss Makimura! Not you, too?!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"A Big Bother, Even for Peter".
I feel like I've seen that robot
somewhere before...
A Big Bother, Even for Peter
The power of justice
will call forth a storm!