[IONA gasping]
Iona?
--[TAMA gasps]
--[RUKO] Iona!
May-Mayu.
[URITH laughs]
It looks like Mommy's angry.
Iona!
[RUKO]
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
[IONA]
I'll be fine.
Don't worry, Mayu can't kill me.
I am her friend, after all.
Her child, too.
And also...
...Mayu herself.
[gasps]
"Mayu...
...herself?"
Me.
Urith loves me.
[IONA]
The girl in the white room.
She was raised alone since
the day that she was born.
The outside world,
a mystery to her.
[MAYU panting]
[IONA]
Mayu was always alone,
never knowing what
that even meant.
[IONA] Every so often,
something or someone would come,
affecting her in some way.
That was all that
she understood.
She didn't know who she was or
what was happening around her.
[IONA] That room, and that
emptiness, was her entire world.
[IONA] Eventually, she noticed
things being placed around her.
[IONA] Occasionally
receiving an unknown visitor,
who would bring
these items to her.
[IONA]
She had no idea why.
Maybe it was out of pity.
Or maybe it was just
a passing whimsy.
[gasps]
[MAYU]
What... is... this?
[IONA]
Thus, she found out...
that beyond her window,
there was a world outside
that she'd never
been aware of before.
[IONA] A world full of
girls who looked like her.
But unlike her,
they were not alone.
A... lot... of... friends.
[MAYU]
Their wish... came true.
Their wish...
[IONA]
Then one day...
She understood
she had been given some
sort of new plaything...
but one that couldn't
be played all alone.
[TAMA gasps]
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA]
She needed friends.
And thus, she created them.
"She created them"?
Yes, though not in the
literal sense just yet.
They were imaginary friends.
They existed only in her mind.
[MAYU] You're the good girl.
Shiro, the Girl of White.
You're the bad girl.
Kuro, the Girl of Black.
We'll be friends
from now on, okay?
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Yup, nice to meet you.
[KURO (MAYU)]
Sure, I'll be your friend, too.
[laughs]
[SHIRO (MAYU)] Okay, next,
Shiro's gonna summon Tlet.
[MAYU]
That won't work, Shiro.
[KURO (MAYU)]
I'll stop that with Vimana.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Oh. You will?
[MAYU laughs]
Okay, it's Kuro's turn.
[KURO (MAYU)]
Here I go. Attack!
[SHIRO (MAYU) yelps]
Oh, she got me!
[MAYU laughs]
Now, it's your turn, Shiro.
Do your best.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
'Kay! Here goes!
[IONA] Eventually, the girl
started a new type of game.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
The outside world?
Yes.
You two will bring girls
from the outside world here.
And you'll tell them this:
That if they win the game,
then their fondest
wish will come true.
[KURO (MAYU)]
All right, but how?
You're going to play
WIXOSS with them.
And whoever wins will take on
the wish of the
girl they brought.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
The girl with the wish,
what's going to happen to her?
[MAYU] She'll be sealed
away in the world of cards.
And for her to escape from it,
she'll have to bring
another girl here.
[KURO (MAYU)]
What about the girl who loses?
[MAYU]
Her wish won't come true.
No, wait...
Not only that, but...
Her wish will be corrupted.
[RUKO gasps]
That's just like--
Just like a Selector battle.
[laughs]
[SHIRO (MAYU)] Hold on.
Isn't that kind of mean?
[MAYU]
Why?
A girl can choose whether
she wants to play or not.
No one's forcing her to do
this if she doesn't want to.
[KURO (MAYU)]
That sounds like fun.
[MAYU]
Doesn't it?
Great! Let's do this!
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Okay, if you say so.
[IONA]
And so, it began.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Now, it's Shiro's turn.
Watch out, Kuro.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Rococo Boundary!
[MAYU]
Whoa! Good, Shiro!
[GIRL A (MAYU)]
Keep making moves like that and
you're going to win this game!
[GIRL A (MAYU)]
Remember, Shiro,
my wish is to become a florist!
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Right! Shiro will do her best!
[MAYU]
And now it's your turn, Kuro.
[KURO (MAYU)] I'm not going
to lose to you, Shiro.
Oh, I hope you win, Kuro,
because I wanna be a
princess more than anything!
Dark Matter!
[gasps]
[MAYU]
Okay! Kuro wins!
[GIRL B (MAYU)]
Thank you so much!
Sorry, but our best
wasn't good enough!
[GIRL A (MAYU) crying]
You mean we lost?
Yes, and now that you have,
your wish will be corrupted.
What that means is you
can never become a florist.
[GIRL A (MAYU) sobs]
That's not all, either.
You'll also never
be able to smell or
even see flowers in
your life ever again.
In fact, you'll live in a world
where flowers don't exist.
[GIRL A (MAYU) cries]
[laughs] So, now I can
become a princess, right?
[MAYU]
Wrong.
[GIRL B (MAYU) screams]
[MAYU] Kuro will fulfill
your wish instead.
If you want to escape your card,
you'll have to bring a
girl here to replace you.
[IONA]
From this,
she bore even more girls...
...into this imaginary
world that she created.
[GIRLS murmuring]
[IONA]
And within it.
The laughter of those girls,
their cries, their screams...
...resonated over
and over again.
[IONA]
But...
...the more that her imaginary
world gained complexity,
the more the girl realized
where she actually was.
[IONA] A world where there
were no colors, voices,
or anyone real, for that matter.
[MAYU]
Hey, Shiro? Kuro?
Isn't it strange?
I get to play with
so many friends.
But I'm the only one
who's ever actually here.
Also, the wishes
they all have...
I can't even see what
any of them are like.
[SHIRO (MAYU)]
Say, Mayu?
You must have a wish, right?
[KURO (MAYU)] Shiro and I will
be happy to make it come true.
[MAYU]
Thank you.
You're both such
good friends to me.
[MAYU]
Very well...
My wish...
Then, you and Tama...
[IONA]
Mhm, that's right.
It's not just Mayu's story,
but ours as well.
[HITOE gasps]
So then, since I met
Mayu in that room..
Yes.
It means that she's still out
there, influencing the game.
She's still alone,
in the same room,
wishing the same
wish for all time.
That's why I'm here.
Huh?
What is this?
[gasps]
[IONA] It was then,
that I truly awakened.
So this is the real world.
My name's Kuro.
And I'll fulfill
your fondest wish.
[IONA]
As for Mayu's fondest wish,
from that lonely room,
she yearns for it.
Strongly.
Sharply.
Earnestly.
Okay, but what is her wish?
--[IONA] Revenge.
--[gasps]
[IONA] Against those who
live in the outside world,
those who are allowed
to have wishes,
and all the girls who
are allowed to select.
She wants one thing
and one thing only.
[IONA]
Revenge.
That's what this is about?
[gasps]
[IONA] As for all the
other girls that Mayu bore,
they became LRIGs.
And I continued my
battles against them.
What about the ones who lost?
[IONA]
They disappeared,
and their Selectors
replaced them as LRIGs.
The LRIGS Mayu bore that
remain alive are me and Tama.
[IONA] Winning led me to
become a human like you.
And then, an LRIG came to me
and from there,
you know what happens.
[gasps]
[IONA] I continued to battle
so I could become an LRIG again,
then a Selector, then an LRIG
again, and so on, and so on...
But why?
[IONA]
My story.
Didn't you listen
to a word of it, Ru?
[IONA]
Kuro?
[MAYU]
Yes.
That's you.
The bad girl, Kuro.
You will battle for
all of eternity,
and you will bring
misery to everyone.
That is your fate,
as the Girl of Black.
[IONA] After numerous times
as both an LRIG and a Selector,
I became the girl
you met, Iona Urazoe.
[IONA]
Then Urith came to me,
in the same form I had
when I was called Kuro.
[AKIRA]
Urith.
[URITH (I)]
Heh.
Why the change in form?
That's cruel.
We're just her playthings.
t's like dressing
dolls in new clothes.
[giggles] Guess it was just
one big game after all!
But you're all
friends, aren't you?
Mayu made you and
Tama to be friends.
Shouldn't that count
for something?
Yes, it should.
But it makes no
difference to her now.
[AKIRA]
I don't care.
Even if she came to Iona, Urith
cares for me. She told me so!
She told me, do you hear?!
Lost it.
I was created by
Mayu to do battle.
But as I continued
to fight more of them,
a new feeling came over me.
Like what?
[IONA] For the first time,
I felt something.
I could actually sense my
own body and soul for once.
It was almost as if
I was finally real.
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA] Since then,
I sought to become stronger
by seeking out only the
most powerful of Selectors.
And then I met you...
Ru...
You were the strongest.
But your LRIG was
Shiro, and not me.
Eventually I lost to you and
my wish came true, but then...
You refused to battle.
It made me so angry.
You were supposed to be like me!
But you preferred
your insipid friends!
I didn't understand
how this could happen.
But then we battled.
Your strength flowed
into me, Ruko.
It felt nice and warm.
Life-altering.
You felt it, too, Tama.
I understand why it changed you.
The strength you and Ru shared.
It comes from a bond,
feeling for others.
You experienced that
and felt it yourself,
and that's why you
were able to change.
That's the reason
why you refused
to fight the battles
you used to love.
Now you have something more
important than battling!
Uh-huh. I don't need
to battle anymore.
'Cause I like Ru
more than battles!
[gasps] Tama...
I like Yuzuki, too.
Hitoe, of course,
and also, Grandma.
I like everybody!
Tama!
[TAMA]
I want Mayu to become friends
with everyone just like I did.
If she does, maybe
she'll stop doing this!
No one will have
to battle anymore!
Tama...
Your memory finally came back!
[gasps]
That's right.
Mayu, she was lonely
being all by herself.
I'd forgotten about her,
but now I can remember.
Tama.
Ruko said you thought
you might be able to
turn the LRIGs back
to normal, right?
[gasps] Uh-huh, but I'm
not exactly sure how to.
[IONA] Well, think about
what changed the two of us.
Huh?
Wait, you mean battling with us?
I think that's the key,
us spending time with
Ru and her friends.
So then--
If Mayu becomes
friends with them,
she might change her mind, too!
That's right.
So, let's get her out of
that room and fix this.
So if we can do that,
we can put an end to
all the Selector battles,
and save all of those poor girls
who turned into LRIGs, right?
Iona.
Tama.
You can hear us,
can't you, Mayu?
Playtime is over now.
What's more, we're going
to get you out of that room!
[MAYU whimpering]
G-Get me out?
[whimpering] I can't
leave. It's scary!
No! I can't!
If we're gonna save
her and everyone else,
We stop Urith!
Yeah, that's right!
And if we defeat her,
we'll also be able to save Tama!
Once Tama's set free,
she and Iona can finally
be together again, too!
[laughing] You losers done
with this sentimental crap yet?
It's supposed to be my
turn again now, you know?
[chuckles] But I will admit,
I enjoy seeing all of you
overflowing with such hope.
Please love me.
[URITH (I)] Because that'll
make it all the sweeter
when I wreck every
last one of you!
And sorry, but Tama
is my weapon now.
She's going to crush the dreams
of all the miserable
Selectors out there!
No! I won't!
[URITH (I)]
Yes, you will,
until your own heart is broken
into tiny little pieces!
You're sick.
We're not gonna let you do that!
Iona's at Level 5, there's
no way Tama can beat her now!
Well then, why don't I try this?
[screams]
Tama!
Oh no, don't!
--[TAMA whimpering]
--[URITH (I)] I'll just overtake
that illuminated
little body of yours
and stain it with darkness!
[TAMA screams]
Leave her alone!
Music to my ears!
Impossible!
Urith's possessing Tama?
This is so beautiful.
[AKIRA]
What? No!
Why Tama?!
Get away from her now!
Urith, I thought you said
you wanted to be with me!
Please help me, Ru!
Iona, what's happening?
I feel like something's
trying to take me over!
No, don't! Stop!
Please, help me, Ru!
Tama!
[TAMA gasping]
Tama.
Now, grow. [chuckles]
[MILULUN]
Not again!
[gasps]
[RUKO gasping]
[RUKO]
No.
It can't be!
[URITH (I)]
Fafnir!
[TAMA yells]
[IONA groans]
Iona!
Now, End Slash!
[IONA grunts]
[IONA groans]
[TAMA yelling]
Tama, no...
Hardcore!
Tama!
We're friends, remember?
[IONA groans]
[IONA grunts]
[RUKO]
No!
[gasps]
Ruko!
[gasps] Iona!
Huh?
[TAMA gasps]
Oh no...
I did this?
It's not your fault!
Listen!
Ru...
Iona...
Iona!
[gasps]
[THUNDER claps]
Too bad for her, huh?
[RUKO gasps]
Iona!
[whimpering]
[URITH (I) chuckles]
That was fun.
See you around,
you hopeless scum!
[RUKO]
No, wait!
Tama!
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe, hang on!
[HITOE]
Yuzuki! Ruko!
[wings flapping]
[URITH (I)]
That felt fantastic.
[AKIRA]
Urith?
Yes, Akira?
Am I... disgusting?
What?
You're beautiful.
As I've said,
you're more precious
than any treasure in the world.
We'll be together forever, and
we're going to have so much fun.
Doesn't that sound nice?
There's a lot more
girls in this city,
which means more wishes
for us to destroy.
[AKIRA]
Urith...
It's over.
[thud]
A... ki... ra...
[CHIYORI]
Uh-oh!
My Selector Sense
detects a villain!
Such incredible evil...
[HITOE]
Does that make us the evil ones?
[CHIYORI] Your time of
punishment's coming!
Justice will prevail!
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Abrupt Separation."