Okinawa's beach was so beautiful!
They call it the beautiful sea!
I hope we can take our time on our next trip.
I saw not one viper battle a mongoose...
At least we bought a lot of souvenirs!
That reminds me, where's Ines?
Hey, wait up!
Hey!
Ines!
Are you okay, Ines?
Are you all right?
Here. Do be careful, please.
So they've got flight attendant Shinkis now.
And she's an Arnval model, just like Ann.
How cool!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Shinkis first gained popularity through Armored Battle games,
Attention Please! This Plane Is
Experiencing a Descent into Hell.
but today, Career Shinkis can be seen supporting humans in many different jobs.
Be it a Nurse Shinki working at a hospital,
or a Guide Shinki showing tourists the sights...
Career Shinkis, huh?
Hey, what would you all want to do if you had careers?
I'd like to make and sell cute dresses
and open up my very own store!
A specialty store for Shinki clothes?
Sounds nice!
And Hina...
I don't need to ask.
She'd wanna be a mercenary or an SDF soldier.
I also have great interest in Shinki pro wrestling.
Huh?
Any career would be fine with me,
but I'd want to be a hard-working Shinki that everyone trusts!
And then I'd return home as a frail, delicate Shinki,
and Master would treat me like his little princess!
Ann, come back from Dreamland.
Girls, it's almost time for our flight.
Okay, Master!
Back to the bag again?
We'll only be apart until we reach Tokyo.
We didn't get left behind again, right?
It sounds like we're on the airplane.
But but, what if we're on the wrong plane?
I don't think you need to worry so much.
Hey, how about we check outside a bit?
Exiting one's luggage is forbidden while in the cargo hold.
C'mon, I'm just gonna take a peek.
Yup, that settles it.
We're definitely on a plane.
The destination is correct as well.
Is someone else here?
Kurara?
What're you all doing here?
Right back at ya.
I'm returning from a wonderful 5-day-4-night Okinawan vacation with my Master.
Remember? It was the grand prize I won by wrecking you all in that race.
Oh yeah, I guess that happened.
Ta-dah!
A star sand accessory!
It's so cute!
Master bought it for me.
Hey, what's your master like?
That's right, we've never seen your master.
Master's really nice, and totally cool.
But our master can't be beaten!
Lemme see a picture.
Huh?
I don't really mind...
These are all photos that Master took.
Um...
Ah, here!
So this is Kurara's master?
Not bad.
But our master really is more wonderful.
How about backing that up with a picture?
Our only pictures of Master are on a card in our bag.
Trying to run away, huh?
'Cuz your master can't hold a candle to mine.
It's not like that at all!
I'll just get it myself!
What's wrong?
Someone is coming.
Some more random Shinkis?
Flight Attendant Shinkis?
They're gonna yell at us if they find out we left our bags!
Wh-What are they doing?
It looks pretty suspicious.
We're looking at something we shouldn't be looking at!
Sto—
Wait!
That's a relief...
What are you doing?
What do you think?
We're changing the course of this plane.
What do you mean?
See for yourselves.
In 30 minutes,
this plane will go
straight to hell.
A time bomb!
A crime using Shinkis...
You disguised yourselves as flight attendants to plant a bomb on this plane!
You'll blow yourselves to smithereens if the plane blows up, so why?
It doesn't matter what happens to us.
This is all for Master.
Stop right there!
Here it is!
Sorry for the wait!
Hm?
Where'd everyone go?
Is this...
Where's she hiding?
We are currently entering turbulent airspace.
Please fasten your seatbelts...
Kurara!
Kurara, hang in there!
I'll be fine.
But these guys are terrorists.
The same model as me?
Hurry, that time bomb is...
Bomb?
That's what I saw earlier...
You've gotta stop it soon,
or we'll all get blown away...
Another Arnval?
She's a terrorist too.
Act like her comrade and ask her how to stop that bomb.
Who, me?
What happened?
I, uh...
Don't worry.
You can do it.
Come on!
A-All clear.
No problems here.
You took her out?
Oh, yeah. It was nothing.
She was like a joke character.
Anyway...
What?
Anyway, the situation's taken an unexpected turn.
We need to shut down the time bomb.
The leader has the shutdown key, not me.
So what's this unexpected turn?
W-Well...
I-It's not something I can really talk about right now...
but it's like this one movie I happened to catch on TV,
and it was so good that I couldn't touch that dial until they caught the criminal...
like that!
I can't understand a word you're saying.
No, I'm saying, uh...
Who are you, imposter?
Shoot!
Ann, what's going on?
Are you all right?
Halt!
Wait for me!
Focus on stopping the bomb!
Master's in danger right now!
I can't find the shutdown key anywhere!
Then that means this Shinki isn't the leader?
There are three of them in total.
The last one left is the leader.
Or rather...
is the Ann in front of us the real Ann?
O-Of course I am!
I'll search for the leader!
Ines, Lene, you focus on finding another way to stop that bomb!
It's our only choice.
Otherwise, we and Master will...
Master!
Another way to stop this bomb, huh?
We can take it apart and dismantle the detonator.
Do I look like a bomb squad to you?
It seems I'm the only one left.
You must be the leader.
Give me the shutdown key.
You'll have to go through me to get it!
If this were an old school bomb,
it'd probably stop if you cut a red or blue wire.
They're really there!
That reminds me, I saw the Shinki Teller on TV this morning,
and it said that today, Altlene's lucky color was red!
Sure...
No, just wait a sec!
We can't use that as a reason!
Why's that?
Because Altines's lucky color was blue...
Ann...
Which is the real one?
How do I tell them apart?
You can compare their serial numbers.
Um,
Arnval models have their serial numbers on their necks, it seems...
Geez, how am I supposed to tell?!
Ann!
Um...
Which one is the real Ann?
I am Ann!
I'm Ann!
Sh-She's wrong! I'm the real one!
No, I'm the real one!
Who do we pick?
I know!
We can ask a question that only the real Ann would know!
Well, let me think...
What's your favorite Jellycan flavor?
Well, um...
I don't really have a favorite,
but if I had to say, then peach?
It's orange!
Who's right?
I dunno.
There's no point if we don't know the answer either!
Don't worry.
The real one will definitely win.
That's because the real one has a duty...
to protect her master...
no matter what!
So, who won?
I can't tell.
What is my name?
Hina!
It's her!
Hurry, get the shutdown key!
I've got it!
Following your master's orders no matter what...
is something all Shinkis do!
Ines!
I got it!
Wrong one!
This is a photo of Master!
It seems that I've won.
This can't be!
Seriously, I thought I was dead!
If you're training, say so from the start!
Please accept our deepest apologies.
We never meant to involve civilian Shinkis in this.
The terrorist Shinkis were supposed to board a practice plane,
but ended up on a Tokyo-bound plane instead.
But thank goodness that it wasn't a real bomb.
But really, a timer Visualizer?
Do you need to go that far for training?
It was quite a realistic explosion!
Ah, there you are.
Hurry, the shuttle bus will leave any second.
You too, Ann.
Master,
there were a lot of Arnvals back there,
so how did you know which one I was?
Hm? Uh...
Well, good question.
But that's what makes someone a master, right?
Right!
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Thank goodness we didn't descend into hell.
That episode title was a total false alarm!
Speaking of hell, have you all heard of RSHSPH?
The Restless Sheep's Heavy Sleep Pointer Hotline?
A Ridiculously Strong Hiker Standing Precariously High.
You're all wrong!
Real Shinki Horror Stories that Probably Happened!
I don't like this...
It was a dark and stormy night...
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
I've said nothing yet.
Next time
"The Visitor that Comes with the Rain..."
Next time on Busou Shinki,
Wh-Who's the visitor?