Romero...
I wonder if you would have looked as peaceful as he does...
...had you been raised in a different country.
You were still here, Lizzie?
Aren't you going to Mexico tomorrow?
I figured I'd nail you down before I leave,
to make sure you behave yourself while I'm gone.
Who is that?
He's quite handsome, isn't he?
I can't really tell Asians apart.
All I know is that they all look so carefree.
Does he look like someone who could kill?
You're joking, right?
He probably couldn't even harm a fly.
Yeah.
You'd think so, right?
Good. You're getting the hang of it.
A knife is both a shield and a weapon.
And that's why...
A close combat fight between two knife wielders will be decided by whoever can parry the other's knife.
You were going easy on me?
What good will binding do when your opponent's still armed with a knife?
An FBI Agent was found dead this afternoon in Tijuana, Mexico.
Learn the words using your eyes and your ears.
Mexican authorities have officially declared this case a homicide,
and have commenced investigations in the area.
American authorities have identified the terrorist group Noche de Sangre as potential perpetrators,
Nothing...
based on the group's recent expansion activities in South America.
She's going to kill again.
How is Zwei coming along?
His technical skills have almost reached full potential.
Just in time.
Come here, Ein.
Yes, Master.
No one can see through you.
Encompassed beneath your soft, white skin.
The dangerous weapon that lies within.
Ready your gun.
Ein, you are perfect.
I created you and I raised you.
You are a perfect specimen.
I want to preserve this perfection to the end of time.
Model Zwei into perfection...
...with your hands.
Make him as perfect as you are.
Yes, Master.
This is your final step before reaching absolute perfection.
Bequeath your perfection unto the next generation, Ein.
Yes, Master.
I thought you'd be back earlier, Ein.
Come.
We need to get you ready.
How much longer are you going to make me wait?
Don't you realize how important I am to your organization?
I've been diverting the military's arms to you for many years,
regardless of all the danger that it's brought me.
Your achievements are quite commendable, Lieutenant Juarez.
But this was quite an unexpected turn of events.
I couldn't help it.
I got caught up in the killing while I was on leave, you know.
That's quite unfortunate.
It appears that the victim was an FBI investigator.
An acquaintance of yours, perhaps?
I've got nothing to do with them.
They're suspicious of me for some reason.
I see.
If I get interrogated, you guys will also be in hot water.
Therefore, Inferno has an obligation to protect me.
But of course.
Rest assured that you will be looking at a Caribbean sunset in just a few hours.
I sure hope so.
Choose the gun you're most comfortable with.
Are we practicing again?
No, tonight will be... a test.
A test?
Follow me.
I thought we were going to an airport.
What's going on?!
What are you people trying to-
Mr. McGuire,
allow me to introduce Lieutenant Juarez, U.S. Navy.
A member of Inferno?
Looks like she's carrying a high caliber automatic.
She must be a bodyguard.
I'm asking what the hell is going on!
This guy...
You were being too greedy.
Things wouldn't have gotten out of hand if you had stuck to selling weapons only to us.
Instead, you decided to sell arms to terrorists as well, and now you're marked by the FBI.
We at Inferno place the highest priority on keeping a low profile.
You betrayed me-
Scythe.
Inferno has decided to give you a chance to save yourself, Lieutenant Juarez.
Please run away.
We'll give you a ten minute head start.
After that, we will send someone to hunt you down.
If you can get away, you win.
I hope that's satisfactory with you.
Absolutely.
There's an armory inside that building.
Feel free to take whatever you want.
What are you up to?
All we've done is pave the way for you to earn your freedom and your right to live.
Is that not the greatest glory that exists for a soldier such as yourself?
Is this how you repay me for everything I've done for you?!
You guys really call yourselves-
I don't think you should be wasting your time here.
Damn it!
You've heard the situation.
Here's your first mission, Zwei.
Kill that man.
It doesn't matter how. Just get it done.
Wait.
I'm not-
Your training is complete.
You've done well.
You were an excellent student.
We're confident that you'll do well.
None other than Inferno's almighty Phantom is acknowledging your skills.
Have confidence in yourself.
Confidence?
How can I be confident in killing someone?
Go, Zwei.
I can't.
How can I?
I'll let you decide one last time.
Will you accept everything that's happened and survive,
or will you deny everything and die?
Do you really think he'll be all right?
He's up against a Navy SEAL, isn't he?
It shouldn't be a problem.
I've asked you all the way out here
to demonstrate just how capable he truly is, Mr. McGuire.
What kind of weapon is he carrying?
When you're the hunter, think as if you're the prey.
When you're the prey, think as if you're the hunter.
Your opponent will also be trying to think ahead.
So...
What's your opinion of this, Phantom?
Lieutenant Juarez is a professional who has received formal military training,
and his field experience far outweighs that of Zwei.
But Zwei is far superior in terms of reflexes and concentration,
provided that he's able to clear his mind.
Your conclusion?
They're evenly matched.
Their respective potentials will probably determine the outcome of this match.
What are Zwei's odds of winning?
I don't know Lieutenant Juarez's abilities, so it's tough to say.
Wait! Don't shoot!
I'm unarmed!
Just hear me out.
I don't know why they're making a kid like you do this,
but just think about it!
We have no reason to kill each other.
Do you have a family?
I have a brother who's much younger than I am.
All I wanted was for him to live freely.
If you can spot one rat, there are at least thirty more nearby.
A man who's lied once will lie again and again.
I've been flirting with danger all my life,
but I was finally able to pay for him to enter college.
I, at least, want to support him until he graduates.
A craftsman always carries many tools.
The same applies to killing.
Inferno is using both of us.
They're the bad guys, not you.
I thought the winner would have been decided within two shots.
What do we do if that boy loses?
Where there's a will there's a way.
Would you prefer to wait inside the car just in case?
Yes.
Playtime's over.
I've seen plenty like you.
Ones who don't have the balls to pull the trigger.
And now, allow me to teach you...
...precisely how to kill someone.
Does it hurt?
Killing someone...
...isn't something just anyone can do.
Don't think that I'm done with you, yet.
Your lesson is just beginning.
Zwei.
That wasn't bad for your first kill.
Why?
Wasn't this all supposed to be a dream?
I told you.
It's going to be a long one.
This is just the prolongation of the dream.
A dream that will not end until you either lose yourself,
or die.
Do you want it to end?
It's up to you.
Abandon your eyes, your ears, and even your heart.
And simply become Zwei.
See everything through Zwei's eyes.
And hear everything through Zwei's ears.
Once you do, you will know no fear,
and know no sadness.
You will be at peace with yourself.
My name...
...isn't Zwei.
I guess it's not after all.
What do you want me to do?
End it...
...all of it.
You are no longer who you once were.
Stand up, Zwei.
Zwei.
Where did you find a boy like him?
He was recommended to us by a certain group in Japan.
I see.
So you mean to tell me that talent is hidden even in a tamed country like Japan?
Yes.
You passed the test.
You are now a member of Inferno.
You are what I used to be.
You know both my despair and my pain.