Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
Rika-chama
mattchewwu2
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetters
ThaEagle
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
It'll leak...
The "Confirm Maintenance on the Command Transmission Line for Direct Communication with Headquarters
in the Case of a High-Level Emergency Situation" mission.
T-That's one amazing name, isn't it?
It's an extremely important mission.
The sort which, should you fail, it's possible that the entire troop would be punished for it.
Depending on the situation, the first series of alerts would be announced,
and all divisions in the area would be placed on emergency standby.
Yeah, really.  It truly is a hugely important responsibility, isn't it?
W-What kind of mission is it?
That is...
Telephone duty.
Huh?
You know that this phone is a hotline to Headquarters at the capital, right?
Up til now, has it ever rung before?
No, it hasn't.
That's right.  Thankfully it never has.
But if it did—
Right.  When it does ring, it's bothersome,
but if it didn't ring when necessary, that would be even worse, correct?
That's why, every six months, we perform a check to test whether the line is properly connected or not.
And that's called...?
T-The... um...
Sheesh, be sure to remember it properly!
Direct Communication with Headquarters in Emergency... what was it?
No, it's the Direct Communication with Headquarters in a High-Level... huh?
The "Confirm Maintenance on the Command Transmission Line for Direct Communication with Headquarters
in the Case of a High-Level Emergency Situation" mission.
Like so!
Yes!  Yes, yes, yes!
Please allow me to accept that mission!
I've always wanted to try speaking on the telephone!
Is it really that exciting?
The basic arrangement is the same as the Takemikazuchi's intercom.
Just because the distance is a little further...
But that's amazing!
To be able to speak with people so far away... it's wonderful!
Well, it's true that it is a curious feeling, to speak with someone you can't see at all.
Well, but once you get used to it, it's nothing special.
However, the only troublesome thing is that we don't know when they will call today.
Despite that, would you still like to do it?
Of course!
All right.  Then you're to stick to the phone for the entire day.
Ring, ring, ring!
This is the 1121st stronghold of the Helvetian Army.  Private Second Class Sorami Kanata speaking!
And then, when the call is finished, you return the receiver back to the same place it was in before.
All right.
Phy-Phy—!
Oh, it's because you're just too cute!
Phylicia-san!
What are you doing?  Honestly...
How embarrassing.
The steam train's leaving.
"Steam train"?
I have some documents that must be rushed to Headquarters...
And Krause-san isn't coming until next week, right?
So I'm going to the station.
I'll leave telephone duty firmly in your care, okay?
Yes!
If it actually rings, at worst,
it's possible for them to think that we've been attacked instead.  So make sure you don't mess up!
Leave it to me!
Hey.
Y-Yes!
I haven't been sleeping!
A-Absolutely have not been sleeping!
Have you seen Noel?
She wasn't in her room.
U-Um...
In the hangar again, huh?
Well, whatever.
So, Kanata, what do you want to eat for lunch?
I-I-I'll make it!
Don't worry about it.  It's my turn.
But...
Hey, why is it that when it's my turn to make food, both you and Kureha try to keep me from doing anything?
You know, before you two got here, I did it all the time.
Well, that's because...
The taste shouldn't be that bad!
W-Well, that's true, the taste isn't as bad as its loo—
What?!
No!  I-I mean, it has a very clear, distinct taste that's totally wonderful!
Doesn't it?
Then today, I'll put in even more effort than usual!
Hello, is there anyone there?
Yes!
Senpai, Naomi-san is here!
I'm busy.
But I need to stay by the phone or else!
Hey, you guys have a guest!
Damn.  There's no helping it.
Yes!  I'm coming.
I don't want to eat sandwiches with pieces of the cutting board mixed in again, after all.
This is...?
Drink up.
It's apple cider.
Supposedly they're home-brewed from where we get our wholesale apple juice.
Then these are related to the calvados we have here, right?
Huh?
Oh, I see... the secret's out.
What?
As a payment, two bottles would be good, right?
Huh?  Oh, yes, I guess so.
"Payment"?
There's going to be a merchant guild's meeting.
In exchange for accommodating us so often, it's become tradition to give them a little something.
Remember that.
Yes!
What's with that?!
Those girls have always tried their hardest to hide that this whole time.
How'd you find out?
T-That's...
Um...
If there's a chance, I'll tell you some time in the future...
Anyway, Naomi-san, would you like to have lunch with us?
What?
Are you saying that I should go, too?
Look here, it seems that everyone wants to hear...
an explanation from the military about the news in this week's paper.
"News"?
About how the armistice agreement meetings have been hitting some rough patches.
Really?
They're working out details for reparation amounts and delineation lines for territory.
Even though things like these always drag on...
Well, the real intention of the old guys at the guild is probably only to see you.
Somehow, ever since you played one of the fire maidens at the water-pouring festival,
your fanbase has been growing, you know.
How irritating.  Really.
So, as you can see, somehow it seems I have no choice but to show up at this meeting.
Even I'm a bastion maiden now, body and soul!
I will carry out this mission on my own!
Got it.  I'll leave things in your care.
Right!
Kanata, I'll give this to you.
It's mine, so I'm sorry it's so old.
This is... a trumpet...!
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Your trumpet-playing has gotten much better, after all.
It's your reward for working so hard.
And also, if you have that, you should be able to stay awake.
Um... this is a C... D, E, F, G...
A...
Well, I guess summer's just about over...
Ilya?
Ah, I might've drunk a little too much.
Noel-chan?  Are you there?
It's raining!  The laundry's going to get soaked!
The courtyard is within scope of the mission!
Kanata~!
Let's play~!
H-Hello?
Kanata~!
Let's play~!
Help me!
You really saved me there.
It's fine.  I'm simply glad that your laundry is safe.
Yeah, really...
I-I'm sorry!  Asking for help out of the blue like that—
Oh, please don't be bothered.
I apologize as well, for coming over to visit so suddenly.
I must return to Treize tomorrow
and so I've come to bid my farewells.
Y-You're too kin—
Even though there's no need to say goodbye to soldiers.
That's not true, Seiya-san.
I've heard that this child has been disrespectful to the people at this base,
so I also thought to apologize for that, as well...
Where is everyone?
They're out at the moment.
The black-haired one, also?  Rio-san, was it?
Yes.
I see...
If possible, I would have liked—
Is this book... yours?
What is it, what is it?!
A trumpet book.
I received it from Rio-senpai.
I see.  I thought so.
Huh?
Oh, no, no, please excuse me.  I was merely speaking to myself.
Kanata, are you here all by yourself?
Yup.
It's the, uh...
"Confirm Maintenance on the Command Transmission Line for Direct Communication with Headquarters
in the Case of a High-Level Emergency Situation" mission!
Then I presume you're waiting for this to ring?
Right!
But this is my first time using one and I'm sort of nervous...
I'm just wondering if I can say what I need to say properly, and all...
Then would you like to practice?
Huh?
Then Yumina-san has also gone to the guild meeting?
Yes.  She's attending to get donations from the people at the guild.
Here you go, drink up!
Yummy!
Isn't it?
Seiya-kun, you drink up, too!
Fine, I'll drink it, but you won't win me over with this!
What are you making?
Mishio, Seiya, do you two know?
A phone!
Is this really...?
Really, it's a phone!
Seeing how the children enjoy it, I make them from time to time.
All right then, Seiya-san.
Right!
A phone, huh...
Hello?
Hello?!
Wow!  This is amazing, Seiya-kun!  I can hear you loud and clear!
That's not right!  When you answer the phone, you say
"Hello" first.  That's a rule when using the phone.
H-Hello?
Hello.
This is amazing.  Really amazing!  I can really hear his voice!
Will it be all right to practice with that then?
Yes!
Um... this is...
Hello?
H-Hello!
This is the 1121st stronghold of the Helvetian Army.  Private Second Class Sorami Kanata speaking!
Yes, understood.
I-I am honored to receive this phone call!
And, uh... um...
Wait, Ms. Birdie!
Mishio-san!
No, stop, Mishio-chan!
What happened?!
The phone!
Excuse me, are the priest and children—
Yes?
Oh, the gods above!
What on earth...
You were supposed to come here and offer thanks and apologies for all that has happened recently,
and instead you end up playing around and causing trouble!
There will be no dinner tonight!
Yes.
For me, either?
Everything's okay now.  Thanks for helping!
But your clothes are drenched...
I'm fine.  I have a change of...
I have a great idea!
This is... embarrassing!
Not at all!
Oh, how dazzling you look!
Still, thanks, Yumina-san.
I'll make sure to wash and return these clothes to you.
No, I'm giving them to you!
They're too big for the children,
and I can't think of anyone else who would look as good in them as you do, Kanata!
I'm sorry, Kanata.
Will you still play with us?
Of course.
Seiya-kun, you come back again soon too, okay?
I-I...
I-If I'm free, I'll come over and play.
Now then, please excuse us.
May there be countless blessings upon you all.
T-Thank you very much.
All right, time for clean up!
Oh, I forgot, I need to use the bathroom.
It'll leak...
Someone, hurry!
Hurry!!
Geez, those old guys...
What's wrong, Kana—
Senpai, please!  Save... me...!
What's the matter, Kanata?
I... can't...
It'll leak out!
Hurry up and go!
You'll get sick!
Thank you!
Was she holding it in the whole time?
I don't know whether to call that being stupid or being honest to a fault...
What's wrong?
I-I'm... fine!
Kanata!
Not... possible!  I can't move at all!
Her timing really sucks...
Hello, this is the 1121st Platoon of the Helvetian Army.  Sergeant Major Rio Kazumiya speaking.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I heard that we were confirming your line, and so I insisted...
Are you running away—?!
No, I'm not running!
I know.
You just haven't forgiven me yet.
After all this time, what do you want?
I beg of you... I ask you to save this country, to save Helvetia!
Morning, Kanata.
Noel-chan, don't tell me you've been... since this morning?
Yes.  I sleep well on the toilet.
No way!
We're ho—
Oh, my!  How cute you look, Kana-chan!
More like, what are you two doing here in the hallway?
Kanata fell over and can't stand up.
Is she hurt?
Then hurry and stand up!
Ugh, I guess there's no helping it then...
Spoiled darling...
No... stop...
Here we...
No!!
Next time, A Typhoon Passes: Imaginary and Real Images.