I don't think my dad could stand
the fact that he was labeled a thief.
And my mom apparently thought he really did steal.
I almost lost my faith in humanity.
I even thought that maybe I'd feel better if I grew to hate one of my parents.
But years later,
I heard my mom regret not believing him back then.
That was when I realized I should continue to love them both.
I realized that my belief in people was one of my good points.
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
Wh-What the hell?
I saw Airi enter the house earlier!
C-Could she still be inside?
Hey!
Airi!
Can you hear me, Airi?
Hang in there!
I can't carry her!
Hey, Airi!
Damn it!
There's no way I can do this alone!
Boss?
Never depend on a manga artist.
We're going down at once!
Steady now!
Satoru, go out the back.
Don't get Airi mixed up in this anymore.
I'll be taking all the credit.
Will Airi be okay?
But that fire...
Don't tell me he was behind it as well.
Oh, right.
Fujinuma Sachiko (Cell)
This is Fujinuma Satoru. Stay right where you are.
That fire was deliberately lit to kill Airi.
And it was set up to look like I did it.
Airi snuck her phone into my pocket so the police wouldn't see this text.
This means the killer already knew Airi's address or followed her.
He might be right under my nose.
I have to look for him.
It's a race to see whether I get caught first or find him first.
Koiwa, Koiwa.
Please be sure not to leave anything—
Hello?
Who is this?
Introduce yourself already.
This is Fujinuma Satoru.
If you really are Fujinuma Satoru, then it's a pleasure.
I've been waiting for your call.
Yes, by all means.
Not here, though.
Let's meet in public.
Right, I haven't introduced myself yet.
Let's save that for when we meet tomorrow.
Because you might be the one
who murdered Fujinuma Sachiko.
Welcome!
Hey, Satoru. Over here.
Nice to meet you.
The name's Sawada. I used to work for the TV Ishikari city desk.
Thank goodness.
You really are Satoru.
You resemble your mother, you know.
It's him.
I'm sure you came here on full alert, but I didn't tip off the cops.
Nor did I murder your mother.
Don't you suspect me?
Of course not.
Why?
Because she wouldn't raise a son who'd kill her.
I see.
I remembered that I had it in my pocket yesterday.
This has become quite the fiasco.
I have no excuse.
This is partly my fault for screwing up so many times in a row.
It's conceited to blame yourself for somethin' after it happens.
As Sachiko used to put it.
I always liked that phrase.
Shall we talk about the phone call I got from her?
Yes, please.
Sawada, do you remember the serial murder case from 18 years ago?
Of course.
Shiratori Jun is on death row
and still hasn't admitted his guilt.
Satoru was right.
Shiratori didn't do it.
Now I know who the real culprit is.
Let's meet at Koiwa Station tomorrow.
I should've asked for a name.
Let's talk about something that happened in the past:
the Hinazuki Kayo murder.
On the night of March 2nd, 1988,
Kayo was locked in the shed after being beaten by her mother and her mother's boyfriend.
She froze to death.
At first, the police suspected the two adults,
thinking they'd hid the body.
But in reality, Kayo had disappeared from
the shed between 10 and 11 PM on the 2nd.
When her mother noticed she
was gone at 12:30 AM on the 3rd,
she quietly began looking for her and called the Fujinumas.
It was Shiratori Jun who had kidnapped her.
One piece of evidence provided was the rubber boot footprints near the shed.
They matched perfectly with boots found at the Shiratori home.
Hokkaido Police
The official version of events is as follows:
He knocked her out with blunt force, photographed her,
and then took her to a commercial freezer,
where he used an atomizer to speed up her death.
The moment her body temperature dropped to 20 degrees, she was brain dead.
He then waited 30 minutes to erase all possibility of her remaining alive
and took the corpse back to the Hinazuki shed before sunrise.
Mr. Yuuki would never do something like that!
A little before Hinazuki Kayo, Sugita Hiromi, and Nakanishi Aya disappeared,
there was a kidnapping-cum-murder case in the next town over too.
The culprit was caught immediately,
and just like Shiratori, they denied any wrongdoing.
Now,
if we also take your current situation into account,
doesn't a certain realization strike you?
I've been ridiculed for years as a crazy reporter who investigates already solved cases.
But not one of them has actually been solved.
Both Hinazuki Kayo and Sachiko were murdered by someone who frames others for his crimes!
And he's in this city right now.
He's one devious son of a bitch.
By framing others, he delays investigations to
a point where eyewitnesses dwindle in number
and crime scenes are no longer preserved in their exact state.
That way, the trail goes cold.
Talk about overreacting.
So he tried to silence her?
Damn that Fujinuma Satoru.
We can't interrogate her now.
But more importantly, what about her own involvement?
She could be an accomplice.
Maybe he forced her to help him kill his mother, and once he didn't need her anymore, he tried to silence her for good.
How awful.
I can't believe he dragged a young girl into his crimes.
You're wrong.
There's no need for you to apologize, Airi.
Yeah. It was all that stalker's fault, not yours.
You must've been so scared.
That's not it, Aunty.
It's fine! Sorry we didn't realize.
You're wrong.
The police are chasing the culprit.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
But you've got it all wrong.
Murder
suspect
targets
co-worker's
home.
(Chiba)
Murder
suspect
targets
co-worker's
home.
(Chiba)
I can't believe Satoru's being hunted for murder and arson.
But who would be willing to believe us?
That girl got a text from Sachiko's phone?
Yeah.
According to the news, she only suffered light injuries, but she's probably still in the hospital.
Here's her phone.
I see.
He tried to speed up the murder investigation by framing you for arson as well.
I'm sure that's partly why,
but I was already the prime suspect.
I don't think he'd go after her,
Katagiri Airi, for just that reason.
Are you saying she was a target herself?
In order to frame me for my mother's murder,
he needed to know when I'd get home from work.
He killed her a little more than a day after she witnessed his kidnapping attempt.
In that timeframe, he visited the
pizza shop and saw the shift schedule.
And Airi must've seen him then.
He might even be someone I know.
I see. To check the schedule,
he must've had staff area access.
We might just be able to catch him.
I'll head to the hospital.
O-Okay.
There are reports on the murders
from 18 years ago on my computer.
Feel free to take a look.
Shiratori Jun might suspect his own father of being the culprit.
There's a chance that he refused to present alibis or evidence
that would draw suspicion to
his father and dug his own grave.
Sounds like Mr. Yuuki, all right. He loved his dad.
Students from school had witnessed Hinazuki Kayo and Shiratori Jun together multiple times.
Fujinuma Satoru's testimony was ignored,
but these were apparently taken into serious consideration.
A suspect list?
Shiratori Jun
Shiratori Seiichirou
Ishidou Isao
Sakashita Shinji
Yanagida Masayuki
The only names I recognize are Mr. Yuuki and his father.
And there were only five suspects?
The police presumed that Sugita Hiromi was mistaken for a girl and killed.
Consequently, the suspect list was whittled down to the five who didn't know him.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
We're having a folk dance today.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Seriously?
I don't wanna hold hands with some uggo.
I'd much rather have Hiromi!
Y-You've got guts!
It's now clear why Hiromi was killed.
The culprit was perfectly aware of his gender,
but killed him with the specific intent of being eliminated from the suspect pool.
Shiratori Jun later called out to a city third-grader who was by herself,
which led to him getting reported to the police and arrested.
Photos taken at the time of Sugita Hiromi's murder were found in Shiratori Foods' storeroom,
which led to the police concluding
that Shiratori Jun was a pedophile.
They also seized several publications containing pedophilic content from his room.
He never had stuff like that!
Perfect
Day for
Pleasure
Perfect
Day for
All You
Can See
Beautiful
Girl
Photo
Album
High School
Girls' Uniform
Reference
Guide
High School
Girls' Uniform
Reference
Guide
It was all planted by the killer
to divert attention from himself!
Where's the suspect list from before Hiromi's death?
Previous Suspect List
The killer's name must be on it!
Ms. Katagiri, I'm coming in.
Uh, I'm here to visit. But first, is the restroom that way?
That's right.
No vacancies...
And only room 201 is empty.
She's sleeping.
I see.
Shit! I'm gonna wet myself!
Pardon my intrusion, Katagiri Airi.
You're not Fujinuma Satoru, are you?
Th-That's right. I'm his friend, Sawada.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Airi's mother.
Episode 6
Reaper
There's no way Satoru could've done it.
There's no way he could've killed
his mother or tried to burn me alive.
He actually came to save me from the fire!
Your manager was the one who saved you.
Inhaling all that smoke must've messed with your memory.
I don't know what you've heard,
but they think I could be his accomplice!
It hurts me so much that nobody believes me.
But people are even less likely to believe Satoru,
and that hurts me more.
Airi,
I still feel I should've gone after your father.
So off you go.
Don't worry. I believe you.
Damn! I forgot to turn it off!
Public Phone
It was still on! Thank goodness!
Is that you, Airi?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
That aside, can we meet at the usual place now?
No, stay away!
If you do that, they'll susp—
It's all good!
I swear I'll come alone!
Go!
Is it actually gonna fly?
I can't believe I actually came.
I should've just asked her about the killer over the phone.
It'll only make things worse for her if she gets involved any further.
What the heck?
It doesn't fly at all!
That's weird.
Why won't it fly?
You need to do this to give it something called aerodynamic lift.
Will that really make it fly?
Yeah.
Whoa! You're right!
It flew toward the river!
It's flying too far!
What's he doing here at this hour?
Is he unemployed?
He must be.
Did Mr. Yuuki go through this too?
Here I am, Satoru.
Yeah.
I came alone, just as promised!
I'm ashamed of myself for thinking this could be a police trap.
I said that out loud.
You damn well should have, too!
You're a fugitive, you know.
But I'm happy you believed in me.
Sure.
The pizza shop?
This Nishizono man is the most suspicious, I think.
Nishizono?
I've seen him two or three times.
The manager's all respectful around him,
and he wears a badge, so he's probably a city councilor.
He would've been able to check the schedule,
and it wouldn't be out of the question for him to know where we live.
I've even exchanged pleasantries with him.
Previous Suspect List
Shiratori Jun
Shiratori Seiichirou
Ishidou Isao
Sakashita Shinji
Kawata Makoto
Fujinuma Sachiko
Saitou Junya
Nishizono?
I didn't see that name on the list.
An alias?
But surely you can't sit on the city council under an alias.
He probably tried to kill me because I knew his face.
Dammit! It isn't coming together!
The final piece of the puzzle won't fit!
Satoru,
I understand how you feel, but don't push yourself.
I have unfinished business from a long time ago.
Oh, I'm talking about a manga I came up with.
It's a story about a reaper who gets his
timing wrong and ends up killing a child.
He tries desperately to undo his mistake,
but the more he tries, the more misfortune he brings to the people he comes in contact with.
He's trying to do the right thing,
but everything he does hurts other people.
You mean to say he's like you right now?
Wouldn't you agree?
What are you, stupid?
For one, I didn't get hurt.
And that stuff about others was just the reaper jumping to conclusions.
I think that reaper needs to believe in himself more.
Everything that's happening right now is just work in progress.
The ending is a ways off, and nobody can see it yet.
I'm so lucky to have met you, Airi.
I said that out loud!
You're Fujinuma Satoru, correct?
Satoru!
Stay out of this!
Airi!
Fujinuma Satoru,
you're under arrest on charges of murder
and attempted murder resulting from arson.
Suspect apprehended at 1650 hours.
Why?!
Satoru didn't do it!
There's no way he could have!
Satoru!
I knew that my relationship with Airi would cease to exist, either via arrest or Revival.
And that time has come. I'll never see her again.
What I'm supposed to do right now is...
I'm so sorry, Satoru!
I probably led these people here,
even though I promised to come alone!
I have to give Airi what I wanted to.
Repay her for what she did for me.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry...
It's all my fault!
What would a superhero say at a time like this?
Isn't it painful to fight all alone?
You've got it all wrong, Airi.
It's because you believed in me that I can keep fighting.
Thank you, Airi.
I'm glad I believed in you.
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory