[NARRATOR] In search of
the dark secrets of the
Philosopher's Stone,
Ed and Al break into
the supposedly deserted
Fifth Laboratory...
There they encounter
two guards who,
like Al, have had their
souls bonded to suits of armor.
In the course of their fight,
Al's opponent, Sixty-Six,
plants suspicions in his mind.
Al begins to wonder
if he is a counterfeit soul
created by Ed, and
bonded to a suit of armor
to become the older
boy's biddable puppet.
[ROSS] Looks like you
can sit up now, huh?
What happened with
the Fifth Laboratory?
Well, it, um...
Somebody blew up the
building and there's nothing
left of it now but rubble.
Damn it...!
You mean they
wiped out everything?!
[SHOCK OF PAIN]
[BROSH AND ROSS EXPRESS CONCERN]
[ED] That didn't
feel good!
This... isn't fair!
[ED] Do you know how close I
was to finding out the truth?!
This is no time for me to
be lying around in a hospital!
[BROSH AND ROSS]
Fullmetal Alchemist, sir!
Huh?
We do apologize
in advance for this!
Huh?
[SLAP]
[ED REACTS DAZED]
You acted like
a selfish child...!
You only escaped with your
life because you were lucky!
You don't have to
do everything all
on your own, you know...
You can lean on other people.
Like us...
Not all adults are the enemy.
You can trust us.
That's all!
Please forgive our
abusive words and conduct, sir.
It will not happen again.
No... you're right...
I should be apologizing.
My punishment...
for slapping you?
[ED] Nothing.
I had it coming.
[BROSH AND ROSS REACT RELIEVED]
[ED] What's got you
two so scared of me?
State certified alchemists
carry a military rank
equivalent to that of a major.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't get my certification
so people would kiss up to me...
You don't have to talk
to me like I'm a
high-ranking officer.
Really? Oh.
Huh... I guess we were
scared of the brat for nothing.
[ED THINKS]
They adjust quickly.
[ED] Where's Al?
I haven't seen him.
Alphonse got his own
lecture earlier...
But... I was the one
who did the slapping.
[ED LAUGHS FOLLOWED
BY A GRIMACE OF PAIN]
I almost forgot...
I have an even less
pleasant lecture in
store for me today.
[PHONE RINGS]
[WINRY] Hello, Rockbell
Prosthetic Limb Outfitters.
Oh, Ed!
Since when do you
ever bother to call us?
Is something wrong?
Yeah... Here's the deal...
I hate to ask you, but...
do you think you could
make a service call out to
Central for me?
[WINRY]
A service call?
Yeah... my right arm's
messed up again.
[ED] I can move the
fingers, but that's about it...
I can't lift the arm at all.
[WINRY] Yeah, that
sounds about right.
Huh?
[WINRY] Nothing,
just talking to myself...
So, what were you doing
when the arm stopped working?
I was in a really rough fight.
You did it again, moron...?!
How could you treat my
precious automail like that,
alchemy freak?!
Um... are you there...?
Hello? Winry...
[WINRY] Guess
I've got no choice...?
Tell me how to get there.
[ED] You're sure in a
good mood today...
I thought you were gonna...
You know what,
never mind, forget it
Yeah... Yep...
Sorry again. And thanks...
Right... Goodbye.
Aw, was that your girlfriend?
My girlfriend? No way!
[BROSH] It's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
When I was your age,
I had a different
girlfriend every week.
[ED] What're you doing,
sitting there in
the dark by yourself?
[ED] Hey...!
Hey, Al!
[AL]
Brother.
[ED] You know you can
come to the room, right?
[AL] I'll be there
in a little while...
You go on ahead.
[ED]
Okay.
[ROBOT STEPS]
Bye!
[66] Are you sure you're
not a puppet created by
your so-called brother?
(ugh) That left me really sore.
I don't understand how Ed and
Al can ride on these things.
Ed said to look near
the west exit--
there'd be someone familiar
there who I'd
recognize right away.
Hello Major Armstrong!
It's Winry!
Hello, Miss Winry.
Did you have a pleasant trip?
[WINRY] Where are those
stupid Elric brothers?
Well, you see...
The hospital?!
[WINRY]
What happened?
[ED] Well... that
didn't take long!
You're gonna charge me
an express service
fee now, aren't you?
No, I... I won't
charge you for this.
I didn't do a good enough job
on your automail last time...
And now you're
badly injured.
It's not your fault!
You can't blame
yourself for this!
[ED] I broke it because
I was being reckless...!
Your repairs were
flawless as ever.
This was all my fault!
[WINRY THINKS] He has
no idea... He never noticed
that I forgot to
put in that screw.
Besides, if my arm
hadn't broken when it did...
I would've kept fighting,
and then I would've
been hurt even worse!
[ED] So don't
worry about it.
Okay? Okay?
[WINRY THINKS] So it
turned out all right?
[WINRY LAUGHS]
Well then, let's go ahead
and get right down to business,
shall we...?
I'll have to charge
you the usual
rush order fee, of course.
Huh?
You didn't drink your milk.
Why should I...? I hate it.
You're going to be small
and stunted forever if
you keep using
that stupid excuse!
Shut up...!
I don't have to
drink it if I don't wanna!
You sound like a spoiled
little brat, Edward Elric!
[ROSS] Every growing boy
needs his milk.
[BROSH] Yeah! You want the
girls to like ya, don't you?
Was that Al?
I don't get it.
Al's been acting
really weird lately.
[WINRY]
Weird how?
[ED] Just seems like
something's been bothering him.
[66] Are you sure you're
not a puppet created by
your so-called brother?
[66] Just accept it...
You'll feel better.
[MIRROR BREAKS]
[WINRY] Okay...
you're all set!
Well done...!
Ah! It feels good
to have it back...!
Wow, thanks a lot.
Sure, no problem.
Yo, Ed, my boy...!
Is it true you brought a
pretty blonde girl into
your room to service you?
She's my automail mechanic
that's all! Nothing more!
Oh... I see.
You've seduced
your mechanic, have you?
[ED SCREAMS]
That isn't what I said at all!
Were you even
listening to me?!
Maes Hughes.
I'm pleased to
meet you, young lady.
You too.
I'm Winry Rockbell.
Nice to see ya, Hughes...
But don't you have work to do?
No, it's all under control.
[HUGHES] I gave
Sheska some overtime.
[ED] You're a
real jerk, aren't ya?
Oh yeah, and I think
you'll be happy to know...
I just found out you
and Al shouldn't need
to be kept under guard
for too much longer.
[ED]
Great!
What'd you say?
Hold on just a second...
How much trouble
have you gotten yourself
into this time?
[ED] Uh... well...
you see... it's...
Well... it's nothing
that concerns you.
Of course not...
I don't know why
I bother to try.
It's not like you'll
talk to me, anyway.
[WINRY] Fine.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I have to go and see if I can
find some place
to stay tonight.
Come on...
No need for that,
why don't you spend
the night at my place?
Really?
[HUGHES]
Yes, of course...
My wife and daughter will
be delighted to have you!
[WINRY] No, I--
[HUGHES]
It's settled. Come on!
[HUGHES] Come on!
[WINRY] Ah, one second...
[HUGHES] Here, let me take that.
No... I've got it! Let's go!
[WINRY] Do you
really have to drag me?
[HUGHES LAUGHS]
[CRACKING OF PARTY FAVORS]
Happy Birthday, Elicia!
[ATTENDEES APPLAUD]
Um... If you don't mind
me asking, Mr. Hughes...
What is this all about?
I'm so glad you asked
that, Miss Winry...!
Today happens to be my
darling little
Elicia's birthday!
Yeah, my birthday!
[WINRY CHUCKLES]
That's exciting.
How old are you now, Elicia?
I'm two...!
No, I'm three!
[WINRY AND HUGHES]
Oh, how adorable!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[WINRY] I've
known the Elrics for
about as long as
I can remember...
We grew up together.
They're like my brothers.
And I'm sure,
knowing those two,
they must give you
plenty to worry about.
That's an understatement.
[WINRY] When they finally
came back for a visit,
it was because Ed's
arm was all busted up.
And now he calls me
out here because he's
been seriously injured again...
[WINRY] Something's
bothering Al, too.
[WINRY] They keep their
mouths shut, though...
They don't ever tell
me what's going on...
It's just like when
they left Resembool
for the first time.
[HUGHES] Maybe nothing
needed to be said.
You know
these boys, Winry.
It's possible they thought
you'd understand without
them saying anything.
Maybe... But there are
some things that I actually
need to be told.
Just what am I
going to do with you?
[HUGHES] In general,
men prefer to let their
actions speak instead of words.
[HUGHES] When they're in pain,
they don't want to
burden anyone with it...
Not if they can help it.
They don't want anyone
to worry about them.
That's how they are.
[HUGHES] Even so, there
may come a time when they'll
ask for your help.
And when they do...
I know that you'll
be there for them.
[HUGHES]
Isn't that enough?
Elicia, we want
to play...! Let's go!
Will you put me down now?
'Kay, down you go.
Hey, you get away from her...!
Elicia wants to play
with me not you!
[BOY A] Huh? No way,
she's playing with me.
She's quite the heartbreaker
already, isn't she?
She picked me!
- Come on,
Elicia!
- She picked me!
- Come on, Elicia!
- Leave us alone!
Listen up, boys...
You try anything
with my daughter...
and you'll answer to me.
Your actions
speak too loudly!
[GRACIA] Are you
sure you have to go?
You're more than
welcome to stay
with us for as long
as you're in town.
I don't want to put you out
more than I have already.
Elicia's gotten very
attached to you.
[HUGHES LAUGHS]
Well, would you look at that?
The two of you could be sisters.
[ELICIA]
Sissy! Be safe, okay...?
And come back and
visit me real soon!
It's settled. You're staying
with us again tonight.
[ELICIA AND WINRY LAUGH]
It looks like I've
found myself a little sister.
So we meet again,
you little bastard...
I'm not gonna
drink you...
[AL] Brother, you have a living
body that needs nourishment.
You have to drink it.
[ED] I don't have to
if I don't want to...!
It may not look like it,
but I have grown some...
But everyone still
calls me a pipsqueak!
I wish I was like you, Al.
You've got such a big body now.
[AL] It's not like I asked
for this body, brother!
[ED] S-Sorry...
You're right...
It's my fault
that it happened...
But I'll make it right...
I'll get you back into
your real body, you'll see Al--
[AL] That's what
you always say!
But you don't
know that for sure!
Look-Look, I promise
I'm gonna get you back...
Believe me Al, I'll do it!
[AL] Believe you?!
[AL] How am I supposed to
believe anything when
I'm stuck in this body?!
[AL] What should I believe in?
My memories?
[AL] Memories are just
scraps of information
that can be made up
as easily as anything else.
Al, what... what are
you talking about?
[AL] Do you remember when you
said there was something
you were afraid to tell me?
[AL] I think... I think I might
know what it was.
[AL] Maybe you wanted to say
that my soul and my memories
are really artificial
constructions you created!
[AL] You, Winry, and Granny...
You've been lying to
me all along, haven't you?
[AL] What do you have to
say for yourself, Brother?!
[ED POUNDS TABLE]
[ED] Is that what
you really think...?
Have you believed
that all this time?
[AL GASPS]
So are you finished...
or is there more
you wanted to say.
Okay.
Don't go.
Ed!
[WINRY]
Al, you...
Moron!!
[METAL HITTING METAL]
[SHOCKED]
[AL] Where did
that come from?
[WINRY BREATHING HEAVY]
[AL]
Winry...!
[WINRY]
You idiot!
[METAL ON METAL]
You have no idea
how Ed feels!
Do you know what he was
so afraid to talk to you about?
He wants to know if
you blame him for what
happened to your body, Al!
It's all my fault.
Al lost his body,
and it's all my fault.
He can't eat anymore.
He can't sleep.
He can't feel cold or warmth...
He's my little brother
and I'm supposed to protect him,
and I did this.
[ED] How could
he ever forgive me?
Al isn't the type of boy
who would resent you for this...
Just ask him and I'm
sure you'll see.
No... I'm... I'm too afraid
I'm too scared
of what he'll say.
[METAL CLANK]
And then, you idiot...
...you said that!
[WINRY SOBBING]
Who would ever do
something like that...?
Who would be prepared
to risk his own life...
to create a fake brother?
[WINRY]
Don't you get it...?
All the two of you
have left... is each other.
[AL] Now go
get your brother!
Start running!
[AL]
Right!
[BREEZE BLOWING]
[AL] Broth--
- [ED] You know something, Al...
- [AL] Broth--
[ED] We haven't had
a good fight in awhile...
I'm starting to get flabby.
[AL]
Huh?
Huh...? Hey!
[AL]
Hold on, Brother!
Stop!
Your wounds haven't
healed enough for this.
I beat you!
The first time I ever won.
That wasn't a
fair fight, Brother.
Don't give me that.
A win is a win,
and you know it, Al.
We've always fought like this...
ever since we
were really little.
Now that I think about it,
we've fought over some
really stupid
things, haven't we?
[AL] Definitely. Like who would
get the top and bottom bunks.
[ED] Yeah.
[AL] We fought over
candy a lot too, huh?
[ED] And that toy,
you remember?
[AL] I won that one.
[AL] And when we played
in the Rain River, too.
[ED] Oh yeah, you shoved
me into the water.
[AL] And that fight we
had during our training.
[ED] Teacher said
we were being too loud,
then she beat us up herself...
Why don't we
call that one a draw?
[AL] We even
fought over which
one of us would marry
Winry someday.
What...?!
[ED] I don't
remember that one!
[AL] I won the fight...
but she shot me down.
Oh... did she?
You're telling me that
all those memories are lies?
[AL]
Sorry.
[ED] And your determination
to be whole again,
to get your body back,
no matter what...
that's a lie too?
[AL]
No, it's not a lie.
[ED]
That's right!
[ED] We're in this
together, all the way.
[ED] Don't forget that,
and we're gonna
keep pushing forward...
We'll make ourselves stronger,
faster and better
until we get our bodies back.
[AL GIGGLES]
[AL]
And the milk?
[ED]
Milk...?!
Fine, I'll drink a little.
[ED AND AL LAUGH]
[ED] Whatever
it takes, Brother.
[WINRY]
Mr. Hughes.
Maybe you don't have
to hear something out loud,
but it sure is
helpful sometimes.
I guess it is.
[STRONG WINDS]
[SCAR]
My brother...
Master...
They're gone... all gone.
[KIMBLEE]
Hey!
[SCAR] You don't look like
an Ishvalan. Who are you?
[KIMBLEE] Oh my,
where are my manners...?
I should have
introduced myself.
I'm a State Alchemist
sent here by the military...
I've been sent to
exterminate this sector.
Hey...! You're awake!
Where am I?
In a slum
outside of East City.
You're among friends now.
Who are you...?
You, old man.
Me? Why, I'm a man of
Ishvala, just as you are, son...
There's nothing
to worry about here...
I won't sell out
one of my own.
Are we the only ones here...?
Are there other
Ishvalan survivors?
Yes... indeed there are...
A run-down slum such as
this may bear no resemblance
to our ancestral home...
but you know
what they say...
"the world is god's bosom"...
our great, loving god Ishvala...
Am I right?
[OLD MAN LAUGHS]
Yes, you certainly are.
You can't, you're not ready!
We found you
floating in the sewers.
You were hurt bad.
Boy... My right arm.
Did I lose it,
or is it still with me?
Yeah, it's still there, mister.
It should be fine.
Your tattoo...
It's really amazing.
Yes... it's important
to me... a precious gift.
From my family.
[NARRATOR] A good friend
became a comrade in arms...
and over time his presence
was taken for granted.
Although the future
they once dreamed of
became bleaker than they
had ever imagined...
this good friend
was always there by his side,
where he belonged.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Ten.
Separate Destinations.
A friend whose presence
comes as naturally
as breathing can
never be replaced.