"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Well... we're going to start
a long vacation tomorrow,
but don't forget your
position as a student,
and spend your days in moderation.
"Various things to watch out for
during summer vacation"
Okay!
Many students get all worked up
during this season,
and cause a lot of trouble to
their neighborhood societies.
I, as your teacher,
am very worried about that.
Please, make sure you don't
cause any problems!
In other words, if you
cause any problems,
you're going to kill my vacation
as well, so I'm begging you!
This is no good...
"The Famous Shooter"
We're finally on vacation now.
It's reassuring to think
that I don't have
to see your face each and every day.
Sis...
Well, even though it's vacation,
I'm going to see our teacher
almost every day anyway.
Why? You have summer
classes or something?
We form parties in our
'net game and stuff.
There's something about that...
'Net game?
Our teacher is a wiz and I'm a tank,
so when we pair up and I pull stuff,
it's pretty good in terms
of both xp and money.
Though I'm always the busy one,
and all our teacher does is click
on one of the AoE skills.
The other day, I pulled a ton of mobs
only to find our teacher had
fallen asleep at the keyboard,
and it took me all day to earn
my death penalty back...
Um, can you at least
speak in Japanese?
Morning...
It's so hot today for so
early in the morning.
Morning. Your hair is
quite amazing right now.
Hey, Sis, how about we turn on
the air conditioning?
There you go again.
Don't rely on stuff like that so quickly.
Use a fan or something and
bear with it, you know?
Here.
Oh...
It gets pretty cool with just a fan.
Don't you think so?
I'm hot.
I get tired when
I keep fanning myself.
And when you stop using a fan,
don't you feel even hotter?
Yeah, well, I knew that...
But you can try a little harder.
We are wearing yukatas together.
Yup, yup.
Well, our obis are
simple pre-tied ones.
The ones you can put on easily.
It's difficult to put a kimono on,
even if it's just a yukata.
Miyuki's obi is tied up
traditionally, isn't it?
Just like you'd expect.
No, I had the person
at the shop do it for me.
After all, even I find tying
an obi to be difficult.
I see.
Konata is wearing a proper one
as well... much to my surprise.
Did you get help at the store as well?
No, Dad tied it for me.
No kidding.
Now, let's go!
How come her dad
knows how to tie one?
Hey, it's Konata!
Someone from the police?
You know her, Konata?
Miss Yui is a relative of mine.
Nice to meet you!
--Oh, hello there.
--Nice to meet you!
Don't wreak too much havoc!
Listen to what these older girls say,
and go home early, okay?
No, no, we're all in the same grade!
"Older girls"
Don't make Konata the standard!
We're all in the same grade.
What?!
Sorry, sorry, that really surprises me.
After all, your physiques are so
different that I couldn't help it.
Oh, no.
Well, that aside, kids these days
really are well-endowed.
No, like I said, don't make
Konata the standard!
We're all normal!
Hey, it's a shooting gallery!
Aren't you good at stuff like this, Yui?
To tell you the truth, I'm so good
that they call me
Sharpshooter Yui at the station!
I can shoot five rounds in
three seconds and nail pinheads!
I can draw a peace mark
on a paper target's head!
Then try it out! Here!
Oh, oh?
The shooting gallery uses a rifle?
What a surprise!
I use pistols.
Excited! Excited!
Narumi! What's got you so fired up?
You're still on the job!
Now, patrol, patrol...
Getting back on hand...
Mister, the stuff lined up over there...
If we hit a target, we can get
any one of them?
Any of them are okay!
Any of them?
Yeah, any of them.
Whoa, missy, I'm not a prize.
When you talk about
a summer festival,
you can't forget the shaved ice!
It's hot, too. Let's go eat some.
"Melon" "Lemon" "Strawberry"
Come to think of it,
"Blue Hawaii" "Melon" "Lemon"
I can understand strawberry,
lemon, and melon flavors...
But what fruit is Blue Hawaii?
What kinda flavor is it?
The flavor would be
Blue Hawaii, I would think?
That's true...
That's how it would end up...
And so, Miyuki-san, do you know
what Blue Hawaii is?
Blue Hawaii, was it?
Let's see... Let's see...
Maybe it's a song...
Blue... That's not it.
That I do not know.
I'm sorry I can't be of use.
I'll look it up later.
Yeah, please do!
--I'd think that it's named after
a juice or some kind of sweets...
--No, the one who wants to know
should be looking it up, not Miyuki...
Um, about that Blue Hawaii...
The name comes from a cocktail
of the same name and color.
The cocktail was named after
and pays homage to
the movie Blue Hawaii, so they say.
So that's what it was...
It's a good reference.
When Tsukasa teaches me something,
for some reason, I feel like
I've really been defeated!
I just realized that I don't
have much money left.
These booths aren't cheap.
You have to think before
you spend, you know? Geez...
But during festivals, you kinda
go with the atmosphere
and can't help but to get
your hands on all sorts of stuff!
Well, yeah.
It's the same illusion as not thinking
that a doujinshi is expensive
when you're at Comiket.
You don't realize just how much
you've spent until later.
As I've been saying,
I don't understand when
you talk about that genre!
You get all tired lining up
from early in the morning,
and the West Hall is so
far away from East Hall...
I don't understand what
you're talking about!
I love cotton candy!
It's so fluffy and sweet!
You're not a kid!
Calm down when you eat!
It's no fun doing that stuff
with another girl.
Don't say it.
Why don't we have that
thing they call romance?
We're at a summer festival
and wearing yukatas, right?
If this was a dating sim,
you'd think there'd be at least
one flag up right now.
Flag?
That, and an event scene.
In yukatas, and outside...
Okay, okay, that's enough!
Kagami-san, you're not
going to play anything?
Well, it's a nice occasion after all,
so I guess I'll do some
goldfish scooping.
I haven't even tried anything.
Why are they running?
They instinctively feel that
you're vicious, Kagami,
and that's why they're running away.
Finally, the evidence is coming out.
Oh, over there, there's one over there.
You're right. Okay...
Gotcha!
All right! I've caught one!
Amazing! Amazing!
I'll take care of it.
I'll take really good care of it.
Right, Gyopi-chan?
Yo! You're all together!
I heard there was a festival
going on around here,
and thought I might as well come.
I love festivals.
Did you come here together today
with your boyfriend or something?
Of course not. There ain't one.
So there isn't even a fragment
of romance around us after all.
Just as we expected.
We see each other again!
Even more people?
Looks like you're having fun.
Hey there!
This time, you really have
a well-endowed girl.
Girl?
She's our homeroom teacher.
I'm sorry, I jumped to the conclusion
that you were one of
their classmates...
Oh, no.
Yui is a relative of mine.
As you can see, she's a cop.
Well, since today is a summer festival,
I have looking-around duty.
Man, in this heat!
Duty? You're having so much fun!
Are you on duty as well, ma'am?
Like, looking around?
No, I was bored, so I was
just wandering around...
I'm so jealous! If I was off duty,
I could have wandered around
by myself and played a little!
No, you're having enough fun as it is!
So are you alone as well?
Yes, I'm alone.
I see, I see.
"Single"
"Husband's on a commuter marriage"
Lucky Star!
As for vinegar, I would
recommend balsamic vinegar,
--but if you don't have any, whatever you
have at home, such as rice vinegar, will do.
--Balsamic vinegar...
Balsamic vinegar...
Balsamic vinegar!
During summer vacation,
you get kind of bored because
there's nothing to do.
You can't help but get a little lazy.
Since you say that much,
you won't be asking me later to
show you my homework, right?
That's true. Yeah. It is cute after all.
How it's kinda pudgy and roly-poly
and how it looks like a frog.
Yeah, yeah. Uh-huh.
I see, so it's depleted uranium.
That's amazing.
Oh, if I talk on the phone
for too long, I'll get scolded.
Yeah! Talk to you later!
I was talking with Kona-chan,
And asked her how summer vacation
ends up being pretty boring.
She said she wasn't bored because
she was playing
all the games that had piled up.
I guess some people have
a very fulfilling summer vacation.
Maybe I should do something too!
Well, that's a good thing
in itself, but...
I'm telling you, do your homework
on top of all that!
Really, each and every time.
I'm gonna pull one.
"Konakona: I'm gonna pull one."
"Yamanka: OK"
"Gatongo: All right, let's do this! (rotfl)"
Debuff, please.
"Konakona: Debuff plz."
"Your friend Nanakon has logged in."
Oh, our teacher logged in.
"Konakona: Hello."
Hello.
"Nanakon: Yo! (^3^)/"
Maybe it's because it's vacation, but
the connection speed is really good.
"Nanakon: Well, yeah (lol)"
I have some time,
shall we go grind some things?
I'm in the cave near Chovron Village.
"Nanakon: All right, I'll go, I'll go! (>w<)b
It's time for a wiz to step up!"
Then I'll be waiting near the gate.
"Nanakon: That's fine, but did you
do your homework? (-_-)"
Huh?
"Nanakon: Have you been cooped up
inside your house? (-_-)"
"Nanakon: Don't forget about the day
you have to come to school (-3-)y-~~~"
"Nanakon: One more thing, even though it's
vacation, don't stay up too late or sleep in too much."
Ma'am, stop talking about real life
every day inside the 'net game world!
It's like Kagami
scolding me every day...
Heya! It's hot again today!
Oh, welcome! Come on in!
Thank you.
You got the fan out.
Yeah, because it's hot.
Chill out there for a bit.
"Ah..."
I thought she'd do it.
I was positive that she'd do it.
Good morning...
Oh, Kona-chan is here.
S'up.
It's not "good morning."
What time do you think it is?
In any case, it's hot out.
You too?!
No, everyone usually does it.
I don't do it.
But you were doing it
this morning, Kagami.
See?
I was seen...
The Comp-Fest seems
to be pretty popular.
What's that?
When you collect the entry tickets
that come with the graphic novels
of series from this magazine,
and send them in,
you get a limited edition
QUO card in no time!
I see...
I also end up taking those graphic
novels to the cash register,
as if I were drawn to the cashier...
You were going on about
QUO cards the other day.
Really, Japanese people are so weak
when it comes to giveaways
or limited edition items.
That's why it's rudimentary to buy
one to store, one to look at,
and one to spread the gospel!
Wait! There's no doubt
that yours is a special case!
Most people don't think like that.
Sometimes you forget who you lent
it to, and end up buying a new one.
Don't forget!
And so, I'd like to ask you
about that usual thing.
Oh, homework.
Again?
I'll teach you all the bits
that you don't understand,
so why don't you do it
by yourself for a change?
Balsamic vinegar...
Kagami, show me how to do this one.
Oh, this here is...
Kagami, I don't understand
from here to here.
Whoa, close.
--Kagami, this bit...
--You aren't even going
to try thinking, are you?!
I am thinking.
Is that really so?
And I don't understand
anything from here on...
You aren't thinking after all!
In the end, she wouldn't teach me...
Hey! I'm here to visit!
Oh, Yui, good timing!
Show me how to do this part!
Math homework... let's see,
which part? Leave it to me.
Well, as a police officer
looking after a good girl...
It's no good to rely on
other people all the time!
I don't get this stuff, it's such a pain...
Even if you don't get it,
just scribble down something
that sounds right.
I mean, the point of homework
is to just turn something in.
Oh, I see! Good thinking!
But that line of yours earlier
seems so superficial now,
because doing that,
it won't do me good.
Well, I did the same thing myself.
I'm so tired...
I think I'll take a breather and
play the 'net game for a little bit.
I'm sure thirty minutes of
solo grinding should be good.
If it's only thirty minutes.
I'm solo grinding...
In this world...
Getting stronger...
A rare drop...
"You have obtained
Enchanted Blade Laevatein."
Laevatein?!
"Something like this"
I've never seen anyone who had it!
That's ultra-rare!
I got the sword Laeva!
"Yamanka: Serious?!? (@@)"
"Gatongo: Oh man (rotfl) Grats (rotfl)"
"Yamanka: I'll go over there right now,
show me show me! (>w<)/"
"Matchy: Let's celebrate. We can gather all the
clan members together, and try it out. O(^^)o"
"Gatongo: All-nighter guaranteed! (rotfl) I'm (lol)
feeling (lol) totally (lol) Energetic (lol) now (rotfl)"
"Konakona: OK, come-come."
Now, where should I
break this thing in?
Oh, everyone's so into going.
I know, I'll celebrate by stocking up
on the high-quality potions,
and give them out to everyone.
First, I'll go back to town...
"Math II"
This is going to get really busy!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
This is Akira Kogami, your navigator!
Time passes by so quickly, Lucky
Channel is already on its fifth show!
I'm going to do my best, and put
even more enthusiasm into it!
And as usual, my assistant is
getting more lines in the actual
episode, and letting it go to his head...
...no, doing very well...
It's Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Clap, clap, clap!
Well, I have no intention
of letting it go to my head.
Oh, I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant. Hope to do well.
Now, we receive mountains
of letters each week!
Today, I'd like to introduce a letter
sent by Mr. USS Gatoh in Tokyo!
Is he a NE__? This one person
sent fifty letters!
I'm sure he's a poor,
pathetic individual!
Anyway, the letter goes:
Hello to Miss Akira and Mr. Minoru!
In the main show, Konata seems
to be playing a 'net game,
but do you play games like
this as well, Miss Akira?
By the way, I role-play as a nekama,
and have a very
fulfilling everyday life.
Wow, how painful!
'Net game... a network game, right?
Unfortunately, I've never
played those things.
Yeah. But you're better off
not playing them.
You sure cut it down again today...
I-Is that so?
There are so many people
who get totally hooked,
and leave their real lives
behind somewhere else...
There was a period of time
where I was pretty bad.
When I had time,
I would be logged in,
and would go on and on
to grind or to PKK...
That was when I was young.
When you were young?
Or rather, there are all sorts of
terms that you just mentioned
which I don't understand...
You're better off not knowing them.
Whatever, it's not like the whole
audience will understand, anyway.
In any case, you had been
playing in the past.
Then, Akira-sama, do you have any
memories about games of the sort?
Oh, yes, memories! I have some!
When I was a beginner,
I didn't understand many things,
and was in trouble when all sorts
of nice veterans helped me out!
They gave me lots of really
expensive armor and rare items,
and I was so thrilled!
I-I see.
It's very fun, so everyone
should try playing them!
Oh, it's already time to go!
Bye-nee!
Then, we'll see you next episode.
Or rather, when you're in games
like that, you're extremely popular.
Oh? Akira-sama?
Is something the matter?
Page 38, cut 12...
Yes?
Who the hell is Yutaka, dammit?!
--Is this where you get mad today?!
--I'm telling you, I'm Akira!
--Yes, that is true, but...
--Whoever is in charge, come out here!
--Wait, director! Director!
--No, the producer is better! The producer!
--You know damn well!
Wait, please, Akira-sama, please calm down!
--Please, I beg you!
--While we're at it...
--Yes?
Let's take the name Minoru Shiraishi
and turn it into
something else... Like Su--
Kagamin, you're so cool!
You're just saying that!
Well, Tsukasa or Miyuki,
which of you will go next?
Me!
Again?! When the hell did you...
You guys weren't putting any in.
It's a waste!
I'm sorry. I'm still picking a song,
so wait just a bit more for me.
I'm sorry...
Oh, it's okay.
Konata's song can fill up
the spare time anyway.
Oh, I know this one!
Amazingly enough, this selection is
from a mainstream series for you!
♪ The best! ♪
♪ Sparking! ♪
♪ Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away ♪
♪ As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being ♪
♪ The Earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry ♪
♪ And makes one of its
volcanoes explode ♪
♪ lf, within the thawed polar ice ♪
♪ There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball ♪
♪ Cha-la head cha-la ♪
♪ No matter what may happen, I feel
as though nothing can bother me ♪
♪ Cha-la head cha-la ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next episode
of Lucky Star?
Konata here.
Right when I was starting to play
Monster Hunter Dos,
defeating five Geanos was
the condition to use a weapon,
so I went to the village and had the
gathering hall offer me the quest,
but when I defeated the five Geanos,
or even when I plucked so much
Snow Mountain Grass,
even when I gathered
so much Poponotan,
I couldn't go back to the village,
and that was when I first realized
that I had to put it into
the storage box by myself,
and the fact is that I was
getting less in rewards
all because I didn't read
the user's manual,
so don't you think that the reason
why you're not making money
is based on what you do in real life?
Next episode: Fixtures of Summer.
"Fixtures of Summer."
Look forward to it!