- SO WHAT'S THE DEAL, AKI?
HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE GOING ON THIS TRIP?
- Fukuhara:
WHAT YOU ARE WITNESSING
CAN ONLY BE DESCRIBED
AS AKIHISA YOSHI CORNERED.
- OH, YOU WANT A NUMBER?
I GUESS MAYBE NINE,
INCLUDING YOU.
- THAT'S FINE.
IF WE RENT A VAN,
IT SHOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM.
SO YOU INVITED SEVEN
OTHER PEOPLE?
WHO ELSE IS COMING?
- WELL, LET ME SEE.
I INVITED A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
THAT I KNOW YOU LOVE.
YUUJI FOR EXAMPLE.
AND HIDEYOSHI OF COURSE.
KOUTA SAID
HE WANTED TO GO.
- GREAT, WHO ELSE?
- RIGHT,
THAT'S ONLY THREE.
UM...
THIS WOULD BE SO MUCH EASIER
IF SHE WASN'T
SO WEIRD ABOUT ME
BEING FRIENDS
WITH GIRLS.
I CAN PROBABLY GET AWAY
WITH TELLING HER
ABOUT SHOUKO
IF I PASS HER OFF
AS YUUJI'S FIANCE.
BUT THEN THERE'S HIMEJI.
AND WHAT ABOUT MINAMI?
( gasps )
AND AIKO!  I CAN'T
TELL HER ABOUT THEM.
SHE'LL CUT MY FACE OFF.
- WELL, WHO ELSE IS COMING?
- UM, OH, SURE, RIGHT.
LET'S SEE.
- GO AHEAD.
YOU LEFT OFF AT HIDEYOSHI.
- IT'S A SECRET.
SEE? SHH.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU ALREADY TOLD ME
THREE OF THEM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS JUST JOKING.
- IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO TELL THE TRUTH.
DO AND I'LL GIVE YOU
A REWARD RIGHT ON YOUR LIPS.
- THE REST OF THEM
ARE ALIENS FROM OUTER SPACE.
- VERY GOOD.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
- NO! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
I JUST LIED TO YOU.
I'M NOT WORTHY.
- DON'T BE MODEST.
ALL PEOPLE ARE
FROM OUTER SPACE
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
- DID I SAY OUTER SPACE?
I MEAN, HORSES!
I'M INVITING
A BUNCH OF ANIMALS!
- ( sobs )
SUCH CRUEL REJECTION.
I'M YOUR SISTER.
DON'T YOU LOVE ME?
( cries )
- I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST THAT
THE WHOLE BROTHER-SISTER
KISSING THING IS A LITTLE--
- KINKY AND SEXY, RIGHT?
- PERVERT ALERT!
THERE IS A PERVERT
STANDING RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME!
- YOU'LL FALL FOR ANYTHING,
WON'T YOU?
I WAS LIKE 30% JOKING.
- 30% MEANS SHE WAS
ALMOST ALL PERCENT SERIOUS.
- YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
I DON'T KNOW BY NOW
WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE
WHEN YOU'RE LYING TO ME?
WHY WON'T YOU JUST
TELL ME THE TRUTH?
I'M YOUR SISTER.
- I'LL TELL YOU
IF YOU WON'T GET MAD.
- I WON'T.
I PROMISE
I'M TOTALLY COOL
WITH THE WHOLE THING
AS LONG AS
THEY'RE NOT GIRLS.
IN WHICH CASE,
I MIGHT HAVE TO CUT YOU.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
YOU GOT A DATE?
- I'M SORRY.
PLEASE DON'T YELL AT ME
OR GROW FANGS
OR GET THOSE WEIRD SWIRLY
THINGS AROUND YOUR HEAD.
- I THINK I'LL BE SICK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU INVITED OTHER WOMEN.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST, UM...
( sighs )
I HAD A LOT OF HOMEWORK
AND THEY'RE THE ONES
THAT USUALLY TUTOR ME.
BESIDES, WHAT WAS
I SUPPOSED TO DO?
WE ALWAYS HANG OUT
AS A GROUP TOGETHER.
I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS GONNA BE
AN OVERNIGHT THING.
- AND I'M JUST SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE
ALL THAT TWADDLE, AM I?
I SUPPOSE I DO.
- REALLY?
THAT'S AWESOME!
- YES, I KNOW.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HOWEVER, IF I CATCH
YOU HOLDING HANDS,
MAKING OUT, OR PLAYING
"HIDE THE SAUSAGE..."
- ( gulps )
- I WON'T HESITATE TO
KILL YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY.
- UH, THAT KINDA
INCLUDES YOU, AKIRA.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: THE DAY OF THE
TRIP HAS FINALLY ARRIVED.
YIPPEE.
- THIS IS PERFECT
BEACH WEATHER.
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
- YUP, I'M ALL ABOUT
THE BIKINIS THAT GO WITH IT.
- I COULDN'T SLEEP,
I WAS SO EXCITED.
I DREAMT THAT
I WAS A MERMAID.
- YOU ARE SUCH A FIVE-YEAR-OLD
SOMETIMES. IT'S ADORABLE.
- I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU TO SEE
THE NEW SWIMSUIT
I BOUGHT FOR TODAY.
- WHAT? YOU JUST
BOUGHT A NEW SWIMSUIT
LAST WEEK.
- YEAH, BUT IT
DIDN'T EXACTLY FIT.
- NOTHING PERSONAL,
BUT DID YOU MAYBE
GAIN WEIGHT?
- IT'S NOT THAT
NOTICEABLE, IS IT?
I SWEAR IT'S NOT THAT MUCH.
JUST A LITTLE OR MAYBE A LOT,
I DON'T KNOW.
- THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- ( growls ) IT'S COMPLICATED,
OKAY? I'M NOT FAT.
I JUST WEIGH
A TINY BIT MORE
BECAUSE MY HAIR GREW
AND GOT THICKER.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
HAIR DOESN'T WEIGH THAT MUCH.
YOUR BOOBS GOT BIGGER
AND I ACTUALLY LOST WEIGHT.
- WHY ARE YOU RUBBING
THAT IN MY FACE?
YOU KNOW HOW HARD
THIS IS FOR ME.
- SORRY, IF IT MAKES
YOU FEEL BETTER,
MY BOOBS SHRANK.
- I THINK MAYBE BOTH OF YOU
ARE BEING A LITTLE
OVERDRAMATIC
ABOUT ALL THIS.
YOU LOOK EXACTLY THE SAME
AS YOU DID LAST YEAR.
- NOT THAT IT'S ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT JUST BECAUSE MY BREASTS
GROW SLOWER THAN YOURS,
DOESN'T MEAN THEY WON'T GROW.
- HEY, I'M A GUY.
I DON'T HAVE BREASTS
THAT GROW AT ALL.
- OH, WHATEVER, I KNOW
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
IT'S A FRICKIN'
MILKSHAKE FACTORY IN THERE
AND MY GIRLS ARE SHRIVELING UP
AND FALLING OFF.
- IT'S NICE THAT
YOU WERE BORN CURVY,
BUT YOU NEED TO BE
WAY MORE SENSITIVE.
- REMEMBER THAT TIME
I TOLD YOU I WAS A GUY?
WELL, IT'S STILL TRUE.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT THE HECK
IS WRONG WITH
THE TWO OF YOU TODAY?
- Both: SHE'S WHAT'S WRONG.
- I JUST WANT
A SLICE OF HER BOOBS.
- HOW LONG DO I HAVE
TO STARVE TO BE THAT THIN?
- IT'S TRUE, SHE COULD
PROVE TO BE THE ENEMY.
WE'VE GOT TO KEEP
A CLOSE EYE ON YUUJI.
- SHE'S PRETTY HOT.
I WOULDN'T BLAME HIM.
IF I LOOKED LIKE HER,
I'D WALK AROUND
IN MY BIKINI ALL DAY
AND WAIT FOR MY TOP TO DROP
SO I COULD CHECK ME OUT.
- OH, NO, WHAT'S WRONG, KOUTA?
ARE YOU CATCHING A COLD?
- NO, I JUST GET CARSICK.
- THAT'S STRANGE.
I DIDN'T KNOW NOSEBLEEDS
WERE A SYMPTOM.
I THINK I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR THAT IN MY BAG.
AKI, CAN YOU HAND ME
THAT BLUE BOTTLE?
- YOU BETCHA.
WHAT THE CRAP?
THE ZIPPER'S NOT WORKING.
COME ON!
( grunts )
AND THAT'S HOW
A STUD DOES IT.
- Fukuhara: I DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER WHAT YEAR
THAT SCHOOL
SWIMSUIT IS FROM?
- Akihisa: WHERE DID YOU
EVEN FIND ONE OF THESE?!
- DAMN, WHAT WAS
THAT ALL ABOUT.
- DON'T YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
SOMEONE IN MY FAMILY
IS BEACHWEAR DELUSIONAL.
- YEAH, I THINK IT MIGHT
BE THE MEMBER WHO'S CLUTCHING
THE SWIMSUIT AND
QUIVERING LIKE A LETCH.
- THIS IS MY SISTER'S
SWIMSUIT, FYI.
- THAT IS BAD THEN.
YOU HAVE A SICK
AND TWISTED THING
FOR YOUR SISTER'S
TIGHT CLOTHING.
I'D SAY THAT'S PRETTY WHACK.
- SHUT UP! YOU KNOW
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
- LOOK, YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO FREAK OUT ON ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAID
YOU'D BE EMBARRASSED
IF I WORE SOMETHING
TOO SKIMPY.
SO I BROUGHT MY
OLD SWIM TEAM SUIT.
- JUMPING JACK CRACK! I FORGOT
HOW HORRIBLE IT WOULD BE
TO WALK AROUND WITH
YOU WEARING THAT THING.
I CHANGED MY MIND.  I'D RATHER
YOU SKANK OUT ON THE BEACH
THAN WEAR THAT.
I TAKE IT BACK!
YOU'RE MY SISTER AND
I WILL PROTECT US BOTH
FROM ALL THINGS GRANNY!
- IT'S OKAY TO ADMIT
YOU'D RATHER HAVE ME
SHOW MORE SKIN.
- YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I WANT YOU NOW.
- I NEVER REALIZED I WAS FRIENDS
WITH SUCH A PERV-A-TRON.
- COMING FROM THE MOST
CREEP-TASTIC PERV
I'VE EVER MET IN MY LIFE!
- YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
SOMETIMES, AS A JOKE, FRIENDS
CALL EACH OTHER NAMES.
- WOULD YOU PLEASE STOP TALKING
TO ME LIKE YOU KNOW THINGS?
- I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO WEAR
THE NEW STRING BIKINI
I BOUGHT.
OH, WELL, THAT OTHER ONE
WAS TOO TIGHT.
MY GIRLS KEPT POPPING OUT.
- ( Akihisa screams )
- Akihisa: YES, NOW THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- IT FEELS GREAT OUT HERE.
- WE PICKED A GOOD SPOT.
- YEAH, WE DID.
C'MON, LET'S GO CHANGE
SO WE CAN SWIM.
- OKAY.
- THIS IS IT.
THE DAY I SHOW EVERYONE
ONCE AND FOR ALL
THAT I AM 100% DUDE.
I PICKED THE RIGHT
SWIMSUIT THIS TIME.
BOTTOMS, NO TOP.
NO WAY THEY'LL QUESTION ME.
- THIS DAY'S GONNA RULE.
CHECK ME OUT. I JUST
NINJA-CHANGED IN THE CAR.
PAY NO ATTENTION TO
THE AWKWARD TAN LINES.
I'M HOPING THIS SUIT
WILL HELP THEM BLEND IN.
BUT WHAT DO YOU THINK, KOUTA?
AM I DEAD SEXY?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA LET YOU
TAKE PICTURES OF ME TODAY,
AS MANY AS YOU WANT.
- THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
MY MEMORY IS FULL.
I KNOW THIS IS HARD
FOR YOU TO BELIEVE,
BUT I DON'T
LIKE THAT OUTFIT.
IT'S HOT OUTSIDE.
MY NOSE IS DRY.
- 28 SECONDS.
I'M IMPRESSED, BRO.
THAT'S LIKE
A RECORD FOR YOU.
- THAT'S A LOT LONGER
THAN LAST TIME.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
- AWW, POOR THING.
LET ME HELP YOU
CLEAN THAT UP.
- YOU MIGHT WANT
TO STAY OVER THERE.
- IT'S HOT!
IT'S SO HOT.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- THIS ISN'T THE END.
I'M GOING TO COME BACK
AS A LITTLE BIRD.
YOU'LL SEE.
- STOP THAT.  IT'S NOT FUNNY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
I PROMISE.
- I'LL STILL BE WITH YOU.
BUT NOW I'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE DOWN YOUR SHIRT
FROM THE SKY AND FLY INTO
THE GIRL'S LOCKER ROOM.
- Fukuhara: AND SO HE WOULD
CONTINUE IN DEATH
AS HE DID IN LIFE,
FLYING AND CRASHING.
- Akihisa:
IT'S TRUE WHAT THEY SAY.
LIME GOES REALLY
GOOD WITH COCONUT.
- HEY, YOU GUYS.
I'M SO SORRY.  I DIDN'T MEAN
TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- I CERTAINLY DID.
- HOW IS HE?
ANY PROGRESS OR...
- HE'S ABOUT
THE SAME I'D SAY.
- I THINK YOU NEED TO STOP
TOUCHING HIM. THAT DOESN'T HELP.
- AWW, I DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING WRONG.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP
HIM KEEP COOL.  SEE?
- MAYBE IT'S YOU.
YOU LOOK SO GOOD
IN YOUR SWIMSUIT
THAT KOUTA GOT EXCITED
ALL OVER AGAIN.
- ( shivers )
I HEARD THAT.
AND THERE IS ABSOLUTELY
NO WAY TO PROVE IT.
- ( giggles )
- EXCITED HOW?
- WELL, THE SAME WAY
ANY GUY WOULD GET EXCITED,
I GUESS.
- GOTCHA.
SCISSORS.
- ( Yuuji screams )
WHAT THE HECK
WAS THAT FOR?
- MUCH BETTER.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE EXCITED
ABOUT SEEING ME
IN A SWIMSUIT, YUUJI.
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO GO THAT FAR.
YOU TWO ARE ALWAYS HOT
SO IT'S NO BIG DEAL FOR US.
- THAT'S SO NICE.
SORRY I'M BLUSHING,
BUT I LOVE IT
WHEN YOU CALL ME HOT.
- YES, THAT WAS VERY
SWEET OF YOU, THANKS.
- AND I GUESS I'M JUST
A TWIG WALKING AROUND
IN A PAPER SAC, HMM?
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.  I MEAN,
YOU'RE PRETTY SCRAWNY
OVERALL, BUT SOME AREAS ARE
A LITTLE THICKER THAN OTHERS.
- YOU JERK-FACE,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
COME OUT AND SAY IT?
YOU THINK I'M FAT, DON'T YOU?
- WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT FAT?
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOING,
YOU GUYS!
I'M FINALLY DONE CHANGING.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?!
GET BACK IN THERE.
- ARE YOU GUYS CLOSING?
WHY AREN'T YOU WEARING
A TOP WITH THAT?
- BECAUSE THIS IS
A GUY'S SWIMSUIT.
IT DOESN'T COME WITH A TOP.
- WELL, GIRLS SHOULDN'T BE
WEARING GUY'S
SWIMSUITS OUT HERE.
- I AGREE WITH YOU,
BUT I'M NOT A GIRL.
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO COME WITH ME.
- PUT ME DOWN!
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG!
I PROMISE I'M A GUY!
LET ME PROVE IT TO YOU!
- I'M SORRY, MINAMI.
IS MY BROTHER BEING
A TURD AGAIN?
DO YOU WANT ME TO PLOW HIM?
- ( cries )
- OH, GOODNESS.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S
WORSE THAN I THOUGHT.
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'LL JUST
LIVE MY ENTIRE LIFE
BEING INADEQUATE.
- I'M SO SORRY.
I CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
THOSE ARE AMAZING.
- DON'T HATE ME.
I'VE JUST ALWAYS BEEN CURIOUS.
IT'S A CRUEL,
CRUEL SUMMER, ISN'T IT?
- NO, THE WORLD
JUST HATES US.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT, YOU GUYS.
TALK ABOUT RIDICULOUS.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, HIDEYOSHI?
YOU LOOK UPSET?
WHAT WAS ALL THAT
ABOUT EARLIER?
- I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
LET'S MOVE ON.
- Fukuhara: THE SUMMER IS
VERY CRUEL,
ESPECIALLY WHEN BEACHES
ARE INVOLVED.
- BAKA AND TEST.
- IT'S A LITTLE BIT
MORE TO YOUR RIGHT,
AKIHISA.
- DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
JUST TRY GOING LEFT.
- KEEP GOING STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE JUST FINE.
- THAT HELPS.
WHO'S TELLING THE TRUTH?
- IT'S PRECISELY 32 DEGREES LEFT
OF WHERE YOU'RE FACING NOW.
AND THEN FORWARD AT 4.7 METERS.
- IT'S TOTALLY
THE OTHER WAY, BRO.
- EVERYONE'S GIVING ME
DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WAIT, WHERE'S YUUJI?
- YUUJI, HOW'S MY SUIT?
- LOOKS THE SAME
AS IT DID EARLIER.
NOTHING'S DIFFERENT.
- THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE STILL STANDING
IN THE EXACT SAME PLACE.
IT LOOKS DIFFERENT UP CLOSE.
- NO! I DON'T WANT
YOU TO TOUCH ME.
I MEAN, IF YOU GET TOO CLOSE,
IT'LL JUST LOOK BLURRY.
- MELON CRUSHER!
WHO'S YOUR DADDY?!
- ( screams )
- DUDE, THAT WAS CLOSE!
- DAMN, I MISSED.
WOW, I'M REALLY SORRY.
I SERIOUSLY THOUGHT THE MELON
WAS HERE SOMEWHERE.
- HUH, THAT'S FUNNY.
NOBODY TOLD YOU
TO HEAD IN THAT DIRECTION.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
THAT I AIMED AT YUUJI
ON PURPOSE?  I AM INSULTED.
- HIDEYOSHI, BACK OFF,
ALL RIGHT, MAN?
DON'T TRY TO GET IN THE WAY
OF A DUDE'S
WATERMELON-BASHING TIME.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NOW STEP ASIDE
WHILE THE PRO
TAKES A SWING.
- ( both strain )
- AWW, WHAT'S WRONG, BRO?
DON'T WANT TO GIVE ME THE WOOD?
- IF I RECALL, YOU ALREADY HAD
YOUR TURN AND TOTALLY FAILED.
- THAT WAS JUST ROUND ONE.
I SAY IT'S TIME FOR ROUND TWO.
AND IN ROUND TWO, I GO FIRST.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO SWITCH UP THE ORDER.
- HEY, GUYS, I WAS
REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO EATING THE WATERMELONS.
DO YOU THINK WE COULD JUST
DROP THE GAME
ALL TOGETHER, PLEASE?
- Both: OH, DON'T WORRY.
NOBODY'S GONNA
BE AIMING AT THE WATERMELON.
- Hideyoshi:
UH, I THINK THIS GAME
IS TAKING A TURN.
- AH, I'M BEAT.
- I HAVEN'T EVEN
GONE SWIMMING YET.
WHY AM I SO
EXHAUSTED ALREADY?
- CHASING EACH OTHER
WITH A BAT WILL DO THAT.
- WE HAVE RETURNED!
- HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
WE BROUGHT YOU LUNCH.
- SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG,
YOU GUYS.
- WAS IT CROWDED?
- NO, NOT EXACTLY.
- YEAH,
BUT WE STILL
TOTALLY GOT HIT ON.
- WHICH IS AWESOME IF YOU'RE
INTO THAT SORT OF THING.
- IT MAKES ME ILL.
- YEAH, MAN,
IT MUST SUCK TO BE HOT.
- YOU KNOW, DUDES'LL LEAVE YOU
ALONE IF YOU JUST LAUGH AT 'EM.
- TRUE STORY.
- STOP RIGHT THERE.
- DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER
EVER TEACH YOU ANY MANNERS?
- MANNERS?
- ( sighs )
SERIOUSLY, YOU GUYS HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE A GIRL.
- HEY, YOU NEED TO FEEL A LITTLE
MORE THREATENED BY THIS, YUUJI.
- ( chuckles )
BY WHAT?
MY BRAIN IS PULSING!
- YOU KNOW,
I WISH WE COULD GET
AKIHISA TO FEEL A LITTLE
JEALOUS OVER US.
WOULDN'T THAT
MAKE HIM EVEN CUTER?
- GOOD PLAN.  LET'S SEE IF
WE CAN MAKE HIM WORRY A LITTLE.
- YEAH, LET'S.
- SO ANNOYING.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT A PAIN.
RIGHT, MIZUKI?
- ABSOLUTELY.
ALWAYS BOTHERING US
WITH THEIR SEXY TALK.
- SO WAIT, YOU'RE SAYING YOU TWO
GET HIT ON A WHOLE BUNCH.
- YEAH, ALL THE TIME
AND BY GUYS.
- THEY JUST WANT A PIECE
OF THIS SWEET ACTION.
- THAT SO? THEN WHY'D
YOU GUYS ACT
LIKE THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME
IT EVER HAPPENED?
- THAT'S NOT WHAT WE MEANT.
IT'S JUST SO DISGUSTING,
IT ALWAYS FEELS
LIKE THE FIRST TIME.
- STRAIGHT UP.
IT MAY NOT MAKE SENSE TO YOU
SINCE YOU'RE ALL ANDROID WHEN
IT COMES TO FLIRTING AND STUFF.
- THAT'S RUDE.  WHEN IT
COMES TO HITTING ON GIRLS,
I CAN TOTALLY--
- YOU CAN WHAT TOTALLY?
- YES, TELL US, PLEASE?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
I BET YOU THINK
HITTING ON GIRLS
HAS SOMETHING TO
DO WITH BRUISES.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT COMES NATURALLY TO YOU.
SO WHEN YOU THINK YOU'RE
BEING CUTE AND CHARMING,
WELL, YOU'RE
JUST BEING AWKWARD.
- YOU CAN'T FATHOM THE DEPTHS
OF A FEMALE HEART, YUUJI.
THAT'S WHY YOU SUCK.
- OH YEAH?! TRY SAYING
THAT TO MY FACE.
- EVERYBODY HAS HIS OR HER
STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES.
YOU BOYS JUST AREN'T GOOD
AT FLIRTING WITH GIRLS.
- ( growls )
- CRAP, THAT WAS
TEN KINDS OF BALLS.
- IT KIND OF FEELS LIKE THEY
WERE ALL GANGING UP ON US.
- WHERE DO THEY GET OFF
THINKING THEY KNOW HOW
OTHER GIRLS SEE US?
- RIGHT? THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
IF I WANTED TO, I COULD HIT ON
ANY GIRL I SAW.
NO PROBLEMO.
( gasps, grunts )
- WHAT THE HELL'S
WRONG WITH YOU, MAN?
- I THINK I MIGHT
BE LOSING MY MIND.
I SAW GIRLS AROUND HIM.
- HUH?
- AROUND KOUTA,
HE'S BEING
HIT ON BY
A BUNCH OF GIRLS.
- YEAH, YOU ARE LOSING
YOUR MIND.
I KEEP TELLING YOU TO CUT IT
WITH THE CRAZY TALK.
- WOW, I BET YOU'RE
REALLY GOOD WITH A CAMERA.
- I JUST TAKE PICTURES
FOR FUN, MOSTLY.
- HE'S SO SHY.
THAT'S ADORABLE AND HOT.
- ( gags )
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
GIRLS DON'T GO
AFTER THAT GUY.
- YUUJI.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- HYPOTHETICALLY SPEAKING HERE,
DO YOU THINK IT
COULD REALLY BE TRUE?
ARE WE THE ONLY
UNPOPULAR ONES?
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT CAN BE RIGHT!
- YEAH, WE'RE
THE EPITOME OF AWESOMENESS.
- ( both laugh )
- KOUTA IS JUST
PLAYING OFF THE FACT
THAT HE LOOKS LIKE
A HOMELESS LITTLE ORPHAN KID.
THAT'S ALL.
- AND THAT'S NOT OUR STYLE
'CAUSE WE'RE MEN, RIGHT?
- WE'RE MEN AND A HALF, YO.
LET 'EM TRY
TO CALL US UNPOPULAR.
- WAIT TILL THEY SEE
ME MACKING ON GIRLS
LIKE I JUST GOT
OUT OF PRISON.
I'LL HIT ON EVERYTHING
THAT MOVES.
- TRY TO KEEP THE CREEPY
STUFF TO YOURSELF.
AND NEVER SAY
THAT OUT LOUD AGAIN.
BUT I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YOU!
- ROCK ON!
THINKING BACK ON IT,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE HELL WAS WRONG WITH US.
YOU KNOW, WE STILL
DON'T HAVE A PLAN
ON HOW TO
DO THIS WHOLE THING.
- I THINK WE GOT TO
TAKE A PAGE FROM KOUTA.
THE DUDE DOES SCORE, MAN.
- SO WE JUST LOOK FOR CHICKS
WHO WANT TO GET
THEIR PICTURES TAKEN?
- YEAH, FIRST ONE OF US
WILL GO UP TO A GIRL
AND OPEN IT UP BY
SAYING SOMETHING LIKE
"YO, DO YOU WANT ME
TO TAKE YOUR PICTURE?"
- OKAY, IT'S DIRECT.
- THEN THE OTHER ONE
TRIES TO STRIKE UP
A CONVERSATION
WHILE WE'RE SETTING UP
THE SHOT.
AFTER THAT, IT SHOULD BE
A PIECE OF CAKE.
- SO HOW DO WE GET
A CONVERSATION GOING?
- THAT'S TOTALLY UP
TO THE SECOND PERSON,
HOWEVER THEY WANT TO DO IT.
- IF THE WHOLE THING
FAILS THEN,
IT'D BE
THE SECOND PERSON'S FAULT.
- ( both scream )
- DON'T BE AN ASS, AKIHISA.
WHY ARE YOU RUNNING LIKE
A MANIAC ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- WHY ARE YOU RUNNING
LIKE A COKED UP CHEETAH?
- JUST LET ME SET
THIS UP FOR YOU!
- NO, I'LL SET IT UP.
AND THEN YOU CAN
TAKE THE PICS.
- YOU JUST WANT
TO GET THERE FIRST
AND WEDGE ME OUT
OF IT COMPLETELY.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
- ( both scream )
- OKAY, IT'S READY.
EVERYBODY SMILE BIG.
- ( panting )
- OH, HEY THERE.
YOU'RE A GIRL.
AND I LIKE THE GIRLS.
YOU'RE REALLY SPECIAL LOOKING.
- I KNOW YOU WANT ME
TO TAKE A PICTURE OF YOU ALL HOT
IN YOUR TEENY BIKINI.
- ( dialing )
( phone rings )
- I NEVER FIGURED
THEY'D CALL THE POLICE.
- SO I GUESS WE SHOULD GIVE UP
THE WHOLE PHOTOGRAPHY ANGLE.
- YEAH.  KOUTA'S A FRAUD.
HE MAKES IT LOOK SO EASY,
BUT IT'S A FLIPPIN' BEATING.
- OKAY THEN.
TIME FOR A NEW PLAN.
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- JUST STICK TO WHAT WE KNOW.
GIVE THEM SOME PHONY COMPLIMENTS
AND THEN INVITE THEM
BACK TO OUR CAMP SITE.
- YEAH, WOMEN ALWAYS
LIKE TO BE COMPLIMENTED.
BUT WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO SAY TO THEM?
- UH, YOU KNOW,
JUST A BUNCH OF LIES,
LIKE TELLING THEM
THEY LOOK PRETTIER
THAN AN AIRBRUSHED MODEL
ON A MAGAZINE COVER
OR THAT THEY SHOULD
BE IN MOVIES.
THEN ONCE THEY'RE DISTRACTED BY
THEIR DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR...
- Both: THEY'LL BE
PUTTY IN OUR HANDS.
- OH, THANKS.
- NO PROB.  ANYTHING
FOR A PRETTY LADY.
- AWW, THAT'S VERY SWEET.
- YEAH, AND THAT'S
A RIGHTEOUSLY HOT BOD
YOU'RE SPORTING THERE.
- I THINK SO TOO.
YOU MUST WORKOUT A LOT.
- OH, STOP.
YOU GUYS ARE EMBARRASSING ME.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE
EMBARRASSED BY THE TRUTH, MISS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE JUST TELLING IT
LIKE IT IS.
THAT'S ALL, MA'AM.
- HECK YEAH.
YOUR CURVES ARE UNSTOPPABLE.
YOU'RE LIKE...
- YEAH, YOU'RE JUST LIKE A...
- Both: LIKE A HIGH-BUDGET
PORNO ACTRESS.
- MAN, SHE HAD A SERIOUS
RIGHT HOOK ON HER.
- SHE PUNCHED ME
IN THE HEAD SO HARD
IT MADE THE BOTTOMS
OF MY FEET HURT.
I MEAN, HOW DOES
THAT EVEN HAPPEN?
- THERE THEY ARE.
WE MISSED YOU.
WHAT HAVE YOU GUYS BEEN DOING?
- YOUR FACES ARE SWOLLEN.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- NOTHING REALLY
HAPPENED AS SUCH.
RIGHT, YUUJI?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, BRO.
WE JUST FELL AND HIT
OUR FACE ON ROCKS, DIDN'T WE?
- I ALMOST FORGOT
THE SWIMMING COMPETITION.
HURRY UP!
- OH, YEAH!
I'M NOT GONNA LOSE THIS TIME.
- WE WERE SO CLOSE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO BRING UP
A PORNO FLICK?
- YOU SAID IT TOO,
OR DID YOU FORGET THAT?
- HEY, DON'T YOU GO TRYING TO
PIN THIS ON ME ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- ARE YOU LOOKING FOR ANOTHER
SKULL-CRACKING?
( sighs )
LET'S STOP.
THIS ISN'T GETTING
US ANYWHERE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
WE KEEP SCREWING
THINGS UP BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT REALLY
INTO THESE GIRLS.
I MEAN, SINCE THEY'RE
NOT OUR TYPES,
I THINK WE MIGHT
BE UNCONSCIOUSLY
HOLDING OURSELVES
BACK FROM THEM.
- OF COURSE,
IF WE REALLY WANTED THEM,
WE COULD TOTALLY
BE UP IN THERE.
- YEAH, NO, WE'RE DORKS.
- ( laughs ) OH, HELL, YEAH.
ALMOST HAD ME THOUGH.
NOW WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT?
- I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE TRY ONE LAST TIME
WITH THEM.
- YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
UM, PARDON ME.
- UH, SO THIS IS
A LITTLE BIT EMBARRASSING,
BUT WE'RE KIND OF LOST
AT THE MOMENT.
- THAT'S RIGHT, WE WERE LOOKING
FOR THE PUBLIC BEACH,
BUT WE COULDN'T SEEM
TO FIND IT ANYWHERE.
COULD YOU HELP US OUT?
- OH MY GOD.
WE'RE STANDING ON
THE PUBLIC BEACH, YOU IDIOT.
- SHUT UP.  YOU SAID WE GOT LOST
SO I WAS JUST ROLLING WITH IT.
- ( theme music plays )
( music winds down )
- HOLD ON, HER HAIR
LOOKS DIFFERENT.
IT CHANGED COLOR!
- IT'S THE SAME COLOR
THAT IT'S ALWAYS BEEN.
- WOW, IT LOOKS GREAT.
- DANGER!
- Kouta: I'M SORRY, AKIHISA.
- NO FREAKIN' WAY.
YOU WOULD BETRAY US?
- I HAD TO DO IT, MAN.
OTHERWISE, THEY WERE
GOING TO KILL ME.
- SO I GUESS THEY KNEW
WE WERE TALKING TO GIRLS.
- THEY SAID IT WOULD
JUST BE THE RIGHT ARM.
- AN ARM IS AN ARM, MAN.
AND I NEED MY ARM.
YOU CAN'T MAKE ME
GO BACK THERE, PLEASE.
- NO, THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING
TO BREAK EVERYTHING ELSE
AND LEAVE YOU WITH
JUST THE RIGHT ARM.
- Mizuki: AKIHISA, HELLO?
PLEASE DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
- Minami: YEAH, BECAUSE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
A FULL DAY'S LESSON
IN ARM TWISTING.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
- Akira: CAN YOU HEAR ME?
THIS IS YOUR SISTER.
COME BACK TO ME, LITTLE BROTHER.
- Hideyoshi: RUN, AKIHISA!
- Aiko: THESE LADIES
ARE READY TO THROW DOWN.
- ( girls grunt )
- ( static )
- GOOD-BYE, AKIHISA.
WE HAD A GOOD TIME, DIDN'T WE?
- ( screams )
- YUUJI.
- YEAH?
- SIT DOWN.
- WHAT?
BUT I CAN'T.
- SIT DOWN!
- UH, BUT WE'RE KINDA
IN AN OCEAN.
- ARE YOU GOING TO MAKE ME
SAY IT AGAIN?
GOOD BOY.
- Fukuhara: QUESTION TWO:
ASIDE FROM WATER, WHAT IS THE
PRIMARY COMPONENT OF SEA WATER?
- Akihisa:
TEARS OF REGRET AND PENITENCE.
- STOP WHINING.
- NEXT EPISODE,
"ME, YUKATA,
AND FESTIVITIES."
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.