She was less than a year old when the extraordinarily talented girl was taken into a special institution.
She had long since learned to speak by then.
There, she was introduced to games.
She was made to play many games to test her intelligence,
but none of them entertained her.
Then, two years later,
she was introduced to a mother-like figure,
and a boy who was seven years older than her.
He spoke carefully to appease the adults while giving a blank smile.
That's when she spoke her first words in a long, long time.
You really are empty.
Hey, let's play a game.
Who is that?
Null...
Null knows...
Did you have a bad dream?
I'll bring you some warm milk.
No! No!
He was with me.
He was always with me.
So...
Shiro.
Shiro!
It's cold.
There you are, Master.
Dora-chan was panicking about how you ran off, so I came to check on you.
Number Of Contacts
Jibril?
Yes, what is it?
Who are your masters?
Why are you asking me—
Answer me!
You are my master, Shiro-sama.
Then who challenged you?
It was you, Shiro-sama.
Who told Stephanie to fall in love with them?
I heard it was you, Shiro-sama.
Who figured out the secret behind the Eastern Federation's games?
That was also you, using the clues left by Dora-chan's grandfather.
I was charmed by your unparalleled brilliance and strategic thinking,
and decided to serve you.
Serve... me?
Yes.
You are the queen of Elkia and designated representative of Imanity.
In other words, she had a partner?
But there's no proof.
I've been asking people
throughout the city in addition to the castle, but...
Shiro's  House
Those involved in the protests didn't know anything about her partner, either.
Which means...
It's likely
that our master competed against someone unbeknownst to us,
lost,
and had her memories altered.
No way!
Who could have...
The Eastern Federation?
Yes, it's possible.
Master.
Let's play a game.
A game?
Shiro's  House
Yes. We'll wager the false memories that you've been implanted with.
False?
And I know it's very disrespectful to ask this,
but would you mind losing?
That's check.
False memories...
Are they really false?
Is that why they're disappearing?
Hey, Shiro.
They say people can change, but is that really true?
They're all...
all disappearing...
If you wish to fly, will you grow wings?
I don't think so.
You can change the way you handle things, but you can't change yourself.
Brother...
You have to forge your own path.
You have to find a way to fly as you are now.
Let's find the wings that will let you fly.
There's no rush.
They're all false...
It's all fake...
If they disappear,
I'll feel better.
Null...
Master?
Null knows...
Null knows no defeat!
Why didn't you lose on purpose?
He's real. Sora is real!
I know he's real!
Sora?
But Master...
He's real! He is real!
Calm down, Master.
If you just think about it...
You're right.
You're right. It's normal to think that he doesn't exist,
but I'm sure he does.
What are you saying, Dora-chan?
Because I know you two would never lose!
Steph...
But...
Yeah, they'd never lose.
There has to be a reason for all this.
There must be something behind all this.
You're getting too emotional.
You need to—
What did we do yesterday?
Yesterday?
I was busy dealing with the protests
while you were playing your games in the throne room.
That was two days ago. The 19th.
st
I'll change my question.
Where did you go two nights ago?
That same night, then?
Um...
Huh?
I can't...
That's right. You can't remember.
Now, one last thing.
U-Um, what are you...
Fondling your breasts.
H-How am I supposed to respond to that?
You're not getting turned on?
Even though I told you to fall in love with me?
Well...
So, you're saying that someone other than yourself told her to fall in love with them.
Yes, it was my brother who told her that.
But weren't you already convinced that he existed?
Why did you fondle my breasts, then?
To thank you.
I wouldn't have noticed if it wasn't for what you said.
Shiro...
Okay, let's think about this.
If this Sora existed, why did he disappear?
Something that also caused our memories of the last day and a half to disappear...
A large-scale magic spell would suffice, but traces of it should've been left behind if that were the case.
What if it was a game?
A game?
What if there was a game, and this is part of the rules being enforced by the Oaths?
A game involving Imanity's representative could affect the whole race.
But Jibril is...
No, since he would be my master,
I'd be his subordinate.
We can assume I would fall under its effects as well.
I see.
But what kind of game would this be?
I don't know.
But... I remember what he said...
I believe in you.
Shiro, the two of us are always one.
He would never leave me alone.
So...
Shiro, are you there?
You're still there, right, Shiro?
Brother!
Would you hold me somewhere... anywhere I can still feel?
I'm going insane...
Brother!
Shiro?
Think. I need to go into overdrive.
Absorb the situation... The situation I've been entrusted with.
Use every last bit of memory I still have!
He said that we are always one,
so he must be somewhere in here.
He said we've always won before starting.
We're bound by a promise.
He said we're not the heroes of a boy's manga.
No!
Think harder!
Harder...
He said he was going to get the last piece we needed.
The last piece?
A game for that piece?
Something we need to challenge the Eastern Federation...
Tools...
Wisdom...
Observer...
Elf?
He's going to get an elf?
How?
Challenge Elven Garde?
Cramy?
No. Cramy doesn't believe him.
She'd never agree to...
A game to steal each other's existence?
Shiro! Shiro!
That's right.
Sky Walk
The 32 stones collectively represent your existence,
the aspect of each one is ranked and assigned
by your subconscious.
Sky Walk
In other words, you won't know which stone constitutes which part of you
until your opponent takes it.
For example, the existence of that elf next to you.
Or your physical body, nerves, or memories.
In the end, your very existence is taken,
and no one will realize you were ever there.
To put it bluntly, you disappear.
Are you serious?
Yep.
Oath Five: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
If you don't like it, just call if off.
What will you do?
Cramy...
Fi, this man is betting Imanity's Race Piece.
We can't simply ignore that.
Seriously... And I was hoping we could come to an agreement.
Of course we can.
You just have to entrust your elf friend to me.
I can't do that!
I didn't think so.
What are we betting?
We'll say the winner gets the right to make two demands of the loser.
For example, you could make the results of the game eternal.
The other's existence would be permanently erased,
and then you could manipulate their partners' memories to make them join you...
In other words, we're each betting our existence
and our partners' servitude, right?
That's right.
You're crazy.
Well, while I'm at it,
I'll propose one more important rule.
Brother?
Master?
Shiro! Are you okay?
Brother!
Jibril...
What is it?
Could you make an existence stealing game?
No, unfortunately.
I can create a virtual world like with
Materialization Alpha and Omega, but...
What if you collaborated with an elf?
Collaborated?
With those forest oafs?
They're nothing. I reduced one of their capitals to a pile of dust with a single blast during the great war!
Could you do it?
It is possible.
Begrudgingly, I admit those oafs can construct complicated spells.
So the game erased Sora's existence?
Yes.
If he was erased, doesn't that mean he lost?
That's right.
If he won, he should exist.
What if it was neither?
The game's still underway?
That can't be...
Jibril, please check if any magic is being used in this room!
Understood.
I woke up here...
We have our own bedroom, yet I woke up here...
He promised he would never leave me alone.
You're right. Magic is being used here.
But I can't detect its precise position.
We just have to search everywhere we can—
Dora-chan, you tripped over nothing.
You don't always need to be the comic relief.
Tripped? Me?
An Othello stone?
That says "three" in the elven language.
Why are there only stones?
That's because they haven't been used.
Even if we can't sense them, they're there.
But even if we know that, there's still only two sets of three stones.
We don't even know if we're white or black.
That's not a problem.
Brother told me that the two of us are one.
Therefore, I'm also participating in this game.
I'll propose one more important rule.
Each of our partners will play in the game.
Should one of us be unable to continue, our partner can take our place.
That's why I still had my memories.
Can you actually see the board?
I can't.
But I can see
what he would do.
Are you deliberately trying to lose?
Not at all.
I'm setting it up so I can win.
How he would lead his opponent on...
What is this?
Your memories?
Are you making me steal your memories
to prove that there's no other race working with you?
Not a bad answer.
How he would get his message across...
Now you can't continue the game.
I win.
But the game is still...
What's going on?
Why isn't the game ending?
What parts of Sora do those three stones contain?
How he would deceive his opponent...
And...
how he would win.
You're amazing, Brother!
Nobody could ever figure this out.
Except for you and me.
The parts of you that are contained in these last three stones...
•
Three: The way to win this game.
Two: Your unwavering trust in me.
And one:
•
Everything that I am.
Okay, Brother...
Come back!
Brother...
Shiro...
Okay!
You can punch me if you want!
I'm ready...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I should've come sooner...
I can't believe I completely forgot my master.
Why?
Cramy! Wake up! Cramy!
Cramy! Cramy!
Now then,
as we agreed, I shall state my demands.
Y-You can do whatever you want with me!
But Cramy...
No can do! Demand one:
Don't!
Return the memories we stole from each other without losing them.
Cramy!
What's going on?
They both keep the memories they stole from the other,
but they also get their own memories back.
Now Cramy and Master know each other intimately,
and can trust each other.
This is the piece that our master wanted.
And...
Demand two:
The elf here...
Fil, I'm invoking my right to alter your memories.
Wha—
Don't worry.
It's fine, Fi.
He only wants one thing.
You want us to spy for you, right?
You've been inside my head, all right.
Spy? What does he mean?
I'll explain it later.
After seeing your memories, I've changed my mind.
I'm in.
Brother, you're amazing!
Right? Tell me how awesome your big brother is.
You're my super awesome big brother.
You're making me embarrassed now—
Master!
Shiro... It's okay now, right?
Yeah.
I'm in standby. I'm ready whenever you are.
Fi...
Cramy...
I was so scared! I'm never doing that again!
I was so scared!
What's going on?
This must be Master's true face,
I guess.
I was so scared!
I carried a loneliness no one could see
And I cried alone
We couldn't smile in front of others
But we smiled together
In the dead hours of the night
In the depths of our imagination
Our emotions run wild
I'm sure we can start again, so goodbye
I bid farewell to the sadness
And then one day we'll light up our empty hearts
I'll piece together the broken words
Our own little world will continue to move on
I wish to the heavens for this to last forever
Blue Rose
It's way faster than Salamander—
Shut up!
Please wait a moment.
It's sad growing up.