kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
being at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
we may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings go deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
at this rate
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
won’t you kiss me? it’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
with our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
Misato West High School
Rise and shine, Yuu-chan.
We’re already done homeroom.
It went by that  fast…?
Where’s Haruka?
Oh, Haruka…
she’s gone.
Wait, no! What I meant was...
she just went for some tea with the others.
drip
Without me…?
I’m finally free!
Where have you been, Kotone?
I had to reorganize the books in the library…
Now I’m beat.
sniff
What’re you guys up to…?
Shizuku-chan… I didn’t know you were so sadistic.
You’re wrong! Probably wrong!
Tea Time with Big Sis!
It’s probably a café nearby.
Why don’t we go join them?
Their matcha cakes are to die for!
Matcha?!
But I could really go for the cheese cake!
But then their strawberry chiffon cake’s good too…
and let’s not forget about the flakey apple pie!
They’ve got blueberry tarts too,
and the lemon pound cake has that hint of tartness!
Don’t get me started on the tiramisu…
Can we decide once we’re there?
Sakura Trick
Town of Misato
Why’d Haruka have to leave me behind like that?
She could’ve woke me up…
I’ll just show her how close I’ve gotten to Kotone-chan!
It almost seems like we’re a family…
In a way, I guess.
Then in that case…
I guess I’d be the wife…
Town Bakery
We’re real sorry for inviting you out on such short notice.
What was it you wanted to talk about?
Let’s discuss that over tea.
It’ll be on us.
I see…
Coffee
Shop
We’re here!
It’s way too crowded in here.
I thought for sure we’d miss the crowds by coming right over…
Wouldn’t it make sense for it to be crowded right away?
I guess everyone else had the same brilliant idea…
A spot opened up over there!
I’ll go hold it for us.
Gotcha.
We’ll handle the ordering, then.
Let’s go.
Sure.
Big Sis
I’m guessing it’d be better for you guys  to save our seats…
Just leave the rest to us.
I’m gliding right through…
Um… Would you mind telling me what I’m here for?
Well you see…
What is it?!
You look just like your sister...
with those eyes, nose, and lips.
S-So I’m her twin, then...?
Of course not!
Yuu-chan’s cheeks are a bit more plump.
A-Alright, I get it.
Gaze...
She’s really staring me down...
Um… Would you mind telling me...
Oh, your hairpiece...
Big Sis
Coffee
Shop
I’ll fix it for you.
No, thanks.
I’ll do it myself!
Don’t be shy.
Oh? The way she just flinched…
When our faces get close, Yuu-chan blushes like that too.
Even your mannerisms are the same.
And just why, exactly, would your faces be getting so close...?
Ah!
Sakura Trick
You yourself have some things in common with her.
I do?
Yuu normally tries not to mention you much...
But she’ll sometimes slip up and go on about you for ages.
You’re the same. You only seem to talk about her...
touched...
Yuu-chan…
I didn’t think you’d even mention me when I’m not around...
touched...
It’s a little unfair…
What did she just mean by “unfair?”
Don’t tell me...
since Yuu-chan seems to care more for me, than her own sister...
Big Sis
Little Sis
My sister
is off-limits!
...she’s jealous of me?!
I tried texting her, but she didn’t reply.
So I just guessed she’d have similar tastes to Yuu.
But what if she doesn’t like it?
You gotta have faith.
Sorry for the wait.
plop
President Mitsuki gets the matcha latte.
Oh, my. How could you have known my favorite flavor?!
We nailed it!
So would you mind telling me what I’m here for?
I think I deserve an explanation.
Each class is choosing an event for the culture festival, right?
Yes...
We were hoping you could lend us a hand.
By the way, we’re doing Snow White.
Isn’t that your  class’s responsibility?
Why do I  have to play the huntsman?!
We haven’t decided the roles just yet...
President Mitsuki, Yuu-chan actually…
Flashback
This is my sister’s last festival, so I’d really like to do something together.
For us, this is the only time we’ll get to have a festival across all three grades.
Even so,
this is such short notice...
Don’t be forgetting how much we helped you that one time...
We’ve just come to collect.
We’re going to regroup.
What’ll we do?
She doesn’t seem as gullible as Yuu...
We might as well just try asking her earnestly.
You’re right.
Thanks, you guys.
Let’s get back out there.
Huh?
’Sup guys?
You brought Yuu-chan along too?
I was planning to come right back to school.
There goes my surprise for Yuu-chan...
Am I not allowed to be here?
Well, you are, but...
By the way, I want more.
You drank my whole  cup?!
She drank my  whole cup...
Why’re you all bubbly?!
Coffee
Shop
Go buy me matcha latte.
cha-ching
Do I have enough change...?
I might be a bit short...
Sorry. Just gimme a sec.
That Yuu.
She’s troubling Haruka.
Yuu, you’re still thirsty?
I’ll give you mine.
Come over here.
This one’s matcha.
Matcha!
I had a coupon!
pat
You can’t beat matcha!
Could this be...
pat
her declaration of war?!
I will  earn your acceptance!
I’ll give it my all!
What’s she all worked up for?
I was just doing what any big sister would do...
I think we’d better call it quits for today.
You’re right.
Yuu’s here now.
Let’s try another day.
President Mitsuki.
Let’s call it a day.
G-Good idea.
Why don’t we try some matcha cake next time?
But there’re better choices...
Ultimately, we didn’t get Mitsuki to join in...
Matcha Baumkuchen
Is she using that as bait?
What is it?
What’s wrong?
Don’t leave me like that!
I want to be with you always!
Don’t go off without me!
Yuu-chan…
Oh, Yuu-chan…
rub
You’re such a baby.
I’ll be selfish for today.
I won’t know what you mean if you don’t say it like usual.
You meanie.
Just kidding.
I’ll kiss for as long as you want.
rub rub
Tea Time With Big Sis!
End
rub rub
Morning, Yuu-chan!
Morning, Haruka!
Hey, we’re doing Snow White for the culture festival, right?
What role do you wanna be?
The Witch.
pierce
What a cute Witch!
Stop trying to slip that in your mouth!
The Witch, the Apple, and the Big Sister
President Mitsuki.
Big Sis
Ah
Is something the matter?
The first-year classes are over that way.
Y-You’re right.
I have something…
Yuu-chan says she wants to be the Witch.
Not so fast!
That’s the Queen, right?
I wanted to play that role too!
How the heck is the Witch so popular?
And why are sparks flying over there as well?
Heh, Yuu likes to play weirdos.
She’s not weird!
She’s really cool!
But I didn’t expect Shizuku-chan to want the role too.
That’s because...
If we really think about the things the Queen did...
I wonder if she can relate to the Witch...
heh
Like talking to herself with the mirror...
Who does that?
That’s your reason?!
Snow White
So how about we do this?
You two try acting.
And we’ll decide who’s better.
Okay.
Hey there pretty girl. How would you like an apple?
I’ll take one!
Calm down, Haruka.
Snow White
Why hello there my pretty... Would you like to gorge on this here apple?
Too realistic!
She’s scaring me!
Ye
s!
Shizuku-chan, you’re too cute.
You call that  cute?
Okay, so who’s the better Witch?
Won’t you tell us?
Yuu-chan!
Shizuku-chan!
Both are kinda questionable.
sense
It feels like we’re being watched...
Hey, Kaede.
President Mitsuki’s watching us.
Oh, you’re right.
Is she keeping an eye on Yuu and Haruka still?
Maybe she finally decided to join us!
She should’ve said so earlier.
You’re dead wrong.
And then…
They looked this way!
I hope they didn’t notice me.
I have to get away from here.
You there!
Of all people, I find the student council head running through the halls?
Ah, I was…
Onee-chan?
Such bad timing...
I was merely taking very large steps.
That’s not gonna slide.
Sakura Trick
What’s up, Onee-chan?
Oh, nothing.
Just passing by.
I think I’m bothering you guys.
See ya later, Yuu.
You’re acting awfully suspicious.
hmm
I know…
You wanted to join us in the play, but you couldn’t bring yourself to tell us?
Snow White
That’s not true.
I really am just passing by.
Oh, please.
I just accidentally saw Haruka.
Aren’t we seeing President Mitsuki an awful lot lately?
Really? How so?
At lunch time, she usually peeks around the door just like she did now.
She does that routinely?!
Then maybe that just means she’s too shy to call out to us.
You think so?
Of course I do.
Why didn’t you reach out to her?
I’m sure she’s just really shy.
Why are you the one getting sad?
Could it be?
You want to join us in Snow White?
Why is that  the consensus?!
Is that so?
Yay!
No way.
It’s not happening.
Onee-chan, this will be the last chance we can be together in the culture festival.
Please.
Do it for Yuu-chan’s sake.
Errr
Big Sis
Little Sis
Aw come on, Onee-chan!
Wai—
Come on!
So how about it, Miss President?
Wouldn’t you say using the play to keep and eye on them beats lurking around?
She’s got a point.
If I join them, I’ll get to talk with Haruka so much more...
Not!
Big Sis
I’m such an idiot!
I’ll do it to keep an eye on them!
Oh? I knew you’d come around!
Hey, guys.
President Mitsuki said she wants to play as Snow White.
Snow White
Really?!
Thanks, Onee-chan!
Hold on.
I did say I was going to join the play, but...
I didn’t say anything about being Snow White…
Snow White
Then what role would you want to play?
Isn’t it obvious?
Snow White
Bang
The Huntsman!
You really want that role, huh?
Anyway, maybe reading the script would help.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah. What was Snow White about again?
In a nutshell!
Snow White
No way.
There’s a kiss in the last scene?!
No.
Haruka hasn’t even agreed to be Snow White, yet...
Although she wouldn’t make a bad prince either...
Hey!
Big Sis
Wait. That’s not it!
What’s wrong, Onee-chan?
Oh, nothing.
Who will you play as, Haruka?
Me?
If Yuu-chan’s playing the Witch, then...
I was thinking of playing the Queen’s attendant,
the Huntsman or the Prince.
I wanted to play as the Huntsman.
Isn’t there another role you’d be suited to?
Does that mean...
growl
Is she saying she won’t accept me as Yuu-chan’s attendant?!
I think you’d be great as Snow White.
No, I think you would be great as Snow White…
I wouldn’t fit the role...
That’s not true at all.
No, you won’t know until you try it out.
Oh, great idea.
...what?
Okay, let’s start with Snow White taking a bite from the Witch’s poisoned apple.
Hold on!
Oh, yeah. Who was the Witch again?
I forgot we had two Witches...
Let’s go with another scene.
Then let’s do the scene where the Prince wakes up Snow White.
Wait, we can do the apple scene...
Haruka, you’ll be the Prince.
Okay.
Snow White
She fell down!
Is this what they call method acting?!
Snow White
Why did it have to be with Haruka again?
Even if it’s just an act,
to pretend kiss with Haruka...
Snow White
No, I  did say I was gonna do it.
It wouldn’t be sightly for me to back out now!
Snow White
Big Sis
Get it over with, already!
Aren’t you having fun...
Snow White
Huh?
President Mitsuki isn’t moving a muscle.
Could it be she doesn’t know this is just a recital?
Snow White
Oh, right. I don’t think anyone mentioned that.
What should I do?
W-What should—
Snow White
If you’re gonna do it then hurry up!
O-Okay!
Anyway, I’ll just go along with President Mitsuki.
Snow White
And tell her it’s a recital later.
O-Ow!
Snow White
Why did you do that, Yuu-chan?
Onee-chan.
Snow White
Onee-chan! Get up!
How long do you plan on lying down?
What?
It’s just a recital, so stand up!
Uh... Reci—
You should’ve told me that sooner!
Sakura Trick
After
School
Misato West High School
Behold, Haruka.
I’m now the Witch.
I’m glad President Mitsuki is joining us in Snow White.
Yuu-chan seems really happy about it.
Did you see that?
It was really witch-like, right?
Why weren’t you watching?!
How’s this, huh?!
This is what you get for not watching.
Sorry! I’m sorry!
I’ll pay attention this time, so take it off!
I-It’s not what you think!
Hey pretty girl want some apples?!
Do it normally!
I’ll have some of Yuu-chan’s apples, though.
I guess I have no choice.
Big Sis
The Witch, the Apple, and the Big Sister
End
A Slice of Shizuku’s Day
This is a service scene.
Extra
A Slice of Shizuku’s Day
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
the time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we share
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
if we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
if we split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
memories to come… let’s make them
ippai ni shichaou ne
we’ll make lots and lots
love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
the miracle of us meeting in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
it had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
it’s something we can’t do alone
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Why do you tie your hair, Shizuku-chan?
Because it can make a cute impression...
But I think you’re much cuter with your hair let down.
R-Really?
I’m 100% sure!
So please let your hair down from now on!
Could it be you don’t like there being another twin-tailed girl on the show?
T-That’s not true at all!
Look me in the eyes!
Next time, Trick 6.
Culture Festival - Overnight Version
Culture Festival - the Real Deal
“Culture Festival - Overnight Version” and “Culture Festival - the Real Deal”
See you then!
You’re trying to trick me!