Is that Satoru?
No...
Who is it?
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
I stopped and looked back at the never-ending days with a sigh
Finally I realized my memories would fade into nothing
And a small part of my heart has been grieving since
I can't let it slip away again
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
Or I'll never be able to tell you on that day
That I regret everything that's happened around me since
Another tomorrow became today as I waited for you
Each day tears another hole in me
It has to be you
ERASED
Morning.
Mornin'.
What're you doing up already?
What, you ask? Isn't that obvious?
You're going to school early again, ain'tcha?
Yeah...
Let's eat.
Slow down. What's the rush?
Can I just come straight out and ask you somethin'?
Go ahead.
What're you doin' this early, and with whom?
That's a secret.
It's not somethin' bad, I hope?
Nope.
All right, then.
I'm off—
Hold up.
Take this.
With such an early start,
you'll get hungry before lunch.
Got it.
Thanks, Ma.
Morning, Hinazuki.
Morning, Satoru.
Here, breakfast.
Isn't that yours?
I'm good. I already ate.
Whoa.
Sorry, Kayo. You must be bored here.
If only there was a TV or something.
It's all right.
Hiromi brought me lots of books yesterday.
I'm sure it'll all be over in a day or two, so hang in there.
'Kay.
That was great.
I'll see you after school, then.
Izumi
Elementary
School
Crap!
The Izumi kids are coming in droves!
I guess I wasted too much time.
I don't wanna give the farewell speech at the graduation ceremony.
What? Really?
Why me? You're better at public speaking, Aya.
Don't worry. I know you can do it, Saki.
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Nakanishi Aya
Izumi Elementary School
Grade 5 Class 1
Whip up your courage and give it a shot.
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
Kayo's absent again, huh?
Have you heard anythin', Fujinuma?
Nah. I dropped by her place
this morning, but nobody answered.
What happened to her? Think she caught a cold?
Dunno, but it's weird that the school hasn't been informed.
What's going on?
Doesn't her mom usually call?
Hinazuki sure is out a lot.
Wish I could just take off like that.
Well, knowing Kayo, she might just show up out of the blue later.
Shall we begin class?
Okay...
Aww, I hate math!
Staff Room
Oh, so you stopped by her place again today?
You must be worried.
Yeah.
And yet you seem to be taking it in stride.
Like you always say:
At times like these, you need to
keep calm and carry on as usual.
Attaboy.
Anyway, I called Kayo's house yesterday and today, but nobody answered.
I even called her mother's workplace, but they said she hadn't come in.
Mr. Yashiro!
Could you call the police or the Child Welfare Center?
The police?
Well, wouldn't it cause a certain someone trouble if I called them now?
I contacted Child Welfare yesterday.
They said they were going today.
I'll be visiting Kayo's place with them, too.
If we want to eliminate the root cause, we'll probably have to start there.
And I can't turn tail after giving you the
"Whatever you do, always give it your all" spiel.
Thanks, Mr. Yashiro!
So Yashiro was already acting to help her!
Yes!
Ms. Hinazuki?
We're from Ishikari City Hall.
No answer, huh?
The lights are on, so somebody must be home.
Let's go around back and check.
Ms. Hinazuki, are you home?
Kayo?
Excuse me.
Mr. Yashiro!
It's all right.
I'll take full responsibility.
The girl's apparently been missing for three whole days.
Let him do what he wants.
The lights are on, and so's the heater.
The fresh remains of a meal for one...
And Kayo's coat is gone.
At the very least, the mother was here until just now.
She must have escaped out the balcony the moment we rang the bell.
Rats. We were hoping we could at least take the girl into protective custody.
Let's come back tomorrow morning.
The mother probably ran out in her nightwear.
She's sure to come back once we leave.
I'm worried about the daughter.
We could ask the police to look for the mother.
No, Kayo's probably fine.
I have an inkling as to what might be up with her.
If you say so.
Let's take a step back and let the mother settle down.
The Child Welfare Center visited the house.
Mr. Yashiro was with them.
Hinazuki's mom wasn't home.
I'm sure things will be settled tonight or tomorrow.
Kayo, they'll separate you from your mother.
Nothing could make me happier.
Hinazuki Kayo being taken into protective custody would also mean her parting from us.
I'll be fine.
Thinking about you will give me warmth and strength.
Satoru.
It's a bit late,
but this is your birthday present.
Here.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Thank you.
I get the feeling...
that I've been waiting for this moment forever.
I never thought you'd be so easily moved, Satoru.
Huh?
Oh yeah, Satoru. Stay with me tonight.
She's got guts!
Not like that.
Nothing really happened,
but someone came here late last night.
I was really scared.
Security? Night watch? A school employee?
Any other possibilities?
Maybe someone came here to hide their porn mags.
It was an adult.
He kicked that cardboard box.
I think he was mad about something.
Shall we take a look inside?
Hopefully it really is just porn mags.
What is this?
I alone realized instantly what those things were for.
Izumi
Elementary
School
And it finally hit me that the serial killer's second victim,
Nakanishi Aya, went to Izumi Elementary School.
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
Nakanishi Aya
Sugita Hiromi
Hinazuki Kayo
We still hadn't broken free from the vicious circle of the past.
Spi
ral
Episode 8
March 2nd.
At some point between 10PM and 11PM,
Hinazuki Kayo disappeared from the storage shed at her home.
The rubber boot footprints found nearby
matched boots found at the Shiratori home.
The killer took her to a commercial freezer,
where he used a spray to speed up her death.
He then returned her body to the shed before sunrise.
This bus isn't safe.
It's right in the center of the circle.
We should leave here at once.
I guess.
While we'd love for someone to find Hina,
this stuff seems dangerous.
Yeah.
What if some pervert found her?
Satoru, do you have a Plan B?
I do.
Okay.
Let's get outta here, then.
It's the killer's footprint. Remember it.
What's that black powder?
Briquettes...
Don't tell me this belongs to the killer too?
Damn it all!
Satoru, that stuff doesn't matter now.
Oh, right.
Yeah. Losing my head won't do me any good.
All right. That should do it.
Too bad. It was a good hideout.
Not when people show up late at night, it isn't.
Yeah.
Right now, I should distance Hinazuki from the case,
even if I have to push my luck.
Child Welfare has sprung into action.
Our actions are definitely changing the future.
This will work. For sure.
Fujinuma
Satoru...
This is your Plan B?
Yep. Simple, right?
Let's dig deep and take another step.
We're attacking head-on after all that?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
G-Good evening.
Explain yourself, Satoru.
I didn't give up on her. So here we are.
I'm proud of you kids.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Though I also had a feeling I'd get yelled at first.
I said that out loud.
Why would I ever yell at you for this?
You did it to help a friend.
I've been meaning to ask for a while, but this aroma...
I figured you'd be home soon,
but I didn't know how many guests you'd bring,
so I decided to go with curry.
So she knew all along.
You three should stop standin' on ceremony and join us for dinner too.
Thank you.
We'll take you up on that.
What were you gonna do with all this curry if nobody came?
Well, people can live on curry for days.
Um, here.
Thank you.
It was delicious.
Well, leave it to me to clean up this mess.
Oh, and I'm not talking about the dinner table.
We know.
Laters.
Hello? This is Fujinuma Satoru's mother speaking.
Mr. Yashiro, Satoru and Kayo came back to our place.
Really? That's great!
I thought as much.
Will Kayo really have to be sent to an orphanage somewhere?
Well...
I've got an idea of sorts on how to deal with that.
No, we couldn't meet with Kayo's mother.
On that note, Ms. Fujinuma, I have a favor to ask of you.
Got it.
Tomorrow at seven, then.
You can spend the night here, Kayo.
'Kay.
Hello.
Sorry for calling so late.
I'm Yashiro Gaku, a teacher at Mikoto Elementary.
I'd like to speak to you about Kayo.
He's called Wonder Guy. Isn't he cool?
One of you go ahead and take a bath.
You first.
Okay, but...
Wanna take one with me, then?
Want me to wash your hair, Kayo?
I can do it myself.
Come on.
Are you feeling itchy anywhere, ma'am?
Here? Or maybe...
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Here? Or here?
You're twenty-nine years old! Get a hold of yourself!
You'll catch a cold if you don't dry your hair.
Y-You seemed to be having fun in there.
Yeah. It was really warm.
That so?
Huh?
Those pajamas...
Oh, I bought them in advance.
She's a demon.
Use this bed sheet. It's been washed.
Okay.
Satoru, you're too sloppy.
Pull that end more.
This is like a school trip.
Speaking of which, the night view from Mt. Hakodate is something else, isn't it?
What're you talkin' about?
You've never even been to Hakodate!
C-Crap!
Uh, I saw it in photographs.
All right, I'm turnin' off the lights.
Okay.
What is it?
We don't use a nightlight at my place.
Oh, should I turn it off, then?
Nah, it's all right.
Let's leave it on.
I guess.
Thank you.
Night.
Good night.
Am I gettin' in the way here?
Yeah.
O-Of course not!
Who actually says "yeah"?!
I said that out—
What was that for?!
Shut it!
For heaven's sake.
Stop it!
No can do!
What are you, stupid?
Morning.
Mornin'!
Satoru, Kayo! Eat up while it's still hot!
Okay...
Let's eat.
Wait, what about the curry?
Savin' it as your dinner for the foreseeable future.
There was enough for a half-dozen people!
You could just invite your friends over again.
Hinazuki Kayo
Grade 5 Class 4
To hell...
Mom...
Kayo!
Where were you these past few days?!
You little...
You two!
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory