Absent-Choinded
Absent-Choinded!
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
#1
Choi in the
bath
Are you doing well, my prince?
I'm fine.
I sometimes get homesick,
but coming here makes me feel better.
Usa Bath
Every date with the number five in it is Ladies' Day. We get fifty percent off.
So that's why you called all of us.
Yup!
It's been a while since I last came to a bathhouse.
Same here.
You've gotten used to this, right, Choi?
Indeed!
A bathhouse expert, eh?
Unfortunately, I've yet to reach such levels of familiarity.
But I do know that we must be wary of a trap.
A trap?
The baths feel so good you get dizzy after a while!
Can you even call that a trap?
You should all be careful!
S-Sure thing.
This feels so good!
Really warms you up, doesn't it?
Huh? Where's Kanna?
I have no problems floating in a bath.
Choi
What's wrong, Choi?
I was thinking about the island I came from.
Oh, is that so...
That
so
The climate's warm there, right?
Yeah.
But I'm having a lot of fun here thanks to you all.
You should stay forever.
Become a part of Tamako's family.
Then you'll be my little sister and Anko's big sister.
Little and big?!
That sounds fun.
And you can just go to school from there.
So does that.
We can be mochi makers together in the future!
And that!
I think you'd make a good florist too.
Wait, she might have something she wants to do.
What would you like to be?
I...
Welcome!
Being a fishmonger sounds good too.
Come on in!
I've got the best fish lined up for ya.
And I bet owning a coffee and record shop is great.
Fortune-telling is a lot like coffee.
It feels sweet at times
and bitter at others.
I can't choose!
You don't have to take it that seriously.
All right.
We should be getting out soon.
Okay.
That was a good swim.
What about you, Choi?
I'd like some more time to think.
You sure you won't get dizzy?
I'll be fine!
I could also be a butcher or open a shop that sells tofu or toys.
But what I want most...
Oh no!
I'm starting to get dizzy!
Absent-Choinded!
Absent-Choinded