My mother went through the trouble of getting me these tickets but...
I need three of them to participate in the drawing.
Yes, you got forth place!
I think I have one here.
Nice, Aoi!
Voila!
I'll leave it to you.
But...
Don't worry.
In case you win anything, I'll be taking half.
Okay!
Subaru, do you have anything coming up after our exams are over?
Nope, nothing in particular.
Ah, right, there's something next week...
There's the field trip with Tomoka and the others.
Huh?
It just so happens to be during our break, too.
I still have a lot I wanted to teach them.
They really learn well at that age.
I want to teach my students, too.
Being the fifth-graders' coach, I can absolutely relate to you.
By the way, where are Tomoka and the others going for their field trip?
If I'm not mistaken, they're going to Kyoto for two days.
I see. Kyoto, hm..?
C-Congratulations!
You've won the grand prize! You get a ticket to an autumn vacation in Kyoto for two!
Whaaaaat?!
Clothes...
Facial cream...
Carsickness medicine...
Nail clippers...
Sewing kit...
Stomach meds...
Eye meds...
Painkillers...
Huh? What happened to my band-aids?!
Argh, now I have to start over!
Prez, this is the fifth time already...
I know you're pumped for the trip with Sensei, but...
No-Not at all! It's just...
I just won by coincidence...
And we'd agreed to split the winnings...
Prez, I honestly congratulate you!
What?
The two of us have perpared a little gift for you.
A-A gift? You shouldn't have...
I beg of you, please accept it!
It's just thanks for taking care of us.
Souno... Shouji... Thank you.
I wonder what this is.
A-Are these...
P-P-P-PA-PA-PA-PA-PANTIES?!
Success!
Hey, gals! Are you prepared for the trip?
But of course. Rather than that, are you ready for the field trip?
Naturally!
I checked the luggage five times! It's perfect!
But I was surprised.
Who'd have thought that Hasegawa-san and Aoi-san go to Kyoto the same day, too?
Oh~! This has to be fate!
"Fate", you say...
Subaru said he'd meet us during free time.
Where are we going to go?
Oh~! As long as I'm with Onii-chan, anywhere is fine.
I can't wait!
Let's make tons of wonderful memories, shall we?
Yay!
Here.
Thanks.
Look, Mount Fuji.
It's beautiful!
Uh, y-yeah.
What's up?
Your face is red.
You got a fever?
D-D-D-D-Don't worry, it's nothing.
You think so? Well, okay.
But still, what a piece of luck that I was be with you back there.
Huh?
If it wasn't for you...
I'm sure I'd have lost.
S-Subaru...
You're thinking so much about me...
Of course, there's no one but you in my heart.
Subaru...
Subaru, I...
If I went on a trip with another girl, her parents definitely wouldn't let us.
But since you're my childhood friend, yours trust me.
I couldn't have gone with anyone else.
Pretty much...
What should we check out first?
Maybe I should ask Tomoka and the others...
Sure, it's nice with everyone, but I want to be alone with you...
Did you say something?
Nothing at all.
Okay.
Subaru-san! Aoi-san!
Thank you both for waiting!
Well then, where should we go?
Let's go to the Kiyomizu temple!
We'll jump off the stage!
Oh~! I haven't done that yet!
Don't do anything dangerous!
Amazing! It's so high!
That's dangerous, Maho-chan!
Onii-chan, I'm gonna to fly!
No flying allowed.
Subaru, let's take a picture!
This is..?
They let you borrow costumes and backgrounds from the Genji story and take commemorative videos.
That sounds great, fantastic! Let's do that!
Suba... G-Genji-sama...
Tomo... Murasaki no Ue...
Verily, ye look beautiful.
N-Nay...
Subarun! Nay, I mean, Genji-don!
'tis I, Yuugao!
Hikari no Kimi, endly we meet.
Good evening, Genji no Kimi.
Onii-chan! I am your wife!
TL note: Pucelle is an archaic expression that refers to young, virgin women.
Magnificent! What splendid pucelles!
Pucelles?! What the hell are you saying, Subaru?!
It can't be helped, it says so right here in the script.
Huh?
By the way, you look pretty good in those clothes.
W-What are you saying?
Y-You, too, Subaru... You look c—
C-C-C-Cool?
Subaru, you look cool! They totally fit you!
Really?
Yes, of course!
I'm sure the Hikaru Genji was someone as great as you.
You look excellent!
Oh~! Onii-chan is a hottie!
Come to think of it, Hikaru Genji raised girls of the age of ten to his liking...
Subaru, too?
Wow, what's this?
We're there.
We just have to stop here.
Youjiya..?
Children's house?!
Shubaru-san, I'm a child!
Child! I'm a child!
Me too!
Me three!
Onii-chan, I'm a child!
Who should I pick?
Subaru! No! Stop! Not here!
TL note: 幼児 (Youji) means "child",
but the homophone 楊枝 means "toothpick". This is a pun, laugh.
You know, Dad's in Hawaii and he wanted me to send him some toothpicks...
Can't I?
Who'd have thought we'd be staying in the same hotel...
What a coincidence.
Sure is...
Why are you guys here as well?!
It's nothing more than coincidence.
I kind of doubt that.
Don't do anything weird.
As if!
The hotel's fully booked, so I guess we'll have to live with one room.
Then again, we're on a couple's trip, so a double room is to be expected.
Aoi...
Y-Yes?!
Go ahead and take a shower first.
Huh?
I can't wait to get in the bath.
Takenaka, let's check out the hotel!
Yeah.
Sure!
Girls, wait up!
Hey, you dropped this!
Hey, Takenaka, what's holding you?
N-Nothing, really.
S-S-S-Shower..?
We've been walking all day and got pretty sweaty, no?
I'll go get some drinks.
P-P-P-P-P—
What am I supposed to do with these..?
Wear them and win!
Good luck!
No, no! No way! Too embarrassing!
I'm back!
What am I supposed to do..?
What do I do with these panties?!
I can't fall asleep here!
Huh? You had trouble sleeping, too?
Yeah... Too many things going through my head...
Wait, "Too"?
I see, I see, you too.
You were worried, too.
I'll get some tea.
Oh, thanks.
Return the panties you took last night.
Onii-chan!
Good morning.
Onii-chan, you look scary...
No... Good morning, everyone!
We kept waiting for you to play with us in our room!
You have to come over tonight, okay?
Hey, what was that supposed to mean? Explain yourself.
Exactly what I said.
You picked up Maho's panties last night. Tonight, you're going to return them.
How exactly do you know that?
Rather, why do you know they're Maho's?!
Su~barun!
I saw Maho drop them.
Then why the hell didn't you return them right then and there?!
I wanted to! But a friend called me and I had to hide them!
I get it.
But why did you make me take those panties up?!
I've been through this already!
You asshole!
When you hid them in your shirt, you lost the right to lecture me!
I'll help you out! Tonight, we're returning Maho's panties!
I'm the one helping you! You picked them up in the first place!
I'm heading out for a bit.
Ah, alright.
Right now, the girls are in the bath.
We'll take this opportunity to sneak into their room and put them back.
Miho-nee?
Watano-sensei?
What are you guys doing?
Planning to peek into the baths?
No!
We're talking about basketball practice and stuff, right?
You basketball fanatics sure never change.
Ah well, better than doing dirty things to Aoi.
Subaru's a safe person like me, you know?
What part of you is safe?
I brought lots of things to play with you, Mihoshi-san.
Let's have fun together nice and slow.
Hey, Subaru, if I ever become a murderer...
I'll leave my sister in your care.
Hang in there, Miho-nee.
We just wasted a lot of time!
Hey, do you even have her panties?
Yep, right here.
Do you want them?
No, I'll pass.
The panties!
What are you doing, you moron?!
Just wait right here.
Hurry up, man.
What?!
What's up?
Tomoka...
Hey!
The girls' bath is over there!
W-What did you say?!
The water feels good...
Yeah, we were walking around a lot, after all.
Yay! Hot springs, hot springs, outdoors!
Whoo!
Hinata-chan?
What?! Don't peek, definitely don't peek, I won't forgive you if you do!
I know.
But just where did my panties go?
Maybe Natsuhi took them like he did a while ago?
What nonsense are you on about? Maho must've dropped them somewhere.
The field trip's over tomorrow, isn't it?
It was fun!
These two days sure went by at lightning speed.
There's still tonight!
Subaru's going to play with us!
We'll make even more great memories!
Oh~! I want to make memories with Onii-chan!
Subaru-san... I wonder what you're doing right now...
Just a little bit further...
One way or another, I retrieved them.
We wasted so much time... They're back already!
It can't be helped. We'll go play with them in their room, find an opening and return the panties.
Will this improvised plan even work?
Leave it to me.
Welcome, Subaru!
Huh? Natsuhi's here, too?
I'm not here because I want to!
Hey! What are you doing?! We're not here for a pillow fight!
I know.
I'll create an opening.
Subaru-san...
Can't put up with it anymore?
A battle is a battle. We won't let you off the hook so easily.
Oh~! Don't be shy!
Hasegawa-san!
A floater!
A no-look pass?!
Go!
Subaru-san, nice shot.
Oh~! That was cool!
Yep.
But this is a pillow fight.
You really do love basketball, don't you?
You got me.
I'm back!
Ao...i?
Hey, Prez, how was our gift?
Naturally, you won, right?
Huh? You feel like dying?
I'm sure he's got the wrong idea...
He must think I usually wear something this perverted...
I prepared myself so much, too...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I just wanted to try them on, nothing more!
I'm really sorry! Please forgive me!
I want to die...
Don't die, Prez! Wasn't that a huge success?
Come back! Earth to Aoi!
Aoi, here.
What's that?
A present for you because you coach the fifth-grade team.
Can I really have this?
Sure. Thanks a lot for everything.
Let's keep going.
Oh, it just can't be helped.
(This seems to be an OVA/recap episode coming up, we won't release subs for that.
By the way, we're recruiting typesetters.)