Here I go.
You can do it, Ruth-san.
Right.
Lottery Drawing
Congratulations!
You win the grand prize.
You get to enjoy a seaside resort and a hot springs!
Tsuzure-Ya
A voucher for a well-established inn!
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Swimming and Plots?!
We get to go to a hot spring together?!
Yes, we can take six people in total.
It also sounds like
we can visit the ocean.
What do you think about inviting everyone?
But...
I'm not sure about these people...
Your Highness,
I think it's sometimes best to
forget your daily struggles
and refresh yourself.
Y-You're the one who won the voucher.
Why don't you decide?
Thank you, Your Highness.
Yay! I want to go to the hot springs!
Don't you, Koutarou?!
Y-Yeah.
I don't have any objections.
Hot springs!
The beach!
Yay!
Thank you, Ruth-san!
I'm going, too.
Magical girls need to rest sometimes, too.
But, only six people can go, right?
Oh no...
I don't think we're going to
have any problems with seven.
Hm?
Sanae is a ghost, so no
one can see her but us.
Way to go, Sis!
You're so smart!
I see.
I'm a ghost.
I totally forgot.
All's well that ends well.
We can all go.
Thank you!
It's nice to get out once in a while.
I guess we can call
a ceasefire for now.
We should start getting ready for the trip.
Yeah.
So, this is how Earth sells their swimsuits.
There's a lot of them, huh?
There's a sale bin!
I kind of want a new one, too.
There's so many. I don't know what to pick.
Yeah, this'll be difficult.
I hope there's a swimsuit
that'll look good on me.
Bounce, bounce.
Bounce, bounce!
Let's go, Ruth.
How about this?
I don't think it quite fits.
She's flat, that's not going to work.
It's vital that a strategist knows herself.
Bounce, bounce.
Your Highness, how about this one?
It's kind of plain.
You think so?
I like the simplicity.
R-Really?
No one will notice your flat chest.
I think it suits you, as well.
Ruth, let's go to the dressing room.
Right now!
Right.
I'll head there, too.
Me, as well.
Don't leave me behind!
Girls have a lot going on.
Oh yeah, Sanae.
What about you?
I'm fine.
I have one from a long time ago.
Huh?
Really?
Yeah.
I see.
I definitely want to see it, then.
Huh?
You like that swimsuit, right?
Just you wait!
Just one question.
Why are we in a spaceship if
we're going to a hot spring?
Impressed, Neanderthal?
Hey! If you have a ship this big, why
are you trying to invade my house?!
That's apples and oranges!
Your Highness, the gate is ready.
Good work.
That's a gate?
Yes, if you go through here,
we'll be able to go directly to the inn.
Her Highness recommended it.
She said we'd be able to
save some money this way.
I see.
I wanted to show you just how
great Fortorthen technology is.
Thanks, Tulip.
It's not like I really cared about how
much money some Neanderthal had...
You're acting like such an adult now!
You stayed the same height, though.
Just go already!
Tsuzure-Ya
This...
It's really...
"Well-established," maybe?
More like "ancient."
Definitely an antique.
Just say it's run-down.
It'll be pretty hard to
have seven people in here.
We've measured it!
It's the same size as the
room at Corona House!
When you subtract the
furniture and other items,
"Other Items"
you get 11/12ths of that of usable space.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault!
We're fine with hot springs and the beach!
Right, Tulip?!
Th-That's right, Ruth.
But, there's someone else
in this room with us.
You can't mean—
Let's go home!
It's okay!
Everyone relax!
I thought this might happen!
What's with all this stuff?
Someone at Corona House
left all this stuff behind.
They might be kind of old, but...
Well, they're more about the mood.
Sorry about that.
Hey, watch it!
Are you trying to get rid of me, too?!
Get rid of you?
I couldn't get rid of you with
something like this, anyway.
What was that?!
Hey. You know I have these?
My grandma gave them to me.
Don't like it? Try to haunt me, or something!
Hey!
Those two are like kids.
They act like they're in elementary school.
Let's head to the beach.
Yeah, let's go, Ruth.
Right.
There we go.
Hm? Satomi-kun, right?
Oh, the cosplayers...
Uh, you all...
aren't planning on swimming, are you?
We're having a club meet-up while
taking a bit of a vacation this summer.
It's almost time for summer's big event,
so we're planning to
focus on making costumes.
We invited Nijino-san, but
she said she was busy.
Yurika?
Yeah, she's new, but she
shows a lot of promise.
I see.
But, what a coincidence.
Sakuraba-san is here at the beach, too.
Huh? Sakuraba-senpai's here?
She has a summer house near here.
Rich people have it nice.
She's cute, great at knitting...
It makes me want to get her
for the Cosplay Society.
You and your plots.
Yep.
Anyway, we have to begin fitting our
outfits, so we'll talk to you later.
Well...
Hm?
Take care of Yurika for me, okay?
Of course.
She'll be great with a little work.
I won't let her go.
See you.
They really care about Yurika.
That was pretty heavy.
Wow, look at them!
Are they models, or something?
Hey, Koutarou, we're here!
I'm so cute, you're struck
speechless, aren't you?
I'll permit your gazes for today only.
Tell me how elegant I am!
I...
Ruth, there's no reason to be embarrassed.
You should hold your chest high.
Everyone's been looking at us
Yurika
How is it, Satomi-kun?
You get six cute girls all to yourself.
Huh?
Sakuraba-senpai...
Satomi-kun...
Are we being ignored?
How dare you, Harumi Sakuraba!?
She'll be tough.
She completely stole the spotlight.
She looks great.
In this case...
Um, Satomi-kun?
Oh, so you're here.
Hm? What's wrong?
You Neanderthal!
Jerk
How did it come to this?
It's because you don't try to
understand women's feelings.
Um, could you help me?
Oh, should I?
You sure are a tease today.
That's because something good happened.
I guess I'm in a cheerful mood.
Hm?
Here I go, Theia-chan!
Ruth!
Wonderful, Your Highness!
Finish, Sanae!
Leave it to me!
Sanae-chan Miracle Attack!
We had a lot of fun.
Should we head back?
Yeah. I'll bet Koutarou-the-jerk
learned his lesson, too.
It seems burying him wasn't enough.
Seems that way.
They look like they're having a great time.
Don't worry.
I've already taken measures.
That was heavy.
Sis got this for us.
Huh? For us?
So, will Koutarou's head split first,
or will it be the watermelon?
You can't be...
Now, Koutarou.
Let's have fun together.
No!
So much fun...
This is going better than I thought.
Theia-dono, a little to the left.
Right there.
Go right forward.
Go for it!
Hey, you guys!
Not you, too, Ruth-san!
You're trying to get her to
hit my head, aren't you?!
Are you sure about this?
Satomi-kun's going to get...
It's fine.
Satomi's pretty tough.
I guess I missed.
Tulip..
If it's that bad,
how about getting up out of the sand?
Well, it's my turn next!
Hm?
Hey, behind you!
What are you saying?
You're not going to trick us with that.
No!
Behind you! There's weird guys!
Weird guys?
Now!
Get them!
Sanae!
Your Highness!
What are you doing?
You brutes!
We're not anyone weird.
Y-Yeah! We're not really interested in normal girls.
That's pretty strange!
So you're after little girls, then?
You perverts...
Divine Punishment!
Damn it.
They're strong.
Who are they?
Bro, the tide's coming in.
Hot Spring of the Gods
I feel better already.
I had fun today.
I guess there were those perverts,
but I got to see Sakuraba-senpai.
Everyone else was getting
along pretty well, too.
I have to prove myself as
a worthy successor in order
to protect my mother, the current Empress.
So, you want apartment 106
to help protect your mother.
That's right.
I can't give it up.
I see.
I guess that's similar to my situation.
I have to wait for my mother
and father in that room.
It'd be terrible if they came
back and I wasn't there.
You can't back down, either, then.
Me, too!
I-I'm not lying.
I owe someone my life, and that's
why I need that apartment.
How about you tell us about it, Yurika?
I'm acting as a magical girl for that person.
They were hurt badly trying to save me.
So, I can't quit.
It's dangerous,
and I'd end up causing trouble for my family,
so I can't visit them.
I'm lonely, but...
That person was in the same boat.
I can't step down because I need the
people of the Earth to prosper again.
Also, there was a roller coaster.
Roller coaster?
Yeah.
When I was young, I went up to the land once.
I didn't get to ride on it.
I've always wanted to try it out.
Talking everything over with you all...
I guess everyone has their own reasons.
Well, this is a pickle.
Not really. I'm going to win.
I'm not going down that easy.
Me, neither.
Hm?
I'm glad we came here.
This is mine!
I won't let anyone have it.
S-Satomi-sama!
Satomi-sama is...
H-He can't...
I...
I found this tree.
I won't let you have it, Makkenji.
If you want your own beetle,
you'll have to find your own tree.
B-Beetle?
Just a little further...
Satomi-sama...
Are you confusing me for a
tree with a beetle in it?
I got it!
It wasn't me you wanted...
My beetle.
Satomi-sama, you jerk!
I'm sorry!
You Neanderthal.
You're the worst.
Hey, Sanae...
Huh?
You know that I roll around all
the time when I sleep, right?
Yeah, but...
I've never had you cling
onto me before, though.
Well, you are a ghost, so...
You like beetles more than
girls, anyway, right?
Just stop and think about this!
I know I was dreaming,
but it was an eight-centimeter beetle!
I just had to catch it!
Big beetles are what men dream of.
You couldn't hope for something
better during the summer.
A beetle...
Don't you guys think so?
Ruth-san?
Satomi-sama, do you really like
beetles that much more than me?!
I don't think I'll be able to go
back to the room for a while.
Hm?
Kiriha-san?
You're out for a night stroll, too?
No... I kind of ran away,
or maybe got what I deserved...
Hm?
Kiriha-san, what's that card?
Doesn't really fit me, huh?
I know, but I just can't get rid of it.
Jeez, that Koutarou.
I got this from someone
I liked a long time ago.
I haven't been able to see them since, but...
You miss them?
Yeah.
I do.
I'm not sure what I'd do if
I saw them again, though.
What is he doing—
All right...
I came to get you!
Sanae!
Are you okay?!
Why do you have that?
Huh?
Do you just not want me around?
Sanae?
I guess so...
I mean, who'd want a ghost
haunting their house?
No one wants that, right?
What are you—
It's fine.
I get it.
It's my fault for thinking
you were different!
Hey!
Hey, what's wrong, Sanae?!
Sanae!
Nothing seems to go right.
Not for me, or Sanae.
We lost today because we
took them too lightly.
They were really cute—
no, I mean, they were strong.
Yeah, they were.
But, we have this trump card.
Bro, you're not planning
on using these, are you?
Yeah, we're getting what we want tomorrow.
Time to eat.
Hey, Sanae.
You know, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
It's not like you to be upset this long.
I'm just an evil spirit.
It's not surprising you'd keep
your grandma's charms with you at all times—
You don't have to say it like that!
I'm a ghost!
I just want to get rid of you!
We'll never get along!
You and I are—
enemies!
Yeah, we are enemies.
That's right.
You're right, we'll always be enemies!
Sanae-chan!
Koutarou, you jerk.
Men
Women
Cold Ramen
When you play table tennis,
you're supposed to say "saa!"
"Saa," right?
Let's try it!
That was hard.
Next Episode: Precious Charms
Yeah, it was.