The universe stretches out infinitely.
Fumizuki Academy is a
prep school created to ensure
that its students could survive
fiercely competitive entrance exams.
In other words, it is a training
school for academic warriors
who fight using academic
performance as their weapon.
Putting their class' prestige on the line,
they fight by making maximal
use of the subjects they are good at
and overrun their enemy's strategic facilities.
Those with power win accolades,
and receive praise and the right
to enjoy an elegant school life.
Those without ability fall mercilessly
and are forced to live an unspeakable hell.
This is the story of academic warriors
who stand up to such a cruel fate.
And here is what happened to
the losers of a Summoner Test War.
Even after my student discount,
a movie ticket costs 1000 yen!
A medium Coke is 300 yen!
A small popcorn is 400 yen!
And all that only lasts 2 hours?!
How frightening these movie theaters are!
Yoshii...
Wh... What is it, Himeji?
Would you like... to see this one?
Oh I see, that looks good.
Let's see this one, Aki.
R-Really? Then don't worry
about me. You two go see it.
--What?! Why?!
--What?! Why is that?!
Then do you want to see an anime?
No, it's not like that.
Just give it up, Akihisa.
Men are... powerless.
Y-Yuuji...
Yuuji, which one would you like to see?
I wanna be free soon.
Then, Apocalypse Now Redux.
Hey, wait! That lasts 3 hours and 23 minutes!
We'll watch it twice.
That's longer than all
the day's classes combined!
Since I can't see you during
classes, I'm making up for lost time.
Definitely going home!
Today... I won't let you.
Wh-What, Shouko?!
What's that?! What?! Ah! Hey...!
Two student tickets for
the next two showings.
Okay! So one student
and one unconscious student
to watch it twice for no good reason, right?
What a happy couple.
Don't you just adore couples like that?
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
Akihisa Yoshii. His parents
are working overseas.
His older sister is studying abroad
and does not live at home, either.
So he was fully enjoying
a carefree life living alone.
I guess for breakfast...
I should eat light so I can have
a bigger meal for dinner, right?
Hmm... I'll eat this one for breakfast
and eat the slightly bigger one for dinner!
He was fully enjoying it.
Ah... Good morning, Mr. Fukuhara.
Ah, good morning.
Ow, ow, ow...
Ah!
You're Yoshii from Class F!
If I remember correctly,
you're Kubo from Class A?
That's right! I'm Year 2's
No. 2 student, Toshimitsu Kubo!
Oh no. I'd better hurry up or I won't
have time to prepare for the first class!
Well then...
--Hey!
--What is it?
That... you don't need that?
No... I guess not, since
it can't be eaten any more.
Can I have it?
What? You don't mind?
No, I don't mind.
To think that he wants
something I took a bite out of...
I-If I pick it up within
30 seconds, it'll be fine.
I... I do mind.
What?! Why?!
You're too bold.
Others are... watching.
I see... That's true.
Then... see you some other time.
O-Okay.
Now!
Hm?
Oh? Did I step on something?
Yes... my lifeline.
Ah, good morning, Himeji!
Huh?! G-Good morning, Yoshii.
Is that... a love letter
to give to Yuuji after all?
But Yuuji's got Kirishima, so...
Hey! You're early for a change, Akihisa.
Ah...
How was yesterday?
This month's food budget disappeared
into the darkness of the
movie theater in no time.
How about you?
When I woke up, it was a scene
where a buffalo tied to a pole was killed.
Huh?
I tried to find a chance to run,
but I got an electric shock
again and became unconscious...
And when I woke up, the buffalo was again...
So you guys really watched it twice.
If I try to run again, I might
lose consciousness again...
I was seized by this compulsive
idea and thought I might forever wake to
the scene where they kill the buffalo,
so I became unable to run any more.
So you'll never be able to see
the first part of the movie, huh?
Ahh... More importantly...
how am I gonna survive until I get
money from my parents next time?
You can sell that mountain
of video games you have.
I can't believe you said that!
Those are irreplaceable, excellent works!
How could I ever exchange
them for something like food?!
Do you know the saying,
"You reap what you sow"?
You can say that because
you still have breathing room!
In my case, it's a life-or-death situation!
Akihisa...
Do you really think that my life isn't at risk?
Sorry...
That's okay.
I never thought... that our equipment
would get worse than that. This is...
Hm?
all your fault!
Complaining about the outcome
of everyone working together?
What an unrefined guy you are.
You lost all by yourself!
What're you saying, Aki?!
Hm?
You're not in a position to talk, are you?!
Neither of us were any help
at all in the war, you know.
Yeah, true...
Lady Minami, too, had poor judgment
so Hideyoshi's older sister was...
--My skull feels like it's about
to split! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
--What's with this "Lady" Minami?! Are you mocking me?
--My skull feels like it's about to split! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
--But you told me to call you that! Hey! Ow!
--Call me just Minami!
Minami had poor judgment so... Ow, ow,
ow...! You're gonna shatter my temples!
This technique... is no fun.
But he was the key to our strategy
and yet he couldn't get 100%
in an elementary school level test!
You shouldn't blame Sakamoto.
What's the problem? I like... this classroom...
I knew it... Himeji really likes Yuuji...
...because in this classroom,
I can sit anywhere I want.
Ding-dang-dong...!
All right, then! Time for homeroom.
Everyone, have a seat!
Oh, you're all sitting, huh?!
Oh? Why are you here, Mr. Nishimura?
Since you guys are so stupid, we
wanted to bring up your scores a little.
So, it was decided that I,
the one in charge of remedial classes,
will replace Mr. Fukuhara as Class F
homeroom teacher starting today!
What?!
And it was also decided
that I'll be the narrator.
What?!
Iron Man is our homeroom teacher?!
I'll mercilessly and vigorously put you
through the wringer. So be prepared!
Ahh...
Now it's like every day is
a remedial class by a demon.
Yeah. I wonder if there's
something that can be done about it.
Oh yeah! All we have to do is fight
in a Summoner Test War again and win!
That's not possible.
Why?!
Once a class loses, the rules forbid
them to declare a war for three months.
Three...!
Well, three months will pass in no time.
We'll come up with a new
strategy in the meantime.
Ahh! Why is this happening?!
There are good things, too.
Hm?
500 yen per pic.
Deal!
--Thanks, as always!
--Whoa! This is an original pic! The Round Card Girl!
--What about your food budget?
What're you worried about?
"Secret Photo Album, Vol. 3"
"2-F Akihisa Yoshii"
I'm a man! I have no regrets!
What a brave man.
Now it's certain that I'll have one cup
noodle per day until I get more money.
Akihisa... Aren't you forgetting something?
What?
Oh, there you are!
Hey, Aki. When and where
should we meet up this weekend?
Meet... up?
Don't tell me you forgot about it.
You promised to treat me to crepes, right?
What?! D-Didn't treating you yesterday cover it?
Yesterday is yesterday. Promise is promise!
May I join you?
What?! You too, Himeji?!
To tell you the truth, there's a
movie I want to see with you, Yoshii.
M... My... food budget...!
Idiot Test!
Now, the weekend after
the new narrator started...
Cup noodle artisans start working early.
That one's for dinner and this one is...
Ah?!
First, I cut it in half and eat one half.
Then next time, I cut the
remaining half in half and eat one half.
And then, the next time, too, I cut that
in half and eat one half. If I keep doing it...
I can eat one cup noodle forever! I might be...
a genius...
He was fully enjoying it in a lot of ways.
Even so, I can't waste money, can I?
Wait! When you think about it,
isn't going out for movies or
having crepes with girls... a date?
That's right. This is a date!
It's not a punishment!
If that's the case, spending a little money
shouldn't be a problem at all, right?
Ah! Himeji!
Ah... That's...!
I knew it... It's a punishment.
What're you doing, Aki?
Hm?
I was being beaten
down by the absurdity of life.
Yoshii?!
Good morning, Mizuki! That outfit is cute.
Thank you very much.
But I spent so much time picking
an outfit that I was almost late.
I couldn't make up my mind what
to wear, either, until just earlier.
I'm glad that I can still
wear the shirt from last year.
I see. In other words,
since last year, you haven't...
My knees are about to be twisted in a wrong...
Hey, I didn't say anything yet!
--I know what you were going to say, so what's the problem?!
--Ow, ow, ow...! Rope! Rope!
Whoa! Almost...! Almost...! Almost...!
What's Muttsulini doing here?
Independent training.
What would you like to see, Yoshii?
You can pick today.
Me?!
They all cost the same, right?
Then maybe a longer one is a better deal?
What do you wanna see, Yuuji?
Will my wish... be granted?
Then, War and Peace.
Hey, that lasts 7 hours and 4 minutes!
We'll watch it twice.
There's no way I can keep
sitting for 14 hours and 8 minutes!
If you get bored... you
can take a nap next to me.
--You mean lose consciousness, right?!
--Don't worry. I'll be with you the whole time so it's the same.
Two student tickets for the next two showings.
Okay! So one student and
one unconscious student again
to watch it twice for no good reason, right?
I envy those who can openly
express their feeling to others.
Don't you just adore couples like that?
I'll pick a shorter one.
Are you sure you're not eating, Aki?
This is good.
W-Well, actually, I'm particular
about food and crepes are not for me.
"Someone who'd try to eat bread
off the ground would say that?"
I have to save even a little here or
I'll have no money to buy food tomorrow.
"You should just be honest and
tell them you don't have money."
I see... My banana crepe
is a little too much for me
so I wanted you to help me.
What?
I wanted you to have a bite of
my strawberry crepe, too, but...
What?!
If you don't like crepes...
Right. Sorry.
Stupid me! Why did I have to do that?!
"See, I told you..."
My chance for a mouth-to-mouth
crepe from Himeji was...
"Well, this isn't that kind of game, is it?"
At the least, with just that one bite,
I could've gotten more
calories than my breakfast.
Why don't you try just a little?
What?
This is good.
I-If you insist...
Y-Yoshii! Have mine, too!
What?! Mine's first!
I don't think it's a matter of who goes first!
Now, open your mouth.
No! Honey!
This is terrible!
To think that you give your sweet, sweet crepe
to that filthy domestic animal with
the fork that you put in your mouth!
I can't let it happen!
In order for this pig to no longer
get carried away and behave rudely...
Er... a pig?
I'll bring him to justice right here right now!
What?! Me?!
"Theory of English Grammar"
Ahh! Out of my way! Out of my way!
"Bam!"
Ahh! The crepes are...!
It hasn't been 30 seconds yet...
Hold it, you pig!
Stop it, Miharu!
Please wait for me, everyone!
Yoshii... You made my face dirty...
"Sarukashira Park"
What did I do to deserve this?
She's special, so...
Special?!
Oh, Akihisa! What're you doing?
Hideyoshi! This way!
Ahh! What's going on?!
You pig! Where'd you go?!
Get your scent on my honey
and I'll burn you to death immediately!
--Where'd you go?! That way?! This way?!
--Wh-Why are you avoiding me, too?!
Well, she said she'd burn me to death, so...
I don't know what's going on,
--but are you guys running away from someone?
--That way?! This way?!
--Yeah. Is there a good way to run away from her?
--Or... this way?! This way?! This way?! Which way?!
I wish I could at least use my Avatar...
--We can't use the summoning system outside of academy premises.
--You pig! You jerk!
Yeah.
That's right. I happen to have an
outfit from my drama club with me.
--Why don't you put this on as a disguise?
--You pig! You pig! You pig!
Disguise?
Hey, it's not a guy's outfit?
The club members said it was for me,
so I just assumed that it was a guy's outfit.
There's no way an outfit for
you would be guy's clothes!
He somehow looks really cute.
What's this sense of defeat I'm feeling?
This isn't good.
There you are!
Stop resisting and...
What's with that appearance?
Don't ask! It's hard to answer.
That's filthy! How impure!
If you think that dressing like a girl is
all it takes to get my honey to like you,
you're dead wrong!
Well, it's you who's dead wrong.
Like normal girls, I like guys!
How dare you profane my sacred
relationship with my honey, you pig!
I'll never forgive you!
What'd I do?!
Looks like it backfired.
Well, there is a bright side...
What do we do? She's still chasing us!
We're out of options.
Let's split into three and run!
Doesn't that mean that
I'll become her only target?!
Oh yeah! I've got an idea!
Let's escape to Fumizuki Academy!
To the Academy?!
Oh, I see!
I found a teacher!
Ms. Takeuchi teaches modern Japanese.
I won't be any help at all.
This isn't the time to be picky!
Ms. Takeuchi! We'd like
to fight a mock ST War.
What? Oh, okay. I approve.
Okay! I'm summoning my Avatar... Summon!
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
I'm summoning my Avatar...
Summon!
Ah! How mean! Are you
trying to hinder my love?!
Summon!
As long as we have Himeji's
Avatar, there's nothing to fear.
We can win!
Shimizu, I'm sorry!
Not so easy!
What?! Me?!
No way!
"Mizuki, Minami, Akihisa Win"
Those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
What?! Today's a holiday!
To me, even a remedial class by
a demon is heaven if I'm with you!
--I'm with my honey!
--I don't want to!
Yoshii! Have you...
discovered your true self?
Huh?
This is a misunderstanding!
Ahh... I'm exhausted.
Yeah. I wonder if Minami and Shimizu are okay.
Shimizu might be happy being with Minami.
Yoshii... About today... I'm sorry.
What?
We dragged you around...
But I had a lot of fun.
Well... I had fun, too, Himeji.
You really are a kind person, you've
been that way since elementary school.
What?
The time we took the placement test, too...
When I left in the middle of the test,
you talked to the teacher,
saying that giving me zero points
just because I had to leave the
room due to sickness wasn't right.
But he said staying healthy to get
ready for the test is also part of the test...
So it didn't go anywhere.
About the Summoner
Test War the other day, too...
You suggested that for me, right?
What?
Sakamoto told me.
Yuuji did?
I was...
very happy to hear that.
I... see...
Himeji...
Yes?
Uhm... about the letter you
were writing the other day...
Is that... really...
You're talking about this?
This letter is... an unhappy chain letter!
What?!
Did you know...
that if you don't mail it out within
three days, you'll become unhappy?
I didn't have the courage to mail it...
so three days have passed.
Feeling this much pain...
This might really be an
unhappy chain letter like you said.
Hime... ji...
If you like... I can...
No...
Someday for sure... I'll deliver
this to him myself, with my own will!
I see.
Someday... for sure...
Will you give me your support?
Yeah. I'll be praying
that it'll work out for you.
Thank you very much!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
The end of the school day is bliss
If I am to put it into words, "It's really angelic!"
My peace was shattered
by a sudden announcement
Talking about the make up test. "This is Hell!"
While my friends and I were
sharing funny stories, I said,
"There's no way anyone is that stupid"
But the truth is, deep down in my heart
I was shouting, "That was me!"
About that "Monthly Parking"
sign you see in the parking lot
I thought it was the name of a company...
All this time...
Sticking to your idiocy can be cool
Is our common sense nonsense?
We don't need rules in this world
It's dog eat dog food! It's social upheaval!
Look!
The sun that rose from the west is setting
Run home! It's dinner time already.
Let's go home! Let's go home!
Breakfast...
At any rate, he was fully enjoying it.
"Yoshii"
Oh? I wonder what this is.
Let's see... "To Yoshii.
You might be surprised
to receive a letter like this.
But I'm writing this because
I wanted to tell you my true feelings."
This... is... a... love letter?!
"You're always cheerful.
I've come to realize that seeing your
cheerful face makes me feel at ease."
Hey! Whoa!
"One day, I'd like to express my manly
feelings to you. Please accept them.
To my dear Yoshii..." I see...
Hey! "Manly"?!
It's from a guy?!
Hey, Akihisa, who did you get the letter from?
It's gone! The letter is gone!
I had an original photo
that I just bought in it, too!
Oh... well... The sender's
(my) name isn't on it, so...
This is...
Good luck.
Noooo!
On top of that, even an
original photo was enclosed.
Someday...
for sure!
Question 4.
What is described as
"made of spice and all things nice"
in one of the Mother Goose songs?
Curry and rice!
Little girls are not food.
Next episode! "Love, Spices, and Boxed Lunches!"
This will be on the test.