Greater Levitation.
Modifier: Empower!
It is time.
I've had to wait too long, Nijino Yurika.
No, Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika.
You will soon find yourself in unending fear and suffering.
I will erase you.
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
mu
and annoying
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
Like I already told you,
I'm not cosplaying!
An Evil Magical Girl Appears?!
I really am a magical girl.
That's Yurika-chan for you.
You really stick to your guns, don't you?
Sorry, she's always like this.
Satomi-san, not you too!
I keep telling you there are evil magical girls after room 106 at the Corona Apartments!
I'm there to stop them!
I'm really sorry about this.
It's fine.
Please believe me!
Stop by the club room sometime, okay?
We'll just come and take you by
force when we need you, though.
How can I get them to believe me?
Don't worry, Comrade Yurika.
You're one hell of a cosplayer!
Like I keep telling you...
Good morning.
This class is getting another transfer student.
Please introduce yourself.
Maki Aika
My name is Aika Maki.
It's nice to meet you all.
M-Maki-chan!?
Maki-chan! Maki-chan!
I'm glad you made it here!
Wh-What?
Satomi-san, Satomi-san, look!
Maki Aika
This is one of the bad magical girls trying to get that room.
She's in the magical organization
Darkness Rainbow. Her name is Dark Navy-chan.
Maki Aika
What?
I'm surprised you have a friend willing to act out your cosplay story with you.
I want the egg next!
Why won't you believe me?
Maki-chan isn't my friend.
She's an enemy!
Dark Navy is good with magic
that controls dark navy hearts—
You're such a pain.
Don't be like that, Sanae.
Yurika, don't worry about what anyone says.
You're fine the way you are.
Satomi-san...
We have aliens, Earth people, and ghosts.
It's nice to have a normal person around, even if your hobbies are kind of strange.
I'm not normal!
Hey, Koutarou.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm saying you should be your own person.
I see!
Anyway, let's head back to the classroom.
I'm...
I'm going to stay here for a bit longer.
Got it.
Don't be late to class.
That was someone who lives at the magical convergence, wasn't it?
Maki-chan...
Do you think you'll be able to stop us from getting to him, or that room?
I had a feeling we'd have to fight.
Of course we do.
Why do you think I came here?
Also, this argument should've ended centuries ago.
The wound I got from your predecessor, Rainbow Nana, has finally healed.
And now I'm up against a failure like you.
I'm not going to lose.
That's not true!
I'm doing just fine as
Nana-chan's successor.
It's true you've gotten a little smarter.
You're pretending to be a cosplayer,
and telling everyone you're a magical girl.
That wasn't really—
Don't play dumb!
And then you told everyone who I was when I transferred in.
That was pretty underhanded.
You've got it wrong, Maki-chan.
It's not like I planned any of that.
Then are you saying that someone else planned it for you?
Huh?
No, that's not—
You're not going to fool me.
I can see right through you.
This is getting interesting.
Please listen to me, Maki-chan!
Huh?
Club Entry Form
Year 1 Class A
Full Name:
Maki Aika
Club
Cosplay Society
I'm going to join that
Cosplay Society of yours.
Then we'll be the same.
Prepare yourself, Yurika.
Not you too, Maki-chan...
Oh, Yurika-san.
Sakuraba-senpai?
Good timing.
I wanted to ask you something.
harukaze
shopping
district
I-I want to get closer to Satomi-kun.
You're already pretty friendly.
That's not what I meant.
I, uh...
You know... Closer...
Oh...
That's what you meant.
I was hoping Satomi-kun would
stop treating me with kid gloves.
Like how he treats you or Theiamillis-san.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I mean, he's kind of mean sometimes,
and has no problem with hitting you on the head.
But Satomi-kun's never hit me or said anything mean to me.
Bop, bop!
Well, he's never been nice to—
I understand how you feel.
I'll do my best to help you.
Glass Masks
I've read this girls' manga for ten years.
I know how to make someone fall in love.
Thank you, Yurika-san.
So, what do I have to do?
You can start by going on a group date.
Ask Satomi-san to go on a date with you!
A-A date?
I see.
So Sakuraba-senpai likes Satomi-san.
Anyway... I guess now that Maki-chan is here, I'm going to have to fight.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
But I have to.
Nana-san saved my life.
Yurika, fight on! Yurika, fight on!
Then, let's toast to Aika Maki transferring in!
Cheers!
A party for Maki-chan!?
Satomi-san, why did you invite Maki-chan here?
Oh, you're finally back, Yurika.
Welcome back, Yurika-san.
Since someone new transferred in
why not throw her a welcome party?
I already told you.
Maki-chan is after this room.
She'll be able to take all the data she
wants if you just let her waltz in here.
That's your cosplay story, right?
It's not a story!
Please, Satomi-san, if we don't kick Maki-chan out,
we'll have a real problem!
H-Hey, Yurika...
You shouldn't talk to a friend like—
What's going on?
Explain it to me, Yurika.
What's going on with Aika-san?
Well...
So get this, Kou!
They were having a sale on snacks and stuff at the store, and I brought some stuff.
What? Makkenji!?
Rhinoceros Man chocolate, and Rhinoceros Man gum.
We got potato chips, dessert pancakes... Huh?
Rhinoceros beetle... Rhinoceros beetle...
You chose a rhinoceros beetle over me.
Over me!
Take this!
And this!
Ruth-san, calm down!
Let go of me!
Let go of me now!
Satomi-san, I need to talk to you!
We're going to lose room 106 at this rate!
This is a bad time, Yurika!
Hey, Makkenji!
Get rid of those snacks!
R-Right...
Hey!
Ruth-san!
Satomi-san, please listen to me!
We need to kick Maki-chan out right now!
Let it go already, Yurika.
Why not let her stay for today?
You can pretend to be enemies tomorrow.
Yes, I think you're going a little overboard with the whole "kick her out" thing.
Yeah, this party is for her.
Why doesn't...
Why doesn't anyone believe me!?
Y-Yurika!
I don't care anymore!
I don't care what happens anymore!
Y-Yurika...
A date...
Like a real date, right?
But I can't...
Yurika-san?
Sakuraba-senpai...
I try to tell everyone the truth, but no one believes me.
And that's why you're crying here alone?
Even if they don't believe you,
you still care about your friends, right?
That's why you're so sad, right?
I don't know why you're sad exactly, but if you want them to believe you,
you'll just have to continue to do things to try and get them to believe you.
Not with words alone, but actions.
Try to get them to believe me with actions, not just words.
Maki-chan is here, so I can...
Thank you, Sakuraba-senpai!
I'll do my best!
You can do it.
Hey, Yurika.
We're going to school.
Do you feel sick?
That's not it.
But today is...
Just go without me.
Are you sure you're okay?
Does this have to do with what you were trying to tell me yesterday?
Well...
Koutarou, we're going to be late!
I know.
Anyway, Yurika, come to school if you can.
I don't think we need to worry about Yurika,
but just in case, I'm going to leave Korama behind.
Thanks, Korama!
No problem, Karama!
Thanks, Kiriha-san.
Anyway, we're going to get going.
You think we should let them know she'll be absent?
Maybe.
I can't depend on words any longer.
I'm a magical girl,
and I will protect this room.
I want Satomi-san—I want everyone to believe me.
I know Yurika-san said she'd come with me,
but I'm the one who has to ask Satomi-kun out.
Sakuraba Harumi-san, correct?
Wh-Who are you?
You want to do a continuation of the Blue Knight play?
Yes.
The theater club has requested
that we have another play at the beginning of the year...
Well, of course they would.
Anyway, Koutarou, you'll have to practice being a knight again.
Prepare yourself.
Koutarou, everyone else, come here.
Yurika left in her cosplaying outfit!?
That's correct.
She went somewhere after
dressing up like a magical girl.
Did she skip school so she could practice cosplaying?
That would be the natural assumption.
Jeez, and everyone was so worried too.
Sis, what should we do?
I'm tracking her on radar.
I can go after her immediately.
Right.
Korama, follow Yurika—
No.
I'll go.
Korama, tell me where she is.
Your friends won't attack that room while I'm out here with you, right, Maki-chan?
Yes, I promise.
I haven't ever lied to you before, have I?
I guess not. You...
Also, I can deploy a wide-area spell to keep people away from here.
That works to both of our benefits.
Sanctuary Modifier.
Effective Area: Colossal!
Here I come, Rainbow Yurika!
I will definitely win.
I'm going to protect that room!
Energy bolt. Target option: Sidewinder!
Quick Cast,
Multiple Energy Bolt!
Taget option: Spread!
Korama said she'd be around here.
Yeah, this is the right way.
This soy sauce cup ramen smell...
It's definitely Yurika's spirit energy.
Yurika smells like that?
In there!
I'm sure she's in there, Koutarou!
Okay!
S-Sanae?
What is this?
Koutarou, I think there's an invisible wall here.
What?
Yeah right.
Let's go.
Huh?
Why?
Yurika...
Yurika's just a regular cosplayer.
Tiny Memory Flash!
Modifier: Extend Length!
Anti-Magic Shield!
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Right here!
What just happened?
Did you forget?
My magic is the dark navy that
controls people's hearts and minds.
That's right.
You can erase people's
memories for a few seconds.
But if I give up now, I won't be able
to call myself a resident of room 106!
I have to use my actions to get them to believe me!
It seems you've got more courage than before,
but you won't be—
I found her!
Yurika! Aika-san!
Satomi-san!
Sanae-chan!
How did you get past both of our barriers?
Let's leave, Yurika.
Let's go back to school.
You can do your cosplay another time.
Satomi-san...
You're just a normal cosplayer.
You don't have to be here.
That's why...
You still won't listen to me?
I'm a magical girl!
Maki-chan is my enemy.
I'm fighting her right now.
Yurika...
I've figured it out.
Satomi Koutarou.
You're a mage that has evolved all on his own in this world,
and then gave Yurika
knowledge and helped her.
What are you saying, Maki?
You even have a ghost.
No!
They don't have anything to do with this.
Your fight is with me!
That's right.
I don't plan on trying to fight you all at once.
I'll be taking my leave.
But only after I take care of you, Yurika.
Bind Person! Modifier: Double Effect!
Quick Cast, Anti-Magic Shield!
I'll send you to hell, Yurika!
You dispelled it?
No way. Without a staff or an incantation...
Also, what was that white light just now?
Maki-san, just stop already!
I've got no choice.
Sakuraba-senpai!
S-Satomi-kun.
Yurika-san.
Why are you here?
I don't know why either.
M-My body is moving on its own.
I can't do anything.
Stop it, Maki-san!
She has a weak constitution!
Don't get her involved in this!
My, my, it seems like Yurika is not the only one who cares about this girl.
What should we do, Koutarou?
Stone Rain! Modifier: Effective Time Twice!
Satomi-san, watch out!
Quick Cast, Force Field!
The stones are...
Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika, huh?
Huh?
You were always telling me that.
I never believed you.
No, it's more like I didn't want to believe you.
Satomi-san...
Yurika, let's save
Sakuraba-senpai together!
Right!
I'm ending this now, Yurika!
Blast Fireball! Modifier: High Concentrate!
What's that!?
Be careful.
Even if you have protective magic, getting hit by that is dangerous!
We have to hit her first, then!
Yurika, back me up!
Sanae, let's do a pincer attack!
Right!
Don't worry.
I have no intention of aiming at all of you.
Sakuraba-senpai!
Recall, pre-cast teleport.
Yurika!
Yurika-san...
Yu...
Yurika!
akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano koyori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do people
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
Even though each and every time
kizutsuitemo
I end up feeling hurt
koi ni
It's love
koi ni ochiru
I fall helplessly in love
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude miruku tii
Just like a milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude miruku tii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kaken ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake honno tii tongai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end
We're playing the word chain game today!
I'll start.
Clay figure da ho!
Holy crap da ho!
Hoax da ho!
Homunculus da ho!
Homing missile da ho!
The Sun and a Rainbow
Next Episode
Why do they all start with "ho"?
Ho?