Run, hurry up!
Tooru-chan is waiting for you.
Okay.
Are you sure you haven't forgotten anything?
I'm fine.
Be careful!
Yeah. I'm off.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Good morning, Run-chan.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
On Rainy Days, Take A Bath
Yeah? Really?
Huh? I did text you yesterday after dinner...
What? Really?
I didn't get any texts from you.
Run-chan.
Your socks.
I forgot to put the other one on!
How embarrassing.
I might as well go barefoot.
R-R-R-R-
R-Run-chan?
P-P-P-P-
What about your panties?
Even if it's me, how did I not notice?!
How did I not notice?!
Don't kneel down! It'll be visible from the front!
Was it because I was sleepy? For such a petty reason?
Don't worry. Everybody forgets things.
Is this really happening?
Usually not their panties, though.
Tooru. Just then...
Just then, you thought, "but not their panties," right?!
Run-chan! Don't run!
Again, huh? You sure have it tough, Tooru.
I'm sorry, Tooru.
You know, I'm just not a morning person.
When I'm sleepy, I tend to space out.
You think that's the problem?
She's already wearing them.
Yeah, you know...
I just thought, maybe...
That's right! Run!
What's up?
You know the notes from yesterday's afternoon classes...
May I copy them?
Oh! Now that you mention it, didn't you leave early yesterday?
Sure you can. There you go.
Thanks a lot. You're a life saver.
What language is this?
Japanese, obviously!
I got drowsy during class.
So it's not just the mornings!
Is it a bit messy?
N-Not at all!
Thanks.
Ask me if you can't read something.
Thanks!
Hey, Yuuko-chan.
Let me have a look afterwards!
I don't mind. Once you're done, pass it on to Run.
Got it.
There.
Hey.
Nagi, are you nearsighted?
How bad is your vision?
It's 20/20. These glasses are fake.
Why are you wearing fake glasses?
Because if I don't wear these...
...I see things I'd be better off not seeing.
You're... not talking about...
Right now, Yuuko, behind you...
Well, I'm only kidding.
Nooooooo!
Like I said, I'm joking.
You are really fun to tease!
Actually, I am nearsighted.
Cut it out! I can't deal with scary stuff.
You got me as well.
You're a good actress, Nagi-chan.
You should be in the theatre club!
I am in it.
I'm playing a ghost, though.
You're funny...
...or not.
This summer, I have received two or three letters from you.
In them, you wrote, "I want to gather a considerable amount of knowledge in Tokyo."
Ah, I want to go to the toilet.
"Best regards."
Erm, teacher?
What is it?
Erm...
Oh no!
"I want to go to the toilet," would be way too embarrassing to say!
My head hurts.
Yuuko, that's your stomach.
No, I mean...
Teacher, excuse me!
As I'd like to go to the toilet, may I take Yuuko-chan to the infirmary on the way there?
Sure, go ahead.
Run?
Let's go, Yuuko-chan.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Run. You saved me there.
Never mind. I had to go as well.
You're also going to the toilet?
No, actually...
Infirmary.
Run!
Hey, Run, what's wrong with you?
Do you feel ill?
I don't know why, but I feel nauseous.
Maybe I caught something.
I feel sick.
Do we go to the toilet? Or the infirmary?
No, toilet... toilet... to... to...
Oh yeah.
Tooru!
Yuuko-chan. That's not gonna...
Infirmary
Run, hey!
Run, pull yourself together!
Yuuko, are you there?
Tooru! Run suddenly fainted!
And the nurse has the day off. What are we going to do?!
Calm down. How about asking another teacher?
Be quiet, you two.
She'll be fine.
She was just deprived of sleep.
It's raining.
I haven't got an umbrella.
Neither do I.
It was sunny this morning.
It's just a light shower.
Can we make it if we run?
Wait, Tooru. Watch for a second.
I discovered this recently.
I attract the rain.
You don't have to stay there. Come back already!
Yay, now I'm wet.
You sure go overboard.
Who's that?
He's staring at us.
And Run-chan is in such a state right now...
Run-chan.
Let's go over there.
Great.
I'm glad I work at this school.
Hand in the training camp
consent form to your teacher or to Yamada.
Run-chan, we have to dry you off quickly.
There, I'm done!
Tooru, wear this!
Ta-da!
Now you don't need an umbrella!
Isn't this bad at my age?
I'd expect this from an elementary schooler.
Hm. Yeah, you're right.
Dressing alike is a little...
Then one of us can-
That's not my point.
What is this?
What?
Should we go in?
Hey! Nagi-chan! Yuuko-chan!
Stay away from me!
Good grief. I was wondering what you were up to.
Run, you're completely soaked!
My house is nearby. Should we go dry your clothes?
Really? Thanks!
But it's still...
Wow.
Do you think there's somebody here who attracts the rain?
So, what are we going to do?
It's a real downpour, but we could just run through it!
It won't be as scary if all of us get drenched!
If it's just to Nagi's house...
This sucks.
I don't want to get soaked, so I'm calling a taxi.
How unusual for a high schooler!
Do you think it'll stop if we wait?
Unlikely.
Like I said, let's get a tax-
There!
Nagi-chan's place is this way, right?
Hey!
Wait, I'm coming too!
You moron, wait up!
There, there!
Wait, don't leave me behind!
People usually get the blues whenever it rains, but they are so cheerful.
This is youth!
It's falling. It's falling!
Kitou-sensei
Hobby       Poem
Poem
Reality
I'm home.
Excuse me.
Get in already.
I want to take a bath right now.
Huh? My brother is home.
You have a brother, Nagi?
Onii-chan, I have friends over right now, so don't use the bathroom!
Nagi-chan, do you call your brother "Aniki" or "Onii-chan"?
I call him "Aniki"!
So here we are.
Only two people can fit in the bath at the same time.
We're going to split into two groups.
Ready, go.
Rock, paper...
Well, I'll go first with Run then.
Have fun!
Let's get changed then.
There we go.
Now that I think about it, I've never talked to Tooru alone.
What should I do?
Isn't there anything to say to break the silence? Anything?
Yuuko?
Y-Yes!
Let's put something on.
There's a bunch of DVDs.
You're right.
"The True Story of a Scary Urban Legend" or silence,
which would you prefer?
A true dilemma!
All right, put your clothes there.
Sure, right here?
Well then, let's jump in already.
Woah, who are you?
I'm Run, you know.
Yeah, I do know that.
However, bangs sure can change how a person looks.
Who are you?
I'm tired of getting that reaction.
Ah, this feels great.
It's really refreshing.
But we have to get out soon...
You're right. We have to let Tooru and Yuuko-chan in, too.
There's only the two of them in my room now.
You think they'll be all right?
Sure they will.
They get along great.
Yeah, I guess they do...
This is bad! This is bad! And it's not getting any better!
I know! If I close my eyes, it's not scary anymore.
Now I want to scream...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
You can now go and take a...
Hey Yuuko, the bath is free.
Yuuko-chan!
Yuuko-chan?
This is bad! Yuuko-chan!
What happened here?
Phew, that was really scary.
Finally we're having a bath, right, Tooru?
Let's jump in then.
Hey...
Tooru, do you ever get scared when you have to close your eyes as you wash your hair?
When I was little, I couldn't stand shampoo at all.
Shampoo got into my eyes!
What was that for, Tooru?
Where's the shower head?
My eyes, my eyes!
Hey, Yuuko! You're being too noisy!
Stop it already!
Geez...
I thought I was a goner.
My senses are going numb.
Run, look, I can see an oasis.
Nagi, Run!
What are you up to?
Yuuko. How was the water temperature?
More importantly...
More importantly, turn off the heater.
I thought we could dry our clothes.
Delicious.
I feel rejuvenated.
Don't make me worry like that.
They're pretty dry.
I wonder if the rain will stop soon?
Doesn't seem like it yet.
It sure is raining hard.
On rainy days, my hair kinda falls flat.
Mine puffs up, and I can't keep it together at all.
Maybe we have different hair types.
Yuuko-chan, let me touch your hair!
Sure thing.
Woah. Yuuko-chan, your hair is beautiful!
Tooru.
You have no split ends at all, right?
You wanna play?
Of course not!
These clothes are cute, aren't they?
Don't move! I'm doing something important here.
Sure.
What's up with this?
Don't move!
Ah, I lost!
You're going to continue playing?
I'm going to beat Nagi's records.
That's nice of you.
Your nails are quite pretty, Yuuko.
Not at all.
Are you doing something to them?
Nothing in particular.
Well, in that case...
Ta-da!
This feels nice, but it's kinda awkward...
T-Tooru, what are you...
Don't move!
Keep still!
Geez...
What am I supposed to do?
houkago yotei mo nan mo nai shi
We have no plans after school,
It doesn't look like it's stopped yet.
ame ga futteru kara
because it's raining.
It sure is raining hard.
Personally, I like the sound of the rain.
uchi ni shuugou
We gathered at my house,
Yeah?
kimi wa fudan kara sunao ja nai keredo
As usual, you weren't being honest.
Ah, I think I know what you mean.
I know, right?
Nagi-chan, close your eyes and listen too!
kyou wa kitto wakaru hazu
Today will definitely be understood.
Well, no. I don't...
egao ga mitai dake da yo
I just want to see your smile.
sonna tokoro ni kakurenai de ii kara
そんな所にかくれないでいいから
You don't need to hide in a place like that.
motto hora chikazuite
もっとほら近づいて
Come closer to me now.
kimi mo tomodachi da yo
きみも友達だよ
You're my friend too.
korekara nandomo sugiteiku kisetsu mo
これから何度も過ぎていく季節も
How many times have the seasons passed?
zutto hora chikaku ni ite
ずっとほら近くにいて
Come closer to me.
kimi to issho ni itai yo
きみと一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you.
kimi to warattetainda
きみと笑ったいんだ
I want to laugh with you.
Well, you're right. It's not bad.
But somehow, it sounds like a grill.
I'm getting hungry already.
Run-chan.
It's mine.
Again?
See you then. Be careful on your way home.
Sure thing, thanks for the umbrellas.
See you tomorrow!
Thanks for having us over.
See you.
Hey, that umbrella is really cute.
You're right.
It's still pouring.
When's the next train coming?
Onii-chan, you can use the bathroom now.
Ten minutes later
I told you to be careful, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
Everybody, sorry to have kept you waiting!
Next time, at long last, Yutaka and Mipo-rin will be appearing.
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Thinking about it, we've been at it for 15 years.
Yeah, enough reminiscing.
On that note, weren't we supposed to appear in episode 1?
We did appear in the opening, didn't we?
You're right about that.
Next time, on A Channel, "Classmates."
Next Time!
Classmates
Of course, upperclassmen will also be appearing, as well as classmates.