This is it.
This is...
All of you, return to your posts.
It looks like a ball of mercury.
It looks alive.
I need to get this out of here.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
Load it on the truck!
Hurry!
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
The Holy Grail War is facing a great crisis.
It's quite possible that Caster's Master
is behind the Fuyuki City kidnappings.
Thus, in accordance with the emergency provisions I am granted as judge,
I shall temporarily alter the rules of the Grail War.
All Masters are to cease any ongoing combat,
and focus their efforts on Caster instead.
Those who defeat Caster and his Master,
will receive an additional Command Seal as their reward.
These are unused Command Seals, left by the fallen Masters
of past Holy Grail Wars.
They should prove of immeasurable value to all of you.
Once Caster has been annihilated,
we shall resume the Holy Grail War.
If anyone has questions, speak up now.
Of course,
that is limited to those who can speak in human tongues.
Well done, Father.
Now the Masters will all hunt him down.
Five familiars were gathered at the church.
Which means...
Which means that Lord El-Melloi has survived.
Indeed.
And offering a Command Seal as the reward
should entice him,
given that he's already used one.
The same goes for the other Masters, as well...
They'll seek to keep it from the rest,
by claiming it for themselves.
But it also means that any Master who wins the Seal
will gain a formidable advantage.
Naturally, it isn't ideal.
Once Caster's been weakened,
and is on the run from the others,
we'll have Archer deal the final blow.
U-Um...
Is this the Mackenzie residence?
Yes. That is the name of landlord.
Well, then...
Might there be a King of Conquerors, Iskandar, at home?
That would be myself.
Oh... I see.
Could I have your signature on the receipt?
My signature? Very well!
You have my thanks.
Th-Thank you for your business...
How fantastic... Having the entire world mapped across my chest!
Why are you dressed like that?
My package just arrived.
You went outside?
See!
I merely tried out this "Shopping Channel" thing.
I told you not to leave the second floor!
If the residents are not at home,
and you are occupied with your familiar,
then who will answer the door?
I had no choice...
A summon by the Holy Church is a big deal.
Don't be so grouchy.
After seeing Saber last night, I merely came to a realization.
If one wears modern attire,
there should be no issue with going outside.
Hey, wait!
At least put on some pants before you go out!
Oh, leggings...
That's true. Everyone in this land wears them.
Must I?
Yes, you must!
And just to be clear,
I'm definitely not going all the way to town just to buy you XXXL pants.
What?
Boy, would you stand in the way of my triumphant conquest?
Conquest and your pants have nothing,
not even in the slightest, to do with one another!
Before you start planning to screw around outside,
at least go beat one of the other Servants!
Then I'll buy you pants, or anything else you want.
I understand. Very well.
Then you swear that, once I defeat an enemy,
you will buy me pants?
You...
You really want to wear modern clothes and go outside that much?
The King of Knights was doing it.
As a fellow King, I cannot allow myself to be left behind.
I like the design on this shirt.
It is a fitting shirt for a ruler!
And we have to find Caster, too...
What are you doing?
Kiritsugu, can we assume that all the others will chase Caster?
It's a safe bet...
However, we retain the advantage.
Out of whatever madness,
he believes Saber to be his Jeanne d'Arc,
which is to our benefit.
We need only wait for him to come.
Master, that is insufficient.
His misdeeds require punishment.
We should seek him, before the damage spreads further.
Iri, are you versed in the spells that erect barriers throughout this forest?
Yes. That's fine...
But our real problem is the curse on Saber's left hand.
Eighteen hours have passed since your defeat of Kayneth,
but Saber's wound hasn't healed.
Lancer must still live.
Shouldn't we defeat Lancer first,
so we can face Caster at full strength?
That's unnecessary.
You just need to use your knowledge of the area to confuse the enemy,
keeping Saber away from him.
You won't have her fight Caster?
Someone else will deal with them.
Those who hunt Caster will actually make the better targets.
I shall attack from the side and defeat them.
Master, you are...
How cowardly will you prove?!
You mock the Heroic Spirits...
Why do you not allow me to fight?
Do you mean to imply that you cannot trust me,
your own Servant?!
We aren't supposed to fight anyone but Caster, right?
It will be fine.
I distrust the judge this time.
After all, he secretly harbored Assassin's master.
He must be working along with Tohsaka.
We must be wary of him.
That will be all.
Kiritsugu...
If...
If I...
If I were to decide to abandon everything and run...
Iri, would you come with me?
What about Ilya?
She's still at our castle!
I'd return for her,
killing anyone in our way.
And then...
I'd give all I have for you and Ilya! And for no other!
Could we get away?
We can escape! If we go now, we can still...
You're lying.
That's a lie.
You couldn't run away.
You'd never forgive yourself for having abandoned the Holy Grail...
For having failed to save the world.
You would kill yourself,
your first and final accuser.
I'm scared.
He...
Kotomine Kirei is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Kayneth as bait, to draw me out.
He anticipated my actions.
I've already sacrificed you to this conflict,
and I've had to leave Ilya behind.
But the most dangerous of them already pursues me...
The single one I wished never to see!
I won't allow you to fight alone.
I will protect you.
Saber will protect you.
And... Maiya is here, as well.
Kiritsugu?
An enemy attack?
I'm glad Maiya hasn't left yet.
We should be able to ambush them, now.
Iri, find a remote-viewing crystal ball.
There they are.
Irisviel, the enemy attempts to ensnare us.
Those are hostages... I'm certain.
I'll have to go down and save them.
He knows we're watching!
As promised last night,
I, Gilles De Rais, have come for you.
I wish to see you, Jeanne. My beautiful holy virgin...
Irisviel...
You may take your time if you wish.
I have come prepared for a lengthy wait.
Now, children, it's time to play hide-and-seek.
The rules are simple.
You need only stay away from me.
If you can't...
Don't!
Now, then... When I reach one hundred, the chase begins.
Well, Jeanne?
How long do you think it will take me to catch them all?
Saber, defeat Caster!
I shall!
Welcome, Jeanne.
How do you like this horrible sight?
Mortifying, isn't it?
Do you despise me?
I'm sure you must.
I'm sure you'll never forgive me for turning from God's love.
Unhand the child, monster!
Jeanne, if you so dearly wish to rescue him...
Rejoice, child.
God's devout messenger will save you.
It's dangerous here.
Now, run away.
Follow this path, and you'll reach a large castle.
I told you...
That when next we met, I would be prepared.
Very well...
I'm no longer interested in competing with you for the Grail!
Oh, Jeanne...
How noble! How beautiful!
Holy virgin, even God's beauty pales before you!
Caster! I now take up my sword to destroy you!
If only I could use my left hand...
Even Caster's prana isn't infinite.
If she can last until it runs out,
Saber can win, right?
Kiritsugu?
More importantly,
is there still no sign of the other Masters having entered the forest?
Maiya...
Take Iri and flee the castle.
Head in the opposite direction as Saber and Caster.
I can't stay here?
You are no longer safe now that Saber is fighting so far away from you.
Most likely, someone else will have had the same idea.
All right.
What's wrong, Iri?
It appears another has arrived.
How?
Is there no end to his prana?
Impossible.
The source of his prana is...
So that book is your Noble Phantasm?
Just so. My teacher Prelati
gave me the means to command a demonic legion.
What do you think, Jeanne?
It brings back memories, right, Jeanne?
Everything is just as it was then.
Your stately warrior's spirit and noble bearing
prove you to be none other than Jeanne d'Arc!
So why?
Why do you not awaken?
Do you still believe in God's grace?
Even amidst this peril, do you still believe a miracle will save you?
How tragic... Have you forgotten the battle at Compiègne?
Even after having endured that humiliation, do you still remain God's puppet?
Pathetic, Saber.
That swordsmanship is unworthy of the title King of Knights.
Who are you?
Who said you could interfere with my battle?
That is my question, monster.
It will be my lance that takes Saber's life!
My prayer...
My Holy Grail brought her back to life!
She is mine...
Every scrap of flesh, every drop of blood, even her very soul is mine!
Hey, Caster.
I've no interest in your love life.
If you insist on making Saber yours, then do it.
However...
I, Diarmuid, will not allow you
to defeat a crippled Saber!
Lancer, you...
Don't misunderstand, Saber.
My sole order today is that I defeat Caster.
So I believe cooperation to be our best option here.
What do you think?
Just to be clear, Lancer,
I could kill a hundred of those things with just one arm.
If there were but a hundred...
I won't let you get away...
Don't get any ideas, thief!
Fervor Mei Sanguis.
The ninth Archibald family head,
Kayneth El-Melloi has arrived.
Magus of Einzbern,
let us duel for the Grail with our lives and our honor!
You rely on traps?
Have you fallen so low, Einzbern?
Very well.
Then this is no longer a duel, but an extermination.
I see... Automated searchers.
Found you, rat.
Scalp!
Time Alter: Double Accel!
You generated a Reality Marble in your own body to control time and accelerate.
Seems you do know a little magic.
Despite having been trained as a magus, you still rely on despicable tricks.
Know your place and die...
Ire Sanctio!
If he's controlling time within his body, it must put great stress on him.
I've found him.
Now then, how far can you run, as exhausted as you are?
Time Alter: Triple Stagnate.
These things don't have eyes.
If I slow my internal time to a third,
and my heart rate and breath as much as I can...
They shouldn't detect me.
Kayneth!
Fool... It's hopeless!
Episode 7
Evil Forest
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
Maiya, no!
I've shamed myself as a magus!
Tremble... Despair.
Strike! Gae Dearg!
By whose order did you fight?
You're ready. Right, monster?
Next Time:
Magus-Killer