Ah, what a great morning!
Suddenly: without warning.
Quickly: with speed.
Huh? What are you doing?
Preparing for class.
We've been a bit busy lately.
Not to mention our student council work.
So I have to use whatever time I have.
Wow,
no wonder you're the top student!
Intelligence gives a woman beauty.
You'll certainly grow into a fine lady.
Oh, stop it, you're embarrassing me!
Hey!
It's you!
Morning, Ai!
Thank goodness I found you!
Here's your mommy.
Aw, Ai!
What a relief.
The truth is,
I received word that a number of valuable accessories belonging to a Heian princess were discovered.
I'm off to buy them,
so look after Ai for me.
Sure...
Huh?!
W-Wait a minute!
We can't do this!
We have school today!
Hmm...
But there's nobody else I can trust.
Besides,
doesn't she look so happy to be with her mommy?
Aww, so cute!
Bye now!
Wai—
He got us.
What do we do?
Hey, Earth to you two!
Sure you aren't forgetting anyone?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Outrageous!
Ai Goes To School!!
You want us to leave Ai with you two?
We'll take great care of her!
Can you really handle it?
What, you don't trust us?
You think we can't do anything alone?
We didn't mean that...
Then let's call Lance, too.
Hello?
You can make calls?
Davi told us how!
Oh dear...
That sounds difficult.
Can I go?
Of course.
I flew at max speed!
We can handle anything!
Just leave it to us!
You got it!
I can't say no to that passion!
Huh?
Yay!
There!
President!
Listen to me!
The soccer club's bein' total jerks!
Nuh-uh, the baseball club is!
Huh? Quit lyin'!
You first!
You wanna go, punk?
Stop!
Sportsmen shake hands before a match.
Now tell me what you were fighting over.
S-Sure...
So what happened is...
Let's go to the student council room for now.
So, you're disagreeing over who should use the field for morning practice.
Yeah.
Baseball Club Field Usage Schedule
How about you take turns using it and switch every day?
Well...
I guess...
That settles that!
Student Council Room
I don't think anyone will come here before school lets out.
Mana and I are always busy like that during school,
so we'll let you handle this.
We've got it!
I've gotta go!
Well, good luck!
Don't worry!
Ai!
We'll be your daddies for a little bit.
And I'll be your mommy!
She's really is cute!
Ai, wanna go upsy-daisy?
Look, they're playing!
Ai, stop...
Just deal with it.
W-Wait, Ai!
Lance!
Kyupirappa!
Help me!
A-Ai...
Kyupirappa!
Student Council Room
How's Ai doing?
Good, you look happy.
What happened here?
N-Nothing bad!
We were just playing with Ai!
What did you play?
The room looks like a tornado hit it!
Did you get played with?
Isn't it time for her milk?
Charles, if you'd please.
Gotcha!
Charurules!
Huh? What's wrong?
Rikka!
Huh?
Umm, if a baby won't drink its milk,
that could mean... a bunch of different things...
I'm sorry!
I have no clue.
No way!
Ai...
Please...
don't cry.
This is...
A new Lovies was born!
Let's try it out!
Yo! Checka Racka!
It turned into night...
Where'd that Lovies...
Maybe it was created from your feelings?
Exactly!
Lovies come from the love in your heart!
Or so Davi told us!
Huh?! I, uh...
Geez, Rachel!
Don't just hold on to info that important!
We've gotta go!
Keep it up, guys!
Will do!
When she's calmed down,
she looks like an angel!
We should let her sleep for now.
Somebody's coming!
What're you doing?
You're gonna wake Ai up!
Student Council Room
Ai, shh!
Someone'll come!
Is somebody in here?
Be quiet!
Don't run off on us!
Rikka lied!
She said nobody would come!
Well you're one to talk!
She went in there!
Kyupirappa!
Hey!
Don't change your pose!
Why is it moving?!
Stop! Stop it!
And because of that...
All right, that's it for practice!
Right!
Kyupirappa!
Hey, I said practice was over!
Ai, wait!
I wonder if Ai's still asleep.
President!
What's wrong, everyone?
We're haunted!
By ghosts!
Huh?
I was walking by an empty music room,
and then I heard something...
When I peeked inside,
I saw portraits of Beethoven, Chopin, and Mozart
flying with a bucket and singing in chorus!
They were definitely chanting a curse!
I saw a demonic ceremony in the library!
A bunch of books were floating around the room.
Then a mop and some rags
suddenly transformed into pink, blue, and yellow monsters,
and started laughing evilly!
Sharuruu, Keruu, Lansuu!
And the bucket made a "kyupi" sounding groan!
It's signaling the birth of this school's seven mysteries!
This has gotta be...
all their fault.
Mana! Rikka!
Truth is...
Huh?
You lost Ai?!
We're sorry!
Let's start looking!
Yeah!
Baseball Club Field Usage Schedule
Soccer Club Field Usage Schedule
Kyupirappa!
You did this, didn't you?
I was gonna say that!
What was that?
No way in heck am I sharing the field with you punks!
Same here!
We need to use the field more!
Well, we're both weak clubs and first-match losers.
Don't put it like that.
Let's just talk it over again.
Aw, talking it out's a pain.
Who's there?
If you want it, just take it.
I shall grant your desire.
Captain!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
I'm a Selfish too!
Selfish Shot!
Selfish Home Run!
Look!
There are two Selfishes!
And they're fighting?
We've gotta stop them!
Yeah.
Lance, get Alice for us.
Roger that!
Let's go, Charles!
Charles!
Rachel!
Okay!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
Oh poor balls who have lost their love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your hearts race once more!
Soccer!
Baseball!
Shut up!
Children look up to baseball and soccer players!
If you fight over something so petty, you'll let them all down.
Kids care about soccer?
Scores get much higher in baseball, so it's way cooler!
What're you talkin' about?
Soccer is totally cool!
Huh?!
Your matches are too short!
Takin' forever doesn't make it good!
Stop tha— Whoah!
Go berserk, Selfishes!
Build egogy for King Selfish!
Ai's over there!
Ai!
Look out!
Rigid Rosetta Wall!
Self?
I arrived in the nick of time.
Cure Rosetta!
Cure Sword!
I sensed a Selfish's presence, so I came to check.
It doesn't matter if the whole gang's here.
You got a lotta nerve!
Bullet Shot!
You can't use your hands in soccer!
Vanishing Pitch!
No-Spin Shot!
I can't read its trajectory!
They're random, but strong!
We're in the World Cup!
We're in the Major League!
M-Mommy...
It's dangerous, so stay back!
Hey, Ai.
Don't worry.
We'll beat those Selfishes up quick.
And then we'll play together again!
It's time to end this.
Finish those Precures off!
Kyupirappa!
Ai?
We've been...
Given a speed boost!
But...
I'm too fast to stop!
What the heck?
Stop!
Joy and sorrow are two sides of the same coin!
I don't care about your cups or leagues,
but we're gonna play like a team!
Everyone, move exactly as I say!
All right!
We'll do it, Coach Diamond!
Halftime's over, cannon shot!
Now, slide!
Now I'll counter...
with a goal!
Or so it's called.
Self...
Sinker!
Just bunt it!
Got it!
It's a grounder!
Run around! Hurry!
F-Fast!
An inside-the-parker?
What're you so down about?!
Now, just to make sure!
I've got it!
Charles!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love looove!
Frack!
How'd I lose with two of 'em?!
I'm out!
Ai!
But that power she used...
Yes...
Ai may be hiding powers we can't even imagine.
How're the two clubs doing?
They're getting along again.
Today's been exhausting.
That's for sure.
If that guy hadn't asked something so demanding,
none of this mess would have happened.
That's right.
He's gonna be in for it when he gets back.
Don't do that, Ai...
Please leggo of my ear...
Quit complaining...
That's enough for today.
Just leave it to us...
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Wow! Makopi transferred into my school!
It's nice to meet you!
But I'm not used to going to school, so it's tough!
Hey! Don't autograph the test!
Tabloid reporters are gathering outside the school!
Leave it to me!
As the student council secretary,
I'll protect our students' ways of life!
Dokidoki Precure:
The Transfer Student's
A Super Famous Idol!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!