[ROY]
Fullmetal!
He disappeared!
What did you do?!
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Heh heh heh heh...
You need not worry
where he's gone--
you'll be joining him
there yourself soon enough.
What is this...?
What's happening?
It feels like...
It is!
It's just like when we
opened the portal of truth!
Ahhhhhh!
[crash]
[splashes]
Damn!
Bastard!
[splashes]
What are you doing?!
Don't be stupid...!
Stay out of this, dammit!
But I must...
It's my solemn vow...
to make sure you're safe.
[splats]
You know your
automail can't support
this weight for very long...!
Now let go and take
care of the old man!
[LAN FAN]
No... It's too late for him.
Briggs men... help me!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
Right!
Here, King Bradley! Take this!
Ow!!
Arrrgh!
[LING]
Fu!
Get a doctor...!
Someone who knows
how to use alchemy...
Hurry...!
I've got a Philosopher's Stone!
Use all that you want!
Somebody, please...!
Somebody...!
This is Amestris, a major
alchemical power...!
Is there nobody...? Anybody?!
How can that be...?
Tell me why...?
[LAN FAN]
My Lord!
Take that... damn monster...
[LING]
Why this?
I've finally gained immortality,
and I can't save even
one of my subjects...
Damn it!
[coughing]
[HEATH]
Captain!
Captain! Please,
stay with us!
Captain Buccaneer!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 3]
Captain!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 4]
Fire!
[gasping; gunshots firing]
[LING]
Because of you, sir...
Bradley was
dealt a lethal blow.
You made sure Fu's
death was not in vain
Still, I can do nothing for you.
I need more ammo!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 6]
That was the last of it!
I'm out of ammo over here, too!
[FALMAN]
Alright, men. Rifles out.
Sir!
Ling... listen...
Or Greed... whichever...
If you feel like
you owe me one...
then do a small
favor for me...
Our orders...
are to keep this
gate from opening
until we get the all-clear
from our general...
I'm asking you...
to defend it for me.
Surely you can do that...
With your power...
you might be...
the only one who can
do it... So will you?
Greed...
[GREED]
Huh?
I need your power...
Give it to me!
[GREED]
All right...
There's still a little time
left before what I have to do.
Lan Fan, you stay back
and fight with the men here.
Right!
Really...? You'll do it?
Yes... I promise I will.
I am a man of Xing...
and people from Xing...
always keep their word!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 4]
Keep firing!
Who is that?
[LING]
Soldiers! Listen up!
If you don't
want to get hurt...
leave now...!
If you have a
family, go home...!
Oh yeah, and ladies...!
I won't fight women,
I'm not that kinda guy!
What the hell...?!
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 8]
Fire!
[crash]
[explosion]
Amazing... Is that Ling...?
Or... Or is that
the Homunculus?
Lucky for us...
he's on our side.
[coughing]
[HEATH]
Captain? Captain!
[FALMAN] Come on,
Captain, stay with us!
[BUCCANEER]
Did he do it...?
Is he fighting for us
like he said he would?
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5]
Yes sir.
That's good--now I can
kick the bucket in peace.
[HEATH] Don't talk
like that, Captain...!
General Armstrong is
close to victory...!
Hang in there.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5] Captain,
you can't leave us now...!
Your work isn't
done here...!
We still need you!
[BUCCANEER] Well...
I'm afraid the sooty air
of Central doesn't
agree with me.
Farewell to you... comrades...
I'll see you...
on... the other side.
[BUCCANEER]
Someplace magnificent...
even higher than
the summit of Briggs.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5]
Captain Buccaneer!
[MAN 1] That light earlier...
what was it?
[MAN 2]
We've had no reports.
[OLD MAN] There seem to be
some strange happenings
at the Command Center.
[OLD WOMAN] Have there been
any updates from the radio?
[OLD MAN]
No, nothing.
[OLD WOMAN] You've
checked all the stations?
[OLD MAN]
I have, and all they're saying
is that we should
stay in our homes.
[ELICIA]
Mommy!
The radio said
that it's not a good
idea to go out today...
You can go over to
Tabitha's another time...
All right, sweetheart?
[whining]
Ohhh...
We can still watch the
eclipse from here...
Come on, what do
you say, Elicia?
Don't you want to watch
the eclipse with Mommy?
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SIG]
Izumi!
Where are you...?! Izumi?!
Alex... do you know
what's happening?
Hmmm...
Perhaps--I believe the Elric
boys once told me about this.
After their transgression...
Edward described how
numerous strange hands
dragged him through
the portal of truth.
[OLIVIER]
And what is this 'portal'?
That I don't know.
What? Repeat that!
[OLIVIER]
You got through?
Huh?
[BLISS] General...
headquarters is safe.
That's good...
So...
Have they received any
intel concerning Ms. Curtis?
[BLISS]
No.
[OLIVIER]
I see.
Is there anything else?
Yes, Captain Buccaneer
and some of his men...
they fought Fuhrer Bradley...
...trying to defend
the main gate...
And they were all killed.
[BLISS] He was working together
with the forces from Xing.
He inflicted a mortal
wound on Bradley
and pushed him
into the moat.
[EDISON]
Impossible!
No! Impossible!
Impossible...!
I know King Bradley.
He's stronger than that!
He can't be
killed so easily...!
He's superhuman!
Ow!
[OLIVIER]
How's the main gate holding?
They're still defending it...
Are you familiar with the
homunculus known as Greed...?
He's come over to our
side, and he's helping.
One of them helping us?!
That's ridiculous...!
The 'good gentleman'
would never be betrayed
by the Homunculi.
About the captain...
they say he died smiling.
[OLIVIER]
I see...
Well if he indeed died smiling,
then he wouldn't want us
standing here weeping over him.
So, let's go!
[BRIGGS SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[OLIVIER]
Mr. Sig, come with us.
We need to find
your wife, as well.
[screaming]
[thud]
[woman groaning]
[ED]
Teacher!
Ed?!
Are you all right?
Yeah... more or less.
What're you doing here, anyway?
I'd like to know that, too...
So... Do you have
any clue where we are?
[ED] None.... I just
ended up here same as you.
[crash thud]
[ED]
Al!
Al...! Snap out of it...!
[IZUMI] Are the sacrifices
being gathered together?
[thud]
Huh?
[FATHER]
One... two... three...
Four of you are here now...
That still leaves
us one short...
I wonder...
Huh...
Perhaps the fifth is
being created as we speak.
What... what is
that thing...?!
It's a monster!
Hohenheim!
Edward... Oh...
And it would seem he's
caught Alphonse as well...
Ah, and Izumi Curtis.
You'll have to excuse
my sorry appearance.
What is going on here?!
It's not complicated...
Be careful to
mind your place...
I plan to take your
Philosopher's Stone
at my leisure...
but I can speed up the
process if you prefer.
[ED]
Hohenheim...!
What is that hideous thing?!
[HOHENHEIM]
It's a copy of me...
You might know him better
as the one the
Homunculi called "Father."
You're saying this is
that bearded bastard?
Yes, that's right...
I destroyed the leather
bag he was in, but--
[FATHER]
Enough.
I warned you to keep your
mouth closed, Hohenheim.
And now... greetings
to the three of you...
my pretty sacrifices.
Welcome to my castle...
Please, everyone make
yourselves at home.
Al... time to get up...!
Things aren't looking
too good for us.
Hey, Al?
Al... Get up!
Alphonse!
[GOLD-TOOTH] Goodness, the
people up there are unreliable.
Honestly, they
can't even manage
to get five sacrifices
ready for today?
Though... they
did only go after
those who were
stupid enough to take
the bait of something small,
something like immortality.
It's no surprise they
failed to get the job done.
[gunshots]
[ROY]
You bastards! Let her go!
What--?!
[clapping]
[GOLD-TOOTH] All right, good...
Just hold him there.
Here we are...
Colonel Mustang...
I'm afraid we're
out of time...
At this point
you've no choice
but to cooperate with us.
I would like you to perform
some human transmutation
and open a portal for me.
Are you serious?!
[GOLD-TOOTH]
It doesn't matter who.
A parent you've lost...
a lover... a friend...
Or that man you
were so close to...
I forget. What was
his name again...?
Hughes, right?
He'll do just fine...
I'll get things set up
for you right over here...
You mean I'm...
a sacrifice?
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Not yet...
But as soon as you've
opened the portal,
you'll certainly
become one.
[ROY] That's why the
Elric brothers were chosen?
Yes, it is.
[ROY] They told me human
transmutation couldn't be done!
Why would I even try do
it knowing it would fail?!
You're right, there...
but all I really
need you to do
is open the portal
and then return.
No! Not a chance...!
I won't be your puppet...!
You open it yourself!
[GOLD-TOOTH]
I told you...
We have run out of time.
[splash]
[thud]
[ROY]
Lieutenant!
Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
Now then...
maybe you've had a
change of heart...
what say you Mustang?
I'll kill you!
[ROY]
Lieutenant...!
Are you still with me...?
Answer me!
Now... perform
the transmutation
and become the
fifth sacrifice.
Come on...
if you don't hurry,
the Lieutenant will
be lost to you forever.
Ah, I understand...
Would you like to transmute
her after she's already died...?
That would be acceptable.
I'm not gonna die.
What you don't know is...
is that I am under
strict orders not to die.
If it were that easy to obtain
an immortal body, my dear...
it wouldn't be very sporting,
now would it?
[GOLD-TOOTH] So tell me,
Mustang, what will it be...?
Your precious woman
is about to die...
If you don't act,
she'll bleed to death...
All of that blood
right before your eyes.
Luckily, I happen
to be a doctor
who knows the
use of alchemy...
and I have a
Philosopher's Stone
to add to the
bargain as well.
Meaning this: I am able,
with all certainty,
to save this woman's
life--but if you don't make up
your mind in time...
there is nothing I can do.
Whether you like it or not,
her fate is up to you
now, Colonel Mustang...
Do you want her blood
forever on your hands?
She looks so quiet and still...
Perhaps she's dead.
What do you think?
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel... Please...
You don't have to do this...
Don't sacrifice everything...
for my sake...
But you will do it.
Won't you, Mustang?
[GOLD-TOOTH]
Well?
[ROY]
All right.
[NARRATOR] Perhaps, in the end,
there is a silver lining...
but know that it
lasts but a moment...
The ground upon which
you stand may fall out
beneath you at any time.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 59 "Lost Light."
And now... at last...
the end begins...