Tooru!
Want some ice cream?
Oh? She's not here?
Run-chan!
What are you doing in there?
I fell in here while I was sleeping.
I can't move.
Help me.
What are you doing?
I just had an urge to do it.
One more!
Stop...
That's a nice shot!
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Here you go, Tooru.
Let's eat!
It's so good!
Tooru, your bangs got long.
I haven't cut them since summer vacation started.
Should I cut them for you?
Scissors!
With those scissors?!
Yup. Don't move.
Wait! Cut at an angle!
Um... You look a lot younger!
You'd look good with a ransel!
I don't even look like I'm in middle school?!
I can't take this. I can't go to school.
It's summer vacation right now.
We have to go for one day.
It's okay! It's cute!
That's why I don't like it.
Then...
Tie this here, and...
Done!
We match!
We match...
A Midsummer Night's...
Coming!
Good morning.
Morning, Tooru-chan.
Sorry, but Run is still sleeping.
Would you mind waking her up?
Of course not. Sorry to bother you.
Run-chan, we have to go to school today.
Run-chan, let's go to school.
It's summer, but you're still wearing these long sleeves...
I told you that you look cuter in short sleeves...
Run-chan!
Okay. Then...
Okay! I'll take it off! I'll take it off!
It's so hot...
I can't stay awake...
Run-chan! The school isn't that way!
Beware of
Kidnappers!
Oh, no. There are a lot more perverts and kidnappers out during the summer.
They say that some try to lure you into their car.
It's so dangerous lately. We have to be careful.
Hey, it's hot out. Want a ride to school?
Kidnapper?!
Help! It's a pervert!
Why...
A pervert?
Should we call the police?
It's a mistake!
I'm a nurse at their school!
Please don't call the police!
Now I'll pass out these printouts. Pass them on back.
Fill those surveys out by next term.
Okay.
Listen up, everyone.
This is a career consultation survey.
Think about it carefully before next term.
Don't fill it with jokes thinking you're only in your first year.
If you don't think about it, the exams will be right around the corner.
And don't try to escape from reality during the rest of your break. Study hard.
That is all.
See you next term.
Kitou-sensei.
Tooru-san?
Sensei, you don't look well today.
Are you okay?
My...
She's very nice. As expected of one of my students.
Yes. I've just had a slight headache since this morning.
There should be medicine in the nurse's office.
My passion should be enough for this headache.
Oh dear, Kitou-sensei. There you go wearing a lab coat again.
That's my thing. Stop.
That's up to me!
And I've been wearing a lab coat since before you came here!
But lab coats are for school nurses, don't you think?
You need to do something about that weird shirt pattern before you can say that!
What?
Trying to say that I have no sense of style?
Look who's talking, Kitou-sensei.
Then we can have Tooru-san decide!
Fine by me.
Tooru-san?
Uni-chan?
Kitou-sensei, maybe you stepped on Uni-chan?
What did you say?! What about you, Satou-sensei?!
No, must have been you, Kitou-sensei.
No, it was you, Satou-sensei!
No, you.
I'm not that small.
No!
What's that?
Could it be...
an SOS signal?!
It's a first-year classroom! I'm coming for you!
You don't need to go down to clean the erasers like this.
How can you get so dirty from cleaning erasers?
Right?
It's not right.
Fire?!
Um... Senpai?
What are those for?
This reaction... I was too hasty again!
Um...
I'm here to clean!
I want to die.
I'm so sorry, Senpai! This girl is really stupid!
No, that's okay. It was my mistake...
I just got another funny story to tell.
Right, Tooru?
If only I had stopped Yutaka from doing that.
Then I would have spared you this embarrassment.
I'm sorry.
Stop it! Don't apologize!
If you apologize, it's even more embarrassing!
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
She's needs to calm down.
Quiet.
It really looked like an SOS signal!
If you saw it, you'd think there was a fire too!
If there were a fire, there would be smoke pouring out.
You just overreacted.
You need to learn to keep your cool.
Here you go, Nagi-chan.
Hot! Fire!
I mean... it's not good to panic like that.
Run! What are you doing with a hot drink in summer?!
I was in a rush and messed up!
It's so hot!
Nothing good comes out of being hasty.
Yeah.
I couldn't help it in my case!
It would be a disaster if there really were a fire.
Then it's the same for me!
Hot coffee in the middle of summer? Where's the sense in that?
Yeah! They should stop putting hot stuff in vending machines in the summer!
Yeah!
No, that's not the point...
Huh?
Hot-Blooded
Confident
in
her
sense
of
style...
maybe?
What should I do?!
I left my survey sheet at school...
Oh, I know!
Oh, it's Yuuko.
I left my survey sheet at school.
I want to go get it, but I'm too scared to go alone. Come with me.
Oh, come on. I told her not to be hasty.
Why not just leave it until next term?
I don't want to!
I want to fill it out seriously! Please! Come with me!
Oh, come on!
Message Received
Nagi
You sure?
To school at night?
Message Received
Yuuko
Please!!!!
I'm too scared
to go alone!!
You're too scared, you say?
Oh no, I'm late!
Nagi's probably already there...
She's here. Hey!
Oh? Why are you two here?
I called them up.
The front gate isn't open?
We came in through the back.
The back is a pretty long walk...
Yuuko, you'd better sprint all the way here.
Right! Let's go! Start!
Wow, you're so impatient.
Listen, Yuuko. Don't look behind you.
Come on, you guys...
No!
Looks like a new personal record.
Now then, let's get that survey.
Wait... I can't move yet...
Oh, she died.
Hm...
Of course it's locked.
So the staff entrance is locked too?
Guess this won't open it.
What are you trying to unlock it with?
Damn.
The school is really scary at night...
Oh.
Yeah, I just noticed that the window was open.
A bit unsettling, but it's good for us.
It sure is.
Yuuko, don't cling to me like that.
But I can't stay calm if I don't hang on to someone!
Okay, fine.
I'll get the anatomical model from the science room.
No! Don't!
Then get off of me!
No!
That looks like fun.
I don't know about that...
Yuuko, you're such a coward.
But the school is different at night than during the day! It's creepy!
Oh?
What is it?
Hey, we don't usually see the school at night.
How about exploring?
Yeah!
Now, let's go!
To the classroom, let's go, forward march
Wait for me!
Hey everyone, you didn't forget anything, right?
The piano plays, notes ringing through the night
Terrirror-lala, you can't solve those seven mysteries
Say hello to that skeleton dancing by the window
Come on, good man, you're dancing with me tonight!
Come on, let's go! It'll be fun! Just don't look behind you!
See, it's fine! Let's keep going! There's nothing to be scared about!
Hey there, David, Mona Lisa! Let's explore together!
Isn't it exciting being at school at night?
Yeah.
It's too scary...
Um...
What is it?
Bathroom...
Hey!
We're going to the bathroom!
Okay! We'll wait here!
I'm not going into the stall with you, okay?
I know that!
Um... lights...
Make it quick.
Okay.
What is it?
No. Just that.
Get out!
Constipated?
Not that!
We saw a hitodama outside the gymnasium across campus!
Were hitodama the things that come out right when someone dies?
Then we can save them if we put it back in!
What are you saying?!
The hitodama has legs!
Don't move!
I want to see it!
Footsteps...
They'll find us!
A burglar?
Come on!
Oh? Uni-chan?
Oh, it's Satou-sensei.
I got all scared for nothing.
What are you doing at school this late?
We're here to clean.
No!
Oh, you left something here?
Yeah. That's why.
Sensei, why the candle?
Right. I like candles.
I always think, this fleeting flame is just like my life.
Almost like we're one and the same.
Oh, he collapsed.
Acting the metaphor?
He's not moving.
What? He actually collapsed?
He had an attack!
Oh no!
We need to get him to the nurse's office!
Don't pull him face down!
You'll scratch his face!
He's too heavy...
Can we even lift him?
Oh, I know!
We can bring the bed here!
Then what do we do?!
Yuuko and I can take this side. Run, take his legs.
Tooru, fill in where we need it.
Ready?
Yeah!
Okay.
Let's go.
One, two...
He's too heavy!
Oh? He's suddenly lighter.
Run! What about the body?!
Huh?
And there.
Man, I'm tired.
He isn't waking up.
Don't do that...
Sensei, wake up.
Don't hit him...
Serves him right.
Is he awake?
Sensei! Sensei! Wake up!
Sensei! Can you hear me?!
Oh?
Run-chan?
Satou-sensei!
Don't die on me!
Run-chan!
I won't die!
Is he okay?
He said he won't die.
Let's go.
Yeah.
I hope there aren't any dogs...
There won't be!
Man, I'm so tired!
Well, good night!
Good night!
Yuuko-chan!
See you!
Yeah! See you!
Good thing they all came with me.
I completely forgot about it!
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
So I didn't get what I needed, and I got scared to death...
Now I can't sleep...
And at this age, I can't ask to sleep with my parents...
Oh, I know!
It's been a long time since we slept together.
Good night.
Next Episode
Miporin, what do you like about summer festivals?
Well, it has to be the fireworks.
I see.
And then takoyaki, okonomiyaki...
Oh, I like hiyashiame too!
Oh, that's good too!
What do you like, Yutaka?
You see, Yutaka likes eating a ton of—
Wait! One second!
On the next A Channel: Summer Festival
eating a ton of oden at the booths!
Oden in the summer?!