Huh? How to lose weight?
I've never been on a diet.
No way!
- But you're so thin!
- Let's do this.
Yeah.
I guess I have a fast metabolism.
Ooh...
It's genetic...
Lucky you. I'm so jealous.
Kawashima's the center of
the girls' attention now.
Yeah.
If you push yourself too hard,
it'll only build stress.
I think it's best to eat whatever you
want, just in healthy portions.
I can't let that one slide!
One, two!
Huh!? What is this!?
Wh-What is this!?
- Hey! Let me go!
- What the...?
- Take that, and that, and that!
- Teach! She's hiding meat in her gut!
You're only allowed to bring 300
yen worth of meat on field trips!
Is this flab under 300 yen!?
Bananas don't count!
This is for the meat buns!
This is for the fancy ice cream!
This is for the corn dogs!
Divine Fist of the Convenience Store!
High!
Calo—
Rieeeeee!
Dedicated to the Diet Warriors
who are now stardust!
So long!
We pulled off the Divine Fist
of the Convenience Store!
Indeed! Though she proved a formidable foe!
Those little...
A-Are you okay, Ami-chan?
They're so mean.
You poor thing...
Oh, um...
Looks like we're in for a stormy season.
Oh?
So this is how Ami reacts
to that kind of approach.
Huh?
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
True Self
That felt so good.
Your performance was brilliant, Minorin!
It gets pretty intense when
girls take each other on.
As a Diet Warrior, I couldn't
ignore her statement.
The gods of weight loss only smile
upon those willing to face their fat.
I'm sure she'll understand one day.
Right... Is that how it works?
What's with him?
Oh yeah.
Ryuji, want me to make a salad for you?
Y-You can make salad?
They taught us in grade school.
I can even make my own dressing.
You buy lettuce, right?
Separate the leaves, right?
Cut them up, right?
Put them on a plate, right?
And it's all done!
You missed washing the lettuce.
As in, rinsing it under running water.
And what happened to the dressing?
You always nag about tiny
details, like an in-law.
In-law...!
Takasu-kun!
Wh-What is it, Kawashima?
Could you please stay close to me for a bit?
It's that guy...
Hey, Kawashi—
You're...
Hey. How long are you gonna cling to him?
Completely ignoring me while
draping yourself all over him...
- Draping, and draping, and draping...
- U-Uh, Taiga? This is...
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
You sick exhibitionist!
Hey, Kawashima, what was that about?
You don't...know him, do you?
W-Well...
These things tend to happen
when you're a famous model.
Some of the fans can get a little pushy.
I even went through this trouble
of transferring schools...
Hey, are you on your way home?
Uh, yeah...
Could you hide me at your
place for a while?
I'm scared of running into him again.
I see.
Don't worry, I'll handle this.
Between a drafty, wood-framed rental...
and a secure, fancy apartment
complex with automated locks...
Which would you choose?
The fancy apartment!
That settles it.
Then you'll be coming to my place.
What?
Back up.
Why do I have to go to your place?
Fine. I won't force you into anything.
But Ryuji's house is so unprotected
I was able to easily sneak in.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
But it's fine.
It's none of my business anyway.
W-Wait!
Aisaka-san!
I said wait, damn you!
It makes no difference to me.
Here you go.
So sweet!
Ryuji made honey-preserved kumquats.
I mixed the juice with soda.
And way too thick!
Honestly...
You want me to drink this?
And you call yourself a Diet Warrior!
Even your brain is small.
Your transformation is really
something to behold.
I'd love to show our class
how you really are.
I have no intention of ever
revealing my true self.
Really now?
Well, your throat should be in tip-top shape
after drinking honey-preserved kumquats.
You refuse to show them the real you, huh?
In that case, we're going to find out
exactly how fake you can be.
What?
Oh, good morning.
Good morning...
Ka-Kawashima?
You look tired.
Yeah, I still haven't recovered
from yesterday...
Right, that was a pretty scary ordeal.
Not that.
For five hours in Aisaka Taiga's apartment...
No, six...
D-Did Taiga hurt you!?
Jackson...
Uganda...
Uganda?
Falcon...
Akechi Mitsuhide...
Matsumoto Seicho...
Oda Nobunaga singing French pop...
Dazai Osamu swimming the 200
meter individual medley...
- Susano'o, Amaterasu, Uzume...
- Uh, hello?
- Quetzalcoatl, Matthew, Judas...
- You okay, Kawashima?
Yep, I made her perform a
medley of 150 impressions!
It was a riot!
How the heck are you supposed to do
an impression of Akechi Mitsuhide?
I told her I'd kick her
out if she didn't obey.
She was so desperate.
B-Brutal...
Not at all. I appreciate it, Aisaka.
- Kitamura?
- Ki-Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka.
I have a favor to ask.
Huh...?
Ami-chan, you look pale.
Really. Shouldn't you see the nurse?
I'm perfectly fine.
Y-Yo...
Come, dumb Chihuahua.
It's chow time.
Dumb Chihuahua?
That would be you.
Acting all cute while yapping
away, perpetually in heat...
What!?
Just come with me.
This isn't funny.
Why do I have to go with you?
I already have plans with my frien—
Michael Jackson as a tour bus guide.
Mona Lisa making a turn at
200 kilometers an hour.
The Thinker in good spirits.
I've made copies of all the pictures I took.
They might accidentally get leaked.
Hey!
Stop!
Fine. I give.
- I just have to come with you, right? Dammit!
- Um, Ami-chan?
S-Sorry!
I forgot I was supposed to eat
lunch with Aisaka-san today!
I'm really sorry about this!
Hey! Wait up, dammit!
Thanks for the grub!
Thanks for the food.
What the hell is this?
If Ami doesn't drop that facade,
she'll never make real friends.
That's why I want you two, since you
know her true nature, to help her out.
Sounds good in theory, and I don't mind,
but Taiga and Kawashima
clearly don't get along.
Aisaka!
I'm begging you!
You're one of the few girl friends I can ask!
No wa—
What!?
Oh! Thank you, Aisaka!
Damn Kitamura...
Leaving us with this mess and
running off to the student council...
Wh-Whoa!
Your lunch is amazing, Kushieda!
It may seem big, but it's
super low in calories!
These are king oyster mushrooms,
and this here is konjac.
- And this is konjac rice!
- Honestly, why am I here?
Here, Amin.
I'll give you some konbu.
Don't want any!
Pfft, be that way.
Lucky you...
Oh, nothing.
Anyway, time to eat.
Hey...
Why is your lunch exactly the
same as Aisaka-san's?
Seriously, why?
Uh, well...
You see...
Problem solved.
My lunch has egg and other fried food,
while Ryuji's has rice and nori.
Wah! My food!
Here.
Now you have a meatball.
Huh? Oh...
Thanks.
But why do you let Aisaka-san
walk all over you?
D-Do I really?
Ryuji was my dog in his previous life.
A dog is happiest when serving its master.
That's right!
They were destined to be together!
Not a chance.
Jeez, there you go again, Minorin.
Sorry. I was kidding!
Jeez...
Hello!
Attention, please!
Today is the monthly community clean-up
organized by the student council...
However, participation is
a little on the low side.
Do we have any brave volunteers?
Sorry, Kitamura.
Kanoya Supermarket has
a special sale today.
Oh, Takasu! You're willing to lend a hand?
Then get changed and come to the courtyard.
Man...
Why do I have to do this?
I already told you that
I'm going to help, too.
So you say, but you just want to
spend more time with Kitamura.
That's another way to put it.
How honest of you.
Takasu-kun!
I'm coming along too.
Since I just transferred here, I want
to familiarize myself with the school.
Minorin.
As a Diet Warrior, I have no choice but
to support a girl who's desperate...
to excise her excess weight.
I never said I wanted to lose weight.
Let's work hard together, Takasu-kun!
R-Right...
Okay, maggots!
Get fired up and move out!
If I catch anyone slacking off,
there will be consequences!
Easy there, tiger...
Gloves on!?
Trash bags ready!?
Checked your assigned area!?
Yeah!
Don't underestimate this town.
Pathetic efforts will get
you thrown off the boat!
Show me some enthusiasm!
Yeah!
The president sure is one of a kind.
Listen up. I'll explain the program!
First up!
Kitamura-kun ended up going
off with the student council...
Sorry!
Student council members are
taking a different route.
Why am I still here?
Hey, doesn't this piece of trash
look just like Aisaka-san?
In terms of being helplessly small.
Yeah? Well this piece looks just like you.
In terms of being doughy, filthy, and flabby.
Let's go that way, Minorin!
Oh, we eloping?
I'm up for that!
Let's go!
Right on!
Garbage awaits!
They took off...
Guess it's just the two of us now, huh?
Uh...
It's pretty fun to pick up trash.
But maybe it's because I'm with you.
Kawashima, actually...
Hey, let's go this way next.
Look out!
Hey! You okay?
Yuck, this is nasty!
What the hell!?
- Damn it all!
- Ka-Kawashima?
Um...
Oh, that was so scary!
Ick, my shoes are soaked...
No!
- Kawashima!
- No, no, no!
- Don't move!
- Get it off!
- Ow! Don't kick me in the face! Damn...!
- It's climbing up! Noooo!
Okay...
Salvaged!
I-It's okay now.
Look, the frog went home, see?
I'm so sick of this crap!
Ka-Kawashima?
Just kidding.
Was that funny?
It's raining.
Omigod, I'm going to get wet.
We need to find shelter.
Right, Takasu—
You know...
You can stop doing that.
What are you talking about?
I don't get it.
I'm the one who doesn't get it.
Why did you bother participating
in this grueling work?
What don't you get...?
Oh...
Guess you're not falling for this, huh?
I've known you were acting this whole time.
Do you think you could, uh...
Right. Be yourself?
Actually...
I have to keep up this facade.
You don't understand how I feel, do you?
I don't, to be honest...
That's fine.
I'm nothing but an airhead...
Kawashima?
What's wrong!?
Hey! Kawashima!
Hey, what's wrong?
If you're looking for shelter...
Hey! What is it?
That guy is back!
Why?
To tell you the truth...
He's a stalker.
Sta—
Why didn't you tell us!?
Because!
It's so frustrating...
Frustrating?
I didn't want to admit that I was letting
some freak mess up my life.
I had to move because of him.
I didn't want to cause my parents trouble,
so I came here to live with some relatives.
I've even stopped modeling
for the time being.
But after all that...
He's still chased me all the way here.
Hello! Hello!
Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hello!
Odd... They supposedly came this way.
Oh well. Let's go home, Minorin.
Ooh!
I've found a cute, miniature monster!
- Monster?
- She's adorable! It's my lucky day!
Taiga!
Be careful!
I don't recall doing anything to warrant...
being called a monster by someone
as suspicious as you.
Uh-oh...
What is she doing?
That guy's a stalker!
And another thing, who gave you
permission to take pictures?
Do you realize how creepy you are?
Wh-Why shouldn't I?
It's no big deal...
In your dreams.
I'll destroy that camera, and you with it!
Why are you running away!?
Ow!
Wait up!
W-Wait! Taiga!?
- Wait up!
- That idiot...
Why...?
- Taiga, it's dangerous!
- I mean... Isn't she scared?
That guy's twisted.
Kawashima?
Because of him...
I had to take time off work,
move, and transfer schools.
I get so upset, the stress builds,
and then I end up binging on snacks.
Could this mean...
I was defeated by that worthless freak,
and by Aisaka Taiga as well?
Takasu-kun.
You just told me to stop playing nice.
Didn't you?
Y-Yeah...
I guess...
I get it now.
I do.
No more cutesy crap.
No more.
No more, no more, no more,
no more, no more, no more.
- Ka-Kawashima?
- From now on...
I'll live with this nasty
personality of mine!
I refuse to let them have the last laugh!
Hey!
Kawashima...
Kawashima was just incredible after that...
Racing through town with a running
form the track team could never match...
Smashing the already frightened
stalker's camera to bits...
Her transformation left the
stalker scared to death.
And then...
Imposter!
That devilish face!
You're not the Ami-chan I know!
You're no angel! Not with
that nasty personality!
Oh, come on.
I'm still adorable.
So who cares...
what my personality's like?
Kawashima.
Are you okay?
Hey! Kawashima!
I did it, Takasu-kun.
No joke.
But...
I was scared...
Here, this'll warm you up.
Honey-preserved kumquats...
How could you tell?
Taiga loves this stuff.
Taiga...
You call Aisaka-san by her first name.
Do you still think there's
something between us?
She's really lucky.
She's self-centered and a total mess...
But she doesn't try to hide it.
Yet she still has friends.
She still has you.
Takasu-kun, what would you do
if I showed you the real me?
Would you fall for me?
Ka-Ka-Ka—
Kawashima?
Well?
H-Hold on!
I'm...
Taiga, are they there?
Kweh.
Taiga?
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Waterproof and water-repellent.
Slight gradation.
One-touch installation.
How do you like this, Taiga!?
The Bogus-Boobie Force!