Fionn MacCumhaill, hero of Aillen and leader of the Fianna,
and my daughter, Grainné, formally announce their engagement.
Everyone, I want you all to celebrate tonight.
That man with the mole beneath his eye...
What is his name?
He is Diarmuid O'Dyna, a knight of the Fianna.
Diarmuid...
Traitor.
You will pay for this, Diarmuid.
Take me with you...
...and run!
Rejoice, Grainné.
Fionn has recognized our marriage!
Do you really think I forgot about what happened with Grainné?
A dream?
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
The dream I just had...
That was the legend of Diarmuid.
Were they my Servant's memories?
Where am I?
It seems you're awake.
Sola-Ui...
What is this...?
Why am I here?!
You don't remember what happened at all?
I...
I was shot.
I defended myself with Volumen Hydrargyrum, but...
What happened to my body?
There are signs that every Magic Circuit in your body went out of control.
It's a miracle you didn't die instantly.
For now, all I've been able to do is regenerate your organs.
Your Magic Circuits have been completely destroyed.
You'll never use magic again.
I...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too soon to give up.
We haven't lost yet.
Sola-Ui...
If the Grail really is an omnipotent wish-granting device, your complete recovery should be more than possible.
You only need to win.
If you succeed and claim the Grail,
everything will return to how it was.
So...
Okay, Kayneth?
Give me the Command Spells.
I'll take over as Lancer's Master.
In order to bring you the Grail.
N-No!
You don't trust me?
I, who will marry into the Archibald family?
No, but...
Sola-Ui.
Do you really think Lancer would
abandon me and swear fealty to you?
I do.
He is a Heroic Spirit who heeded the Grail's invitation.
He seeks the Grail, just like us.
Even if he has to change Masters, he will accept it to reach his goal.
Sola-Ui!
Lancer isn't as admirable as you think!
Why do you say that?
When I asked him what he'd wish for, he
replied that he doesn't seek the Holy Grail.
A Servant with no desire for the Grail is categorically impossible.
He must be hiding something.
But no matter what he's hiding, he must obey me as long as I bear these Command Spells.
Kayneth...
I won't give you the Command Spells.
Kayneth, you don't seem to understand.
That we must win this, no matter what.
You know, Kayneth.
An unskilled spiritual healer like myself cannot
hope to extract ingrained Command Spells by force.
I can take these without resistance if the bearer agrees with it.
If you won't give me your consent, then I guess I'll have to...
...cut your right arm off.
Well?
Irisviel.
Don't worry.
Magical healing places great stress on the patient.
I think it'll be a while until she wakes up.
Please watch over her for the time being.
You're reporting to Kiritsugu?
I'm sure he's worried, too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
I'd like you to talk to Kiritsugu.
Tell him we must pursue Caster immediately.
Saber...
Leaving Caster at large will only
result in the deaths of more children.
Kiritsugu?
How long until we can use Maiya again?
She won't be able to move for another day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stay here.
I'm going to go after Kayneth.
Wait a minute, Kiritsugu!
Did Saber say that we should go after Caster first?
Looks like I'm right.
Are you mad at Saber for not stopping Lancer?
Iri.
Saving a few, or even a few dozen, children isn't our goal.
Saber probably never doubted that Lancer wouldn't kill me.
But what if Lancer had betrayed her?
The Grail War would've ended for us right then.
There's no need to tell her where I'm going.
Lancer.
Please show yourself.
Sola-Ui-sama, how fares Lord Kayneth?
Not very well.
I've performed the routine treatments, but...
This isn't your fault.
Kayneth brought it upon himself.
It just means the Grail War was too much for him.
No, but...
He isn't worthy of being your Master, Diarmuid.
Kayneth has abandoned the war,
entrusting me with his rights as your Master.
I pledged my loyalty as a knight to Lord Kayneth.
Sola-Ui-sama, I cannot give you my consent.
What?!
To begin with, aren't you a Servant who manifests physically using my mana?
And now I have the Command Spells, too!
Before I am a Servant, I am a knight.
I can only serve but one lord.
Am I not worthy of being your Master?
That's not the issue here-
Look at me when you speak!
Lancer.
Fight with me. Protect me!
Support me.
Win the Holy Grail with me!
I can't.
If Lord Kayneth has abandoned this battle, then I shall seek the Grail no longer.
We need a miracle to heal him!
Only the Grail can make that happen.
If you feel responsible for his current condition...
If you wish to restore Lord El-Melloi's glory to what it used to be...
You must offer the Grail to your lord!
Sola-Ui-sama, you speak as Lord Kayneth's partner and seek the Grail only on his behalf, do you not?
Y-Yes...
Of course!
Will you swear that you have no other desire?
I swear.
As wife to Kayneth El-Melloi, I shall bring him the Grail.
The look in her eyes...
It's the same one Grainné bore.
I harbor no hatred for anyone.
However, fate was simply too cruel.
All I seek from this life is the loyalty denied to me in my last.
I don't want that sad fate to repeat itself, yet...
In my previous life, I threw myself into many battles.
There were times when I had to turn a blind eye to lives lost.
That's why I can understand Kiritsugu's reasoning in this matter.
However, the Holy Grail War has clear rules.
It's supposed to be a proxy war over the Grail by
means of Servants to avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
Is that not the case, Irisviel?
If Lancer's Master and Kiritsugu hadn't
fought in secret, we would've slain Caster.
We wouldn't have to worry about
more innocent children being killed.
Lancer and I could have finished our duel in an honorable fashion.
Is there no chance of Kiritsugu changing his mind?
Believe me when I say this, Saber.
For Kiritsugu and me to make our ideal world a reality, you are absolutely essential.
Man, that drink felt good!
Ooh, thank you.
You need to tell us earlier when you have guests over!
No, no. Don't trouble yourself, ma'am.
There is no better welcome than the simple flavors of home.
My, you're such a flatterer!
We couldn't help but worry about how Waver was doing in school in England.
But if he's made friends with a trustworthy man
like you, then we were worrying over nothing at all!
Nah, I'm the one who's in his debt.
Look, he even picked out and bought these fine pants for me.
So how long will you be in Japan, Alexei?
Oh, I should have my work here wrapped up in a week or so.
If you'd like, why don't you stay here with us?
I'm sure there's enough space for another futon in Waver's room.
Right, Waver?
Futon?
Oh, the bedding the people of this country sleep on?
It probably feels strange to sleep on the floor
instead of in a bed when you're not used to it yet.
That's what's best about visiting foreign lands.
Unknown surprises give me great joy.
No matter the age, Asia always gives me much enjoyment!
You're absolutely right!
I told you... to take spirit form... when you come and go!
But I couldn't have brought this back in spirit form.
I even acquired pants for that purpose.
To begin with, boy...
Didn't you order me to do it?
Why must I, King of Conquerors, go
draw water from some country river?
Because it's way more productive than
eating rice crackers and watching videos.
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Fuyuki
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Harbor
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
New Town, East
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
Mion River
Seichou
Seichou, South
What's this? Are you pretending to be an alchemist?
I'm not pretending.
This is alchemy, idiot.
What on Earth is that?
Spellcasting residue.
Remnants of magic present in the water.
Seichou, South
Fuyuki Harbor
This means someone was using magic near the river.
Seichou, South
Fuyuki Harbor
If we follow the lead, it may give us a clue to the location.
Boy, did you already realize something like that was in the water?
Of course not.
But this city happens to have a river flowing right through its center.
So it's obvious to start by looking at the water.
Rider.
Yatsu Library
Yatsu
Was there anything between these two locations?
An irrigation channel or a drainage pipe, maybe?
Oh! There was one of considerable size.
That's it.
Caster's atelier probably lies at the end of it.
Boy, are you sure you aren't an incredibly talented Mage?
A talented Mage wouldn't do it this way.
It's probably the simplest of methods.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Not in the least!
Using a simple method to accomplish something impressive
far outshines using a complex method to achieve the same thing.
As your Servant, I am proud as well.
All right!
Once we grasp his location, he's all mine.
Hey, boy.
Let's go raid them right now.
Wait a minute, we're going against Caster here.
I know that.
You don't!
His class enjoys the greatest advantage when it comes to territory defense.
Harbor
Fuyuki
What kind of idiot would just go bursting in?
Harbor
Fuyuki
You know, territories can change by the second in battles.
Fail to strike the enemy once you know their location,
and it'll be too late to even regret missing the chance.
Why are you so eager today?
Isn't it obvious?
My Master has finally contributed something of worth.
As a Servant, I must also do my duty and bring back the enemy's head.
Come on, don't give up before we've even started.
Let's just go see what we find.
Things might work out better than you think.
Bullseye!
See? Things did work out!
Caster seems to be away, unfortunately.
Is this some kind of water tank?
Uh, boy...
I think it's better if you don't see this.
What are you talking about?
If Caster isn't here, we should at least search for clues to his whereabouts.
That may be true, but don't do it.
This is too much for you to handle, boy.
Shut up.
Didn't I warn you?
I told you not to look.
Shut up!
Damn it, you're always making fun of me.
Damn it...
This isn't the time for pride, fool.
Nothing wrong with it.
I'd punch anyone who could see this and not bat an eye.
What do you mean you'd punch them, idiot?!
Aren't you standing there looking just fine?
That's because now isn't the time for emotion.
For my Master is in mortal peril!
Assassin?
But that's impossible!
Assassin's supposed to be dead.
This is no time to be surprised, boy.
H-How?
None of that crap matters now.
However, one thing is certain.
Everyone who believed in their demise has been deceived.
Did they... run away?
Don't drop your guard.
Two have been killed, but there were another two.
At this rate, who knows how many Assassins might show up?
This is their preferred terrain.
We should withdraw quickly.
Should we really leave this place as it is?
You might find something if you looked, but let it go.
We'll just destroy everything that we can for now.
If nothing else, it will slow Caster down.
With his hideout in ruins, Caster can no longer run or hide.
He'll have to stumble out into the open.
It won't be long until we put an end to them.
Hey-
I get it!
Quit doing that!
Let's get out of here, boy.
Don't worry about it, Kirei.
Indeed, it was unfortunate that they learned of Assassin's
existence before we could discern the nature of Rider's trump card.
But from this, we now know that Rider's Master is a third-rate Mage.
Had they not been discovered...
Other options would have been available to you?
Yes.
While it's true that your plans are important,
you must remain in control and graceful at all times.
Elegance is required, even in battle.
But I never thought he'd be this boring.
Another chance to discern Rider's trump card will surely come.
Have the Assassins continue to monitor Rider, but ensure they take utmost care in doing so.
Understood, my teacher.
Episode 9
Lord and Vassal
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
You infused too much mana at once.
I'm sure there's something I can do to help!
I can't believe she went to Fuyuki...
This is the magic of the Matou family.
We're just about to start a party.
I can't accomplish anything at this rate!
Next Episode
Rin's Adventure