Pi
ping
Hot
Oden
Soba-Dango
Shiruko
Sweet Sake
Yukine, tend to the shop
when you're done over there.
Okay!
All right.
The oden is ready!
Already working hard this
early in the morning, I see.
Good morning!
Hiyori! Welcome!
So you really have started
working here part-time.
W-Well, you know...
I at least wanna pay back the money I took.
Yukine-kun...
Not even mean old Daikoku
could say no after hearing that.
A lot's happened, but it looks like you've finally been set straight.
I-I guess so...
but it's also because, between me and Yato, someone has to be making money!
Oh, right. Don't you have something you wanted to ask Hiyori-chan, too?
I-I said it doesn't matter anymore!
What is it?
Well, uh...
You're going to be a
high schooler soon, right?
He was hoping he could have your old textbooks and workbooks.
He wants to do the same
stuff everyone else does.
I mean, if you were gonna
throw them away anyway...
Huh?!
Of course! You can have all of them!
What's gotten into you guys?!
Oh, there you are, you two!
Don't forget about the
money you owe me, okay?
Huh?
You asked us to save Yato-chan,
remember, Hiyorin?
We charge this much per request!
Oh, 5 yen?
5 million.
And since we helped twice...
50,000
500,000
5,000,000
7,000,000
8,000,000
9,000,000
10,000,000
10... million...
Don't worry!
You're pretty cute and inexperienced, so I'm sure you can earn it in no time!
Wait, Kofuku.
Hiyori should get a student discount.
Oh, right!
Just 1 million, then!
Sweet! 90 percent off!
That's what I call a steal!
You're bargaining with the god of poverty like it's a walk in the park!
You still haven't fixed my body,
and now you're gonna
throw that debt on me?!
You will help me pay!
What wrestling federation
does she belong to?
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Tenjin!
I'm here to say thanks
for the other day!
It sounds like you had
a tough time, Yato-kun.
Oh? You think so?
Of course!
Why would you ever let
your blight get that bad?
I'm sure you were in
pain long before that.
Sekki has rare,
outstanding strength.
I couldn't give him up just like that.
More than anything, I wanted
to properly reforge him.
I purposely let my condition worsen to give him a wake-up call.
Well, I understand the sentiment, I suppose.
Anyway...
You seriously saved the day!
I'd expect no less from
my former buddy Tomone!
Mayu is a nice yet gutsy girl,
as a matter of fact.
All thanks to a certain
lowlife who took her in.
Well, I am pretty strict.
Oh? So you follow the four Cs rather than the normal three.
Crass. Childish. Crude. Clueless.
This is...
...how he thanks him?
Come. Let us talk over here.
No! Cool, classy, confident, and cultured!
Huh? One of the Regalia is gone.
Miyu-san, is it?
Oh.
Yes, she was kicked out
for stinging Michizane-sama.
She was corrupted?
What happened to you is
actually very contagious, you see.
Just seeing or hearing about it is enough to infect others.
When I grow up please
let me become a school
teacher.
Stinging a master even once
means immediate banishment.
Michizane-sama has always
been strict about this rule.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Harming others or yourself...
is no different from betraying your master who named you.
Revoking your name and sending you away after
an ablution is actually considered a generous act.
Because, if you're lucky,
a new master will take you in.
But, without that mercy...
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
What's done is done.
You mustn't let this bother you.
It would affect Yato-san.
We completely understand
how you were feeling.
Regalia are quickly corrupted if they don't maintain their Borderlines.
Because, ultimately, we're Far Shore beings
who dwell alongside Phantoms, out of sight.
Be careful.
The darkness is always
right there next to you.
Darkness...
Even so, Yato-san refused to abandon you.
You need to swear on your name that
you'll protect your master from now on.
Got it!
I swear on my name "Yuki"!
What?
Nothing.
By the way, Tenjin...
I was hoping you could
give me some advice.
Hm?
It's about Hiyori.
Ever since her accident, she ends up in
her spirit form from time to time, you see.
Ah.
And I accepted her request to fix that.
But I have absolutely
no idea what to do,
so I've been putting it off all this time!
But she's helped me out a few times now,
so I feel it's time to finally
get started on her job!
How pathetic can you be?
Try cutting her ties with you, then.
Huh?
Doing so might just fix
her strange condition.
Cut her ties?
Being connected to you is
pulling her closer to our world.
Try cutting that connection
and see if it has any effect.
That is your specialty.
Regarded with Hate
Chapter
Studying at the library's way better than studying at home.
I know, right?
All right!
Another good day of studying!
We have some important
exams after the new year.
We need to pick a shrine to pray at!
Yeah, can't forget to wish to a god!
I want to graduate, be healthy, be popular, travel safely,
be popular, and for my
family to be in good health!
You wished to be popular twice.
It's that important.
You shouldn't keep the gods busy with too many wishes, you know.
Listening to people's wishes is their job!
Who cares about their schedules?
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of wishes, there's this one god people have been talking about lately.
Oh, yeah. Him.
What's this about?
They say that if you tell him the
name of someone you want gone,
he really will make them disappear for you.
"Rabou-sama, Rabou-sama! I beg of you!"
That's how it goes, right?
Yeah, that's it!
Rabou-sama?
I've never heard of that god.
It's probably just an urban legend.
Yeah.
Huh? Are those textbooks, Hiyori?
Wait, those are our old ones.
What are you doing with them?
I'm giving them to a friend!
Rest Stop
You kids working hard in here?
Daikoku! I'll have a tea snack!
What are you doing here?!
Oh, come on.
Lighten up a little.
I'm letting Yukine use this room! It ain't for you to relax in!
And you can go suck on some tea leaves!
Man...
No good. Do it again.
You're a pretty strict teacher, Hiyori.
It's easy to mess up
these parts. Be careful.
Okay.
Let me see!
The trick to learning this
stuff is visualizing it!
There!
The Pillow Book's Sei Shounagon,
Houjouki's Kamo-no-Choumei,
and Tsurezuregusa's Yoshida Kenkou!
Those are great!
Amazed, are we?
Do you know how long I've been a god—
Quit doodling on my stuff!
Don't refer to my talent as "doodling"!
Then earn some money with that talent!
Man, you always gotta butt in!
Wh-What did you say?!
What?
N-Nothing.
Hiyori!
Could you put the black beans in these?
The street slasher has yet to be found...
Despite being in plain sight...
Still No Clues About Serial Street Slasher
Shimoito City Center District
Yesterday
Scene of the Incident
Okay!
There have been a lot of stories like that on the news lately.
Be careful when you go on your New Year's shrine visit tonight.
I'll be fine.
Serial Street Slashings
Investigation Task Force
to be Assembled Today
Yama-chan and Ami-chan will be with me.
I'm still a bit worried.
You're not already asleep are you??
Let's go all out with this shrine visit!!
Yama
I can't believe you took a dumb job like this on New Year's Eve!
If you know all the tricks, year-end
cleaning can be some really lucrative work.
Still...
Why does this dog
have its own mansion?
Man, it's huge!
It really is, huh?
Whoa, no way!
A heated floor?!
Seriously?!
I'm so jealous!
Hello! Delivery God Yato,
at your service 365 days a year!
Yato.
Oh, Hiyori!
What's up?
Um, would you like to visit the Yushima Tenjin shrine tonight for the first shrine visit of the new year?
Huh?!
Why do you have to visit that geezer?
You should visit me!
Well, I have some
big exams coming up...
Plus, you don't even have a shrine.
I'm using your part-time
wages to buy one, then!
What are you,
a tax collecting god?!
There's going to be a ton of food stalls and stuff there, you know.
Food stalls?!
We'll be there!
I want some candied fruit!
See you soon, then!
Let's go all out with this shrine visit!!
Yama
All out, huh?
Now don't run, okay?
You don't want this to get too loose.
Okay.
Turn this way.
You look lovely!
Well, I'm off.
So that's the half-Phantom
that misleads Yato?
Yes.
Let's slay her, Reiki.
Wait.
What is it?
We still may have use for her.
NORAGAMI
Hiyori!
Abby New Year...
What happened to going all out?!
We still are! I'm offering
a ton of money this year!
Besides the tests, we're gonna be entering high school!
Grant me popularity!
Simmer down, dummy.
Seriously, it's pretty much a given that our
whole class will move on to high school.
I'm not as thrilled as Hiyori is, at least.
I am not thrilled!
S-Say, someone might join us later.
I hope you don't mind.
A m-man?! Is that why
you're all dressed up?!
So you want to win his heart by saying, "I'm a different person this year"!
N-No! It's not like that!
Staking it all on New Year's?
You've got guts!
Seriously, it's not like that!
Come on! Quit it!
Popularity! Popularity!
Popularity! Gimme popularity!
Please let me move to high school without any trouble.
Until now, I used to visit
shrines just because, but...
Please let me continue to
have fun with all my friends.
I want some octopus dumplings!
Looks yummy!
Hey, Hiyori. You gonna buy some, too?
Oh, yeah.
Yato! Wait!
Hiyori! Hey, Hiyori!
Hiyori!
Her first snooze attack of the year.
Aw, man.
We missed ringing in the new year all
because you had to take your sweet time!
It's not my fault!
Every last bit of moldy grime I see is just begging to be cleaned up!
I hope Hiyori hasn't gotten
sick of waiting for us.
A text message?
Another regular Phantom-slaying job.
Wait, it says that it should
be right here, actually.
Come, Sekki!
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
Nicely done!
Thanks.
Huh?! How many are there?!
Calm down, Yukine!
It'll be okay!
You've changed, Yukine.
And you're going to
change even more!
Believe in yourself!
Now show me, god named Yato,
the power of the Regalia
you have tempered.
Yato?
Where did you go?
I don't smell him.
Nora...
H-Hello.
Say, have you seen Yato?
I thought he came this way, but...
Huh? Is that—
Could you not speak so casually to me, you lowly Phantom?
Huh?
When did I...
You played a big part in his ablution.
You were watching?
That was the perfect time to revoke his name, too.
Huh?!
Wait—
You're quite fast on your feet, I see.
Go for her Cord.
But try not to accidentally bite it off.
Why are you attacking me?!
Why?
Because I don't like you.
These things just keep coming!
Yeah, they really are persistent!
They disappeared.
What a shame.
I guess that's all my Masked Ones can do.
Were you scared?
Even scarier things will
happen now, you know.
Huh?
A god of calamity known
as Rabou has woken.
Rabou...
"Rabou-sama, Rabou-sama! I beg of you!"
You mean...
If someone wishes for it, Rabou can easily kill a Phantom...
or a person...
or a god.
Rabou, a blood-soaked, aberrant god of calamity from the Far Shore...
has come to kill Yato.
Huh?!
But... But Yato has
Yukine-kun with him.
Yato has grown weak
after meeting you.
So, please...
Just stop existing.
Over here! Come get me!
Looks like you've rounded them all up!
All right.
Show off the power of your callused heart!
The heart that demolished the school windows... and hurt everything it touched!
Stop!
Let's take all of them out, Yukine!
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
That's all of them, Yukine.
Now let's hurry to Hiyori!
Yeah!
Candied fruit! Candied fruit!
Ten candied fruits using Hiyori's money!
That's too much, you freeloader!
That's...
That's how strong Yato is now?
Now don't pass out on your way home!
I'll be careful.
Hiyori!
Happy New Year, Hiyori!
HNY!
Whoa, what? You're going home already?
The food stalls are still open! Let's go!
It can be your first food offering of the year!
Oh, maybe your first money offering of the year could come before that?
Huh?
Um...
What is it, Hiyori?
Who are you?
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
What's wrong, Veena?
Have you caught a cold—
It looks like you're sneezing, too, Kazuma.
On the next Noragami:
"Abandoned God."
Huh? These hairballs...
Oh, Kuraha must be shedding.
Next Episode
Abandoned God