- YUUJI, I CAN NEVER REMEMBER
WHEN THE TAIKA REFORMS WERE.
- WE'RE IN THIRD GRADE.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS BY
NOW. YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT.
- WELL, MAYBE YOU COULD
TEACH IT TO ME.
- THERE'S A SIMPLE
TRICK TO REMEMBER IT.
YOU SAY, "TAIKA ALIVE
IN SIX TWENTY FIVE"
- TAIKA ALIVE?
- THEY CENTRALIZED POWER FOR
THE IMPERIAL COURT LIKE CHINA
BUT KEPT A NEWLY UNITED JAPAN
FROM DYING ON THE VINE.
"TAIKA ALIVE."
- TAIKA ALIVE IN
SIX TWENTY FIVE.
- CAN YOU REMEMBER THAT?
- I'VE GOT IT NOW.
I DON'T THINK I CAN EVER FORGET.
( theme song playing )
- Nishimura: AT FUMIZUKI ACADEMY
YOUR SKILLS IN THE CLASSROOM
ARE YOUR POWER
AND THE TEST RESULTS
ARE YOUR JUSTICE.
- WHAT'S UP, HIMEJI? YOU WANTED
TO TELL ME SOMETHING?
- ACTUALLY, IT'S MORE LIKE
A QUESTION I WANT TO ASK YOU.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- ( Mizuki gasping )
- SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED. THE
VERY FIRST BATTLE OF THE TERM
BETWEEN THE
SECOND YEAR STUDENTS
ENDED UP WITH CLASS
F BEATING CLASS E.
- I SEE. A GOOD START
TO THE YEAR.
HOWEVER, THE LOSING CLASS
IS LIKELY DISPIRITED
ABOUT MOVING TO WORSE
EQUIPMENT SO EARLY ON.
IF THEY KEEP UP WITH THEIR
STUDIES THEY CAN JUST AS EASILY
TAKE IT BACK THE
NEXT TIME THEY MEET.
THE NEXT BATTLE IS ALL
WE CAN EVER PREPARE FOR IN LIFE.
- ACTUALLY...
AFTER THE BATTLE, THE STUDENTS
DECIDED THEY DIDN'T WANT
TO TRADE EQUIPMENT.
AND WHAT WOULD MAKE
THEM DO THAT?
- MAN, THIS SUPER GLUE
IS RIDICULOUS.
MY DESK IS TOTALLY
FIXED ALREADY.
- WILL WONDERS NEVER CEASE?
LOOKS LIKE YOSHII
GOT HIMSELF BETTER GLUE.
- WE CRUSHED CLASS E.
IF WE CAN'T GET SOME BETTER
GLUE OUT OF THE DEAL,
THEN WHY BOTHER FIGHTING?
AND SHE'D HAVE A CLASS E DESK
NOW, IF I WERE RUNNING THINGS.
OKAY, EXPLAIN TO ME
ONE MORE TIME
WHY WE TURNED DOWN
OUR NEW DESKS?
- THEY'RE NOT NEW.
YOU REALLY WANT THE
CRAPPY WOODEN DESKS
THEY GOT IN CLASS E?
- IT'S BETTER THAN THESE
KINDERGARTEN TABLES
THAT THEY PULLED
OUT OF A DUMPSTER.
( grunting )
- I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE MAKING
SUCH A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT.
YOU NEVER USE IT
TO STUDY ANYWAY.
- BUT I DO USE IT. FOR REAL.
I EAT LUNCH ON IT. I SLEEP
ON IT. DRAW STUFF ON IT.
A DESK IS LIKE THE
TRUSTY STEED YOU RIDE
WHEN YOU DO BATTLE AT SCHOOL.
- YOSHII HAS ALREADY BECOME
ONE WITH HIS DESK.
- GO AHEAD AND KISS
THOSE TABLES GOODBYE.
WITH CLASS A
DECLARING WAR ON US,
WE'LL BE TRADING THEM IN TODAY.
I'VE GOT THIS WORKED OUT.
WE BEAT THOSE GUYS
AND THEIR GEAR IS OURS.
I'VE HAD TO CHANGE MY TIMETABLE
BUT IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
EVERYTHING IS ROLLING ALONG JUST
AS I THOUGHT. RIGHT, HIMEJI?
- I GUESS SO.
- ALL RIGHT. WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE CHECK OUT CLASS A?
- SO THIS IS CLASS A.
- IT SEEMS MORE LIKE
A FOUR STAR HOTEL.
- NOW YOU SEE WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I COULD LIKE, SO SEE MYSELF
SLEEPING IN HERE.
- LOOK AT THAT YOSHII,
IT'S LIKE A FREE COFFEE SHOP,
THEY CAN EAT AT
WHENEVER THEY WANT.
- YEAH, DON'T LET THEM THINK
YOU'RE BLOWN AWAY
BY THEIR AWESOMENESS
CAUSE THEN THEY'VE GOT YOU.
JUST TRY TO ACT CASUAL, LIKE ME.
- YOU'RE THE ABSOLUTE PICTURE OF
NONCHALANCE, SIR TABLEHAND.
- MY, MY. I DIDN'T THINK WE
STARTED TILL TOMORROW.
- HEY, SIS.
- I UNDERSTAND IF YOU WANT
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL.
- Yuuji: NAH. WE THOUGHT
WE'D CHECK OUT OUR NEW STUFF
BEFORE WE TAKE IT FROM YOU.
- Yuuko: WELL, LOOK AT THE
LITTLE NARCISSIST.
- THAT'S A PRETTY BIG
WORD FOR A CHICK.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO MIX IT UP A BIT.
HAVE A REP DUEL INSTEAD.
- ( all gasp )
- Yuuko: AND YOU'RE AN IDIOT,
TOO? WOW.
IN WHAT WORLD COULD ANY OF YOU
POSSIBLY DUEL OUR TOP STUDENT?
- GETTING SCARED?
SEEMS LIKE IT.
SINCE YOU'RE PICKING ON
THE WEAKEST CLASS HERE
WHILE THEY'RE STILL RECOVERING
FROM THEIR LAST BATTLE.
- WE CAN DO THIS RIGHT NOW,
IF YOU LIKE.
- Shouko: WAIT.
I ACCEPT. THIS DUEL IS MINE.
- BUT, SHOUKO!
- ONLY...
I HAVE ONE CONDITION.
THE LOSER HAS TO DO ONE
THING THE WINNER SAYS,
UNCONDITIONALLY.
- SO THAT'S THE REASON
YOU'RE PICKING ON CLASS F
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- DON'T BE ABSURD. IT IS
OUR DUTY TO CONFRONT YOU.
WE ARE CLASS A AND AS SUCH
REPRESENT THE HIGHEST
STANDARDS OF THIS SCHOOL.
YOU'VE SET SOMETHING
IN MOTION HERE.
WHEN BOTTOM-FEEDERS
START WARS
WITHOUT EVEN CRACKING
OPEN A BOOK
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO
TEACH THEM A LESSON.
- FINE BY ME. THE LOSER DOES
WHAT THE WINNER SAYS.
THIS SHOULD BE AN
ENTERTAINING DUEL.
- IT'S NOT A DUEL.
IT'S FIVE AGAINST FIVE.
- ( all gasp )
- BUT YUUKO...
- I'M CERTAIN OUR REP
WOULD EMERGE VICTORIOUS,
BUT THE WISE ARE ALSO PRUDENT.
- ALL RIGHT. WE'LL GO ALONG
WITH THIS FIVE ON FIVE DUEL,
AS LONG AS CLASS F GETS TO PICK
THE SUBJECTS TO BATTLE IN.
- WE'RE AGREED.
- Nishimura: AND WITH THAT,
THE BATTLE HAD BEEN SET.
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
WHY'D YOU AGREE WITH
THAT CREEPY PSYCHO?
- RELAX. THEY HAVEN'T
GOT A CHANCE AGAINST US
AND NOW WE'LL GET TO BOSS THEM
AROUND WHENEVER WE'RE FINISHED.
- DON'T BE SO SURE.
FROM WHAT I HEAR,
SHOUKO IS NOT REALLY THE
GIRL YOU WANT TO MESS WITH.
- IF YOU GET WHAT I'M SAYING.
- OH, YEAH?
- EVERYBODY SAYS HOW
SMART AND PRETTY SHE IS.
BUT FOR WHATEVER REASON THE
BOYS IN THIS SCHOOL DON'T WANT
TO GO ANYWHERE NEAR HER.
- THAT IS WEIRD.
GUYS LOVE THE PRETTY NUT-JOBS.
- WELL, APPARENTLY SHE'S A
TOTAL ICE PRINCESS TO MEN.
- HOW COULD SHE NOT
LIKE US GUYS, I MEAN...
WAIT A MINUTE.
SO, WHAT IF SHE'S AFTER...
- ( giggling )
- RIDICULOUS. THERE'S NO WAY
THAT'D EVER HAPPEN.
I MEAN NO JUDGMENT. BUT THAT'S
JUST STUFF THEY MAKE UP
FOR LATE NIGHT CABLE, RIGHT?
BACK ME UP HERE.
- IT'S REAL.
- WHAT?
- THERE'S THIS ONE GIRL.
SHE'S ALWAYS JUMPING ME.
- THERE'S MY SWEET BABY.
- MIHARU.
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
WANT TO HURT ME?
YOU LEFT ME JUST SO
YOU COULD HANG AROUND
WITH THESE STUPID LITTLE BOYS
AND HIDE YOUR LOVE AWAY.
- HEY! OKAY. WOW! YOU'RE
GETTING ALL UP IN THAT.
- WHO'S THAT?
- MIHARU SHIMIZU,
SECOND YEAR, CLASS D.
- STOP IT! GET OFF OF ME.
- THERE'S NO REASON
TO BE SHY, SWEETIE.
I KNOW DEEP DOWN INSIDE
YOU REALLY LOVE ME
AND I CAN'T WAIT
'TIL YOU REALIZE IT.
- FOR THE LAST TIME, I TOLD YOU
I DON'T SWING THAT WAY!
YOSHII, A LITTLE HELP
HERE, PLEASE.
- I'M AFRAID SHE'S RIGHT. BUT
I CAN SEE WHY YOU'RE CONFUSED.
SHIMADA'S GOT SMALL BOOBS,
THAT ARE BARELY EVEN THERE,
A BAD TEMPER AND KINDA
JUST LOOKS LIKE A DUDE
IN A FIGURE FOUR LEG LOCK!
- I DO NOT LOOK LIKE A DUDE.
TAKE IT BACK!
- THAT'S RIGHT! I LOVE SHIMADA
BECAUSE SHE'S A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
- MOVE, MOVE, MOVE.
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING
OUT OF THIS THAT EASILY.
NOBODY TALKS ABOUT
MY BREASTS LIKE THAT.
- I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU SAY!
- THAT'S SO SWEET.
THEN YOU'RE GONNA TAKE ME OUT.
I EXPECT CREPES AT LA VEDITZ
BY THE TRAIN STATION.
- WHAT? THAT PLACE?
IT'S TOO EXPENSIVE.
- FINE!
- NO, OKAY. I'LL DO IT.
- GOOD. FROM NOW ON YOU
BETTER TRY TO BE SUPER NICE
AND CALL ME LADY MINAMI.
AND I GET TO CALL YOU AKI.
- ( groaning ) YES. MY LADY!
- I WANT... I WANT...
YOU SHOULD... YOU SHOULD JUST
SAY... SAY YOU LOVE ME SOMETIME.
- FINE. HERE GOES.
- NO, YOU WON'T!
- SAY IT!
- ( screaming in pain )
MOVE. MOVE. MOVE!
- SAY IT! SAY YOU LOVE ME
RIGHT NOW OR LOSE THE LEG.
- YES, MA'AM! "YOU LOVE ME
RIGHT NOW OR LOSE THE LEG!"
- ( all screaming )
- YOU IDIOT!
- ( bone snapping )
- THAT WAS NOT REAL
FUN FOR ME.
HIMEJI?
MUST BE AN IMPORTANT LETTER
YOU'RE WORKING ON.
- YOSHII, DON'T.
- ( gasps )
THAT TOTALLY LOOKS LIKE
A LOVE LETTER.
WHY WOULD ANYONE RISK
WRITING A LOVE LETTER
AT SCHOOL IN THEIR CLASSROOM?
- IT ISN'T LIKE THAT.
OKAY, YOU GOT ME, IT IS.
BUT IT'S NOT REALLY
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
- IT'S A SILLY CURSED
CHAIN LETTER.
- AND NOW YOU'VE MANAGED TO MAKE
THINGS EVEN MORE COMPLICATED.
- IS IT TO SOMEONE
IN OUR CLASS?
- YES.
- OKAY.
THEN HOW ABOUT I TEACH YOU
HOW TO WRITE A REALLY GOOD ONE
THAT'LL FREAK EVERYBODY OUT?
- NO THANKS. IT'S NOT A
PASS-IT-ON-OR-BE-CURSED LETTER.
- STOP. I KNOW
IT'S ONE OF THOSE.
OH, GREAT. SEE, THE CURSE IS
WORKING ON ME ALREADY.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- I SEE. WHAT'S SO GREAT
ABOUT THIS GUY?
I BET YOU'LL SAY HE'S HOT.
- WELL, I DON'T CARE
HOW HE LOOKS.
BUT I THINK HE'S
PRETTY AND CUTE.
YOU KNOW MY FRIENDS ARE
ALWAYS SAYING THAT
WHEN YOU AND YUUJI
ARE WALKING TOGETHER
THAT THEY CAN'T KEEP
THEIR EYES OFF OF YOU
BECAUSE YOU GUYS ARE SO PERFECT.
- YOUR FRIENDS
SOUND PRETTY NICE.
YOU SHOULD KEEP THEM AROUND.
- THEY ALSO ARE PRETTY SURE THAT
YOU'RE THE DONUT TO HIS BANANA.
- YOU SHOULD LOSE THOSE FRIENDS.
- HE'S... IT'S NOT ALL
ABOUT THE WAY HE LOOKS.
IT'S ABOUT HIS INSIDES.
- WELL, WHO AMONG US DOESN'T
HAVE A FABULOUS SPLEEN?
- PRETTY SURE THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
- OH, YOU MEAN HIS PERSONALITY.
- UH HUH. HE'S SO KIND
AND CHEERFUL.
I ALWAYS SEE HIM HAPPY.
I'VE LIKED HIM EVER SINCE
THE FIRST TIME I MET HIM.
- THAT'S GREAT.
SO THIS LETTER ...
- WHAT ABOUT IT?
- I HOPE YOU GET THE RESPONSE
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
- THANK YOU.
- HERE'S WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
READY TO START TALKING STRATEGY?
OH, MAN. WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
WALKING WITH ME.
- COME ON, DUDE. TALK TO ME.
TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG, MAN.
- I'M NOT... I'LL NEVER BE...
I'LL NEVER BE YOUR DONUT!
- OKAY, IT'S TIME TO
START ROUND ONE.
- Hideyoshi: UNBELIEVABLE.
WHY AM I THE ROUND WHORE?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, HIDEYOSHI?
DO YOU SEE ANYONE ELSE
AROUND HERE AS PRETTY YOU?
- GOOD POINT. THOUGH YOU'RE
AWARE I'M NOT A GIRL.
- ONE PLAYER FROM EACH CLASS,
PLEASE STEP FORWARD.
- DON'T SCREW IT UP, ALL RIGHT?
- WATCH AND LEARN BOYS, 'KAY?
- I'LL TRY TO GET THIS OVER
WITH QUICKLY.
NO SENSE IN TORTURING
THE UNFORTUNATE.
- DON'T LET THAT F FOOL YOU.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
- AND HERE WE GO!
- RIGHT. SUMMONING MY
AVATAR. SUMMON!
OH, I FORGOT TO
MENTION SOMETHING.
MY TEST SCORES IN MATH WOULD
HAVE EASILY PUT ME IN CLASS B.
- OH, WOW. I THINK I MIGHT
START CRYING. SUMMON!
- THAT SUCKS.
- OH, I FORGOT TO MENTION THAT
MY MATH SCORES PUT ME IN A.
- WINNER, YUUKO KINOSHITA,
CLASS A.
- ( cheering )
- WHAT CAN YOU DO? IT'S NOT LIKE
THAT CLASS B BRAIN OF YOURS
CAN DEFEAT A CLASS A ONE
JUST BECAUSE YOUR MATH.
SUCKS THE LIFE
OUT OF MY LUNGS!
- OH YES. IT FEELS SO GOOD!
STRETCH IT! YEAH!
- ALMOST. ALMOST.
- ROUND TWO!
- THE SECOND ROUND BEGINS NOW.
PLAYERS, STEP FORWARD.
- CLASS A. MIHO SATOU.
- WELL, IT'S ON YOU.
SINK OR SWIM, DUDE.
- WHY ME? YOU KNOW IF I LOSE
WE'RE SCREWED.
- DON'T SWEAT IT.
WE BOTH KNOW YOU CAN DO THIS.
- I GUESS SO. DOES THAT
MEAN IT'S ABOUT TIME
TO BRING OUT THE BIG GUNS?
- HELL YEAH. CAN'T KEEP IT
LOCKED UP FOREVER.
YOU NEED TO LET EVERYBODY KNOW
WHAT YOU CAN REALLY DO.
- THAT'S COOL.
I GUESS I'LL LIVE.
- OH, NO. YOU'RE HIM.
- YEP. AND THIS IS LIKE
THE FIRST TIME
I'VE BEEN SERIOUS IN MY LIFE.
- IT'S TRUE.
YOU'RE REALLY THE ONE.
- YES, I AM. I DON'T LIKE
TO SPREAD IT AROUND.
I'VE TRIED TO HIDE IT.
BUT NO MORE.
I FIGHT WITH MY LEFT HAND.
- THE WINNER IS MIHO SATOU
FROM CLASS A.
- YOU THOUGHT JUST BECAUSE
YOU WERE LEFT-HANDED
THAT IT'D SOMEHOW
MAKE YOU SMART?
- MY ARM, LET GO,
GET HER OFF ME.
- ALMOST, SO CLOSE, UP PLEASE.
- OUR REAL FIGHT IS COMING
UP NOW. GAME FACE TIME.
- OH, THANKS. AND WHAT HAPPENED
TO BOTH OF US KNOWING
THAT I COULD DO THIS?
- WELL I NEVER SAID
WHAT IT WAS YOU COULD DO.
- I SERIOUSLY WANT
TO PUNCH YOUR HEAD
WITH MY LEFT HAND RIGHT NOW.
- Takahashi: OKAY, STUDENTS
ON TO THE THIRD ROUND.
AIKO KUDOU FROM CLASS A
AGAINST KOUTA
TSUCHIYA FROM CLASS F.
HAVE YOU PICKED
YOUR SUBJECT YET?
- PHYS. ED ALONG WITH HEALTH.
- WELL, WELL. THERE'S
A RUMOR GOING AROUND
THAT YOU'RE SOMETHING
OF AN ATHLETE.
I'LL BET NOBODY'S EVER TOLD
YOU HOW AMAZING I AM.
AND HOW HARD
I WORK MY BODY.
AND HOW MUCH I SWEAT.
- I FEEL SICK.
( groaning )
- I'M COMING!
HOW DARE YOU HURT
HIM LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF HIS DISABILITY. THAT'S SICK.
- YOU COULD ALWAYS STEP IN
FOR HIM IF YOU LIKE.
BUT ACADEMICS AREN'T
REALLY YOUR THING, RIGHT?
IF YOU DON'T MIND
GETTING A LITTLE ROUGH
I CAN TEACH YOU PHYSICAL
EDUCATION AND HEALTH.
OF COURSE THEN,
I'LL MAKE YOU SWEAT.
- Mizuki: YOSHII!
- Minami: AKI?
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HIM.
HE DOESN'T NEED A GIRL
TO TEACH HIM ANYTHING.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOSHII ISN'T EVER GOING TO
NEED YOUR SWEAT EDUCATION.
- OKAY, YOU'RE DEPRESSING ME
WITH ALL THE NEGATIVES.
DUDE, STAY DOWN.
- I'M OKAY. JUST DIZZY.
- ALL RIGHT.
THEN LET'S BEGIN THE MATCH.
- SUMMON.
- OVER 400 POINTS!
- PRACTICE VERSUS THEORY.
WE FINALLY GET TO SEE
WHICH IS STRONGER.
SAY GOODBYE YOU LITTLE PERV!
- ACCELERATE.
- ( gasps )
- ACCELERATION COMPLETE.
- THAT CAN'T BE.
I REALLY LOST.
- WINNER, KOUTA
TSUCHIYA, CLASS F.
- HE'S STRONG. HIS HEALTH AND
PHYS. ED. SCORE ALONE IS BIGGER
THAN ALL MY SCORES COMBINED.
- AND NOW WE MOVE
TO ROUND FOUR.
- OKAY THEN, TIME TO FIGHT.
- GO KICK SOME BUTT, HIMEJI.
- I WILL FIGHT THIS ONE.
- THAT'S TOSHIMITSU KUBO. THIS
IS THE MATCH WE HAVE TO WIN.
- WHY IS THAT?
- HE'S THE NUMBER TWO
STUDENT HERE.
UNLESS SHE PICKS ONE OF HIS WEAK
SUBJECTS, IT'LL BE A TOUGH ONE.
- HOLY CRAP!
- TELL US, IN WHAT SUBJECT
WILL YOU BE FIGHTING?
- I WOULD LIKE ALL
SUBJECTS COMBINED.
- HE CAN'T DO THAT.
IT'S OUR CHOICE. TELL HIM TO...
- THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
- OR NOT.
- THIS IS NOT GOOD. WHEN YOU
FIGHT IN COMBINED SUBJECTS,
YOUR STRENGTH IS
BASICALLY YOUR RANK.
- AND HE'S...
- BEGIN THE MATCH.
- NOW, SUMMON.
- Minami: LOOK AT THAT SCORE!
THAT NUMBER TWO STUDENT
MUST BE SMART.
- Akihisa: HIMEJI!
- I AM SUMMONING MY
AVATAR. SUMMON!
- IT'S OVER 4000?
- SHE'S RIGHT UP THERE WITH THE
TOP STUDENT IN THE ACADEMY.
- FROM WHERE DID YOUR SKILL
LEVEL ORIGINATE?
- I JUST DECIDED TO DO MY BEST!
I KNOW WHY OUR CLASS STARTED THE
SUMMONER TEST WARS THIS YEAR.
THEY'RE SUCH A GOOD CLASS,
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT LIKE THEM.
THEY ALWAYS TRY TO HELP
EACH OTHER OUT
AND THAT'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANYTHING TO ME.
BESIDES, I'VE STILL GOT A LETTER
TO GIVE ONE OF THEM.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T GIVE UP.
I HAVE TO GIVE MY ALL.
- THE WINNER, FROM CLASS F,
IS MIZUKI HIMEJI.
- CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS AKI?
SOMEHOW WE'RE TIED WITH
THE TOP CLASS IN SCHOOL.
- Akihisa: HIMEJI.
- SO THE NEXT MATCH DECIDES
THE WHOLE THING I GUESS.
- OKAY, IT'S TIME TO BEGIN OUR
FIFTH AND FINAL ROUND.
- WELL THEN,
I GUESS IT'S MY TURN.
- READY?
- WE'LL SURE FIND OUT.
YUUJI SAKAMOTO. CLASS F REP.
- CLASS A REPRESENTATIVE.
SHOUKO KIRISHIMA.
- VERY WELL,
WHAT IS YOUR SUBJECT?
- WHY NOT RAISE THE STAKES?
I'D LIKE A RESTRICTED JAPANESE
HISTORY TEST.
HOW ABOUT WE
LIMIT THE QUESTIONS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL LEVEL WITH
A PERFECT SCORE OF ONE HUNDRED.
- A TEST MATCH?
- THEY'RE NOT USING
THEIR AVATARS?
- Nishimura: THIS SUMMONER
TEST WAR IS BASED
ON THE STUDENT'S SCORES
ON AN ACTUAL TEST
IN THE REAL WORLD.
AS LONG AS THE ATTENDING
TEACHER APPROVES,
THE CHOSEN TEST CAN BE ON ANY
SUBJECT FOR ANY SKILL LEVEL.
- YOU HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
I WILL GET THE TEST PREPARED
AND THE PLAYERS CAN GO
WAIT FOR ME IN THE CLASSROOM.
- Akihisa: HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR MIND, YUUJI?
- Hideyoshi: FIGHTING IT OUT
ON AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEST
WILL SIMPLY GET YOU
EACH A PERFECT SCORE.
- Minami: THE BEST
WE CAN DO NOW IS TIE.
- Mizuki: NOT NECESSARILY.
NOW EVEN A SIMPLE MISTAKE WILL
MEAN A LOSS FOR THAT SIDE.
- ( all gasp )
- EXACTLY. NOW THE BATTLE
IS ONLY ABOUT
STRENGTH OF CONCENTRATION
AND WILL POWER.
- OH, MAN.
- JUST TRUST ME, YOU GUYS,
I'VE GOT THIS.
WHENEVER SHOUKO MEMORIZES
SOMETHING SHE NEVER FORGETS IT.
- ISN'T THAT BAD SINCE A HISTORY
BATTLE IS ALL ABOUT MEMORIZING?
- NO, THAT'S HOW I'LL WIN.
SHOUKO SEEMS TO THINK THAT
THE TAIKA REFORMS
HAPPENED IN THE YEAR 625.
SHE MEMORIZED THEM AS "TAIKA
ALIVE IN SIX TWENTY FIVE."
I JUST NEED THAT ONE QUESTION
ON THE TEST AND I'LL WIN.
- HOLD ON, YUUJI.
THE TAIKA REFORM DID NOT
START IN THE YEAR 625?
- NO. THE RHYME'S
"TAIKA ALIVE IN SIX FORTY FIVE."
BUT IT'S EASY TO GET CONFUSED IF
SOMEONE TEACHES IT TO YOU WRONG.
- OKAY.
- HELLO WORKSTATIONS
FROM CLASS A,
YOU'RE ABOUT TO
BECOME CLASS F'S.
- OKAY. YOU MAY BEGIN
THE TEST.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
- WHAT HAPPENS IF THERE ISN'T A
QUESTION ABOUT THE TAIKA REFORM?
- IF YUUJI CAN'T KEEP HIS FOCUS
AND LOSES CONCENTRATION
THEN SHE'LL DEFINITELY BEAT HIM.
- Mizuki: BUT THAT QUESTION
MIGHT NOT EVEN GET ASKED.
- Akihisa: I KNOW.
HE GOT IT.
- ( bell chiming )
- Takahashi: OKAY, I HAVE THE
TEST RESULTS TABULATED.
FOR SHOUKO KIRISHIMA,
OUR CLASS A REP,
NINETY-SEVEN POINTS.
- ( all jeering )
- THAT'S RIGHT!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
LITTLE MISS SUNSHINE
DIDN'T GET A PERFECT SCORE!
- WE'RE GETTING A
CLASSROOM MAKEOVER BIG TIME!
- CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
- I KNOW.
- NOW FOR THE SCORE MADE BY THE
CLASS F REP, YUUJI SAKAMOTO.
- ( laughing excitedly )
- FIFTY-THREE POINTS.
- CLASS F'S LOW TABLES TURNED
INTO CARDBOARD BOXES.
- ( theme song playing )
- I DIDN'T THINK
IT COULD GET WORSE.
WHAT IS UP WITH THAT SCORE? DID
YOU STROKE OUT OR SOMETHING?
- GUESS THAT'S
MY REAL SKILL LEVEL.
- WHAT USE IS YOUR STUPID PLAN
IF YOU CAN'T EVEN GET
A HUNDRED POINTS?
- SOMETIMES IN LIFE YOU JUST GET
HIT WITH THAT UNKNOWN X FACTOR.
- ESPECIALLY WHEN THE X-FACTOR'S
YOUR OWN PUNY BRAIN!
- YUUJI.
YOUR PROMISE. IT'S TIME.
- RIGHT, THE PROMISE. HE'S GONNA
DO WHATEVER SHE TELLS HIM TO.
- I DIDN'T FORGET.
LET'S HAVE IT.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS SHOUKO.
IT ONLY HAPPENS ON CABLE!
- YUUJI, I WANT YOU
TO GO OUT WITH ME.
- I THOUGHT YOU'D
FINALLY GIVEN UP ON THAT.
- I CAN NEVER GIVE UP. YOU'RE
THE ONE I ALWAYS LIKE BEST.
- CAN I SAY NO?
- YOU CAN'T. YOU MADE A PROMISE
AND NOW WE'RE GOING
OUT ON A DATE.
- WAIT A MINUTE,
CAN'T WE TALK.
( slapping )
- OKAY. WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
- DON'T KNOW. BUT SO SWEET.
- THEN WHAT WAS THE DEAL WITH
SHOUKO ALWAYS LOOKING AT HIMEJI?
- I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE SHE WAS SIMPLY TRYING
TO INTIMIDATE THE COMPETITION.
- UM... I'M SORRY, HIMEJI.
OUR CLASSROOM IS EVEN WORSE
THAN BEFORE ALL THIS.
- I LIKE OUR CLASSROOM.
CLASS F IS LIKE MY NEW HOME.
AND I THINK THAT I LOVE IT.
AND BESIDES...
( whispering ) I'VE GOT YOU
HERE WITH ME.
- YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M HUNGRY AND
AKI STILL OWES ME SOME CREPES.
- WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
UNTIL THE WEEKEND.
- THERE'S NO TIME
LIKE THE PRESENT.
( in German )
MACH SCHNELL LIEBEN.
- NO WAY! YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE ME BLOW THROUGH
MY WHOLE FOOD BUDGET
BEFORE MY PARENTS CAN
SEND ANY MORE MONEY.
- HOLD ON. YOSHII PROMISED
HE WOULD TO TAKE ME OUT
TO THE MOVIES INSTEAD.
- HIMEJI, THIS MAY SOUND BAD,
BUT HOW COME I HAVE NO
MEMORY OF ASKING YOU OUT?
- BECAUSE I JUST
MADE IT UP NOW.
- COME ON. IT'S TIME TO GO EAT
SOME CREPES, YOU GUYS.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT MOVIE YOU PICK FOR US.
- PLEASE DON'T! NO!
I HAVE A LIMITED BUDGET.
I'VE GOT ISSUES WITH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND NEED MY FOOD. HELP!
- I DIDN'T THINK IT
COULD BE POSSIBLE,
BUT HE MAY JUST BE
A GENUINE IDIOT.
- Fukuhara: QUESTION THREE,
WHAT DO YOU CALL THE PART
OF YOUR HOUSEHOLD BUDGET
THAT IS SPENT ON FOOD?
- Akihisa: I ONLY GET SALT
AND WATER THIS WEEK.
- Fukuhara: I DIDN'T ASK YOU
HOW YOU'D SPEND YOUR BUDGET.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME, FOOD
BUDGET, DATES AND STUN GUNS.
- Fukuhara: THIS WILL BE
ON THE TEST.