What's the matter?
Really?  So you've been deployed to Mistral, huh?
That's tough.
But supposedly the food's good and there's no shortage of beautiful women.
It's already been almost half a year since the armistice was declared.
It's a relief that we've survived this long!
Look!  Grim Bourlouge!
Maaaan!
What?  That's impossible!
Not again!  Dammit!
You up, little missy?
Here's your share of the spoils.
Caramel!
T-Thank you so much for giving me something so expensive!
Um... Sergeant, sir!
What's that for?  Rumor goes if you treat the trumpeter good, you'll hear the retreat signals better.
It's rare to see a new recruit, with the draft being over and all.
Were you a volunteer?
Yes!  I wanted to learn how to play music—
What?!
Oh... I mean...
At least you're honest!
Just like that!
Good luck with that, missy.
Private Second Class, what's your name?
Kanata...
Sorami Kanata, at your service!
Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
Korokun
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
Tressflin
Saoen
Insert Song
Translation
(French)
DeathWolf
Timer & Typesetter
Yuurisan(s)
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
There's a festival in Seize today.
A festival?
So I can only take you this far.
Look there!
That's where you've been assigned to.  It's called the Time-Heralding Bastion.
Keep your sights on that and follow the roads.
Yes, sir!
"Notice of personnel change.  Private Second Class, Sorami Kanata.
You are assigned to Platoon 1121, Seize, Trois Province.
Signed, Helvetia Republic Army Command Headquarters."
1320 hours, mission completed!
Thank you very much, sir!
The city of lakes and glass... Seize!
Ah, no, wait!
Check-in time is at 1500 hours.
I can finally let you sing.
Direction check, confirmed!
Check-in time, confirmed!
Equipment check, confirmed!
Forward... march!
G-flat.
What a beautiful sound!
Wow, they're fish figurines!
10 and 25 sen...
What a pretty doll th—
I-I'm sorry!
What's the matter, Rio?
A kitten excited by the festival just went scampering off any which way.
I guess there's no helping that.
Kittens are inherently meandering creatures.
Isn't that what makes them cute?
That'd be fine if it were a stray,
but unfortunately, that one was more of a pet.
She startled me!
But I found another wonderful thing.
What's the matter?
Thank you!
Oh, it's a soldier!
A girl from the bastion?
That's lucky!
Thanks for the helping with the fire!
Thank you!
All right!
I'll pay you back for that!
Take...
this!
Thank you!
To you, too!
Hey!
Are you an idiot?!
Getting involved in all of that...
What do you plan to do about that uniform?!
Um... uh...
Bless you.
Tha—
That's it, come with me!
Is the temperature okay?
Yes, ma'am!  It's wonderful!
That's good.
You made such an easy mark.
Couldn't you have just kept clear of the shots?
What's wrong?  This sort of dye will wash out easily once it's dried.
There's no need to worry.
That... was a part of the festival, right?
It's connected to a legend of Seize.
A legend?
What sort of legend?
About the maidens of fire... who protect this city.
Sorry, there's more work now, isn't there?
I won't forget.
Those repairs you requested were completed, also.
And also...
The repairs on this, too.
Phylicia, huh?
That meddling...
She's late.
Late, late...
Laaaate!
And after we came all the way out here to pick her up, too!
It's fine.  Let's wait calmly, shall we?
It was a gift from your father, wasn't it?
It's a nice article.
D-flat.
Thank you so much for the bath!
I'm always getting lost somehow...
but thanks to that, I was able to have such a wonderful encounter!
Think nothing of it.
Still, do your best to not get lost around here, all right?
Huh?
Oh, wow!
You can... interpret sounds?
This has a very calming tone that's somehow nostalgic.
That's not what I meant—
You thief!
Idiot!
T-Thank you very much.
You really...
Were you going to die for something like that?!
But that bell...
It's fine.
It's fine... I'm sure of it.
Late.
Happiness.
Um...
I've something to take care of, so I'm leaving.
Don't get lost anymore.
That bell...
I'm sure it was something important.
What should I do?
Oh no!
That direction?
Forward march!
Aimerais-tu en chantant voir quelque chose se passer?
Would you like to see something develop as you sing?
Et que l'air soit plus pur, les cœurs des hommes transformés?
For the air to be more pure, to see the hearts of men transformed?
Et pourtant tout est si fragile ici sur la Terre.
Yet everything is so fragile here on Earth.
Il n'est rien qui soit futile, tu sais.
Nothing is without reason, you know.
D'un côté au bout et quelques fois pour tes yeux,
In the end, only sometimes is reality mirrored in your eyes,
The fire maidens?
A long time ago...
Long before the world became what it is today...
et de l'autre les pauvres et bien souvent monstrueux.
and at others in those of the wretched and often very demonic.
In the valleys of this city, there lived a winged demon.
Qu'importe ce que ton coeur te dira,
No matter what side you hear being told,
souviens-toi que la différence n'est que dans tes yeux.
remember that the difference is only in your own eyes.
The demon breathed fire,
shook the earth,
Chantons toutes les couleurs du monde,
Let's sing all the colors of the world,
and wrought pain amongst the people.
Finally, it kidnapped the maidens living in the bastion,
sans manquer une couleur.
without forgetting a single one.
and trapped them in an underground labyrinth.
Chaque chose a sa place ici,
Everything has a place here,
Even so, the maidens refused to give in,
chaque étoile dans la symphonie de notre vie.
like every star in the symphony of our life.
and used golden horns granted unto them by angels to call out to one another.
Once escaping from the maze,
they borrowed strength from a great spider,
and vanquished the demon, severing its head.
Chaque humain nous dit du ciel.
Every human makes sounds of the skies.
When they did so, it began to spew forth flames violently.
Chaque tout était cintré,
Everything is tightly bound,
Had it continued unchecked, the town above would have undoubtedly been engulfed entirely in flames.
In order to contain the belching flames, one by one the maidens embraced the demon's head.
et quand on se voit aussi,
and when we see each other,
pour nous monter dans les étoiles.
we'll be taken to the stars.
Each day, the citizens would pour water onto the fading flames surrounding the demon's head and the maidens.
The fire burned for an entire year before it was finally extinguished.
Every year since, in order to soothe the spirits of those maidens who rescued the city,
the water-pouring festival has been held.
Seems she didn't make it after all... that new girl.
What's it matter?
Look, Captain, it's Rio-senpai!
You're right.
That role really suits her.
What a great idea it was to have her do it.
But didn't we draw lots—
I've gotten myself lost again.
I'm a good-for-nothing, aren't I?
Sometimes being lost can lead to fun situations too, but...
that's usually because you meet someone you didn't know before, right?
I don't want... to be alone.
Are you lost?
Yeah.  I want to find my mommy.
It's all right.
If that's what you wish, then that's the feeling that will be conducted.
Really?
Yes.
Sounds will always resonate.
Will always resonate...
Always resonate and...
And so, be conducted.
Fire maidens, may you rest here in peace.
We beg you to embrace the demon, placate its curse,
so that it may never again awaken.
This is—
A golden horn!
Has the demon—
You think it's awakened?!
Kureha!
Extend...
Someone... please hear my sounds!
It reached someone.
Sounds resonate, and...
Hurry and wake up already!
Private Second Class, Sorami Kanata!
Huh?
Where am...
Going to stay half-asleep the whole night?
This is the garrison of Platoon 1121, the Time-Heralding Bastion!
About yesterday... um...
I-I'm sorry for causing you trouble!
You really did.
I-I apologize!
But...
I was kidding.
However, reckless actions are forbidden from here out.
For just a small bell like this...
I'll teach you...
The trumpet?!
...why this fortress is called the Time-Heralding Bastion.
The sounds of the skies.
Kazumiya Rio.
That's my name.
I'll be guiding you in becoming a trumpeter.
I look forward to working with you, Sergeant Major Rio, ma'am!
Just Rio is fine.
Huh?
That's Phylicia's...
That's the Captain's policy.
There's no rank or class here.
Oh...
Then... Rio-senpai!
Well then, let's get off to a rolling start, shall we?
Let's hear a wake-up call!
The girl this time is pretty bad, isn't she?
Next time, First Battle: The Story of the Chair!