This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
The first day of recording for
her debut song "Myself" has finally arrived!
But Takuto, fell asleep in
his stuffed toy form and
got kidnapped by a little girl!
He's so irresponsible!
Mitsuki was able to persuade
the little girl to return him,
and the recording went off without a hitch!
Takuto! I won't tell
the boss about this!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Please continue to listen to my show!
Our spotlight song
this week is this!
On sale this week, it's "Myself."
By the Cinderella girl,
Full Moon,
who was chosen from among
10,000 people
at the Seed Records New Face audition.
It's her debut song.
It's produced by Kohei Takasu,
but the sound is distinctly different
from his usual sound.
- Excuse me, please turn off the radio.
- So it's worth paying attention to it.
- I strongly dislike music.
- So, let's listen to it.
- Uh, yes...
- It's Full Moon.
Welcome home, Ma'am.
Where is Mitsuki?
She's in her room.
Is that so...
Has there been anything
out of the ordinary?
This comic is funny.
What's going on?
Mitsuki, that's disgraceful!
Yikes!
I'm sorry, Grandmother!
I'll be careful from now on!
Cripes.
Such a nag.
Ah, Takuto and the others are so lucky.
Right about now they're in Shibuya...
What are you doing
just standing around?
It's your first live show in a shop, right?
Where are you going to do it?
I wonder where?
Huh?
I guess it can't be helped,
I'll find it.
Where did your manager say it was?
She didn't say.
She said if I went to
the main street I'd know.
Hey, where's the main street?
Over there.
You're such a country girl.
After all, it's the first time
I've been to Shibuya.
Anyways,
where in the world is it?
Why is everyone looking up?
Who's that?
It's that girl.
You know, the girl who was
chosen at some audition.
I know, they play
her song on the radio.
Oh, that girl.
Anyways, she's cute!
They say you're cute.
So now, what's your opinion?
What's wrong?
I wonder why.
Somehow it doesn't look like me.
You're feeling the difference between
your virtual image and your real self.
Is that so?
Please line up here.
Those of you who want to see Full Moon's
special live show today,
please line up over here.
Wow, this many people are lined up
for a new face even before her debut.
I-It's awesome.
I'm going to sing in front
of this many people.
Huh?
What's wrong?
A-Am I going to be able to sing properly?
What if I make a mistake with the lyrics?
In that case...
In that case?
Cover it up by laughing.
I don't want to do that!
I worked so hard to write the lyrics.
If so, then sing it without
making mistakes.
I'm worried about whether I can or not.
Hey, hey, what are we going
to do about that now?
More importantly,
you have to transform somewhere.
Over there.
Let's see, the waiting room is...
You're Full Moon, aren't you?
You don't remember me?
Uh... Have we met somewhere?
At the audition.
Ummm, umm...
You can't remember?
I'm sorry.
I was supposed to go after you.
Huh?
My audition number was 22.
Thanks to you,
I was sent home without auditioning.
The audition today is over.
We won't be having the third round
of auditions as planned.
I see, at that time...
I'm so sorry.
Oh no, there's nothing to apologize for.
That's right.
If one person succeeds,
everyone other than that person fails.
Y-Yeah...that's true.
After all, I don't think that I lost to you.
Huh?
If our order had been reversed,
I would have succeeded.
Th-That's probably true.
After all, I sing much better.
She's got a lot of confidence.
I guess it's an advantage to be cute.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Oh my, you don't know.
You weren't chosen for your singing,
but you were chosen for your pretty looks.
If not, there's no reason
you would have been chosen.
You're singing isn't all that great.
I'm looking forward to
your live performance today.
With a CD, they can cover it up by
working on it,
but that can't be done with a live show.
To sing in front of people
time and time again
even though you're just a pretty face,
you probably don't know your own limits
so this will put you in your place.
For some reason,
that girl is really horrible.
Huh?
I was chosen because of my looks?
Not my strength or my talent?
Miss Full Moon's
Dressing Room
She's late.
That's right...
I wonder if she doesn't know
where the place is.
Yes!
She's here.
Ah, she's here, she's here.
Sorry I'm late.
Did you see it?
It's an awesome sign.
I saw it.
It's because you're making
an appearance for the first time.
It was Mr. Takasu's idea
to make it really flashy.
What do you think,
were you surprised?
I was.
What?
Are you nervous?
N-No.
I...remember it too.
When you were an idol?
That's right.
It was my first time on
a stage since my debut.
I was singing on a poolside stage
in an amusement park.
Before the show I was super nervous.
Another idol saw that and told me
that at such times,
I should write on my palm
the word "hit."
And then, if you swallowed it,
you won't get nervous.
That's not right, Oshige.
It's not "hit,"
it's "hito," as in person.
What, is that true?
Th-Then, is that why I was unsuccessful?
Ah, I've been cheated.
Darn it!
Give me my youth back!
Give it back! Give it back!
Give it back!
I don't think that's the reason
why you were unsuccessful.
Mitsuki, do it properly and write "hito."
Y-Yes.
Ms. Oshige...
- Huh?
- Oh?
When I was chosen at the audition...
was it because of my looks?
Who told you that?
Who?
That's quite offensive.
Well, this means
you're not a full-fledged star.
Was the singing meaningless?
No, it wasn't meaningless.
I don't know who told you this,
but your success at the audition—
Uh, if we don't start to prepare soon...
We're pressed for time.
That's right.
Well, it's about that time,
I'm counting on you.
I understand.
Anyway, right now just think of
the live performance.
All right.
Well, come this way.
Okay, me too.
It's amazing outside!
They're lined up all
the way to the sidewalk.
We'll make you glamorous.
I wonder...if I can really sing.
Can I come in?
Yes.
Oh, where is she?
The restroom.
Oh, is that so...
Mr. Takasu, would you like some?
It's a new kind of potato chip.
Oh, sounds good.
To sing in front of people
time and time again
even though you're
just a pretty face,
you probably just don't know your own limits,
so this will put you in your place.
So this is
where you are.
Takuto...
Takuto... I...
Huh?
Nooo!
W-What are you doing?
My hair's all rumpled!
That's mean! They took the trouble
of making it so pretty!
You were worrying that
you're just a "pretty face,"
but just as I thought, you were
thinking about your appearance.
Or better yet, how about putting on
a mask or something?
"The Birth of the World's
First Masked Idol."
It would be a big topic of conversation.
Where are you going?
Running away?
Sing properly, okay?
I can sing...
After all, it's my job.
Huh?
What?!
Huh? W-What?
Putting on airs...
What about your job!
"It's my job,
so no matter how painful it is,
I'll work hard with my business smile."
That's not what I'm saying!
If you sing with that cold face
because it's your job,
your singing won't echo
in anyone's heart.
Huh?
First, you have to sing
with pleasure from your heart.
It's true...
Yes, that's it.
But...right now, I...
I'll say it now,
but at the time of the audition...
At that time,
I was so surprised I couldn't move.
Huh?
It's like...
you sing with such a beautiful voice.
Somehow it's not a "voice,"
but a "sound."
With no limit on the low notes,
it's as clear as a bell.
Like I was dreaming.
I was happy that this
kind of singer existed.
At that time I was happy too.
It had been a long time
since I'd sung so loudly.
It didn't become painful to breathe.
To other people it's normal,
but for me,
I was happy that I had
that kind of voice.
You can express your feelings
when you sing.
If you sing thinking "I'm not confident," then
you convey that to the people listening.
Yeah.
Even so, I...
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry.
Okay!
I'm going to go.
Ms. Oshige...
Mitsuki!
Look at that, look!
Huh?
What is this?
Amazing, it's a mountain of postcards.
They're the postcards this shop
received to reserve your CD.
What?
I'm just telling you, these are only
the ones this shop's received.
Please reserve Full Moon's debut single,
"Myself" for me.
I liked it the first time
I heard it on the radio.
It's a really good song.
It's the best.
I wonder what kind of girl
is singing?
I really like it.
She's probably young,
but she's got a good voice.
It was like her feelings
were coming through.
These are from people who
have only heard you on the radio.
You weren't just chosen for your looks.
You can believe that, right?
Eichi...
It's difficult to become stronger.
But now I feel like I can start.
Surely...I...
am not alone.
Why do I like you so much
My tears are falling
Because in the past
there were a lot of things I lost
And I couldn't sing
A distant place was where I belonged.
I found a loneliness
in your eyes that day
Are we both the same
I realized you were
always next to me
Why do I like you this much?
Your voice echoes
and it sounds almost sad
Up to now who was supporting me?
I realize, now that I'm far away,
what was supporting me.
Why do I like you?
That's too easy to answer.
Mr. Takasu,
what a beautiful special effect!
It was an awesome production.
Oshige, you really did it!
That was amazing, Mr. Takasu.
It was really amazing, Ms. Oshige.
It looks like
they both think the other did it.
Oh, it's you.
- I lost.
- What?
I'm nothing compared to you.
Your singing was amazing.
It's only natural that
you were chosen.
And...I'm embarrassed...
for what I said.
I'm really sorry.
I was confident in my singing,
but I'll work harder.
And I have to work harder than ever
to convey my feelings to everyone.
We both have to work hard.
I guess so!
I thought you'd be here.
Thanks for earlier.
Growing wings.
It's nothing.
No...
What you said before,
it really cheered me up.
Hey! Don't get the wrong idea.
I hate wishy-washy, sensitive people.
Hey, are you listening!
You conveyed your feelings...
properly...
Mitsuki's song is selling
like crazy!
I'm sure the kids at her school are
gossiping about Full Moon!
Naturally. The manager said
it was a big hit, too.
What? Nobody's talking
about Full Moon.
Okay! If nobody's listening, I'll make
them listen! Leave it to me!
Wait, Meroko!
If you go out, then everything
will get more confusing!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Is It Really A Hit?"
- Look forward to it!