Today is the day of your first
rank advancement exam.
Remember all the training you've been through
until now and keep focused,
so you won't have any regrets afterwards.
I think you'll all be just fine.
Nina-sensei is really acting like a teacher today.
I-I'm getting kind of nervous!
I understand. I felt the same way
when I took my first exam.
Even today, I'm extremely nervous.
Probably more than you are...
Oh, so that's it - she's just worried, huh?
Pardon the intrusion.
I'll be at the testing grounds as a guard today.
Captain Saku!
Good luck, you four.
I'll be rooting for you.
It's so weird how nice you're being to us,
Captain Saku!
Well, that's rude!
You do know it's because
I'm always worrying about you!
You're Nina's beloved students, after all.
Chiya, you especially need to make sure
you don't cause any problems. Got it?
Yup!
That's what she's worried about?!
Okay!
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
RANK NINE ADVANCEMENT
EXAM GROUNDS
Wow, there are so many girls!
Is everyone here taking the exam with us, too?
C'mon, hurry up, everyone!
Hold it, Chiya, you're gonna embarrass us
if you make such a big fuss!
Right, you two?
VICTORY!
Pass
or
Bust!
I'd say you're the embarrassing one here, Kon.
I will now explain how the Rank 9
Advancement Exam will be conducted.
Rank 10
The Rank 9 Advancement Exam takes place
twice a year, in summer and in winter.
For this exam, the examiner rotation
has left me to oversee the proceedings.
My name is Tokie, and I am the head of Tatsumiya.
I look forward to working with you today!
Question!
Doesn't that mean the girls from Tatsumiya
will have a big advantage?
A valid concern, but there's no need to worry.
Urara are all colleagues as well as rivals.
Teahouse heads may have a higher rank,
but we are Urara the same as you.
In a sense, everyone here
is competing with one another.
Today, it doesn't matter if the girls here
are my students or my daughters.
I'll be grading you with the full intent
to fairly and seriously crush your hopes and dreams.
I'm super worried!
Because there are so many Rank 10 Urara
taking the exam, you will take the exam as a team.
As a team?!
The symbol of your home teahouse
on your chest designates your team.
Natsume
The exam will test the strength of the bonds
between you and the girls you've been training with.
So that means the four of us will fight together!
I'm so glad I don't have to fight against you!
E-even if I had to go up against you,
with dignity and solemnity, I-I would kick your-
Thank God!
Kon, don't force yourself!
Now, I'm sure you're all excited to see
what the exam is about, so take a look.
ENTER THE GIANT
MAZE AND FIND
THE ARROW KEY
The exam will take place in the enormous
underground labyrinth beneath Meirocho,
"The Bowels of the Cursed Serpent."
Cursed...?
Serpent?
Some say that any person who enters
that extremely expansive and confusing maze
will find themselves painfully lost in a world of illusion.
Seal
Because it's a dangerous place,
it's usually sealed off, but the seal just wore off.
Not much of a seal, was it?!
Enter the labyrinth and, using your skills
as diviners, find the Arrow Key.
Teams that return to the surface
with the Arrow Key will pass.
However, there are only three Arrow Keys.
Out of the ten teams here, only three will pass.
So it's a treasure hunt escape game!
Sounds really fun!
My, what high hopes you have!
But the legendary Rank 9
Advancement Exam is not that easy!
Tokie-san looks like she's having fun, too!
Come on out, everyone!
Uh, what're those?
Here we have nine oni.
The oni are played by the heads of your teahouses.
What the heck are they doing here?
That one's definitely Nina-sensei.
The oni will use their divining powers without mercy
to get in your way and capture you.
These are some really harsh rules...
There's no way we can beat our teacher's divining skills!
And that's not your only handicap.
In the Bowels of the Cursed Serpent,
there are so many dangerous places that not even we,
as instructors, know where they all are.
That is why only those who pass this test
can open the door to Bloque 9.
Alright, everyone, one last question.
Do you want to be a Rank 9 Urara?!
Yeah!
Good work keeping watch!
Look at me, Saku! I'm an oni!
Wh-what a lewd outfit!
Isn't there something you can put over it?!
Th-th-this is a public place, s-s-so you can't just... Aargh!
Hey, Saku, I've been thinking it for a while,
but since I'm an oni today, I'll just say it.
Th-th-this is a public place, s-s-so you can't just... Aargh!
If you think anything and everything is lewd,
then perhaps you have a lewd mind.
The reason the Captain always has lewd thoughts
is because she's always looking
to take down lewd individuals!
Even if she was a lewd person,
we would still be with her!
Three cheers for our lewd Captain!
Captain Saku is the lewdest of them all!
The Queen of Harlots!
The Star of Strumpets!
Cut it out, you two!
It's not that lewd...
C-Captain!
It's almost time for it to start.
I'm getting really nervous!
It's okay, we're all doing it together!
I wonder how big this "Pit of the
Cursed Serpent's Stomach" labyrinth really is.
What a creepy name.
And if you go in, you might not come out...
It's fine, it's fine!
It's not that big!
I've been in there tons of times!
But since we don't have a lot of time, we'll have to hurry.
Especially since we'll get digested.
I don't think that was a labyrinth!
Huh? What're they doing over there?
Divining Tool Rental
They're lending out divining tools for the exam.
I didn't bring anything to use.
Hey, let's all go...
Kokkuri
Kokkuri                            Pendulum
Kokkuri                            Pendulum                          Matsuko
No
tools
So much for a team. I'm already left out.
I mean, it's an exam.
Most people would bring
the tool they know best with them.
Koume's right.
I see.
So what are you going to do then, Chiya?
U-umm, I...
"Wait, I've been studying with everyone all this time,
but I'm the only one who
doesn't have a skill she's good at?!"
Looks like you've just realized that, Chiya.
Wow, I can't believe the pendulum knew that!
I didn't need to use it to figure that out.
I've been with you this whole time.
Huh?! Really?!
It's okay. Your kind of divining
is more like your wild instincts, anyway.
And you might find the one skill you're good at soon!
What should I do?
I've worked so hard to get here, but I still...
Get it together, Chiya!
Kon?!
That reaction's not like you.
We decided we'd become Rank 1 Urara, right?
So this is no place to get hung up on things!
It doesn't matter if it's your wild instincts or whatever.
You've got to be your usual, happy self.
The four of us are a team!
Right. Thanks, Kon!
A smile looks best on you, Chiya!
I knew Kon-chan could do it.
Okay! That makes Kon
the leader of the Natsumeya Team!
Huh?! N-no!
You're the best manager we've got.
And the most mature.
D-don't flatter me! The only thing I can do
is give you headbands!
Take any you like! Here! Here! Here!
Uh, no thanks.
Alright, everyone. Are you ready?
There is one last warning I must give you all.
If you get lost and would like to
withdraw from the exam,
blow the whistle you were given at check-in.
A high-rank Urara will come to rescue you at once.
But if that situation would result in us
being stranded there too, well, then... that's that.
Let's all do our best.
Are you sure you should be glossing that over?!
Now, let's move into the Bowels of the Cursed Serpent.
Will you be eaten and digested,
or live to see another day?
That is up to your skill alone.
Good luck, everyone.
Wh-wh-what is all this?!
I didn't know there was something like this
underneath Meirocho!
It's almost like an underground city.
It looks like it really could swallow us whole.
That just means we've gotta give it our all!
R-right!
Hey, uh, as your leader, I'd like to propose an idea...
Uh... can we join hands?
What now? We gonna summon something?
That's not the way I wanted to do it!
We did this before...
It's really corny, but it's still important.
Hey, are you scared?
A little bit.
But more than that...
...I'm excited!
Okay, we're definitely gonna win this!
Urara... Fight!
The exam has finally begun.
Those young girls who have been
pit against one another...
Clashing hopes and dreams,
the invocations they've memorized ringing off the walls...
The thunderous roar of the traps they spring,
their beautiful screams...
This is the Rank 9 exam!
Wh-wh-what is all this?!
Nobody told us there'd be traps!
It's like a haunted mansion full of traps!
It's so much fun!
Let's take the path with the most traps!
Why would you suggest that?!
Oh, but Chiya-chan might be right.
What?
Say, for example, Koume-chan
had a special manju she was saving...
Uh-huh...
If she put it out in the open
where people could find it, it would get eaten.
Uh-huh...
One time she tried hiding it on the roof,
and the mice got to it.
Why're you bringing this up now?!
So what you mean is that they wouldn't hide
the Arrow Key somewhere safe.
Yeah.
Then leave it to me!
Finding the right path is my specialty.
I'll use this pendulum to lead us down
the most dangerous route!
Oh yeah, you used that before!
I'm different from how I was back then.
I've been secretly practicing this for hours and hours...
Pendulum
Cadence
(Age 18)
And my pretty little girl has grown up
into a full-figured woman!
Do you really need all that setup for it to work?
In the name of Miss Plum, I command you.
Swing, swing, O Queen of pendulums.
Cadence, Cadence, Mademoiselle.
Lead us lost sheep to victory!
Oh, yeah!
That's so cool, Koume-chan!
Awesome, Koume!
Oh yeah, you spent all night
coming up with that cool invocation!
Like I said, why are you bringing this up now?!
This way would be dangerous.
Cadence is responding!
Cadence says it's down this way.
It's very dangerous.
You might not make it back in one piece.
The real question is how
we're going to get around these traps.
That'll be easy! Let's go!
Hey, Chiya-chan!
Hup!
Nono's technique to hide behind others...
Good work, Nono.
Kon-chan, behind you!
An oni?!
If she catches us, we'll fail!
Fate can be so cruel.
To think that I would be the one
to destroy your hopes and dreams.
Th-that voice!
It's Nina-sensei!
Oh, no, I am not your sweet Nina-sensei now.
I am the formidable oni, Oninya-
Oninina!
She messed up.
It's the same old Nina-sensei.
And now more of them showed up!
Wh-whatever, we have to run!
Oh no!
There's nowhere left to run!
It's time to pay the price for your actions!
Wh-wh-what should we do, Matsuko-san?!
Calm down, Nono! There must be a way!
Let's think together!
R-right, what could we do?
Please let us go, Onina-sensei!
I'm afraid I can't do that!
I am doing this for your own...
A paper doll, handed down...
The story of a speaking doll, handed to me...
A song?
I am but one fragment on the side...
Nono's invocations sound like an angel's singing...
So, did you find a good way to get out of this?
Matsuko-san said I just needed to sing
an invocation, so I tried that, but...
What's that supposed to...
They fell asleep!
Her singing has the same soothing effect, as always!
Nice job, Nono! Now we can move forward!
B-but Chiya-chan passed out, too...
Chiya!
She woke up!!
It's dangerous here!
Cadence moved again!
Is that it?
There! Thanks, Cadence!
There are a lot of them.
I guess any one works.
Let's go with this one, then.
Wait!
Mother wouldn't have left the Arrow Keys out
for someone to take this easily!
There's gotta be a-
Whoops, wrong one.
Then what about this one?
Aww, that wasn't it, either.
What about this-
Nono!
I-I'm sorry!
Hey, wa-
K..Kon-chan?!
They were all duds!
Ugh, I can just see Tokie-san's smug face right now!
That woman's definitely enjoying this!
And all these traps are so old!
Koume-chan, don't say that in front of Kon-chan!
It's alright, Nono.
Today, my mother is our enemy.
And I'm not going to let her win this.
Kon-chan looks really scary!
Like mother, like daughter.
Alright, let's go find the real Arrow Key!
If we don't hurry, the other teams
will get them before we do!
You're right!
There's a secret technique
I've been working on for today.
I didn't want to use it if I could avoid it,
but it looks like I've got no choice!
A secret technique?
Kon-chan, what kind of divination ritual is it?!
Hold up, seriously, what are you trying to do?
I ask you, o strange and mysterious spirit
Kokkuri, kokkuri, come out
I offer up my body to you and beseech you to reply!
That's just your usual kokkuri fortune-telling, Kon.
Kon?
It's so good to see you, Chiya!
Hurry up and rub my head!
She smells like a fox!
She must be the fox spirit
from the last time we did kokkuri!
Correct as usual, Chiya!
And, by the way, I'm not smelly.
Hey, what're you doing all of a sudden?!
Come on, let me play a little!
Wh-what's going on?
Sorry to scare you all.
I've been practicing this in secret for a while,
like Koume was with hers.
It's a forbidden technique that lets
the fox spirit use my body instead of a coin.
Well, now, did it scare you?
She looks like a really mentally unstable person.
Someone with multiple personalities...
I-I can't control it yet, but it's much more accurate
than the usual method!
Really?
It's really mysterious!
Now then, little girls.
What did you want to ask of me?
Fox
Mode
We want you to find the Arrow Key for the Rank 9 exam.
Hmph, boring.
You called me out for such a stupid-
If you help us look, I'll pet you as much as you want.
W-well, looks like I have to!
As easy to convince as ever.
I see it. Two of the three arrows
have already been taken by the others.
We must aim for the last remaining arrow.
This way!
Alright, this is helpful!
I didn't know you could do this with kokkuri divination...
I figured it out myself, after hearing that I didn't
have to go by the book, that I was free to try anything...
It's all thanks to my training with you!
E-even though it's super embarrassing!
Note: A pun combining "kuda-gitsune," a type of spiritual possession
at the hands of a kitsune, and Kon's name.
You can do it, Kongitsune!
The Arrow Key is definitely around here.
But where?
I do not know the path from here.
I've already grown tired of you all.
See you later, Chiya.
Miss Fox?
She went back.
Oh.
Hey, what's this rope?
I don't know.
I-I bet something's gonna fall on us from above!
Ow, ow, ow! I hit my butt!
What's this room here for-?
Wait!
There it is!
Th-this one's real, right?
Let's grab it together, on three, okay?
One, two...
I-I'm sorry, I'm really sorry!
I wanted to do this with you,
but I've never done it before,
and I didn't get the timing right...
It's fine, really.
After all, it's thanks to you and the fox spirit
that we even got this far.
You're the one who should have it.
No, it wasn't just Kon and the fox spirit.
Nono and Koume were really cool, too!
I didn't do any divining, so I feel a little sad.
Chiya...
So I decided I'm gonna train even harder!
You dummy.
You helped a ton today, Chiya!
That's right! We found this because
all four of us worked together!
You're right. But the test isn't over yet.
We're still in it until we get out of here.
Kon!
Hold onto this, Chiya.
Let's give it our all until the end!
Yeah!
Chiya.
Okay, let's go!
Huh? R-right...
Hey, is that the exit?
Let's try it!
What was that?
I feel like something was calling my name just now...
Wh-what's happening?
Chiya.
We finally found you.
Disgusting, treacherous child...
Chiya, we're gonna go without you!
Huh?
Chiya?
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Chiya and the Dark Sometimes Cry"!
We'll use underwear divination
to see what kind of episode it'll be!
Hey, girls shouldn't show others their underwear!
Okay, then, we'll use yours, Captain Saku!
"Chiya and the Dark Sometimes Cry"
What?!