It's over!
Homura-chan...
You...
What the hell did you just do?!
I see. You're that "irregular", huh?
You're using a strange technique there.
Don't get in the way!
Sayaka-chan!
She's okay. She's just unconscious.
Who are you?
Whose side are you on?
I'm on the side of those who maintain their composure,
and I'm the enemy of the idiots who initiate fights needlessly.
Which are you, Sakura Kyouko?
Wha-
Have we met before?
I wonder.
I won't fight you, since I haven't a single clue what hand you're going to play.
I'll back down for today.
A prudent course of action.
You saved her?
How many times must I warn you?
Just how big of a fool are you?
I have warned you numerous times not to get involved, correct?
I...
I will not hold back against a fool.
Homura-chan... Why?
At any rate, it's obvious she's planning something.
Be careful.
Akemi Homura, you can't be...
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 6     There's definitely something wrong with this
Miki
Now you should be fine for a while.
Wow, it turned black.
It's dangerous now. If you taint it any further, a witch might hatch.
It's fine. Give it to me.
Now it'll be fine.
You ate it?!
It's one aspect of my job.
But in order to continue purifying your Soul Gem, you'll need to find a new Grief Seed.
Is it really that important to keep this bright?
Sakura Kyouko was strong, right?
If you have a Soul Gem that's got plenty of room to spare, you can use all the magic you want without concern.
That's the source of Kyouko's power.
But that doesn't mean you can just sacrifice innocent people to get Grief Seeds.
The more you use magic, the more it taints your Soul Gem.
Sayaka, you should assume you can't beat Kyouko until you acquire some Grief Seeds.
This is kinda...
Mami-san didn't have enough Grief Seeds, right?
But she was able to fight just fine.
Are some magical girls just more talented?
Well, that's definitely true.
That sucks!
That's not fair at all!
You can't really help that.
Not only does Kyouko have talent, she's also a veteran.
But there are completely inexperienced geniuses who could surpass magical girls like Kyouko through pure talent.
Who would that be?
Kaname Madoka.
Madoka?
Is that true?
Yeah.
That's why if you really want an edge in your fight with Kyouko, you could always ask her.
If she contracts with me...
No!
This is my fight.
I can't get her involved.
A note to customers
「Please do not play and eat or drink at the same time.」
「We reserve the right to refuse customers attempting to hit on customers, perform sales, or
otherwise attempt to take customers to other locales.」
Hey. What do you want this time?
I want to leave this city to you.
What brought this about?
Girls like you are fit to be magical girls.
Miki Sayaka is incompatible.
Hmph. That was always the plan.
What are you planning to do about this Sayaka girl? If you just leave her be, she's going to charge back in again.
I want to end this as peacefully as possible.
Don't interfere. I'll take care of it.
You still haven't told me what I need to know.
Who are you?
What are you after?
A Walpurgis Night will come to this town two weeks from today.
How do you know that?
That's a secret.
Anyway, once that's defeated, I'll leave this city.
You can do what you want after that.
A Walpurgis Night, huh?
That'd be pretty hard to handle myself, but we might be able to win if we team up.
Want some?
It's not going to work. Too much time has passed.
It doesn't look like we have any clues to help locate the familiar from last night.
I see...
Hey, Sayaka-chan.
If you continue to hunt witches, won't you run into the girl from yesterday again?
Well, I guess I would have to, yeah.
Then you should go find her and try to talk things over.
If you don't, you'll end up fighting again before you know it.
A fight, huh?
Did last night look like a normal fight to you?
That wasn't just a fight; we were trying to kill each other.
We were only messing around in the beginning.
By the time we were halfway through, we were seriously trying to kill each other.
That... makes it even worse.
And you want me to try to talk to her?!
Don't be stupid.
She's someone who wants to treat humans like live bait just to get more Grief Seeds.
How am I supposed to get along with someone like that?
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch... She's a magical girl like you!
There's a way to get along if you look for it.
Even if she does things differently, you both want to take out witches, right?
I'm sure she feels the same.
Homura-chan, too.
If Mami-san didn't fight with Homura-chan-
That wouldn't have happened!
You saw her, didn't you?
She waited for Mami-san to get killed before she came to kill the witch!
She let Mami-san die because she wanted the Grief Seed!
That's not what happened...
That transfer student is the same as Kyouko!
They only think about themselves!
I understand that now.
Mami-san was the only one who was different.
All the other magical girls are like those two!
No...
The familiar that got away last night was a small fry, but it'll still kill people!
It could go after your mum or dad next!
Maybe even Takkun!
And you're saying you don't care about that?
Could you really forgive someone if they just let that happen?
I'm not just fighting against witches.
I wanted this power to fight to protect people I care about.
That's why I'll fight anyone worse than the witches themselves,
even if that person is another magical girl.
Sayaka-chan...
Kyubey, say something to her...
The only thing I can tell her is that she's being too reckless.
Sayaka currently has no chance of winning against Akemi Homura or Sakura Kyouko,
but she won't listen to what I say.
Welcome Home
There's some potato salad in the fridge
Tomo
Can't sleep?
Yeah... Mind if I sit down?
Things are going really poorly with my friend.
What she's doing and saying probably isn't wrong,
but the more she tries to do what's right, the worse everything gets.
That happens a lot.
It sucks, but you can't reach a happy ending just by doing what's right all the time.
Actually, the more stubborn people become and insist that they're in the right,
the farther away happiness gets.
It's terrible not being able to be happy even though you're not wrong.
Yeah.
What should I do?
Well, even if someone said something, it wouldn't work itself out nicely, huh?
Do you want to solve this, even if what you choose to do isn't the prettiest method?
Yeah.
Then you just have to do something wrong.
Huh?
Somebody has to be in the wrong to balance out her need to be in the right.
Do something wrong?
Tell a white lie, or run away from something scary.
Sometimes, you realise that was actually the best choice in the end.
Sometimes, when you hit a dead end with no real alternatives, making a big mistake is an option.
Would they understand that I was doing it for them?
They might not. Especially right afterwards.
I told you it might not be the nicest way to do it.
But which do you think is better: you giving up on her completely, or her getting the wrong idea about you?
Madoka, you grew up to be a good girl.
You don't lie, and you don't do anything bad.
You're always trying hard to do what is right.
You're already a wonderful child.
That's why you should start studying how to make mistakes before you grow up.
Studying?
When you're young, you recover from getting hurt faster.
If you learn how to fall down now, it'll be easier for you later on.
When you get older, making mistakes gets harder.
The more things you're responsible for, the less mistakes you can make.
I see.
Isn't that hard?
Being an adult is hard for everybody.
That's why they let you drink.
I want to grow up and drink with you.
Hurry up and get older. As difficult as it is, it's fun being an adult.
Oh, Kamijou-san was released from the hospital yesterday.
His rehabilitation was going well, so his schedule was moved up.
I-I see...
Kami
You're going to go home without even seeing him?
You chased after him all day, too.
You're...
I already know. The boy in this house, right?
He's the reason why you made a contract with Kyubey.
My god, you used your only chance for a miracle on something retarded.
What do you know about what happened?!
You're the one who doesn't get it, idiot.
Magic is supposed to be used one hundred percent for granting your own wishes.
No good comes out of using it for someone else.
Tomoe Mami didn't teach you about that either?
Kami
If you want to make a guy you fell in love with yours, there's a better option using the magic you just got.
W-What?
Rush in there right now and break his hands and legs so he'll never be able to use them again.
Make it so he won't be able to do anything without you any more.
Then he'll be yours. His heart, body, everything.
Kami
If you'd feel bad about that, I can always do it for you.
You know, common courtesy between magical girls.
It'd be simple.
I'll never... I'll never forgive you.
This time I'll...
How about we go somewhere else?
People will probably see us here.
Somebody has to be in the wrong to balance out her need to be in the right.
Yeah, but...
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in trouble!
Follow me!
We won't need to hold back here.
Let's go all out.
Wait, Sayaka-chan!
M-Madoka!
Don't get in the way.
This isn't even any of your business.
No, there's definitely something weird about this!
Hmph. It's not surprising that the annoying bitch has an annoying friend.
Then what would that make your friend?
Damn.
This isn't what we discussed.
I thought I told you to keep your hands off of Miki Sayaka.
Your method wouldn't get the message across!
She's not backing down either way.
I'll take her on, then. Don't get involved.
Then I'll wait until I'm done eating this.
That's plenty of time.
I won't be that easy!
Sayaka-chan, I'm sorry!
Madoka, what the hell?!
But if I didn't...
Sayaka-chan?
That was bad, Madoka.
There must be something wrong with you, throwing your friend like that.
What... What are you saying?
Stop it!
What's going on?!
She's dead!
Sayaka-chan?
Hey, Sayaka-chan?
Wake up! Say something! W-What's wrong?
I don't want this to happen!
Sayaka-chan!
What the hell is going on?
Hey!
You magical girls can only control your bodies from a hundred metres away, at most.
A hundred metres?!
What? What the hell does that mean?
You normally walk around with them, so accidents like this rarely happen.
What are you saying, Kyubey?
Save her! Don't let Sayaka-chan die!
Madoka... That's not Sayaka. It's just an empty container.
You just threw Sayaka.
W-What...?
I couldn't ask you to fight witches with a fragile body just like a normal person's.
A magical girl's old body is nothing more than a piece of external hardware.
Your actual soul is given a much safer, compact form that is capable of controlling magic much more efficiently.
It's part of my job, when I complete a magical girl contract.
I remove your souls and change them into Soul Gems.
What the hell did you do to us?
You bastard! You basically turned us into zombies!
Isn't it more convenient that way?
Even if your heart is torn to shreds, or you lose every drop of blood in your body,
if you heal that damage with magic, you'll be able to operate again right away.
You're basically invincible, provided that your Soul Gem doesn't break.
Isn't that much more useful during a fight than a human body full of potential problems?
That's terrible... That's really awful.
You're all the same. You always act the same way when you're told what's going on.
I don't get it.
Why do humans place so much value on where their soul is located?
What?
What's wrong?
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Illustrator Ueda Hajime
You had a wish so important that you agreed to a fate of combat, am I correct?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
Episode 7     Can you come to terms with how you really feel?
Can you come to terms with how you really feel?