I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Think you forgot this.
But what would an old fart like me
be doing with a stuffed toy?
And I don't have any rugrats either.
But I didn't say it
was yours, now did I?
Yeah, it's a customer's.
A kid probably lost... it.
Hey, listen, the evening's young,
and I know a rockin' joint.
Care to join me
and check it out?
I hit the sack early.
I'm not a night person.
It's a first-rate hotel that offers
free bodyguard service and meals.
The place has every amenity.
One could... live there.
I'm sure they require reservations.
Nope, you don't need
one for Hotel Prison...
Teddy Bomber.
Nice offer, but I'll pass,
Spike Spiegel.
Oh, you know me?
Anyone who has a price on
his head knows who you are.
We dread getting caught
by either you or Andy.
Andy?
I'm finishing what I set out to do.
Sorry, pal. No fireworks today.
'Cause I pulled the ignition pin out.
Three million, pal.
Those Woolongs are mine.
There's more than one bear.
You'll be killed too.
Well, nobody lives forever.
Why do you wanna
blow everything up?
Because, Spiegel,
that's how I deliver a warning.
I'm sounding the alarm.
Alerting the masses.
You'd better listen up
while you still can...
Hm?
Andy!
Andy?
You can call me Wyatt Earp.
Reach for the sky, Teddy Bomber!
Who, me?
I figured that you'd plant
an explosive here today.
It wasn't difficult after
I studied your crime patterns,
and profiled your criminal mind.
That's your serial bomber, there!
Yeah, right, that old security guard.
But look at his face, Andy!
Faces are too unreliable
to count on, nowadays.
Then what do you rely on?
Well, my... gut instinct.
And inspiration.
Hey, come back here!
Wa-hoo!
You're all doomed!
Ah, shit.
I told you that was
Teddy Bomber, you idiot!
Do you have any idea--
Let's ride!
Phee-yew!
That one was mighty close.
Hyah! Giddup!
- Horse, you say?
- Horse. Correct.
A horse, huh? I thought
it sounded kind of fishy
when you said you'd nab him
while you were out foraging.
What do you mean?
I mean you spent all our
food money, didn't you?
- I what?
- What'd you blow it on?
If I'm lying, then how the hell
do you explain this on my back?
Okay, okay, chill.
- I totally buy the horse.
- You do?
But you're lacking creativity in
the cowboy character. He's lame.
Yeah, maybe that's the problem.
Perhaps if he was
a samurai instead.
Now that I wouldn't question!
Here he is, Little Andy!
He was registered as
a member of the YMCA!
- How about that?
- He's a Christian?
No, not that Y.
The Young Men's
Cowboy Association.
I've never heard of that one before.
But he got kicked out
shortly after he joined.
- The reason?
- For being a nuisance to others!
That figures.
Andy von de Oniyate...
He's the heir to
the Oniyate Ranch!
And he's pretty handsome.
Damage to private property: 123 counts.
Damage to public property:
89 counts, numerous injury victims.
He sure reminds me of someone.
- See? He exists!
- All right, all right!
Anything?
No, not yet. However...
We can't chance an explosion
with all these people around.
He's only targeting the building.
Murder isn't part of his M.O.
You sure about that?
His type is more concerned
with aesthetics.
Well, he couldn't pick a better place
to hide than a masquerade party.
There's a serial bomber
coming tonight, you know.
Oh, really? I wasn't aware of that.
Oh, he'll be here.
My man!
It's all about making love and
peace in the world, sugar bear.
Yo.
H-How did you know it was me?
This baby showed us the way to papa.
Yeah, and the teddy bear suit
wasn't a tip-off at all.
Jeez, you guys don't know
when to quit, do you?
Look who's talking.
What's with your bomb obsession, baby?
You wanna know? I'm here to
bring a warning to the world.
Listen, heed these words.
The root of all evil is--
A horse!
A cowboy!
I know that's you, Teddy Bomber!
Who, me?
- I told you.
- Or is it you?
Are you brain-dead, or what?!
We met each other yesterday!
Hmm... I don't recollect.
Why, you--
Excuse me, sir,
horses aren't allowed in here.
And it's quite disturbing
for our guests.
Ah-ha, but my Onyx
is no ordinary steed.
She's a good compadre who eases my
mind and plays a decent game of chess.
- Horses can't play chess!
- Who cares?
If it's one thing I hate,
it's being ignored!
What happened to aesthetics?
Calm down! Calm down, folks!
Remember peace and love!
- My, what a lovely animal.
- You like horses, ma'am?
How about a ride?
Sure, my pleasure.
You--
I've never before in my entire life
seen such a total lack of taste.
Prepare for a treat.
This is my own special recipe
called Son of a Gun Stew.
Mmm, it'll sure blaze a trail.
So why would a man like you
become a bounty hunter?
Since you're so rich--
I mean, you have such
a comfortable lifestyle.
That's true. But why?
I'd have to say
because it suits me.
Uh-huh?
And boy, what a rush!
Like a cowboy cornering a bull!
But seriously, such a dangerous
line of work seems unnecessary.
Now I understand why no one
goes after Teddy Bomber.
Nobody wants to get his butt
blown off in some damn explosion.
Well, we can't worry about that.
Man... I can't worry about that.
When my mind is set,
well, I'm wearing blinders!
Nothing else matters!
The personality is way too familiar...
- Hm?
- Oh, nothing!
Now...
Why don't we drink to me...
and my reflection
in your lovely eyes.
- Cheers.
- Yeah, cheers.
Brought you a souvenir.
Yee-haw! Souvenir! Souvenir!
I'm not gonna eat this can of crap.
- But it's all we've got.
- I'd rather starve.
You'll be sorry.
Andy really pushes your buttons.
What is it about him
that gets you so bent?
I know why he hates the guy.
They're too much alike.
What part of me could be
anything like that stupid ass?!
The part that makes you
so damn troublesome.
Hey, we're missing Big Shot.
It's already on.
Our final news item is on Ted Bower,
the Teddy Bomber, a.k.a. TB.
TB sent a letter to our station
to read on our show.
What?! Are you kidding me?!
Um... here we go.
"A warning."
"All of you who put me down
and laughed at me,"
"the job I do next
is your last chance."
"This time, I will blow you up
as well like fireworks!"
Shucks howdy,
that's a rather harsh tone!
"Unless you can figure out what
my next target will be. Ha, ha, ha."
"Lastly, I shall tell you
my purpose for doing this."
Oops! Well, Judy,
it seems we've run out of time.
That's it for today!
I'm sorry I couldn't read all of it, TB!
Till next time, folks!
Good luck!
- He's gonna blow up City Hall.
- You know already?
Targets have been by height,
starting with the tallest building.
Really, it was something
as simple as that?
I'm out. I don't want this one.
Yeah, I'm gonna pass too.
Spike, what about you?
Like you have to ask!
They're late! Damn them!
Those fools are sadly mistaken if
they think they'll get away with this!
You alone?
How dare you insult me
by showing up late!
Wait.
Damn, it's the wrong guy.
You know, it has never been
my intention to murder anyone.
But in your case,
I'll make an exception!
- Bastards like you deserve to be--
- Shh.
He's here.
So... you again.
Finally remembered me, huh?
- You're always--
- You're always, always butting in!
- Stay outta my way!
- What?
You're the one who's
always in the way!
Now that I have both of you
gentlemen here together,
I will explain my reason
for blowing up things.
- The reason is--
- Let's settle this, once and for all!
- Fellas?
- Dammit, you stole my line!
- Why won't you listen to me?!
- Shut up!
What do you want? Who are you?
Why can't you take me seriously?!
- Shit, we gotta catch him first!
- Wait!
Come on!
You fellas have grossly
underestimated me.
That elevator door is never
going to open again.
Soon the car will start moving,
and that will be the end!
It won't stop until it
arrives at the top floor.
There, my adorable little teddy
bears are waiting to greet you.
And at the very moment
the elevator reaches them?
Boom!
Let me leave you
with a word of advice.
Enjoy the rest of your
lives without regret.
Good luck.
Now, don't panic. I'm one step
ahead of old Teddy Bomber.
Rest assured, I know
exactly how his mind works.
I knew that he would alter the
secret emergency access code,
so I reverted it
this afternoon. Yah!
But I reverted it this afternoon!
If I did, and you did...
That means it's back to what it was!
Stop it, you moron!
Wha-- What do we do?! Oh no!
It's too tight!
- Idiot! We're stuck!
- Let me through! Get outta my way!
Fond farewell.
Come to think of it, they were
a pair of truly brave young men.
They're climbing up.
Like a couple of monkeys.
I guess they like to be up high.
Scary how similar they are.
- Can we leave now?
- Yeah, all right.
I just have to drop
this guy off first.
You don't even deserve to stand
in the shadow of a cowboy.
You're one person who
I could never forgive.
Wow.
Oops.
You win.
That was some punch!
I see now that
you're the real cowboy.
As of today, I retire from the job.
My hat's off to you, partner.
So... what are you gonna do now?
I have no doubt
I'll find some new career.
See you space cowboy.
It was only a rich boy's hobby.
He was on a different level, or should
I say, out of his league with me.
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah, yeah...
Andy wasn't my adversary after all.
Of course, I never really had
anything personal against the guy.
Yow-wee! Ya-haw!
Ya-haw! Ya-hoo!
- Hey, are you listening?
- Yeah, yeah...
Well, anyway...
What were you trying to achieve
by blowing everything up?
I only wanted to
send out a warning...
against the needless waste created
by capitalism without philosophy.
The needless colonization of planets.
The needless circulation
of slanted media.
And needlessly tall buildings
that symbolize all of this!
You see, by destroying these monoliths,
I intended to remind the world what
the pioneering spirit is truly about--
Wait, wait, wait!
Andy!
Call me Musashi!
Go, Jiroumaru!
But then...
it was all needless too, wasn't it.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
So did everyone catch me
in action this past episode?
Hey, wait a minute!
Now about the next episode...
Why are you doing the preview?
Once again, I, Andy,
will be the man in action.
You had your turn already!
Now that I've become a space samurai,
I will slice up the cowboys one by one!
I said, you're not coming back!
Next time on Cowboy Bebop:
"Andy's Counterattack!"
That's not the right title!
"Brain Scratch"