Precure! Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
Cure Marine!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
You've been paying attention, haven't you?
You gotta make Marine look cooler than that!
Coffret!
Rumi!
Jeez, Rumi!
Naminami!
Shiku!
Why's Rumi so upset?
There was going to be a puppet show at her kindergarten, but they canceled it.
They're all really upset.
How disappointing.
Hey, I know! Could you put on a
puppet show with your plushies?
A puppet show?
Well, um, I dunno if that's...
Yeah, thought so.
I figured they were really precious to you, but it was worth asking.
Let'sh do it!
L-Let'sh do it!
Let'sh?
W-We'd be happy to put on a show for you!
Y-You're good at that, Itsuki!
W-We've always wanted to do something like this!
Thank you!
Yay!
Yesh!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Ms. Noriko, are the puppets here yet?
I wanna see the puppets!
They'll be here soon, okay?
Ms. Noriko!
Come play with us!
No!
You can go play with a ball, Kouta!
We wanna play with her!
Don't pull!
One at a time!
Ms. Noriko!
This is for you!
She fell for it!
What are you kids doing?
You mustn't tease Ms. Noriko like that!
Honestly, you're far too lenient with these kids.
You need to keep them in line!
Sorry, I got all caught up in the moment.
Well, just keep it in mind.
Right...
The Fairies Transform?!
We're Putting on a Precure Show!
Ms. Noriko, let's play house!
But the puppet show's about to start!
Come on kids, sit down.
The puppets aren't here yet, though!
We wanna play!
Okay, just for a bit, then.
Come and sit down, everyone.
Um...
The puppets will go home if
you don't sit down and watch.
No way!
I'm so nervous.
All right, this is our moment!
Oh no!
S-Somebody save us!
Nobody will save you!
I hates humans! I hates them so much!
Erika, you're not supposed to actually frighten them!
Hold it, evildoer!
Stop that at once!
There you are, accursed Precure!
We're gonna crush you flat!
Get them, Precure!
Don't lose to him, Precure!
Stomp that Desertrian!
Marine Dive!
Sunflower Aegish!
Why don't you go and watch the show, Hiro?
I don't wanna watch some dumb kids show!
You aren't scared of the monster, are you?
O-Of course not!
Blossom Kick!
Now you've done it!
Hiro actually behaved for once...
I'll get you for this!
We'll punish the forces of evil!
They really loved the show!
Yeah!
Feel free to dance along too.
Okay!
They're all getting into it!
She's far better with these kids than I am.
I can't hold a candle to her.
Delicious!
Thanks for the food!
This is really nice!
Yeah!
Are you okay, Rumi?
Thank you.
Ms. Noriko!
I dropped my spoon!
Give me a second!
Ms. Noriko!
What is it?
You don't get much of a chance to eat your lunch, do you?
I'm used to it by now.
The kids always have me rushing around for them.
I know I should be able to keep them in check like she can, and yet...
Ms. Noriko!
Can you peel my orange for me?
Of course I can, Haruka!
I'm the Orange Monster!
Come on, don't play with your food.
Orange, orange!
I wanna play too!
Kouta, please!
You think you can beat the Orange Monster?!
Yeah! Cause I'm Orange Superman W!
If I beat you, I'll be the Orange King!
What?!
What about my orange?
It's on!
Take this! Orange Punch!
I need to keep them in check.
I have to stop them from misbehaving.
I have to...
S-Stop it!
Sit down and... eatyourlunch...
Ms. Noriko?
What are you doing?
Just sit down and eat!
You're acting really weird today, Ms. Noriko.
Losing Sasorina was unexpected.
She fought hard, until her last breath.
But the HeartCatch Mirage's power is truly remarkable.
King Dune shall soon arrive on Earth.
It is imperative that we destroy the Precure before he arrives.
Sir!
Kumojacky?
I'm going to avenge Sasorina's death.
I'll smash their HeartCatch Mirage into pieces!
Just sit down and eat!
You're acting really weird today, Ms. Noriko.
How very convenient.
Wh-Who are you?
I am Kumojacky, a commander of the Desert Apostles.
I will use the weakened Flower of your Heart to draw out those Precure!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
A Desertrian?!
Ms. Noriko's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen!
We need to transform!
Leave the children to me.
Thanks!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
There you are.
You really do seem to have gotten stronger.
But know this! I'm far stronger than Sasorina was.
It's time you runts learned that for yourselves!
Blossom!
Right!
What's going on?
Help us, Ms. Noriko!
Ms. Noriko!
I love those kids so much.
But I need to make them listen to what I say!
I can't keep spoiling them like this!
How can I be firm with them like she is?!
How can I be a proper influence on those kids?!
See for yourself, Desertrian!
Where are you, Ms. Noriko?!
I'm scared, Ms. Noriko!
Ms. Noriko!
Do you hear that?
The first person they call for when they awaken
is their beloved Ms. Noriko!
You! You, and nobody else!
And yet you want to change, to be someone else?!
Tch! Get them already, Desertrian!
You dumb monster! Where have you taken Ms. Noriko?!
Give back Ms. Noriko!
Where are you, Ms. Noriko?!
Get lost, monster!
Believe in the children!
They all love you the way you are!
Ms. Noriko!
Give back Ms. Noriko!
What a pathetic Desertrian!
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
We can't fight him here!
Let's get him away from the kids!
Right!
You're not getting away!
Those weak attacks won't even scratch me!
Are you okay?
Moonlight!
Apologies for the delay.
I take it you noticed how defenseless he is when shooting those wind blasts from his mouth?
That's when we strike.
Okay!
You want to get blown away that badly?!
Sunflower Aegis!
Blossom Shoot!
Marine Dive!
Now!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
Retreat!
Let's restore the Flower of her Heart!
Ms. Noriko?
What have I...
Are you okay, Ms. Noriko?
Ms. Noriko, do you need to rest?
Does it hurt anywhere, Ms. Noriko?
I'm sorry...
for worrying you all.
Come closer, Hiro.
This is for you.
Jeez, you scared me!
Ms. Noriko...
I'm sorry.
Come on, join us!
Yeah!
Thank you, everyone.
I love you all so much!
In the language of flowers,
a safflower means "tolerance."
She extends her kindness to the children around her.
She finally remembered the talent she truly has.
I'm sure they'll grow to love her even more now!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Kumojacky was no match for the Mirage either.
It seems your power...
no, you yourself will be required,
Dark.
It won't be long now.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Could this letter adorned with a heart be...
It's a love letter!
I've never seen one before!
So a guy finally took note of my good points, huh?
No, this is clearly addressed to me!
Settle down, you three!
Then who is it for?
What are you doing, girls?
Wait, is this love letter for...
HeartCatch Precure:
Yuri's Lost at Sea!
We Saw His Love Letter...
We'll catch everyone's hearts!