Where... am I?
Class A river
River Styx
Hell
Class A river
River Styx
Hell
Class A river
River Styx
Hell
Burnt-out bums
Still alive
Is this... the river Styx?
Come here! Come over here!
This is a nice place!
Look how much fun we're having!
There's nothing to be afraid of, Akihisa.
This really is a great place.
Yuuji! Why are you on that side?
Don't be afraid, Akihisa.
As you can see, I'm perfectly all right.
Don't worry about me.
Come here!
A single or a couple without love, which one is...
FABULOUS?
Love!
How far do we take our chat
of my colorfully rotating future?
Pretending not to notice!
How far do we take our chat of my colorfully rotating future?
My feelings for this giant world are evergrowing
I'm loving today, too
I'm really looooo-ving it!
looooo-ving it!
My idiocy is truly more vast than the ranks of the stars
Honestly still cannot accept that
I had a dream of walking with you
Still I'm sorry
Because I did not know about love, you know.
Answer: You and the riddling me are an infinite jump!
Episode 2
Me, Yukata, and the Uproar at the Festival
Where are we?
I don't really remember, but I feel I just saw Hell.
Whence I saw you two muttering deliriously, I did think you were done for.
We're alive... somehow.
Akihisa and Yuuji took on a challenge to hit on girls.
They were found out and punished accordingly.
It was probably one hell of a punishment.
I'm surprised they not only did that, but also that.
Still, we didn't really expect this to happen.
Yeah, we really crossed the line this time.
It's an unspeakable offense to go girl-hunting when you're already with some girls.
Then again, the punishment was much lighter than I had expected.
One doth not call a near-death experience "light punishment".
I can't believe they let us off with just this.
They might still have something else in store for us.
What do we do, Yuuji? Run away?
Who's running away?
Ah, you all changed into yukata!
Yes, it's a festival, after all.
How is it, Akihisa?
It really looks good on you!
I think this is my first time wearing a yukata.
Oh right, you were raised abroad, Minami.
What're you looking at?
Ah, nothing.
She charmed you for a second, didn't she?
She's even cuter wearing yukata.
What are you—
Kimonos are so practical. They look nice even with small breasts, don't they?
I really don't understand what you're talking about—
Let me show you then.
Look.
Peek.
See? His reaction was faster than usual!
Whatever in the world?
Get a hold of thyself, Voyeur!
I don't really mind this kind of bad end.
Yuuji...
...how do you like my yukata?
It suits you.
Then, do you want to marry me?
Not at all.
Then, do you want to get engaged?
Not in the slightest.
Then, Yuuji...
No way.
Do you want to stay alive?
You're so cute, Shouko!
You're not honest, Yuuji.
You made me say that!
My mother told me all is fair in love and war.
What happened to the girls?
I thought they'd all be mad at us.
Well then, let's all head to the festival!
That's right, Akira.
It'd be a shame if we were late.
This will be my second festival in Japan, and I'm looking forward to it so much!
Let's hurry!
It's so lively!
It looks like so much fun!
Oh look, are those Turkish kebabs?
They look really delicious.
Don't they? Then let's give 'em a try!
As punishment, you'll pay, Aki.
I should've just kept my mouth shut.
Aki, will you try some too? My treat.
Yeah, I have no objec—
What? You will?
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
What's going on? There's no way she's forgiven me so quickly...
Let's share it!
I want to try out the other stalls too.
Then you take the first bite.
Really? Thanks.
They don't make it out of lamb here in Japan.
Here, have a bite, Aki.
It's great!
Hey, Aki, there's sauce on your cheek.
Thank you, Sis.
Akihisa, I bought some octopus dumplings!
Would you like some?
Thank you, Himeji.
I'll have one.
Here, say, "Ah."
Is something wrong, Akihisa?
No, nothing.
Then say, "Ah."
It's hot and juicy, and the squid makes it chewy too.
This isn't what it looks like, Sis!
It's not an illicit sexual relationship!
What's wrong, Aki?
Did it taste bad?
Are you fooling around again, Aki?
You look like you're having so much fun.
You're really just a kid.
You're having fun too, aren't you, Minami?
I just got these as gifts!
You've lived in Germany for so long, so I guess you were quite the attraction.
I know! Do you want some cotton candy?
It's really good!
Sure...
Okay, say, "Ah."
Is it good?
Yeah! It's great!
I'm so glad!
Yuuji, do you want some fried noodles?
Yeah, I guess that'd be nice.
I have some pizza pancakes too.
That was fast.
Here, lemonade.
Thank you.
That's nice, it looks like Yuuji's been forgiven too.
It's a festival, after all. Everyone wants to have fun instead of being angry.
Akihisa!
They are selling colored chicks yonder!
I thought they were extinct.
Oh, those are just painted.
Heavens, I dide think they were endangered.
Of course not!
Right, Voyeur?
Dyed chicks
I'll paint you in my colors!
Yeah, that's common knowledge.
Aki, are you having fun?
Yeah.
Yuuji, is it fun?
Y-Yeah.
The First
Evening
Delight
Miss
Yukata
Contest
Hey, Akihisa, there's something interesting here too.
The First Evening Delight Miss Yukata Contest?
A beauty contest?
It looks interesting.
Time to get some good shots!
Come
see the
prettiest girl
in town
Shall we go watch too?
Why don't you girls participate?
I don't really want to force you or anything.
I mean... I thought it'd be a nice memory of the summer...
That's a good idea.
Really?
Yeah, let's enter the contest!
I'm sure it'll be memorable.
Let's participate!
All of us.
Troops dismissed!
Where do you think you're going?
Everyone will enter the contest.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't get it either!
You didn't think that...
we'd forgive you that easily...
did you?
It's fine. I brought makeup!
Wait! I can't cross-dress with my build!
Please just make Akihisa cross-dress and let me go!
You want to leave me in trouble alone?
Damn you... you... you traitor!
You two just don't know when to give up.
Just accept it as men. Look at Tsuchiya!
They're so, so cruel, Hideyoshi.
My apologies, but 'tis in their nature to go full force.
Makeup is also a part of the performance, nay?
Yoshii Akiko
Did they have to go this far?
Tsuchiya Koumi
This is humiliating.
Tsuchiya Koumi? Why...?
Huan Shunli
You got off easy, Voyeur!
I'm supposed to be a cross-dressing foreigner!
Well, there are lots of foreign sportswomen with your physique.
You three look gorgeous!
Yeah, you're so cute!
I'm so glad you grew up to be beautiful, Aki.
You shouldn't say that about your little brother.
You don't have enough sex appeal, Yuuji.
You still have complaints?!
By the way...
...why must I enter as well?
That goes without saying.
Question 2:
Translate the following sentence into Japanese.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
"John wanted to take a flight
to Japan with his wife's
home-cooked lunch,
but realized while boarding
that he'd forgotten his passport."
Teacher's comment:
Correct.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
"John-"
Teacher's comment:
is John.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
"John boarded a flight to
Japan with a home-cooked
passport."
Teacher's comment:
Please think again what
"home-cooked passport" really means.
Let me get the First Evening Delight Miss Yukata Contest started!
The First Evening Delight Miss Yukata Contest
Obata
Chairman
Besides being one of the judges, I will also be giving the commentary tonight.
To my right is Mr. Obata. A few words, please.
I hope we'll see some hotties show up in yukata.
Well then, good luck!
It'll be all right! No one will find out!
Yuuji, believe in yourself, and you can win.
Can I now?!
I'll be sure to film all your cute moments!
Dammit!
It's almost time, Yuuji.
Let's just lose quickly and get released!
I have an idea! We should just reveal that we're guys!
That won't work.
What if there are people from our school in the crowd?
If they find out,
they'll not only call us cross-dressers,
but they'll think we're disgusting exhibitionists,
confident enough to enter a contest like this!
If that happens, my reputation will be ruined!
Methinks 'twas not in much good state to begin with.
Listen. Our only way out of this crisis
is to lose the contest without getting found out!
This is a fight with our masculinity at stake!
Thank you for your applause.
Round 1 is over
Show your appreciation, folks!
Next     up
Round 2 has begun!
Contestant number one, please come on stage!
The First Evening Delight Miss Yukata Contest
Contest points
Inner voice
What do I do now?
Please tell us your name.
I'll hide my face and answer in a really soft voice.
I'm Yoshii Akiko.
Well, it looks like Akiko is quite shy.
She's dressed quite cutely.
This is worth a lot of points.
Why?
Do you have any special talents?
If I say something really outrageous, I might get caught if they cross-examine me.
If I had to say, I'd say cooking.
Paella, carbonara, and whatnot.
Do you cook at home?
Yes, almost every day.
That's not something you see in girls these days.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't!
Recruiting a boyfriend
That's good news for the men in the crowd!
Any further comments, Mr. Obata?
Give me your cell number, and I'll babysit you.
Thank you. If you weren't a sponsor, I'd knock you out.
Akiko, what did you pay attention to when putting on that yukata tonight?
Contest points
Inner voice
That it wouldn't show much of my figure.
I see.
Do you have any comments about Akiko's great dress, Mr. Obata?
Please tell me if you're wearing underwear!
Underwear? Girl's underwear?
I don't!
Thank you for answering such a shockingly vulgar question.
Nice high score.
Damn.
Inner voice
What's your name?
My name is Tsuchiya Koumi.
Did you come here to bathe in the sea today?
Yes.
Do you often wear yukata?
No.
Are you with your friends today?
Yes.
Are they here with us?
No.
Then, what kind of clothes do you like besides yukata?
Chinese dresses, kimonos, race queen, cheerleader, nurse,
flight attendant, waitress, and policewoman outfits, leotard,
pants suits, sailor suits, blazers,
shrine maiden, maid, and tennis outfits are all simply breathtaking—
Oh, nothing really.
This is a surprise!
Despite her cool attitude, Koumi is quite the cosplayer!
Please forget what I just said!
Koumi
T-This is so embarrassing.
Look at the crowd cheering for you!
I believe you'll definitely make it to the finals!
Please, this is really embarrassing.
Nice goal.
Why did this happen...?
I'm Huan Shunli! Nice to meet you!
Inner voice
My, she's a tall contestant!
What do you think of her, Mr. Obata?
Amazing! I love tall women!
What?!
The judge just gave high praise to the contestant!
Any further quest—Huh?
How would you like the honeymoon in Cambodia?
I think you're mistaken about my nationality.
It'll be fine. Just say yes, my honey.
I'm not your honey!
I was confident you'd say, "Yes"!
I hate you!
I don't mind if we have to start out as friends.
I'll treasure you forever!
Cut it! I'll beat you into a pulp, you shitty geezer!
You can do whatever you want to me!
I won't allow you to have an affair.
Shouko! Why?!
This has seriously wounded my heart.
It's going to be hard to forget this summer. That's for sure.
I'm ruined for marriage.
'Tis good the contest was canceled.
Too bad we had no winners.
We kind of went too far, didn't we?
Let's forgive them now.
Considering everything that's happened,
it seems like they've reflected on what they did,
so let's forgive them, just this once.
But I wonder who would've won if the contest went on.
I wonder. I'd bet on Hideyoshi.
All hell would break loose if I'd stepped foot on that stage.
I think Voyeur's cross-dressing was very cute.
How about you, Akira?
Hmm. I'm already used to Aki cross-dressing,
so I preferred the other two.
Hey, wait, Sis! I don't cross-dress!
Whatever are you saying, Aki?
Weren't you wearing a skirt last night when you were sleeping?
What did you do to me while I was sleeping?!
Don't worry. Half of it is a lie.
Lie
A lie?
How can you make just half of that a lie?
Because it was only slightly above your knees.
So you put it on me just halfway?!
No, in this case, I'd say I pulled it half down.
Half down
Half down...
Okay, guys, I think it's ready!
Let's eat!
It tastes great!
Sakamoto's really good at this.
My pride, my husband.
I wanted to help cook too, but Akihisa wouldn't let me.
It's not like I would've gotten in his way or anything.
That's not it, Himeji.
It's just that you don't need a kitchen knife to kill people.
If she got her hands on one, though, we'd be even more dead.
A murderous meal.
There's no way we'd let such a dangerous person cook.
Then how about we girls have a cooking competition next time?
The guys can be the judges.
Please don't!
But how do you decide the victor of a cooking competition?
Knockout or technical knockout, I think.
'Twas filling.
I'm still hungry, though.
But we have no ingredients left.
Then let's find some!
Find?
We have the whole sea before us!
A fresh crab would be nice fried!
I see!
Now that you mention it...
I once made madeleine cake at home.
Let's go find some crabs, Yuuji!
Yeah, Akihisa! Let's get so many that we can't eat anything afterward!
Isn't the night sea so inviting, Voyeur?
I love crabs!
What's wrong with them?
Who knows?
And how was that madeleine cake?
Yeah, I made a madeleine cake, but I forgot about it after I put it in the oven.
That's a shame.
I won't die yet!
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go
I've fallen in love
I don't want any doubts in my heart
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway
Sparkling, glittering
The right answer is pop!
Goodness, they're fast asleep like little kids.
Guys will always be children at heart.
Look at those innocent sleeping faces.
So cute.
They must be tired from running around like that.
I'm glad they had so much fun.
They really fell asleep in no time.
They were staggering before we got in the car too.
They ate such a healthy breakfast,
but it just made them more sleepy.
They must've been hungry.
They didn't even leave us anything.
It's really a shame, Mizuki.
Yeah.
I didn't get to ask them if they liked the breakfast I made.
Come here!
This is a nice place!
Question 3:
Answer the following
question.
List things you
must not bring to
school.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
Manga, videogames and
other toys
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
School is a place of learning,
not just lexical studies but
the correct social stance as well.
It's not enough to attend classes.
One must also be able to live with regulations.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
Can you put a snack into
a banana?
Teacher's comment:
Should I say, "That's bananas!"
Question three: List things you must not bring to school.
Can you put a snack into a banana?
Should I say, "That's bananas!"
Next time: Me, that girl, and a plushie.
This will be on the test.