See? See?
This thing really flies!
Y-You're a surprisingly advanced driver...
Oh, yes!  I may not look it,
but I'm a driving maniac!
Of all the toys Kiritsugu has given me,
this is definitely my favorite!
It's a toy?
Back at the castle,
I could only do laps around
the inner courtyard.
So this feels great!
Wouldn't hiring a chauffeur
have been better?
Oh, that's no fun.
I mean, it's too dangerous.
What if the enemy were to ambush us?
I suppose...
Stop!
Irisviel...
Get out of the car,
and stay close to me.
I sense he's a Servant.
I have come for you, my holy virgin.
Do you know him?
I do not think so.
Don't say that!
You must surely remember my face!
I have never seen you before this night.
Perhaps you have me
mistaken for another?
It's me!
Gilles de Rais...
I prayed for your resurrection,
longed for the miracle that
would reunite us,
and even leapt through time
to find you,
Jeanne!
Jeanne?
I know neither your name,
nor that of the Jeanne
of whom you speak.
No...
Can you have really
forgotten your past life?
As you have revealed your
true name to me,
I am honor-bound, as a knight,
to give you mine.
I am Arturia.
Daughter of Uther Pendragon,
and King of Britain.
Summoned to this era as the Saber class.
How regrettable!
How heart-wrenching...
This isn't simple amnesia, but madness!
Damn you...
Damn you!
How much more torture
must my maiden endure
before God is sated?!
Cease your pathetic ravings!
Awaken!
Cast aside the mantle of Saber.
The Holy Grail War has
its victor already!
Without spilling a single drop of blood,
the Grail has chosen me, Gilles!
I know this, because my wish
has been granted.
My virgin angel, Jeanne d'Arc,
has been revived!
Mock the prayers of our fellow
Heroic Spirits any further,
and next time, I shan't miss!
Stand up!
Your mind is locked away so tightly, Jeanne.
I suppose I have no choice.
Clearly, drastic measures are called for,
and I must prepare accordingly.
I swear this to you, Jeanne.
I will free your soul from the
wretched curse of God.
Another enemy unable to keep up
a proper conversation.
How exhausting.
Next time, I shall slay him before
he can utter a single word.
I loathe dealing with that type.
Nonetheless, I have been
fortunate tonight.
I sensed he was far too dangerous
an opponent for me to fight
with my left hand still injured.
Tailing Saber's Master has proved
surprisingly helpful.
We've even located Caster.
Both trails are worth following.
That's no good.
The thumb should go here.
There we go...
Perfect!
Oh, welcome back, sir!
Hey!  Come on...
Wretched God!
His accursed shackles still bind
my dear Jeanne's soul!
Jeanne?  The woman you saw
in the crystal ball?
We must prove it beyond
the shadow of a doubt!
Prove that God has no power,
prove that love is in vain!
That no deed, no matter how evil,
merits divine punishment!
Yeah, yeah.  I feel you...
Damn, you're cool!
Therefore!
We must fall further from grace,
commit unspeakable blasphemies,
create an entire mountain of sacrifices!
Uh, so...
It's quantity over quality now?
Precisely, precisely!
Astute as always, Ryuunosuke.
We will start by sacrificing
the eleven in the cells immediately.
Then we'll need a new set
of children to slaughter.
Kinda seems like a waste, though.
Ah, well...
We interrupt your regularly
scheduled programming
for an emergency news brief.
Unexplained Explosion
An unexplained explosion occurred tonight,
at a Fuyuki City bayside warehouse district.
We go live to the scene where...
What prevented you from
killing Saber tonight,
not once, but twice?
I even had to squander a Command Spell,
and still, you didn't end it!
Was your battle really that much fun?
It's not like that.
I swear it on my pride as a knight:
I will bring you Saber's head.
I don't need to hear you
swearing anything!
Of course you will!
You made a pact with me
to acquire the Holy Grail!
And yet you swear to defeat only Saber?
I don't think you understand
how this works!
Are you sure you aren't the one
who's mistaken,
Lord El-Melloi?
Sola-Ui...
Lancer fought well.
I think the problem was rooted
in your judgment.
Saber is the strongest of
all our opponents.
I didn't want to miss my chance
to eliminate her.
You dealt her a wound that cannot heal.
All that's changed is that now you can defeat
her at any time you please.
And if you're so concerned by
the threat Saber poses,
why did you not target her Master instead?
You were hiding in the shadows,
like a pitiful coward.
Kayneth,
I don't know if you fully realize
the advantage you hold
over the other Masters.
You added a non-standard clause to
the traditional Master-Servant pact.
The Command Spells are yours,
while I act as a secondary Master
and mana supply.
Only the Necromancy Department's
top performer could have
pulled that off.
It's best to be conservative
in the early going...
Oh, really?
But you were in such a hurry to
have Lancer finish her off.
That's enough, please.
Any more, and I shall have to take it
as an insult to my Master.
As a knight, I cannot permit it.
Oh, no.  I didn't mean...
I'm sorry.  I went too far.
What's that?
Okay, thank you.
A fire on a lower floor.
An arsonist, I'm sure.
Arson?  On tonight of all nights?
They're just clearing the place out.
Then we're under attack?
Obviously, Saber's Master will want to
break the spear's curse
as quickly as possible.
Lancer, go downstairs,
and greet them properly.
Do not let her escape alive.
As you wish.
Perhaps our guests would like to test
the magic atelier of Kayneth El-Melloi?
I've reserved an entire floor for my perfected atelier.
Twenty-four layers of barriers.
Three mana circuits.
Dozens of demonic spirits,
acting as guard dogs.
Countless traps.
And hallways containing portals leading
to alternate dimensions.
A match in which we can both use
our powers to their full extent.
When I'm done, I'll have you retract
that "pitiful coward" remark.
I shall be happy to.
Mr. Archibald!
Mr. Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald!
Are you here, sir?
Yes!
Don't worry, I'm right here.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and his wife,
Sola-Ui, have evacuated the building.
I see...  Yes, very good, then.
Everyone's accounted for.
Good.
All set here.  What's our status?
All clear.  Awaiting your signal.
Maiya...
The target has not moved at all.
He did not evacuate the hotel.
A 150-meter free-fall...
No magic barrier would
protect you from that.
Fall back, Maiya.
Look at this.
It's difficult to believe that a mage
would resort to destroying an entire building.
But then...
Perhaps that's what makes you an expert
at outwitting your fellow mages.
Kotomine Kirei...
I don't believe we've ever met,
but perhaps, you have a reason to know me?
In that case, I can guess who you are.
I dislike talking to myself, woman.
Just answer me this.
Where is the man who
should have been here
in your stead?!
Not bad at all.
You've been well trained.
She didn't throw this.
Oh, well.
Just learning that someone else
is watching out for her
has made this worthwhile.
Kirei-sama.
I told you not to show yourself in public.
My apologies.
However, I have an urgent message to relay.
We have located Caster.
I had Assassin proceed with
an investigation.
Caster and his Master
have been snatching children
from their beds,
in Miyama and in the next town over.
Over the course of the night,
they abducted fifteen.
I'm nearly certain...
that they are the serial killer
that's had everyone up
in arms recently.
They use magic with reckless abandon,
making no attempt, whatsoever, to hide it.
It seems as if they're not even particularly
interested in the Holy Grail War.
A mad Servant running amok,
with a Master who doesn't care
enough to control him?
Why would the Grail have
chosen trash like that?
We cannot ignore this, Tokiomi-kun.
Their actions are in flagrant violation
of the rules!
Absolutely.
As a fellow mage, charged with the
protection of magic's secrets,
I won't stand for this.
Our only real choice is to eliminate
Caster and his Master.
Unfortunately, that will mean pitting
one of our Servants against them.
And I cannot deploy my Assassin.
I do have the authority to make
minor rule changes.
Let us convince the other Masters to
ally with us, against Caster.
Archer?
You are better stockpiled than Tokiomi,
even if it is a lesser quantity.
What a pretentious pupil he has...
What do you want?
I imagined you must be as bored as I.
Bored?
Why else would a Master
under Church protection
be gallivanting about town alone?
I don't know what you mean.
Are you already dissatisfied
with your pact, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi summoned me into this world,
and his mana keeps my body here.
And how could I ignore such an
earnest vow of allegiance?
But I had no idea he'd be so insufferable.
You don't care for
Master Tokiomi's strategy?
Reach the swirl of the Root?
A dull goal for a dull man.
Finding the Root is a desire
peculiar to mages.
Those who are not mages
shouldn't comment.
In a sense, searching for
the path to the Root
is tantamount to searching for
the exit to this very world.
We who think only of the inside
can only perceive it as a foolish endeavor.
Interesting.
But what of you, Kirei?
What would you ask of the Grail?
Me?
I have no wish for the Grail to grant...
Oh, come now.
Does the Grail not choose only
those worthy of its power?
That was my understanding.
I have no answer.
I cannot guess why it would
choose me for this war
when I have neither ideals
nor desires of my own.
No ideals or desires, you say?
Then why not simply wish for bliss?
Never! For my own bliss?
You would have me stain my soul,
with such a sin?
Sin? Stain your soul?
Is that not a bit much?
Why do you equate bliss with sin?
I...
Yes, bliss gained by wickedness
would be a sin.
But happiness may be achieved
through good works, as well.
To associate bliss with sin,
as an absolute,
where is the logic in that?
There is no happiness within me.
Even should I search, I will not find it.
Kotomine Kirei...
Suddenly, I find you quite intriguing.
How do you mean?
Exactly as I've said.
Take a seat.
Put another way, perhaps bliss is one
shape the soul may take.
It is not a question of whether it exists,
but whether you know its appearance.
Kirei,
to claim there is no happiness within you
is but to admit you have no idea
what shape your soul has taken.
I hardly need a lowly Servant
to lecture me.
Don't start snapping at me, cur.
Your tutor is a king who's sampled every
form of bliss and luxury this world offers.
Now hold your tongue.
Kirei, you should learn
what pleasure really is.
Direct your gaze externally.
In fact,
why not begin by joining me right now?
I have no time to waste on frivolity.
Don't say that.
You can afford to enjoy yourself
between Tokiomi's errands.
Tell me, Kirei...
Your job is to monitor the
other five Masters, is it not?
It is.
Don't focus merely on their intentions and strategies.
Look at their motivations, as well.
Then tell me about them.
I could ask the Assassins.
But, Archer, why should you
care about all that?
I've told you.
I enjoy watching people as
they scurry about.
At least one or two should turn out
to be interesting...
Compared to Tokiomi, at least.
Fine, Archer.  I'll play along.
But it will take some time.
That's just fine.  I shall be patient.
In the meantime,
I have your wine to occupy me.
A reason for seeking the Holy Grail...
I was too unguarded.
Certainly, it isn't for bliss or happiness!
However,
if I can learn what motivates that man,
will I learn what it is that I seek, as well?
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Episode 6
A Night of Schemes
I shall temporarily be changing the rules.
They will kill Emiya Kiritsugu.
We can get away!  It's not too late!
My spear will pierce Saber's skull!
I won't fight you for the Grail!
Don't get cocky with me, little girl!
Next Time:
Dark Forest