[TAMA]
There exists a room of sorrow.
It has a window, and the views
from it can be seen clearly.
Everyone besides me,
they look so happy.
I can see them and
the world they live in
moving and changing,
but I'm frozen in place here.
In this lonely room,
I waited for the day
I could finally go outside.
However, there are
no doors in this place.
So because of this, I want
the world outside the window
to stop and stand still,
just like it is in here.
And that is my only wish.
[HANAYO (Y)]
You actually came.
I'm surprised,
but I'm glad you did.
Yeah, this isn't
awkward at all, huh?
[HANAYO (Y) laughs]
I bet.
But I wanted to talk
to you about something.
[YUZUKI]
Yeah, what?
You hate me, don't you?
I can't blame you.
Yuzuki...
[YUZUKI]
How far did you go with him?
[HANAYO (Y)]
How far?
A kiss, that's it.
You... kissed him?
[YUZUKI]
No, it's okay!
Look, you've gotta remember
that was my wish, too.
All Hanayo did was fulfill it.
She did what I couldn't.
She kissed him!
Something that I never had the
guts to do with Kazuki myself!
[BOTH gasp]
But he's--
[laughing]
[YUZUKI]
Hey, what's so funny, Hanayo?
[HANAYO (Y)]
You haven't changed,
even after being an LRIG.
Still straightforward
and gullible.
Hey, watch it!
And hurt easily while trying
your hardest to look strong.
But you know what?
You and Kazuki
are so much alike.
I need you to understand
that when I started this,
all I wanted was
to grant your wish.
One that wasn't easy to bear.
[STUDENT 11A]
Isn't that...?
--[STUDENTS laughing]
--[STUDENT 11D] Gross.
[gasps]
[HANAYO (Y)]
When we were together,
that's all I thought about.
At least at first.
But soon...
I realized that I
was in love with him too.
Oh no...
[HANAYO (Y)] That's why
I can't do this anymore.
Don't get me wrong,
I love Kazuki.
But I like you a lot as well!
I know in my heart that if
finding happiness with Kazuki
becomes my wish and not yours,
then that would be a total
betrayal to you, Yuzuki!
Hanayo...
[HANAYO (Y)]
And I don't want that!
I can't betray you
or deceive him!
Kazuki doesn't know the truth
and he believes that I'm you!
He's so sweet, I can't keep--
[crashing noise]
Kazuki...
[KAZUKI]
What was that about?
Yuzuki... What was all
that stuff you were saying?
[RUKO]
Um...
No!
[gasps]
[KAZUKI]
Yuzuki? What's going on here?
Kazuki, hold on!
Kazuki, look,
you're not a Selector,
so you can't
hear Yuzuki's voice!
Hanayo, wait!
"Yuzuki's voice?"
"Hanayo?"
Yuzuki. Listen.
I'm really sorry about this,
but I can't fulfill your wish!
[RUKO]
Hanayo, wait!
--Yuzuki!
--[HITOE] No, let them go!
I'll explain everything
about what happened to Yuzuki,
but you have to listen.
What do you mean?
[HITOE]
Um...
[MAYU crying]
[MAYU] I don't get it.
Why don't they understand?
Even the ones I created.
They're leaving me behind, too!
[URITH] Don't worry.
I'll stand beside you.
[RUKO]
Hanayo!
Oh my gosh!
[RUKO]
Are you okay?
[HITOE]
Ruko!
[YUZUKI]
Where's Hanayo?
Hanayo!
Continue to fulfill my wish!
I don't care if you think
you're betraying me, just do it!
You have to keep it up
or else you're gonna die!
Don't stop!
[HITOE]
Yuzuki, calm down.
It's okay.
Yuzuki... She'll be fine.
[sobbing]
[RUKO]
So... You believe us?
I can feel her
presence in this card.
So yes, I do.
If an Eternal Girl
doesn't fulfill her wish,
then she ends up disappearing.
That's why we gotta save Hanayo.
I've gotta hurry
and become an LRIG.
You only have one win.
You'll have to fight
a lot more Battles.
[YUZUKI]
There's not enough time!
[HITOE] Then I'll
start battling again!
As long as it's not
with the same LRIG,
I can do it too, right?
So now...
We just have to split up
and find Selectors--
[YUZUKI]
It'll be too late!
Hanayo doesn't have long!
[IONA] Maybe you don't
have to win multiple times.
Think back to what happened
when you were a
Selector before.
You were on the verge of having
your wish granted, but then...
Tama didn't accept it,
and as a result of that,
an Eternal Girl wasn't born.
Does that mean...?
If Tama is willing
to accept Ruko's wish now,
it can come true
and end this whole mess?
Yeah, but...
I thought you couldn't
even go to the White Room
unless you became an LRIG first.
[IONA] Yes, but the Battlefield
is linked to the White Room.
What?
Tama will be nearby,
so I'll call out to
her during the Battle.
And if my voice is
indeed able to reach her...
Then that means
my wish can be granted!
Yuzuki...
[YUZUKI]
Um, Hitoe?
Can you ask Kazuki
something for me, please?
Huh?
I know this is kind of weird,
but it's eating me up inside.
I need to know if he loves me
or Hanayo in my form better.
Okay.
[YUZUKI]
Uh, no, wait, never mind!
I'll ask him.
When I'm released
from this dumb card!
Right, Ruko?
Yeah!
[HITOE, RUKO]
Open!
[TAMA]
So... This is how things end?
Me, stuck here?
I can't see Ru again?
Hitoe!
Don't try to lose on purpose!
Only serious Battles are
going to make Ruko shine,
and light the way to Tama!
I gotcha! Yuzuki?
I heard her.
And I'm not gonna go easy!
Fiery Ambition!
Yuki!
[TAMA]
Yuki?
That voice, it's--
[RUKO]
Tama?
Who is this... Yuki?
Tama.
[IONA]
It's me. Kuro.
No, wait. I'm not her anymore.
I'm Yuki now.
See, just like you,
Ruko gave me a brand new name.
Yuki!
[IONA] Tama.
We were both born from Mayu.
[TAMA]
Uh-huh.
[IONA] But the person
who gave us our names,
the one who taught us about
the outside world, was Ru!
Right.
[IONA] Well, we should
show her our gratitude, then,
by granting Ru's wish together!
Yuki!
What do you say?
Let's help the one
who's done so much for us!
Yuzuki!
Ready?
[TAMA]
I'm ready!
Let's do it. "I accept."
[IONA]
Ruko!
"I accept the
laws of the Selector."
"And upon this sacred oath..."
[RUKO, TAMA] "...a new
Eternal Girl shall be born!"
[YUZUKI screaming]
Yuzuki!
[HITOE]
What?
[YUZUKI]
The room...
[KAZUKI] Hitoe!
Did Yuzuki come back, too?
[HITOE]
Ruko!
[YUZUKI]
What the...?
Um, maybe her wish was granted?
I-I think something is wrong.
Yuki's card hasn't changed.
We should be able to tell.
This isn't normal.
Guys, listen.
I know I'm an outsider here,
but can I say something?
Ruko only did that Battle
to get to the White Room
so she could meet
this Mayu, right?
[HITOE]
Uh, yeah.
Is that the only place
that Mayu could possibly be at?
What?
[KAZUKI] You told me
that Mayu created a world
of Selector Battles
to escape the miserable
one she lives in, right?
If so, is there a chance she's
suffering in this real world
as we speak?
[gasps]
[YUZUKI]
Yeah, you're right!
So then even if we
don't go to the White Room,
maybe we can find the
real Mayu here and convince her!
If so, then why
didn't Yuki tell us that
in the first place?
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe, what's wrong?
[HITOE] That place we
got a small glimpse of
before we exited
the battlefield?
[YUZUKI]
Yeah! That's the White Room!
[HITOE]
That's what I thought.
But I just remembered...
I've seen a place
like it before.
You must be her.
Mayu.
You're so incredibly stupid.
That Shiro...
She's playing hide-and-seek now.
It doesn't matter.
Even if both of your
feelings are in sync.
Without Shiro, your wish
is never going to come true!
[IONA]
Mayu, please listen.
We just came here to talk.
What did you just say to me?
Um... She said,
"We just came here--"
[MAYU]
"We" came here to talk to Kuro?
"We?"
You're supposed to
be all alone, you know.
The word "we" isn't one
that suits you at all, Kuro.
Yeah, well, her name's
not Kuro anymore!
It's Yuki now!
"Yuki"?
[laughing]
Pathetic!
I know it means "snow,"
but seasons don't mean anything
when you're
trapped inside a card!
And get over yourself!
She's just an LRIG.
You don't need to
bother with her feelings!
But Yuki's feelings
are your feelings, too.
[RUKO]
And so are Tama's.
Because both of them
were born from you.
They're both part of you.
They're the two sides of Mayu.
One side loved the snow,
because it covered up the sounds
you didn't want to hear
with a dark silence,
like a security blanket.
But your other side
longed for something else.
The pleasant summer sun
that was bright
and gave warmth to
everything its rays touched!
Yuzuki told us what it's like,
being trapped inside a card.
She said it's lonely.
You can see and hear the outside
world, but you can't take part!
How sad.
And being alone like that
is just what you've been
dealing with, too, isn't it?
You hate being the only
one locked away in this room,
so you want everyone else
to feel as lonely as you!
You think I'm lonely, do you?
You think you know
so much about my life?
We're trying to help you!
[URITH]
Don't worry, Mayu isn't alone.
Been awhile since you've
seen me in this form, huh?
[IONA]
Urith!
Become an LRIG
to a strong Selector.
That was your wish,
wasn't it, scum?
Me, on the other hand,
I wanted to be an
LRIG to a Selector, as well.
One who could bring
pain and despair to everyone.
My wish came true and
it led me right to her.
I couldn't ask for
a better partner than Mayu.
She's brought so much
suffering to countless girls.
I've finally found
my true Selector at last!
Well, what are we
waiting for? Let's battle!
I've been wanting to smack that
ignorant little face of yours
for a long time!
You're not scared, are you?
Mayu! We didn't come here
to fight with anyone!
We only came here to talk!
So please listen!
These Battles don't have to
be painful and heartbreaking!
It's a game.
It's supposed to be fun!
[MAYU]
Fun, huh?
For you, but I'm afraid
I don't share your opinion.
You mean like the Battle
you had in the library courtyard
with no wishes at stake, right?
A Battle so boring that it
actually made me yawn.
I know all about that.
All right.
Then, for laughs,
I'll give it a try myself.
[RUKO gasps]
Now, let's begin.
You spoke of having
fun in your Battles.
So show me, Ruko.
Damn it!
This won't change anything!
All I wanted was to talk.
If we just battle, there's
no way I'll convince her.
On the contrary,
that might be the only way.
What?
Mayu used to play
WIXOSS all the time,
but she never battled
someone else before.
Being alone, she only faced
the imaginary opponents
that she created.
Ru.
I was able to change due to
the Battles I saw you fight.
That's right.
See, the way that you battle...
It's so brilliant,
it transforms people.
It moves their hearts.
What are you two
babbling about over there?
I'm going first since
you're taking so long.
Urith. Now Grow!
[RUKO]
She's strong. But...
Yuki. Looks like
what you said is true.
If we don't move how she
predicts, she gets agitated.
And starts to lose control.
[RUKO]
End turn!
Huh? Wait, why?
Mayu, hurry up with
the next order, would ya?!
[MAYU]
What? I don't get it.
I thought she would have
launched another attack.
If she had, I would
have gained enough Ener
to unleash Arts on this current
turn, but since she didn't,
I don't know what kind of
strategy she's planning anymore.
It's wrong.
Mayu!
[MAYU]
Even so... I won't lose.
Because of the rules I created.
Summon Brionac
and attack Ahriman!
[URITH] That didn't
do a damn thing, amateurs.
[MAYU]
Kuro?
Did you happen to forget
the rules of Selector Battles?
[IONA]
What?
Just look at yourself.
[MAYU]
There was someone else
you should have
been worried about
other than Hanayo.
With the real Iona Urazoe
returning back to her old body,
"Yuki,"
you failed at
being an Eternal Girl
according to the
rules of the game.
[RUKO]
Please, no!
[IONA]
It's fine.
Sooner or later,
I knew this was going to happen.
What?!
[IONA]
Don't worry about me.
I never really
existed, after all.
I'm not a real person.
Just a character Mayu made up.
Just like my namesake,
I'll disappear, like snow.
Yuki! You can't!
No please, I won't let you!
[TAMA]
Ru...
Tama?
[TAMA]
I can't get out of this place.
Sorry.
Can you please bring
Yuki to where I am?
Please, Ru.
I can try.
Hey, what's the hold-up?
C'mon, keep this Battle going!
Ruko? Wait, what are you doing?
Get back here!
You can't quit in
the middle of a Battle!
[HITOE]
Over here!
The library?
This courtyard seems familiar.
[HITOE]
It's right up ahead!
[YUZUKI] Whoa,
there's a mansion back here?
Behind the Library.
They're both on
the same property
and used to be
part of the house.
I heard it got remodeled
and the library was moved.
I think I've seen
this house before.
Mm-hmm.
It does feel awfully
similar, doesn't it?
[YUZUKI]
Do you think Mayu's in there?
I dunno. But still...
Let's go find out!
[RUKO]
Yuki! Stay with me!
I'm taking you to where
Tama is, so just hang on, okay?
What gives?
That yard was exactly
like how it was at the library,
but then, everything else
here is all wrong!
[IONA]
I think I understand now.
[RUKO]
Huh?
[IONA] It's why Mayu
kept Tama sealed away,
and wouldn't let her participate
in Selector Battles for so long.
I never understood what changed.
What made her awaken.
But now I--
I think I understand why.
You do?
It's because--
[KAZUKI]
I don't think anyone lives here.
[CUSTODIAN 11A]
What are you kids doing?
This is private property.
[KAZUKI] Um...
We're not trespassing, sir.
We're friends with
the girl who lives here.
[CUSTODIAN 11A]
Hm? The girl who lives here?
[IONA] Mayu. She probably
died some time ago.
[MAYU]
That's right, Kuro.
As you guessed,
I'm no longer among the living.
[RUKO]
You're really dead?
[MAYU]
Now, Kuro.
Since you're a part of me,
you won't let me die all alone.
Shouldn't you disappear with
the one who granted you life?
Urith. Now Grow, Level 5.
[screaming]
[RUKO]
Oh no... Yuki!
Yuki! Wake up! Say something!
Yuki! No!
No!
[RUKO]
Next time: "This Selection."