Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
When that happens, what you have
to do is take your challengers head-on
and become a wall for them to overcome.
And when the time comes,
you must fight with all
your strength and be defeated.
Giving your challengers a battle will be
another important duty of yours from now on.
Don't forget that.
All right.
Miss Layla is right.
Really even I think that there's no
such thing as a world without battles.
But even now I still sort
of think it would be nice
if there weren't any
battles on the stage at least.
Challengers, adventurers, pioneers...
All who are called by such names are fools.
What awaits the fools who
pursue the dreams no one else dreams
is either scorn... or applause.
Be my dream, Sora.
"To the Amazing Promised Place."
Okay Mom, Dad, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yep.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ken, are you sure it wasn't a burden on
your parents to take in my whole family?
Well, my mom's the one that
offered, so it's probably okay.
Then I guess it's all right...
So tomorrow's the opening day at last, huh?
Although it looks like they still
haven't finished construction...
Yeah. It is a pretty big
construction project, after all.
No big deal, we're almost there.
Right. I'm sorry.
You shouldn't apologize too lightly.
You gave us a job really
worth doing. I'm actually grateful.
We'll make this brilliant.
I'm counting on you!
Did May and Rosetta's
maneuver end up getting okayed?
The directorial team was supposed
to decide at yesterday's rehearsal,
but Miss Cathy tested them again today.
I guess I'll okay it,
but Rosetta, I'd like a more
commanding presence from you.
You can do that, right?
Of course I can.
Oh, good.
And Anna's clown team too?
Yep.
So...
We get to do it?
Hey... I can't breathe... seriously...
That special training was really worth it, huh?!
Everybody got their dreams, huh?
But aren't you going to perform anymore, Ken?
Me?
Yeah. I mean, really you
wanted to be a performer, right?
So when you found a path
as a clown in Anna's team,
I thought "Hooray! Congratulations!" but...
That's not my dream now.
That's a dream from a long time ago.
It is?
Oh, that's right! I hear
our opening show is sold out.
Really?!
Yep.
I was concerned since
curtain is at an unusual time,
but now we have one less thing to worry about.
Yuri was the one who planned
the tie-in with the tour company.
Well, well. So he has his
father's sound business sense?
It looks like he'll make a good partner for you.
Maybe I'll make my confession...
Confession?
I...
Yes?
I'm full of myself.
Huh? What? What's this about?
Please explain.
I thought you were helping me out so much
because you were entrusting
your own dream to me.
Huh?
Oh, don't get me wrong,
I do understand it's really because I'm
the one most hopelessly in need of help!
I do get it, really!
But every time I look at it that way, it makes
me feel like "Okay, I'll give this my best!"
and it gives me strength,
so I've been letting myself think that way.
Ken, it's thanks to you that
I've been able to come this far.
Thank you.
You're not full of yourself.
Huh?
But from now on,
you'll become someone who shoulders
lots of people's dreams, not just mine.
Yeah.
So, shall we go? After all, we
have to get to bed early tonight.
Yep!
A stage with no battles, eh?
It's definitely a ridiculous dream,
but I'm at the age where I want to
try believing in those foolish dreams.
The only people who can become true stars
are the ones who, as they come
to realize their dream is foolish,
believe in it even more and keep pursuing it.
That's a very difficult thing...
That day,
everybody called up their own memories
as if they were being
led by Sora's performance.
The memories of when they wanted
everybody to smile, both themselves and others.
That's a true Kaleido Star's maneuver,
one Sora arrived at on her own power.
I'm sure all the audience's
hearts will become one.
Don't you think that's right?
What I don't think is right
is that you were practicing the
Angel's Maneuver without even telling me.
I'm sorry.
When the apology comes so
meekly it sort of throws me off...
You want to take my car tomorrow?
I'm not going tomorrow.
What? Why not?
I already know Sora's going
to become a true Kaleido Star,
and I'm not sure it's good for me, who
lost, to go looking like I'm her guardian.
Even if you did lose the competition,
I think to Sora you'll always be
the Layla Hamilton she admires.
Why not go watch her?
Okay.
That was fast!
I mean, why are you so meek today?
Because your advice is sound.
I see, I didn't know you thought
of me that way. I'm flattered.
In that case, be that meek
after we get back to Broadway too.
That I can't promise you.
I thought not...
Anyway, I think you should
watch the show tomorrow.
I have a feeling something
else is going to happen.
Something?
Yep. Something.
Angel's Maneuver jump!
Jump!
Oh, Sora.
Welcome back, Sora!
I'm back Marion, Jonathan!
Everybody's still doing their individual
practice, so there's nobody in the dorm.
Okay! Then I'll go at it too and--
Sora.
Yes?
You're going to rest.
Oh, but...
Everybody's seen you trying your best,
so they're doing their best to catch up to
you as much as they can, even if it's just a little.
So you can take a rest, and believe in everyone.
Okay.
Sora, I've decided.
I'm going to take a real audition
and join the Kaleido Stage!
Really?!
Jonathan says he'll try too,
since he's got nothing to lose.
Amazing!
Wait, why do you understand him?!
Okay, do your best tomorrow!
B-Bye-bye! Take care...
Well, I'll be going now too.
Okay, thanks.
A stage without battles, eh?
I heard you always personally
inspect the trapezes you'll use.
I guess it's true.
What do you want?
I thought maybe we could talk, as two people
who couldn't completely become demons.
It's true,
perhaps I just couldn't leave Sora alone
when I saw she couldn't completely
break herself apart on her own.
On a basic level, the Angel's Maneuver
is something that can be performed alone.
We're just extra.
Just extra, eh?
Those women are strong.
They can run anywhere, all by themselves.
But sometimes they want to
lean on somebody, just a little.
We just need to support
them during those times, that's all.
That's our role.
Just like angels, huh?
Yep.
So I guess it would make sense
that we couldn't make it as demons.
Manami, Sayaka, and Miki say they'll come too.
I see.
I wonder if Yume will really watch.
It looks like you can't sleep.
Nope.
Well, tomorrow I'll just believe
in myself and give it all I've got.
Goodnight, Fool.
Goodnight.
The Angel's Maneuver, eh?
I hear it's also called "The Fool's Maneuver."
It says Odette fights with the part of her
own heart that starts to doubt the prince's love.
So basically it's about how you have a
tough time when you date a popular guy?
Odette keeps on believing that
there's an angel heart inside Odile too.
That sounds like Sora.
Pretty nice, isn't it Yume?
She's in a good mood.
We could've done the afternoon showing.
I'm fine.
Ack, I can't read this!
Is it going to start soon?
It's like, a full house, even
though it's so early in the morning.
They say there's supposed to be a stage event
cool enough to warrant an early-morning show.
I wanted to see your Odette as well, Miss.
I'll never stand on this stage again.
Did you invite anyone, Mr. Leon?
I sent Alain passes to
the show and plane tickets,
but he might have sold them to buy alcohol.
No, he wouldn't do that... I don't think...
I know your old partners will
come too, and get their smiles back.
Do you still believe in a stage without battles?
I've decided to believe in it.
The legendary great maneuver is something
you can't do unless you believe in it absolutely.
So I'm sure the Angel's
Maneuver is the same way.
By the way, I'm sorry about that.
Huh? About what?
When I said Layla was a lukewarm performer,
you told me to apologize, didn't you?
Ah...
I thought she'd retired after pulling off
the legendary great maneuver with you
so she could keep that glory forever.
But Layla mastered the Angel's Maneuver
and came back, fully prepared to lose,
for your sake.
For my sake...
If you hadn't fought Layla that day,
your confidence most likely
wouldn't be as firm as it is now.
You're right.
Please raise the curtain.
Let's all get the very best applause together!
Next is Scene 5. Odette
is going to meet the prince.
The prince falls in love...
He's got a nice expression on his face!
The material is good, after all.
Scene 11: The ball. Anna's clown team is on.
Wow. Anna's looking good!
It's time at last for her special
training to be put to the test!
Don't go!
They like it...
There's nothing there, but it looks
like she's being pulled by a string!
Come back!
This laughter is for me!
I finally got it, Papa, Mama...
Congratulations, Anna.
Next it's Demon Lake.
The prince has his heart stolen by Odile!
Odile is the demon heart.
Mysterious and bold,
more lively than Odette!
Yay!
Big sister, you look so cool!
Change the backdrop to the deep forest.
Odile leads the prince into the
deep forest and is trapped there as well.
And Odette discovers
the conflict in Odile's heart.
The fairy that leads Odile
back from her mistaken path...
I'm counting on you, Rosetta.
The very best applause,
together with everyone...
Here we go. Eternal Illusion.
Yes.
Eternal Illusion!
Pretty good.
Yeah. Thanks, May.
It's finally time.
Scene 32. The angel's flight.
Let's believe in Sora's angel.
Three minutes to go. Please open the gate.
Sora's going to become an angel.
O Fool,
go forth believing that what
awaits you in the end is applause!
How beautiful...
That's Sora?
It's a success. Please lower the Angel Trapezes.
I'll show my angel heart to everyone...
I pray that everyone
who came to see this show...
That everyone's angel hearts become one.
It's mysterious...
I always thought of a show as an ordeal
to be gotten through as quickly as possible.
But when I'm flying through the
air matching Sora's movements,
each moment starts to seem precious.
Every moment seems irreplaceably precious...
I want you to like the
stage a lot more too, Leon.
If I become a true star,
I'm sure you'll change too.
Say, Leon, on the stage no
moment is ever the same twice, right?
There's never anything but the present.
That's why I'll live in the
present with all my strength.
So that no matter what
happens, I'll have no regrets.
Sophie, I finally understand your feelings.
I want to be on this stage.
I want to perform with Sora, right now.
Me too.
What is this feeling?
Somehow I just can't stand still.
Yeah.
Sora!
May! Rosetta!
This is...
Mute!
This is what a true star is.
Let's go!
Yeah.
Let's go too!
Can such a thing be real?
Amazing...
Even the performers
who have stormed the stage
are acting in harmony,
without instructions from anyone...
Why don't you go?
Yes!
This is the stage Sora dreamed of.
Here, in this moment, a stage
with no battles definitely exists.
I've seen your miracle, Sora.
My role is over, then.
The dream everyone is
looking for must be someplace
It has to be somewhere
Until your wish comes true
someday, you're not alone
Miss Layla!
I've seen it through, Sora...
What you were aiming for,
the show of a true Kaleido Star.
Sora! You're the best!
Bravo!
You did it, Sora!
So the dream's crossed the finish line...
It's a little sad that it's over.
No, this is the starting line of a new dream.
All right, I'm going.
Okay.
Um, is it all right if I keep on
thinking of myself as your dream?
No. You're not my dream anymore.
You're my pride.
Miss Layla...
Okay!
The colors of the evening sun and
The wind that I saw that day
Are still stored away in my heart
The truth is I knew all
along, but I couldn't say it
You alone were beside me the whole time
Miss, yesterday I tendered my
resignation as Hamilton family maid.
From now on, I'll be working to
make a stage debut on Broadway.
Please allow me to accompany you.
That's fine. Come on.
Yes, Miss!
The light I haven't seen yet
Is beaming toward the promised place
Until your wish comes true
someday, you're not alone
I-It's just my imagination, right?
And so the dream is passed on
to the next fool.
I hear that all the tickets for the
next two months are already sold!
Amazing, huh!
I'm so happy!
I wonder if I can be in the show too.
Rosetta, is something wrong?
Oh, no, nothing...
If you don't like shouting out the
name of the maneuver, just tell her so.
What did you say?!
Now, now...
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...