[Attendant] Resembool! This
stop, Resembool Station!
[Ed] Are you ever gonna
tell me what's going on?
This is starting to
feel a little too much
like a kidnapping.
I haven't been fully
informed on the details...
My only orders were to retrieve
you and to rendezvous here.
Rendezvous?
With who?
I'm glad you made it alright,
Major Armstrong, sir!
Heyyy. S'up, big guy?
Lieutenant Breda?!
[Al] This is weird...
Brother should have arrived
in Resembool by now.
So why hasn't he called?
Not to mention that he's got
me here to do his repairs.
And this stuff with
Lieutenant Ross,
I have no idea
what's going on.
[Ling] Good thing
I can explain it all.
Hmm?
Huh?
[Al and Winry scream]
Uh.. When'd you get here?
And how'd you even get in?!
The window.
I mean.. It seemed
appropriate for a criminal.
First.. There's no need for you
to worry about Ed's well being.
Huh?
I'm sure he's
just fine.
Hot.
Colonel never said we'd
be crossing the border...
Tight-lipped bastard.
Mr. Han.. How much
further do we have left?
We've almost made it. Look...
You can see the ruins ahead.
My automail almost
seared through my skin.
Who's idea was it
to bring the kid?
It was a direct order.
So this is Xerxes, huh?
Looks just like
the fable described it.
Did you say a fable?
Yeah, the Eastern Sage.
It's a story about the origin
of alchemy in Amestris.
It claims the entire
kingdom of Xerxes
was destroyed in a single
night.. And that the only
survivor wandered into
Amestris shortly afterwards...
He was the one who went on to
spread the science of Alchemy.
How interesting.. We have
a similar legend in Xing
about a drifter from the west...
It's said that his teachings
were combined with our
ancient techniques to form the
alkahestry we practice today.
And alkahestry's primarily used
for medical needs.. isn't it?
Yes. He guided this process...
And we greatly revere him.
We know him as
the Western Sage.
[Lt. Breda] So the
'west' in his title
is supposed to refer to here?
[Fu] It is believed so, yes.
[Lt. Breda] Hmm...
I wanted to visit the ruins of
Xerxes. That route goes by them.
Sure ya did, Ling.
And now I know why.
[Lt. Breda] But if Xerxes was
such a highly advanced society,
how were they wiped out
in a single night?
[Fu] It could very well
just be a legend.
[Fu] What are you
gawking at?! C'mon!
[bird crows]
We're goin' in pretty
deep now, aren't we?
[Lt. Ross] Edward!
Hmm?
[Mustang] Back east, where
I was... It's a nice place.
None of the big city noise...
and lots of beautiful women.
That damn colonel!
Ho-ho-ho! Lieutenant Ross!
Thank the heavens! My heart's
been congested with grief!
No hugs, Major!
There really wasn't anyplace
in Amestris we could safely hide
a dead girl.. Especially one
that's still alive, you know?
So the Colonel knew
that Lieutenant Ross
was innocent all along?
[Armstrong] Oh, come here!
[Lt. Breda] This seems
a little too showy, sir.
[Mustang] Is that
what you think?
Yeah... They make a point
of arresting her in public,
and now they announce her
guilt to the newspapers,
before she's even had a
trial? Somethin's not right.
I'm here.
Warrant Officer
Falman is calling
on a public line for you.
I'll take it.
[Falmon] Colonel, we
need to speak to you
about General Hughes murder.
[66] Hey, Falman! Gimme
the phone for a sec.
Barry?!
Yo, Mustang! You seen
today's paper?
'Cuz there's an
interesting article on--
Heyyy, Bunny! You know better
than to call me at work!
Let me call you right back!
Just hang on, okay?
[Mustang] Really?
You sure about this?
[66] Oh, yeah... The lieutenant
fired a bullet alright...
but it was at me, not
Hughes. I've still got
a hole in my right hand
where it passed right through.
Well that changes things.
Barry.. I've got a proposition
that you might like.
[66 laughs] Gotcha.
I promise not to kill anyone...
How 'bout second street
in the warehouse district?
Huh?
I need you to gather
everything on this list...
On the double, okay?
Sixty pounds of pork, carbon,
some ammonia... What is this?
The ingredients for
a well-cooked corpse.
Human transmutation!
Of course not.. I'm just
gonna whip up something
that looks like a human corpse.
But wait, what about
when they do the autopsy?
Trust me, it'll be too
charred for them to ID it.
That won't stop 'em from
checking the dental records.
I've got it
under control.
Think you can
pull it off?
I'm not claiming to be an
expert on human anatomy...
...but I've got plenty of
experience burning corpses.
[Mustang] Let's go.
You're Maria Ross, correct?
[Mustang] It's a dummy.
From this point
on, you're dead.
Snap out of it.
Huh?
[Havoc] Shhhh.
Hey there... Fullmetal.
[Ed] What happened here,
Colonel? Tell me!
What? Is that
the Fullmetal kid?
Oh, man... we didn't
plan on this one.
Edward's here?
Yeah, but I'm
sure the Colonel
will come up with
something... Come on.
[Lt. Ross] Right.
[Fu] After Madam Ross
was prematurely freed,
the young lord made a deal
with Barry the Chopper.
The orders I've been given
are to personally escort
this woman to the
east to take refuge.
[Lt. Breda] So we all
agreed to rendezvous here,
in one big effort to aid
the lieutenant's escape.
I see.
You've gotta be joking.
I can't believe the Colonel
was able to pull one
over on us like this.
He knew it'd be easier
to convince you
if you actually saw
Lieutenant Ross.
Fine, I'll admit it, alright?
He actually knew what
he was doing this time.
He mentioned
something else.
He said he didn't want to take a
chance on some hot-tempered kid
endangering the operation...
so he sent you out here.
Hot-tempered kiiiiiddd?!
You said operation...
Is there a phase beyond
liberating Lieutenant Ross?
Indeed. He's got a plan
to reel in the puppeteer...
the one that's behind
the conspiracy.
No one calls me a--
Wait, what'd you say?
You remember Barry from
the Fifth Lab, right?
He went on one
hell of a rampage.
They're bound to send
someone to reclaim him.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Al] So Lieutenant
Ross is innocent!
[Winry] But why take Ed?
The Colonel was just
trying to keep him out
of his hair, wasn't he?
Ha, you got it.
So, I struck up a deal with
Barry to help him out
with the jailbreak in
exchange for the secret
to his immortality...
But of course...
The science guys that put me
in this body are all dead
and it's not like I
know how they did it.
[Ling] Whhaat?
That's not fair!
Y'know what? You should
ask that Alphonse kid.
He's also just a soul
glued to metal.
So here I am.. You're supposed
to tell me your secret...
And I was promised
you'd tell me.
Yeah, but.. I
don't exactly see
how I have anything
to do with it.
I've got nothing to do
with this.. zilch...
And yet here I am,
stuck in the middle of it...
And framed by Homunculi.
[Lt. Breda] We've collected
a fair amount of intelligence.
And once we properly
piece it together
we'll have the
general's killer.
I promise you this, Lieutenant...
we will absolve
you of this crime!
Lieutenant Col--
I mean General Hughes...
It's just hard to accept
that he's dead.
And what shall you do
now, Edward Elric?
You boys just have to
keep moving forward...
In any way you can.
Al and I committed a taboo...
but we still have
people that help us.
Some people get angry at us...
And others support us silently.
Each one of them
has tried to help me
keep my promise
to my brother.
So I have no choice...
I can't turn back.
Which means, all I can do
is move forward, right?
And I'll protect everyone
I can along the way.
I refuse to let another
person become a victim...
Not while I'm alive.
I know that's a hard
promise to keep...
It's hard enough just trying
to take care of myself.
And to think that I'm
even capable of it...
Maybe I'm just arrogant.
But.. It's the only
thing I can think of...
So I have to do
it... I have to.
And you Lieutenant? Where
do you intend to seek asylum?
Well.. I think that I'm
gonna give Xing a shot.
Any parting wishes?
Shall I tell your parents?
No, sir.. As much as I want
them to know I'm okay,
I'm scared it would be
too much of a risk...
I just don't want to put
them in that kind of danger.
Very well.
[Lt. Ross] Major Armstrong...
Lieutenant Breda.
Please deliver a message
to the Colonel...
I need him to know how grateful
I am for what he's done.
If there's any way
I can help him,
tell him to send for me...
I owe him a great debt,
and I am willing to put my
life on the line to repay it.
Right.
Goodbye, Edward...
Take care of yourself, okay?
I still owe you...
for slapping me, that is.
You can get me next time.
Alright.. next time then.
[Fu] You're blessed
to have such good allies.
Mr. Fu..? Tell me,
what's Xing like?
It's a country steeped
in a rich culture
and the people are
hardworking and honest...
I'm certain you'll
feel at home there.
So I can expect
to find a paradise
on the other side
of this desert?
Yes.. Although, I can assure
you the trek across this desert
is severe.. You'll
need to be careful.
I recommend preserving your
fluids from this point on.
[Mustang laughs] How 'bout
I swing by the shop...
Sometime tomorrow?
And if you ask me nicely,
I'll bring a gift...
[Hawkeye] Huh? I'm
sorry, hold on, Roy...
Hey, Kate? We have a customer.
Could you please
let Jacqueline know?
[Fuery] Jacqueline?
We have a customer.
[Havoc] Copy that.
Hold on!
Barry?!
Try and relax, Falman...
We want this one alive,
so don't kill him!
Smells like an
ashtray.. Jean Havoc?!
Falman! Don't you think
I'm wearing this mask
for a reason?! Man, I can't
stand working with amateurs.
Sorry about that!
[Havoc] Yeah, and I'm sorry
that you got dragged into this.
Just don't do anything
that would give away
your involvement. They could
be watching us from anywhere.
[growls]
Heyyy...
Take it outside!
Uh, yeah.
But isn't there a good chance
the enemy's waiting outside?
We'll be safer there.
[growls]
Aw, dammit!
Lieutenant!
Ahh!
Told you it was safer...
We've got the hawk's eyes
watching over us out here.
[Mustang] I heard a loud
noise. What happened?
[Hawkeye] It was nothing.
A customer was getting
fresh with Jacqueline...
So I slapped him
around a little bit.
Oh, yeah?
[Mustang] You don't
mess around, Elizabeth.
Alright, don't even
think of moving.
I've got a few questions
for ya. Wait a minute...
I don't think he knows
what I'm saying.
No way.. I thought
this guy looked familiar.
That's my old human body!
What?! Are you sure?
Those sick bastards
must've dumped the soul
of some feral lab
animal into my body...
And it came to find me because
it wants its real soul back.
[66 laughs] Talk
about memories!
I haven't even
seen this guy
since the day my soul
got yanked out of him.
[Ed] I thought so.
It's like that transmutation
circle from the Fifth Lab.
A two-headed dragon...
And the sun.
Ah, dammit! Why does the top
part have to be missing?!
Whadda ya want? I don't
have any money, so you've--
You're an Ishvalan?!
'Scuse me, young man...
I'm afraid that we're gonna
have to take you hostage
until your military returns
our holy land to us.
They're not gonna return
squat.. Not over a single kid.
It was the death of a single
child that triggered
the entire Ishvalan civil
war.. So you really shouldn't
doubt your significance
in the eyes of history.
[Shan] That's enough
of your shameful behavior.
[Leader] Madam Shan!
Look at you fools...
Are you all trying to
dishonor the name of Ishvala?
Look, he won't try
to attack you again...
Can you please just
let him go now?
You stood up for me...
I don't get it.
I always heard that you
guys hated Amestrians.
Despite the atrocities your
country has committed,
I know that not all
Amestrians are bad.
Madam Shan and I were both
injured during the civil war...
But then we were saved by
these two Amestrian doctors...
To be honest.. I do hate you...
But the two of them saved me...
And you deserve
the same treatment.
Wait a minute...
You're not talking about
the Rockbells, are you?
Are you saying you were
a friend of Dr. Rockbell?
Uh.. yeah.
They saved the lives
of countless Ishvalans...
All throughout the course
of the entire war.
No kidding.
They were like an
aunt and uncle to me.
They refused to
abandon their post...
It didn't matter how much
the fighting escalated.
How did.. how did they die?
They were killed.. They were
both murdered in cold blood.
And it was by the hand
of an Ishvalan they'd saved.
But that's so...
[Shan] I'm so sorry.
There was nothing
we could do to stop him.
[Ed] Tell me who did it!
His face was wrapped
in bandages...
but he was an Ishvalan monk
and his right arm was tattooed.
[Shan] If you should
have the chance...
Would you deliver a message
to the resting place
of the Rockbells for us?
Give them our thanks...
and our apologies.
[66 laughs] You know
how amazing this is?
I mean, how often does
a guy get the chance
to chop up his own body
into tiny little pieces?
I'm pretty sure
that would kill him
and you told me
not to do that.
Well this changes
things, dammit!
[66] I'm getting' chills
up and down my soul!
I've gotta get my
knives into it!
Back off, Barry! I thought you
were supposed to have the urge
to return to your body,
not chop it up into pieces.
[66 scoffs] That body's way
past its expiration date.
Oh, man...
that's what stinks?
This is just cruel,
I have to do it!
It's my body,
so it's up to me.
And I'm puttin' it on
the choppin' block!
Dammit! I said no!
[Mustang] What's wrong?
Just a squabble.. One of the
customers is mouthing off.
Oh, no.. I'm gonna have
to call you right back...
I've got a customer
of my own to deal with.
[growls]
[Narrator] She is
a proud woman,
filled with an abundance
of strength and determination,
admired by her colleagues for
both her beauty and her skill.
But when confronted with
the loss of the weapons
that pierce her enemies,
the flame of her life
will flicker out...
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 19: "Death
of the Undying."
The contortions
of agony are culled
from the well of
savage memories.