kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
being at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
we may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings go deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
at this rate
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
won’t you kiss me? it’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
with our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
G’morning, Haruka!
Good morning, Yuu-chan!
One More Cherry Blossom-Color
Here. Thanks for lending me your notes.
Math
Takayama Haruka
Gee, at least try to do it yourself next time, ‘kay?
Math
Takayama Haruka
I used them for the first bit, but the rest was all me!
Oh, really?
Of course! Let me show you…
Huh? They should  be here…
Ah!
You scribbled your math answers in my classics notebook!
Classics
What’s wrong with me?!
Motorbikes
Bicycles
Haruka! Yuu!
G’mornin’!
Oh, good morning, Shizuku-chan.
Mornin’!
Good morning!
What was with Shizuku-chan just now?
She definitely looked a little weird, huh?
That smile was kinda creepy!
Our usual Shizuku-chan would be like…
G-Good morning…
Whoa, look at Kaede trying so hard to look pretty…
I’d expect this from Yuzu, but Haruka and Yuu, too?!
Howdy there!
Oh, it’s Kotone-chan!
You’ve gotta stop doing that!
Kotone-chan… We noticed that Shizuku-chan’s acting kinda weird…
Did something happen?
Last night we had a little fight,
and now I think she’s a bit mad.
They both don’t look very mad at all…
I’ve been staying at Shizuku-chan’s place, y’see…
Shizuku-chan! Feel free to take a bath now.
Asleep already?
Time for some drawing!
Of course that’d make her mad!
Let me finish!
She’s out like a light…
I’ve really taken a liking to your place…
It’s a little cramped, but cute and cozy all the same…
Your folks are real nice, too.
And best of all,
it’s not far from school.
I’m really in your debt.
Whoa, whoa, hold on a sec!
Going right for a kiss?! Were you drunk or something?
Kotone… most people would find that weird.
But if you’re real close with someone,
Sometimes you’d be like, “Aw, I just love you!”
Am I right?
Ah! I get tha—
Not a chance.
I don’t get that feeling, either.
Sakura Trick
It’s a bit of a shock to think that Shizuku-chan and Kotone-chan share our kind of secret.
Don’t you think we’re a bit different though?
Shizuku-chan seems a little upset about it.
You feel the same way?
Why do you have to ask that every time?
Get off my back.
But I’d want to know if you really  didn’t like it…
Ah! So that’s  what you meant when you said we’re different!
Don’t go jumping to conclusions…
I’m heading to class…
Yuu-chan, wait up!
It’s Shizuku-chan!
Hello, you two…
She really does seem upset…
It shows in her eyebrows.
H-How’s this?
Her mouth’s still showing it.
So you heard of this from Kotone…
Can’t she keep anything secret?
Since I have a naturally sour look, when I get upset, it seems overblown.
That usually scares people, so I try to cover it up with a smile…
Don’t worry, Shizuku-chan! You’re really cute, so just be yourself.
Yuu-chan…
Let go of her…
Let go of my Yuu-chan…
There’re people who let their feelings spill out like that, after all.
Let her go!
Even I know I should stop feeling sorry for myself…
But she just likes my house ‘cause it’s near school?
It sounds like anyone’s place would do, as long as it’s close by!
And who wouldn’t  give you a kiss if you let them freeload off you?
So the kiss  isn’t why she’s upset!
But there’s no way I could tell someone what I’m thinking right now…
We kinda just heard the whole thing, though…
Are you really okay with leaving things like this?
If you just keep avoiding your problems, they’ll never go away.
Well then, Sonoda…
It would seem that your math and classics homework is overdue!
It’s time for an earful!
But Ma’am!
Haruka hasn’t handed her classics homework in, either!
You’re coming, too, Takayama!
I would have, if you’d written in your own book!
Homework…
That’s right. I have math next.
I’ve got to get my notes back.
Guess what! Today, in front of the station…
Hey, guys!
I have the math homework to hand back.
Come get yours!
Why does it have to be  her handing them back…?
Hm? There’s still one left… I wonder whose.
Get lost
Get lost.
Don’t leave  with it!
I bet she’s trying to mess with me again…
But what if she took them so she could talk with me?
Maybe it’s something else…
She could be having the same thoughts I am…
And she wants to let me know…
No
No…
The one with something to say…
is me.
You’ve been avoiding me all morning… I thought you wouldn’t come.
What is it?
I’d like my book back soon.
I’m sorry.
You didn’t want me kissing you, right?
I just wanted to apologize.
I’d hate not being able to talk with you anymore.
Well then, let’s head back to class.
That’s not it!
I’m not really upset that you kissed me…
Are you just staying with me since I live nearby?
Or maybe since my mother’s so nice?
Are you living with me just for those  reasons?!
It feels like I’m just an afterthought!
Peek
Why’re you backing away?
Fire Extinguisher
I don’t know…
Shizuku-chan! Behind you!
Why’d I  get yelled at too?!
I wonder what’s going on with Shizuku-chan…
Don’t change the subject!
That voice!
Shizuku-chan! What happen—
This is the real deal!
Gotcha!
I think I get why you’re upset with me.
Let’s try it over… what we did yesterday…
Wait!
I’m alright with what happened yesterday, so we don’t have to forget it…
But right now I wanna try a different one!
Mouth-on-mouth?
Despite it being cramped, I like it since you’re there.
I like that it’s cozy, and I like your mother…
But mostly I love it there because of you.
I think we should try to sneak away now.
They might be hurt to find out we saw them…
And also… I’m starting to recall the times I kissed Yuu-chan…
Why? Why’d she just grab my hand?!
Is this making her want to kiss again?!
No, she’s not the type to go in for a kiss.
But then…
Ah! So that’s what you meant when you said we’re different!
Don’t go jumping to conclusions…
I’m heading to class…
Which is it?!
I’m probably overthinking things…
Maybe I’ll find out if I lean in…
Ah… She closed her eyes…
Hey, hey, Yuu-chan!
If Kotone-chan and Shizuku-chan are getting like that now…
I wonder what Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan could be up to now!
It looks delicious.
Want a taste?
I don’t think that’ll be quite enough.
Well if it’s with you…
I really doubt that, y’know.
Hey!
Gimme back my Pokitz!
That was my last one!
It’s already in my mouth!
See, they’re going at it!
One More Cherry Blossom-Color
End
Haruka! Lemme see your notes!
I’m gonna copy your homework.
Again?
We have a test next week. At least try doing it yourself.
Pretty please?
No.
This is a far cry from middle school, okay?
So don’t come crying to me if you fail and get held back a year.
I don’t really care if they hold me back.
But Yuu-chan, you’ll be stuck as a first-year, y’know?
People will treat you as though you’re younger, y’know?
Why do you look so happy?!
Yuu-chan, held back a year…
First-year
Second-year
Haruka!
My, if it isn’t my former classmate, Sonoda-san.
Are you always this chummy with your seniors?
Sorry, Haruka-onee-sama.
I was hoping you could fix my tie.
Stab
She calls me ‘onee-sama’!
That’s foul play!
What the?!
After School with Mr. Hedgey
Since she’s lonely, Yuu-chan visits me during break time.
You really should get back to class, Yuu-chan…
No!
I want to be with my Haruka-onee-sama!
Oh.
But our school will be dissolved in three years, with no more first-years arriving,
so wouldn’t she be expelled in this case?
Expulsion
I wanted Yuu-chan to call me ‘onee-sama’!
I wanted to fix Yuu-chan’s tie!
What the heck happened to her?!
Music
Prep Room
Our test will cover up until this part.
Neutralization Reaction
Mixing of Hydrochloric Acid with Sodium Hydroxide
Ionic
Formula
That is all.
I can’t let Yuu-chan get expelled!
I have to be strict to get her standing on her own!
‘Cause if Yuu-chan gets expelled, there’s no reason for me to come here anymore.
Haruka, lemme see your notes!
Sure thing!
I mean, no!
Tch, I was so close too.
There you go seducing me with your charm again!
Do you enjoy playing with people’s feelings?
I wonder if Shizuku-chan or Kotone-chan would lend me theirs…
Anger
We’re going to have a study session after school for you!
What?!
Well then, let’s start our study session.
Let’s study hard until the test!
Yeah!
C’mon, wake up, Yuu-chan.
You can’t doze off, Yuu-chan.
Who do you think this study session is for?
Plop
Math
Sonoda Yuu
She looks so tuckered out!
Wake her up!
C’mon Yuu-chan, wake up!
Why’re you dozing off?
You don’t wanna get expelled, right?
Alright already…
Harupoppo, how would I solve this one?
Oh, that uses the formula we learned a while back.
The one on this page.
You apply it to this right here…
I get it now.
Thanks!
Don’t mention it.
Yuu-chan, how’s your work going?
Yuzu-chan, we’re trying to study here!
So it’s my  fault?
There’s gotta be a way to make Yuu-chan less drowsy.
That’s the Mr. Hedgey thing Yuu-chan said she liked a while back.
But what  is that thing?
bear
A bear?
A tanuki?
tanuki
bear
What’s that fluff on its back?
tanuki
bear
I know it’s popular, but I’ve no clue about it…
tanuki
bear
Hey, Shizuku-chan.
Yes?
What’s that thing hanging from your bag?
A bird?
Pig?
Cow?
Fox?
Or a tanuki?
gurgle
Her stomach just answered.
Ah, so it was  a tanuki!
H-He’s a hedgehog!
Oh, so he’s a hedgehog!
That’s it!
Wake up, Yuu-chan.
I drew Mr. Hedgey in your notes to keep you awake!
You won’t be bored now, right?
Math
Takayama Haruka
Whoa! Mr. Hedgey?!
Lemme see!
Eww, gross!
That looks nothing like him!
You butchered him…
I guess it didn’t work.
You expected it to?!
Though Yuu’s not helping…
How about we start with Yuu’s favorite subject?
Um… What subjects would she like…?
Right here!
I’ve got a hunch!
I heard she really likes PE!
That’ll really  help her on the test…
I see. PE!
Hey guys, let’s play some volleyball outside.
Count me in!
What? Weren’t we supposed to study?
Besides, isn’t the baseball club using the grounds right now?
I’ll bet the equestrian club’s taking their horses on a ride out there.
I kind of doubt that.
No worries.
Club activities are suspended before big tests!
We really should  be worried!
They suspend them for a reason!
We’re gonna try memorizing chemical symbols while playing Yuu-chan’s beloved volleyball.
Makes sense.
Nice one, Haruka.
Let’s go.
Hydrogen!
H.
Water.
H2O.
Carbon dioxide.
I dunno!
Let’s try some easier questions!
Okay!
Bring ’em on!
Yuu-chan, give this next one a serious try, okay?
You won’t get off easy this time.
Leave it to me, yo!
Here it comes!
Hey you!
Don’t you all know there’s a test coming?!
Sorry.
dorori
I guess trying to study like that was going a bit far…
Looks like it’s back to pen and paper…
Great taste, better health.
That’s no good, she’ll just doze off again.
dorori
You just need to recall the key concepts, right?
So try studying with her in a way she won’t forget.
For example?
Something that’ll embarrass her maybe?
Great taste, better health.
Kinda like what we’re seeing now?
What?
Great taste, better health.
Yup, you can’t forget this one.
I’ve gotta think of something…
A way to embarrass her…
Try translating this one.
You can use a dictionary if you want.
If you fail, you’ll have to do what it says.
Um…
She beats her…
three times.
What about “her hips”?
noun
Her hi…
Hi…?
Hi…
You don’t know?
Or perhaps you want a more… physical example?
Whoa!
bang!
There’s no way I could do that!
Haruka?!
I wonder what happened to Harupoppo?
But if it’ll save Yuu-chan from expulsion…
That was out of the blue…
Looks like she’s still breathing.
No, it still seems weird.
Of course she is!
Oh, not anymore…
I need to come up with a more practical embarrassment.
You okay?
Still breathing?
Something embarrassing…
Why would she be dying?!
What is the resulting coefficient of 2H2 + O2?
Three!
Wrong!
Okay, remove one piece of clothing.
B-But…
This is your punishment. You have no choice.
I’m doing this for you.
Would you like me to help you?
It’s…
embarrassing.
You’re embarrassed being the only one to undress?
Let me fix that right up…
Okay…
What are you making me imagine?!
Yuzu-chan, you pervert!
Do ya have something against me, or what?!
It’s getting pretty late.
We should get going.
C’mon, everyone.
We’re finally done.
Let’s go buy some Pokitz on the way home.
Oh, we’ll stick around for a bit.
Huh?! Say what?!
All right, see ya.
Bye bye.
Yakisoba Flavor
Limited Spring Edition
I-I hope you haven’t forgotten about our secret!
W-What are you getting at?
Well…
I, um…
I was thinking that if we kissed while studying, you’d be sure to recall what you learned…
What kind of response is that?!
Besides, if you would study like you should, I wouldn’t be suggesting this!
Why’re you still backing away?!
I’ll bet you just want an excuse to kiss.
No I don’t!
I’m not trying to seduce you or anything!
I don’t want you to get expelled!
I want to spend my high school life with you!
That’s why I want you to study!
We’re gonna study, right?
O-Okay.
Okay, I’ll ask some questions…
and you’ll answer after we kiss.
Fill in the blanks.
Fill in the blank.
In Japanese it’s “May I go with you?”
Math I
Ready?
Let’s do this.
It’s so long I can’t answer.
Um… It’s “go”?
Fill in the blank.
Yup, correct.
Next: Correct the word in brackets.
In Japanese it’s “I want one more piece of paper.”
More.
Correct.
Huh?
More.
More!
Does she mean “more?”
Yakisoba Flavor
Limited Spring Edition
What’s wrong, Yuu-chan?
Let’s go home.
Thanks…
One week later
English
Oh, this question. We did this one before.
I wonder if Yuu-chan’s doing alright…
She’s recalling it!
English
Takayama?!
Oh, Yuu-chan!
After School with Mr. Hedgey
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
the time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we share
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
if we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
if we split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
memories to come… let’s make them
ippai ni shichaou ne
we’ll make lots and lots
love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
the miracle of us meeting in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
it had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
it’s something we can’t do alone
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Sonoda Yuu here!
You’re quite the cutie, Yuu-chan!
W-Why’re you here, Kotone-chan?!
Well, I didn’t get much screentime last week…
Probably since you kept repeating the same thing.
snap
But Shizuku-chan really  is so cute…
Oh, alright already!
Yuu
Haruka
You’ve got a pretty cute temper too!
Next time, Trick 3.
My Sister’s the President
A Promise Made by the Pool
“My Sister’s the President” and “A Promise Made by the Pool”
See you then!