Iona?
Iona!
M-Mayu...
Looks like you made your mommy mad.
Iona!
What's wrong? Are you okay, Iona?
I-I'm fine...
Mayu can't kill me.
I'm Mayu's friend and child.
And...
I'm Mayu herself.
Mayu...
...herself?
Ulith loves me, after all...
That girl...
She grew up all alone ever since she was born,
without once setting foot in the outside world.
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
She was so alone... that she couldn't tell what being alone even meant.
Every so often, something came and did something to her.
She didn't know a thing.
Neither who she was, nor why she was there...
That room...
was all she had.
That was her whole world.
Friends
Then she noticed things that were being placed around her.
From time to time, something would come by and leave those things.
She had no idea why.
Maybe it felt pity for her.
Friends
Perhaps it was simply a passing whim.
What...
is... this?
It was then that she found out.
She realized that there was a world outside,
just beyond that window, she never knew existed.
And that there are many girls out there who resemble her.
She made a lot of friends
The next day, and the next,
they were always together
She made a lot of friends
The next day, and the next,
they were always together
They all played together
She made a lot of friends
"Frie...nd..."
Her wish came true, and
they all lived happily ever after.
"Her wish... came true..."
Wish...
Then, one day...
She understood that it was some sort of plaything,
and that it couldn't be played on one's own.
So then, she...
created friends.
She created friends?
Imaginary friends that solely existed in her mind and could only be seen by her.
You're the good girl Shiro, the Girl of Light.
You're the bad girl Kuro, the Girl of Darkness.
From today on, we're friends!
Yup, nice to meet you.
I'll be your friend, sure.
Shiro's going to summon Tourette.
That won't work, Shiro!
I'll stop that with Vimana.
Aww, no...
It's Kuro's turn next!
Here I go. Attack.
Yikes, she got me!
Now it's your turn, Shiro. Do your best!
Yup, I'll try my best!
Next, she started a certain game.
The outside world?
Yes.
Shiro and Kuro, you're going to bring girls from the outside world here.
You'll tell them that if they win the game, their wish will come true.
What will we do then?
You'll be playing WIXOSS,
and whoever wins will steal the wish of the girl they brought.
What's going to happen to the girl?
She'll be sealed away in the world of cards.
For her to escape from there, she'll have to bring another girl.
What about the girl who loses?
Her wish will never come true.
No.
That's not all!
Her wish will be flipped over!
Isn't that...
...a Selector battle?
Oh?
But isn't that a bit mean?
Why?
The girls can choose whether they want to play or not.
They don't have to play if they don't want to.
Hm, that sounds fun.
Right? Come on, let's do this!
Yup, I'll do it too.
And thus it began.
It's my turn now. Here I come, Kuro!
Rococo Boundary!
Wow, great move, Shiro!
Shiro-chan, please do your best for me!
I want to become a florist!
Yup, I'll do my best for you!
Hey, it's your turn now, Kuro.
I won't lose to you, Shiro.
I hope Kuro-chan wins so I can become a princess!
Dark Matter!
Game over! It's Kuro's win!
Kuro-chan, thank you!
I'm sorry that I lost...
I lost...
Now that you lost, your dream will be flipped over.
You won't become a florist.
That's not all.
You will never be able to smell or see flowers again.
You'll live in a world where flowers don't exist!
Now I'll become a princess!
You won't.
Kuro will fulfill your dream in your stead.
If you want to escape, you have to bring a girl to replace you.
And so, the world that had sprung from her mind
began to be painted in vivid colors.
Within that imaginary world,
the girls' laughter, their cries, and their
screams resounded over and over again.
However...
The more realistic her imaginary world became,
the more she was forced to face the harsh truth.
She had been left behind in a world without color or voices—the real world.
Say, Shiro and Kuro...
Isn't it strange?
Everyone's my friend, yet I'm the only one here.
I can't even think of wishing...
Not when I'm unable to even see a real florist.
Hey, Mayu? What is your wish?
We will make it come true for you.
You will? You're so kind, you two.
My wish...
So she's...
That was... the story of me, Tama, and Mayu.
Then... the reason I met with Mayu...
That's right.
She is continuing to wish.
To this very moment, she's still wishing all alone in that room.
After all that, I...
Huh?
Wh-Where am I?
That was when I understood everything.
Oh. So that's how it is.
I'm Kuro. I will make your wish come true.
Mayu is constantly clinging
to her wish in that room.
It still bears strongly, acutely, urgently on her mind.
What is... Mayu-san's wish?
Revenge.
Revenge on all who live in the
outside world and are free to wish...
Revenge on all girls who are allowed to select...
Revenge.
Revenge...
The other girls born in Mayu's mind all became LRIGs,
and I went on to battle with them.
What happened to the LRIGs who lost?
They disappeared, and their Selectors became LRIGs in their places.
The only LRIGs originally born from Mayu who are still alive are me and Tama.
A string of wins led to me becoming a human.
Following that...
a LRIG came to me.
I continued to battle in order to become a LRIG again,
then a Selector again, then a LRIG again, and continued my life as such.
Why?
I've already told you.
That's just what I am.
Kuro?
Yes, you are Kuro.
Kuro, the bad girl.
Battling for all eternity,
bringing misery to everyone...
That's your fate as the Child of Darkness.
After many cycles between Selector and LRIG,
and after I had become Urazoe Iona at some point,
Ulith came to me,
bearing semblance to when I was still called Kuro.
Ulith...
But why did her looks change?
She's playing with dolls...
We're just... dolls?
Everyone was just being played with!
But you're friends, right?
You said that you and Tama are Mayu's friends—that you're Mayu herself!
That makes no difference.
It makes no difference to her.
Who cares?
Who cares if this is all just someone's wish or a game because I got to meet Ulith...
I got to meet Ulith!
She's mental...
Battling is my fate.
But the longer I battled,
the more serious I became about it.
Serious?
It made me feel alive for the first time.
I felt my own soul and my own body;
I felt that I was really here.
I've sought to become stronger by looking for the greatest of all Selectors since then.
And finally, I met you, Ruu...
And you were there too, Shiro.
I lost to Ruu and my wish was granted, but...
you stopped battling.
I couldn't forgive you.
You were supposed to be the same as me,
and yet you became friends with those dull girls.
I felt that everything had gone to waste!
But then, you entered me...
It made me feel nice and warm.
Tama, you felt that as well, right?
Your bond and understanding were what made you and her so strong.
It's because you felt this that
you were able to change, too.
That's why you refused to battle even though you loved it so much.
You've found something more
important than battling, haven't you?
I don't need to battle...
I love Ruu more than battles!
Tama!
I love Yuzuki.
I love Hitoe.
I love Grandma.
I love everyone!
Tama...
I want Mayu to become friends with everyone, too...
Then she'll stop with all this!
No one will have to battle anymore!
Tama...
Did you get your memory back?!
Mayu was feeling lonely being all by herself...
But I forgot all about her...
Tama, you said that you think you could bring back all the girls who became LRIGs, right?
I'm not really sure, but...
You said that because you are Mayu's light.
Mayu-san's light?
Being with Ruu and her friends made you and me change.
That must mean...
Mayu can become friends with Ruu and everyone?
Yes. Let's both show her the feelings we hold.
If that really happens,
then we can end Selector battles and save all the girls who turned into LRIGs, right?
Iona... Tama...
Mayu! You can hear us, right?
The time for your games is over!
We'll get you out from there!
Wh-What...
What's with those girls?!
No! I'm scared!
To save everyone...
...we need to defeat Ulith.
If we can beat her, we'll finally be able to save Tama!
Then Tama-chan and Iona-san can be together again!
I'm tired of all this stupid yapping.
You already forgot the next turn is mine?
It's beautiful to see you all shine
so radiantly, with hope in your hearts...
Don't dump me...
I will smash that radiance of yours!
Sorry, but Tama is mine.
I need her so I can break even more girls.
I-I don't want that!
And I won't stop before I see my sweet, sweet Tama-chan's own heart shattered to pieces!
I... I won't let that happen!
Iona is one level above Tama's level 4!
We'll see about that...
Tama!
I'll stain that pure body of yours in darkness!
Tama! Tama!
What a lovely cry...
Impossible! Ulith is entering Tama?!
Ah, so beautiful...
No! No! Why?! Why her?!
Ulith is mine!
R-Ruu... Iona... What's happening to me?
Something is entering me!
No... I don't want this...
Help me...
Tama!
Tama. Grow.
Again?!
No...
Fafnir!
Iona!
End Slash!
T-Tama...
Oh wow...
Stop! Please stop, Tama!
No!
Ruuko!
Iona?!
No... I...
I-It's not what it looks like! Tama, you—
Ruu...
Iona...
Iona!
What a shame.
That was fun, you pathetic scum.
W-Wait! Tama!
Hitoe! Hang in there!
Yuzuki... Ruuko...
That felt great.
Ulith...
What is it, Akira?
Am I... unsightly?
What?
You're beautiful.
You haven't changed a bit since I set my eye on you.
We'll stay together, forever.
Let's keep having fun
with the wishes of all the girls in this city.
Ulith...
you're...
A... ki... ra...
This
World
is
Mine
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
I sense an unusual evildoer aura...
Huh?
Such evil.
I'm... evil?
Your time of punishment will come!
Justice will prevail!
That
Parting
is
Abrupt
That parting is abrupt.