Ami-chan, does that mean you took it?
That big...
It's still a job, after all.
By big, do you mean it was as big as this?
No, it's even...
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's Yuusaku.
What are you talking about that's big?
Don't tell me you're talking about pe-
Gosh! I'm talking about dogs.
I have to take pictures with a super-huge dog for a magazine shoot.
Oh my gosh, what did you mistake it for?
Maruo, are you all right?
Somehow, you don't look too well.
All right, everyone sit down!
Now, let's begin the final homeroom session before we go home.
Class President, please give your instructions.
Kitamura-kun?
Stand.
Bow.
Let's eat.
What?
A gag?
Somehow, things aren't going well...
But let's cheer up, okay?
Kitamura?
The weekend is tomorrow.
After the break,
it's the long-anticipated student council president election.
Oh, so it's here.
We have an event!
Kitamura-kun, cheer up and give it your best shot, okay?
You're the number one candidate for it.
Actually, you're the only one.
Yeah! Let's make it more exciting!
But it's already decided that the next president will be Kitamura.
Kitamura, good luck.
We'll also help you-
No...
I'm not going to run for it.
I'm resigning my seat as vice-president.
I'm quitting the student council.
I'm quitting... I'm quitting...
Kitamura-kun?
I'm quitting it all!
All!
Kitamura-kun?
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
The Stars Are Far Away
In the end, Kitamura didn't reply.
What happened to Kitamura-kun?
He said he's quitting the student council.
Student council...
Were you bullied by that evil student council president?
What's that?
Let me go!
What are you thinking?!
Minorin, what's wrong?
Look at that! This is bad!
K-Kitamura-kun.
Interview Room
What's with his hair?
He's not even responding to us.
That's why we want to ask the people who are closest to him.
So any ideas?
Nope.
I can't believe there are still people who express themselves like this.
No... I don't really...
Kanou-san, what about you?
I don't know, and I can't even comprehend it.
Besides, he has already left the student council.
What he does has nothing to do with me anymore.
Kanou-san...
Sensei, you're wasting your time on that idiot.
Wait...
Kanou-senpai, aren't you getting colder and colder?
I bet that you're the reason why Yuusaku has gone bad.
Hey, Kawashima...
Perhaps you're correct.
Huh?
But if that's the case, I'll be even more disappointed in him.
Ami-chan, have you found out why Maruo is like that?
Nope, but I think the student council president knows.
You mean Kanou-senpai?
Taiga?
Get in!
I've brought the mastermind here!
T-Taka-chan, save me!
Kushieda is horrible!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything...
Last night, Kitamura called me and
asked me how to dye his hair blonde,
so I told him how...
You saw what Kitamura-kun was like yesterday, right?!
Didn't you question why he was asking you that?
But I never thought he'd really do it...
Is Maruo really quitting the student council?
Hey, Ami-chan...
Let's try and do something for Maruo's sake.
That self-proclaimed honour student is doing this to get people's attention.
He's probably trying to say, "Has anyone noticed that I'm deeply troubled?"
He's a junior,
and yet he dyes his hair blonde to show people that he's gone bad. How lame-
Stupid Chi'!
Don't tell me you're not worried about Kitamura-kun.
What use is there to worry about him?
It'll just make us look like idiots.
What?!
Both of you, cut it out.
Hey, isn't that Kitamura?
Where? Where?
Calm down, Kitamura-kun!
I said I'm going home.
Kitamura-kun!
Wait!
Kitamura-kun...
People who think someone is bound to help them if they shout loudly are very lucky.
All right, everyone.
Class is about to begin.
I was thinking that we should visit Kitamura's house.
Huh?
I don't have club activities or work today, and I'm worried about him.
What do you think, Taiga?
Never mind, I think it'll be easier to talk to him with less people.
I see.
Then, Takasu-kun, wait for me at the gates.
I'll be back after going to the club activity room.
S-Sure...
Are you fine with it?
Although I'm really worried about him, I'm no help at all.
Huh?
Besides, I really want Kitamura to quit the student council...
He has to be separated from that stinking president.
Taiga?
That's how it is. Go help him, you mongrel.
Even if she says that...
Sorry for the wait.
It'd be great if Kitamura-kun is at home.
I have no idea what's going on with him...
Yeah...
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
You're very quiet today.
Well, no, um...
I'm just wondering what's going on with Kawashima and Taiga, so...
Kawashima hasn't said anything like that to her childhood friend before, has she?
I think Amin is definitely worried about Kitamura-kun.
Look, Amin works in the world of adults,
so I think she knows a lot more than we do.
She surely knows about Kitamura-kun, too.
But having things only she knows,
she must be really patient to deal with kids like us.
I wonder...
But I don't think Amin is wrong.
There aren't a lot of people in the world
who can talk about their friends like that.
That's why I think Amin has her own reasons for being so direct today.
Or should I say, I wished for her to do it.
I shouldn't say this, but there are a lot of things you don't know.
For example, not being able to understand someone you want to understand.
True.
But I think Amin has considered all of it already.
Because we're still immature,
we can't understand him.
But I think... that's why we're his final salvation.
Oh, what am I saying?
I think Kitamura-kun's house is over there.
Kushieda... How should I put it?
You're a very kind person.
Kind?
No, I'm not!
I'm actually very arrogant...
...and dishonest...
Kushieda?
In the end, Kitamura wasn't at home,
so we didn't get to see him.
I'm back!
Oh, you came over.
W-Welcome back, R-Ryuuji-kun.
What's wrong?
Did you eat something weird?
Yo.
Sorry for intruding.
K-Kitamura?
Yasuko-san let me in, so I did-
Not that!
Actually, I ran away from home...
Huh?
Aisaka, do you usually come here?
Ya-chan said I'm allowed to eat here whenever I want,
s-so I'm just going along with her good will.
I see.
It must be great to live near Takasu.
Yeah.
Ah, tatami mats sure are great.
I don't have tatami rooms in my house.
M-My house is fully western too!
Well, Japanese style is the best.
Yeah... We have the same interest...
Nutmeg... Nutmeg...
H-Hey, let me help you.
Help wha-
All right, I'll help you peel them.
I'm good at this!
Good?
I see.
You just want to show off your good side, right?
Yeah.
Fine.
So, let's make that tasty fried egg again!
S-Sure!
Yeah, put the egg in the pan and close the lid...
Lid?
What lid?
What other lids are there apart from frying pan lids?
Now add a bit of water.
Water? Add it to where?
It's on fire!
Add some water!
No!
Well, Kitamura, this is...
Hey, Kitamura?
Don't eat it!
Actually, I'm not that good at cooking-
It still tastes like fried egg.
It's just right.
Kitamura-kun?
Aisaka.
Thank you for making it to cheer me up.
I feel better already.
Oh, this must be Takasu's beef patty!
Yeah, it has my special red wine sauce.
It's good!
As expected from you!
I'll try and make it next time...
Sure, I don't think there'll be a problem if Takasu teaches you.
Wow, I'm full!
The food was awesome!
That's great.
So, tell us what's up with your hair.
Ryuuji!
I don't want to be the student council president anymore.
No one will have any expectations if my hair is like this.
So yeah, that's it.
Even if you say that...
Y-You don't need to push yourself to be the student council president!
After all, it's what you've decided by yourself!
I think that's enough.
Thanks.
Hey Ryuuji, take the video games out!
Huh?
Sure! Let's play!
Tomorrow is the weekend, so let's play to our heart's content!
Yeah, let's play!
I fell asleep...
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun?
Ryuuji, I want to eat ice cream...
What? There's none here.
I want ice cream...
You're hopeless.
I'll go to the convenience store.
Are you coming?
Huh? Where's Kitamura-kun?
Oh, he went inside to sleep in a futon by himself.
How cheap...
I'm going to look at Kitamura-kun's sleeping face...
Here, it's cold, so put this on...
Taiga?
I'm still no good...
What am I happy about?
I'm so selfish...
Kitamura-kun's pain, sadness, and troubles...
I didn't realise any of it.
I'm really no good.
No good at all...
You're not-
I am!
I am no good.
I can't help Kitamura-kun...
I can't help him!
When I was in trouble, Kitamura-kun
would always reach his hand out for me.
Because of that, I was able to console myself...
He told me, "You can live..."
"You can live in this world."
Kitamura-kun is...
Kitamura-kun is my...
Final salvation, right?
Taiga, look at the Big Dipper.
That's the North Star.
Orion.
Which one is Orion?
Look, those three consecutive stars.
Oh, I see it.
Those stars look like they're close to each other,
but they're actually very far away, right?
We learned that in elementary school.
It's like Kitamura-kun and I.
The things you see aren't always real.
How hard must I try to be able to understand the hidden truth?
How far away is...
...the distance between Kitamura-kun and I?
You want to understand him because you don't understand him, right?
You want to understand because you like him.
You reach out your hands so you'll gradually get closer to it.
Yeah.
Good morning, Takasu.
Morning...
I drank the milk in the freezer.
Sorry.
It looks like you had a lot of fun last night.
You should have woken me up.
S-Sorry...
Oh, right.
I had a feast with Taiga last night.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Oh, it's already this late.
I'll make breakfast right now.
Taiga?
Hey, wake up! You look bad!
Never mind, she's fast asleep.
She looks so happy.
You stink of milk!
What an amazing stretch!
K-Kitamura-kun?!
Oh my god!
Don't tell me you saw me sleeping!
I'm sorry, but I did.
No!
What now?! You saw my weird sleeping face...
No! No! He saw such an awful side of me...
Calm down.
We've been kicked out.
It can't be helped.
Let's go have breakfast-
All right, let's go have fun!
I was busy the whole time because of the cultural festival,
so it's been a long time since I went out to have fun.
Oh, right! I know a good place!
100 hits of every ball speed...
Kitamura sure is a weird guy.
This really is the best; sweating it out as a healthy student!
No matter how you look at it, it's a sickness.
All right.
Takasu, it's your turn next.
No, I'm-
Kitamura-kun, I'll go next!
Oh, Aisaka, you seem determined.
Taiga?
Just watch.
I'll hit it for sure.
All right.
Aisaka, don't spread your arms.
Nice! You hit it!
I might have discovered our next star player!
Amazing!
You're amazing, Aisaka!
Why is someone so talented like you not in the baseball club?
Home
Run
I'm back.
That was an awesome home run!
Aisaka, you have talent!
T-That's not true...
Oh, welcome back.
Ryuu-chan, can you help me hold Kitamura-kun still?
Like this?
Yes, don't let him go.
Taiga, help me!
Just then...
Your father gave me a call.
He sounded very desperate,
so I thought it'd be best for you to go home normally.
So you've teamed up with my parents against me...
In the end, guardians are just guardians!
You're going to become the student council president, right?
So dying your hair blonde is a no-no.
I'm not going to become the student council president!
I'd rather die!
I wonder if Kitamura-kun made it home safely...
Beats me.
I think he's serious about it.
Is he really?
Do you remember what Minorin said during the summer at the villa?
She said she loves horror, so that's why she says she hates it.
Oh, that reverse psychology thing?
Kitamura-kun says that he doesn't want to become the student council president...
I wonder if he means the opposite...
So he actually wants to?
Don't you think so?
Even if that's the case,
we can't do anything about it with him as he is right now.
But...
So we have to get his spirits up, huh?
Is it really all right?
Yeah, I've decided on it.
Then, put this on.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Student Council President Candidate
What kind joke is this?!
No way...
Seriously?
I was thinking-
Quiet down!
I'll announce it right now.
When I, Aisaka Taiga, am elected to
become the student council president,
this school, your high school life, and your memories of this election...
...w-will all be buried!
What?!
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
One Step Forward
When I am elected to become the student council president, everyone will be in a pit of terror.
It's an abyss.
I'll still b-bury-
You're still...
Come over here, you guys!
Hurry and shake hands with me.