I'm sure Mokkan is having...
quite the heartthrobbing time at Subarun's place right now!
She's probably taking a bath at this time.
Oh~! Onii-chan and Tomoka are bonding naked in the bathtub!
N-Naked?
Airi, calm yourself.
I doubt they're taking a bath together.
Y-Yeah.
But how will this make her better at catching his passes?
Let me tell you!
In other words: Mokkaan is unable to catch because she's too nervous!
Uhm...
That was the first time Tomoka played with Subaru as a team, wasn't it?
Um, you can sleep on the bed, Tomoka.
Subaru has always been on the other team during practice, right?
I-I-I'll be sleeping in the bed you always use, Subaru-san?
Tomoka was nervous because she likes Onii-chan?
Don't worry, I've changed the sheets recently, so it's not dirty at all.
No! I'm fine with the floor!
That's right!
So if she's in an even more exciting event,
No way, you're the guest!
catching passes won't be a problem anymore!
Please sleep on the bed today.
Then I hope she gets as much the excitement as possible!
A-All right.
Hehe, that's right.
I-I may be incompetent but please teach me well!
T-Tomoka, something sounds wrong about that...
Can't sleep?
Y-Yes.
My heart's beating so hard...
I see. That's how it is.
I'm also a bit nervous.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being a bother but I want to be able to catch your passes, no matter what.
But I want to be able to catch your passes, no matter what.
I don't want to weigh you down anymore.
I'm sorry for not noticing earlier.
I may be the cause of your issues.
N-Not at all! It's my fault!
I feel responsible for you.
We're a team, so we need to support each other.
Believe in your friends and help them out...
That's the basketball you girls have taught me.
Subaru-san...
Tomoka, let's do our best together.
Let's improve while getting past our worries.
I want you by my side.
I was so scared...
So scared... I thought I'd disappointed you with my play...
I'm not disappointed at all.
Even if you mess up one hundred times in a row,
I'm sure you will bounce right back with one hundred amazing plays.
Subaru-san...
I'll do my best.
Tomoka!
Here!
Mokkan, you're doing great!
Yep!
Seems like the secret training worked.
What's the matter? Come at me!
Attack harder!
What's wrong, Airi?!
Stop! Stop!
Banri-kun, you're pressuring her too much.
S-Sorry, I just get worked up when I play basketball.
I know that, but can you calm down first?
Mokkan, we've decided on the date for the rematch, right?
Yep!
Finally, we can get our revenge.
Do your very best, you two!
S-Sure.
Only three of us are on the court,
but we're all together during the match!
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
I can't wait!
Tomoka's got her groove back, it seems.
What training did she do during this short while?
W-Well...
You see...
Hasegawa!
Here you go.
What's that?
This is the video of our game against Suga in middle school.
Please use it to think of strategies against him.
Thanks!
Hasegawa, about Airi...
Banri, please...
Airi is the type who doesn't give up until the bitter end.
That's right.
Airi-chan has always cleared any obstacles that get in her way.
She's absorbing all of the techniques I'm teaching her.
Please support Airi.
Sure.
Come on! Come at me!
Hurry up already!
Why did Hasegawa want to play against him?
His fighting spirit is similar to Suga's, he said.
The reason he couldn't read Suga's jab step
is because his fighting spirit and aggression makes the feint hard to predict.
But Subaru found out that's not really everything there is to it.
Yeah!
Got it!
Takenaka!
One more time!
Hell yeah, flawless victory!
Subaru! You're moving strangely!
Your fakes are too obvious.
Why? My fakes aren't working...
Ah, what a disappointment.
Ya always sound so high and mighty as a coach, too.
What?!
Don't underestimate me!
A floater?!
Yes!
That was dirty! You call yourself an adult?!
Hey, hey, hey!
I guess I got a bit too into it...
A floater, huh...
That'll probably work against Suga.
No, I can't use it yet.
There's a great chance that it won't go in.
I can't use an imperfect move against Suga.
You're so lame. Who cares if it doesn't work?!
It's much better to shoot than to be scared of shooting.
I'm clutch, so I don't miss during crunch time.
You may have a point.
That's pretty good, coming from you.
Don't be so arrogant!
I'll beat you to the ground!
But just what exactly am I doing wrong?
Oh? Your brother?
He's been practicing with me, but I haven't gotten any better...
Why am I so weak?
You'll be fine, Airi. You're working too hard.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
I'll practice with you until you say you've had enough.
Hina-chan...
We're all your friends.
We all love you so much!
Hina-chan... Thank you.
I couldn't stop you after all.
Were my fakes any different from my usual ones?
No...
I see.
Your fake makes my heart beat so fast...
N-No! I don't mean anything weird by that!
Um... I just don't know what's coming next.
We're the only ones here, but I find myself thinking whether you'll pass me the ball.
I'm sorry for saying such strange things.
It's not strange at all.
But I'm stumped... How do you make your fakes look so natural?
Natural? What do you mean?
Natural...
Oh! That's it!
I stopped you!
Thank you, Tomoka!
Everything's clear now!
Really?
Go! Go! Subaru!
Go! Go! Hasegawa-san!
Go! Go! Onii-chan!
Go! Go! Subaru!
Why do I have to do this, too?
Fight!
Since you challenged us for a second game, does that mean you are confident in stopping me?
I don't want to say this,
but right now I can't stop you.
Do you even listen to yourself?!
But we won't lose.
Even if I don't win personally, as long as my team wins...
It's alright!
Nice steal, Tomoka!
Th-Thanks!
Run, Tomoka!
No way she can catch that...
I did it, Subaru-san!
Nice shot, Tomoka!
Mokkan, you did it!
You're in perfect sync with Hasegawa-san!
Oh~! That's my Tomoka!
I hope the tide stays on our side...
Uh... here I go.
I-I'm sorry.
That's fine. We're only getting started.
We still have plenty of chances left.
Airi!
Airi, don't worry.
You can definitely beat Mayumi-san!
Airi-chan, remember your practice!
Go for it! Airi!
Don't lose, Airi!
Oh~! Go for it, Airi!
I won't run away! I can't run away!
My body...
Airi!
Are you okay, Airi? She fouled you there. It wasn't your fault.
Just take it easy and do what you can—
I hate that! I hate it!
I hate how I'm useless!
I cannot move like how I want to move...
I worked so hard... But my legs just shrink in fear...
Is she really that scary?
I'm sorry.
I see. So... how scary is she?
How scary?
Is she even scarier than I am, for example?
You're way more scary!
I see. Then everything's fine.
You aren't a coward. Go get her.
Yep!
You're not scary anymore, Onii-chan.
I know you're kind.
Airi!
Yes!
Now!
Nice, Airi!
Nice timing!
Nice shot!
That was super amazing!
Oh! Airi, you're so cool!
Good grief, we're getting pushed around by grade schoolers.
My girls aren't doing so hot.
You seem to be enjoying yourself, though, Suga.
Quit yer yapping.
What?!
Tomoka!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
More importantly, I stopped him!
I stopped him, Subaru-san!
Yes, you're the best.
You're the best partner.
Yes...
Was that a fluke?
He was stopped again!
Wow! How is he doing it?
Suga has a bad habit.
Bad habit?
Exactly. When he passes, he always has this angry look.
But when he isos, his confidence goes sky high.
Tomoka sees the iso coming and double teams him.
Yes!
Oh~! Tomoka's amazing!
But how did he find this out?
Good job!
Amazing!
Is this your basketball?
Sure is.
You happy with this?
Not until I beat you one-on-one!
Huh?! Think ya can do it?
That's why I came here.
Show me what you've got.
Sure. That was the plan anyway!
A floater?!
Getting desperate now?!
Our school may not have an official team but I haven't been fooling around.
Now Suga has to guard something other than a normal drive.
His reaction time is bound to be lower.
It's your turn to attack, Suga.
I'll pass. I can blow by ya anytime, so it'd be a waste of time.
Or are you saying you have a plan for defense, too?
Nope. I'll just go with the flow.
Come on, show me. You've still got something up your sleeve, right?
Right.
Hey! Are you messing with me?!
Not at all.
Yes, Subaru! You're amazing, Subaru-san!
It's only been a few days. What did you do?
You were doing such obvious fakes before.
I figured out my style of play.
Well, more like someone made me figure it out, I guess.
...Huh?
My fake should be natural.
I don't have the talent like you to dress up my fakes like the real thing.
But I noticed that I'm pretty good at making others think I do.
One more time! Come at me!
Sure, as many times as you wish.
I won't be using it for much longer anyway.
Shut up.
Don't think I've completely lost.
I don't think
I've completely beaten you, either.
We're not done here.
We can settle this later.
Next year.
Sure. Let's play full court next time.
5v5. Nashiba vs Itoda.
You'll have to find five others for a team first.
You won't have too many more chances to play me when I'm serious.
Sure.
You should get in on this too if you're serious, Kashii.
Shut up! Don't get too cocky, you loser.
I didn't lose! At least not completely!
W-Wait up, Ryuu!
I'll remember this!
Ryuu!
Seems like we have a game set up.
We've got to pick up that offer.
Next year for sure.
Yep.
Thanks for today, everyone.
You two were the best!
It was fun playing together.
For me, too! I was really happy to be your partner!
Tomoka...
Um, will I be able to become your partner, too?
Airi.
Wait right there!
Right there~!
That's not fair! We want to become your partners, too!
I'm sure I can help you too if we're on the same team!
Onii-chan! Me, too! Me, too!
Of course, you're all my precious partners.
Come on! Let's all play basketball!
Yay!
Tomorrow, I'll be going on a training camp with everyone!
We'll be staying the night, so I'll have to bring lots of handkerchiefs!
Well then, I'm off!