Kobe's at Charle's house right now
Sometimes ya gotta go down to go up
She is cleansing herself, I say.
Oh~ Charle's pulling the moves on Kobe?
M-moves?!
O Airi, calm thyself.
Editor's note: "be" is used in the subjunctive mood here.
'tis unlikely that the two be sharing their cleaning.
Thas rite
But how in the hell she gonna be training?
Lissen a me!
You tryna tell me Kobe's out of the zone?
erm
Kobe hath not played with Charles previously, hath she?
Kobe get the fuck in my bed
Charles hath always taken a position of the adversaries, if my memory lies not to me.
I don't know Charles, I'm not on the pill
Kobe's nervous cause of the baby?
Don't worry, I've changed the sheets recently,
and ran a blacklight so it's not dirty at all.
I told you I'm not on the pill!
Shit yeah!
Kobe gets wrecked in high-pressure
Fucking get in the bed
situations, she breaks down, yo
This is my Crib
I sho do hope she gets her groove on
S'all set
Haha, verily so.
Least use rubber, aight?
Kobe, I'll take it to your hoop!
Go the fuck to sleep, Kobe
Nah son
You don't  tell me what to do
I see. That's how it is.
Editor's note: Too many lines talking about himself, he must be an egoist!
This is my first time sleeping with someone.
I'll be gentle
I'm sorry for eating all the fried chicken earlier!
It calms me down when I'm takin' it rough
It's a tough life in the hood
I'm sorry for drinking all the koolaid
That shit's the bomb
I lied about the abortion!
I'll take responsibility
I'll go down to Welfare and get us set up
Then we can start a family
Just like mama always wanted
Charles Barkley...
Kobe...
I can't wait to have a lil' Travin Younger
With my shorty by my side
Ah'm so scared Charles
So scared, what if I'm disssaponting you?
I'm not disappointed at all.
Even if you mess up one hundred times in a row,
I'm sure you will continue to screw up, time and time again
Charles...
I'll do my best.
Kobe!
Yo!
Kobe! Your killing it!
Yeah!
I see
Come on you fucking loli, attack me
Attack me ya pussy, come on
Kareem what the fuck?
Stop! Stop!
Hey Gregg Popovich, back off!
My bad, I can't handle myself when it comes to ape-hoop
I hear you, just back off
Kobe, you al set for the rematch?
Yep!
'tis time to exercise our vendetta!
You two nigs gotta bring it!
K
Only da 3 of us out here,
but we a family
Lets win this shit!
Yeah!
I can't wait!
Kobe's kicking some ass out there
What kind of training did Charles Barkley do to her?
Heh, well
Steroids.
Charles!
Take this
What's that?
This is Kareem's shower cam you wanted
Please use it to your heart's content
Thanks!
Charles, about Kareem
Gregg, please
Kareem is the type that'll keep goin', running on steam
Yeah!
Lelouch's note: All the conditions have been cleared, commence attack against Cornelia!
Kareem's the kinda nigga that'll open fire
And pull the trigga like a nigga
Watcher's note: What is this, an election?!
Please support Kareem
Sure.
Come on, faggot, fite me
Fucking pussy, get at me
Why did Charles want to play against this punk?
I really have no idea what this is supposed to accomplish
It's got something to do with that blonde faggot
His feinting or whatever's similar to his style
But Charles found out that's not really everything there is to it.
Fuck yeah!
Suck my cock!
Hey you kid!
Again!
Haha, fucking owned, loser
Charles! You're moves look weird!
Your fakes are way too obvious.
Why? My fakes aren't working...
Wow man, like, you fucking suck
You always prance around like the fucking king of the NBA
What?!
Don't underestimate me!
A floater?!
Yes!
Up yours, nigger
I'm just a kid!
I guess I got a bit too into it...
A floater, huh...
That'll probably work
No, I can't use it yet
There's a great chance that it won't go in.
I can't use an imperfect move against Suga.
Stop being such a pussy, just go for it
You can't live scared of failure, ya know?
They call me the King of Clutch
That may be
That's pretty good, coming from you.
Don't be so arrogant!
I'll clean your clock!
But just what exactly am I doing wrong?
Oh? Your brotha?
He's been practicing with me, but I haven't gotten any better...
Why do I suck?
Its all goood Kareem, you'll be fine!
I'm sure you be fine
We can pracrtice, I'm sho you can do it!
Lebron!
We're all friends here
Watcher's note: Heart attack alert! Oh whoops, too late.
We all love you so much!
LeBron... Thank you.
I couldn't stop you after all.
Were my fakes any different from my usual ones?
No...
I see.
Your fakes put me on edge
Don't be getting the wrong idea!
It's jussat, I don't know man
I don't know what's going on either way, if ya can hear me out!
Sorry for saying such wack things.
It's not strange at all.
But I'm stumped... How do you make your fakes look so natural?
Natural? What are you on about?
Natural...
Oh! Got it!
I stop you!
Thank you, Kobe!
I can see clearly now!
Realy?
Go! Go! Charles Barkley!
Forth! Forth! Barkley-san!
Go! Go! Onii-chan!
Go! Go! Charles!
Editor's note: Because you've got curves, duh
Man, why do I gotta put up with this shit?
Go! Go! Charles!
Fight!
Since you challenged us for a second game, does that mean you are confident in stopping me?
That's exactly it
I think we're going to cream you
Listen to your own words!
No really,
We're going to sweep you
It's awwright!
Nice steal, Kobe!
Th-Thanks!
Run, Kobe!
Nah man she aint catchin that
I did it, Charles!
Nice shot, Kobe!
Kobe, ya did it!
Thou art like Charles's right hand!
Ohohoho ,das my Kobe!
We gotta keep this up
errr well...here goes....
Sorry guys!
It's cool, we're just warming up!
You'll get 'em next time!
Kareem!
Kareem, don't worry about it
You can totally crush that emo whore!
Kareem, remember the basics!
Go for it! Kareem!
O Kareem, I pray that thou dost not lose!
Oh~! Get 'em, Kareem!
I think I can, I think I can, I think I can!
My body's...
Kareem!
You alright Kareem? Don't get twisted, yo, she fouled ya
Take it easy, chill out
I HATE THIS
I CAN'T STAND BEING USELESS
I'm just here as a third wheel!
Heh, that's all I am, huh? A third wheel.
Get your act together?
I'm sorry.
It's that emo, isn't it?
Yeah
I bet she listens to Linkni Park, huh?
Watcher's note: Holy shit, saying that with a smile gotta hurt for poor Banri...
And cuts her arms!
I see. Then it's all good
You aren't a coward. Go get 'er
k!
You're not scary anymore, Big Brotha.
I know you're kind
Kareem!
Yeah!
NOW!
Nice, Kareem!
Nice timing!
Nice shot!
Truly, I have witnessed a spectacle that hath led to my amazement.
Oh! Kareem your the coolest!
God Damn, we're getting our asses handed to us
My shortie's playin' like shit
You seem to be enjoying yourself, though
Screw you negro!
What?!
Kobe!
You aright?
Yep, I'm good
Did you see? I stopped the nigga!
I stopped him, Charles!
Oh Yes Kobe, I saw
You're the best partner.
Yes...
What was that?!
He was stopped once more!
WOW!? HOW'S HE DOING THAT?!
He's got a bad habit
Bad habit? Please do speak thy mind.
Thas rite. When he passes, he always has this bitchy look.
But when he isos, he's a stone cold nigga killa
Editor's note: I have no fucking idea what's going on anymore, is this Pokemon?
Kobe sees the iso coming and gang bangs.
Yes!
Oh~! That Kobe's amazing!
How could he discover that?
Good job!
Amazing!
Is this your 'basketball'?
Damn right
You happy with this?
Not until I beat you 1v1
Hah! You think you can do it?
Hell yes I can
Show me what you want
What you really really want
Thas rite, that was my plan!
Grumpy TL note: Seriously, it's a single fucking throw, stop getting excited over it.
A floater?!
Getting desperate now?!
Our school may not even be good, but I haven't been screwing around.
Now this busta's gotta protect his rear, as well
His reaction time's gonna be slower.
It's your turn to attack, nig
Nah, son, I'm too good for you, not worth it
Or you saying you have a plan for defense, too?
Not one bit, the spice must flow
Come on, show me. You still got something up your sleeve, right?
Yeah
You fucking with me?
That's exactly it
Thank you Based Charles Barkley!
It's only been a few days. What did you do?
You were doing such obvious fakes before.
I figured out my style of play.
Well, more like someone made me figure it out, I guess.
wat?
My fake should be natural.
I don't got the talent like you to play faggy games and rely on tricks
But I noticed that I'm pretty good at making others think I'm good
Again, Come at me!
Sure thing, whatever you want
I won't be using it for much longer anyway.
Shut up!
I'm not out of the game yet!
I haven't beat you 100% yet either
We're not done here.
We'll be settling this later.
Next year.
Sure. Let's play full court next time.
5v5. Crips vs Bloods
You're gonna need a team for that!
You won't have too many more chances to play me when I'm serious.
Sure.
You should get in on this too if you're serious, Popovich!
Who you think you are scrawny nigga?
I'm NOT scrawny! Just Toned!
Wait up scrawny!
I'll remember this!
Scrawny!
Seems like we have a game set up.
We've got to pick up that offer.
Next year fo sure.
Yep.
Thanks for today, everyone.
You two were the best!
It was ballin' playing together.
For me, too! I's real to happy to be your partner
Kobe...
ehem, can I be your partner too?
Kareem....
One moment, please!
Right there~ ohohoho~
That ain't fair, we want in too
I am certain that I can help thee as well if we are on the same team!
Brotha, don't forget LeBron!
Of course, you're all my precious partners.
Department of Health note: Viewer discretion advised: This line is so cheesy that uncontrolled throwing up may be unavoidable.
Lets go everyone! We run this!
Yay!
Tomorrow, I'll be going on a tour of the cotton fields!
We'll be staying the week,
so I'll be workin' my fingers to the bone!
Wish me luck in Georgia!