Lulu... I failed you as a friend.
I knew how you felt, but I pretended not to.
I lied to you even though you're my friend.
Maybe it's too late now,
but I want you to hear...
...about the day I let go of
Kureha's love, and why I did it.
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"WHAT WE HOPE FOR"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
"Flashback"
"11 Years Ago・(History)"
She's done for.
Yeah, she'd slow us down. Let's exclude her.
Exclude her.
--Exclude her.
I prepared myself that day
to die there all alone,
without anyone ever finding me.
But...
It's okay, you're not alone. I'm your friend!
We'll be together forever now.
My mom told me that as long as you don't
forget love, you'll never be alone.
If you don't give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you'll never be invisible.
Growl...
I'm going to protect you...
Is your love the real thing?
Growl?
Kureha! Kureha! Where are you?!
I won't forget love. I won't give up on love.
Growl!
We...
...are friends!
And so Kureha and I became friends.
We shared so many things.
Love was sweet, and kind, and made
everything seem to sparkle like a star.
So I got the wrong idea,
and thought the world had approved me.
But...
There's the traitor!
Don't come out!
I heard you're hanging out
with a bear. Another girl saw you!
Not cool!
Wh-What do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
My mommy says bears are our enemies!
Bears are evil! We gotta exclude them!
That's not true! We can be friends with bears!
You're gonna defend them?!
Not cool!
Then you're evil, too!
Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
--Hey guys, she's an evil girl who defends bears!
--Exclude! Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude all traitors!
Please stop!
Growl... Kureha got hurt for me.
Lick... lick...
This happened to her because I'm a bear.
It's not okay for me to be a bear.
If... If I were a human girl...
Could we be together forever?
Could I protect Kureha?
Please tell me, Lady Kumaria!
Is your love the real thing?
My love's the real thing, growl!
Court is in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
This is the land of enlightenment
for all living things...
yes, even human and bear.
Let us now pass judgment--
for the sake of humans and bears!
LIFE Sexy!
LIFE Cool!
LIFE Beauty!
Is this where Lady Kumaria lives?
Lady Kumaria has been lost.
She became meteors that
scattered across our planet.
Oh, no...
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Defendant-bear Ginko Yurishiro,
is there anything you wish to say?
Growl...
I want to be with Kureha forever!
I want to protect Kureha!
So please... make me a human girl!
Very well.
However, there is one condition.
You must relinquish love.
In other words, she will forget you.
And you're not allowed to tell
anyone what happened here!
Ah, it's just like The Little Mermaid! Sparkle!
When Kureha Tsubaki wakes up,
she will most likely reject you.
Reject?
No!
A-A bear!
Stay away!
S-Someone help!
No!
That's right, Lulu.
To get my wish to be a human girl,
I let go of Kureha's love.
And then...
Someday, the time will come when
bears and people can be friends forever.
I was sent back to the bear world.
Yet you insist that you love this human girl?
I won't give up on love, growl!
Dreadful... You are no longer a cub of Kumaria!
You are Ginko the Lone Wolfsbane,
a blight on this world!
Begone, sinful child who betrays our Mother!
You must wait. The time will come,
and you will find Kureha Tsubaki.
And, if you can make
friends with her again... Sparkle!
My wish will come true?
Yes. Exchange Promise Kisses with her.
If you do that...
I can be a human girl, growl?
Now, defendant-bear Ginko Yurishiro, I ask you:
Will you become human?
Or will you give up on love?
I won't give up on love.
I'll become human, growl!
I waited for the time to come.
And then...
I met you, Lulu.
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Yes?
Is your love the real thing?
It is, growl.
The Invisible Storm has begun. Now is the time.
I know.
I won't give up on love!
I won't, either. I'll support your love, Ginko!
Lulu, you always stayed by my side.
You gave me love without
seeking anything in return.
Lulu...
Thank you.
Huh?
Sure!
We'll be fine! I'll protect you, Ginko.
Okay, let's go to the human world! Growl!
"The Day They Transferred In・(History)"
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so I became a human girl.
Kureha, I wanted to become true
friends with you. To cross the wall...
Sniff, sniff.
She's here! She really does smell delicious!
Lulu... You were my true
friend from the beginning.
We all see the problem, agreed?
We must exclude the bear lurking in our school.
I assume everyone's ready.
Let's confirm this one more time.
Who should we use as bait for the bear?
Let's search sacrifice!
"4. Saori Shimabukuro"
"5. Hinako Serina"
"3. Aoi Uezu"
"2. Karen Tanaka"
"1. Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
Shall I lick your wounds for you?
No, growl.
Oh, you're giving me the cold shoulder today?
Listen to me: I want to eat Kureha Tsubaki.
That's a desire you and I share.
Come on, let's find her and eat her!
Oh, I smell it, a delicious smell.
I smell a girl who won't back down on love.
Delicious smell. Grr.
Grrrrrrr...
Yes, that's how it should be.
These girls need to learn that a hunter
is always in danger of being hunted.
Growl, growl, growl!
This is Bear-Killing Beam Truck.
Target Alpha sighted.
Preparing to fire Eco-Kumagical Gun!
Nasty?
Buzz buzz! Nasty nasty!
Eco-Kumagical energy replenishing.
We'll be at full power in 10, 9, 8...
Nasty nasty!
They really are beasts.
To think she just walked
right in here after her bait!
So, how did you tame her?
Did you tell her you loved her,
maybe give her a little kiss?
Hmph! You way disgust me!
This is Bear-Killing Beam Truck.
We fired on Target Alpha and managed
to scratch her, but she got away!
Damn!
This is D5. I've been informed
that the door in the lily bed is open.
I'm heading there to investigate.
I was right, they're using that place
as their gateway. Wily bears...
Oh, right, I have something good!
I found this when I searched your house.
That's...!
Your mom wrote it, right?
A bear and a human, friends?
Writing this crap is what
got her killed by bears!
"Lady Kumaria"? Are you stupid?!
There are no gods in this world.
The only thing ruling us is
the invisible atmosphere.
Here, bearie bearie bearie!
I have your food right here.
That was close. When did they
get that tasteless weapon?
Well, shall we go eat Kureha?
You won't lose.
The desire to monopolize someone
is stronger than anything, after all.
I won't forget love.
I won't give up on love.
Nasty...
--Nasty...
--We've got trouble!
Nas... ty...
I've finally found true love.
What are you talking about?
You've already accepted me, haven't you?
True love doesn't break in some stupid storm.
True love...
...doesn't leave me all alone!
I can hear her... Kureha's calling me!
It's the same as back then!
When I got separated from the others,
Kureha was the only one to find me.
She gave me love.
So this time, I'll be the one to save her.
Don't!
Don't do that. We're bears.
You can't tell me you've forgotten...
Because I'm your desire. Your love itself.
No!
True love...
...makes me leap into the storm!
You want to abandon me?
That's not possible! I'm your desire!
Beasts who lose their desire die!
Goodbye.
I will tear...
...myself...
...apart!
Growl!
Silly girl.
Kureha, I found you, growl!
Stay away!
Don't come any closer to me.
What do you even want at this point?
It's your fault this happened!
You were never my friend anyway!
Humans and bears are severed!
We can't be together no matter what we do!
I know, growl. That's why...
I'm going to become your friend again,
no matter how much you resist.
I'll become your friend,
and we'll do a Promise Kiss.
Because if we do that, I can be human!
As long as you don't forget love,
you'll never be alone.
If you don't give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you'll never be invisible!
Stop it! It's your fault
everyone died! Even Sumika!
I won't forgive you... I won't forgive bears!
Go away. Go back to the other side.
I sent Yurigasaki back, too.
Go, and never come back.
Stop!
No... stay away... Please!
Kureha, I'll never back down on love.
"Flashback"
Kureha, I'll never back down on my love.
No, I don't want to lose anyone else...
Lulu!
Sorry, Kure-chin... I came back.
Muahaha, you're a bad liar, Kure-chin.
Lulu... Lulu!
Kure-chin let me escape.
She said I wasn't her friend,
but her lie was... super obvious...
So I know she'll forgive you, Ginko.
No, she already has.
Lulu...
You can be her friend, Ginko.
Make your love... come true, okay?
You can get a Promise Kiss.
I believe in you, Ginko...
Here, I collected your future.
See? I'm so clever, right?
Damn...
Lulu?
Lulu!
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love
Defendant Kureha Tsubaki,
do you admit your crime?