In the
time
of the
warring
states
A time of corruption
There existed
an
ultimate
Way of
the Sword
that used
no swords
Oushuu
Hida Castle
The rebel,
Hida Takahito.
Kyotouryuu's...
Note: Kyotouryuu = Swordless Style
I see...
So this is how I'll meet my end.
At this point, it is unavoidable.
Miss?
It's in sight now.
What kind of business might you have on an uninhabited island like that?
It's not an uninhabited island.
That's the island where the hero of the rebellion was exiled.
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
己をはらはら花に例えて散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsui ga kureta guren no tama wo
終がくれた紅蓮の珠を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarauka no hi arashi no neyo ni
さらうかの火　嵐の寝夜に
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
恐るるまま命は羽ばたいて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
やがてやがて天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
紅く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai hime no yume wo ataeta mou
すれ違い姫の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabidata meiyo ni samayoi
待ちわびた冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
思いがはらはら舞うゆえに
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sore he egaite
絆を更なる空へ 描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Zettou
Kanna
The one who came to power after the rebellion, Shogun Yanari, fearing the power of the hero of the rebellion, Yasuri Mutsue,
exiled him along with his family to this uninhabited island.
For 20 years after that, no one else stepped foot on the island.
What a hassle.
What are you doing, Shichika?
Nee-chan...
It looks like the cistern's out of water, so...
Don't come out dressed like that, it's cold.
I'm fine.
It feels good if it's just for a bit.
Also, wasn't it my turn to do the housework today?
Was it?
Didn't I tell you to stop treating me so delicately?
I wasn't trying to.
It's fine.
This is just another part of training.
I don't remember teaching you to be overly considerate.
See, go back inside I said!
There's no meaning to training anymore.
Nee-chan...
What meaning is there in maintaining a combat style that will end with your generation?
I don't think about the meaning or anything.
Hey, Shichika...
It's already been a year since father died.
Can't you let it go already?
You don't need to say it like that...
I mean, just yesterday, I thought up a new ultimate move.
It's a really awesome... move...
To begin with, the one who got banished was father alone.
It'd be impossible for me, but you could make a boat for yourself and—
Don't say stupid stuff!
That wasn't the kind of topic to bring up so early in the morning, was it.
I'll prepare breakfast, so come back quickly.
Yeah.
A new ultimate move, you say...
Show it to me later.
Leave the island, huh...
I was expecting this topic to come up eventually,
but this is the only thing I inherited from father, so...
I want to cherish it while I still can.
I don't have anything else, after all.
What a hassle.
If father was around he'd cut them down with one strike, too...
Hey!
A person from the mainland?
First time seeing one.
A sword?
First time seeing that too.
I don't personally mind if strangers or outsiders come here, but...
Um...
It's absolutely forbidden to carry blades onto this island.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Pardon me, then.
I wasn't aware.
Forgive me.
Well, I wasn't the one who decided it.
How did you come to this island?
By boat, of course.
It's not like I particularly wanted to know,
but I'm supposed to say that in this situation.
Next is...
"What did you come here for?" right?
Yeah!
What did you come here for?
I heard that the 6th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Mutsue lives here.
Do you know him?
If you're talking about dad, he died.
A year ago.
I see...
Right now I'm the family head.
The 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
I see.
Excuse my insensitivity.
My information was 20 years old, so I had considered he may have passed away.
I see...
He's got a strong body.
Doesn't look terrible either.
I'd say it gets a passing grade.
What are you talking about?
Ah, just talking to myself.
It seems you had business with dad... sorry about that.
You're right, but a little off.
My business is with the Kyotouryuu head.
Which means the business I had with Mutsue-dono has now changed to business with you.
Shichika, I haven't told you my own name yet.
I'm Togame.
Togame?
Weird name.
In my position as general director for the army of the Shogunate, I serve as a strategist.
I'll first of all be putting Kyotouryuu to the test.
This is an early work of Mibu Kasamaro, one of the 36 Fugaku swordsmiths.
Test?
That's what I said.
Here I come!
Yasuri Shichika and Togame the strategian.
The unfortunate meeting that began their destiny together,
took place in the middle of January, in a time when the word "gyafun" was not yet outdated.
I'm back.
You said you're Togame the strategian, right?
As you're our first visitor to this island, I'm not entirely sure how to welcome you...
No.
Pardon me for arriving here unannounced.
I am Yasuri Mutsue's daughter, Nanami.
I heard you came to visit my father, but what connection do you have with him?
I don't really have any "connection" to him.
You don't?
No.
You can think of me as someone who just got involved, Nanami.
I'll keep your sword in my care.
It's forbidden to bring or use blades on this island.
Because of Kyotouryuu?
It's written as "flow of the empty sword",
a hidden style that uses no sword.
The only ones who have openly demonstrated that style,
were the first generation head Yasuri Kazuni...
and the 6th generation head Yasuri Mutsue.
When the whole country was plunged into rebellion, it was used in the midst of the chaotic battlefields, the deadliest of sword styles.
That man is the 7th head.
Togame-san.
You tried to attack my brother?
I really wanted to see Kyotouryuu in action.
I'm not used to that sort of thing though.
I'm a strategian, not a swordsman.
That was still pretty impressive, given that.
I practiced that.
Why don't you keep practicing till you master it?
That was a rather violent method, no?
It's understandable if you see it that way, but I had my reasons.
I'd heard of the name Yasuri Mutsue, but I don't know his face.
It would be big problem if I got the wrong person.
If he demonstrated Kyotouryuu, that would be more convincing than any name could be.
Even if Mutsue were Shichika, it'd be the same?
In that case, why don't you test him again?
Consider yourself lucky to have tripped over that rock.
If your blade had reached Shichika's body, you wouldn't have escaped with just a bump on your forehead.
No.
I'll accept those words as proof of Kyotouryuu.
Is that so?
Let's hear what you have to say then.
Alright.
Hey you, wouldn't you like to rule the world?
No.
Exactly.
It's a natural desire for all who live in this world.
There's no shame in having ambition.
Who can deny the motivations of rebels?
If you look into it, you'll find that even the current Shogunate were originally servants who supplanted their masters.
Which means... wait, you said "no"??
Yeah.
I don't really get what you're saying.
Don't get it?
Togame-san.
Being born and raised on this island, we don't really know about the world.
It's better if you assume we don't understand wordy language.
Is that right?
In that case, could I have you leave?
I can't agree to that.
There are two reasons why.
The first is that Kyotouryuu is an art inherited by blood.
Even if dad were still here, he'd have let us stay too.
And the other reason is because I'm bad at thinking.
Really? You're bad at thinking, huh.
Then I'll continue under the promise of confidentiality.
Do you know a swordsmith by the name of Shikizaki Kiki?
No.
Exactly.
Even on this isolated island, any swordsman will at least have heard that name.
For a school like Kyotouryuu which fights without weapons, someone like Shikizaki is a natural enemy.
Wait, you said, "no"??
Yeah.
Though I get the idea that he's a big deal.
Shikizaki Kiki...
If I recall, he was a famous swordsmith from the Sengoku period?
That's all you know about him?
I only heard that he had a close connection to the founder of Kyotouryuu.
Shikizaki didn't belong to any sword school.
He isolated himself from others, the most heretic of the heretical swordsmiths.
However, it's said his swordsmithery dominated the Sengoku period.
Dominated the Sengoku period?
I don't understand the meaning of those words...
Belonging to no country or house, he distributed the swords he made indiscriminately throughout the land.
Within 25 countries, he gave out a thousand swords.
A thousand?
That's a lot!
Not very many.
Not many then...
The more of his swords a country had, the better they did on the battlefield.
If that's not dominating the Sengoku period then what is?
Couldn't you say it's the other way around?
Being large and powerful enough to hold an advantage in combat allowed some countries to amass more of his swords.
It's true that's how it must look from a practical standpoint.
On the other hand, it's also true there's a basis for that myth.
They say 150 years ago, Shogun Kyuu obsessed over those mythical weapons,
and when he achieved unification of the country, he held a majority of the swords, 507 of them.
How childish...
After that, Shogun Kyuu, who put all his trust in Shikizaki's swords, made that corrupt decree to collect up all swords.
The one he said was for making a Buddha statue or something?
That was only the face of it.
I heard the real purpose of it was to bring together all the swordsmen into one place.
No, the true goal was—
"to collect together all of Shikizaki's swords"?
Exactly.
That's quite surprising to hear.
That said, Shogun Kyuu collected over 100,000 swords.
100,000 swords?
That's not very many!
Quite a lot.
Quite a lot then...
So did he collect all of Shikizaki's swords?
No.
He gave up at the very end.
He managed to track down the locations of all one thousand swords...
but only their locations.
Shouldn't he have been able to collect them all then?
He had the authority of the Shogunate after all.
It didn't work out that way.
Among the thousand, the final 12 remaining were incredibly unique.
It's currently believed that the first 988 were mere practice for the purpose of creating those 12 swords.
A thousand for the sake of 12?
Pretty crazy story, right?
Kanna.
Plane, the Absolute
Namakura.
Blunt, the Decapitator
Tsurugi.
Blade, the Thousand
Hari.
Needle, the Light
Yoroi.
Armor, the Grudge
Kanazuchi.
Hammer, the Pair
Bita.
Poor, the Evil
Kanzashi.
Sai, the Tiny
Nokogiri.
Saw, the King
Hakari.
Scales, the True
Mekki.
Gild, the Poison
Jyuu.
Gun, the Flame
The evilness of those swords is incomparable to any other famous sword you've heard of.
The records say that the armies sent by Shogun Kyuu to collect them were wiped out by the power of a single sword.
This is the first time I've heard that.
And that is why I've come to this island.
Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
I've come to convey this command to you, to gather the last 12 swords that the legendary swordsmith Shikizaki Kiki made.
So that's what you meant when you asked if I wanted to rule the world.
Indeed.
I didn't actually mean you would rule the world.
The Shogunate right now has been stable for a long time, right?
They had the power to suppress the rebellion with brute force.
Indeed, with brute force...
N-No I mean, that rebellion was a problem.
The Owari Shogunate has been in power for 150 years now.
No one in this generation really understands what the Sengoku period was like anymore.
These days no one really thinks of Shikizaki Kiki's swords as anything more than trinkets, but just think about it...
If the conspirators behind the last rebellion had gotten a hold of those 12 swords,
what would have happened to the current Shogunate?
They fear a revolt...
"You can never be too careful" kind of thing?
So where are those swords currently?
The ones we know of are in Inaba, Izumo, Satsuma, Ezo, and Tosa.
The rest are still under investigation.
You only know half of them...
Say "you've already found half of them" instead!
What is it?
If they're afraid of a revolt, wouldn't it be smarter not to provoke the current owners?
"Do it skillfully" was the order given by the Shogunate.
What does doing it skillfully mean?
We have a strategian for that very purpose!
Someone who can move about in the shadows.
Um...
What exactly is a "strategian"?
Specifically, I'm the army general director in support of critical tasks under direct control of Yanari Shogun of the Owari Shogunate,
the strategian Togame.
Um...
Is that a new post that was created in the last 20 years or something?
No, I just made up that title.
Self-named...
If tactics are created by a tactician, strategies are created by a strategian!
I'm abnormal, so abnormal orders are given to me.
That being the case, can you lend me your strength?
If you're really from the Shogunate, there's no need for you to rely on Kyotouryuu...
I know what you're trying to say.
However, I can't use people who will work for money.
The ninja who were entrusted the task of collecting the swords...
betrayed us.
Even though they're ninja?
Your surprise is understandable.
If they did that, the trust in them that they'd built up over all those years would collapse.
Even so, once they found the swords, they disappeared.
The entire ninja army, along with their whole village.
Unbelievable...
The perfected Deviant Blades are such a high class treasure that you could buy an entire country with the cost of a single sword.
That's why people who'd work for money are unacceptable.
I see.
Then how about honor?
My father taught me that swordsmen should do what's right.
Honor, huh...
Swordsmen are no good either.
The Shogunate picked one of their strongest, most loyal and honorable swordsmen.
His name was Sabi Hakuhei.
They tasked him with retrieving what they thought was hardest sword to obtain - Hakutou Hari.
However, he obtained it in a shockingly short time.
Wow!
He obtained it, then disappeared.
Hey!
Its poison is too strong.
And he betrayed us precisely because of that honor — he was unable to resist the honor of owning one of Shikizaki's sword.
Ninja and swordsmen...
So the swords are now in the possession of really strong guys...
Your followers must all be running away.
That's right!
What can I do about it?
Like I'd know!
So that's why you sought out Kyotouryuu.
Swordsmen who don't work for money nor wield swords.
Exactly.
Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika!
In order to ensure the prosperity of the Owari Shogunate, will you wield the skills you have forged?
I understand what you came for,
and it sounds urgent for you, but I don't have any interest in swords.
Are you scared?
Of course I am!
But more importantly, it's a hassle, leaving the island and crossing the sea and all.
Do you think I didn't anticipate that answer?
Do you believe that this strategian who has been betrayed so many times in the past,
came to this island without preparing an appropriate reason for you?
You've been betrayed, have you?
Well do you have one? A reason?
Yeah.
People who work for money are no good.
People who work for honor are also no good.
That leaves only one reason.
Love!
L-Love?
People who work for love can be trusted.
Yasuri Shichika...
fall for me!
Shuriken?!
What the hell!
This is the home dad built!
Shichika...
Honestly, so hasty...
No, that was the right thing to do.
For aerial weaponry, you have to make split-second decisions.
Well, he's just moving on instinct...
A ninja... from the Maniwa corps, it seems.
Maniwa?
The ones who turned traitor the instant they learned of the value of Shikizaki's swords.
How many are there?
Probably just one.
Maniwa shinobi hate working in groups.
What I don't know is why they're here...
I wasn't tailed, and I didn't tell anyone my destination.
If the enemy is really here alone,
then Shichika is probably leading them to the beach ahead.
You seem pretty confident.
The enemy is from the Maniwa corps, you know?
Kyotouryuu won't lose to a mere ninja.
That's reassuring, but what's most important right now is why is a Maniwa corps soldier is on the island!
That's true...
Togame-san, are you certain there was no possibility you were followed?
Don't insult me.
It was precisely because the opponent is a ninja that I was more cautious than usual.
That's also why I didn't tell anyone my destination.
I really wonder how...
Did you come to this island alone?
You're seriously asking that?
How did you get here then?
I came by boat, of course!
Did you row the boat yourself?
What a strange question.
My specialty is brain work.
Does it look like I'd have the strength to—
So there was a ferryman?
Yes, but...
Oh no!
That man wields one of Shikizaki's swords!
I hope you're not thinking you've driven me into a corner.
It's the opposite!
I'm the one who led you here!
Wait, wait...
My head is spinning from all the visitors here today.
Could you not all come on the same day like that?
I don't give a damn about your problems.
I'm one of the 12 heads of the Maniwa corps, the great Maniwa Koumori!
Maniwa corps?
Oh yeah, I heard you're a ninja or something.
The fact that you heard that is bad luck for you.
If it weren't for that, I'd have just ignored you.
My objective is that woman who has all that information.
You were eavesdropping?
That's a distasteful hobby.
You should say it's a good hobby!
You tailed Togame here?
Nope.
I didn't do anything so sneaky.
We came here together.
I rowed the boat all the way here.
It was hard work you know.
That woman just sat on her ass the whole time without lifting a finger to help.
Does everyone from the mainland talk as much as this?
She's got quite the nerve, geez...
Don't you think so?
Right...
You're a pretty dull guy.
Well, you are from the boonies I guess...
Can't help that.
It's nothing personal, but I'll have to kill you here.
Come to think of it, this is my first real battle, isn't it?
You scared?
No...
I was just thinking you aren't carrying a sword, as far as I can tell...
Oh right, you're a swordsman who doesn't use a sword?
When it comes to "swordsmanship" you usually assume you're going to be fighting with swords.
That's some ridiculously absurd swordsmanship!
Not really, it's just that I don't know much about how ninja fight.
Don't worry.
While I'm not a swordsman, it's not like I can't use a sword.
As you wish, how about I bring out the sword I'm carrying?
What?
Humans can do something like that?
Listen and look in shock!
This is one of the 12 Deviant Blades that Shikizaki Kiki perfected, Zettou Kanna!
Kanna
Zettou
I'm more shocked at your body than the sword...
They call me Hades Koumori!
Meaning, I have a very generous personality when it comes to serving up presents from hell!
Koumori the maid?
Note: "Hell" sounds like "maid".
That sounds strangely cute...
Stop spouting that nonsense!
That aside, aren't you feeling anything right now?
This is one of the Shikizaki swords that that woman was talking about earlier, you know.
Nothing at all?
I don't really want to take it when it's all sticky like that.
It's really valuable, right?
Should you really be carrying it around like that?
Quite the opposite.
If I didn't keep it stored inside my body, I'd be worried about the safety of such a valuable treasure.
On top of that, this thing has an interesting power.
That woman called it poison, but this thing is the ultimate medicine!
When you hold it, you feel its desire to cut off people's heads!
Houfuku Zettou!
Note: Absolute Retribution Strike
Houfuku
Zettou
Kyotouryuu, first dance: Lily of the Valley.
Then how about this?
Houfuku Zettou!
Kyotouryuu: Chrysanthemum!
Huh?
You little...
You saw through—
You're so noisy!
Let me thank you.
It's been a long time since I've been surprised at anyone.
You use your arms and legs as swords...
You know your stuff, I guess you really are a swordsman.
I'm not nearly as surprising as you though.
Nor...
as surprising as that "Kanna".
Did you notice anything from that attack?
The technique I just used isn't meant to catch swords.
Kyotouryuu: Chrysanthemum is a technique that breaks your opponent's sword in two.
That sword is definitely weird.
What are you talking about?
Of course it's weird!
If would be strange if it didn't seem weird.
This Zettou Kanna was created with toughness as its main focus.
Swords are expendable, so when you use them they'll break or bend and lose their ability to cut.
However, this Kanna is different.
It can't ever be broken or bent.
That's why it always cuts so well.
Wow...
Even though it's a straight sword, no matter what you do it doesn't chip.
It's a Japanese sword that wouldn't break even if elephants trampled it.
It'd sell for a really high price too!
I did some research and found out...
Even though that Shikizaki geezer was a swordsmith, he also dabbled in the occult and alchemy.
Rather suspicious methods, don't you think?
A guy who pulls swords out of his mouth like you is 12 times more suspicious.
There was a reason for that little story.
You must now understand that Kyotouryuu cannot match up to Shikizaki's swords.
Your sword-breaking technique couldn't break it after all!
I see that Kyotouryuu aims to destroy the opponent's weapons.
Really, that's outstanding!
I would have loved to see you do it though!
Kyotouryuu, second dance: Daffodil.
This time I will definitely shatter that Zettou Kanna.
Idiot!
What do you mean shatter it?!
If I brought it like that to the Shogunate, they'd make me commit harakiri!
Ah...
Didn't you listen to a single word I was saying?
It's not like I said I'd accept your request anyway...
That's not the problem here!
Don't you understand the value of things?
That's right!
As one who understands the value of things, smashing something of monetary worth is unthinkable to me.
Yep.
How about I start off with this?
It's been a while, little kitty.
Maniwa Koumori...
Don't be so mad.
Ninja may be traitors, but sneakiness is our selling point.
Why you...
We'll have plenty of time to talk about that later, Miss strategian.
Nice and slowly, after I destroy this Kyotouryuu guy!
Shichika, defeat him!
Actually, that Kanna has got me riled up.
Like I said, don't break it!
Yeah, yeah.
If you have any other requests, say so now.
I'm going to end this right now.
Well, in that case...
If at all possible, do it with a flashy move.
I'll have to hand in a report describing how we obtained the sword.
If you have some cool move that'll capture the reader's attention, I'll ask that you use it now!
Once again, don't destroy that sword, even accidentally.
If you do, this story will end at chapter one!
Chapter one? Are you writing a book?
I'd also like to do that sometime in the future.
It'd sell!
I guess I'll show you something flashy then.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Koumori.
Wha... hey!
No no, it was me delaying this.
What are you doing?
It's not going to be much of a fight like that!
Yep.
I'm not a swordsman, after all.
I'm particular about this sword, so being beaten by you here wouldn't be very shinobi of me.
Note: "shinobi" also means "to steal"
Oops, was that a pun?
I don't care.
I'll beat you either way.
You're no match for me if I fight with ninjutsu.
My actual battlefield experience is on a different level from yours.
So far this has just been a welcoming reception.
Just think of it as a bad habit of mine.
I'm going to be serious from now on.
Stop screwing around!
That thing isn't just a decoration for you to get your drool all over!
Take it out! Take it out right now!
Geez, such a noisy little kitty.
Fine...
Oh? You're unexpectedly cooperati—
Ow...
Huh?
Damn, that was close.
That kid is really something.
Though I was expecting something like that, little kitty.
What's this?
Oh, you're awake?
Don't worry, I'll be killing you soon.
Koumori!!
You probably think you've found something good,
but that's too naive!
He may be used to battling, but he's never been on a battlefield.
You're just a coward who runs away.
Hey hey, what are you blabbing about?
Isn't a wise person supposed to fight strength using intellect, Miss strategian?
All you do is bully weaker people!
I come up with strategies that allow the weak to challenge the strong, by whittling away their life and spirit.
Don't even compare us, you lowlife!
I see strategians are also good at running their mouths off.
Though even so, that's not what you did, is it?
What?
"Fall for me"?
Come on, that's pretty wild!
I was so surprised I accidentally spat out those shuriken.
That attack wasn't intentional?
It was way too embarrassing for me to bear.
That's touching, I'd have liked someone to say that to me.
Well I overheard all the information I needed, so it's fine.
Hurry up and kill me!
Stop trying to act so dignified, little kitty.
Even while you say that, you're trying to think of a way to outsmart me, right?
You're even more tricky than me.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
I deliberately missed with that shuriken attack earlier.
You don't understand the concept of moderation do you?
If one had even nicked me, I would have died!
You don't know how fragile I am.
That's not something you should be bragging about!
I'll torture you when I return, so bear with it a little longer.
I'm sure you're not completely clueless about the location of the remaining swords.
Though since this is the end I guess I'll ask you.
How about turning your back on the Shogunate and following us?
I'll be sure to give you a piece of the action.
I decline.
People who work for money can't be trusted.
You're afraid of being betrayed?
I'd say it's more strange to trust in a ninja.
Now then...
I'm sure you've been thinking it, but the truth is you're not actually a hostage.
How about this?
What if I changed my appearance to that of yours?
This way even that Kyotouryuu guy will let down his guard.
You must be aware of my ability, right?
After all, I found Kanna under your orders, then stole it.
After I kill that Kyotouryuu guy, maybe I'll transform into him to kill you.
Sorry, but I'll have you wait there until then.
Wait!
I originally betrayed you for money,
but even were it not for that, if i had known what kind of person you were from the start, I wouldn't have worked with you.
Even that invitation just now was just so I could work with you again,
and then betray you again.
There's no one in this world who'd stay by your side.
That's strange...
Where on earth did they go?
Leave the island, huh...
This late...
What a hassle.
It's true that Kyotouryuu is a particularly troublesome opponent against Shikizaki's Deviant Blades.
I'll have to make use of this chance to kill him.
He's dead for sure. It's too bad...
Well, once that woman set her eyes on him, his luck had already run out.
Here I go.
The premise is I barely escaped with my life from captivity.
Before he can say anything, embrace him...
And then kill.
Shichika!
Kyotouryuu: Peony!
Kyotouryuu
Peony
Why?!
What was wrong? The disguise?
No, this isn't even a disguise, my transformation was perfect!
Now that I look, it's Togame?
This guy...
He used that technique without even knowing who I was?!
Huh?
Wait, then I guess you're Koumori?
Guess?
Y-You...
Can't you even recognize who you're facing?!
Well, today's the first time I've ever seen another human besides Nee-chan.
I can't recognize faces that quickly.
What the hell?
This wasn't even a question of disguise!
From the beginning, this guy couldn't even differentiate between people?
That was close...
If it was her, she'd have died.
This is beyond boonies...
This guy's an animal!
She asked for a flashy move, but it turned out kind of boring.
You...
Do you really want to help that woman so badly?
I'm asking if you want to be used by her!
Used?
Didn't you think there was something strange about her story?
Why does the Shogunate suddenly want to collect Shikizaki's swords after all this time?
That was... because they fear a revolt?
That is indeed a reason.
Correct, however...
don't you think it sounds too convenient?
The Shogunate today doesn't hold the same reverence for Shikizaki's swords as Shogun Kyuu did.
They're far more pragmatic.
Ultimately, collecting up the swords this time is just a means for that woman to gain recognition.
Togame the strategian...
It's nothing but a move on her part to gain fame within the army as general director.
I don't really understand that recognition stuff,
but isn't general director of the army already pretty high up?
That woman isn't happy with that level.
She's aiming for the top.
Don't you know what it means to doubt someone?
That young woman will use any dirty tactics she needs to rise to the top of the system.
Raw strength isn't everything in this world.
When we first met, she terrified me.
There is ambition in her eyes.
You can sense her willingness to sacrifice anyone and anything for her goals.
She was perfectly willing to use the Maniwa corps, too.
A fearsome ninja brigade made up of professional assassins, you know? Madness!
And she is merely using you too, Kyotouryuu head!
Is it going to end here?
In this place?
So before you were betrayed, you betrayed others?
That's right.
There's no way I'd follow that woman.
Where do you think her ultimate aim lies?
The right hand of the Shogun!
The current Shogun is getting old.
It won't be long before he retires.
When that happens, I'm sure you can imagine what the natural step will be for the young lieutenant at his side?
Ruling the world...
I threw away my name and my family, all for it to end on this island?
That's not really something to condemn her for...
Well, for someone like you who was used, I'm sure it doesn't feel right.
I don't really care about being used.
Being used and using others is the way of the world.
However, my problem in this case is the reason I was used!
In case you don't know, my head isn't that great, so saying stuff like that doesn't really get through to me.
That woman is the daughter of the leader of the last rebellion, Hida Takahito!
Who can deny the motivations of rebels?
If things had gone better, she'd have been the princess in her castle, ruling over a whole country.
I can already see it.
It's within my grasp!
That woman is aiming for promotion without a care for the means.
She aims to be the right hand man to the current Shogun.
I'm sure you understand what that means.
Father's dreams...
Father's regrets...
She was willing to ask for help from her father's enemies to collect those swords?
It must be clear to you by now what she's planning...
Revenge!
I should have been able to avenge father's death!
It's revenge for having her whole family exterminated!
After all, that girl was watching as her family was killed!
Even if that was the only possibility, to ask the person responsible for my father's death...
Even if not that, to depend on his son...
Even though I'm the son of her enemy...
Maybe I was wrong to rely on Kyotouryuu after all...
She's an insect born from the leader of the rebellion.
I don't want to hear about treachery or cowardice from her!
This is a good body.
Allow me to use it as a reference.
Your strength, musculature, and balance are all a perfect fit.
Though,
you've got the pain from when my shuriken hit your arms and legs, so I have a bit of an advantage.
Just so you know, an attack like that doesn't hurt or even itch anymore.
Seems it, so I guess we're as equal as rock vs rock.
Though my "rock" here is quite strong.
Hey.
Is there anyone else who knows Togame's secret?
There's no way I'd just give away such intriguing information.
So it'll be fine if I just finish you off here, right?
You're suddenly in a fighting mood now that you're facing me?
I am the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
Here I go!
Don't try to act cool!
Come!
I'll finish you with an extremely flashy move!
Ultimate secret technique!
Houfuku Zettou!
Wh-Why?!
Kyotouryuu men don't have any skill whatsoever with a sword!
We're not swordsmen who don't use swords,
we're swordsmen who can't use them!
I'm going to be...
Incidentally, I called it "ultimate secret technique",
but the reason it sounds so generic is because it's an ultimate move I only came up with yesterday!
The opponent take 7 hits from this secret technique, getting ripped apart in the blink of an eye!
Kyouka
Suigetsu
So for now, I'll call it:
Kachou
Fuugetsu
Hyakka
Ryouran
Ryuuryoku
Kakou
Kinjou
Tenka
Kyotouryuu: Shichika Hachiretsu!
Rakka
Rouzeki
Shichika Hachiretsu
What a state I'm in now...
And I'm from a samurai bloodline too!
Before my appearance becomes any more embarrassing, I've got to...
It's not like this rope can't loosen or unravel...
It's my strategies that are infallible and sharp!
There's no way I can lose to this!
So you were here.
So that's the "eye" he was talking about.
To me at least, it sparkles in quite a pretty way.
Well for now, I've got one of them.
Why does he sound like he's just getting started?
Shichika, what about Koumori?!
I finished him off with an awesome move.
You missed it.
That's too bad.
Don't get me wrong, I did it for you.
It's not that I want money or that I've been lured in by Shikizaki's swords.
And I don't have a shred of obligation to help the Shogunate either.
I've just decided I want to help you.
I've fallen for you.
Togame-san.
I wanted to let you know I approve of this decision.
Is that right?
I thought for sure you'd object.
I suppose...
Well to be honest, I don't really care at all about the actual basis of your journey.
If that child has found a reason to leave this island, I approve of it.
He's been on this island for 20 years, training and studying hard,
and it'd simply be too much of a waste if he didn't accomplish anything.
Just so you know, it's not going to be any sort of simple journey.
There's the Maniwa corps and Sabi Hakuhei of course, and on top of that, any other monsters that may lie where we're headed.
Demons and serpents...
I'm bringing along your brother to fight those kinds of battles.
You're quite kind, aren't you?
You truly care about him, don't you.
I have no worries entrusting him to your care.
I'm...
I'm not such a kind woman.
Yasuri Shichika, I have four directives for you.
Four?
Let's hear them.
First I'll repeat what I said earlier - don't break the swords.
Understood.
I will protect the swords.
The second?
Protect me.
Even though our objective is the collection of Shikizaki's swords, if I die it'll all be in vain.
Understood.
I will protect you.
The third?
Protect yourself.
This is not me being considerate of you or anything.
Until we collect all 12 of Shikizaki's swords, dying is unacceptable.
Understood.
I will protect myself.
The fourth?
Protect yourself.
This is me being considerate of you.
Don't die.
The road will be harsh, but you mustn't die.
You can do that right?
I won't let you say you can't.
Hurry up and say you get it!
I completely understand.
So what do we do now?
No need to rush ahead.
When we get to the city, I'll buy you some clothes.
Got it.
I love you.
Yep.
Love me as much as you want.
A man unknown to anyone, a woman who closed her heart.
And so those two began their journey.
With no destination nor destiny, a journey to collect swords.
Demons and serpents await them.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening...
ends here.
Though...
That child is so weak... will they be okay?
tadayou namini yorisou hana wa
漂う波に寄り添う華は
The flowers caressed by the drifting waves
amari ni mo moroku chirisaku
余りにも脆く散り咲く
are so fragile and small
utakata no ryouran monogatari
泡沫の繚乱物語
An ephemeral abundant fairy tale
tasogare no yoitsuki ni benisome no geka ga saki
黄昏の宵月に紅染めの月華が咲き
At dusk, the early moon, red dyed moonlight blooming
inochi no tomo no tamashii
命のともの魂
Life along with soul
hagane no karada ni
鋼の身体に
On a steel body
chikai wo haotte
誓いを羽織って
put on a vow
me ni sasu hana wo
目に刺す華を
The flower that pierces the eye
mamorita mou karete nao
守りたもう　桔れて尚
Protected, withered, and still...
garasu no bin ni toraware saita
硝子の瓶に囚われ咲いた
Blooming while imprisoned in a glass bottle
ichirin no seisanna kako wo tsuyuni tokashite
一輪の凄惨な過去を露に溶かして
A single flower, melting a ghostly past into the dew
misogi no mizu ni sasowareshi chou no
禊の水に誘われし蝶の
The butterflies drawn to the the water of purification
egaku hakanaki zankoku no
描く儚き残酷の
describe a fleeting, cruel
hakuchuu no yumemi monogatari
白昼の夢見物語
daydream fairy tale
This is the army general director in support of critical tasks,
under direct control of Yanari Shogun of the Owari Shogunate,
Togame the strategian here.
Everything is going according to plan.
You doubt me?
I also calculated you'd think that.
Now then,
it's time for my peerless, uplifting, solemn story of justice to begin, but...
About that Kyotouryuu man,
Yasuri Shichika...
How far will he serve as my blade?
Zantou
Namakura
Next episode: Katanagatari - Zantou Namakura
Cheerio!