Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Have any of your dear friends ever said
"Please!" asking you to do something?
When you see your good
friend having a hard time,
you can't just let it be, right?
I was able to reach this point
because many people helped me a lot.
Rosetta, please don't look so sad.
It'll be all right.
Don't worry. Let me handle this.
It's my turn to help you
this time! Okay? Okay? Okay?
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa
aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
"Another Amazing Newcomer."
I hate it! I really hate
it! Please do it now!
"Now" is easy for you to say, but I cannot...
I can't stand it another second!
Don't be so irritated.
May, why don't you give this a try too?
You're from China, so I bet you
already know this! Cat's paws martial arts!
It will calm your feelings, meow.
I don't know that phony martial art.
Phony?
I cannot just ignore what you just said!
Never mind that...
Never mind that?! Hold on!
If what you said is true,
what about that correspondence class
--How should I know?
--I took all week?
You're so irresponsible!
I have nothing to do with that!
I can't believe this! Oh, I'm in shock!
--Anyway, do something about this right now!
--Now, now, now, now, now...
--I do not want to live in the
room right underneath Sora's!
--Both of you!
The person who will be the top star someday
should not live in the room underneath Sora's!
So change my room right now!
--Unbelievable.
--Now! Now now now!
I'm the one who's supposed to unite
Kaleido Stage now that Miss Layla's gone.
Miss Layla is Miss Layla.
She's right.
Overdoing it doesn't do you any good.
Oh, I know!
Let's have a welcoming party!
A welcoming party?
Yes! A welcoming party for the newcomers!
If we invite Mr. Leon and May and have fun,
I'm sure we can be more friendly!
I wonder if it'll be fun...
It's difficult to say.
It will be all right!
Good, I'll talk to Miss Sarah later too.
How can she come up with holding
a welcoming party after what May said?
If I want to be a gag character,
being someone like her could be a big help.
You really want to be a gag character?
Of course!
Of course, I think a cake is a must!
What? A break-in?
It sounds like the shower's running.
What kind of robber takes a shower?
Fool!
It was so sudden.
I missed my chance.
What?
Oh... She's coming out!
I'm not sure what is going on,
--but in the meantime...
--Hey, what are you doing?
Leggo! I wanna see!
What?!
Rosetta!
Oh, Sora. Welcome back.
I'm home...
I borrowed your shirt.
What are you doing?
Oh, no. Nothing.
Or rather, what are you doing here, Rosetta?
Help me, Sora!
What?
So you're being chased by your agent?
I told my agent I wanted
to join Kaleido Stage.
What?
But my agent is such a blockhead,
she wouldn't listen to me at all.
You want to join Kaleido Stage?
Yes. After I saw you and Miss Layla
perform the legendary great maneuver,
I was so moved by it.
And I wished I could have that
kind of amazing applause too, one day.
So...
I don't want to go back to my agent anymore.
So, please, help me.
I'm willing to do anything I can to help
you since you helped me so much, but...
If my agent finds me, she will punish me.
What? What kind of punishment?
That is...
I hope she's not going to give
you ten lashes or anything like that.
Right, right! Not just ten!
More like a thousand!
A thous--
A thousand lashes?
Well...
Anyway, you're the only
person I can depend on right now.
Okay.
I'm glad.
I'll do anything! Cleaning or laundry.
So please don't hesitate to ask me anything!
Okay.
Clear on the right.
Clear on the left.
Clear in the fro--
Oh...
So you were able to
switch to the room over there.
I bet if I hold a welcoming
party, we can get along well.
We can! We can.
We can...
Just looking at her like this,
she doesn't seem like a
diabolo prodigy girl at all.
I have to make sure to protect her.
The appearance of stars that
will influence Sora's Sagittarius...
There are so many, they almost eclipse
Sagittarius and its dreams of the future.
It looks like the path to be a real
Kaleido Star will be a tough one.
Huh? Huh?!
Huh?!
--May, Good Morn--
--Miracle elevator, shut, shut, shut!
Wow, Sora!
That's enough for two people.
Oh, well. I thought... I'm kinda
in the mood to eat a lot today.
Triple Food Get!
Well... I'll eat in my room today.
Good idea...
Bye!
Bye...
Oh, I remember.
Everyone, I'm going to
hold a welcoming party tonight!
So, please look forward to it!
May, you come too.
--She said a welcoming party.
--So, please come!
--I can't wait.
Kaleido Star...
Amazing, amazing...
A-mazing.
Welcome back, Sora.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's eat--
uh...
Oh, I tried to wash them.
Okay!
As long as you didn't hurt yourself...
I was trying to clean the place...
Oh... Thanks.
I was trying to replace the light bulb...
I know...
I'm sorry.
Hey, Sora.
Hey! Over here!
Can you rescue me?
I wasn't paying attention,
and I got sucked in.
I'm so embarrassed.
So, what are you gonna do?
Okay! Let's eat!
Hey, Sora,
how did it feel when you were
doing the legendary great maneuver?
How did it feel?
Yes.
Weren't you scared?
No, not at all.
During practice, I thought about it a lot,
and I got anxious sometimes...
But I wasn't scared,
because I was with Miss Layla.
Well, Sora...
I'm also going to try out for the trapeze.
What?! Are you serious, Rosetta?
Yes!
Wait... I don't think we can
make changes like that now...
If you increase my stage time, the
quality of the performance will improve.
Sora's your partner, and you're trying to...
I'm not saying you should eliminate her turn.
But her appearance will be
less than five minutes like this...
I'm saying that she's
worth only that much now.
If she doesn't like it, she can leave.
Leon's suggestion is reasonable.
Do what he says.
Yes.
But in exchange, don't leave in
the middle of the performance again.
I make no promises.
Well, I'm leaving.
Okay. Good luck.
Please don't take a bath
while I'm gone. Okay?
Okay.
That was uncalled for!
Kaleido Stage...
I can't believe this.
Sorry, Sora.
There was no other way.
Most of the other ensembles
are also shortened.
It's practically a one-man show for Leon!
These are Mr. Leon's instructions, right?
Yes.
I understand how everyone feels about this,
but Kaleido Stage needs Mr. Leon right now.
I understand.
Well, everyone, let's change the mood,
and do our best to make the show exciting!
Yeah!
You're right!
We'll do our best on stage again today.
There's only one thing I ask from all of you.
Do not get in my way.
That's all.
Rosetta, you say?
No, I have no knowledge of her coming here.
All right.
If you hear something, please contact me.
Certainly.
By the way,
don't you think Sora's
performance is a little flat lately?
So, you noticed that too?
I'm Sora's number one fan, after all!
I know losing Layla means a lot to her.
I hope the guy who joined this
time can be a good partner for Sora.
By any chance, can you see me?
My name is Fool.
I'm the spirit of the stage.
Those who can see me are
the chosen ones for the stage.
Since I already found those who were able
to perform the legendary great maneuver,
my new purpose is to find
someone who can be a real star.
Oh... I wish I could try the swing soon.
So she can't see me.
Since we just have a
daytime performance today,
why don't we go to see the Boss
together after the performance?
Okay.
I wonder if I should go see
Sora's performance for a little bit.
Practice rooms...
I wonder what kind of practice they're doing.
You're wonderful.
You are certainly impressive, May Wong.
Of course.
You're so confident.
Instructor, please let me
appear on the real stage soon.
What?
To be frank with you, my abilities
are better than Sora Naegino's!
I think you should hurry up
and pull her from the stage,
and make me the leading star.
I think everyone should be
honest and admit the truth.
I feel sorry for Mr. Leon that he
has such an amateur as his partner.
Kaleido Stage doesn't need
Sora Naegino. Don't you agree?
Why?!
What?
Why are you talking about Sora like that?
Who are you?
You don't even know Sora's abilities.
I know her abilities.
Her abilities are no match for mine.
Sora is amazing!
How can someone like you
know anything about Sora?
Oh my! Aren't you Rosetta?
--Oh, shoot!
--Rosetta?
The diabolo star?
Oh, I didn't know.
You may be a diabolo genius,
but this is a Kaleido Stage matter!
It's got nothing to do with you!
Rosetta?!
Oh, there you are!
Hey! Your agent's looking for you!
If there's a reason why you're
here, you should talk to her!
You can't be my partner the way you are now.
I'll reduce your part further tomorrow.
Yes.
Something like this is not Kaleido Stage.
I wonder if we can create
performances with this man in the future.
Mr. Leon looked so great.
I think I'll come back here again tomorrow.
She just entered the Kaleido Stage.
That's right.
Thank you.
I'm sorry that Rosetta has imposed on you.
Not at all.
But I wonder why
Rosetta came to Kaleido Stage.
Well, she...
Rosetta?!
Rosetta!
Hey, wait, Rosetta!
Rosetta?!
Oh, Sora.
Rosetta just ran through here!
This way?
Rosetta!
The agent who whips her a thousand times?!
Where'd she go?
This way!
Rosetta!
Rosetta, get down here!
No. Go away!
That's enough!
Please wait!
Please listen to Rosetta's story!
Rosetta wants to join Kaleido Stage!
What?!
I'll cancel the contract with my agent!
I'll work for you for a newcomer's fees!
So, what do you say, Kalos?
We'll take her.
I won't let you have your own way!
But I think we should take
Rosetta's feelings into consideration.
You still can't make it on your own!
I'm not a kid anymore, Mama!
Mama?
Can't you listen to what I say?
Please understand, Mama.
This place is very special to me!
When I thought that perfecting the
performance was the most important thing,
they taught me the performance was
something we create with the audience.
I was able to get back the feelings
I had when I started doing diabolo.
And that's not all!
After I saw Sora and Miss Layla
perform the legendary great maneuver,
the door which had been
closed inside of me finally opened.
I wished I could perform an
amazing show like that too.
That's all I can think about every day,
and I can't stay still!
Rosetta...
For the first time,
I aspired to be like somebody.
I want to appear on stage with Sora!
I can even do the trapeze!
What?!
Rosetta!
Sora...
You're so reckless, Rosetta.
I'm sorry.
We're going back.
Okay.
Rosetta... she's laughing.
There!
Sora, thank you.
Rosetta...
What I'm most afraid of, Rosetta...
Is that you may turn into
a diabolo machine again.
You're very hard on yourself.
To be certain, I'm the one who trained
you so hard when you were little,
but...
After you became the youngest
champion on record in the world,
you strove for greater perfection,
and you tended to drive
yourself into corners.
Mama...
But it's tough to see you like that.
I'm the one who raised you like that...
but if you put yourself in
a tough environment again,
I'm certain you will...
Mama...
It's true, you were scary when
I was little, and you were strict.
But I'm very grateful
that you taught me diabolo.
Don't worry, Mama.
I won't be a machine anymore.
I'm sure she'll be mortified and she'll cry.
She'll have to go through
all kinds of things,
and she won't be able to smile all the time,
but I don't think she'll
have time to be a machine.
You're right.
This is the place that let
you regain your smile, after all.
Mr. Kalos.
May I ask you to take care of Rosetta?
Of course.
But, when she does diabolo performances,
I expect you to pay the
fees we already agreed on.
What?! Oh...
So, I can stay here. Right?
Yes, you can.
We did it!
I have some business with
other artists, so I'll be leaving now.
Call me when you have a problem.
Mama...
I love you, Mama!
They're such a nice mother and daughter.
Welcome to Kaleido Stage!
Nice to meet you.
May and Leon didn't show up.
Huh? Where is Sora?
She was here a second ago.
She left here with a piece of cake.
Who cares about the welcoming party?!
Uh, I thought it would be nice if you
could at least have a piece of cake with us.
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck*
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (Here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
It doesn't matter which one.
Just satisfy me.
And so, Mia's idea for the
new performance is "Dracula."
It's mysterious, but it's
also a passionate love story.
But May made a big fuss again,
saying that she should be Leon's partner.
The deadline is a day away.
For Miss Layla who entrusted me
with her dream and for everybody else,
I will never be defeated! Never! Never!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Passionate Rival."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...