Messages deleted.
Onii-chan...
Eh?
Hirono-kun! Are you there?
Hirono-kun...!
Ah, Miyamura-senpai. What do you want?
W-What, you say?
Where is Hirono-kun?
Onii-chan is sleeping right now. Can you keep it down?
Let me see him at once! There's something important I need to tell him. Let me see Hirono-kun!
You aren't allowed in.
I won't allow you in.
I will always be with Onii-chan after all.
It's over.
Ah! Hello, Renji-kun.
A-Ah. Hello.
What's for lunch today?
Ah.
I'm a bit hungry.
Delicious. I always enjoy Renji-kun's bento.
What score would you give it today?
There's no need to score it. It was very good.
Eh? Ah, really?
Next time, can you teach me how to cook?
Teach you?
Right now, Onee-chan is learning to cook, so I want to be able to cook something as well.
Is that so? Well, why don't we try something simple for starters?
Yes!
The number you have dialed is in an area without service and cannot be connected-
Thanks for waiting.
So, what did they say?
Umm, it's a medial something something collateral something something injury.
That's a lot of "somethings".
That's because of how the name is written.
You should at least remember the name of the injury.
"In order to relieve the pain, try not to move too much and apply plenty of ice."
Is that so? I guess you won't be able to play basketball for a while then.
Yeah.
Here.
Thank you.
Onii-chan, what about practice?
The same as always, though I really should rest instead.
It probably would be a good idea to slow down a bit.
Eh?
After all, you have to rest your leg as well.
Looks like I'll keep you company for a bit then.
Okay.
"The girl spent a lot of time looking at the painting."
"Looking at the boy in the painting gave her a strange feeling."
"I want to marry him.' For some reason or another she thought about that."
"In a book, she found out a lot about marriage."
"Inside, it was written that it was important how people lived their lives."
"The girl was interested in how the ideals of marriage worked and carefully studied it."
Renji-kun, have you thought about what career to go into?
Eh?
There's the career survey to fill out after all.
Yeah, at the moment I haven't really decided.
Renji-kun, you'd be great if you became a novelist.
Your stories are so interesting.
It's tough being a novelist though. Perhaps it just won't work.
Why is that?
Whenever I read what you write, Chihiro, I can't seem to come up with anything better.
Guess I just don't have the right talent for it.
No, that isn't true!
Eh?
It isn't talent that is important, but the ability to try your best.
That's what you taught me, Renji-kun.
Thanks to you, I'll soon be able to finish my novel even though I always believed that it was impossible and wanted to give up...
Chihiro...
Even though I can't remember anything after thirteen hours...
and even though what happened when I was twelve keeps coming back to me...
you showed me there was always a way to make it, Renji-kun!
So please do not ever give up.
As long as you have a dream, please do your best and don't give up.
Okay.
It's still there.
Not that way.
Eh?
This part was like this.
Yeah, you're right.
It's strange...
Why am I so depressed?
I just want things back the way they used to be.
To be able to live freely no matter where I am.
This is neither a place to return to nor a place to come to.
Leave me alone.
To be trapped in the ruins of the past isn't a good thing to do.
Where should I go?
You know where that warmth is.
As long as you embrace these wonderful memories, you'll never choose the wrong path to take.
Such a faraway memory I can't recall.
But you are starting to remember, aren't you?
Maybe it would've been better if we never met.
If we didn't meet, I wouldn't have tried to remember this warmth.
Is the girl Chihiro doing better?
Yes, little by little. Just recently, her memory has started to recover.
That isn't possible.
But...
A miracle happening is an unrelated matter.
Nevertheless, there is no possibility that such a thing has happened.
What we have is what is expected, unexpected, and what one has done. That is all.
Have you remembered what I have told you?
Eh?
No, it's probably too late already.
The number you have dialed is in an area without service and-
That Miyako...
Class 2-B's Hirono Hiro-kun...
Class 2-D's Miyamura Miyako-san...
After school, please come to the guidance counselor's office.
Uhh...
What was that about, Onii-chan?
"What are you going to do about the career survey?" they said.
The same with Miyamura-senpai?
She ditched.
I see. Wouldn't it be better to concentrate less on work and more on your studies after all?
Yeah. And maybe I should do some work on the rehabilitation.
That's right! After this is over with, why don't we go out somewhere? I-
Huh?
Hello, this is Shindou Nagi.
Yes. I'm doing what I can about it.
The run is finished?
Hmm...
Okay. I'll give it a go.
Sometime this week, I'll bring over a draft copy.
Okay, talk to you later.
From work?
The run was finished and they want something else to be serialized.
Are you going to do it?
Yeah, it is a chance after all.
Why? You just said earlier you were going to take a break...
If I said no, there wouldn't be another opportunity.
For a newcomer like me, if any kind of chance comes along, I have to take a stab at it.
Really? Well, so you'll do whatever you want?
Where are you going?
Club activities. If I don't move around my body is going to get weak.
Idiot! Didn't you say you were going to rest?
Onii-chan, even though you aren't getting better, you aren't going to stop either, right?
If you really injure your leg, you won't be able to play basketball anymore!
Well if it gets worse, you won't be able to write manga anymore, Onii-chan!
If I don't do this, some other artist is going to steal my chance!
Don't you think I understand that?!
In any case, you can't possibly do anything with that injury!
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Was I asleep?
Huh?
How much time has passed?
About how long was I asleep?!
Umm, it was about five minutes, I think.
I... see.
Maybe you just stopped because you were tired?
No I wasn't. I'm not tired at all!
Really? Things are okay then I guess.
Yes, I'm fine.
Seriously, what an idiot. Jumping back into work even when he is lacking attendance, what is he thinking?
Even if you request for him to plan in advance, it's useless.
Kei-chan, why did you take up basketball?
I've always liked it.
To be able to blow past the operation and set up for the shot is a real rush!
That's the same as me.
When you take a shot at the right time and place that touches your heart, it gives you a great feeling.
Oh?
It's probably the same for Hirono too.
He's always trying to move ahead, so his path is one that's more difficult than ours you might say.
But he's still an idiot.
You really are oblivious, aren't you?
What do you mean by that?
Mmm...never mind.
Stopping in the middle like that is a cheap shot.
You see, when trying to film a wild animal in their natural habitat,
you can't interfere with what they are doing.
Otherwise, you cannot get footage in its natural state.
And what do you mean by that?
If I cut into the conversation, it'll just be interference.
Don't equate people with the behavior of animals!
Geez, don't give me that know-it-all talk, okay.
I understand though.
With the camera's viewfinder, I can see everything.
Hmm?
Chihiro.
Chihiro!
What's wrong?
I was just thinking about something.
In the middle of a meal?
I'm sorry.
11:50. I arrived at the library.
Four minutes later, Renji-kun showed up.
We ate lunch together.
The bento consisted of fried halibut, Japanese-style salad and for dessert, strawberry jelly.
It was delicious. I always enjoy Renji-kun's bento.
"What score would you give it today?"
"There's no need to score it. It was very good."
"Next time, can you teach me how to cook?"
"Well, why don't we try something simple for starters?"
Three hours to go.
It's okay, I still remember.
What are you doing?
Working on your studies this late at night?
Didn't you already do your reading before you went to bed?
Yes, everything except the summary.
Summary?
The diary I keep is only a summary. With the things that I had fun with, I write that "I had fun".
This way, how I had fun or what feelings I experienced won't all disappear.
Is that why you are writing down your memories?
While reading this, I can remember every detail.
This way I will be able to remember the events of the previous thirteen hours.
This way I will remember what happened when I met with Renji-kun this afternoon and everything up until now.
If you do that, you'll be writing until morning.
I know.
And you will continue?
I don't want the time I spent with Renji-kun to disappear.
I am an ordinary girl after all.
Is that it? There isn't much time after all.
What are you doing?!
It's pointless to do this!
It isn't pointless!
There's no reason to continue! Don't be ridiculous.
There is a reason to continue!
Listen to me, this won't help you!
Give it back! Give it back, I beg you! Give it back!
Inside of it... Inside of it my Renji-kun is there!
I won't forget this...
That just now... I will never forget it!
I understand.
I'm sorry for that disobedience.
Don't overdo it.
What was it like the first time we met?
Eh?
I want to paint this important memory in my heart again.
Chihiro...
We were gazing at the sky I think.
Chihiro, you looked deeply into the sky that day. It was a mysterious feeling.
The sky?
That day... was definitely like that.
But looking ahead towards the future is a lot more fun.
Umm...
What is it?
Renji-kun, I... umm...
If it's all right with you...
Could we hold hands?
Eh?
It's okay if it isn't possible.
It's not that it's the end if we don't. I was just thinking that I wanted to try it out...
It isn't... possible, is it?
Okay.
Let's hold hands.
Yes!
Chihiro! What's wrong?!
Chihiro!
"The next day, the girl married. She wore a dress she found in the castle."
"In her head, to the words, 'Will you accept the vow of matrimony?' she answered yes."
"Then, she touched lips with the man in the painting. It was oily."
"She then took some flowers to use as a bouquet and tossed it."
"A feast was properly prepared. It was a party to some degree."
"But due to the tightness of the dress around her waist, there was much that was leftover."
"The girl took the bouquet, dress, and the leftover food and tossed it over a cliff like garbage and slept."
"Thus the wedding ended."
It's you.
Umm...
Come in.
Eh?
You heard me, didn't you? Come in.
Is Chihiro... all right?
It was a lot of strain, lack of sleep and emotional stress.
All these factors that were built up inside her disappeared after she was at ease.
No matter how many times I tried, she wouldn't wake up.
Since the time limit has passed, I let her sleep.
Time limit?
Chihiro?
Onii-san... who are you?
Huh? Why am I...?
Huh?
Why? Why do I look older?
What is wrong with my eye?!
Chihiro...
Onee-chan? Where is Kei-oneechan?
Where is Hiro-oniichan? What happened to me?!
Calm down, Chihiro! You've already-
Why... Why... What has happened to me?
Ah, wait!
Chihiro, do you remember me?
Himura-oniichan.
It's good that you remember.
Do you understand now?
This is Chihiro.
She will always be a twelve-year-old who can't remember anything past thirteen hours of time.
Forever.
Yes, this is Hirono.
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Miyako?
Bingo.
Miyako...
What, you actually remembered me?
What's going on? You got me all worried when I couldn't get a hold of you.
Turn on your cell phone!
I haven't disappeared.
Huh?
I haven't disappeared yet.
To the ones who don't know pain, it is a more painful tragedy.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Forget Me Not.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?