Thank you so much!
Because of you, we've found happiness!
True happiness!
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
You know those two?
Got nothing to do with those fools
Palm-top Tiger of Happiness
committing public indecency, and so early, too.
Tiger!
What's with them?
A-Aisaka-san...
What's wrong with you people!?
Why'd you move, Tiger?
I won't say to lariat us or anything,
but maybe you could just kick us,
or grind your heel on us.
Ew, nasty!
Get away from me!
All of you!
What's going on?
I find it hard to believe
in jinxes like this one.
What!?
See, you just go like this.
What are you doing, Dumb-chi!?
Ami-chan's majestic features...
Uncensored...
See? The rumor's a sham!
Look at how miserable I am!
Hey!
Don't use my skirt to
wipe your finger!
But there was snot all over it.
How are you going to make
up for contaminating me?
You're the one who stuck it up my nose!
- What's this rumor?
- Huh? Oh.
So, our wrestling show drew
in a huge crowd, right?
The battle spilled outside the ring once,
and some were hit by Tiger's lariat.
Others, a headbutt.
Whatever the contact, anyone who
Tiger touched became happy.
Happy?
Yep.
Like girls popping up to confess their love...
Inheritances from grandfathers
they never knew...
An outburst of happy ooh-la-la!
Every wish can be granted!
That's the basic gist behind the so-called
Legend of the Palm-top Tiger of Happiness.
I see.
So that's why.
What the hell!?
Making up a story about me...
What's the problem, Tiger?
It only takes a second...
Don't act like we're friends!
I won't be letting any of you touch me!
Good morning-morn!
Why are you all standing out here?
Minorin!
Minorin's the only one allowed to touch me!
Aww, there, there.
That's a good girl. Yes, good girl.
Touching Taiga will make you happy, huh?
On that day...
The day of the Culture Festival,
Taiga was anything but happy...
If Taiga helped other people
find happiness that day...
That'd be...
What is it?
Give me my lunch.
Oh, yeah.
- Really ironic...
- Isn't it ironic for Takasu-kun?
Considering he's the closest
person to Aisaka-san.
She sure looked like she enjoyed
dancing with Maruo.
He's always with the tiger, and touching
her is supposed to bring happiness,
but he lost her to Maruo at
the Culture Festival in a flash.
Wh-What the...?
What's with the weird rumors?
You poor thing...
Yes, Kitamura-kun took me from you.
Hey, now.
Shouldn't we squash all these rumors?
Sure, it's a little upsetting
to be called a dog's ex.
I mean, I'm human.
But it sounds like I was the
one who dumped you.
And then, Kitamura-kun and I...
Guess I was worried over nothing.
Oh, thanks.
I'm going back to my seat!
That single woman's going
to show up with that...
single look on her face and
start her single homeroom!
S-Single look...
Takasu-kun, your lunch looks awesome!
Are those spring rolls?
Y-Yeah...
I wrapped leftover salad in rice paper.
Ooh! Way to go!
You're always amazing, but this
rice is better than ever!
Hey, everyone's gunnin' for you, Taiga.
Seriously. I can't even eat a meal in peace...
That's pretty hard to believe.
Mind if I join you?
Oh.
Aisaka, don't you worry one
bit about those rumors.
Huh? Wh-Which rumors?
Oh, nothing. Never mind...
What matters is that the Culture
Festival was a real blast.
For real!
We won the class exhibit, the pageant,
and even Mr. Lucky Man!
I'm so proud!
Yep, and it was all thanks to Aisaka.
That's not...
Taiga?
H-Hey...
H-Here! Drink this!
N-No way!
Huh? But...
I only drink juice!
Orange juice...
Is this really the time to be picky?
Jeez... Every single time...
At least she's back to normal, I guess?
Uh-huh, I know.
But I have a test coming up.
Uh-huh.
Just give me a little more time.
Got it.
I'll call later.
Till then.
Yo.
What was that call about?
What's this? You want to know my secret?
I don't really care.
Uh, where's the orange juice?
Having juice for lunch?
You're such a child.
It isn't for me. It's for Taiga.
She refused to drink milk coffee.
Wh—!?
H-Hey!
See ya.
What am I supposed to do...
with this?
No running in the halls!
- Student Council
Calcium hypochlorite kick!
Took you long enough!
I was forced to drink from
the water fountain!
How're you gonna make it up to me!?
Hell if I know!
Why did you suddenly—
H-Hey, you okay?
U-Uh... I-I'm sorry!
Th-That wasn't on purpose!
I have a favor to ask of you, Aisaka-senpai.
So I thought I'd grab some juice
as a reason to approach—
You again?
You've been sneaking around me for a while.
A while?
Oh, is this related to that nonsense
about touching you?
Y-Yes!
Because, there's this girl I like,
and I want things to go well.
I'll help you go, all right.
To the afterlife.
Man...
Have to be a survivor if you wanna be happy.
Come on, let's go!
Lunch break's almost over!
Huh? Where are we going?
I heard they posted pictures
from the Culture Festival.
What about lunch?
I'm done! Move it!
But I haven't eaten!
Walk, boy!
Come to think of it, you're
touching me all the time.
More or less.
Huh? Don't make it sound dirty!
Yeah...
Taiga's touching me all the time.
So shouldn't I be the happiest
person in the world?
It's not fair.
She gets to be happy all by herself.
133.
Don't get it wrong.
Sh-Shut up.
But yeah, it's a really nice picture.
That one, and that one, and that one...
- and that one, and that one!
- Minorin!
Listen up, Taiga.
Amin in 200 is a must-see.
The keyword...is underboob.
You disgust me, you sick mutt.
L-Lost myself for a second there...
Your libido passes the "eye-rolling" stage
and reaches "stab you to death" sometimes.
That's one hell of a jump.
If you're so interested in Dumb-chi's
underboob, I might as well tell you.
She has six breasts!
I saw them!
Bull.
I'm starting to feel dirty just
standing next to you.
Minorin, I'm gonna check out the other side.
Damn Taiga...
The time is upon us, Takasu-kun!
The duel of fate!
Bam!
I will sacrifice 90 yen to
summon 9 pictures!
And then, Reverse Card Open!
Activate Quick-Play Spell Card,
Newly Spotted!
93, a shot of the softball team that just
caught my eye, is summoned for 10 yen!
End phase!
Now it's your turn!
What? Turn...?
Please don't play dumb.
I obviously mean we should show
each other the pictures we bought.
Oh, that's what you meant?
- You'll attack with our class photo, right?
- She makes no sense to me sometimes...
Show me what you've got!
Oh, 85.
- Uh, that's just...
- 85 is...it's...where...?
Guess I should buy this one too.
For a keepsake.
R-Right...
A keepsake...
What's wrong with you?
You only bought pictures
of Sudo from class B?
Shut up! Don't look!
Buying pictures of the girl you like...
So typical.
- What's that? You're one to talk!
- Then we should try that place next time.
Making such a fuss over a few pictures...
They're such children.
Amin...
I get my picture taken for a living,
and they're sold all over Japan.
It doesn't matter who has my picture...
Let alone why they have it.
In the end, it's just a picture.
Uh-huh, just a picture...
You're right.
It's just a picture.
Uh-huh.
Golly gee, a lecture by Professor Amin!
You're so mature!
Up for anything on the way home?
Sure. Mind if we drop by the station today?
Fine with me. Any particular reason?
The other day, I saw this rad...
The single look...
Single possessions...
A single palm reading...
Oh, there goes my luck with money...
Teach.
Got business with this single
backside, Kawashima-san?
I've been meaning to ask all morning.
Your cardigan was in this year's
Winter Collection, wasn't it?
O-Oh, you noticed?
I can tell!
You always have impeccable style.
So very adult.
It's wonderful!
I'm sure the fashion conscious will recognize
your womanly charms, Miss Yuri-chan.
Kawashima-san, you're such a...
Such a nice girl...!
Such an adult, you mean.
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
Let's stop by the supermarket
on the way home.
Yeah, I'm in the mood for...
Oh! Meat?
Some kind of fatty meat?
You always ask for meat.
So? I help pay for the food, don't I?
You should eat a balanced diet...
You realize that buying a picture of
you holding hands with Minorin...
doesn't mean you get to act
all high and mighty, right?
What!? You were watching!?
I had a hunch you'd buy it.
And I was right.
Y-You bought pictures, too!
Sure.
Not that I need them.
Since I'm his girlfriend.
Ow...
Him again...
Ah, s-so sorry! I...
You again?
A-And now you're trying to
p-peek up my sk-skirt...
- I wasn't, I swear!
- Hey! Come back here!
She's completely back to the way
she was before the festival.
Even after everything that happened...
Or maybe because of it...
President.
We've finished tallying the
Culture Festival expenses.
Oh, let me take a look.
S-Someone's attacking Tomiie-kun!
What's her deal?
Oh, it's probably the Legend of the
Palm-top Tiger of Happiness.
Your wishes will be granted if you're
touched by Aisaka Taiga.
So the rumor goes, anyway.
So Tomiie's giving it a go?
Doesn't matter if it's a rumor or a lie.
I can understand the urge
to rely on superstition.
I'm surprised to hear you say that.
Really?
U-Uh...
President...
Kitamura.
We need to talk.
Aw, I didn't get to touch the tiger.
I'm so jealous of everyone she's touched.
And she even gets to be happy with Maruo.
They only danced together!
The tiger couldn't possibly want Maruo!
Why are you getting so worked up?
Like I said...
It's just plain stupid to believe in that jinx.
Well sure, you have it easy.
It'd be simple for you to make your
romantic dreams come true.
Yep, you're mature, with a body to die for.
There isn't a man alive who wouldn't
succumb to your charms.
There you go again...
Ami-chan?
Pork Loin
Domestic Beef - Steak
1,800 yen each?
You're really splurging.
Kawashima?
I know you're just deep in thought and all...
But you've attracted the attention
of the undercover security.
How about a smile as you shop?
R-Right...
But, look.
I could buy four packs of
pork for the same price.
If you're so worried about the price, can't
you just ask Aisaka-san to touch you?
You'll get an inheritance from a grandfather
you never knew you had, right?
I mean, you become happy when
Taiga touches you, right?
That rumor has zero credibility.
But if we pretend it's true, how's Taiga
supposed to find her own happiness?
She's happy enough as-is.
You should go with quantity over quality.
She won't complain so long as she's stuffed.
True enough.
Pork it is!
Using reusable bags reduces CO2
and helps to save the environment!!
Oh, I don't need a bag.
Wow, Takasu-kun.
You've accumulated a lot of points.
You're such a housewife.
Bite me.
Oh, hang on.
Here, take this.
You can have it.
I only have three mouths to feed,
so one or two will be plenty.
There's no point in taking
this when I don't cook.
Go on, eat some pork.
You looked a little pale today.
Probably a vitamin B2 deficiency.
You've been acting subdued
since this morning.
Remember when I bumped into
you by the vending machines?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You sound like my grandma.
I can live with that.
You're probably living off snacks.
Seriously, you're such a child.
Don't forget to cook it with ginger.
Ginger helps to warm the body.
Later.
A child, huh?
Man, stupid mongrel...
He's got balls to ditch his master
and go home by himself.
Ki-Kita-Kitamu—
Aisaka...
What are you...doing?
Oh...
Nothing at all...
The Palm-top Tiger of Happiness...
Sorry...
Man, what am I doing?
You okay?
Did you lose your wallet or something?
Was that spiteful student council
president being mean to you?
No, not at all.
It's nothing.
Um, y-you can go ahead and touch me!
I don't know if it'll do anything...
But you can touch me
as much as you want!
Touch me lots and lots!
Oh, man! Wh-What am I saying?
Aisaka.
Sorry, it's okay.
Thanks.
Tomiie-kun, are you really okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Really?
Are you really sure?
Yeah, Sakura-chan.
I'm fine now.
Hey, welcome home.
Jeez! Why did you go home without me?
Hey, Ryuji.
You made more than usual.
Is today special?
Uh, well...
Um...oh! I didn't eat lunch,
so I'm really hungry.
Oh, it smells great.
This was in your repertoire?
Yeah, western-style stewed pork.
The key's the shinshu miso
I added to the sauce.
I can't be outdone by that restaurant
your old man took me to.
A-And once the gratin's finished...
Are you an idiot?
I really don't care anymore...
Forget it.
Get to work!
Yeah, yeah.
The Legend of the Palm-top
Tiger of Happiness, huh?
Honestly, it's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
- Pat, pat, pat, pat...
- Y-Ya-chan?
Yay, I feel happy already!
A little fast, no?
You see...
When I get to pat Taiga-chan's head,
and eat dinner with my whole family,
I'm the happiest person in the world.
Family?
That's right!
You're a member of our family!
Stop! Ya-chan, that hurts!
The Palm-top Tiger can grant
any wish if you touch her...
If that really worked...
Uh-huh.
So, Mom...
I'm planning on staying here.
Uh-huh, I've made new friends.
So...
It's okay.
I'm acting responsibly.
Uh-huh, people tell me how adult I am.
What would I wish for?
I still don't know what form
my wish would take...
And I can't say that I want to know...
Ryu-chan gets the pat treatment too.
I'll help. Here.
Gross! Don't use your feet!
banira sorutode
Add vanilla salt.
BURNING LOVE
Burning love.
amai dakenara
If it's too sweet,
soruto kakemashou
we can add some salt.
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I tell you all these things because
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
modokashi sugiru
This is so frustrating.
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
But a love that's purely sweet
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
shiroto iwaretara
If you say white,
kurodatte icchau
say black.
sunaoni narenai
A little imp
amanojaku
who can't be honest to herself.
sukito iwaretara
If you say love,
daikirai datte
I say hate.
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
soruto kakeru youni
to sweet vanilla...
I quit, quit, quit, quit, quit,
quit, quit, quit, quit, quit!
Wow!
Kitamura-kun's so great!
He said it ten times without
biting his tongue!
So, what are you quitting?
Everything!
I quit everything!