Who's the next target?
Frank Clard. I was finally able to locate him.
Are you gonna use those mysterious guys again?
I believe we've already decided to send them in.
You're gonna put on a big show, right?
It's necessary to raise awareness of our existence.
Their power becomes hell fire and burns hell to the ground.
We will build our world from the ashes.
You injured?
Just a scratch.
I...
kill.
In order to live...
I kill!
Awakening
I'm gonna be killed!
I have to escape or I'm gonna be killed.
I can't escape from those black eyes.
What should I do?
If I can't escape, I have to kill.
It's kill or be killed!
Wh-Where am I?
What's this? What am I doing here?
Wh-who am I? I don't... remember my name.
What was I...
Japanese?
A traveling bag...
This is... me...
I'm a Japanese traveler... and...
Why? Why can't I remember it?
Those guys who attacked me may be around!
Don't go places by yourself, Clo.
Otherwise there's no point in having a bodyguard, right?
Do you wanna take a ride in my car?
Don't worry. I'll just go check up on them.
I can't just leave things to that man.
That snake, he must be playing with that fine toy by now.
Geez... How disgusting!
But he contributes a lot to the organization.
That puppet is the favorite of McGwire and the others, so...
We use whatever it takes to achieve our goal. That's Inferno's style.
I know. But Clo...
You're treading on dangerous ground too much.
Let me know if you need me.
I'm counting on you, Lizzie.
If only she didn't drive like that.
Ability to assess the situation, 074.
Awakening rate, 087.
To think that he's reached these values less than a few minutes after awaking...
I told you...
he's a gem.
I'm gonna go to hell.
No, I may already be in hell.
That ability of his to sense things is...
That's the true nature of animals.
It's the wild instinct that was hidden within his reason.
But not yet...
He... still hasn't reached the range that I seek yet.
It's about time for you to appear, Phantom.
But... don't overdo it.
Yes, Master.
If you don't wanna die...
Those eyes...!
come at me with all you've got.
A crisis of the heart, a crisis to one's life, a crisis of existence...
In such cases, one's survival instinct is all that can deal with them.
If one relies on things like morals and kindness...
and considers that his safety is guaranteed based on those...
that means he is a weak human who has abandoned life...
In this world, that has become the norm. I really hate this world.
Well, well. If it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
If I had known you were coming...
What's going on?
I think we'll see the result soon. Would you like to see it?
Yes.
Then please come over here.
Who is she? Why is she after me?
I don't even know why.
I don't know where I am... or who I am.
I can't escape.
I can't go anywhere.
If I can't escape...
For you and me both...
It's kill
or be killed!
It's about to start.
Start?
Please watch carefully.
Why?!
Come at me with all you've got.. if you don't wanna die.
I have nothing... No past, no future, not even my life...
Even so, I...
don't want do die!
Where should I go...
when I don't even know where I came from...
when I don't even have memories...?
What do I have to do to become free?
What is freedom when you have to kill people for it?
What is it?
Tell me...
please...
Where is this place?
Who... Who am I?!
Zwei...
Y-You are...
I'm Ein.
You are Zwei.
Zwei...
That's your name. Your name is Zwei from today.
Zwei... What is that? What's...
You are me.
I am you.
What do you think? Don't you think he's a wonderful find?
All things considered, the result turned out to be excellent.
This boy has neither prior training nor knowledge of tactics.
He acted that way solely by following his natural instincts.
On top of that, though it was temporary, he surpassed even Ein.
How shameful, Phantom.
I'm sorry.
He's a prodigy.
And he has the talent that isn't revealed until he falls into a life or death situation.
He is certainly a human who was born to join Inferno.
Even so, would he want that?
There's no egg that refuses to hatch nor are there any seeds that refuse to bud.
It has nothing to do with his will.
Your specialty, brain washing, huh?
It's perfect. By using hypnosis and drugs,
I sealed only the memories that had something to do with his own identity.
Please understand, Ms. McCunnen.
This is mercy.
He happened to be somewhere very unlucky for him.
Under normal circumstances, he'd have been a witness to be eliminated.
However, I'd like to give him one more chance to live a fruitful life.
A lone traveler and Japanese...
This'll be a problem.
No one can trace his trail any longer. Our top secret is perfectly safe.
Okay then.
Scythe Master, I'll leave this boy to you.
Thank you very much.
Ein and Zwei...
You should think more when you name your pupils.
I wonder how long you'll be able to keep giving me orders like that.
mademoiselle...
I'm the first woman, Ein.
You're the second man, Zwei.
We are...
What're you doing?
That will be all, Ein.
Go back to your post.
Yes, Master.
We are...
ghosts that have no place to exist...
non-existent phantoms.
Hm...
Welcome back, master.
Yeah. Where are the others?
Yes, they're resting.
In the middle of the day? What's going on?
Wh-who are you?
Phantom.
Phantom... the strongest assassin in Inferno...
the title given to the top sniper in the organization...
my greatest masterpiece...
And... he too is...
That's overkill.
I see...
His organization is done for.
Two out of five organizations in LA have now gone under.
This is a start, my friends.
We are going to create a new era with our own hands.
We will create... the era of Inferno.
Ghosts that have no place to exist...
Non-existent phantoms...
Next Episode
Training
You are now only allowed to exist for the purpose of killing people.