After the incident at the audition...
...things were awkward between Takuto and me.
So, I couldn't go home.
Mitsuki said that she would make sure I'd go back.
We weren't too eager at first, but...
...thanks to Mitsuki's hard work...
...I was able to make up with Takuto.
To celebrate the rebirth of the combo...
...we launched some spectacular Spring Onion Ramen fireworks that went boom !
It felt so good!
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
There's no trace of your cancer...
How does it look?
Is it all right for her to go back to work?
It's true that if you look at her body when she's twelve...
...and then look at her body when she's sixteen, it's like she isn't sick at all.
So, how about it?
Well...
As long as she doesn't push herself...
All right!
Isn't that great, Mitsuki?
Yep.
Wakaouji-sensei.
I promise.
I won't push myself too hard!
Dr. Wakaouji...
Thank you very much!
New Feelings
Anyways...
...isn't this great?
You can sing your songs as Full Moon  again.
Yep!
But best of all...
...Wakaouji-sensei forgave me...
That makes me really happy!
Yep, yep.
Something wrong?
Um...
You're Takuto-kun, right?
Yessiree.
Then... the bunny next to you is...
I'm Meroko!
Ah, I see...
Ah...
This feels like a bad dream that I still haven't woken up from.
Excuse me!
Calling this a bad dream...
...that makes us sound like ghosts or demons...
Despite the fact that we're obviously Shinigami!
Shinigami?
So that's what it was...
Ah.
Meroko, now's not the time for that.
Why?
Speaking of which...
Why does she know about us?
What happened while I was gone?
It couldn't be helped!
Things just happened to turn out this way.
Ah...
It feels like the situation always just takes us along for the ride...
Is this okay for Spring Onion Ramen?
W-Well... if that's the case...
It's fine since you've been helping out Mitsuki.
Starting now, Mitsuki's health is our biggest concern.
Thank you, Ooshige-san.
Let's give it our all!
Okay!
I'm finally...
...going back to work, huh?
I have to do my best!
I heard that it was really fun last time...
Ah. Good morning, Tokoroki-san!
Ah, Ooshige-chan!
It's been a while.
Full Moon  is coming back to work today.
Please treat us kindly!
Ah... now that you mention it, that's right...
Well, are you feeling better now?
Yep!
Sorry for causing so much trouble!
That's fine... just watch your health.
Okay!
Excuse us, then.
Excuse us.
They said it was because of poor health...
I wonder what the real reason was.
What do you mean?
It's rumored that she has a boyfriend.
They say she doesn't even deny it herself.
She's sure got guts.
No shame at all, huh?
Eh? Is that so?
But, who'd you hear that rumor from?
Well, that's...
Sasaki-san.
Hmm?
She comes back today, right? Full Moon, that is.
Yeah.
Looks like it.
Today she's at a recording for a TV music program.
The rumor about her skipping the audition like that...
...it's already spread everywhere in the business.
If she thinks she can come back that easily...
...she's mistaken.
Or, you could say...
...I won't let her.
Good morning!
Ah!
She's here.
Isn't that wonderful... she has a boyfriend...
Slacking off from work... must be more important.
Just 'cause she's a little popular, it's gone to her head...
Even though she's a new artist... how naive...
What an unpleasant atmosphere.
Just ignore them, Mitsuki.
But...
This is what it's like on the day back, huh?
His name's Eichi-kun.
Eh?!
How do they know that?
What's with this?!
I can't take it!
You! Don't just sit there!
Give them an earful!
Meroko...
Yo.
Good morning.
Takasu-san!
Congratulations on your return.
Eh? Um...
I was surprised when I heard you'd collapsed.
You're back today... good luck!
Takasu-san.
Thank you very much!
Such a wonderful bouquet...
Wow, they smell so good!
Well, I figured they'd cheer you up.
It's almost time...
Shall we get going?
Yeah.
Then... good luck!
Okay!
That old guy... unexpectedly,
he has a good side to him.
Yep, I was pretty surprised.
But still...
What is it, Ooshige-san?
The rumor about Eichi-kun has spread a lot more than I thought it would...
Yes...
Hopefully, it won't be a big scandal...
Huh?
What's the problem?
Isn't that okay?
If there's a little scandal...
...then Eichi-kun will definitely find Mitsuki!
You could think about it that way too, huh?
I don't always think this, but...
...you're the type of girl who doesn't let a setback keep her down.
I guess so.
Wait! That's a compliment, right?!
Hmm?
Yeah... well, let's just leave it at that.
And then...
Takasu-san talked with her...
What?
What is this?!
Why is it going so well for her?!
Why are they so willing to forget what happened?!
She hasn't had to work hard at all...
If it were me...
...things wouldn't go so well.
I wouldn't be welcomed by everyone.
I know...
Because... the whole world...
...has always been cold to me...
I wonder if she's lost...
Ah!
Ah...
Thank you very much.
Um...
How much farther do you have to go?
Well, you see...
I'm trying to get to my grandchild's house here on this map.
If that's where you're going, I know where it is.
Granny, I'll take you there.
Good morning!
Morning? Do you know what time it is?
I'm sorry.
You're an hour late.
Do you want to quit?
I'm sorry.
I'll go get ready right away!
There's no need for that.
We've already found a replacement.
You don't need to come anymore.
No way...
What were you doing?!
That's 'cause...
There was an old lady who was lost...
You know...
In this world, you have to put yourself first.
If you worry about other people...
...you'll never be able to reach the top.
After that...
...a rumor started about me being stuck up...
...and job after job was canceled.
Even though I was only doing the right thing...
...I won't forgive her.
Why?
I've come so far since then...
I've had to go through so much...
After failing once...
In order to get rid of my image of being stuck up...
...I did everything.
I always looked at the faces
of the people around me...
Always wary...
Yet still...
Why is everything about her?!
Mitsuki.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Full Moon-san!
Please head to the rehearsal.
Ah...
Okay!
Let's start the camera rehearsal, then!
Let's do a good job!
Here we go!
In five...
Four...
Three...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I lost way too much back then.
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all.
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
I wonder if they're talking about me.
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
Who was that?!
Ah!
I'm sorry!
Cut the music!
How unbecoming...
Interrupting someone else's singing.
Komaki-san!
I-I'm sorry!
If you are professional singers...
...you should listen carefully and respectfully!
Y-Yes!
It's just as you say, Komaki-san!
You too.
You were singing without any spirit.
What's wrong?
Where's that energy that you showed me?
I-I'm sorry!
And... you over there!
If you have the time to sneak around behind someone's back...
...couldn't you at least learn how to put on a plausible act?
Madoka-san...
It looks like all you've been doing is spreading rumors...
Don't you have any real strength
to challenge her with?
If that's the case...
...you've lost before you've even begun.
Madoka-san is... spreading the rumors...?
T-That's right!
We were just...
...taken in by what Madoka-san said.
I'm sorry.
I... may have done something unforgivable.
But... I was jealous of Full Moon-san.
Madoka-san is...
Jealous of me...?
But spreading rumors behind her back...
I had no intention of doing that.
Just that...
...it seemed so nice to have someone you like...
I just wanted to have that too...
...just wanted to try liking somebody...
And just like that...
I would have never thought that it'd turn into such a huge rumor.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want it to be like this.
Eh?
No...
It's okay.
Eichi-kun will surely find you.
Thank you.
Madoka might be a nicer girl than I thought...
That's right.
Because she couldn't say what she wanted to say.
I guess that works...
Eh?
Meroko, what do you mean?
Well...
Ow... ow... ow...
What's wrong?
T-That?
Eh?
Ah!
Did something happen?
What? What?
Ah!
Who did such a horrible thing?!
Ah... hello?
This is Ooshige.
Is the stylist, Yasuno-chan, there?
What?
She's not?
Do you know where she went?
Eh?
There's a huge problem with Full Moon's  costume!
Ah... come on...
Why is it that when something happens... I can't find anyone?!
Mitsuki!
What was that?!
Didn't she make it look like we were spreading the rumors?
Even though she was degrading Full Moon  herself...
It's like she was just making up excuses.
Today's the first time I've truly understood just how scary show business can be.
Just now...
What were they talking about?
Uh... that's...
It's just as I thought.
Eh?
What do you mean by that, Meroko?
Back there... Madoka's crying was just an act.
Eh?
Then... Madoka-san did this?!
Stop it.
We don't have any proof.
But...!
After what we just overheard...
...what else am I supposed to think?
Saying that won't get us anywhere!
Anyways...
...we need to do something about this.
T-That's right!
I can't get a hold of Yasuno-chan!
Ah!
Man, what am I supposed to do?!
That's it!
Hey, hey.
This situation is a perfect chance for me to use my real power.
Eh?
Real power?
What's that?
Well, just leave it to me.
Mero Mero Change!
T-This is a little...
What are you doing?!
H-Huh... that's funny...
One more try!
Meroko.
Are you just playing around?
Um...
We don't have much time...
J-Just leave it to me.
H-Huh?
Ah...
I'm begging you...
There's only thirty minutes till she's up!
This is strange...
W-What's an idol's costume supposed to look like?
It's okay.
Huh?
Eh?
Some unknown person...
for some unknown reason...
I don't understand why they would do this to my costume...
But...
...despite the fact that someone did this...
...I won't break down.
You...
Mitsuki!
Hey!
I said hey!
Have you lost it?!
Stop it! Stop it!
What's wrong, Mitsuki?!
At this very moment...
...she's probably freaking out about her costume.
That's what you get...
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Doushite kimi wo suki ni nattandarou
Why is it that I've fallen in love with you?
Kantan sugite kotae ni naranai
I can't find an answer easily...
Everyone...
About what happened recently...
By taking a vacation so suddenly...
...I've caused many problems.
I'm very sorry.
I... myself...
...will do my best from now on!
So... please treat me kindly!
That was good.
Though after seeing your last rehearsal...
...I wasn't sure how things would turn out.
Thank you very much!
Keep up the good work!
Okay!
Man...
I was surprised about the sudden costume change, but...
...it's good.
Your return to work was a big success, right?
Thank you very much!
Well... it looks like some weird rumors were spreading, but...
...don't worry about it.
It happens all the time in this business.
Okay!
Well, then... let's keep it up!
Great job!
I never thought I'd see...
...your costume arranged like that.
Not in my wildest dreams.
The one who doesn't let a setback keep her down...
...is this little one here.
Yep!
I had no idea what was going to happen today...
...but she toughed it out!
That's for sure...
But you know...
...that Madoka...
I won't forgive her.
Don't say too much, Meroko.
I haven't heard much of the conversation, but...
...did something happen?
Someone tore her costume into shreds!
Eh?
What did you say?!
It's okay.
Don't worry about it, Wakaouji-sensei.
But...
I'm fine.
Something like this doesn't get me down at all!
'kay?
Mitsuki-chan... you really love to sing, huh?
Eh?
I understand.
I won't doubt you anymore.
Wakaouji-sensei...
Mitsuki-chan...
I'll find a way out of the surgery.
Really?
Yeah.
However... don't push yourself too hard...
Coming back to work after so long...
You'll have to be careful for a while.
Really... don't push yourself too hard.
Okay!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Oh no! Oh no!
Takuto, what should we do?!
What are you yelling about, Meroko?
Her first solo live concert has been scheduled, so...
...this isn't the time for that.
As I was saying...
...there's a big problem with that live concert!
Huh?
What's wrong?
The reservation for the location of her live concert...
Someone canceled it!
What?!
Wait... the live concert's tomorrow!
What are we supposed to do?!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sahasgite:
Exciting Solo Live Concert!
Look forward to it!