- Fukuhara: LAST TIME,
AKIHISA AND THE GANG
SUDDENLY FOUND THEMSELVES
PARTICIPATING IN AN INTER-GRADE
COURAGE CONTEST.
DUE TO THE ADEPT STRATEGY
OF THE YEAR THREE STUDENTS,
LED BY TSUNEMURA
AND NATSUKAWA,
ALSO KNOWN AS
THE SOO-NA-KAWA DUO,
THE GANG FOUND THEMSELVES
IN A BITTER STRUGGLE.
YADDA YADDA YADDA.
LET'S FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT.
- WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO NOW?
MOST OF OUR CLASS
HAS BEEN TAKEN OUT
BY YEAR THREE ALREADY.
- WE'VE GOT A WEAPON.
A SECRET WEAPON,
SO DON'T WORRY.
- A SECRET...
- WEAPON?
- HUH?
- All: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SO...
- ( whimpers )
- I GUESS WE'RE
THE SECRET WEAPONS, HUH?
- YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
I MEAN, I'M NOT
SCARED AT ALL, ARE YOU?
- ( both scream )
- ( whimpers )
- NICE.
THAT WAS SCARY.
YOU OKAY?
- YEP.  WELL, SORT OF.
I'M JUST NOT USED
TO SEEING JAPANESE GOBLINS.
GERMAN GOBLINS WOULD BE
A DIFFERENT STORY.
- AAH!
- ( both scream )
( muffled screaming )
- ( groans )
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
PLEASE LET ME GO.
- I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS ANYMORE.
LET'S GO.  PLEASE, AKI.
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S SHE DOING?
THIS ISN'T LIKE
HER USUAL SELF.
WHY IS MY HEART
BEATING SO HARD?
WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
THEY MUST HAVE A SPECIAL
PEN THROWING DEPARTMENT
OR SOMETHING.
- ALL PIGS WHO DARE
TRY TO SEDUCE MY LADY
SHALL BE ELIMINATED!
- WE GOTTA GO.  LIKE NOW.
- WHAT?  WHY?
- I'LL NEVER LET YOU
GET AWAY, MY DARLING.
I'LL SEPARATE YOU FROM
THAT DISGUSTING SWINE
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
( cackles )
- HEY, MIHARU,
DO YOU REALIZE YOU LOOK
MORE LIKE A GOBLIN
THAN THE ACTUAL GOBLINS?
- ( groans )
- WELL, THAT'S ODD. I WAS
CERTAIN THEY RAN THIS WAY.
LET'S MOVE ON THEN. WE'LL SIMPLY
HAVE TO LOOK ELSEWHERE.
- I'LL BE RIGHT THERE,
PUMPKIN.
- HECK YEAH.
THEY FELL FOR IT.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SURE
THEY'RE NOT HIDING SOMEWHERE?
- ( chuckles )
I GUESS IT'S TIME
YOU GOT USED TO
JAPANESE GHOSTS AND GOBLINS.
- NO WAY.  I'LL JUST
GO BACK HOME TO GERMANY.
SCREW THIS.
- YOU SURE?
YOU'LL GET SO LONELY.
- HOW COME?
GIVE ME SOME CREDIT.
I ACTUALLY HAVE FRIENDS
IN GERMANY TOO, DUMMY.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
- WHAT?
- I WASN'T TALKING
ABOUT YOU, SILLY.
IT'D BE LONELY FOR
THE REST OF US IF YOU LEFT.
- ( gasps )
PLEASE, I KNOW
YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO GET ON MY GOOD SIDE AGAIN.
- THAT ISN'T TRUE AT ALL.
I MEAN, WE'RE ALWAYS
TOGETHER, AREN'T WE?
I CAN'T IMAGINE NOT BEING
ABLE TO SEE YOU EVERY DAY.
- ALWAYS TOGETHER?
- WHAT DID I SAY?
ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
- NO.  JUST THINKING.
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY IF I TOLD YOU
I WOULD ALWAYS BE BY YOUR SIDE?
- WELL, I'D SAY WHERE I SIT
IN THE CLASSROOM IS DRAFTY,
SO IT'S USUALLY COLD.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
I WAS TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
- OKAY, LIKE WHAT?
- IT'S JUST THAT...
WELL, I--
AAH.
( groans )
- ( gasps )
MINAMI, WHAT HAPPENED?
OH.
I'M BACK.
- OH, WELCOME BACK,
AKIHISA.
HEY, WHERE DID MINAMI GO?
- I DROPPED HER OFF
AT THE NURSE'S OFFICE.
SHE PUSHED HERSELF TOO HARD
AND NEEDED TO REST.
- WELL PLAYED, AKI.
THE PLAN WENT OFF
WITHOUT A HITCH.
- All: HMM?
- ( both grunt )
- ( gasping )
- BOO!
YOU INTERRUPTED
THE SEARCH FOR MY LOVER,
AND NOW YOU MUST PAY!
- ( Avatars grunting )
- ( screaming )
- THAT GIRL'S A MONSTER.
- IS SHE THE SECRET WEAPON
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
- THAT SHE IS.
- WEIRD.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
WHY MIHARU IS
LOOKING FOR MINAMI,
BUT WHAT IS KUBO LOOKING FOR?
( gasps )
DO YOU THINK KUBO MIGHT
HAVE A THING FOR MIHARU?
- OH, AKI.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
BE SO DAMN CRUEL?
- YOU'RE GONNA MAKE KUBO CRY.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE TOO MEAN.
- WHAT THE CRAP, GUYS?
- WELL, YOU SURE DID
KEEP US WAITING LONG ENOUGH.
WE MAY HAVE LET
OUR GUARD DOWN THIS MORNING,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA GET A TASTE OF
WHAT THE REAL YEAR THREE POWER--
- EXCUSE ME, BUT HAVE YOU BY
CHANCE SEEN AKIHISA YOSHII
AND MINAMI SHIMADA?
- ( groans )
HEY, YOU INTERRUPTED MY
IMPASSIONED THREAT, YOU BASTARD.
- YOU THINK THAT'S FUNNY?
WE CAN GIVE YOU SOMETHING
TO REALLY LAUGH ABOUT.
- Both: SUMMON!
- I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
- Both: SUMMON.
- All: NO WAY!
- THEY'VE GOT OVER 400 POINTS.
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- SCIENCE GEEKS ARE
SCIENCE GEEKS.
NOT MUCH WE CAN
DO ABOUT IT.
- ( gasps )
- ( cackles )
- WILL YOU STOP IT WITH THE
FREAKY LAUGHING?
ENOUGH ALREADY.
- YOU'RE UP, JACK WAGON.
- ( gasps )
- TAKE THIS!
- ( Class F sighs )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE KUBO LOST.
- IT'S UP TO US.
WE SHOULD GO NOW.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU TWO HAVEN'T GONE YET.
- NOT SO FAST. THE FIGHT WON'T
BE A BIG DEAL FOR SHOUKO,
BUT MY PHYSICS SCORE
IS 150 AT THE MOST.
THAT'S GONNA MAKE FOR
A PRETTY ROUGH BATTLE.
- BUMMER. WE NEED ANOTHER
PAIR TO GO IN THERE,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYONE LEFT.
- BUT THERE IS
ANOTHER PAIR LEFT.
RIGHT THERE.
- ( gasps )
WHO, ME?  I MEAN,
I KNOW I'M NOT DISQUALIFIED,
LIKE I DIDN'T
SCREAM OR ANYTHING,
BUT MINAMI CAN'T
GO BACK INSIDE.
- NOT HER.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
THERE'S ANOTHER GIRL HERE
WHO HASN'T BEEN INSIDE
THE HAUNTED HOUSE YET
AND ISN'T SHOUKO.
- I GOT NOTHING.
- AKIHISA?
I THINK THEY MIGHT BE
TALKING ABOUT ME.
- SHE CAN'T. SHE'S AFRAID OF
GHOSTS AND GOBLINS BIG TIME.
SHE WON'T MAKE IT.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
I CAN DO IT.
- ( gasps )
- MINAMI WAS AFRAID TOO,
BUT SHE DIDN'T
LET THAT STOP HER,
AND NEITHER SHOULD I.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL DO IT.
I'M GOING INTO
THAT HAUNTED HOUSE WITH AKIHISA.
COULD YOU WALK
A LITTLE SLOWER PLEASE?
- YEAH, SURE.
- I'M NOT AFRAID.
I'M FINE.
I'M NOT SCARED AT ALL.
I'M WITH AKIHISA,
SO I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO BE FRIGHTENED OF,
WHICH IS GOOD,
SINCE I'M FINE.
- HEY, HIMEJI,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
- NO, I DON'T KNOW WHAT.
- I'M GLAD YOU CAME IN.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
- ( gasps )
THANK YOU.
I'M ALWAYS DEPENDING ON YOU,
SO IT SEEMED LIKE IT WAS
YOUR TURN TO DEPEND ON ME.
- I DON'T THINK THAT'S TRUE.
PLUS I DON'T MIND IT AT ALL
WHEN YOU DEPEND ON ME.
- ( whimpers )
- YOU'RE REALLY CUTE,
AND YOU'RE LIKE WAY SMART.
ON TOP OF THAT,
YOU'RE SUPER SWEET.
IT'S LIKE I'M
PROTECTING A PRINCESS.
- ( gasps )
- THE ONLY WEIRD PART IS THAT
YOU'RE HANGING OUT
WITH A GUY LIKE ME.
YOU OKAY?
- I'M FINE.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
I'M NOT A PRINCESS.
- ( gasps )
- I'M A KLUTZ. I GET REALLY
JEALOUS FOR NO REASON,
AND I HAVE A TENDENCY
TO FAINT.
I'M SO NOT A PRINCESS.
- COME ON, THAT'S NOT--
- YES, IT IS!
YOU JUST REFUSE TO
ACCEPT THE TRUTH
FOR SOME STUPID REASON.
YOU DON'T NOTICE ANYTHING
THAT'S NOT PERFECT ABOUT ME.
AND I THINK IT'S SO
YOU CAN HAVE A REASON
TO KEEP FROM GETTING
CLOSE TO ME.
- WHY WOULDN'T I
WANT TO GET CLOSE TO YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S PROBABLY
OUT OF CONSIDERATION.
YOUR EYES SEE ME,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
ACTUALLY SEE THE REAL ME.
I DON'T THINK YOU DO.
CAN YOU SEE THE REAL ME?
- THIS IS AWKWARD.
- Nishimura:
BAKA AND TEST.
- ( panting )
HIMEJI.
( yelps )
DAMN IT.
I DON'T REMEMBER
A WALL BEING HERE.
OW.  SON OF A CRAP!
AAH!
( grunts )
AH, FINALLY.
WHERE WERE YOU?
YOU GOT UGLY.
- OH, CAN IT.
AND LET GO OF MY HAND.
- WAIT, YUUJI?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHERE'S HIMEJI?
MOTHER TRUCK.
WHERE AM I?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
HIMEJI'S PROBABLY
JOINED UP WITH SHOUKO BY NOW.
- WHAT?  I NEED YOU
TO BREAK THIS DOWN.
- IT WAS ALL A PART OF
THOSE YEAR THREE LOSERS' SCHEME.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
EITHER SHOUKO OR I
ARE GONNA SCREAM AT
MUCH OF ANYTHING.
- YEAH, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- SO THEY TURNED OFF
ALL THE LIGHTS
AS A WAY TO GET US SEPARATED.
AND ONCE THAT WAS DONE,
THEY JUST MADE A PARTNER SWITCH.
- I GET IT.
- WELL, SHOUKO AND HIMEJI
ARE STRONGER TOGETHER
THAN THEY WERE
WITH EITHER OF US,
SO IT WORKS OUT.
- BRO, TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- WHEN I'M ALONE IN
THE HAUNTED HOUSE WITH SHOUKO,
THE FEAR I FELT WHEN
SHE ATTACKED ME
WITH A SPIKE ROD RETURNS.
- OH.  I THINK I SEE HER
AROUND THE CORNER.
-  ( gasps )
AKIHISA DEFLECTOR SHIELD.
- AND NOW I KNOW
HOW AFRAID YOU REALLY ARE.
- MIZUKI,
IS ANYTHING THE MATTER?
- YES, I THINK SO.
- DO YOU HEAR THAT?
HEY!
( whispers )
HIMEJI, OVER HERE.
- Ghostly Voice:
- THERE'S NO ONE WHISPERING.
I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
I'M FINE.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
- WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING
ISN'T WORKING.
YOU'RE GONNA FREAK THEM OUT
EVEN MORE, DUDE.
WE DON'T WANT THEM
TO SCREAM, DO WE?
- YOU'RE RIGHT. MAYBE WE
SHOULD KEEP OUR DISTANCE.
- Both: TIPTOE, TIPTOE.
TIPTOE, TIPTOE, TIPTOE.
- ( gasps )
- AAH!
- ( silent scream )
- ( grunts )
- ( whimpers )
- MIZUKI, CALM DOWN.
WE'LL BE FINE.
- HUH?
- FACE MY ULTIMATE CURSE.
- ( silent scream )
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
RIGHT.  I'M NOT SCARED.
WE'RE FINE.  I'M SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
YOU ARE A GOOD GIRL.
- SHE'S SCARED.
- TRUE.
DUDE, LOOK. I GOT IT.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT HER,
BUT YOU HAVE TO LET HER
DEAL IN HER OWN WAY.
- OKAY, WHY DO I
HAVE TO DO THAT?
- SHE WANTS TO BE
A CLOSER FRIEND TO US.
ONE WE CAN RELY ON
AND WHO DOESN'T NEED SAVING.
- ( gasps ) YUUJI, YOU COULD
HAVE TOLD ME THAT EARLIER.
- OR YOU COULD HAVE
JUST LISTENED TO HER.
SHE COMPLAINED A LOT ABOUT
ALWAYS BEING HELPED BY EVERYONE
WHEN SHE DIDN'T NEED IT.
- I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( moaning )
- ( murmurs )
- JUST KEEP WALKING.
WE'RE FINE, AREN'T WE?
- YES, WE ARE.
AND I'M NOT SCARED.
I'M NOT SCARED BECAUSE
THOSE AREN'T EVEN REAL.
- YOU CAN DO THIS.
I BELIEVE IN YOU, HIMEJI.
- DID WE MAKE IT?
- DAMN.
YOU TWO ARE CHICKS.
SHOULDN'T YOU HAVE
SCREAMED OR SOMETHING BY NOW?
- THEY'RE JUST
ANOTHER OBSTACLE.
ALTHOUGH I WAS REALLY HOPING
THIS WOULD BE OUR MOMENT
TO TRASH THOSE LOSERS
YOSHII AND SAKAMOTO.
- YEAH, I BET THEY RAN
THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- LOSERS AND COWARDS.
- THEY ARE NEITHER LOSERS
NOR COWARDS.
- Both: HUH?
- TAKE IT BACK.
- HUH?
- ( both laugh )
- YOU DON'T KNOW THEM
VERY WELL, DO YOU?
- THEY'RE ALWAYS
GETTING INTO TROUBLE,
AND THEIR GRADES ARE
COMPLETE AND UTTER CRAP.
IF THOSE TWO ASSES
AREN'T LOSERS,
THEN I DON'T KNOW WHO IS.
- SHE BRINGS UP
A GOOD POINT THOUGH.
GARBAGE MIGHT BE A BETTER
TERM FOR THOSE TWO.
- HOLD ON.
THAT WAS TOO FAR.
YOU ARE BEING
TERRIBLY RUDE TO GARBAGE.
- ( both laugh )
- TRUE, GARBAGE AT LEAST
HAS THE COURTESY
TO STAY IN THE DUMP
WHERE IT BELONGS.
- YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
THEY'RE IDIOTIC LOSERS
WHO ARE TOO DAMN CHICKEN
TO FIGHT THEIR OWN BATTLES.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO AWFUL?
- ( beeping )
- YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT MAY BE TRUE THAT
AKIHISA AND YUUJI'S GRADES
AREN'T THE BEST
IN LIKE THE WHOLE
ENTIRE WORLD,
AND YEAH, MAYBE THEY DO
HAVE A WAY OF GETTING
INTO TROUBLE A LOT,
BUT THAT DOES NOT
GIVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO SAY SUCH MEAN
AND HATEFUL THINGS ABOUT THEM.
YOU DON'T KNOW THEM.
THEY'RE TWO OF THE KINDEST
AND MOST WONDERFUL PEOPLE I'VE
EVER HAD THE PLEASURE TO MEET.
- THAT COULD BE,
BUT IT'S A LOT MORE LIKELY
YOU JUST DON'T REALIZE
HOW STUPID THEY ACTUALLY ARE.
- AND HOW STUPID ARE YOU
TO JUDGE SOMEONE
BASED ON THEIR
GRADES IN SCHOOL?
THERE'S A LOT MORE
TO LIFE THAN THAT.
SOME THINGS CAN'T BE
MEASURED WITH SCORES!
- JEEZ, WILL YOU STOP YELLING?
THEY'RE LOWER THAN DIRT
AND WE DON'T CARE,
SO JUST GET OVER IT.
- THEY'RE NOT LOWER THAN DIRT!
- ( beeping )
- AND THEY'RE NOT LOSERS AT ALL!
YOU'RE THE STUPID ONES!
- ( beeping continues )
- SERIOUSLY, SHUT UP.
YOU'VE BEEN DISQUALIFIED.
GET OUT.
- YOU'RE THE ONE YELLING NOW.
WE'RE LEAVING.
COME ON, MIZUKI.
- DID YOU HEAR WHAT
SHE SAID, YUUJI?
APPARENTLY YOU AND I
ARE PRETTY WONDERFUL.
- THAT'S NEWS TO ME.
I MEAN, I'M NOT
AS BAD AS YOU ARE,
BUT I WOULD HAVE BET MONEY
THAT I WAS A GIANT LOSER.
- ME TOO.  IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M AS BAD AS YOU.
BUT I COULD HAVE SWORN I WAS
LOWER THAN DIRT, AM I RIGHT?
- TOO BAD THEY GOT
DISQUALIFIED.
TALK ABOUT A WASTE. SHE
DIDN'T SCREAM THAT WHOLE TIME,
AND IT WAS ALL FOR NOTHING.
- I KNOW RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A DUMB GAME.
SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO TAKE
IT SO SERIOUSLY.
- WELL, I GUESS
IT'S UP TO US.
- YES, IT IS.
SHALL WE?
- Both: GET READY, YOU BASTARDS.
IT'S ON NOW.
- COME ON.
I'M KIND OF OVER WAITING
FOR THESE GUYS, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, BUT WHY WOULD
THEY WANT TO SHOW UP?
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'LL WIN
WITH THEIR SCORES.
- SURPRISE.
WE SHOWED UP.
- WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
- FOR REAL.
IT'S ABOUT FREAKING TIME.
LET'S DO THIS!
- NOT SO FAST. WE HAVEN'T
CHOSEN THE PENALTY YET.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HOPE YOU'RE NOT TRYING
TO GET OUT OF THIS,
'CAUSE THAT'S NOT HAPPENING.
- WHY DON'T YOU TRY
NOT FREAKING OUT?
IT WAS YOU THAT MENTIONED
THE PENALTY IN THE FIRST PLACE,
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
- ALL RIGHT. WHAT
KIND OF PENALTY?
- HOW ABOUT THE LOSERS DO
WHATEVER THE WINNERS SAY?
SOUND GOOD ENOUGH TO YOU?
- SURE.  WE CAN WORK WITH THAT.
- LET'S GET STARTED THEN.
- All: SUMMON!
- WHAT KIND OF CRAP SCORES
ARE THOSE?
- THERE'S NO WAY YOU'LL
BEAT US WITH THOSE NUMBERS.
- YOU HAVE A GOOD POINT.
READY TO DO THIS, AKI?
- BORN READY, YUUJI, MY MAN.
( chuckles )
- Both: GO!
- DAMN IT! THOSE IDIOTS
ARE RUNNING AWAY.
- WELL, LET'S GO
CATCH THEM THEN.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE THEY DOING?
- WHERE DID THEY GO?
- I THINK I HEARD THEM
OVER THERE.
- ( both panting )
- THE HAUNTED HOUSE
ISN'T MAKING THIS EASY.
- Yuuji: YOU BOYS AREN'T
ALREADY TIRED, ARE YOU?
- THE HALLWAY
BACK OVER THERE.
DAMN IT.
- HEY, UPPER CLASSMEN GIRLS,
WE'RE RIGHT HERE.
- WHY, YOU--!
- Akihisa: DUDE, YOU GUYS
ARE SLOWER THAN I THOUGHT.
- Yuuji:
HEY NOW, THAT'S RUDE.
- Akihisa: COME ON, THEY ACT
LIKE THEY'VE NEVER RUN BEFORE.
- Yuuji:
AW, GIVE THEM A BREAK.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'RE
GIVING US ALL THEY GOT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, BOYS?
- YOSHII AND SAKAMOTO,
GET OUT HERE!
- Yuuji: WHY DON'T YOU USE
THOSE BIG OLD BRAINS OF YOURS
AND FIND US ALREADY?
- Akihisa: SERIOUSLY,
I'M GETTING TIRED
OF HIDING.
HOW HAVE THEY NOT
FOUND US YET?
- ( both chuckle )
- WE KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
- YEAH, WE CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH
IT, LOSERS. THEY'RE GONE!
- DID WE LEAVE
THE PHYSICS FIELD?
( gasps )
- ( beeping )
- I DO APOLOGIZE,
BUT THIS IS A DECOY.
- YOU DIDN'T SEE
THROUGH ANYTHING.
- I DON'T GET IT!
- MAY WE HAVE YOUR PERMISSION
TO SUMMON?
- YES, YOU MAY.  I APPROVE.
- Akihisa and Yuuji:
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- GUESS WHAT? WE'RE IN THE MATH
FIELD NOW, SUCKERS. YOU CAN'T
FIGHT WITH YOUR FAVORITE
LITTLE PHYSICS SCORES ANYMORE.
- NO! THAT WAS
A DIRTY TRICK.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
SO UPSET ABOUT?
THERE'S NO RULES SAYING WE CAN'T
CHANGE AROUND THE SUBJECTS
AT CHECKPOINTS.
- DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
TOO AFRAID TO FIGHT US WITH
ANYTHING OTHER THAN PHYSICS?
COME ON.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
WE'RE JUST AS AWESOME
AT MATH AS WE ARE SCIENCE.
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE GONNA
LOSE TO YOU IDIOTS, REGARDLESS.
- Both: SUMMON!
WHAT?  NO.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THOSE TWO CRAZY PEOPLE
HURT OUR SCORES THIS MORNING.
- Both:
THEY PLANNED THE WHOLE THING!
- NO!
- STOP SCREWING AROUND!
- ( shouts )
- ( groans )
- IT'S TOO LATE TO STRUGGLE.
MIGHT AS WELL
GIVE IT UP.
- NEVER.
- Yuuji: IDIOTS ARE INTERESTING,
DON'T YOU THINK?
WHEN THEY GET DESPERATE,
THEY EXHIBIT A DOWNRIGHT
MANIC ABILITY
TO COME THROUGH.
YOU MAY HAVE BETTER
GRADES THAN WE DO,
BUT WE HAVE SOMETHING THAT
DOESN'T CARE ABOUT NUMBERS.
IT'S CALLED STRATEGY,
AND IT'S ABOUT TO KICK YOUR ASS.
- Tsunemura: WHY DON'T YOU
SHUT THE HELL UP?
GET ON WITH IT.
- ( Avatars shouting )
- Yuuji:
YOU ASKED FOR IT.
- Both: IT'S HIS HEAD!
- Yuuji: HOW DOES IT FEEL
TO LOSE TO A COUPLE OF LOSERS?
- ( both gasp )
- BUT HOW?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- Both: HOW DID WE LOSE
TO TWO IDIOTS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.  WE WON.
AND NOW YOU HAVE TO
FACE THE PENALTY.
- GREAT. WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA MAKE US DO?
- YOU HAVE TO ASK?
IT'S OBVIOUS.
HIMEJI? ( gasps )
- YOSHII?
- HEY, SHOUKO.
- YOU'LL FIND MIZUKI
UP ON THE ROOFTOP.
GO TO HER NOW.
- ( chuckles )
ON MY WAY.
THANKS A LOT.
- THAT WAS MIGHTY
CONSIDERATE OF YOU.
- NO IT WASN'T.
I JUST HAVE A SOFT SPOT
FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE SCARED
BUT STILL GO FOR IT ANYWAY.
- HMM?
- I LIKE IT A LOT.
- WELL, I SURE
DON'T GET SCARED.
AND I'M NOT A BIG "GO FOR
IT ANYWAY" KIND OF GUY.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'RE SO CUTE WHEN
YOU'RE IN DENIAL, YUUJI.
- HUH?
AKIHISA.
- HEY.  EVERYBODY'S
GONNA GO GET CREPES
TO CELEBRATE OUR WIN.
- DID YOU KNOW,
THOSE UPPER CLASSMEN CAME
UP HERE JUST A LITTLE BIT AGO
AND APOLOGIZED TO ME.
THEY DID THAT BECAUSE OF YOU,
DIDN'T THEY?
THAT WAS SWEET.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING
SO DRAMATIC
AND ALWAYS
CAUSING YOU TROUBLE.
- YOU DON'T DO THAT.
( chuckles )
LISTEN, I REALIZE YOU'RE
NOT A PRINCESS, OKAY?
- HUH?
- A PRINCESS WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN STRONG ENOUGH
OR SMART ENOUGH TO STAND UP
TO THOSE GUYS LIKE YOU DID.
- OHH. THAT WASN'T
A BIG DEAL.
- THANKS, HIMEJI.
IT MADE ME REALLY HAPPY.
ON TOP OF THAT, YOU GOT YUUJI
AND ME TO FOCUS FOR ONCE.
- OH, THANK YOU, AKIHISA.
THAT'S SO NICE
OF YOU TO SAY.
- ( chuckles )
YOU WANT TO GET GOING NOW?
I'M PRETTY SURE
THEY'RE WAITING FOR US.
- WAIT, NOT YET.
THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO
ASK YOU ABOUT FIRST.
- SOMETHING LIKE WHAT?
- IT'S, UM... WELL...
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
START CALLING ME MIZUKI
INSTEAD OF HIMEJI
FROM NOW ON?
- WHAT?!
- IT'S JUST THAT YOU'VE BEEN
CALLING MINAMI BY HER
FIRST NAME FOR LIKE EVER.
BUT YOU AND I HAVE
KNOWN EACH OTHER
EVER SINCE WE WERE KIDS,
AND YOU STILL
DON'T CALL ME BY MINE.
- YEAH, BUT THE THING IS
THERE'S A REALLY COMPLICATED
REASON FOR THAT THOUGH.
- BUT WHAT'S SO
COMPLICATED ABOUT IT?
- IT'S JUST THAT YOU AND I...
I MEAN, WE BOTH WENT TO THE SAME
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, RIGHT?
- WE DID.
- SO WHEN I TRY, YOU KNOW,
LIKE SAYING YOUR FIRST NAME,
IT JUST SOUNDS WEIRD IN THE
VOICE I HAVE NOW, THAT'S ALL.
- THAT'S A BIG LIE! SINCE WE
STARTED HIGH SCHOOL TOGETHER
I HAVEN'T HEARD YOU EVEN ONCE
TRY TO CALL ME BY MY FIRST NAME.
- THAT'S, WELL, 'CAUSE--
DON'T LAUGH.
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T LAUGH.
- I PROMISE I WON'T.
- YOU SWEAR?
- I SWEAR IT.
- OKAY, WELL, HERE I GO THEN.
- YEAH?
- I PRACTICE IT AT HOME.
- WHAT?
- IT'S TRUE.
I PRACTICE SAYING
YOUR FIRST NAME.
- OH.
( gasps )
- NO, I WAS JUST KIDDING.
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
( gasps )
- ( giggles )
OKAY.  THEN I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD TELL YOU
A SECRET OF MINE TOO,
SHOULDN'T I?
HERE I GO.
I'VE ALREADY HAD
MY FIRST LOVE.
AND IT'S STILL
GOING STRONG.
LET'S HURRY UP AND GO.
WE DON'T WANT TO BE LATE, DO WE?
- ( gasps ) HOLD ON A SEC,
HIMEJI, WHAT-- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- WHAT THE CRAP, AKI?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME YOU
WERE COMING UP HERE?
- MINAMI?
- YOU PROMISED ME
THAT YOU WOULD STAY BY
MY SIDE FOREVER, YOU JERK.
- ( screams )
- WAIT, WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
- Yuuji: OUT OF MY WAY!
MOVE, AKI!
- ACCORDING TO THE
CONTRACT YOU SIGNED,
IF WE DIDN'T REACH
THE GOAL TOGETHER,
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GET
MARRIED IMMEDIATELY.
- GET HER AWAY FROM ME!
- YUUJI, WAIT FOR ME!
- THERE IS NO ESCAPE.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- YOU HAVE SOME
EXPLAINING TO DO!
- I GUESS IT'S NICE TO KNOW
SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( all shouting )
- WHAT DO YOU GUYS
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
DON'T YOU KNOW THERE'S
NO RUNNING IN THE HALLWAY?!
- ( chuckles )
- AND THERE THOSE
KIDS GO AGAIN.
WHAT A BUNCH OF IDIOTS.