[Roy] The Freezing Alchemist?
Really. He's here?
[Bradley] We have information
that he managed to slip
into Central a few days ago.
That's why I've
summoned you here, Colonel.
I need you and
your men to smoke him out,
and bring him in.
Consider it done, sir.
I'm glad you're with us in
Central for a while, Mustang.
It's good to know I have
people here I can count on.
Sir.
[Bradley] Ah, one last thing.
Our rising young star
is here as well.
I'm placing him at
your disposal.
Forgive me, Fuhrer
Bradley, but...
just to be clear, are
you referring to--?
I am... The Fullmetal Alchemist.
Edward Elric.
Ah, dammit...
The colonel's never gonna let
us get outta here, is he?
[Alfonse] We already
bought our tickets for
Liore, too. Does this
mean we're not going?
I don't know, Al...
For now, let's just get
this over with... OK?
[AL]
Lead the way, brother.
[Military Police 1]
There he goes! That way!
You, halt! Halt
or I'll shoot!
[electric shocks]
[screams]
[running footsteps]
[gun shot]
[grunt]
[Military Police 2] Ahh!
[electric shock]
[muffled grunt]
Water freezes. Water boils...
Either way, you're
just as dead.
[whoosh]
[kerchank]
That's alchemy... [gasp]
[Edward] What a nasty
thing to do.
You of all people should know:
Great deeds require
great sacrifice!
Isn't that the law of
equivalent exchange?!
Save your breath.
The laws of alchemy
don't justify murder!
[magical electric shocks]
[epic morphing sounds]
No transmutation circle...?!
Don't be too impressed...
Now!
[surprised grunt]
[Al] Huh!
[metal impact]
[groan]
[Isaac] Ugh!
[Ed] Yah!
Ugh!
What?!
[whamp]
[Al] Ahh!
No! I had you!
Any water in there
should've boiled!
If it's any consolation,
you did ruin my coat.
An Automail arm...
[cloak swoosh]
A young, gifted alchemist...
One who doesn't use
transmutation circles...
and who has an
automail right arm...!
I know you...
You are the Fullmetal
Alchemist! Edward Elric!
[Isaac] So..it's not you?
Oh, um. No. I'm his
younger brother, Alphonse.
But he's a runt...!
Oh yeah?!
Can a runt do this?!
[electric shocks]
zszzerk
Ooh!
I'd heard the stories, but
still, I never imagined this...
The Fullmetal Alchemist
is just a little kid...!
Don't call me little!
Ooh!
[Al] You know, Brother,
I don't think he was really
talking about your
height just now.
Well, even if he wasn't
he still pissed me off!
So you're the one
we've been hearing
all the stories about lately...
The Fullmetal Alchemist!
You're as good as they
say. Thanks for the help.
[Al] Um, You're
welcome, but...
I'm really not the one you
should be thanking...
There!
C'mon, let's get goin' Al...
We've got a train to catch.
[Al] Oh, okay, if you think
it's alright to leave...
[footsteps]
Ha!
Huh?
[laughter]
[typhoon-force water]
[cough]
What is that? Steam?
[Al]
Brother! He's gone!
Huh!
[Ed] Dammit, now he
really pissed me off!
[Roy] Looks like
you underestimated
your opponent, Fullmetal.
Who is this guy, anyway?
[Roy] You'd know that if you
listened to the briefing
like I told you to...
But no, you had to go
charging right after him--
Yeah, yeah!
I get it, all right?
I'm sorry, 'kay?
Whatever.
Next time a superior tells
you to pay attention,
you might just try it.
[ED]
Fine.
Now then... His
name is Isaac McDougal.
Or, as he was known back in
the day, "Isaac the Freezer."
He's a former
State Alchemist.
[ED]
Former?
[Roy]
That's right...
He served in the
Ishvalan War...
During that time,
he gave us no signs
that he'd turned traitor...
But after.. he immediately
resigned his commission
and went into hiding...
He's been working with
the antiestablishment
movement ever since.
Taking him into custody
is a matter of top priority.
[Roy] Whether it's dead or
alive--that's up to him.
No way. I'm not
killing anyone for you.
[Roy]
And that's your choice...
Your orders are simply
to help us contain him.
That's all.
Hmph... Off topic...
Have you turned up any leads
for getting your bodies
back to normal?
Maybe if you ever
gave us time to look!
Roy! How goes?
Heard you let 'em
put you in charge of
catching the Freezer, huh?
One hell of a nasty assignment...
But hey, could be your chance to
earn that promotion to Central?
Oh, say!.. Looks like my
timing was perfect!
You two are the Elric
brothers, right?
[Ed and Al] Uh-
Wow, it's an honor
to finally meet
the youngest State
Alchemist ever.
You're a real legend
around here...
I'm Lieutenant Colonel
Maes Hughes. A pleasure.
Um, you want Edward.
I'm actually his younger
brother, Alphonse.
What?!.. You're the
Fullmetal Alchemist?
Sorry, I had no
idea you'd be so--
[thinking] Go on,
say "little." I dare you--
[Roy] Hughes.
Yeah?
What are you doing here?
Go home.
Actually...
I'm here on official business.
You. Elrics...
I understand that
you two don't have
a place to stay,
which means you'll
have to come with me.
[Al] Huh?
Ahh!
My wife Gracia and
my daughter Elicia.
We'd love to have you!
Hi, princess...!
[laughter]
Ow!... Daddy,
your beard is itchy!
Like this? Itchy! Itchy!
[wholesome laughter continues]
[Hughes] Look! We have guests!
These are the Elric brothers.
Big brother!
Little brother!
Urg!
Nice to meet you.
My name is Edward Elric...
This is my younger brother,
Alphonse Elric...
Get that?...
Youn..ger..bro..ther!
[Elicia]
But younger means little.
You're little!
[steam]
Where do you get
off ...!
[Al] Just let it go, Ed.
These people are being
nice to let us stay here.
[Hughes] Hope you
boys are hungry.
Gracia's cooking is delicious.
[Ed] Whoa...!
[Elicia giggling]
[Hughes] Ok, eat up.
Thanks...!
[Ed]
Wow, you weren't kidding!
This's great!
[Gracia] Don't be shy,
eat all you want!
[Ed]
O-K!
Alphonse, how're you gonna
eat wearing that armor?
Take it off, relax!
[Al] W-well,
you see, uh...
He's not allowed to!
He has to wear it
all the time!...
It's, uh--
It's part of
his alchemy training!
You know how it is...
But I'll eat enough for
both of us...!
Training! Ch-choo!
[wind blowing]
whoooooo
[evil laughter]
bwahaha
[Kimblee] Hands down,
that's got to be the funniest
joke I've heard in
a long, long time.
The Freezing Alchemist
wants me to
come play his sidekick.
Well, as fun as that sounds--
The Crimson Alchemist
works alone.
I always have.
[Isaac] Kimblee.
If we work together,
we can bring down Bradley
and his god-forsaken military!
You saw the horrors that
took place in Ishval...
You were there, dammit!
You know the things
Bradley ordered us to do,
the kind of man
he really is!...
That's why you killed all
those officers, isn't it?
To send him a message?
[Kimblee laughs]
I think you've got
me all wrong.
My motives
aren't so sophisticated
as "revenge" or "honor"
or any of that...
The reason I killed
all of those men...
...was because I could.
It's that simple.
[Isaac] That's too
bad, Kimblee...
That truly is too bad.
[door squeaking open]
oooh-eeeee
[door slamming shut]
ker-shut
Keep up the good work.
[crash and shatter]
crashatter
[Hughes] Huh?
[Gracia] Maes, dear.
What's wrong?
Can't sleep?
Guess not.
I know what's in
that head of yours.
Hm?
You're worrying about
those boys, aren't you?
[sigh]
You do know what they call
State Alchemists, right?...
"the Dogs of the Military"
not exactly the most
popular bunch...
When I try to imagine
what that must be like,
enduring that at his age...
Hmm...
[Al] Brother...? You awake?
Huh?
[Al]
Miss Gracia's quiche...
It looked a lot
like Mom's, huh?
[Ed] Yeah. Almost
as good, too.
Really?!.. In that case,
I'm definitely adding it
to the list of things I'm gonna
eat once I get my body back.
Right! Put it on there!
Right near the top!
[Al] Brother...?
[Ed] Hmmm?
[Al] I sure would like to
get our old bodies back soon...
[Ed] I know. Me too.
[chalk scraping]
[footstep]
[Isaac] One more... One more,
and "Fuhrer" Bradley's
on his way to hell.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Roy] We have a confirmed report
that McDougal broke into
Central Prison last night.
Whatever he's up to,
he's growing bold...
That means our time is short.
[murmurs]
[Roy] Close off all roads,
search every square
inch of the city.
[Roy] When you find
him, shoot on sight...
That is an order from
the Fuhrer himself.
[Roy] But if I find him first...
He's mine.
[Soldier A] Get a medic!...
Hurry!
[Soldier B] Report to
headquarters! Five men dead!
[Al] How awful.
It Looks like a
steam explosion...
Raise the temperature
of water fast enough,
it expands with the
force of a bomb blast.
...and the human body is
70-percent water.
Let's hurry.. We
have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
[chalk scraping]
Finished.
Huh?
[electric rumbling]
[Armstong] Impressive
reflexes, Isaac.
Few are able to dodge
my alchemy so easily!
I know that voice!
Is that you, Armstrong?!
[Armstong] Indeed! None other!
♪ Adventure Strings ♪
[Armstong] It is I! The
Strong Arm Alchemist...
Alex Louis Armstrong,
in the flesh!
Ah..Shut it!
[rushing water]
[Isaac] I've always wanted to
chop that ego down to size!
Heeyaaah!
Except you'll need far
more than water...
to quench my fists!
[explosions]
[Edward & Alphonse] Huh?
[surprised sigh]
[earth settling]
[Al] Major!
Huh?
Arg!
[Al] Look out!
[splashy explosion]
[run steps]
Water from his canteen, huh?...
Thanks for the quick save, Al.
[Al] Let's go.
He's getting away!
Come then!
After me, Elric brothers!
[Both] Right!
[car engines]
[whitsling wind]
[Roy] It's been
a long time, Freezer.
[Isaac] Well, Roy Mustang...
So the Flame Alchemist
came out to play?
[Roy] You can make this
easy on both of us.
I'd rather not fight
an old war buddy.
War buddy?
Please, don't flatter yourself.
I knew no friends in Ishval...
Only military bastards
and their damn dogs!
[explosion]
Ugh!
[All] Huh?
[splash]
garble garble
When water meets flame...
the flame goes out.
[footsteps]
Dammit...!
[moving stones and happiness]
Still there! Perfect!
Stop! Right there!
I was wondering what you
were doing in this alley,
so I came back to check
it out--and bingo.
[maniacal laughter]
[Al] There's nowhere
to run this time!
Clearly... But who's running?
[low hum and electroshocks]
[shocked gasp]
[awe-ful gasp]
[magical hum]
[Ed] An alchemic reaction...
on this scale...
[Al] Impossible... unless...
you don't think he's--?
A Philosopher's Stone!
[whistling wind]
He's freezing all the
moisture in the air...
[Isaac] Edward Elric!
You've sworn your
life to the state as
a Dog of the Military...
But do you really know
the ones you serve?
Or what their true plans are?
Who cares?!
It's not my problem!
Don't be a fool!
He'll lead us all to ruin!
I'm only doing what
needs to be done!
I told you! I don't care!
Ugh!
[punches and kicks]
Oo-ogh!
[rolling grunts]
[defeated sigh]
[Ed] All right! Nice work, Al!
[Al] But we still have
to stop his alchemy!
[Ed] I know.
So where is it?! You have a
Philosopher's Stone, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I won't ask again! Where is it?!
And what are you
going to do, boy?...
You're out of your league!
[wrathful water]
[gasp]
[bad guy laugh]
[breaking earth]
Stand back!
And prepare for a display
of Armstrong alchemy!
[Ed] He's all yours, Major!
Witness the alchemic arts
passed down the Armstrong line
for generations!
[explosion]
That's unexpected...
What the heck're you doing?!
You're making it worse!
Oh, I was merely...
[shaken yells]
[explosions]
[Al] The ice walls...
They're merging.
But... that would mean...
[Ed] If they all meet
in the middle--
Ah, dammit! It's
Central Command!
[Ed & Al] He's going
to freeze it over!
Major! Al and I'll try
to slow him down!
Can you handle the
transmutation circles?
Consider them erased!
I'm on it!
[rumbling]
Fuhrer King Bradley...! For your
cold-blooded crimes in Ishval,
I condemn you to a frozen hell!
[Ed] Not so fast!
[grunt]
[electroshocks]
[fightin' strings music]
[clanging armor & tribal drums]
Two can play that game!
[ice crubling]
Ah!
[unintelligible panicking]
[electric ice footsteps]
[Al] Brother!
[Isaac] Too slow!
[electroshocks]
Alphonse!
[grunt]
[powerful whoosh]
There's no one in there.
It's empty...!
But that... that
could only be true
if his soul was bonded
to the armor...
So you lost your arm...
and your brother...
he lost his entire body...
Heh! I see...
it all makes sense...
You fools committed
the ultimate taboo!
You attempted human
transmutation, didn't you?!
Alchemy's one and only
unforgiveable sin!
[Ed] Al!
[Ed] Dammit!
This can't be happening!
NO!
He's gone! What have I done?!
♪ Sad Music ♪
[Ed] Give him back!...
He's my brother!
Just give him back.
He's my little brother!
He's all I have left!
[magical eagle screech]
You know...
There are some lines you
really shouldn't cross.
Huh?
[fierce hits]
[ice dagger crunching]
[ice shattering]
Ha!
[hard core kick]
Ooh!
[bouncing]
[ice slide]
[landing grunt]
[hurting groans]
[Ed] Give it up. There's
no water for you to use here.
Heh! You've forgotten something...
I have all the water I need...
70-percent of my body!
[shocked gasp]
[magical explosion]
[Al] Ed!
[pained gasp]
Why can't you fools
understand?
I'm trying to save
this country!
[heavy earth crumbling]
[mad laughter]
[Al] Brother. Brother!
[Ed] Come on...
We're going after him.
I'm not done...
Not even close.
[explosions]
Boom! Bang! Boom!
[Combat Engineer A]
Did we get it?
[Combat Engineer B]
Not again...!
[mad breathing]
[huge explosion]
What do you think of my
flames now?! You bastard!
When will he learn...
It's bad enough that he's
useless on rainy days...
[stumbling]
[Isaac] Bradley...!
[exhausted breathing
and laughter]
Perfect!
[magical morphing]
[insane laughter]
[maniacal tongues]
[rabid laughter and yells]
[liquid explosion]
[dying grunts]
[Kimblee] Now that is too bad...
[explosion]
Major...! Go! Now!
Leave it to me! The Armstrong
fist will not fail!
[ground crumbling]
[surprised gasps]
[Ed] Fuhrer Bradley.
You're here?
Ah, yes... Job well
done, Fullmetal.
I came out to see if I could
lend a hand... And to think--!
that I'd actually be
the one to catch him!
If nothing else,
this should make an
exciting story for my son?
[sparrows spritely singing]
[sneeze]
[Hughes] Ew, that a cold I
hear? Ah, nevermind...
From what I'm told, you're
the man of the hour!
[Roy] Nah, I just destroyed
the transmutation circles...
The Fuhrer is the one who
actually brought down McDougal.
[Hughes] Sure. But the Fuhrer's
telling everyone it was you.
So congratulations!
[Hughes] Oh, it's like that,
huh? Suit yourself.
But some friendly advice--next
time a superior tells you
to take credit for
something you didn't do,
you might try it for once.
[Al] You know, we never
did find out whether
or not he had a
Philosopher's Stone...
No, but...
maybe it'll say something
in the official report...
[door opens]
[Armstrong] Greetings,
Edward Elric...
When I heard you were
here in the hospital...
I dashed right over!
[shocked gasps]
And as I suspected,
you are in desperate
need of my assistance!
[screams of horror]
[Armstrong] You need the example
of a perfect physical specimen
to inspire your
recovery! You see?
You're looking
livelier already!
[Ed] Will you get out?!
Ah... I see,
so Isaac's dead, is he?
That's a shame. I had such
high hopes for him, too...
But--the Philosopher's Stone?
♪ Dissonant Strings ♪
Sounds like he overused it.
[disgusting chewing]
Gluttony... Try to chew quietly.
I'm on the phone.
[chewing continues]
Yes, things are going
well here in Liore.
We'll be ready. It all begins.
Very soon.
[Narrator]
Resembool. A quiet town.
The place where Edward
and Alphonse were born.
The home they once shared
with their mother.
In the hopes of returning
to happier times,
the boys commit the
ultimate taboo,
and are forced to
confront the truth.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode 2. The First Day.
The day they resolved their
hearts to begin the journey.