Hey, there! It's time for Kaleido Star!
When you watch Kaleido Star, please
keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Does everyone
like amusement parks?
Merry-go-rounds and roller coasters!
They thrill you and make
your heart skip a beat.
They're fun, aren't they?
Our show is performed in a different
space from a regular stage.
In order for everyone to enjoy our show,
we will give it everything we've got!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Dare mo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Dokoka ni aru
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja nai
Saigo made yareru to ittetane
Kitto tsuyogatte itanda
Itsudatte muchabakka de zutto karamawari de
Dakedo anata dake ga soba ni ita
Daremo sagashiteru yume wa kitto aru
Arukidaseru
Koko kara nanika ga hajimaru
Shinjite itai
Mada minu hikari yakusoku
no basho e to tsuzuite yuku
Negai ga itsuka kanau made hitori ja naisa
Who? Who's that?
She's amazing.
She nailed everyone's
attention in an instant.
There's only one who's capable
of doing something like this...
"The Amazing Mystery Star."
So under these conditions,
I would like to make a contract
with all members of Freedom Lights.
What do you think everyone?
We got a job! We did it!
We're looking forward to working for you!
I'm counting on you.
Especially on that Masked Star.
What?
That masked...
Well, she is really incredible.
What would you say if I suggest that you
drastically increase the Masked Star's time?
But... that Masked Star is...
I understand.
We will definitely consider
what you just said.
I'm counting on you.
What are you going to do,
saying something like that?
She's right.
We don't know who that Masked Star is.
You want to patch things up for
the moment by using a substitute?
It's not necessary.
What?
'Cause I know the identity of
that Masked Star is Miss Layla.
Miss Layla is not here right now.
What? Then do you know about
what time she'll be home?
She left here for Europe about
a week ago for a movie shoot.
What? Europe?
Isn't there some kind of mistake?
No. Excuse me, but I have to go now.
I cannot believe this.
Then that Masked Star is...
As we were saying, we have
to use a substitute tomorrow.
You're right.
Since someone caused all this...
I think we have to ask her to do it.
Here, wear this.
Tada!
You look good.
It was worth staying up all night making it.
But the difference in height is way too much.
That's what I thought. So I brought these.
I can't wear something like that and perform.
Hey, let's try to contact
Miss Layla one more time.
She's in Europe.
Going over there is ten hours one way.
It's impossible, Sora.
Um.... Then why don't we tell
the Park Owner the truth?
That the Masked Star is not
a member of Freedom Lights.
And you're going to risk losing
the contract by doing that?
Good morning.
Hey, listen... Hmm?
Rosetta.
Why is the Masked Star here?
She looks different, somehow.
Oh... No... It's not her. Rosetta, it's me.
Sora...
Rosetta, tell them there's no way I
can substitute for the Masked Star!
Sora is going to substitute
for the Masked Star?
Yes...
Oh, I never realized that
we can use that trick.
Here, look at today's newspaper.
What? This is about yesterday...
"The amusement park where I
went with my family by chance.
There, they were performing a wonderful show
as good as anything you'd see in Las Vegas.
The performance of the Masked
Star who appeared for the finale
was especially bold and elegant.
When I thought I was able to see a show
like that just for the price of admission,
it really moved me."
Oh, no...
Because of this article,
we may have more customers.
That's impossible! It was just yesterday.
We have plenty of time until
the Masked Star's show starts.
Please don't push. Please
enter slowly in order.
All these people came to see the Masked Star?
Now what are we gonna do?
I didn't know you were here.
Thanks to you, this is the biggest crowd
we've ever had since we opened this park.
Owner...
That's nice.
This is all thanks to that
Masked Star right there.
No, not at all.
We're also glad we could help you.
That's also what this Masked Star is saying.
Hmm? I don't know why, but doesn't
she look different from yesterday?
It's just your imagination.
Hmm... I wonder if it's my imagination.
Well, anyway, we also
have a TV reporter today.
So make sure to give us a nice show.
A TV reporter?!
Resign yourself to it, Sora.
A flying jellyfish girl!
It's not popular.
Here I go! Yeah!
Wow... Amazing!
It's awesome!
The Masked Star is late.
Yeah, she is.
Daddy, where's the Masked Star?
Isn't it about the time she shows up?
Yes, it's about time.
Is it time yet?
Who knows?
It's the Masked Star!
Close-up!
Yes.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Something is... different.
What?
Oh, I wish the real one would show up...
Masked Star! Masked Star! Masked
Star! Masked Star! Masked Star!
I have no choice but to just do it!
Just do it! Just do it!
Ouch! Ouch! Huh? Oh...
She's a fake.
Disappointed...
It was a waste of time to
come all the way down here.
We're looking forward to your next visit.
The real Masked Star will
appear for sure tomorrow.
I hope you're telling me the truth.
So tomorrow, she will be here.
Yes, of course.
So please make sure to advertise our park.
I can't believe this.
I can't have you doing this!
Well, to tell you the truth...
I don't want to hear your excuses!
If the Masked Star doesn't show up tomorrow,
I'm going to cancel the contract!
And you're going to pay for the forfeit!
Capisci?!
Did you come up with any good ideas?
Not at all.
I think...
Yes, yes.
That Masked Star is Miss
Layla. Don't you think?
So that's what you were thinking?
I never realized you were so tenacious.
No matter what you think, it's impossible.
Who else could it be?
I can't guess who she is, but...
'Cause Miss Layla...
Even if Kaleido Stage closes its door,
it cannot close the door to my future.
It will not be my last
show, unless I wish it.
I think that's the way
Miss Layla really feels.
There's no way I have time
for anything like that.
First of all, my father is
managing my schedule right now.
At that time, Miss Layla looked like she
was forcing herself to act that way.
That's why I thought she came
back as the Masked Star.
But I wonder if I'm wrong
like everybody else says.
Well, then, I'm afraid we
have to use the last resort.
What last resort?
We're going to make the show get canceled.
What?
How?
We're going to pray for rain!
Rain, Rain. Please rain. Please rain.
Rain, rain. Rain, rain, rain.
Drop rain. Drop rain. Drop rain.
Katsu!
It's a nice day.
Once we get a clear day,
there's nothing we can do.
Here, pull yourself together, and go.
All right...
If you're worried about the
forfeit, you don't need to worry.
It's not an amount we can pay easily anyway.
Once you come to terms with the fact that
you'll be paying it back the rest of your lives
it'll be no big deal.
Well... You're not encouraging at all.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning Kate.
Don't they look wobbly?
Don't worry. They're just a little depressed.
Really?
By the way, what's wrong with
the current Kaleido Stage?
There haven't been any
injuries for a long time now.
It seems that is the way Yuri does things.
He's controlling all dangerous
performances by computer.
Hmmm, so that's why.
But without any chance
to show off her skills,
I can understand why Miss Layla doesn't
want to come back to Kaleido Stage.
Yeah, I know.
But as an emergency doctor,
I don't have a chance to
utilize my skills either.
All right now, I'm sure the
Masked Star will show up today.
Thirty more minutes until the show starts.
Until our life ends...
Thirty more minutes.
Oh, dear...
Hey, everyone!
'Cause unless the Masked Star
shows up, our show will end today.
And we will have the fate of paying
back the enormous forfeit fee.
Hey, these kids want to get some autographs.
Autographs?
I see.
I'm sorry, but the Masked Star has
some business to take care of, and...
No.
I want an autograph from that person.
Me?
Yes.
Thank you.
I had so much fun. Right, brother?
We saw the show for the first
time the day before yesterday.
So you guys came back here again.
Yes. Well, my brother didn't have
enough money for the admission fee.
So he got an advance on his allowance.
He begged Mom a lot, saying
that he would pay her back
by mowing the lawn for the next month.
Melissa, you don't have
to tell them all that!
But he paid for mine too.
So I'm going to help him mow the lawn.
Right?
You don't need to do anything.
If you help me, you'll end up
increasing what I need to get done.
I'm a big girl.
I can do all kinds of stuff by myself.
They're looking forward to
seeing my show this much.
All right, both of you.
Today's show will be a lot
more fun than the last.
I'll give you a show worth more
than a whole month of lawn mowing.
Wow!
Good luck!
Please have fun watching the show.
I can’t believe you promised that.
I bet you'll end up disappointing them.
No, I won't. I'll never disappoint them.
I won't allow myself to disappoint them.
So I think we have no choice
but to do our best now.
Even though we don't have
the Masked Star with us,
let's make our show satisfying
for the audience.
Either way, we have to pay for the forfeit.
So why don't we let ourselves go and perform?
Yep.
Mia, don't you have any ideas?
Something we can prepare in
the next fifteen minutes...
Okay, I will come up with something.
Also, each of us should try to think if
there is anything we can do better than yesterday.
Yes.
Oh...
Did you come up with something?
Wait.
If it takes five seconds for each...
Good! Maybe, we can do this!
Ken, Marion, please help.
What? What?
We can take care of this.
I hope it starts soon.
I want to see the...
They're late.
It's already past the starting time.
I hope you're not telling
me that they took off.
There's no way...
Here they go!
Here!
I can't see.
This way!
Hey! There!
Someone's there!
The Masked Star?
No, that's not her.
Over there!
Hey, don't miss that photo op.
Yes.
Brother...
Let's go Melissa!
What?
It says "Keep out"!
Don't worry.
I wonder if those kids are watching.
The Masked Star!
Finally!
Bravo!
No matter what I think, there is
only one person who can do this.
That is...
I'm scared.
Be a big girl.
Those kids!
Call a rescue team quick!
Yes!
The ladder is ready to fall off.
What?
Oh, I know! I should use the rope.
Help!
I'm scared!
All right...
Okay...
The Masked Star is here.
You go first, Melissa.
What about you?
I'm your big brother. So I will go next.
Melissa, go!
Okay.
Miss!
You're okay now.
She's going to crash!
Hold on tight.
Oh... Shoot...
If I stay like this,
I don't know where I'm going to hit.
Good.
I'm glad...
Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
What?
The identity of the Masked
Star is... as I thought...
I can't think of anybody
else other than Miss Layla.
Elegant performance, strong movement...
They're the same as Miss Layla.
This feeling traveling through me,
and everything else is
the same as Miss Layla's.
I believe that the Masked Star is Miss Layla.
If Miss Layla is with us,
I think creating our own
Kaleido Stage is possible.
Not only that... I think
I'm able to do anything.
One day... without that mask,
I hope we can appear on stage together again.
One day...
The Chariot...
The opportunity is right.
The only thing left is going forward.
It seems the show in the amusement
park is beating our show.
Our show is, like, showy
using computers and stuff.
But, like, it makes the show kinda fake.
But, of course, it makes my job easy.
And, of course, I don't need
to worry about injuries either.
Oh...
Let's practice, practice.
In this way, a brother and
sister were rescued safely.
Later, both Sora Naegino and the Masked
Star who performed after this incident
Damned Masked Star...
won applause from all the audience
That is...
"Next Kaleido Star"
Yuri, thank you for the flowers.
And so, Freedom Lights' performance
is on the right track, but...
But Yuri started meddling in
our business again, and...
It seems he's intent on
completely destroying us.
And the mysterious Masked Star.
When the Masked Star's mask is removed,
the things reflected in her eyes are...
are... are...
Next time on Kaleido Star, "The
Amazing Resolve Beneath the Mask."
My wings are my dream and
on towards the sky...
Boku wa koko ni iru sora to
michi no aida de mukai kaze
Soshite mae o muiteiru mou nido
to kanashimi ga furanai youni to
Ano kabe o koete kokomade kitanda
Nigedashitaku naru koto wa nando mo aru
Dakedo kokoni irunara taishite bibitte inai
Kakinaguri no uta "hajimekara yareba iisa"
Umaku kakenakute boku wa waratte iru