They've finally been gathered...
The three Princess Precures!
Oh, Minami looks as beautiful as ever!
Kirara is as radiant as the sun!
And her...
It's like she's in a garden...
where she's the only flower that's still a bud.
Who's she?
A bud...
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
This secondary student council room is rarely used,
so don't worry about anyone coming.
The day has finally come for me to use this!
Hey, isn't that...
Indeed, this is Hope Kingdom's legendary treasure!
It's known as the Princess Lesson Pad!
It's a special pad that only princesses are allowed to use!
We were protecting it in this Princess Bag!
Haruka, Minami, Kirara,
today begins your Princess Lessons!
Princess Lessons?
You'll need it...
to become the Grand Princess!
Grand... Princess?
Your First Lesson!
Aim to be the Grand Princess!
Strength...
Grace...
And beauty!
Beauty!
The ultimate princess!
That is the Grand Princess!
If you all work hard, you can become Grand Princesses!
Ultimate...
I'll do it!
I totally wanna be a Grand Princess!
I'll learn everything I can from this Princess Lesson!
So, we Princess Precures have to do
more than simply defeat Dyspairvils.
We have to become those Grand Princesses, too?
Indeed!
Academics, athletics, fine art,
gourmet, etiquette, and fashion...
A true princess must study to become a Renaissance woman of culture!
That is what the Princess Lessons teach!
Now, let's call our lesson's teacher.
Teacher?
First, remove the stylus from the pad.
You mean this?
Now point the stylus at the heart and twirl it!
Like this?
Bonjour, mademoiselles!
I am your professeure royal, Madame Siamour!
A cat?
She's so cute!
Vous three are ma élèves de princesse.
Now, may I ask pourquoi have you not greeted me?
Bonjour, Madame Siamour!
Bonjour...
Ah, très bien.
Alors, ma princesses,
let us commençons le lesson!
A tea set?
And biscuits!
This is an English-style thé de l'après-midi, correct?
Oui.
Thé de l'après-midi?
Tch, tch, tch!
It means a tea party in the afternoon.
A tea party?
For la princesse, not offering
la invitée tea is a big non non!
That is la forme of hospitality
known as le thé de l'après-midi!
Now, let's essayons la proper technique for pouring tea!
Okay!
The cups and pots are splendid!
A princess tea party...
Why'd you just pour in water?
Heating the cup with hot water
keeps the tea warm and delicious.
Kirara, that's incredible!
Pouring from such a height causes the force of the water to open the tea leaves, so it's more fragrant.
Oh, you two are excellent!
Mais...
Haruka, what're you doing?
Uh, um...
First, pour the tea leaves into the pot!
Why aren't they coming out?
'Cause the lid's still on.
Oh!
I'm sorry, Aroma!
Oh, non...
Vous are still but a bud of la princesse.
Perhaps vous should practice opening lids first.
I will...
I got called a bud again...
That concludes today's lesson.
We'll meet again for your next one.
Bonne journée!
Good job, girls!
I'm just hopeless...
Oh, Princess of Flowers, you're ever so far away...
Huh?
Wasn't Cure Flora the Princess of Flowers?
Oh, not that!
Uh...
She's a princess that shows up in my favorite fairy tale.
I've wanted to be like her since I was little.
I know that story as well.
Ah, so that's where your dream came from.
Yeah, but I totally flubbed the lesson...
Can I ever be like her?
Aroma, Perf.
That voice...
It's Sir Kanata!
Sir Kanata!
A hologram?
I'm sorry for taking so long to contact you.
There are few chances for me to send a transmission under Dysdark's nose.
I can't speak long,
but are you all safe?
Yes! And seeing you well puts my own heart at ease!
Thank you, Aroma.
Kanata...
Haruka...
Is it really you?
Yes.
It's been quite a while, Haruka.
Or should I say, Princess Haruka?
Sir Kanata, this is Cure Mermaid, Minami!
This is Cure Twinkle, Kirara!
Bonjour.
A pleasure to meet you.
I am Prince Hope Grand Kanata.
I must apologize for involving you all in this.
Well, it's kinda late for that.
But I do have a few questions.
About what we should do...
and who they are.
Dysdark.
That is the name of the dark army
lead by the Witch of Woe, Dyspear.
My land of Hope Kingdom fell into their hands.
And then...
everyone in the kingdom had their dreams stolen and sealed within cages of despair.
Their dreams were stolen?
Why would they do that?
I don't know Dyspear's intentions...
but stealing another's dreams is a crime that nobody can be forgiven of.
And I...
failed to stop them.
Sir Kanata, you're still in the kingdom battling Dyspear!
Kanata!
Tell us what we can do!
Ask us anything!
We'll help however we can.
Thank you.
Princess Precures...
there are two things I must ask of you.
The first is to gather all twelve of the Dress Up Keys.
Twelve?
There are that many?
Yes.
Long ago,
the ancient Precures used sacred treasures to dispel the darkness.
Those were the Dress Up Keys.
With the power of all twelve Keys,
I'm sure we'll be able to break through the Gate of Despair.
The Dress Up Keys were once under Hope Kingdom's supervision.
The Keys are our final hope.
As such, Dyspear views them as a hindrance.
They planned to seek the Keys out and destroy them.
But just then...
the Dress Up Keys lit up and flew away...
to the world where you all live.
We need both the twelve Keys and the power of the Precures to stand against Dyspear.
That's why I gave Perf and Aroma the Perfumes capable of drawing out a Key's power
and had them flee the kingdom.
I prayed for them to revive the Princess Precures...
And that's when we met you girls!
You've each already found your own Keys.
That leaves nine left.
Dyspear is also searching for the Keys.
She plans to destroy the Keys
and envelop the world in despair!
Close.
I see you allowed the Princess Precures to return.
How foolish.
Lady Dyspear, there is naught but to entrust this to me.
I will naught but prove my ability to
defeat the Precures and find every Key.
No, send me!
I'll whoop those tossers next time!
Next time?
If there is one.
I've already sent Lock.
Lock?!
Yes, the final of the Three Dusketeers.
What a drag, 'kay?
Close, Shut...
we don't need you now that I'm here, 'kay?
Show me your dream, 'kay?
I'm gonna play in the majors!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
So you've appeared again...
Kanata?
What?
Dysdark has made a move.
Most likely against you, as well.
Could it be a Dyspairvil?
I must go as well.
Wait!
We've only heard one of your requests!
Tell us what else we should do!
The Grand Princess.
Once all the keys have been gathered,
it takes someone special to unleash their true power.
That would be the Grand Princess.
To save everyone's dreams, please become...
a Grand Princess.
Do I... have what it takes?
You do.
That day, I was led to you by the Dress Up Key.
It was long before Dysdark ever appeared,
so why did that key alone fly to you?
I know not the answer,
but I do know this.
The Dress Up Key chose you.
I'm happy to see that you're still the same girl I met that day.
You held your dream close to your heart.
Thank you.
I'm certain we'll meet again.
Yeah!
Now go!
Protect the dreams of your people, Princess Precures!
Right!
We'll meet again, right, Kanata?
If you believe deep down that we will, I'm certain.
Sir Kanata!
Please take care!
Kanata, I promise I'll become a Grand Princess!
Dyspairvil!
And I'll protect everyone's dreams!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspair! Vil! Vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair! Vil!
'Kay, I see.
So you three are the Princess Precures, 'kay?
You look kinda lame to be the Princess of Flowers.
Wh-Who are you?!
Dyspairvilllllll!
Flora!
I may still be a bud...
But Kanata gave me courage!
So I promise you...
I'll make my dream bloom!
Dyspairvil!
That was great, Flora!
Our little Flora's no pansy!
Late bloomers always have the largest blossoms!
Dyspairvil!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Now's your chance!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
That was all right, 'kay?
You again!
The name's Lock.
I was just sayin' hello, 'kay?
See ya, Princess of Buds.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Let's find the nine remaining Dress Up Keys.
And become Grand Princesses, too.
It's a promise, okay?
Yeah.
Kanata, I'll make my dream bloom!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Don't tell me I have to pair with him for the tennis tournament!
Go! Princess Precure:
Reunited by Tennis!
My Old Bully?!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hyougo Prefecture - Yuuki (Age 5)
Ibaraki Prefecture - Rin (Age 5)