THE POWER OF ANIMATION
Sound of the Skies
Does the light of the sky reach your heart?
The melody we dreamed of was serene.
Even though the dream is so far from you
Try to recall that gentle voice.
Someone's singing a graceful chord for you.
May the sound of the skies resound,
overcoming sadness with all its might.
Only the real world reflects in your eyes.
Don't let your tears form any more.
Within the overflowing light,
may you play out the morrow.
Rio!
Good work!
Find it?
Yeah, we got it!
You can find anything here.
It's so warm!
I feel so much better.
But, Rio, were you on yard duty today?
There was something
I wanted to burn.
It's been six months since Kanata
came to the fortress.
She's gotten pretty good.
She has a good teacher.
Ow. That's hot.
I guess I can finally put
away those earplugs...
Hey, madam, shouldn't you
stay in town this winter?
I'm fine.
I won't kick the bucket that easy.
I've been living alone on this
mountain for fifty years.
A Departure • The First Snow
Go. Go. Go. Stop!
It's finally starting to
look like a real tank.
You can take care of the rest
yourself, right, Noël?
Yes. I'm happy.
Then let's go get some tea.
Yeah.
Hey, Kureha...
Huh?
Where did it go?
It should be here...
Oh, my. What's wrong?
The army almanac is
around here, isn't it?
Kanata wanted to know
about Princess Iliya.
I'm sorry.
If it isn't there, I can't help you.
Darn...
Naomi might have one!
I'll ask her next time we see her.
OK!
Princess Iliya is the eldest daughter
of the current Archduke Arkadia.
I think I already told you,
but she's a really famous tanker!
Claus was saying things would be
different if she were alive.
Yeah, she passed away.
Hmm, about two years ago...
In the war?
No.
She was assigned to
the royal guard,
but military parades and stuff were also part of
her job, so she'd travel around the country.
On her way to a city, she tried to save
a child drowning in a river...
But I feel relieved.
It's just a rumor, but...
Iliya...
Kanata!
Yumina, and...
Um, it's Kanata.
Um...Yumina...uh,
brought Yuuko...
Yuuko is the daughter of Martin
and, um, a lady named Jacott...
She lives alone in
the mountains...
I sometimes buy vegetables and
stuff from her at the market.
Oh, I know! You said you liked
those pickled vegetables, right?
She's the one who made them.
Anyway, uh, lately
no one's seen her,
and she's kind of frail,
so they're worried.
She lives deep in the mountains,
and...
Fine! Fine!
I'll listen to what you have to say,
so wait just a second.
OK!
People were saying
she was going to marry
the emperor
of the holy city, Rome, to improve
relations with them.
But she'd have been
his third wife!
The third!
No way, right?
So basically, she'd have
been a hostage, right?
But that stopped once she died,
and we fought them until
this year's peace treaty.
Geez, we're finally here...
A newly built house?
Didn't she supposedly live alone?
That's what I heard.
Madam!
I see... Yuuko sent you.
Yes.
She's such a kind girl.
She's too good for that
runny-nosed Martin.
This is a really nice house.
Thank you.
I built this house.
Wow!
Then what about that
one over there?
It was for my son...
You have a son?
He lives in a far away city now,
but I keep it ready for him.
I have to keep it nice and
clean, so my son and them
can use it whenever they want.
When will your son
be home, madam?
He'll be here soon.
Winter is what's coming soon.
You should leave the mountain
before the first snow.
I can't.
I have to finish that house.
I won't leave for any reason
until it's done.
But...
Don't be stupid!
Are you ready for winter?
Do you have firewood?
Provisions?
You're not ready at all!
It will work out.
Thanks for worrying, ladies.
Madam!
What a stubborn old lady!
She's just like you, I bet.
Quiet.
Why would I...
Sometimes you won't listen
to anyone else, either,
even when you know you should.
Shut up!
Hey, that letter...
Why show it to me?
I heard this in last week's
communications,
but the Roman army on the Eastern
border has started moving.
So these are for old
lady Jacott, huh?
OK! Take these, too!
Thank you!
By the way,
do you know what's going on
with the peace talks?
I... I'm sorry.
If only Princess Iliya
were still alive...
By the way, Martin, didn't Princess Iliya
have a younger sister?
And your 4,000,000 change!
That's the first I've heard of it.
Well, she's not really a legitimate child,
so no one talks about it.
She's third in line to the
throne or something.
Um, that little sister...
Bye!
Thanks!
Thank you.
Want to take a walk?
Hey, Kanata...
What kind of place was the village
where you were born?
Just a normal country village.
There were fields and goats and cows,
but not many people.
It's not like this place.
But it was a nice place, I bet.
And you had good parents.
I can tell by looking at you.
What kind of place did
you grow up in?
I grew up in a small village near the capital,
with pretty lakes and forests.
I lived there with my mom.
It was boring. Nothing ever happened.
My one comfort was my sister,
who loved me very much.
She was only my half-sister, but she would
come and play with me sometimes.
I always looked up to her.
She was beautiful and kind.
And she accepted her
fate with pride.
I learned the trumpet from her.
But she was too kind...
And that became her undoing.
The first time I came here,
I thought this town was like a labyrinth.
I got lost and ended up here,
but I felt like I'd finally reached my goal.
But I noticed later, that this
was just a dead end.
That's not true!
I get lost all the time.
But I like to get lost!
Who cares if you were lost?!
Or if it's a dead end?!
That's how I met you!
At times, I'm jealous
of you, Kanata.
If only I could be so
true to myself.
This'll do it.
Why are you so worried
about me?
You remind me of my mother.
I never had a pretty girl like you.
I was born from a forbidden love.
My mother always waited for him.
He might come by once a year.
And then she died,
still living unhappily like that.
Why do you think that
she was unhappy?
But-
I'm quite happy here.
He promised he'd come back.
He promised he'd come get me.
For me, that's enough.
But...
What else could I have done?
That's right.
If there had been something else
I could've done, I might have.
But you know...
Is that enough for you?
Are you really happy?
Because I have my memories of them.
I have my memories of them
and the hope that I will see them again.
That's enough.
It's more than enough.
I thought it was getting cold.
It was on a snowy night like
this that I first met you...
When Madam was young,
Seize was a famous resort city.
She fell in love with a young man
who was a rich merchant's heir.
And soon, she came to bear his child.
But he already had a family.
For good or ill, the man's own
wife never had a child,
so he took her child
and went home.
He promised he'd someday
come for her.
Now that I'm old, I sometimes
think to myself... What if...
Life is losing things,
one after another.
But to have lost, you must
first have gained.
And the greater your joy at your gain,
the greater your sorrow at your loss. But...
But if you have the memories
of your happiness...
With those memories, you can live on.
Oh, right.
This may not be the time, but I found that
picture of Princess Iliya you wanted.
Naomi!
Filicia, it's OK.
I guess it would be from
five years ago,
when she visited Seize.
Is that Shuko?
Rio!
I think my parents wanted me to marry
and inherit the household.
But I was entranced by the
sound of that trumpet.
And I couldn't forget it.
That was Iliya, wasn't it?
I knew it. You met her, too.
Her music welled up within me.
It was so wonderful.
And you and I met.
I think I ran away to this town,
so at first, I didn't care.
I knew I would leave someday.
But now, I don't really
want to leave.
That's probably why I have to go,
to do what I can.
To do what only I can do.
I won't say goodbye.
No matter how far away you are...
...sound fills the air.
Sound fills the air...
...and reaches people's hearts.
Kanata, was I a good
teacher to you?
Yes.
Thus, Rio left us.
Leaving behind a music that
I would hear forever,
a wonderful, wonderful
sound of the sky.
Let's get friendship, love, and other feelings together,
and play out how important they are.
I cried from joy.
I laughed from pain.
But that's all a part of me,
and tells me that I'm alive.
Let's take this slowly.
Everybody singing
Can you tell me how you really feel?
You're just my friend
Even when friendship and love waver,
I know, you know, will be happy
I hope this melody will ring forever.
Can you count my precious flower
Overflowing words are hardly enough to describe it.
This is our harmony.
Can you hear our harmony?
A Visitor • A Burning Field of Snow
Next time:
A Visitor.
A Burning Field of Snow.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.