Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
West Misato High School
Student Council Office
The budget's sure looking skimpy.
Misato West High School Next Year Student Council Budget Form (Draft)
President
It's a crying shame we can't provide anything for the third-years.
You said it.
Especially since they've done so much for us.
Isn't there anyone around who can lend a hand?
Actually, I have a friend who said she wanted to throw a graduation party.
Shall I introduce you to her, President SumiSumi?
How dare you call your president "SumiSumi"!
Struck a nerve.
smirk
"The President is SumiSumi!
President Mitsuki Farewell
Party (temp)
Things the president likes
Matcha!!
Now that I'm listing out the things President Mitsuki likes,
President Mitsuki Farewell Party (temp)
Things the president likes
Matcha!!
all I really know is that she likes the same matcha foods Yuu-chan does.
What should I do?
She's probably really busy around this time of year too.
What are you doing, Yuu-chan?!
Did you forget about me?!
Oh right, Yuu-chan!
How's President Mitsuki been doing lately?
Let's see...
We started taking baths together again...
Is there anything suspicious about her scent?
And we're sleeping together more often again too.
Are there suspicious marks on her anywhere?
Why can't that be me?
mutter
What else? What else does she do to you?
Yo, Haruka.
Look here. She's the new student council president, Otokawa Sumi-san.
She wants to have a word with you, Haruka.
Mitsuki-senpai! What happened to your hair, height, and glasses?!
What came about you?!
I'm her sister!
Come to think of it, she did mention something about having a younger sister.
So you're her sister Haruka?
This one is Haruka.
I am little sister Yuu.
That's right, I'm Haruka.
I haven't seen you around before.
So next year's president is a first-year?
Let's be friends.
A first-year? Stop that fooling.
But we aren't second-years until April.
I'm telling you, that's just you girls.
Ah
I'm so sorry! Misato West isn't taking applications for next year.
I'm a second-year! Next year will be my third!
Ehh?!
You're really a year older than us?!
Why are you so shellshocked? There's nothing curious about it.
You talk funny.
Yuzu! Show some respect to your elders.
I don't wanna hear that from someone who calls me "SumiSumi"!
But no matter. I am the President now,
so it's my duty to be kind on the young'uns.
I'll learn you the secret of my way of speaking.
My grandpappy is an extremely dignified gentleman,
so as his granddaughter, I was naturally born with this speech pattern.
Well? Well? Isn't that amazing?
As expected from our President SumiSumi! You rock!
Stop calling me SumiSumi!
President SumiSumi, your speech's gone back to normal.
What a blunder...
She's doing it on purpose...
So?
What do you want with Haruka, President SumiSumi?
Stop with the SumiSumi thing. Please.
I heard you were fixing to host a farewell party for the third-years.
It's not all the third-years. Just President Mitsuki.
Really just for her?
Big Sister
Yep, just for President Mitsuki.
Did I just hear Haruka-san calling my name?
That can't be. I just happened to be passing by...
What do you think about hosting Vice President Sakai Rina as well?
Ex-Vice President
Oh, the girl who's really close to President Mitsuki!
Those two always lent me a helping hand.
You should say that part with more conviction.
Y-Yes...
It's all right, Sumi-chan. Just take it slow.
Thanks to them, I started to like being the secretary despite my original hesitation.
I want to thank President Mitsuki and Vice President Rina
and make them feel it was worth coming to this school.
...young'uns.
Don't forget your "thing".
whisper
I was trying to be serious there!
Gah
Despite the declining budget, they organized a sports festival for us to enjoy,
so I was trying to think up something comparable to do for them...
Let's do it! We'll hold a sports fair
with the two of them!
Yuu-chan, what kind of sports does President Mitsuki like to play?
Onee-chan's bad at all of them.
fwump
What
She
Hoped
For
What
She
Hoped
For
Just when I thought we'd be able to reform the Sonoda Yuu cheer squad!
Are you just in this for yourself?
Don't forget that this whole thing
is to thank the seniors.
If sports won't do, what kind of things do the president and vice president like?
Oh yeah, we got too focused
on sports for a while there.
Hey, Yuu-chan.
What are some things and activities President Mitsuki likes?
And don't say matcha.
Well, Onee-chan's tastes are basically the same as mine...
Extra-sweet red-bean soup,
Mmm
and mochi with heaps of brown sugar syrup and soy flour...
Very Japanese.
Enough with the food already!
More generally, we could hold a girls-only tea party with traditional sweets.
Sounds like a sugar overdose.
A yakisoba-for-brains like you will never understand the appeal of Japanese sweets.
Don't you look down on yakisoba bread!
snapped
President SumiSumi, do you know anything about their tastes?
To be frank, I haven't spoken much with President Mitsuki myself.
All I could do was watch her from afar.
I also noticed that Vice President Rina would often gaze at her as well.
She must be head over heels!
My!
Ah! Now I know who Vice President Sakai is in love with!
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
S-Sorry about that.
Anyway, Yuu-chan, is that really all you know?
Hey...
Why don't you try going to their classroom
and looking around to see what's popular?
What a good idea, Shizuku-chan!
pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_pat_
That's my girl!
All right. Let's move out, Yuu-chan.
I'll accompany you!
I almost never go up to the third-year classrooms, so I'm getting kind of nervous.
Me too.
Really?
They have colored shoelaces!
You two'll doubtlessly be doing the same thing a year from now anyway.
A lot of them are doing last-minute studying for entrance exams.
And come of think of it, I don't really know anyone other than President Mitsuki and Vice President Sakai.
Same here.
Things might've been a bit different up here if we still had club activities.
Could we get through?
Oh, sorry to block you.
They're all so adult.
Yeah, everyone seems so refined.
But still, your boobs are bigger than any of theirs.
muffle
Don't say unnecessary things!
Huh?
For some reason...
Everywhere we look...
They're eating pudding!
It's the same in every class, isn't it?
Right, they're all scarfing it down!
But why? Is it trending among the third-years?
Bucket matcha pudding.
That's it!
Om nom nom.
How does holding a bucket matcha pudding eating contest sound?
No objections!
It'd be even better if we added some red beans...
I'm sure the seniors will find it to their fancy!
I'm just raring to do this!
President SumiSumi, are you—
So soft!
You must be a D-cup. Let me cop a little feel, girlie.
fondle
The way you talk makes that sound so creepy!
What are you saying? Haruka's a C-cup.
grope
Y-You too, Yuu-chan?
See? She's a C.
grope
This sensation is none other than a D.
S-Sto...
You've got quite the squeeze box, Haruka.
I'll be excusing myself to the classroom now.
Let's finish this later!
President SumiSumi's kind of a weirdo.
Yuu-chan, you know how much I hate it when people touch my breasts...
But I just couldn't help myself!
You think everything's fine as long as you can touch my boobs?
Are my breasts all you like about me?
Answer me.
I like...
Is it something you can't say out loud?
I'd really like to hear you finish.
Nope.
Go on. What do you like?
H-H...
Hurry up. I can't wait...
Yuu-chan, you're really aggressive today.
D-Don't say that!
Nya-ha-ha
Let's go back to class already!
Big Sister
Okay, I got it!
freeze
"The President is SumiSumi!
The end
Big Sister
Little Sister
Good morning, everyone. I'm Takayama Haruka.
My best friend Sonoda Yuu-chan and I
have a special relationship where we do things no other friends would ever do.
peek
That's her hair accessory!
Yuu-chan!
And this may surprise you...
Good morning, Haruka-san.
...but I'm in a situation where I
can't kiss Yuu-chan anymore!
Flashback
I can't believe I ran into President Mitsuki right after what happened yesterday!
Just now, what were you two doing?
What did it look like to you, Rina?
They were k-kissing, I suppose...
That is not appropriate behavior at school, much less between two girls.
And moreover, it didn't look like your first or second time either.
Who started all this?
It was Haruka.
It was you!
So which is it?
Are you two in a relationship where you've admitted your love for one another?
I won't tell anyone about it.
But Haruka-san, you need to open your eyes.
Yuu is my precious little sister.
So from now on...
You are forbidden from kissing her!
Aahhhhhh
"Sakura-colored Truth"
Today's Lesson: Creative Dancing
Light warming up
Practice dancing in pairs
Decide theme for next week
Wh-What do I do now?
Harupoppo, something on your mind?
Y-Yeah...
Don't worry, I'm sure you can dance just fine.
Uh, that's not the problem...
Wait, Kotone-chan might actually understand.
Um, please don't tell anyone else about this, but...
Oh no, I'm gonna be smooched! What do I do?
N-No, that's not it!
Her joke just made this super awkward.
If someone found out about the secret you and Shizuku-chan have,
and that person said "That's wrong, don't do it anymore", what would you do?
Probably just not listen.
Huh?
If you've been keeping it secret, you just have to make sure they don't catch you again.
I guess that's true. I just have to not get caught.
Haruka.
I've been commissioned by President Mitsuki to keep an eye on you again.
What'd you do this time?
She asked me to watch you again out of nowhere.
Uwa
Nailed it! How'd you like that turn?
Bam!
Did President Mitsuki seem angry?
Not exactly...
None of you were looking! Come on!
I was watching. You're really
good at dancing, Yuzu-chan.
Thank you, Shizuku-chan!
She's sweaty...
Listen up, girls.
Next up is creative dancing.
I haven't gotten the chance to speak to Yuu-chan all day.
I have no sense of rhythm so I can't dance at all.
Come on, you just gotta have fun with it.
Partner up with the same people as last time.
That means...!
I can legally be together with Yuu-chan!
Haruka!
Hey, Yuu-chan.
We probably shouldn't kiss anymore, right?
TRIP
Ah! S-Sorry, Haruka! I didn't mean to...
I really tripped just now.
Of course you did!
Oh Yuu-chan, you need to be more careful.
Just check this one out!
There are other people here.
Ah, sorry about that.
Besides, Kaede-chan's monitoring me.
Hey—Yuzu! I can't see!
Whoopsie!
You can't see?
Then I'll just have to do it again!
tehe
We collided!
Hey—Haruka, that was on purpose!
Yes, you're the best.
We can't do this.
It was just an accident.
No...
I said stop!
Mad
I'm going to go straight for your
weak spot from now on.
Sorry, I really am.
Okay!
Sister-protecting time!
Are you headed down to Yuu-chan's classroom?
Sure am.
I can't let my guard down just
because lunch break is short.
I definitely won't let them kiss.
She
Was
Too
Late
I know! I'll stop by the school shop and buy something for her.
Yakisoba bread!
I found the matcha pudding we usually have together!
So you're after the pudding too, Mitsuki-senpai!
shock
Why is pudding so happening in your grade?
Oh, it's just you, Sumi.
What are you doing here?
I'm tracking the flow of the pudding.
Presently the trend is that the third-years are buying the most.
First-year
Second-year
Third-year
But why? Explain it to me!
Oh, that's because...
Because what?
Big Sister
Rina once told me that eating pudding before you study helps you concentrate better,
and then somehow it spread across the grade...
She was just joking around,
but everyone took it seriously.
I suppose it's fine if it puts
them all at ease, though.
So you were the one who lit the fire on the pudding boom!
Lit the pudding
boom fire!!
President Mitsuki
lit the fire on the pudding boom!!
By the way, Mitsuki-senpai.
Where will you be taking lunch?
Let me accompany you!
No problem. I'm going to class 1-A.
They're the upperclassmen with the colored shoelaces.
One of these, please.
Same for me.
Got it, same as usual.
Even they're buying pudding.
So those two are wont to study as well.
Goodness, isn't that obvious?
They're all good students.
Come on, let's go.
One day, we'll catch up with Mitsuki...
...and get boobs as big as hers.
All we have to do is eat the same things!
You shouldn't go judging people by their appearance, Sumi.
Right, I'll take that to heart.
Mitsuki-senpai, you're easy to read. Quite different from myself.
A-Am I?
I love how earnest you are.
O-Oh, is that so?
touch
I love how plump you are too!
You seriously are strange.
They're even bigger than Haruka's!
Hey, you...
Wait, you know Haruka-san?
Yay.
I had Kaede make our acquaintance.
Oh, so that's how.
D-Does that mean that you've touched Haruka's breasts before?
Why are you so agitated?
Not even I know why.
Is it my fault?
N-No, it's not you...
There's just something I wanted
Haruka-san to reflect on.
And thinking about it puts me on edge.
Don't you have something else
you want to say to her?
If you want to touch her too, you should just ask!
I was not thinking about touching her at all!
There must be more on your mind regarding Haruka than you're letting on.
I'm bad at expressing myself through facial expressions, so I learned to say what's on my mind.
Well, now that you mention it...
You turned out a lot differently than I originally imagined you.
At the beginning, you spoke a lot more normally.
PAST
Got it! Please leave it to me, President Mitsuki!
Please don't dredge up my dark past!
Wait, but now you're kind of...
Young'uns!
Ah!!
I forgot that I left my lunch back in the classroom!
Then go and grab it.
R-Right!
Something I want to tell Haruka-san...
I just want the two of them to act like normal friends...
But if there's something else I'm always thinking...
It's that I want to become Haruka-san's lover!
What?! Wait! What did I just think?
N-No way, could this mean...
D-D-Do I...
But Haruka-san, you need to open your eyes.
I acted so high and mighty...
The one who needed to open her eyes... was me.
This whole time, I've...
...been in love with Haruka-san?!
This can't be happening! How am I supposed to face her now?!
The bell...
"Sakura-colored Truth"
The end
Big Sister
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
In the season of fluttering sakura petals,
Yuu-chan and I became high school students.
So much has happened, and we've met so many people along the way.
These fun days we spent with our new friends
passed by with the seasons.
And today, the season of fluttering sakura petals has returned.
And I...
Last episode:
"Pudding and Mitsuki's Determination"
"Sakura Trick"
and "Sakura Trick".
Please look forward to it.