saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
Youko, have some rolled omelet.
What?
N-No, I wouldn't want to impose...
Hayama really drives me up a wall!
Um, are you a friend of Hayama's?
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
Stand.
Bow.
Thank you very much.
What are you having?
Maybe lunch combo A.
I'm starving!
My name is Youko Nishikawa.
I am now living as a commoner,
since my father lost his fortune
when his company went bankrupt.
And the other day...
Futaba, what do you usually eat for breakfast?
I was able to make...
...two wonderful friends!
Plain rice!
Youko, have some rolled omelet.
What?
N-No, I wouldn't want to impose...
Please, I insist.
But there would be less for you.
It's fine!
But then you...
It's fine.
But...
This is not fine!
We're being way too polite!
Let's relax a little! Re-lax!
R-Relax?
Yup! Like, we should call each other
by nicknames and stuff.
'Cause we're friends!
Friends...?
So now we're friends
all of a sudden?
Oh, you mean we're not?
Gosh, we're just teasing.
Right?
Wh-What...?
A cat!
Perhaps it's a stray.
Hayama?
T-Too cute!
Nothing Good For You Is Tasty
What's the matter, little kitty?
Are you lost?
You're so cute!
Hayama looks quite pleased.
She does like cats.
Not just cats.
I also like dogs, birds, cows, and horses! I love them all!
My dream is to buy an island and build Hayama Park!
How grand!
Not what you'd expect, huh?
Hmph, is that
what you think about me?
Do you have any pets at home?
Yeah, a cat named Bel.
A cat!
My family named him, though.
His name is Beelzebub,
or Bel for short.
Beelze—
Beelzebub!
A prince of demons.
Demon prince.
Also known as Lord of the Flies!
A-A demon who takes
the form of a fly!
Demon prince.
He was swarming with flies
when we took him in.
So we named him Bel.
Hey, do you have a minute, Hayama?
Oh, yes?
Would you mind handing
these out before the next class?
Okay.
Can you also collect the
homework notebooks during break?
Man, that's a lot of worksheets!
What on earth was I thinking?
Hayama isn't a demon;
she's a model student!
Being class representative
sounds difficult.
I didn't really want to be class rep,
but they insisted.
Oh? Why didn't you refuse
if you dislike it?
Well...
I don't like having
to do random duties,
but it'll look good on my résumé.
What?
Class Rankings
Shoot, I tried really hard
this time too.
th
Serina Nishiyama
Wow, you're amazing, Nishiyama!
You're ranked tenth in our grade!
And where's Hayama...?
th
Hayama
Don't say it! I don't want to hear it!
Yeah, you're right!
Grades aren't everything!
This is higher than your rank
in middle school!
It's a huge improvement already!
Hayama really drives me up a wall!
She's always getting in my way.
I wanted to be
class representative too.
I know, right? It's too bad.
They just chose her
because she looks like a class rep!
It wasn't random.
It was part of her plan.
Haa?...ya...ma!
An acquaintance of yours?
Hayama had a "talk"
with her before.
She called me out
for being full of myself.
It was so scary!
What's going on?
Did something happen?
She's crying...
You won't get away with this!
Do people actually say that?
Oh, that was so scary...
Hayama...
Perhaps she is a demon.
May 9
QUADRATIC EQUATION
So, what if you apply
the formula to this equation?
Todoroki, come up
and try the first problem.
Okay.
Hey, get those legs moving!
Ugh, they're timing us for this?
Why...
Huh?
Hayama...
She's beating me!
Or not. I'm about to lap her!
C'mon! Run like you mean it, or you'll do another one!
Hold your tongue, Hayama...
Don't talk back to a teacher!
Hold your tongue!
I'm tired!
I'm gonna die...
You okay?
How could I be?
She was trying to run us to death!
So even the great Hayama
has a weakness, huh?
Nishiyama.
What's your problem?
Don't mind her, Futaba.
It's so sad that she looks down on people over the smallest of matters.
She needs our kindness.
Who are you calling sad?!
Yeah! And you are not small.
You have a great figure!
What are you talking about?
W-Well, I do make sure to exercise
and eat balanced meals.
Beanpole...
BEANPOLE
I win!
You have it rough, Nishiyama.
You're so young to be gaining weight when you don't watch what you eat.
That's way off!
Why are you always
making a fool out of me?!
What? You're so mean.
That's not true.
Hayama...
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Ugh, I still feel nauseous...
You really dislike running,
don't you?
Not running specifically.
I just don't have stamina.
I'm almost out of gas...
Hayama?
You don't look low on gas to me!
Please take care of us.
Oh my, are they abandoned?
Wh-What should we do?
To think that someone
would abandon such young kittens...
It's terrible!
What on Earth were they thinking?
Hayama actually has
a gentle spirit.
Please take care of us.
"Please take care of us," huh?
I'll take care of you, all right!
Whoever abandoned these kittens,
show yourself!
That's the voice of a demon!
I found homes for two of the kittens,
but there's still one left...
I-It would be a struggle,
but I can house it!
First, I'll find a place to live
that allows pets...
That's step one?!
I wonder if there are
any cat lovers around.
Oh, cats?
Kondou?
Nishiyama used to have a cat.
A cat?
I did have one,
but it died three years ago.
Your family had that cat
since before you were born, right?
You really loved it, huh?
Hey, don't give them my life story...
Nishiyama!
There is value in the existence
of someone like you!
So there wasn't any before?!
I'm home.
I actually took it.
Well, what else could I have done?
Nobody else would take it.
I don't like the fact that
it was from Hayama, though.
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
You need a name.
A name that will give you a long life.
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Oh yeah! We're not done yet!
What?!
Remember how I wanted to come up
with nicknames for all of us?
Did you?
That's right.
A nickname!
We need nicknames
to become true friends!
We don't need them...
Hayama, Futaba,
please give me a splendid nickname.
Well, er...
Yokoppy!
Princess Haircut.
Rejected!
What? You don't like those?
No, no! They're unacceptable!
Something more elegant, noble,
and intellectual would serve better!
Er...
Former Rich Girl!
Princess Haircut.
As I was saying!
Please address Miss Youko
as Miss Youko.
Ah, it's just you, Yamaji?
You crept up on us, so I thought you were someone suspicious.
Oh, you jest.
Now, if you please, address Miss Youko
as Miss Youko.
Wha—?
Understood.
Got it!
Miss Youko!
This is not what I had in mind
for a nickname...
Okay, so Miss Youko
is Miss Youko.
Next is...
Wait, what's Hayama's
first name?
I'm Futaba Odagiri,
Miss Youko is Youko Nishikawa.
What's your first name?
Isn't this nice?
It's so fun to eat outdoors.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, come on!
Tell us your first name!
Come on,
what's your first name? Hey...
Miss Youko, what's your next class?
Oh, it's—
Sheesh, why won't you tell us?
What's your first name?
Teru!
Te...
...ru?
Teru?!
Teru. That's my first name.
Teru! Miss Teru! Teruloo!
Don't keep saying it!
What's the problem?
It's cute, right?
Yes, it's quite a lovely name.
Oh, and Terurin...
No way!
Teru, I don't have
chopsticks for my lunch.
You can just get disposable ones
at the school store.
Oh, that's right!
I knew I could ask you!
You're so smart.
I didn't think of that.
Um, are you a friend
of Hayama's?
Oh, I'm not her friend.
I'm her older sister.
What?!
Older sister?!
She's Hayama's...
A demon and an angel!
Hey, hey! April Fools' is over!
I know...
Nice to meet you.
I'm Teru's older sister, Kou.
P-Pleased to meet you.
Are you Youko?
Y-Yes!
I knew it!
Wait here for a second.
What?
Wait?
Here, take one.
I made them from scratch.
Oh no...
Why, thank you.
No fair!
Go ahead.
Yay!
Uh-oh...
I'll try it!
Futaba?!
It's full of nutrients!
Homemade fermented bean candy!
Fermen—?!
Youko, I heard that
you only eat bread crusts.
Teru is all black on the inside,
but please get along with her
in spite of that, okay?
Wh-What?
Don't get the wrong idea.
She's a bit of an airhead, so she'll say and do
bizarre things without meaning harm.
Airhead?
Oh, jeez.
Lunch will be over
if you don't hurry!
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm going to try out new ingredients next time!
Yeah, yeah. That's nice.
It's still early, Bel.
It's the weekend.
Let me sleep in a little.
B-Big Sis!
Good morning, Teru.
Wh-What is it?
I'm going to make
a breakfast drink for you.
A drink?
Special garlic banana milk!
I'm still sleepy.
Aww...
Then I'll give some special
garlic banana milk to Bel instead.
I'm up!
I told her not to add the garlic...
Teru, you'll come grocery shopping
with me today, right?
Huh?
Won't you?
Maekawa  Produce
It's been a while
since we've gone out together.
It has.
So, what's on our shopping list?
Let's see. Books, and...
Books?
I'm going to buy a cookbook.
And a photo album?
An album?
Hayama!
Oh!
It's Futaba!
What are you two up to?
Shopping?
Yup! It's been a very long time
since I've gone out with Teru.
You two sure do get along!
I'm an only child,
so I'm jealous.
Only when she's
not trying to poison me.
Are you shopping too?
Yup. Picking up some giblets.
Wow, that sounds good!
I'll buy some giblets, too!
Oh, Big Sis, wait!
Super
daimaru
Giblets, Chinese yam,
okra, and mulukhiyah,
SPRING SALE
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
all mixed together to make candy!
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Why are you so obsessed
with health foods?
And then making
candy out of them?
They're easier to eat
in candy form.
.
Daily
Special
Sale!
Daily
Special
Sale!
Today's limited-time sale is...
500 grams of mayonnaise for 98 yen!
Limit one bottle per person!
A sale?
.
Daily
Special
Sale!
Daily
Special
Sale!
Don't miss your chance!
I-I have successfully obtained...
Mayonnaise
...the on-sale mayonnaise
that's limited to one per person!
Mayonnaise
Miss Youko!
I see.
So you're out shopping
with your sister?
Really, are you sure about this?
Raffle Ticket
I can really have
these raffle tickets?
Of course. We bought a lot.
Win every time!
Fifth prize is pocket tissues!
Fourth prize is a coffee set!
You're too excited.
Third prize is new crop rice!
You too?!
Central Shopping Plaza
Plaza Raffle
Fifth prize, pocket tissues...
Fourth prize, a coffee set!
Yeah!
Koshihikari Rice
Third prize,
the amazing new crop rice!
Koshihikari Rice
An unselfish win?
Gah! I can't believe
Hayama won and I didn't!
Congratulations!
Third Prize
New Crop Rice
Second Prize
Halogen Heater
~First Prize~
Hot Springs Vacation
Teru, help me!
Wh-What?!
She has pretty good luck
with these.
That's not just "pretty good"!
She also won
those bathhouse tickets.
She did?!
I can't carry all this!
I'm glad Youko and Futaba took the heavy things for us.
I'll give the hot springs vacation to Mom and Dad, and...
Oh no!
What?
I forgot to go to the bookstore!
Even if you buy a cookbook,
you'll end up adding other things anyway.
And... a photo album.
A photo album?
I found lots of photos in the closet.
Pictures from when we were little.
Big Sis!
You'll fall!
Don't worry!
I'm a good climber!
A little farther...
Almost there...
I'll give the pretty butterfly
to Teru!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
I fell...
Wait...
Oh, Teru!
You used to get sick and hurt a lot.
I'm pretty healthy now.
Don't take it for granted.
Make sure you stick to
a healthy diet!
Is she always going on
about nutrients...
Okay!
I'm going to try my best
at cooking!
...because she's worried about me?
Thanks.
Sh-She says it's
a thank-you for yesterday.
They're rice balls!
With liver, white roe,
and bitter melon!
All together?!
But where's all the stuff
you bought yesterday?
H-Healthiness really
isn't a factor here...
But Hayama's sister
went out of her way to make them for us.
It's food that she made... for us!
Whoa!
She's eating it!
Miss Youko's actually
a courageous hero!
Please do not allow Miss Youko
to consume strange foods!
Miss Youko, don't force yourself!
Yeah, even if this is
a rare chance to eat liver!
Don't encourage her!
Nothing good for you is tasty.
Oh, now that you mention it...
Don't encourage her!
Miss Youko!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if it's turned black inside
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if I can't be extravagant
ryou ga ookutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
sannin dakara tabechaou
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm not wasting electricity at night
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
egao ni nareru mono
Things that make me smile?
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
Food! Money! And things I can't say
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
Let's have fun and make silly memories
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
Will continue forever in just the same way
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
If you want to know the answer to one times three
nee koko ni oide
Then come on over here
Being rich isn't all that wonderful.
But that doesn't mean
my current life is great.
You wouldn't be green after eating a strange rice ball, though.
"But the chance for us to enjoy the rice balls
that Hayama's sister made...
...is true happiness!"
Your real thoughts are leaking out!
Next
Time:
A Taste of Maid
Next
Time:
A Taste of Maid
Next
Time:
A Taste of Maid
Miss Youko!