I present you with this, Mother.
Why... that's a Princess Perfume.
Indeed.
Where did you find it?
No, that matters not.
Mother?!
I bequeath this to you.
Could this be...
This time, be certain to drown the Precures in despair.
I shall.
M-Mother!
Princess Twilight!
Good work, everyone!
We got nine Keys!
They're so pretty.
What?
Girls?
Where am I?
That gate...
Wait... am I in...
Hope Kingdom?!
Thanks for helping us reach episode 555!
Please keep cheering the Precures on!
Follow your dreams and Go, Go, Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
A Reunion With Kanata?!
Onward, To Hope Kingdom!
Why are we in Hope Kingdom?
I don't know...
How'd we even get here?
The only way in or out of Hope Kingdom should be the gate inside the castle...
Girls, where are you?
Why did this happen?
You want me...
to go that way?
It seems the Precures have arrived.
What?!
How the heck...
Dyspairvil!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Dyspair... Vil!
Dys!
Dys.
Dyspair... Viiiiil!
Cure Flora!
Dyspair.
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Haruka...
Kanata...
Why are you here?
Welcome to Hope Kingdom.
It is a pleasure to meet you once again, Prince Kanata.
You've become a splendid princess, Haruka.
Kanata...
Oh, it restarted.
Could this mean...
Perhaps you were lead here by the Key.
By the Key?
The Key may be trying to tell you something.
Is that...
the crest of the Princess of Flowers?
Cure Flora...
She who has received the Key of Flowers...
That voice... it's the previous Princess Precure!
The Princess Precure of Flowers before me...
It seems the great darkness has finally awoken.
The great darkness?
You mean Dyspear?
Long ago, the three of us combined our powers to seal the powers of darkness.
However, we knew the day would come when the darkness would return.
The darkness would only grow more powerful upon its resurrection.
As such, we thought it fit to
leave behind one more Perfume.
A Perfume?!
There's one more?
However, the darkness is now closing in on that Perfume.
You must hurry.
The Perfume must not be dyed in darkness.
So that's the story...
Can't say no to that!
Wish!
This light most likely leads to Hope Kingdom Castle.
Let us go.
We're on it.
Let's go.
Fluffy Pigtails!
We must hurry. I'm certain Haruka and Kirara are on their way.
There's naught...
but to stop you here.
Shut!
This forest shall be...
naught but your doom!
You're gonna get defeated now, 'kay?
Please. You're the one who's going down.
You oughta watch that mouth, 'kay?
Watch yours first!
I hope Mermaid and Twinkle are all right.
I'm worried...
but I'm sure they're all headed
toward the remaining Perfume.
You've matured as a Princess Precure.
N-N-Not at all!
Oh, but I wanted to get closer to becoming a princess, so I started playing violin!
Violin?
Yeah!
Madame Siamour even taught me a few songs you played often.
I see...
Oh yeah, and she told me you had a sister!
I never knew!
I suppose I haven't told you yet.
My sister, Towa...
went missing long ago.
Towa loved to play the violin,
so we often practiced together.
Oh, not again!
I'll never become a Grand Princess if I can't play this piece properly!
You really intend to become one?
Only Princess Precures have been able to become Grand Princesses.
I'm aware.
But I shall still try!
I promise I'll become one!
I'll be a Grand Princess with the strength, grace, and beauty of the legendary Precures!
But one day, Towa was nowhere to be found.
And no matter how hard we searched, she was never found.
To Hope Kingdom's townspeople and I, Towa was a ray of hope.
Losing that hope weakened our hearts.
It wasn't long before we lost sight of our dreams.
That was when Dyspear appeared.
Our weakened hearts couldn't hope to stave off the invading darkness.
I had no idea...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to sadden you as well.
No, I'm sorry!
I was so insensitive...
Don't worry.
Haruka...
It was thanks to you that I learned to smile once more.
Huh?
Maybe I can't be a pretty, pink princess...
You can.
Really?
Thanks to you, I remembered how important dreams were.
I'll do it!
It was because I met you that I could bear the battle against Dyspear.
And it's what kept me from succumbing to the darkness until now.
Haruka, I'm glad I met you.
No, I'm the glad one!
You still encouraged me despite
everything you were going through...
I want to do more to help you!
Every now and then, I think...
that my violin's tune still reaches Towa somewhere.
That's why I'm sure I'll find my sister, Towa.
Yeah!
You are naught but to give in and fall!
We'll protect that new Perfume from the likes of you!
The world won't be drowned in despair!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Sorry, but I can't afford to quarrel with you.
Curse you...
You're persistent. Least you ain't boring, 'kay?
Gee, thanks.
But I'm too busy to play around with you!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Good grief.
Hope Kingdom Castle...
The place where I once lived.
Dyspear is in here...
Yes, and likely the Perfume, as well.
But it's strange.
What is?
It's too quiet.
There are typically Dyspairvils guarding the gate.
Let's go.
Haruka!
Haruharu!
Goodness, Prince Kanata!
Prince Kanata!
Girls!
Perf! Aroma!
You've carried out your duties well.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're all safe!
Cure Mermaid and Cure Twinkle, I thank you as well.
Save the warm fuzzies for later!
We understand the situation.
We also heard the previous
Princess Precures speak to us.
I see.
Let's go!
Agreed!
Welcome to the castle of despair.
Twilight!
Kanata?
Towa!
Madam Towa?
Prince Kanata's sister...
S-Sister?
Since when?
There's no mistake! It's her!
Towa, it's me, Kanata!
Towa, why?
Kanata...
Towa...
It's me, Kanata!
Don't you recognize me?
What are you talking about?
I am the Black Princess and the daughter of the great witch Dyspear, Twilight.
That's it!
It's the Perfume!
With refinement, majesty, and elegance...
I am truly...
the one and only princess.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Remember! You're Kanata's sister!
Go! Princess Precure:
Open Your Heart!
Princess vs. Princess!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Kanagawa Prefecture - Nana (Age 12)
Saitama Prefecture - Kokomi (Age 5)