The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
I've got something to take care of that means more than my entire life.
I'm close to forgetting my own face!
Umm...
Hey!
Yagiri Pharmacy, eh?
Is this really the place where they
perform the human experimentations?
That's not Harima Mika...
Use as much of the money you want, whenever you want.
I want what we have now to last forever.
I love you, Selty.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Everyone is fake.
There are too many fake people in this world.
They say stuff like "I love you" just to appease others.
All they do is face your way, stay by your side and search for something.
They simply fawn.
However, my love is different.
It is more vast and absolute.
Yup.
Yeah.
I know, Sis.
Thanks for the deposit.
Later.
Want me to go and get you something to drink?
The vending machine is right over there.
Just wait for me.
Whoa.
You're so adorable.
Madly in Love
You still haven't found him?
No, I sincerely apologize.
Just what were the watchmen doing?
The one who was in charge last night said that even though Seiji-san had been staying in the same hotel for some time,
he suddenly switched locations in the middle of the night.
He still picked up his phone around seven in the evening!
If something were to happen to him...!
He promised not to leave Ikebukuro, so I'm sure they'll find him soon.
Don't you understand?
What do you think is going to happen to us if that thing were to catch the eye of a police officer?!
That's...
Enough.
I don't have the patience to wait for you all.
Chief!
I'll be back soon.
To me, "that thing" was nothing more than a doll.
Reference Room
Just like those expensive, beautiful imported dolls that my uncle used to buy for me when I was little.
I've never liked dolls, even in my youth.
My guess is that my uncle didn't send me these dolls to delight me.
He only sent them to me because he liked them himself.
Look, Seiji!
Isn't she pretty?
I wonder what this other gift is?
I wonder.
Our house was always so quiet,
and Seiji and I were always alone together.
Even before he was born, I was often placed in the care of my uncle,
and I had access to his study.
And that's where "that thing" was.
Uncle was always staring at "that thing," which was supposedly smuggled from a foreign country,
occasionally talking to it.
She really was beautiful.
Moreso than any doll that he gave to me.
For some reason, I didn't sense anything cruel about it.
It just seemed like a single living being, with only a head.
But that's all it meant to me.
I only secretly invited Seiji to the study that day to play around,
and perhaps I just wanted someone to share the secret with.
See? Isn't she pretty?
That's where it all began.
My first and only regret, which still haunts me to this day.
This is the first time we actually met, right?
Did that list of illegal immigrants help you out at all, Yagiri Namie-san?
I'm honored that the chief of the sixth lab of Yagiri
Pharmacy came all the way here to such a filthy place.
Please, take a seat.
This is an emergency.
Please find my little brother immediately.
Huh?
I'll pay you however much you want.
I haven't been able to get in touch with him since last night,
but he should be in Ikebukuro somewhere.
It hasn't even been that long since you last spoke to him.
Why are you so worried?
He's with a woman.
A woman who has scars on her neck.
A woman?
Come on, he's at an age where that kind of stuff isn't uncommon.
Please begin your search immediately!
Hang on a second.
Aren't there some more important things you want me to search for?
Isn't there a rumor that your company might be absorbed by a large, foreign corporation called 'Nebula'?
If that happens, you'll also-
Orihara Izaya-san,
there's no time for chit-chat.
This is unexpected.
I would have never thought a talented woman like you would be in love with her little brother.
What do you know about me?
The Yagiri Namie-san I know is a respectable woman.
Even though it's a family business, your father screwed up and lost his position.
And I heard that the current president, who
happens to be your uncle, is calm and collected.
So you were able to enter the company with your own effort,
and gained your current status despite being so young.
Not to mention how beautiful you are.
Can't put anything past you, it seems.
It should be a walk in the park for you to find my little brother, then.
Your little brother, eh...
It's not good to meddle too much.
I'm not meddling!
I'm the only one who can protect him!
I've heard that stalkers don't realize they're stalking.
Apparently, they believe that they're 'protecting'-
Don't you dare put me on the same level as a stalker!
You're frightening.
I'm just pulling your leg.
Okay, I'll lend you a hand.
However, I'll be doing things my way.
Cops and informants are totally different.
What rules are you playing by?
Let me ask one thing.
Are you jealous of this woman who has scars on her neck?
Why do you ask that?
There's no way I'm jealous of her.
This red, rusty form of jealousy that burns in my chest is from...
Sis, there's someone I'm in love with.
I knew Seiji was starting to act stranger by the day.
He kept insisting on entering our uncle's study,
and as soon as we would sneak in, he would stare intently at "that thing."
Seiji didn't fall in love with a person.
He fell in love with someone who has neither a heart nor a body.
Because I wanted to get "that thing" away from Seiji,
I asked Uncle as soon as I entered the company whether we could have it placed in the lab as a research specimen.
And that's when it happened.
Nebula began establishing contact with us,
and I was frantic about not leaking our research.
That's when my security card was stolen.
The card only I had.
Sis, I may...
have just killed someone.
What should I do?
The feeling that arose in my chest at that time was neither fear nor anger.
It was an indescribable feeling of rejoice.
The one Seiji really needs is me.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
Let your sis handle everything, okay?
I'm not talking about her, but the other girl.
So you were the one who took her.
Don't worry.
You can let me handle that as well.
It'll be okay.
I swear.
I wasn't aware that a dumb girl by the name of
Harima Mika had been stalking Seiji at that time.
When she snuck into his room and saw "that thing," Seiji...
I'll do anything to protect you.
Ah, yes.
It may not be necessary for you to be panicking so much.
I think the cops will take him into custody soon and give you a call.
I know I just said "cops," but there's nothing for you to worry about.
Not a big deal.
I think.
Quit messing around!
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Message
Watch out. You're still being pursued.
Where are you now?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Huh? You want to leave?
But we're still...
Hang on!
I'm happy that you love me so much.
I love you too.
Forever. And I mean forever.
I'm scared.
Of what?
Please, take me somewhere far away!
I want to be with you, too!
But where do you want to go?
What's that about?
A lovers' quarrel?
Stop it!
Please, calm down.
Trust me, we're not as suspicious as we look.
Listen to-
You-
Huh?
Let go of her.
Oh, I'm fine.
Shit doesn't even hurt.
Go ahead.
I don't really get it, but you need to go after her, right?
Man, I've always wanted to say that!
"Leave this to me. You go on ahead!"
Wait!
I-I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Hey, you're...
Wait!
No, you wait!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Is she your girlfriend?
Yeah!
She's my soulmate!
Why is she like that?
Hell if I know!
What the hell do you mean by that?!
You don't know about the problems of your loved one?
Don't you think that's a tad bit irresponsible of you?
Huh?!
What does that have to do with loving someone?!
Oh?
Then why is she your "soulmate"?
Because I love her!
There's no other reason!
You can't put love into words!
That's why I'll...
I'll display it with action!
I'll protect her!
That's all there is to it!
I like you a lot more than Izaya.
That's why I'll let you off the hook with just this.
I'll start bleeding once I remove this, right?
Should probably buy a band-aid before I take it out, then.
Nah, maybe superglue would be better.
So basically,
your head had stuck onto a body, and was roaming around town.
You caught her, but a high school student got in your way.
When you went after her, another high school student came to interfere and took her away.
You expect me to believe that?
I'm not forcing you to.
I do believe you.
But why was Shizuo-kun with you?
Oh, I totally forgot to mention.
I was in the park because I was in the middle of completing the job request I got from Izaya.
Shizuo happened to walk by, so we were having a chat.
I got a call later saying that the job was canceled, so it all worked out.
Orihara-kun, huh...
Either way, I wanted to talk to you about it.
Seems like you're still puzzled.
I'd be happy to hear what you have to say.
For starters, why the heck is there
another body attached to my head?!
Well, I don't know how much my hypotheses will help since I didn't actually see anything,
but if you're fine with mere speculation...
For example...
He found a girl who had a body that would match your head,
and removed her head and replaced it with yours.
That's hideous.
Or there could have been a freshly-killed corpse.
Stop that!
But...
Th...
That can't be...
I didn't do anything wrong.
I created her after that incident for Seiji's sake.
I have to go...
It's okay.
Everything's fine now.
It must have been scary.
She's...
But see? Nothing bad happened to you.
Even after she escaped from this place and reunited with Seiji,
my love did not waver.
Seiji's love exists because he can use my love as a stepping stone.
He knows that, and I know he knows that.
Everything is distorted, and even then...
Dammit...!
He was wearing Raira Academy's uniform.
Just who is he?
I understand.
Leave it to me.
Anyway, I have to find that student who goes to Raira.
And I have to meet with my head and talk some sense into it.
The head that did nothing but scream after seeing you?
What are you going to do with a head that supposedly lives a life of its own?
Are you going to cut it off that body for your sake?
Selty.
I just don't want to admit it.
I don't want to admit that my head and my memories are lost forever.
I don't want to admit that what I've been doing for these past twenty years was for nothing.
It wasn't for nothing.
I'll get her back for sure.
You just wait here, okay?
Oh, hey.
Where's your phone?
Did you lose it?
I don't know.
I can't find it.
I thought I put it in my bag.
Huh?
She...
She needs me by her side...!
We need to be together, alone...
Oh... I see.
Don't worry. Just leave everything to your sis.
What a cheeky doll.
That doll should have simply stayed still, as every other doll would have.
Without interfering with my love.
I've decided.
The last thing I want to do now is regret.
Not ever.
Do I make myself clear?
Contact the underlings immediately.
I don't care if they capture her dead or alive.
If necessary, get rid of her on the spot.
Untitled
Are you safe?
Where are you now?
Ryugamine Mikado
There is currently no one in the chat room.
I see.
Looks like everyone's busy.
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
Even though I'm an informant, there are so many things I don't know about in this city!
They appear and disappear!
This is precisely why I can't leave a city where humans gather!
I love humans!
I just love them!
I'm in love with them!
And that's why...
humans should come to love me as well.
Thanks.
Have you calmed down a bit?
Do you think you could answer a few of my questions?
You said you don't remember anything, right?
Which means you're...
Suffering from amnesia?
Well... I said this earlier, but...
Perhaps you should visit the police station or a hospital...
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
No, it's fine.
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Please don't apologize.
I have to go.
Before that person interferes again.
Forever and ever...
I have to go.
Seiji...
Seiji-san...
I love you.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
The First and Probably the Last
Umm...
The headless rider, Orihara Izaya and the girl with the scars on her neck showed up again.
And to top it off, the guy who's in the classroom next to me is in Dollars...!
Next time: The First and Probably the Last.
I always dreamed of living an abnormal life.
But...