Science Lab
Hmm...
I'm back!
Found anything out?
I don't know the specifics,
but I can say for certain that it's not of this world.
Not of this world?!
Where did you get this?
I got this from a ball of light when I transformed,
and I got this from a man I met at a jewelry stand at the Clover Tower.
Do you know what this is?
Nope.
We came here just after we were born,
so we don't know.
Well that explains a few things.
How rude!
We're doing the best we can here!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're right.
We've learned a lot thanks to your cooperation
Like what?
Like how the Cure Lovies is the source of the Precure's power.
I'd wager that the more Lovies one finds,
the more abilities a Precure can use.
The Cure Lovies is really something.
Huh?
Oh, you two are still here?
I'm sorry!
We had something we just had to investigate today.
The teachers already left.
So if you don't clean up in three minutes,
you'll get locked in.
Oh no!
Wait a second!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
The Ultimate Partner Has Arrived!
Cure Diamond!
All else aside, I'm curious about this man who you said gave you the Lovies.
This requires further investigation...
Mana?
Kenzaki Makoto
Hey, did you hear?
It's about Makopi's next concert at the Four Leaf Stadium!
They had 60,000 tickets for sale,
but they sold out in three minutes!
Aww, I wanted to go...
Really Mana,
this isn't the time to get distracted.
Oh...
That's right.
And we don't know who that Precure who saved Mana really was...
Mana?
Grrr
All right!
I can't work on an empty stomach,
so how about we go to my house and work out a plan over dinner?
No objections!
Yay!
Oh, let me make a call while we have the chance.
What's she doing?
Rikka's mom is a doctor,
so she gets home really late pretty often.
That's why Rikka's calling her.
Now then, eat up!
Don't mind if we do!
My taste buds are in heaven!
Mr. Aida, your cooking's definitely the best!
Good to hear.
That's my dad for you!
Hmph!
Only half as good as my work, I tell ya.
Want to put that to the test, Dad?
You needn't ask!
If you think I'm the same chef I once was, you're sorely mistaken.
Why you whippersnapper—
Now now, settle down.
We have customers waiting, so save it for later.
I'm sorry for always eating up your food.
I can't thank you enough.
I keep telling you not to worry about it!
With neighbors, it's all about give and take!
Welcome!
Take your time.
We've got plenty left if you want seconds.
Thank you very much!
diner
Pig's Tail
Thank you for dinner.
You're welcome for dinner.
You two get along great.
So how about you become a Precure too, Rikka?
Huh?
Well, um...
you're really smart and kind,
so I thought it'd be nice if you were my partner...
That sounds great!
With you by my side, we'd be unbeatable!
M-Me? A Precure?
And her name?
Let's see...
I'm already Heart, so...
how about Cure Dia?
Yeah!
Hold on a minute!
I'm not nearly as athletic as you are,
and I'm bad at taking center stage.
Those frilly clothes would look terrible on me, too...
Besides, you can't become a Precure just by asking to be one!
Don't worry!
If I can do it, you can too.
Nobody has a stronger sense of justice than you.
Everyone trusts you and relies on you.
I know what it takes to be a Precure.
But I can't do it.
It's all I can do to look after myself.
That's not true!
You're always there to help me.
Thank you.
Rikka!
Don't worry!
I'll be your backup just like I always have.
Tomorrow, let's go look for that man who gave you the Lovies.
Good night!
She got away.
I'm back.
Hm?
It's from Daddy!
Rikka, are you well?
Your daddy's in a place called Machu Picchu.
The people here are really nice,
and sold me some great antiques on the cheap!
Machu Picchu?
Oh Daddy,
you're supposed to be a professional photographer,
so why not send a photo every now and then?
To my beloved Daddy,
Thank you for another unique souvenir.
Mommy and I are doing well.
Mommy's so busy with her hospital work that she can't even afford a sick day.
I shouldn't write anything about the Precure.
Last week was Greeting Week,
so I woke up at six every morning to go to school.
Mana's greetings were really loud,
almost enough to wake the dead.
Well then, Daddy, stay happy and healthy.
I look forward to the tales of your travels.
You seem tense.
I darn well should be!
I had two of my Selfishes beaten!
You can't win the game if you let them get to you,
Ira.
Bel!
Oh, you're here too?
Orders from the top.
I'm here to observe.
How is a lone little girl giving you so much trouble?
She's not alone!
They've been recruiting.
There are two Precures.
Sounds difficult.
Shall I lend a hand?
I don't need you!
No matter how many there are,
I'll get rid of them all at once!
A lovey letter?
Mana!
It's my father!
He'll get pouty if I don't reply.
Getting a letter would make anyone happy!
Especially when it's from your daughter!
Then do you write to your dad?
My dad never goes overseas like yours does,
so there's no point in sending a letter across the hall.
But isn't it wonderful how your dad's cooking can move people to tears?
Why not write about how wonderful he is?
But my dad's got nothing on your photography award-winning dad!
Let's go, you two!
Let's go talk to that man who gave you the Lovies!
Okay, fine, we'll go see him—
Mana!
Ouch!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Sorry about that.
Oh!
Hello!
Do you know him?
This person...
is the man who gave me the Lovies!
We meet again, baby.
What a pleasure.
For me to happen upon you two on the day I open for business,
why, it must be fate.
Business?
That's my shop.
Wow, it's cute!
Would you like to take a peek inside?
Totally!
Wait!
For what?
There's clearly something strange here!
I'm not buying that he just happened to open a store here.
I think he may be following you!
No way!
Something up?
Just who are you?
Oh, Rikka!
Mana transformed with the power of this Lovies you gave her!
Don't tell me you didn't know!
Now say something!
What's so funny?
Oh, I'm sorry.
So, she "transformed"?
I suppose such simple things make a huge difference to young girls.
This isn't figurative!
I really did transform, you know.
The power of my Lovies is the power to discover a new you.
To see you so pleased with it
pleases me as well.
Thank you.
Stop that now.
Oh, I know.
I found this while sorting my inventory.
Sharu!
It looks just like Mana's Lovies!
I'll give this to you.
M-Me?
Consider it a grand opening customer reward!
That's it!
Rikka?
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
You seem to like it.
Sorry...
but I cannot accept this!
Rikka...
You're a stranger to me,
so I will not take something from you without reason.
And above all,
I will not play to your whims!
You seem to be misunderstanding something.
Misunderstanding?
I did not choose you.
It was the Cure Lovies that did.
However you use its power
is up for none other than you to decide.
Just send the love letter already!
But...
What do I do if he never responds?
You can worry about that after you send it!
Now, woman up!
What? But, but...
Love letters are such a load.
I've never even gotten a New Year's card from a girl.
They oughta stop delivering mail period.
Let's leave.
Don't go there!
Junk like that is the reason nobody likes me.
It's not your fault.
Who was that?
I will grant...
your desire.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Whaddyawant!
They oughta stop checkin' mail baaaaaahxes!
Now come, Precure!
This time, I'll send you to your graves!
Letters're tasty.
What are you doing?!
I said, "Go berserk!"
Postcards're tasty.
You selfish jerk!
Bad news!
What is it?
I heard the heartbeat of a Selfish!
Rikka!
Your friend is calling for you.
I'll be right back.
Let's go!
Selfiiiish!
Junk mail's tasty.
So it's a Selfish!
It's eating the letters!
Let's go, Sharuru!
Gotcha!
Sharuru!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Oh poor goat who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
There you are, Precure!
Selfish, go deal with her!
Express mail's tasty.
Listen to me for like five seconds!
This is...
Rikka's air mail!
Give those letters baaaaaack!
What's wrong?
Fight, Cure Heart!
These letters are filled with their writers' emotions...
I will not allow you to eat them!
Go, Selfish!
Finish the Precure!
Selfiiiish!
Run, Cure Heart!
I will not give them up!
Mana!
I was always with Mana.
Every day was fun because Mana was there.
They were brilliant!
Student Council Candidate Application
That time of year again?
Next year's student council prez has gotta be Mana!
Totally.
M-Me?
Of course!
Only you could handle it.
Mana, you should run!
Totally!
Then join me, Rikka!
I'll be the president,
and you'll be my secretary!
Wait a minute!
Why me?
Because I need you, Rikka!
With you by my side,
I feel like I can do the impossible and more!
Mana...
Baaaaah!
Cure Heart!
However you use its power
is up for none other than you to decide.
This is my power!
Selfiiish!
What's that?
That light!
Rikka!
Raquel!
Place that light inside of me!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
I won't allow you to trample upon peoples' hearts!
I, Cure Diamond,
shall cool your hot head down!
Cure Diamond!
They got another one?
Selfish, get her!
Selfiiish!
My name's Aida Mana!
Nice to meet you!
With Mana as my wings, I can fly too!
No matter how far or high!
Raquel!
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
Love, love, loooove!
H-Huh?
Drat! I'll remember this!
Cure Heart!
Hm?
That's good.
I totally knew you could transform!
This is a good thing, right?
Rikka, good luck from here on out.
Raquel found a partner, so all that's left is Lance!
Lance?
Where's Lance?
Wait, how long has Lance been gone?
Huh? How long...
I think Lance was with us after school yesterday...
This is bad!
Lance is gone!
You seem to be in trouble.
Alice!
Good day, Mana, Rikka.
Who's that?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Mana, there is camera footage of you in a Precure's outfit.
Alice, really?
What do we do?
At this rate, the secret of the Precures will be exposed.
That's a problem!
As such, I shall be your Precure Producer!
P-Producer?
Dokidoki Precure:
I Must Refuse!
I Will Not Become A Precure!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!