- Fukuhara: AKIHISA YOSHII...
A PECULIAR YOUNG MAN
WHO IS QUITE PARTICULAR ABOUT
THINGS HE DOES.
- Akihisa: DOWN THE HATCH!
( sipping )
NOTHING LIKE SALT WATER SOUP.
AND I GOT SUGAR WATER
FOR DESSERT...
I'M GOING ALL OUT TONIGHT.
- THE DEGREE TO WHICH HE
IS PARTICULAR
SEEMS TO BE LOWERING EVERY DAY.
- ( doorbell rings )
- YEAH?
- Akira: LONG TIME NO SEE.
WHAT'S UP?
- ( slams door )
- GREAT. MY SISTER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara: AKIRA YOSHII.
E CUP.
SHE IS AKIHISA'S SISTER
AND LIVES ABROAD.
- WHY DID YOU COME HERE
DRESSED LIKE THAT, AKIRA?
- WHY IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
YELLING AT ME RIGHT NOW, AKI?
YOU'RE BEING SILLY.
- SAYS THE GIRL WEARING A ROBE.
- IF YOU'D SHUT UP, THEN I COULD
TELL YOU WHY I'M WEARING THIS.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY
HAVE A VERY GOOD REASON.
- I'M SORRY...
PLEASE GO AHEAD.
- YOU SEE, I HAD TO CARRY MY
HEAVY LUGGAGE FROM THE AIRPORT
ALL THE WAY TO THE TRAIN STATION
WITHOUT ANY AIR
CONDITIONING AT ALL.
WHEN I FINALLY
MADE IT ON THE TRAIN,
I WAS ABSOLUTELY DISGUSTED
TO SEE HOW SWEATY I'D BECOME.
- MM-HMM.
- WELL I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN SUCH A LONG TIME,
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
I LOOKED MY BEST.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO THINK BAD OF ME.
- MM-HMM.
- IN ORDER TO TAKE CARE OF THE
SWEAT, I CHANGED INTO A BATHROBE
BECAUSE THEY'RE SO
HIGHLY ABSORBENT.
- WHAT? THAT'S MESSED UP!
- THIS WAY I WAS ABLE TO REUNITE
WITH MY BABY BROTHER
WHILE MAINTAINING THE
SWEAT-FREE APPEARANCE
OF A DIGNIFIED, OLDER SISTER.
- THAT'S EVEN MORE MESSED UP!
- IT'S A GOOD THING
THE TRAIN WAS RATHER EMPTY.
IF IT HAD BEEN MORE CROWDED,
I WOULD HAVE BEEN THOROUGHLY
EMBARRASSED.
- WAIT... WHERE DID YOU CHANGE?
- YOU SHOULD KNOW.
THE REASON I CAME BACK
WAS TO TAKE CARE OF
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
- ( gasps )
- I NEED TO INVESTIGATE
HOW YOU'VE BEEN HANDLING
BEING ALONE
FOR THE PAST FEW MONTHS.
THEN I CAN DETERMINE WHETHER
OR NOT I SHOULD ALLOW YOU
TO CONTINUE
LIVING BY YOURSELF.
- WHAT?
- WHEN YOU FIRST
STARTED STAYING HERE
WITHOUT ANY ADULT SUPERVISION,
I GAVE YOU TWO RULES
TO FOLLOW.
I'M ASSUMING YOU STILL REMEMBER
WHAT THEY WERE.
- ARE YOU GONNA BE MAD
IF I SAY NO?
- OF COURSE I WON'T.
- WELL, GOOD...
IN THAT CASE, I ...
- WHY GET MAD WHEN I CAN
JUST GIVE YOU A KISS?
- REMEMBER THEM BOTH!
- AND THE KISS I HAVE IN
MIND WILL RUIN MY CHANCES
OF EVER GETTING MARRIED.
- THAT IS NOT EVEN
A LITTLE FUNNY!
- IT REALLY ISN'T.
RELAX. I'M THE ONE
WHO'LL DIE ALONE.
- HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO RELAX?
- THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
I MEAN, YOU'LL SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
FEELING GUILTY FOR WHAT
YOU'VE PUT YOUR POOR,
SPINSTER SISTER THROUGH.
- I REMEMBER THEM, I SWEAR.
PLEASE STOP THIS.
- GOOD. THEN WHY DON'T YOU
TELL ME WHAT THEY ARE.
- UM, THEY'RE, UH...
- OH, AKI. CLOSE YOUR EYES.
- ( screams )
I CAN ONLY PLAY VIDEO GAMES
THIRTY MINUTES A DAY
AND ILLICIT SEXUAL RELATIONSHIPS
ARE FORBIDDEN!
- I'M SO SORRY.
- WAS I WRONG?
- NO, YOU'RE RIGHT, I
JUST CAN'T KISS YOU NOW.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SORRY FOR THAT!
- IT'S A LOT CLEANER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
- WHY? I'VE NEVER REALLY
BEEN THAT MESSY.
- YES, BUT AS THEY SAY,
YOU'RE "AT THAT AGE".
I WAS EXPECTING
YOUR ROOM TO BE BURIED
UNDERNEATH TWO THOUSAND
DIRTY BOOKS BY NOW.
- I CAN'T AFFORD
TWO THOUSAND DIRTY BOOKS!
- SO BASICALLY,
YOU HAVE AT LEAST ONE.
A DEDUCTION OF 20 POINTS
FOR A SEMI-ILLICIT SEXUAL
RELATIONSHIP.
- WHAT ARE THE POINTS FOR?
- I'M SCORING YOU
BASED ON THOSE CONDITIONS
TO SEE IF YOU'VE EARNED THE
RIGHT TO CONTINUE LIVING ALONE.
FOR THE FINAL SCORE,
I'LL AVERAGE EVERYTHING HERE
WITH YOUR NEXT TEST
AT SCHOOL.
- GREAT. NOW I HAVE TO
MAKE SURE I GET
AT LEAST TWENTY EXTRA POINTS
ON MY MIDTERM EXAM.
THAT WAY IT WILL CANCEL OUT
THOSE POINTS.
- DON'T GET AHEAD
OF YOURSELF, YET.
ANY OTHER ILLICIT
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIPS
I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
- IF SO, WHAT WOULD
THAT SCORE BE?
- IF YOU'RE CAUGHT
HOLDING HANDS WITH A GIRL,
SUBTRACT ONE HUNDRED POINTS.
- ONE HUNDRED POINTS?
- IF YOU WERE TO TAKE GIRLS
OUT TO THE MOVIES,
OR TREAT THEM TO CREPES,
OR EVEN IF THEY MAKE
YOU LUNCH OR WAFFLES
OR ANYTHING TO THAT EFFECT,
THAT WOULD BE MINUS FIFTY
THOUSAND POINTS.
- ( muffled grunting )
- Akira: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- OH! NOTHING!
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
A HEALTHY YOUNG MAN.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH YOUR BODY YET.
- HOLD ON A MINUTE,
I NEVER SAID THAT.
- DON'T WORRY. I'LL ALLOW YOU
A LITTLE FUN.
ILLICIT SEXUAL
RELATIONSHIPS WITH GIRLS
ARE AGAINST THE RULES.
BUT ILLICIT SEXUAL
RELATIONSHIPS WITH GUYS,
THAT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
- IT IS NOT PERFECTLY FINE!
AND QUIT SAYING ILLICIT
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIPS!
YOU'RE CREEPING ME OUT!
- OH, STAR LIGHT. STAR BRIGHT.
- NOT GOOD.
YOUR SCORES ARE MUCH WORSE THAN
I EXPECTED THEM TO BE.
- I TRIED REALLY HARD
IN MY OWN WAY.
- TRYING HARD IS ONLY
A MEANS TO AN END.
IF ALL YOU DO IS TRY WITHOUT
EVER ACCOMPLISHING ANYTHING,
WHAT'S THE POINT,
LITTLE BROTHER?
FAILING IS FAILING
NO MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT.
- THANKS. THAT'S JUST
WHAT I WANTED TO HEAR.
- GET BETTER GRADES
AND I WON'T HAVE TO NAG YOU.
JUST ONE DECENT SCORE
WOULD BE HELPFUL.
- WELL, YOU'RE NOT PERFECT.
NOT AT EVERYTHING.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- Akihisa: COOKING.
- MAKING FOOD HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH ACADEMICS.
- BUT IT'S IMPORTANT FOR LIFE.
BESIDES, THE ONLY THING
YOU'RE GOOD AT IS SCHOOL WORK.
I'LL BE FORCED TO KISS YOU
UNTIL YOU SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
- I'M SORRY. I WAS WRONG.
- YUUJI. I WANT TO SEE
YOUR CELL PHONE.
- Yuuji: WHAT FOR?
- I SAW A SHOW LAST NIGHT
THAT SAID YOU CAN TELL
IF YOUR PARTNER'S CHEATING
BY LOOKING FOR SPECIFIC CLUES
ON THEIR PHONE. GIVE ME.
- HELL, NO.
( screams in pain )
MY EYES! YOU CAN'T GIVE LASER
EYE SURGERY WITH YOUR FINGERS!
- OH MY GOD!
- FINE, BE THAT WAY.
I DON'T MIND TAKING IT
BY FORCE.
- HEY! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
- I HEARD IT WAS SEXY
TO BE NAKED
WITH ONLY A GUY'S SHIRT ON.
- YEAH, THAT'S FOR CHICKS,
NOT A DUDE!
- LET ME BE THE JUDGE.
- OKAY, I GIVE UP! TAKE IT.
YOU CAN HAVE THE PHONE!
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO SOUND
SO DISAPPOINTED.
- GEEZ. HERE.
- YUUJI, YOUR EMAIL.
YOU GET MORE FROM YOSHII
THAN FROM ME.
- YEAH, SO WHAT?
- THAT MEANS YOU'RE HAVING
A LOVE AFFAIR WITH YOSHII.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- Akihisa: CAN I STAY OVERNIGHT
AT YOUR PLACE?
I KINDA DON'T WANT TO
GO HOME TONIGHT.
- WAIT A SEC... SHOUKO... I...
( screams )
- TAKEN CARE OF...
- Hideyoshi: GOOD MORNING,
AKIHISA.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
IT'S WEIRD, BUT YOU LOOK A LOT
HEALTHIER THAN YOU NORMALLY DO.
- YEAH. I GOT TO EAT
ACTUAL FOOD THIS MORNING.
- Fukuhara: AKIHISA SOLD HIS
MANGA AND VIDEO GAMES
TO A SECOND HAND SHOP
AND GOT MONEY TO BUY FOOD.
- EVEN IF IT JUST
GETS ME THROUGH AKIRA'S STAY,
AT LEAST SHE'LL THINK
I'M TAKING CARE OF MYSELF.
OTHERWISE, SHE'LL TAKE
MORE POINTS AWAY.
- NO PANTS DAY, HUH?
- NO, IT'S NOT NO PANTS DAY,
YOU IDIOT!
I GOT PUNISHED BECAUSE OF
YOUR SUPER WEIRD EMAIL.
- THERE WAS NOTHING WEIRD
ABOUT MY EMAIL.
- WHY DON'T YOU TRY
READING IT OUT LOUD THEN.
- CAN I STAY OVERNIGHT
AT YOURPLACE?
I KINDA DON'T WANT TO
GO HOME TONIGHT.
- OF COURSE! NOW IT SEEMS
SO OBVIOUS!
- YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
EXPERIMENT UNTIL YOU'RE OLDER!
- THAT'S JUST OBSCENE, YOSHII!
UH...
BAKA AND TEST!
UH, YOSHII,
GO TO THE NURSE'S OFFICE.
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS THINK
I'M SICK WHEN I'M STUDYING?
- SO WHAT HAPPENED, AKI?
I MEAN, WHY ARE YOU
STUDYING ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- YOU'RE ACTING
A LITTLE STRANGE TODAY.
- REALLY? I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- WOW. YOU'VE GOT QUITE THE
WELL-PREPARED LUNCH TODAY.
- I KNOW. NICE FOR A CHANGE.
- LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
WHO MADE THIS FOR YOU ANYWAY?
- OH, I MADE IT.
- Minami: LIAR.
- Mizuki: YEAH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- WHAT? I AM NOT LYING!
- SOMEONE SUPER TALENTED
HAD TO MAKE THIS.
MAYBE IT WAS YUUJI OR KOUTA.
- TELL US THE TRUTH , AKI!
COME ON!
- JUST CONFESS,
WHO REALLY MADE IT FOR YOU?
- I THINK I'LL JUST LEAVE IT
TO YOUR IMAGINATION.
- AKIHISA, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO HOME TODAY.
- WHY DO THE GOOD ONES
ALWAYS PLAY FOR THE OTHER TEAM?
- NO! I REFUSE TO BELIEVE IT!
- I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
- WHAT'D YOU IMAGINE?
AND WHY THE HELL
IS KUBO IN OUR CLASSROOM?
- HEY, SO I WAS WONDERING,
WHY'D YOU WANT TO STAY OVER
AT MY PLACE ANYWAY?
- WHAT? OH, I JUST THOUGHT
WE COULD STUDY.
- DON'T LIE TO ME.
YOU DIDN'T LET ME FINISH!
MIDTERMS ARE COMING UP.
I GUESS GETTING A GROUP TOGETHER
TO STUDY ISN'T A BAD IDEA.
- REALLY?
- LET'S DO IT OVER
AT YOUR PLACE.
- NO, NO! NOT MY PLACE! TODAY
ISN'T GOOD. NO, NOT AT ALL!
IT'S NOT GOOD AT ALL!
- PRETTY SURE HE'S H
IDING SOMETHING.
- SHOULD PROBABLY CHECK IT OUT.
- GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
- NO! YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA!
IT'S JUST MESSY! VERY MESSY...
- THAT'S OKAY!
I'LL HELP YOU CLEAN!
- NO. I'LL DO IT.
NEEDS TO BE SOMETHING A GIRL
WOULDN'T WANT TO TOUCH!
THIS MESS IS BAD.
IT'S TWO THOUSAND DIRTY BOOKS.
- I'LL STILL HELP!
- WE CAN GET RID OF THEM!
- YEAH, I'M IN TOO.
- Akihisa: DAMN IT! THAT ISN'T
WHAT YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO SAY!
- Announcer: BAKA AND TEST.
- SO, UH, WE'RE REALLY
DOING THIS THEN?
- LOOK DUDE, WE JUST
WANNA KNOW WHAT YOU'RE HIDING.
- YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
RATHER SUSPICIOUS ALL DAY.
- Kouta: I BET HE'S GOT
A SECRET GIRLFRIEND.
- IS THAT TRUE?
WHAT'S A SECRET GIRLFRIEND?
- UM, YOU SHOULD ASK KOUTA.
- CALM DOWN, MINAMI.
YOU KNOW YOSHII WOULD NEVER
EVEN DREAM OF DATING SOMEONE
BEHIND OUR BACKS LIKE THAT.
- Mizuki: ISN'T THAT
RIGHT, YOSHII?
- Akihisa: WHY ARE
YOU SQUINTING?
- WELL, IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT
THERE'S PROBABLY
NOTHING GOING ON.
THAT'S YOUR CUE, AKIHISA.
OPEN THE DOOR.
- I DON'T WANNA.
- DO YOU WANT TO GET PANTSED
LIKE I DID? THIS IS YOUR CHOICE.
- IF YOU COULD LOOK UP AT THE
SKY WITH TEARS IN YOUR EYES,
THAT'D BE GREAT.
- WHAT FOR?
SO YOU CAN PROFIT FROM MY PAIN?
- YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE? I MEAN
TO MAKE IT MORE MARKETABLE?
YOU SHOULD HAVE HIM UNBUTTON
HIS FIRST TWO BUTTONS.
- I AM NOT A PRODUCT TO BE
MARKETED! FINE, I'LL DO IT!
I'LL OPEN IT
IF YOU'LL LEAVE ME ALONE!
- Minami, Mizuki: YOUR SHIRT?
- Akihisa: NO! THE DOOR!
- ( Akihisa screaming
in frustration )
I CAN'T EVEN MAKE SOMETHING UP
TO EXPLAIN THIS.
- NO, I THINK WE KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- Kouta: I'M SO JEALOUS
I COULD KILL HIM.
- THIS IS NOT A VERY GOOD
THING, YOSHII.
YOU BOUGHT A BRA SIZE
THAT WOULD NEVER FIT YOU.
SMALLER CUP WOULD BE BETTER.
- All: SHE'S REFUSING
TO FACE IT.
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
- A COTTON PAD FOR MAKEUP,
I THINK.
- WRONG. MUST BE A FISH CAKE.
- All: A FISH CAKE?
- LOOK!
- DUDE, THAT IS DEFINITELY
SOMETHING A CHICK WOULD EAT.
- ( Mizuki crying )
- ARE YOU ALRIGHT, HIMEJI?
- I CAN'T KEEP DENYING
THIS ANYMORE!
- SERIOUSLY? UNDERWEAR
AND MAKEUP ARE OKAY.
BUT ONE STUPID LUNCH
SENDS YOU OVER THE EDGE?
- HELLO. I SEE WE HAVE COMPANY.
- AN OLDER WOMAN!
WITH... HUGE BOOBS!
HOW CAN YOU BE SO CRUEL?
- Minami: YOU ARE TEARING
OUT MY HEART!
- I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
SHE'S MY OLDER SISTER.
- All: YOUR SISTER?
THAT'S RIGHT. I'M AKIRA
YOSHII. THANK YOU.
IT'S VERY NICE OF YOU
TO BE FRIENDS
WITH MY EXTREMELY
STUPID BROTHER.
I'M SURE IT'S NOT EASY, UNLESS
HE USUALLY ISN'T THIS RUDE.
- WOW. SHE LOOKS NORMAL EVEN IF
SHE IS BEING MEAN. I'LL TAKE IT!
- HEY THERE, I'M YUUJI SAKAMOTO.
- I'M KOUTA TSUCHIYA.
- AND I'M HIDEYOSHI KINOSHITA.
PEOPLE USUALLY ASSUME
I'M A GIRL, BUT...
- YOU'RE A BOY, AREN'T YOU?
YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE WHO'S
EVER RECOGNIZED ME AS A GUY.
THAT'S AMAZING!
- WELL, IT'S KIND OF OBVIOUS.
THERE'S NO WAY MY STUPID, UGLY,
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING LITTLE BROTHER
WOULD BE ABLE TO GET GIRLS
TO BE FRIENDS WITH HIM.
ALTHOUGH I MUST SAY
THE TWO OF YOU
ARE RATHER STRANGE
LOOKING BOYS.
- WHY ARE YOU SO RUDE
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
GO BACK TO BEING NICE, OKAY?
ALL THREE OF THEM ARE GIRLS!
- HOW MANY WAYS CAN I PUT IT?
- GIRLS? REALLY.?
WHEN DID YOU START BRINGING
GIRLS INTO THIS HOME,
AND WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THEM
WHEN THEY'RE HERE?
- AKihisa: CRAP!
ILLICIT SEXUAL
RELATIONSHIPS WITH GIRLS
GETS YOU TWO HUNDRED
POINTS TAKEN AWAY.
- ( Akihisa crying helplessly )
- AKIHISA, IT HASN'T BEEN EASY
FOR YOU EITHER, HAS IT?
- YUUJI...
- HOWEVER, I WILL ALLOW ILLICIT
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIPS
WITH BOYS, THOUGH.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
- IN FACT, I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
TEN POINTS!
- WHAT? LIKE THAT'S SUPPOSED TO
MAKE ME HAPPY?
- HEY, AKIHISA!
SINCE WE CAME HERE UNINVITED,
WE CAN AT LEAST HELP
YOU MAKE DINNER.
- THANKS. THAT'D BE COOL, MAN.
- I CAN HELP.
- MAYBE I COULD COOK!
- ( all gasp )
- NO WAY. WE'LL BE FINE.
YOU STAY HERE.
- YEAH, WE GOT IT.
THANKS FOR OFFERING.
- Mizuki: REALLY? ARE YOU SURE?
- HEY SIS! KEEP 'EM COMPANY.
- SURE. WOULD YOU ALL LIKE TO
SEE SOME OLD PHOTOS OF AKI?
- YEAH, I MEAN IF THAT'S OKAY.
- Akira: LET'S SEE
THE EMBARRASSING ONES FIRST.
- Akihisa: ANYTHING BUT THOSE?
- WE'RE GONNA LIVE.
- SO, THEN,
WHAT ARE WE MAKING?
- LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE EVERYTHING
WE NEED TO MAKE PAELLA.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
IT'S ACTUALLY MY FAVORITE DISH.
- CONVENIENT. DID SHE KNOW
WE WERE COMING OVER?
- NO. SHE CAN'T COOK
TO SAVE HER LIFE EITHER.
MUST HAVE BOUGHT TOO MUCH
BY ACCIDENT.
- ( girls laughing )
- Yuuji: YEAH, PUT IT
OVER THERE.
- OKAY, HERE WE GO! THESE ARE
PICTURES OF AKI TAKING A BATH
WHEN HE WAS TWO.
- OH! LOOK, HE'S ADORABLE!
- AND THESE ARE PICTURES OF AKI
TAKING A BATH WHEN HE WAS FOUR.
- Minami: AW, HE FELL ASLEEP!
- THESE ARE PICTURES OF AKI
TAKING A BATH WHEN HE WAS SEVEN.
- THIS WAS IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, RIGHT?
- THESE ARE OF AKI TAKING A
BATH WHEN HE WAS TEN YEARS OLD.
- WAIT A SEC! HOW COME I'M
ALWAYS TAKING A BATH?
- THESE ARE OF AKI TAKING A BATH
WHEN HE WAS THIRTEEN.
- ( all gasp )
- WAIT. WHY'D YOU ALL GET QUIET?
- AND THESE, ARE OF AKI
TAKING A BATH YESTERDAY.
- NO!
AH! WHEN DID YOU TAKE THOSE?
PLEASE DON'T AT MY
PRIVATE PARTS!
PLEASE DON'T LOOK!
PLEASE DON'T LOOK AT THEM!
- Yuuji: COME ON, BATH BOY.
YOU'VE GOT SOME COOKING TO DO.
- Akihisa: NO!
- THIS LOOKS DELICIOUS.
- LOOK AT THAT.
YOU MADE PAELLA.
- IS IT OKAY?
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT YOU BOUGHT
ALL THOSE GROCERIES FOR.
- IT SMELLS REALLY GOOD, AKI.
- WOW. I HAD NO IDEA YOU
COULD ACTUALLY COOK.
THAT'S SUPER NEAT.
- ( Akihisa screaming
in frustration )
HOW DID YOU NOT KNOW?
- OH, NO. AKI'S YELLING AGAIN,
THAT'S NOT VERY NICE.
MINUS TEN POINTS.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
THIS IS ALL YOUR DAMN FAULT!
GAH, WHY DO YOU HATE ME?
IT'S LIKE YOUR DOING YOUR BEST
TO STRESS ME OUT!
- AKI, YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT I COULD NEVER HATE YOU.
- WHAT?
- I CARE ABOUT YOU AS A WOMAN.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- THERE'S AN OLD, FAMOUS SAYING
THAT GOES LIKE THIS.
THE DUMBER THE CHILD
THE CUTER...
- GIVE IT UP, AKIHISA.
IT SEEMS TO ME SHE
LOVES YOU MORE
THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THE WORLD.
BUT YUUJI, WOULDN'T
THAT MEAN SHE THINKS
I'M THE DUMBEST
PERSON IN THE WORLD?
- SO WHAT IF SHE DOES, AKI?
I HAPPEN TO THINK YOU'RE
THE DUMBEST PERSON
IN THE WHOLE WORLD, TOO!
- SO DO I! YOU'RE
STUPIDER THAN ANYONE ELSE
ON THIS ENTIRE PLANET
IN MY OPINION!
- STOP IT! WHY ARE YOU
GOING OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO HURT MY PRECIOUS FEELINGS!
- WOW, YOU REALLY ARE AN IDIOT.
- OKAY, NOW THAT DINNER'S
FINALLY OVER, WE SHOULD STUDY.
- IF YOU'D LIKE, I CAN HELP
ALL OF YOU. I REALLY DON'T MIND.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I WENT TO SCHOOL OVERSEAS
AND GOT A DEGREE IN EDUCATION,
SO I'M KIND OF TRAINED FOR IT.
- WHERE OVERSEAS?
- JUST IN BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS.
- Yuuji: YOU'RE KIDDING ME. DO
YOU MEAN... SHE WENT TO HARVARD?
- ( Minami, Mizuki gasp )
- INTERESTING...
SHE GOT THE GOOD GENES.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN,
YOU, JERK?
- LOOK WHAT I FOUND
UNDER AKI'S BED TODAY.
THEY MUST BE FOR
REFERENCE PURPOSES.
- Akihisa: BUT THOSE ARE MY
ULTIMATE OF TOP SECRET SECRETS!
- UNFORTUNATELY, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO TAKE AWAY SIXTY POINTS.
- SO, YOU'RE SUBTRACTING
TEN POINTS PER BOOK?
- NO. YOU'RE LOSING POINTS
FOR NOT HAVING DIRTY BOOKS
ABOUT SISTERS.
- NO! IS THERE NO END?
THIS IS BRUTAL!
- THEY LOOK LIKE PHYS. ED
REFERENCES TO ME.
- STOP! I CAN'T SHARE THOSE
WITH THEM, THEY'VE BEEN USED!
- AKI TENDS TO STUDY BY FOCUSING
ON VERY SPECIFIC SUBJECTS.
APPARENTLY HE LIKES THE
SUBJECT OF GIRLS
WITH BIG BREASTS AND PONYTAILS.
- ALL RIGHT THEN. LET'S GET TO
THAT STUDYING, SHALL WE?
- AND JUST WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TO YOUR HAIR, MIZUKI?
- I THOUGHT I'D JUST TIE IT BACK
SO IT DOESN'T GET IN MY WAY.
- OH, HERE!
I CAN DO IT FOR YOU!.
- OW! YOU'RE HURTING ME, MINAMI,
PLEASE STOP THE PAIN!.
- I DON'T NEED YOU TO HELP ME!
- WAIT A SECOND.
YOUR HAIR DOESN'T
NORMALLY GET IN YOUR WAY.
- ANOTHER ONE HUNDRED POINTS
TO BE DEDUCTED.
- WHAT? HOW COME?
- TRUST ME, LITTLE BROTHER.
ONE OF THESE DAYS, YOU'LL
UNDERSTAND WHY.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, MAN?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
- THE OTHER ONE THOUSAND NINE
HUNDRED NINETY-FOUR BOOKS.
- YOU THOUGHT I WAS SERIOUS?
- Mizuki: HEY THERE.
GOOD MORNING, YOSHII.
- Minami: WHAT'S UP, AKI?
- HEY GIRLS. MORNING.
DID YOU CHANGE YOUR HAIR
STYLE, HIMEJI?
- OH, YES. I JUST WANTED
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
- DID YOU CHANGE YOUR
BOOB STYLE, MINAMI?
- NO WAY!
THEY JUST GREW OVER NIGHT!
- SERIOUSLY?
- YES, SERIOUSLY.
I'M STILL GROWING.
- ( popping sound )
- CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO
DISGRACE THE FEMALE BREAST
WITH SUCH IMPERTINENCE.
- ( Minami growls )
- YESTERDAY WAS FUN, WASN'T IT?
- WE MANAGED TO GET
SOME STUDYING DONE, TOO.
- YEAH, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE I
WON'T BE ALLOWED TO LIVE ALONE.
I WISH SHE'D GO BACK TO AMERICA.
- YOU SHOULDN'T TALK THAT WAY
ABOUT YOUR FAMILY.
- Yuuji: SHE SEEMED
PRETTY COOL TO ME.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
SHE ALWAYS TAKES AWAY POINTS AND
TRIES TO KISS ME.
I THINK THIS IS ALL JUST
BECAUSE SHE HATES ME.
- Mizuki: THAT'S NOT
TRUE AT ALL.
YOSHII, YOUR SISTER LOVES YOU.
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS.
- SO SHE REALLY DOES THINK
I'M STUPIDEST.
- DON'T BE SILLY. HER ONLY
REASON FOR BEING HERE IS
TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE OKAY,
WHICH JUST GOES TO SHOW
HOW MUCH SHE CARES ABOUT YOU.
- SHE TRAVELED ALL THE WAY HERE
FROM AMERICA FOR YOU.
DIDN'T HAVE ANY OTHER
REASON, DID SHE?
- Akihisa: MAYBE THEY'RE RIGHT
ABOUT MY SISTER.
WHAT SHOULD I MAKE
FOR DINNER?
SHE HASN'T BEEN BACK
HOME FOR AWHILE NOW.
I KNOW WHAT I'LL COOK.
JAPANESE FOOD.
I'M HOME, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU HAVE CLOTHES ON.
- VERY FUNNY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY? GOOD?
- IT'S OKAY. I'LL GET DINNER
STARTED HERE IN A SECOND.
- DINNER? NOT SO FAST, AKI.
- AREN'T YOU HUNGRY?
YOUR MIDTERMS
ARE COMING UP SOON?
THINK ABOUT THIS.
SHOULD YOU BE WASTING YOUR
TIME MAKING ME DINNER?
- WELL, NO.
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T.
BUT YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY,
SO I THOUGHT...
- YOU DIDN'T THINK.
YOU'RE MISTAKING THE MEANS
FOR THE END AGAIN.
THE REASON I CAME BACK
WAS TO CHECK ON YOU
AND MAKE SURE YOU WERE OKAY.
IF YOU'RE WASTING TIME ON ME,
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH WASTING
MY TIME, AS WELL.
ON TOP OF THAT,
I DON'T WANT YOU TO USE ME
ME AS AN EXCUSE
WHEN YOUR GRADES SUFFER.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COOK FOR ME,
I'M DOING JUST FINE.
IN FACT, I'LL MAKE US DINNER
WHILE YOU STUDY.
- HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
- SOUNDS PRETTY STUPID TO ME!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
ALL YOU EVER CARE ABOUT
ARE THOSE DUMB TEST RESULTS.
FINE. I'LL GO STUDY, THEN!
SHE'S SO STUPID.
I'LL MAKE SURE
I GET A GOOD GRADE.
THAT'LL SHUT HER UP.
- ( clock chiming )
- OH, COME ON.
- GOOD MORNING, YOSHII.
HOW ARE YOU?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, AKI?
- PLEASE DON'T TALK TO ME..
THE STUFF I MEMORIZED AND
CRAMMED INTO MY HEAD
MIGHT COME OUT.
- WHEN'S THE IDES OF MARCH?
- O... KAY.
GUESS WE'LL LET YOU STUDY.
- Nishimura: ALL RIGHT. WE'RE
ABOUT TO BEGIN THE TEST. READY?
BEGIN!
- ( reading to himself )
I CAN DO THIS. QUESTION ONE.
334 BC! THE LAST KING OF THE
ACHAEMENID EMPIRE OF PERSIA WAS.
ALEXANDER THE GREAT!
NEXT!
- I BET HE'S TAKING
THE TEST RIGHT NOW.
WELL THEN, I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD START TOO.
- ALL RIGHT. I DID MY BEST.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE TIME LEFT
OVER TO DOUBLE CHECK MY ANSWERS.
- ( clock chimes )
- OKAY. PUT YOUR PENCILS DOWN.
LOSERS IN THE BACK,
COLLECT THE ANSWER PAGES.
GOODBYE SWEET LIFE
ALL ON MY OWN.
- REALLY? ALEXANDER THE GREAT
IS MY BROTHER.
YOU PUT THE FIRST ANSWER WHERE
YOU SHOULD'VE PUT YOUR NAME,
SO EVERY ANSWER
YOU PUT DOWN WAS OFF BY ONE.
- PLEASE! DON'T CALL ME
ALEXANDER THE GREAT ANYMORE!
- Akira: HOW ABOUT
DARIUS THE THIRD?
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO
HUMILIATE ME LIKE THIS?
I COULD'VE GOTTEN A DECENT SCORE
IF I HADN'T SCREWED THAT
SIMPLE THING UP.
- DO YOU THINK THEY'D
FORGIVE YOU IF YOU MADE
THE SAME MISTAKE
ON A COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAM?
- NO. BUT I REALLY DID
TRY MY HARDEST.
- YOU KEEP SAYING THAT.
REMEMBER OUR TALK ABOUT "TRYING"
BEING A MEANS TO AN END?
- YEAH, I DO.
SHE IS RUTHLESS.
- ( frustrated grunt )
- ( water dripping )
-( tap turning on )
- IT'S A MESS IN HERE.
WAIT. SHE CAN'T COOK.
THESE LOOK LIKE
FAILED PAELLA DISHES.
I WONDER.
WAS SHE PRACTICING
MAKING MY FAVORITE MEAL?
- Akira: TRYING HARD
IS ONLY A MEANS TO AN END.
IF YOU BECOME PROUD
OF THE EFFORT ITSELF,
YOU'RE MISTAKING
THE MEANS FOR THE END.
- FOR REAL? SHE'S SO STUPID.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Akihisa: HEY, AKIRA?
- YEAH?
- THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
AND... I REALLY DO LOVE YOU.
- YOU DO?
- OF COURSE I DO,
BUT ONLY AS A SISTER.
- THAT'S SWEET,
BUT I'M STILL NOT GOING TO
IGNORE YOUR TEST SCORE.
- WELL, THAT SUCKS.
- SO, AKI...
- WHAT?
- I WAS THINKING THAT
MAYBE ONE OF THESE DAYS
I COULD MAKE DINNER FOR YOU.
- REALLY?
- REALLY. BUT ONLY IF
I FEEL LIKE IT.
- YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S FAIR.
- HEY, AKIRA?
- YES, AKI.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT THE BEST
SPICE IN THE WORLD IS?
- HMM. HOW SHOULD I KNOW,
I DON'T COOK.
FINE, I GIVE UP.
TELL ME, WHAT IS THE BEST SPICE?
- THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION!
- Fukuhara: QUESTION TEN:
NAME THE JAPANESE NOVELIST
WHO INTRODUCED
THE "ADOLESCENT DETECTIVE GANG"
AND THE "MYSTERY MAN OF TWENTY
FACES" TO THE WORLD.
- Akihisa: THE THIEF
IS AMONG US!
- IT'S NOT ME.
- NEXT TIME: PREP TESTS,
MYSTERIOUS THIEVES,
AND LOVE LETTERS!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.