This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old.
You
have
no
new
mess
ages.
Lens.
We were in danger the other day.
A word appeared backwards in our handbook.
It was a dangerous word that was trying to shorten Mitsuki's life.
Thanks to Takuto, everything turned out fine, but what will happen the next time?
We will have to keep an eye
on Mitsuki from now on.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Hey, how much longer do I have to be doing this?!
Ah, please don't move.
I have to hand in this homework
assignment tomorrow.
I get it!
I need a break.
Me too!
Well, well? Show me!
What!?
What the hell is that?!
It's you!
How the hell does that  look like me?!
Look!
Huh?
Cat ears.
Come on...
Hey, hey, Takuto, look at my picture, too!
You know...!
I drew twinkling stars in your eyes.
Oh, maybe I should do that as well.
Hell No!
How about some flowers in the background?
Don't take something like that to school!
Why not?
It sucks.
What do you mean it sucks?!
I put all my heart into it!
It doesn't matter how much heart you put into it... it still sucks.
I posed forever for you, and then you drew a crappy picture like that!
I won't be a model for you anymore!
Eh?
But it's my homework...
Like I care!
Huh? Wait, Takuto!
It's not that  bad...
But... maybe it really does suck...
Spring Onion Ramen and the Saint's Stone
Huh?
Oh my...
What happened?
I'm so hungry... I can't move...
Hungry, you say?
If he's lying here like that...
...the neighbors will start spreading rumors!
R-Really? Please come in.
I'm sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Huh? Where did he go?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Oh no!
It's bad enough that he was lying outside, but if he's lying in the house like this,
what will the neighbors say?!!!
A-Are you all right?
Oh... oh! Sorry.
I was checking the feng shui  of the house when I got sleepy all of a sudden.
Let's dig in!
Eh?
Feng shui ?
Did the shoes look like this?
Wait for me, Takuto!
Takuto! Your shoelace!
Huh?
Your shoelace is undone.
Come to think of it, she didn't
draw my shoes, did she?
I'm obliged to you.
Not at all. You're welcome.
Oh. Please accept this in return.
I wonder what it is?
Huh?
Give me your hand.
Y-Yes.
What's this?
The Saint's Stone.
I thought he would give me something better...
Saint's Stone... what's this supposed to be?
Did you say something?
N-Nothing at all.
Then it's all good.
Well then, I'm obliged to you.
Not at all. You're welcome.
Phew.
That thing sure was heavy.
M-Madam.
Welcome back, madam.
I'm back.
What's that?
T-This is the Saint's Stone.
An old man left it here...
He said it brings good luck...
Throw it out.
Yes.
Shinigami
Expulsion
I wonder if she managed to draw the shoes.
Hey, Takuto.
Huh? What is it?
How was my drawing?
It was okayish...
Look. It's good isn't it?
What should I say...
I put all my love for you into it!
Huh? All your love...
I put all my heart into it!
I understand that you did.
Really? You do?
Yes! Love! Love! Love!
It was love that was moving my paintbrush!
Huh?
Let's go back.
Hey, wait!
Geez.
He didn't have to get so mad...
Or say that it sucks...
Huh?
What was that?
Since we finally get some time alone, let's go out on a date!
Enough. Let's go home.
Shinigami
Expulsion
W-What the...
Takuto, what did you do?
I didn't do anything!
One more time!
Here we go...
Takuto!
It hurt!
What happened?
Dunno.
But something's wrong.
W-What's this?!
Let's see... uh... uh...
Oh no, it's not in here.
Then... in that case...
In case of troubles not mentioned in the entries...
Huh?
"...contact your supervisor directly."
Is it you, chief?
It's Spring Onion Ramen.
Yes. I have a question.
We, the Shinigami...
...we've been able to enter the house before, but suddenly, now we can't...
Huh? There's a reason?
What is it?
Yes... yes... what?!
There's a barrier?!
What?! A barrier?!
Did he tell you the cause of this barrier?!
Yes.
The chief said that...
...the barrier is caused by...
...a stone called the Saint's Stone.
Saint's Stone?
You can recognize it from...
...a sign on the back that says Shinigami Expulsion.
And, what do we do with that stone?
We have to break it or throw it in the water.
All right...
...so I say, but we still can't get past that barrier.
Let's meet her.
Okay.
But who could have brought that stone?
Maybe that grandmother?
What if she  did it?
She wouldn't do something like that!
I'm not so sure...
If we aren't there for her, then she's the one who's in trouble!
Well that's very true...
Geez...
Anyways, let's get in touch with her.
Hello, this is Mitsuki.
Ooshige-san?
Public Phone
Who is it?
Hello! Hello!
It's me, Takuto!
And Meroko!
Stop fooling around!
I'm not fooling around!
Stop harassing me!
Stupid! Don't hang up!
She hung up...
But what did she mean by "harassing"?
Could it be that the barrier doesn't let our voice in either?
Since this didn't work, that's  next.
"Come out of the house. - Takuto."
Okay. This should work.
It isn't okay at all!
Stop it, Meroko!
But... do you even know what you're writing on?!
Come out
of the house.
- Takuto
This?
Yes!
Come out
of the house.
- Takuto
My picture!
This is an emergency. Forgive me.
Okay, it's ready.
All right...
It worked!
Man! Just when I'm cleaning up!
There you go...
It came back!
Huh? Why?
What happened?
Oh!
What is it?
The letters have disappeared.
Really!
Can it be...
My drawing's gone too!
Written stuff can't pass the barrier, either...
My drawing of Takuto...
Takuto and Meroko... they're not back yet.
Maybe he's still mad at me...
Miso soup with tea.
Pickles with sauce.
What's wrong with her?
Well, he's stubborn anyway.
Huh?!
Takuto and Meroko didn't come back after all...
Did I hurt his feelings that much?
Stop it already.
She'll go to school tomorrow anyway.
Tomorrow will be too late!
Why?
She needs us today...
Hello!
Huh? Who is it?
Don't you recognize my voice, honey?
Please, stop harassing me!
Hey, don't hang up!
Huh?
Village Pro
It's me, Ooshige!
Ooshige-san!
What did you mean?
I'm the only one who knows your phone number.
If you ask "Who is it?", maybe it's because you have a boyfriend...
There's nobody else for me but Eichi-kun!
You're right.
Then what is it?
Yesterday, somebody harassed me on the phone.
Eh? Really?
That worries me, should we change the number?
No. It was only one phone call.
Is it really all right?
Yes.
I see.
Anyway, about the meeting at Ikebukuro today...
...please be there 30 minutes early.
Y-Yes.
That's all I wanted to tell you.
See you at the meeting.
Yes.
I'll have to leave at 12 if I don't want to be late.
What should I do?
Without Takuto and Meroko,
I can't change and go out!
It hurts...
Just give up already.
I won't give up when we already got this far!
Damn! We could do something if only she would come out...
Mitsuki?
All right.
Let's ask the housekeeper to send her out.
Leave that to me!
Are you perhaps...
What is it?
Who are you?!
Would you happen to be from the household of Kouyama-sama?
I am, but...
That's great.
Actually...
I am greatly indebted to the young lady, Kouyama-sama...
...and I'd like to express my gratitude to her.
Would you please send her out?
I-I'll go and ask madam!
Please do...
See? Everything went well.
What went well?
Didn't she just run away
because you scared her?
What's this fireball for anyway?!
It's a prop.
(Note: Originally a Chinese story; there are also many film versions.)
From the "Ghost Story of Peony Lantern"?
Bingo!
You got it!
Huh? What are you doing?!
Just as I thought... I can't leave it to you.
I'll do something about this somehow.
What should I do?
If I cancel...
...it'll be a problem for Ooshige-san and the others who are waiting for me.
Pizza from Wakaouji-sensei?
I wonder why...
Huh?
What's this?
"Mitsuki:
We can't enter the house
because of the  Saint's Stone.
It's a stone that has  Shinigami Expulsion written on its back.
It's okay if you don't understand it!
Just write down and deliver the note together with the pizza!
If you don't know why, then come outside, and we'll think of something.
Anyways, let's go."
So that's why they didn't come back, it was because of the barrier.
Takuto... I'm sorry I doubted you.
Okay, nobody's around!
Mitsuki-chan! Where do you think you're going?
J-Just for a walk.
You cannot!
But... I feel fine today...
I even ate a pizza, so I'm full of energy!
No way!
There's a suspicious couple in weird costumes lurking out there.
They were asking about you.
If something happens to you,
it's my responsibility.
So, please, stay in the house all day.
B-But...
I wonder who that "suspicious
couple in weird costumes" are?
Who else but us?!
What should I do?
There's nothing else left but to call Ooshige-san and tell her I can't go.
One of those stones must be the Saint's Stone !
Shinigami Expulsion  is written on the back.
Hurry! Hurry!
We don't have much time!
What are you doing, Mitsuki-chan?
Um... n-nothing...
You'll get scolded by madam!
Anyways, the stone yesterday...
You carried a big stone to
the garden yesterday, right?
"Old mansion...."
What's with that stone?
I'd like to drop it into the pond.
Why for?
"Why?" You mean I can't?
Do whatever you want with it,
but don't tell madam!
Don't tell her?
The stone I used for pickles
broke, so I threw it out.
Huh? That stone was for pickles?
I see...
I got a new stone yesterday.
I see.
Huh? A new stone?
Shinigami
Expulsion
I've found it!
Shinigami
Expulsion
One, two... there!
(Note: This is a parody of Matsuo Basho's best-known haiku: "Old pond - the sound of a frog jumping into the water")
"Old pond - the sound of a stone
falling into the water."
Shinigami
Expulsion
The barrier's gone!
We don't have much time! Let's hurry!
Takuto! Meroko!
Hurry! Let's go!
Okay.
Good luck!
We did it.
I'm sorry for doubting you.
Huh? What do you mean?
Even though you were so nice to model for me.
My pleasure!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Why does it always have to be me..?
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
This mini-concert is a great idea, but why in the mountains..?
Hiiragi
Preschool
It was her only wish to give a concert at the Hiiragi Preschool.
Now I see!
She even said that the girl over there looks just like she did when she was little.
Yeah... I hope everything goes well.
Wait, Takuto!
That boy Taiki is trying to run off with Mitsuki's costume!
What's going on?
Weren't all the children looking forward to this concert?
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
A Tiny Concert
Look forward to it!