The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
My motorcycle engine roars as if it's singing a song.
Blow up louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Blow up louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
I'm going to rely on numbers!
Here it is!
So this is the Dollars?!
What's this?
Don't tell me, these people are all...!
For example,
I don't want to admit that what I've been doing
for these past twenty years was for nothing.
you should marry me.
You've kept your secret about 'that thing' as well.
What's your name?
Selty.
This is more than I expected.
The people who aren't looking at the text on
their phones right now are our enemies.
Don't attack them;
simply stare at them.
This is fun.
I'm screaming!
I was born right here and now!
Give back Selty!
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Being and Non-Being Mutually Exist
I should thank you.
If it weren't for you, my sister probably would have locked her up in a cramped research lab again.
Yagiri-kun...
Are you all right?!
Anyway, give Selty back.
I have to escape with her before the cops arrive.
You'd do something like this just for that...?!
You don't understand anything.
I've been watching her ever since I was a little kid.
I wanted to release her.
I wanted to free her into this vast world,
and I hoped to live alongside her.
Those were my thoughts...
that haunted my mind every single day.
Geez... no one can stop the power of love, didn't you know?
And on the other hand, what's up with you?
Now, and even back then, you continue to rely on numbers.
My love won't shatter with something like this...!
It won't work!
I feel pain, but I'll forget about it eventually!
Pain is unnecessary in the life I'll live with Selty!
That's why this pain I'm feeling right now doesn't bother me at all!
You're not making any sense!
Stop!!
Please, that's enough!
Seiji-san can be harsh, violent and different from others...!
But he's not a bad person by any means!
But he already has someone he loves...
No...
Don't tell me...
That's why...
No way, no way, no way..!
You can't kill him...!
No... This girl is...!
That's not my head.
This girl... Her name is...
Harima Mika-san?
Am I right?
You're Harima Mika-san, the one who was killed by Yagiri-kun, right?
No way.
Hey...
That can't be true, right?
I'm sorry!
Hey, hey! I know you're in there, Seiji-san!
I'm here again today!
Uh-oh! You forgot to leave the door open!
I can't come in like this!
Don't tell me you're asleep?
Do you remember?
I sat next to you during the entrance exam.
Ryugamine Mikado
The person who sat to the right of me had this cool last name of 'Ryugamine,'
so I was wondering what name the person sitting to the left of me had.
I glanced over for a second, and instantly fell in love.
When our eyes met, you smiled.
So please, show your face to me!
I'm begging you, please!
Could it be that you're not feeling well?
Is that why you can't come to open the door?
Then I'll open the door for you!
Just wait!
One second!
Hey... I've done a lot of research since the day of the entrance exam.
Your birthday, family...
S-Seiji...san.
You saw it, didn't you.
Well... umm....
I...
Look... I swear I won't tell anyone.
Umm... umm...
Don't worry!
No matter what kind of hobbies you have, I'll try to find some common ground!
Umm, so...!
It's fine.
Seiji-san...
Seiji...san?
It's fine.
I'm sorry!
I hadn't died yet!
And then your sister...
Do you want Seiji to love you?
What a good girl.
And then...
And then a doctor came and said...
"If you undergo some cosmetic surgery and get some makeup, I can make you look just like that head."
The head you're in love with.
"Your name is Selty."
"Because that's the name of the head."
That's why I tried to become Selty for you!
But then, Namie-san told me that it wouldn't be enough.
She said that the truth would be discovered soon,
so they were going to erase my memories and emotions with medicine or 	surgery.
But I...
The one who knows my real name...
A doctor who knows that I'm a dullahan...
That can only be one person in this city!
I wanted to be with you!
That's why I tried my best!
That... can't be true...
Then I...
Well, to put it bluntly, you couldn't even tell the difference between the real one and a fake.
I guess that just goes to show how 'passionate' your love is.
Sucks to be you.
Seiji-san!
Umm...
I think it's admirable that you tried to get her back even while risking your life.
I had the wrong idea about Harima-san.
She's definitely got some issues personality-wise,
but I can say for certain that she's not a stalker.
Because, look, you risked your life for Yagiri-kun's sake.
I don't think that's something that can be done by someone who only looks out for their own selfish greed.
Still being in love with someone who almost killed you is pretty amazing, I think.
In many ways.
I think you two are really alike.
Welcome home.
You're wanting to ask, "What's this all about?" Right?
And this is what you want to say next.
"So you knew that my head was at that research lab."
"Both you and your father must have been
helping out Yagiri Pharmacy from the start."
"Could it be that your father was the one who stole my head in the first place?"
"And though you knew that, you hid it from me and performed surgery on a girl who almost died."
"I'm also a monster, but you're the true monster who really devours others!"
How close was I?
Oh, I'll tell you beforehand to avoid any misunderstandings.
I don't know whether my father was the one who stole your head, and I'm not interested in finding out.
And I performed cosmetic surgery because she wished for it.
The people at Yagiri may have led her to the decision,
but that's none of my concern.
Now you're thinking, "Can you read my mind?"
Yup, I can.
I've been in love with you for 20 years.
It's not a difficult task.
Why are you acting like this all of a sudden?
If you knew, why didn't you tell me where my head was until now?!
Because I love you.
That's the reason why I didn't tell you.
If you had gotten your head back, you would have surely left to go somewhere else.
I won't be able to endure that.
Don't expect me to say something like, "I'll give you up if it's for your own happiness."
This is a battle with our love at stake.
I'll never let you go.
And to ensure you stay by my side, I'm willing to make use of the love and death of others, and even myself.
And this may sound like a contradiction, but I'll also make use of your feelings.
Even if I get my head back, I won't leave your side-
Even if that's how you happen to feel,
there's no guarantee that your head will feel the same.
That's why I gave it some thought...
Why is a faerie revealing herself to humans in this ordinary world?
Could it be that you were able to
materialize because you lost your head?
If that happens to be true, then after you get your head and memories back...
you may disappear like smoke as if all this were nothing but a dream.
And that is my greatest fear.
Will you believe what I'm about to say?
I will.
Actually, you're the only person I believe.
I'm afraid as well.
I'm afraid of death.
I understand that in my current state, no one can kill me.
Not trying to be conceited or anything.
I'm accepting it as a simple fact.
It doesn't make me happy, nor am I moved.
But...
No.
That's the reason why I'm afraid.
There's no core inside me that presides over death.
That core is my head.
If someone were to destroy my head,
then my current self, with complete
disregard for my feelings or the situation...
Do you believe me?
Someone like me who has no eyes or brain has nightmares.
Do you believe a woman who has seen those nightmares and is now cowering in fear?
I've been seeking my head because I'm afraid.
I want to govern over my death and not have it in the hands of anyone else.
If I were to tell you this, would you believe me?
Didn't you hear what I just said?
You're the only one I believe.
I'm completely perplexed.
So we were being stubborn with ideas that were nothing but conjectures.
That's so dumb.
Yup.
Hey, Shinra.
Yeah?
I owe you a punch.
Fine.
Okay... then let me hit you once too.
See, Selty?
You look cutest without that helmet on.
That punch was a substitute for our marriage kiss.
Okay?
Are you crying?
You're such an idiot.
But geez, that was amazing...
Yo, Izaya.
Oh hey, Dotachin. Been a while.
Stop calling me that.
By the way, do you know where the name 'Dollars' came from?
It's not something like "hand over your money," is it?
You'd think so, but it isn't.
This organization doesn't actually do anything.
Because they laze around, they're the 'Dollars'.
TL Note: One of the ways to say "lazy around" in Japanese is "daladala."
That's where it's from.
Dotachin, did you see that thing?!
The black motorcycle!
Jesus Christ, was that thing for real?!
So I was just seeing things, was I!
Then could it be CG? Yeah right!
That CG you're talking about is also in the Dollars.
Amazing!
Is that true?
To be honest, I'm quite surprised.
I knew that a lot of people were claiming they were a part of the Dollars online.
But I didn't expect that many people to make an effort
...to gather here after suddenly telling them that there will be a 		meeting today.
Humans always exceed my expectations.
You seem to dream about escaping your ordinary life,
but life in Tokyo becomes ordinary after half a year or so.
If you want to experience something more exotic, you could go to a different country,
or perhaps you could get involved with something underground.
But even that will probably become
'ordinary' to you after about three days.
If you really want to escape it, you just have to keep evolving.
Whether what you're aiming for is above or below you.
Just enjoy what your daily life is now.
But,
to pay my respects to you, I won't charge you for Yagiri Namie's phone number.
I also won't sell this valuable information here that you're the founder of the Dollars.
It's your own organization.
You should use it whenever you want to.
I-za-ya!
Looks like it's about time for me to go.
Well then, good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
You punk! Get back here!
I-ZA-YA!
Huh?
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black motorcycle today!
Oh, good evening, Setton-san.
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black motorcycle today!
Wow, you witnessed the black motorcycle, Tanaka Tarou-san?
Dollars?
Have you ever heard of the Dollars?
Why, of course!
What do you mean by that?
Well, to be blunt...
It's sort of like a monster.
What do you mean, a 'monster'?
Well, to be blunt...
It's sort of like a monster.
What do you mean, a 'monster'?
Dotachin says it's a grim reaper.
What?
It can't be...
No way!
The next day was just like any other day; it was almost too soon for the turnaround.
For him...
Also, for him...
And of course, for that boy as well.
Listen, Mikado.
I saw this online.
Apparently, there was a Dollars meeting last night!
And I heard that both Simon and Shizuo are members!
Also something about that woman on the black motor-
cycle not having a head and riding down a building.
She took out a large scythe, and, man, apparently there was some black fog!
I heard it was extraordinary!
You're not making any sense, dude.
And even those two...
I don't love you.
But as long as I'm looking at you, I won't forget my love for her.
That's the reason why I'm willing to accept your love.
Until I get her back someday, that is.
Tanaka Tarou-san has entered the chat.
Good evening!
Evening. I've been waiting here.
Thanks.
I'm a bit tired tonight, so I'll probably be leaving early.
Didn't get enough sleep last night, eh? Did you pull an all-nighter?
Yeah, something like that.
Looks like Kanra-san still isn't here.
I wonder if he'll show up...
Oh, looks like something urgent came up for me.
Oh, I see.
Sorry, I need to go.
See you later.
Setton-san has left the chat.
Sorry to ruin your fun.
It's pretty urgent.
Setton-san has left the chat.
See you later.
Sorry, I need to go.
Setton-san has left the chat.
See you later.
Sorry, I need to go.
Setton-san has left the chat.
No problem.
And my life is back to normal as well.
And just like always, I happen to run into people I don't want to see.
Looks like you've freed yourself of your worries.
You know, people are afraid of ghosts because they sneak around and appear out of nowhere.
But you appeared so flamboyantly.
No one's going to be afraid of you anymore.
Oh yeah, you didn't end up killing anyone.
Can you not cut with that scythe or something?
Could it be that you're looking for that woman?
If you ever need me, just give me a call. I'll be happy to help.
Later.
I don't know where Yagiri Namie went.
But I don't care.
I'm me.
I don't feel lacking in any way.
The ordinary days...
A generic day without any significant hope or despair.
Nothing has changed.
And yet, I feel so fulfilled.
I'm right here.
And you're right there.
If I'm your source of solace, then you're mine, too.
And so the boy thinks deeply about what Orihara Izaya said to him.
Can someone who wishes for an impossible reality desire that new reality to last for all eternity?
And will that 'eternity' turn around to
become part of an everyday life as well?
Sorry about everything.
Thanks.
H-Hey, that's my seat.
Oh, there's an empty seat behind the class rep.
What?
What's the deal, geez?
You show up for the first time, and this is what you do?
She'll probably stop hanging around with Harima Mika like she did back then.
Only she can determine whether that's a good thing or a bad thing.
But is that really true?
In the end, is a person really unable to understand someone else's emotions?
"You have to keep evolving."
Izaya's words continue to echo in his mind.
The boy thought he was capable of doing anything after pulling off such a bold act.
But little did he know...
how much courage it took to invite a girl in his class to hang out.
30 seconds until boy meets girl.
35 seconds until the boy finds his best friend hitting on the girl.
45 seconds until the boy kicks away said best friend.
74 seconds until the girl rejects the boy's offer to go out for tea.
78 seconds until the girl invites the boy to eat lunch with her on the roof.
How many seconds until the boy falls in love with the girl...?
How many seconds until the boy confesses his love to the girl...?
But man, you sure did something stupid.
You blew everything for your
brother's distorted feelings of love?
Are you okay?
As long as they have a means to contact him,
you two will never be able to be alone
with each other.
Message
Watch out. You're still being pursued.
Where are you now?
Let me take that back. Perhaps it was your distorted feelings of love for your brother?
So, aren't you in a tough spot?
Isn't Nebula going to merge with you?
And on top of all that, if you run away with something like this,
a mafia member or perhaps some skilled
sniper will shoot you right in the forehead.
Check.
A garbage truck?
Yes, the usual collection squad.
Got it.
Hello?
Things are getting a bit intricate over here.
Could you leave that room right away?
Can't they make a rule where the kings fight one-on-one?
I think your uncle was just like me.
Doubting the afterlife more than anybody, fearing death more than anybody,
and longing for heaven more than anybody.
But...
I'm sure of it now.
The afterlife exists.
Let's just keep it at that.
It is said that there are usually only female dullahans.
Any idea why?
No.
Some of my men were looking into mythology,
but I personally thought it would be a waste of time.
You must be a rationalist.
Well, leaving that aside for now...
There's a heaven by the name of Valhalla...
Well, not exactly.
In Norse mythology, there's a saying that valkyries, armored female angels,
guide the souls of brave warriors to Valhalla.
A woman comes to greet the dead...
Haven't you heard this somewhere before?
There's also a saying that those valkyries who roam the land are the dullahans.
If that's true, then this head is probably waiting...
for its awakening, and for war.
In order to look for the holy warrior she shall invite to Valhalla.
The reason why it's not opening its eyes despite it being alive is because we're not on a battlefield.
If it were possible, I'd like to be chosen as that warrior.
If a place called Valhalla truly exists beyond death,
what should I do?
I can't imagine myself doing well in strife.
In that case, I'll just have to start a war that only I can fight in.
Ain't that right?
I'm so lucky.
I've been living a life so far from the standards of Heaven, not even believe in it...
And despite all that, I was able to meet an Angel of Death who had fallen.
Those are nothing but your conjectures.
Those who believe shall be saved.
And besides, like I said, this is just insurance.
Even if I happen to end up in Hell, or some place where only pain awaits...
As long as I exist there, I wouldn't mind.
But, well,
if it were possible, I'd like for it to be Heaven.
Hey, Namie-san,
let's all go to Heaven together.
I'll be holding on to this as a member of the Dollars.
It's often difficult to see what's right in front of you.
Selty certainly won't think that her head is with the group she belongs with.
Oh yeah, you should join the Dollars too.
Our boss has the policy of, "Drag them in if they come near."
Well, I'm actually the person who began to gather members midway through.
What do you say we work to give the fallen angel a pair of wings again?
Yeah?
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My dear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Suddenly and Precipitately
Nothing happens in her daily life.
Nothing changes.
Even though something is born in the city every day,
and at the same time, something also disappears.
Next time: Suddenly and Precipitately.