All right.
It's autumn already.
So, your dad was a tank driver?
That's right.
He led the escape of over a thousand citizens and soldiers
out of the beseiged city of Wardenburg with just six Type-2 Millipads.
He's a legendary strategic evacuation hero!
Amazing.
Isn't it?
And my father, who was wounded in battle,
met my mother who was a medic when he was hospitalized.
And the child they had together was...
Kureha-chan.
Yeah!
Hey, I'm not a potato!
My! What a wonderful potato...
It's because you cultivated them so well, Kana-chan.
With these, we'll be able to share some with the townspeople, too.
And, Klaus-san is coming, too.
Maybe we'll give him some as souvenirs.
Is he coming?
You really like Klaus-san, don't you, Kureha-chan?
I-It's not that I adore him...
I respect him.
Poke.
Rio-senpai...
Wow, she can even do something like that.
How amazing of Rio-senpai.
The wind has started to blow.
The weather seems to be getting bad, too.
Shall we go inside?
Yes!
Yeah!
You too, Noel-chan.
Okay.
That's why...
Don't you think Rio-senpai is acting strange?
In what way?
The way she was playing the trumpet?
Wasn't that wonderful?
She's so cool.
She seems to be depressed.
It's normal for Rio-senpai to keep to herself.
But... Oh yeah, dinner!
That tempura was yummy, wasn't it?
Yup! The potatoes were so crispy...
That's not it!
Here you go, Rio. Eat up while it's hot.
Thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
I see. I'm glad.
She munched down the green peppers!
Rio-senpai did?!
Yes!
No matter how finely chopped they are, Rio-senpai would definitely find them and remove them!
Well, that's...
...pretty serious, I guess.
Poke.
Is this Klaus-san?
Yes! That's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Klaus!
On his left breast, symbolizing the unity and glory of the 481st platoon,
is a tattoo of a wolf head.
Isn't it cool?
I'm not giving it to you though.
You don't have to worry that much, do you?
We were overly anxious about the captain the other time too.
Well, it is Rio-senpai!
She's cool, attractive and pretty.
Yeah!
Even with the peppers, I'm sure she must have overcome eating them.
Kureha-chan, you really like Rio-senpai, don't you?
She's the person I admire!
I feel the same too, but...
What do you think, Noel-chan?
Poke...
Careful!
Noel-chan's asleep.
Oh, well. I'll let her have half my bed, then.
Kanata, you grab that end.
Yeah!
You forgot to put out the light in the bathroom.
Sorry. That was careless of me.
It's part of your charm to be decisive and know where to head, but...
But lately, there seems to be a shortage of that.
I'm sorry.
Do you regret hanging up on your father's call?
It can't be helped, I guess.
I'll cover for your errors at work.
At least be a cool senpai in front of the kids.
Is that the wind?
No.
Sorry about the late hour.
It's a Class-1 Priority.
Who's it for?
Master Sergeant Kazumiya Rio of the 1121 Platoon.
Please accept it.
Major, please come in anyway.
You can't get anywhere in this weather...
...not even the Desert Wolf.
I told you not to call me that.
I'm sorry.
As an apology, how about some hot tea and a bath?
Thank you for completing your mission in this typhoon!
I apologize for serving you leftovers from last night's dinner.
Please help yourself.
You should have woken me up when Klaus-san got here.
It's well made.
It's delicious even when cold.
The green peppers are well cultivated, too.
Is that true?
I was the one who picked and fried them!
Kureha will make a great wife someday.
Is that a newspaper?
Yes, the Major brought it along with him.
How are the peace talks?
The conference doesn't look like it's going to be resolved.
There doesn't seem to be any agreement on the conditions...
If Princess Iliya were still alive, things might have been different.
Princess... Iliya...
You don't know her? She was the hero of Vingt!
The first daughter of Archduke Arcadia!
She's the Helvetian Army's goddess of victory!
She's a tank goddess, equal to that of the Desert Wolf Major Klaus!
Kureha, that's actually-
Is everyone here?
There's an emergency!
Rio!
What's going on?
One of the kids at Yumina's place has been missing all day.
Please lend us a hand!
What?
Yumina-san, who's missing?
It's Seiya-san.
The river's risen quite high.
The fields downstream haven't been harvested yet.
If the dam breaks, they'll be destroyed.
I'm not familiar with the city.
I'm depending on you, Kureha.
Yes sir!
I'm really sorry.
As soon as I took my eyes off him...
Search and rescue is an army's job.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
Okay!
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
It's dreadful. There's so much water...
If he falls in...
Seiya!
Seiya-san!
What is it?
You!
You know something, don't you?
You came out here because you know something, right?
Tell me!
Where is Seiya?
The fields...
The fields?
Eggplants... are Yumina-oneechan's favorite.
So, we bought some seedlings with everyone's allowance...
Seiya must have...
Where are they?
What's the matter with you?
Why are you here during a typhoon?
I must protect the eggplants!
What are you talking about?
You idiot!
We're risking our lives for you!
You came on your own accord, right?
I never said I needed help!
What did you say?!
Behave yourself already!
Listen up...
Kids without parents have to be stronger than other kids.
If you cause any trouble, people wil brush it off as if they had expected it.
And not only towards you guys...
But Yumina, your oneechan, too.
Kureha...
Okay...
I'm an orphan, too. So I know.
Now, let's get back.
But...
Are you still gonna complain?
Well, just hold it.
Things that you work hard at nurturing,
are as precious as your own life.
These are big enough to be eaten.
So, they'll be really delicious when pickled.
Thanks, Mister
Major...
Seiya-kun has started to climb up.
Major, please go on ahead!
N-No... You go first.
Leave the rear to me.
Yes sir!
The two of them are safe.
But...
Now, their way back up is cut off.
The situation is... disastrous.
Thank you very much.
The situation has become bad.
But, you're with me!
I believe we'll manage, somehow.
You're wrong...
Huh? Did you say something?
No...
Listen, don't be afraid.
You're now with Miracle Klaus!
I won't!
The ground isn't gonna hold any longer!
Water erosion...
Damn! This is why I hate kids!
Kids who don't listen should just be bound and locked up!
Rio!
What good will come of upsetting them?
Those kids are always watching you.
I'm sorry... That was too harsh.
B-But I'm sure it'll work out somehow.
Klaus-san is said to bring miracles.
That's not true.
He's not the Desert Wolf or Miracle Klaus.
He just happens to have the same name and similar appearance, that's all.
When they first met, Kureha just assumed and got excited...
Klaus is a poor talker, right?
He just went along with it until he could find the chance to tell her...
No way...
Anyway, we need to think of a way to save the both of them,
the courier soldier with only long service,
and the enthusiastic but inexperienced one.
Give them a rope?
There's no foothold above them.
And it's too far to send it from here.
A way to send them a rope...
Exists!
The first time I met you, Klaus-san,
I thought my father would have been like you if he were still alive.
I speak to others like I knew my dad really well,
but it's all gathered from what I've heard from others.
I don't actually know much.
He died when I was very little.
Kureha...
Pay attention to the upper left?
Pull! Pull! Pull!
The Takemikazuchi!
Stop!
Noel-chan, how is it?
Linear Anchoring Coil online.
Targeting system partial trajectory from B7 to F5.
Commencing alignment.
It'll make it.
Prepare to fire the wire anchor!
Kanata, do it!
Right!
It's coming!
I'll protect you, in your late father's place!
Yes... Major...
Ready!
Fire!
Come here!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Retract the anchor!
Hurry!
Hey, Kureha...
We're somehow safe now, so I'll tell you...
I-
I knew it...
You are the person I admire!
Blue skies after a typhoon, huh?
So, you wound up pretending the whole time.
Honestly, I'm surprised.
I didn't think you could go that far.
When I saw the faith in her eyes,
I got more afraid of shattering her dreams than of dying.
That was why I was able to something crazy like that.
In the end, I guess I'm a coward.
That's not true!
You're wonderful, Klaus-san!
isten up, missy.
The illusions you make up,
and what you can feel from the actual person, mostly differ.
Eyes filled with admiration are usually clouded.
Someday, when you're looked at in that way, you'll understand the pain.
Won't you at least stay until Kureha-chan wakes up?
Can you tell her for me...
...that this is the most honorable wound I've ever received!
Next time:
Setting off - Time of First Snow.