"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Okay, everyone to your seats!
Happy New Year.
Well, last year just flew by, so
I'm giving you my best regards.
Though, of course,
for some of you, my regards only
go for about three more months.
I wonder who I'm talking about.
Ma'am! You're not talking about me, are you?
"Delicious Day"
I can trust you, right?
They say "a New Year's feeling,"
but it's true that there
is a strange atmosphere.
And when school starts,
the atmosphere changes
drastically, much to my dismay.
It's true that there's a strange power
working over the New Year's holiday.
Even though I was so busy helping
out at the beginning of the year...
I gained weight!
Oh, it's the magic of New Year's.
Since it's cold, it's harder
for the fat to burn.
I moved quite a bit too.
I was really busy with shrine maiden
stuff for the first days of the year.
But you ate to make up for it.
Shrine maiden New Year's food,
shrine maiden rice cake soup,
shrine maiden snacks, snacks, snacks, snacks,
shrine maiden snacks...
Something along those lines.
But, speaking of enjoying
the New Year's holiday...
You see pictures of hanetsuki,
the 100 poem card game,
and flying kites a lot.
But I've never seen people
really playing those games.
Well, they say that it's dangerous nowadays
because of the power lines
and all the traffic.
I spent my time watching
TV and reading books,
after the busy first three
days of the year were over.
Um, I played them.
I enjoyed playing hanetsuki,
the 100 poem card game,
and "Fortune's Smile."
That's not how I imagined you.
It's true that we have a
very westernized house,
but our country house is
strictly traditional Japanese.
I went to the first shrine visit in a kimono,
and I played together with all of my cousins.
"Even when the gods Held sway in the..."
She's far more Japanese than me!
More traditional than we are! Or,
what kind of "Fortune's Smile" face?
The 100 poems in the card game
are all waka poems, right?
Yes, it's a game that the
players pick up the cards with
the second half of the poem after
the first half is read out loud.
I'm amazed you can do such a thing.
No, I'm still nowhere close to good...
Those who are really good move quite
briskly, with a nice slap on the card.
No, it's more like...
It's like I'm studying archaic Japanese,
and I don't like it because it doesn't
feel like I'm playing a game.
Those that find intelligent games troublesome
are the ones that are ruining Japan's future.
I mean, while we're at it,
why can't we have card battles
with the 100 poem cards?
You know, that monk... Semimaru, wasn't it?
Semimaru's shiny-bright attack!
Versus Komachi Ono-no's lovely attack!
That sounds fun.
Going that way again?
But if you played games that move
your body a bit like this one,
maybe you'd lose at least a little weight?
Shut up!
It's because of the rice cakes...
Rice cakes are high in calories.
Even a piece the size of a matchbox
has basically the same amount of
energy as a small bowl of rice.
Which means, Kagami was eating
giant bowls of rice each time!
Wait, didn't you guys eat rice cakes as well?
We don't have a mom at home,
so I don't remember eating much
stuff like rice cake soup.
Or rather, I don't eat many
rice cakes to begin with.
Wow, what a waste!
Rice cake soup, red bean
soup, soy flour mochi...
There are all sorts of ways
to eat delicious rice cakes.
Oh, at this rate, you're going
to screw up again next year
with the rice cakes, aren't you, Kagamin?
What does your family eat instead
of rice cakes, Izumi-san?
Like, pizza and pasta?
Our family's year always
begins with fresh pasta!
Every year, at the end of the year,
Dad washes the pasta machine.
Did you know? If you don't use
that thing for a while, it rusts.
And if you use it without washing it,
it's like, the pasta turns all black.
And so we clean it up,
and make fresh pasta and
bake handmade pizza dough.
That sounds authentic.
Well, I'm sure that in your house, Kagami,
the pizza is delivered and
the pasta is the dried stuff.
Or rather, we don't eat pizza
or pasta for New Year's...
You're kidding!
It doesn't go well with
traditional New Year's dishes.
It does too! It's perfect with roast chicken.
That's a New Year's food?
It's a New Year's food.
It's a westernized version
of New Year's food.
Is that how it is?
What did you guys eat during
New Year's, Miyuki-san?
Me?
Miyuki-san, you have the image
of a very westernized rich girl,
so I bet you don't have rice
cakes and New Year's food.
So do you eat full-course French
cuisine on New Year's Day?
That's not really true.
I ate traditional New Year's food,
and I couldn't bite through the rice cake,
so I did one of those "stretching
out without end" things.
What's with this walking moe factor?!
Rice cake, stretching without end...
But the New Year's vacation
goes by in a rush.
That's true. Winter vacation
ends really quickly.
It counts as a long break, but
you do the big house cleaning,
write New Year's cards, do some homework...
In the end, there isn't much time to rest.
Wait a second! I didn't get
a New Year's card from you,
and you copied my homework yesterday!
Uguu...
By the way, Kona-chan, did you
have your first dream of the year?
Oh... that thing that's said
to give you good fortune
if you happen to see one?
Right, right.
Normally, they say one is Fuji, two is hawk,
three is eggplant, right?
I hear that it continues further.
Four is fan, five is tobacco,
six is a lutist monk.
I see, so there's up to sixth place...
But, you know...
Those things don't normally
show up in your dreams.
What kind of dreams? What's a lutist monk?
I guess.
Hey, do you have to see all of them at once?
If you saw all of them, that
would be tremendously lucky,
but I believe any one of them would suffice.
I thought that you needed to see
two hawks or three eggplants in your dream!
Or rather, to be blunt,
I don't remember most of the
dreams I see in the first place.
People that really think about that
stuff seriously enjoy New Year's.
That's true.
My first dream of the year was about
my shoes being missing when
I opened my school shoebox.
Since I couldn't do anything about it,
I tried to head home with
someone else's shoes,
but the size wasn't right...
That was my dream.
I looked it up in the "Dictionary
of Fortune-telling with Dreams,"
and it said that it meant that
I was seeking social skills,
but to gain such skills, it will
still take quite a long time.
Apparently, shoes in dreams
mean social status.
Cheesecake?
Miyuki-san... You're quite the ambitious one.
I kinda get it, but I kinda don't.
I heard a bunch of people got worked
up at their coming-of-age ceremony,
and went up to the stage,
or caused other problems.
Don't they feel any responsibility, now
that they're part of the face of Japan?
I wonder why we have to go all
the way out to the ceremony site?
Yeah, really.
The coming-of-age ceremony is such
a pain. I mean, I don't want to go.
This girl's on her way to becoming
a good-for-nothing adult...
Kagami, what are you guys gonna
wear to the coming-of-age ceremony?
I'd think since it's a rare occasion,
I would wear a long-sleeved kimono...
Since you asked, how about you?
Well, I'm sure Dad will recommend
me wearing a long-sleeved kimono.
Yeah, if it's him...
Yoo-hoo!
But...
When you wear a long-sleeved kimono,
it's more of a seven-five-three
festival than coming of age.
Happy New Year! Best regards for this year!
Oh, Sis, Happy New Year.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Well, my husband was home,
and New Year's is busy.
That, and my younger sister caught a fever.
Oh... That's right, she's very frail.
I wasn't trying to weasel my way out
of giving you New Year's allowance!
Don't get me wrong on that, okay?!
How the truth comes out,
and I didn't even ask...
I guess that's what makes her a cop.
There was a tournament for
the 100 poem card game,
and it had a great turnout.
Come to think of it...
When you were a child, Sis,
what did you do for play on New Year's Day?
When I was a child?
Let's see... I did all sorts
of stuff... well... um...
Dot... dot... dot... dot...
I'm sorry, I forgot. Clean memory wipe.
Sis really just lives every
day in her own groove.
I don't think I've gotten one
decent conversation out of her.
I blasted all the memories behind me!
Lucky Star!
Lately, Tsukasa's been cooped
up in the kotatsu all the time.
'Cause it's cold.
Oh, I know, I know! Kotatsu
are wonderful things.
When you have a kotatsu, even
going to the bathroom is tough.
Right, right.
But you shouldn't say stuff
like that so loudly...
But there is a killer line in our house
that can move people who
are cooped up in a kotatsu.
Really? How does it go?
Konata, if you're planting
yourself in the kotatsu too much,
I'll put the kotatsu away!
So he's fine without a kotatsu?
He likes it as much as anyone.
I think it's just as a lesson to be learned.
I mean, sometimes both of us fall
asleep while sitting in a kotatsu.
Oh, I can understand.
But they say that you'll catch
a cold sleeping in a kotatsu.
Right, right. So when I notice it,
I try to make sure to turn it off.
You know, kotatsu carry heaven
and hell together in one.
It's like that when you
first turn it on as well,
but turned-off kotatsu seem
even colder than necessary.
I definitely know how that is!
Isn't it tough to get out
of the bed in the morning?
Yeah. When you say that,
the time between the changing room
and the bathtub is really cold too.
But you think twice about
running around stark naked.
Because it's slippery.
That, and don't you hate it
when you want to go to the
bathroom late at night?
Yeah, there's that too!
Hey, guys, we need to get off the bus.
The trip from the bus to
the classroom is also hell.
Yeah.
It's almost Valentine's Day.
The air around us gets all
colorful this time of the year.
Each and every year,
the hidden anxiety that
shows itself every so often
in everyone acting normally
really tickles me.
I think it would be really
wonderful if you ask someone out
or get asked out, and your feelings
for each other go through
on days that everyone finds
special, like this one.
Tsukasa, you're such a romantic girl...
Not that I'm going to go calling
it a candy-company conspiracy.
Well, if you say that it's special
for me as well, it might be.
Every year, the leftover
chocolates get really cheap.
The make-your-own chocolate
kits are worth aiming for.
Whereas you don't have any dreams at all.
They say that you can't buy love!
But in a way,
Valentine's Day chocolates are
a show of love with money.
For someone who's only had
romances within games,
that's a pretty harsh thing to say.
Well, in games, getting your
impression points up first
is more important than the actual day.
For me, there's not much difference
even if it's Valentine's Day.
The boys have too many dreams.
Nobody was able to trigger
the Kagami flag, huh?
And what about you? You have something?
Hey, I'm really popular!
Yeah, yeah, that's in your game, right?
Sometimes I seriously
worry about your future,
with all your talk of flags and
impression points and stuff.
Really, what's with only
talking about in-game events?
I hate it when people talk about their
biased opinion when they don't know.
Oh, then it's different?
Lately, the in-game time for
it has been really short,
so you completely miss
Valentine's Day when playing.
So what?
But this year, I have plans
to give chocolate to someone.
Seriously?!
Yeah. To someone playing
the same online game as me.
To one of your gaming buddies?
Yeah.
Don't tell me, in person?!
No, it's not like we're physically
going to see each other or anything.
Huh?
I'm going to give chocolate to
someone as a character in-game.
I mean, there's another
human playing it, after all.
Can you really say that it's a real person?
In the end, it's just a character in a game.
How dare you talk about my bride that way?!
Huh? Bride?
Yeah. We're married in-game,
and I play a male character.
Wait a minute. A guy giving
chocolate to a girl?
Or rather, isn't that like a girl
giving one to a girl, right?
If the other end is a girl.
Don't worry. My partner
is a guy in real life.
Huh?!
Well, for these things, so long as the
ones doing it are having fun, it's okay!
That's right!
I want to go overseas.
That's straight out of the blue.
Well, Miyuki-san said yesterday...
It's only in Japan that women give
chocolates to men on February 14th.
In Western countries, people
give candies and cards
to friends and loved ones,
regardless of gender.
I see!
That's what she said,
so even a girl like me would get
lots of sweets and stuff, right?
The simplicity of your mind aside,
you really have confidence,
in all sorts of ways.
That was based on the premise
that you're popular.
It's okay, it's okay!
In foreign countries, smaller girls are--
Okay, stop right there! Dangerous
comments are forbidden!
You're awesome!
Happy Valentine's Day!
Kona-chan, this is for you.
Whoa! Amazing wrapping... is a uniform.
It's amazing inside too! Heart-shaped!
"Happy Valentine's to Kona-chan"
I put a little effort into it.
Tsukasa gets pretty elaborate
on things like this.
She made lots and lots of them until morning!
Even though they're all
obligatory chocolates.
Tsukasa, obligatory or not, don't
give these things to any guys.
They'd all get the wrong idea!
What?
Anyway, you can have this.
From Kagami?! For me?! Chocolate?!
Because Tsukasa was making
them, I just made some too.
You don't want it?
"Oh!"
When someone who can do anything
does something they're not good at,
it feels like they put in a tremendous
effort behind the scenes...
That's Kagami moe...
Shut up! Hush, and put it away!
Huh?
Kagami...
Here, I'll give this to you.
I'm telling you, it's
obligatory, okay? Obligatory!
Excuse me for it having
such a distorted shape!
You're such a fool... What's
more important than shape
is the fact that you made it for me, Hiiragi.
Wha--
Idiot, you idiot, it's not like that at all!
Isn't that what's going on?
Nope. Just shut up and put it away.
I've never experienced
something like this before.
The beginning's the most important.
So, did you give chocolates
to anyone, Miyuki-san?
I gave some to my father
and to a male relative.
I gave some to everyone that's
friendly to me every day.
I gave some to you, Tsukasa, and Miyuki.
What, everyone had a very
boring Saint Valentine's...
Wait, I don't want to hear that from
someone living in the game world.
Come to think of it, your cousin
applied to Ryouou, right?
Yeah, she said she got in!
Since her house is a long way from here,
she'll stay at our place starting next month.
She's like a little sister anyway, and
our families were talking about it.
Oh, I see.
But compared to you,
isn't it hard to tell which
of you is the younger sister?
No, I'm telling you, she's like a
little sister, in all sorts of ways.
She's that small?!
But the fact that she got
accepted here smoothly
means that your cousin must be really smart!
Depending on how you take that line,
it sounds a little egotistical.
Don't you go here too?
I'm sure I just barely made it in!
Entrance exams, huh...
We'll be going through
entrance exams next year.
Man, I guess we'll be immersed
in studying all year.
Wow, no way.
Entrance exams... Should I take them?
I haven't thought of my future plans at all.
I think it's better for you to seriously
think about your future, okay?
Well, the words "academic" and "labor"
don't exist in my dictionary.
What kind of future does that
kind of person have in store?
A game creator based on hobbies
and her actual skills?
Well, in actuality, it's a
hobby in some way or another.
Or a manga artist that only
makes money at Comiket?
Megassa, undara, cheese nyoro-n...
Or maybe she'll use her
curiosity as a report writer?
There is only one truth!
Yeah, this has to be it!
How about an author whose popularity
spikes like the tip of a pin?
Well, in this day and age, you
have to go with the light novels!
Since she's good with computers,
maybe a web designer?
I won't compromise on this point!
Or a scriptwriter that uses lots of small
everyday events instead of an actual story?
Or the impossible, moving on to college...
Wait, all of them are the same image!
What is it?
What's up?!
Manager! It's Legendary
Girl A! She's here again!
What?!
We let her slip out of our hands last time...
Manager!
Today will be the day
that we will have the Legendary Girl A
make it all the way to the
goal named the cash register!
Giro.
She seems to be indecisive about something.
Then we should solve her indecision for her!
All right, everyone, raise
your voices! Let's go!
Yes!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah, we say, yeah!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Manager, I'll go check out Legendary
Girl A's purchase target for today.
Good. I'm counting on you.
New comics in stock?
Sir! That would be Sgt. Frog volume 14!
All right! Lift up the
height of the flat stacks
so that they get in Legendary
Girl A's line of sight!
And put up a pop-up banner as well!
Equipment complete!
...sir!
All right! Observe her actions for now.
Furthermore, put all the
hot sellers along the path
that Legendary Girl A will take
from there to the cash register!
Roger!
...sir!
Manager! The purchase target of
Legendary Girl A is not a comic!
What?!
Manager! Her target has shifted to DVDs!
All right! Just to be on the safe
side, shut off all side corridors,
so that Legendary Girl A can head
straight to the new release DVD area!
Roger!
...sir!
Oh, my apologies!
Tama! Tama!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Tama tama tama tama, tamarincho!
Gero gero gero gero, gemarincho!
"DVD New Releases"
All right, all right!
Manager!
Finally, she picked up some merchandise!
Finally, I have become victorious today!
My comrades, let us drink the
sweet wine of victory tonight!
Yes, sir!
It was a feint!
This calls for the last resort!
Now... Bring me that bargain
ultra-rare out-of-print DVD!
Manager, she's heading to the cash register.
Yes... That's it!
This is such an emotional scene!
Right now, the entire United States
within me is cheering and applauding!
All right!
...sir!
That will be 1,785 yen!
Oh, I'm three yen short.
I'm sorry, can you put that back?
We'll be back!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Yes, we're going to cheerfully
bring it to you again.
Times pass by so quickly that Lucky
Channel is already on its 13th episode!
Yes, your navigator is your
well-acquainted Akira Kogami!
And...
Yes! I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
assistant to Akira-sama!
Nice to see all of you!
That's right, times pass quickly
and we're already on episode 13.
We're going to enter the second season!
How to put it, is it like reaching
the halfway station on Mt. Fuji?
Akira-sama?
Huh? Mt. Fuji? You can get to
the halfway station by car.
Oh, yes, that's true, but...
Oh! That's right! I climbed
up Mt. Takao for starters.
Huh? Don't you have something
to notice before all of that?
Oh... you're right...
Well, um, how to say it, your twin
drills are really nice, Akira-sama!
How is it good? In what way?
Oh, it's all wound up like a seashell...
Huh?!
Oh, well... oh!
That's right...
Today we're announcing the results
of the special plan we had,
the Lucky Star action figure project!
We'll have you, Akira-sama, make
the announcement right away!
Yes, the honorable character that will become
an action figure is Miss Konata Izumi...
Oh, Akira-sama, please read it properly!
Congratulations!
I knew this would happen.
What is this? A fixed race?
No, no, no...
So in the end, the radio and this segment
are less important than the
main show or something?
That's not the case at all, okay?
Yes, yes.
See, the producer is telling us so too.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be fooled
as many times as you want.
I'm used to getting betrayed, after all.
Fooled? That's such a
disgraceful way to put it.
Or rather, you haven't had some
sort of blueprint in your head
like you'd get yourself made into an
action figure or anything, right?!
Oh, no, of course not!
Yes, the action figure will
be that of Miss Konata Izumi.
And, as a booby prize, an action
figure of Minoru Shiraishi?!
What is the meaning of this?!
Well...
Oh! It's already time for us to say goodbye.
And so, we ask that you continue
to send us your impressions,
encouragement, and opinions
about the program!
We accept them on our homepage,
among other places!
Right, Akira-sama?
I'm going home.
Wait a minute!
Bye-nee!
Akira-sama, please wait...
Okay, all staff gather around!
Drill...
"Clap clap" "Meaningless handclaps"
♪ Wa-Wa-Wa... ♪
♪ Wa-Wa-Wawawawawawa... ♪
♪ S-S-S-Something forgotten ♪
♪ My, my something I forgot ♪
♪ That day, that time, I left it behind ♪
♪ A fragment of a memory ♪
"Snap"
♪ It's all gone ♪
♪ With that girl ♪
♪ The red setting sun is
somehow really bright ♪
"He's too rowdy."
"Don't make eye contact with him."
♪ Jougashima of love ♪
♪ He's a fool ♪
♪ Laugh at me like that ♪
♪ That's what is fitting for me ♪
♪ But... ♪
♪ Once in a while, embrace me gently ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's up with the
next episode of Sgt. Frog?
No, that's not it!
It should be the next episode
of Lucky Star, right?
Gero gero! I've thought
of something wonderful!
Japanese anime is now a global
motion picture industry.
We can use this to brainwash
the people of Pekopon,
and that will end the conquest
of Pekopon in one sweep.
Sergeant, you're so smart!
How stupid. As a military man,
do it like a military man and
pull it off with military power!
Quiet, you red daruma!
In this era, those that seize
information seize the battle.
You might not understand that with
your old-fashioned head, Giroro.
Damn you, when I let you talk...
And so, the next episode: Under One Roof.
Look forward to it!
Ge-gero!