Please return that!
Cram it!
You think just 'cause you're rich, you get to show off with some 72 color pencil set?
But I...
Stop right there!
You've gotta be pretty low to gang up and bully a single girl!
Mana...
Today's tea is a first flush Darjeeling.
Served with a side of cherry jam to enjoy at your leisure.
Don't mind if I do!
It's delicious!
It has that spring flavor, doesn't it?
This is no time to be drinking tea!
We've gotta find Lance, and fast!
Yeah, we get it.
So, what is it, Alice?
Didn't we have our monthly tea party last week?
You wanted to talk?
I did.
Naturally, I wish to ask...
about the Precure.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
So uh, Precure...
Why do you ask?
Sebastian.
Right away.
Why, hello there.
La—
Lance?!
I Must Refuse!
I Will Not Become A Precure!
Lance, what the heck happened?
Well you see...
Hey, you two are still here?
The teachers already left.
So if you don't clean up in three minutes,
you'll get locked in.
Oh no!
Wait a second!
Sharyl, Raquel,
where are you guys?
Don't leave me all alone, please...
Oh dear!
What shall we do?
Stay strong!
And that's the story!
You don't say...
You can't reveal the Precure's secret!
Don't get mad...
Lance is not the one you should blame.
Sebastian.
Right away.
Precure Love Link!
I...
can explain...
This was taken from one of Clover Tower's security cameras.
I was fortunate enough to delete it when I found it,
but you narrowly avoided making the Precures a household name.
That'd be a huge problem!
Please, Alice!
You've gotta keep this a secret!
Be at ease.
None beside Madam and I know of this incident.
But we cannot lower our guard.
And so, I have a proposal.
A proposal?
Allow me to be your producer.
A third one?
Is that true, Ira?
Yep, they got another one.
She's all blue and floaty.
And glittery, too!
Oh my,
Ira has a crush?
Like heck!
Then what?
You saw a new Precure and ran screaming?
I-I wouldn't be scared... of a hundred of 'em...
But didn't you lose?
Just shaddup!
But really,
how many more Precures will there be?
It's so stressful.
The sooner we destroy them, the better.
Just like we did with Trump Kingdom.
Producer, huh?
What will you do?
Well, I'll...
The dark heartbeat of a Selfish!
Huh? Where?
Oogai City's train station, it seems.
Huh?
You know?
Yes.
The Yotsuba's information networks are nothing to sneeze at.
Sebastian.
Right away.
So, shall we make our leave?
Sound leeakaaaaaaaaaaaage!
Good work, Selfish!
Stop right there!
Br-Brimming with love, Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom, Cure Diamond!
Are you okay?
Carsick...
Selfish!
Max volume!
Do your best out there!
Great, Selfish! Get 'em!
They're fighting hard...
Now, Alice!
Let's transform too!
Would you like more?
Thank you.
What are you doing!
We should fight, too!
There is no need to worry.
Besides...
the battle is already over.
Selfiiiiish!
Selfy?
What's up?
Why're you—
You're outta power?!
Now is your chance!
Heart!
Right!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love looooove!
All video from the station's cameras have been deleted.
All eyewitness accounts on the internet have also been deleted.
Excellent work.
Your butler's amazing!
Oh, I'm nothing of the sort.
Well, that's that.
I plan to produce you by supporting you from the sidelines.
Well, that's a big help...
Alice...
Lance?
Alice, why didn't you fight?
Mana and Rikka were fighting with all they had,
but you were sitting back and drinking tea!
It's not right!
Lance?
You should transform into a Precure and fight with them!
The thought's nice, but...
Alice needs a Cure Lovies, right?
Cure Lovies?
Oh.
This.
Without this, you can't transform.
Sebastian.
Right away.
A Cure Lovies!
How?
A jewelry stall owner in Clover Tower gave it to me.
That must be...
Then it's settled!
Alice, I came to this world to meet you!
Please!
Become a Precure and fight with me!
I apologize.
I...
will not become a Precure.
Alice, you poopyhead!
Lance!
Lance...
Why won't Alice become a Precure?
About that...
I think I have an idea.
Mana!
An idea?
We all went to the same elementary school.
Girls as rich as Alice were pretty rare,
so she was picked on pretty often.
You two should be ashamed!
Though it wouldn't have mattered if it stopped there.
What happened?
Well, you see...
So you the punks that done gave my kid bros trouble?
I'll get a teacher!
Don't worry!
I'm no scaredy-cat, and I don't needs a grown-up to save me!
What'd you say?
Says you!
You're always butting in when nobody asks!
I bet you're just doin' it to show off!
What? Absolutely not!
Y'know everyone says you're annoyin', right?
You're lying!
Nuh-uh, she's an annoyin' showoff!
Buttin' in with her big butt!
No...
I'm not like that!
Not a bit!
Aw, she's cryin'!
Yay!
Take back your words.
Alice?
You say sumthin'?
You will take back your insults to Mana...
right this instant!
Alice got in a fight?
So, what happened?
Well you see,
Alice learned a lot from her grandfather.
Not just piano or calligraphy,
but karate, judo, kendo, aikido...
So then...
U...
Uncle...
Alice?
Alice!
After that, Alice quit all of her martial arts.
When people made fun of her friends,
she lost control of herself.
She probably knows it full well.
So that has to be why she won't become a Precure...
A dark heartbeat!
Huh? Again?
Mana!
Right!
Lance?
I'm...
I'm gonna talk to Alice one more time!
Gotcha.
Let's hurry!
Madam, it seems another Selfish has appeared.
Where are the others?
On the scene.
I see.
Are you certain?
I am only a producer.
I leave the real work in their hands.
Do you not wish to fight by their side?
Huh?
What I've noticed in my long life of service
is that you truly shine brightest when you are with those two.
Perhaps you should be more honest at times.
I cannot.
I am...
scared of it.
I may lose my composure again,
and possibly wound someone deeply.
In my hands, the Precure's power...
is dangerous.
That's not true!
Lance!
The Precure's power is for protecting those you hold dear!
You shouldn't be afraid of it!
Alice.
I heard of what happened.
Grandfather!
Power is not meant for subduing your foes.
Reflect upon this.
For what purpose do you clench your fists?
Power is meant to protect those you love.
So long as you remember this, you shall never be controlled by your power again.
Alice, fear not!
Improve yourself, and open your heart!
Power is...
meant to protect those I hold dear!
Thank you, Lance.
I am no longer afraid!
Hey yo fool, betta listen to mah sound!
I like my sandwiches stackin' by the pound, yeah!
It's a boombox this time?
What're those?
I'm kinda lost here, but let's go!
Sharyl!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Raquel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
There you are.
Oh poor boombox who has forgotten love,
I, Cure Heart—
Hey, let me finish!
Can't stop mah swag!
We'll have to wait for his power to run out!
Right!
Morons!
Take a look at that!
A power cable?!
Hit 'em with full power!
Yeyah!
Catch them!
Catch dat heart!
Get paper!
Round 'n round,
y'all get around!
Get away!
Finish them, Selfish!
Ain't no thang.
Stop, if you'd please.
Any further attacks on my dear friends...
will be punished!
Alice!
Now then, Lance.
May I have your aid?
Of course!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The warmth of the sun?
Another one?!
Only love makes the world go round.
Now, you and I
will nurture that love!
Are you kiddin' me?!
Beat her up, Selfish!
Aww yeah.
Amazing.
This...
is the power to protect those I hold dear.
Rosetta!
Think you can jump in? My volume's bumpin'!
Now eat mah bazooka, all day I'm pumpin'!
Lance!
Rigid Rosetta Wall!
Yo!
It blocked it?
Amazing!
But it's just a defense.
No.
Being defensive is what makes it such a powerful attack!
The sound disappeared!
Why?
I see, that was noise canceling!
Now!
Sharyl!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love looove, yeah!
Curses! I'll remember this!
Huh?
Thanks, Alice!
You're the best partner I could ask for!
Good luck from now on.
Now we've got three Precures!
Four if you count Cure Sword.
Cure Sword?
There's one more Precure out there.
But we don't know if she's on our side.
If that's the case,
I may have a lead.
Really?
The Clover Tower's hidden cameras filmed one more Precure-looking person.
And that person...
Ace Tea
looked like her.
No way...
Makopi?!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
Kenzaki Makoto
What are you shouting over?
D-D-D-Don't freak out,
j-j-j-just listen calmly!
Take your own advice, first!
Mana, would you like some tea?
Tasty!
I mean, this is no time to drink tea!
So, what?
I found out Cure Sword's secret Identity!
Dokidoki Precure:
No Way!
That Girl Is Cure Sword?
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!