There's a lot of Roman troops in no-man's land at Seize's border!?
Aisha!
What's going on now!
We caught the Roman soldier!
Is she dead?
No, she's still breathing.
Well done!
Now, we'll join forces with the first and third divisions, which are deployed at the border!
What are you doing!
Don't move!
If you move, I'll shoot!
Platoon leader!
Colonel.
Tell your people to get out of the fortress.
Music in the Sky
What on earth is going on there?
It's a rebellion.
The girls of the fortress are holding our commander hostage!
What did you say!?
Fortunately, it didn't hit any internal organs.
So...?
I don't think she's in any immediate danger.
Thank you, Yumina-san.
Well done.
She'll become a sacrifice in order to start the war.
If she's dead, she won't be valuable anymore.
What are you talking about!
In the past month, we've had Roman troops moving near the borders of our nation.
I'm afraid it's a show of force in order to put pressure on the peace talks.
They have despised us.
But Taiko, his majesty, is so weak-kneed that he said to do nothing.
So, in order for them to make the first move, we must take a hostage.
For example, having the prisoner cry and shot dead in front of their eyes.
I can't believe you guys are...!
Peace making is just acting!
Rome must be destroyed!
Right, Kannagi Noël?
No. Our friend, the Witch of Helvetia.
Did you ever think that I wouldn't find out?
Stop that!
Noël was only used by you guys!
Noël-san.
So that Invisible God of Death has something to do with this.
The Invisible God of Death!?
You're called the genius that comes out once every one-hundred years at the Academy.
The Invisible God of Death!
The one that restored the biological warfare plant from the past...
Is that girl right there.
I want your talent.
Come back to me.
Kureha-chan.
Put that man in the underground distillery.
Our colleagues are already in position to battle the Roman military.
A small incentive can change the situation.
Will we still retreat from the battlefield?
I thought it was finally over...
We're so unlucky, both of the sides.
I've locked the Colonel up in the distillery.
Thank you very much, Kureha-chan.
If you don't mind, please eat this.
These are some pastries that I got from Treize. They're delicious.
Naomi-san, I didn't know that you were still here!
If it got really bad, I would've left.
Oh, it's really messed up.
The Maidens of Flame would protect the town.
We gotten the town into a war!
About that...
I asked Aisha-san about the tale of the Maidens of Flame when we were hiding.
And, she said that in Roman literature, a totally different story is told.
What is it?
The Maidens of Flame protect the lives.
W-What!?
It's my turn.
OK. I'm still not sure if you can do it well...
The reason is... I'm not sure if you can shoot anyone.
If I can believe it's right, I might be able to do it.
Really?
Because, I'm also a maiden at the fortress.
Like those Maidens of Flame in the past.
What are you talking about? You believe it?
A fairy tale created randomly by the Romans?
Umm.
I feel I can accept it.
The Maidens of Flame protect the lives.
It must be real, I guess.
What's happening?
I can hear it.
Um? What do you hear?
Kanata!
Despite how good your hearing is, it wouldn't spread to a place like that.
A cease-fire signal?
Yes, I heard it.
Really?
I'm definitely sure!
It's still too early to be happy!
It could have been misheard.
Even if it's true, we still don't know if the peace talks were successful.
Anyway, we must tell Colonel Hopkins.
Oh my god!
I was bringing some food to the Colonel, and he's gone!
It's so great that you're safe.
Start attacking in ten minutes.
Colonel-dono.
You thought that the Colonel would just listen to you?
It was worth a try, wasn't it?
Yes ma'am.
No way...
The Colonel... He laughed...
He laughed because he saw the God of Death that I revived and many deaths.
He... kills.
He fights until there's no one.
But, I helped him. Because of my mistake...
If you think so, then please save the lives that haven't been taken yet.
Noël-san.
Aisha...
A cease-fire!
Stop kidding.
But that girl's ears should be trusted.
Right! We'd like to be witnesses.
You are so careless, forgetful, childish and so uncool!
Onee-chan never lies!
Take this old woman!
So you want to start a war that much!?
It is war that pushes civilisation and science forward.
I want to take it back.
The pride that we once had as human beings.
What!?
The Roman military plans to start attacking tomorrow morning!
Then, we can't avoid the war any longer.
Naomi-san's been arrested.
Let's go.
No way!
We are fighting against the God of Vingt!
But I want to show him the sound that someone showed me!
That's so pointless!
That's selfish.
How can you just do whatever you want?
We're soldiers!
Someone said that the world has already ended.
But I... love this world.
I love this town.
I love all the people here so much.
I can't just... give up.
Kanata...
Please...
Please stop the war.
Aisha-san said the same thing.
But, I...
As a soldier, I have killed people too.
I'm just like you, Noël.
I'm... just like... you.
You have suffered enough.
You've suffered a lot.
So even if no one else forgives you... I will.
So, even if...
You forgive me?
Thank you, Aisha.
If you go, then there is no turning back.
Are you okay with that?
Umm.
Then, I have nothing to say.
Do whatever you want.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
Thank you for saying "no" to us all these times.
Of course, I... do... not... want a girl of the same age as me to be interrogated either!
But, Rio-senpai is not here!
Noël... and Kanata... are not reliable either.
So, I must work hard!
Sorry for being an irresponsible platoon leader.
Kureha-chan.
Let's go, everyone.
Yes.
All the gods, please bless the Maidens of Flame.
The main conversion reactor is increasing power.
FAB, FAC, DMR, ECB are normal.
Superconductivity is stabilising.
No problem with the weapon-control system.
The main and secondary artilleries have initialised properly!
Release all the locks on the joints!
The self weight-reducing system is working.
The coefficient is at about negative five.
Departure preparation completed.
If we perform like we did during training, there won't be any problems.
Let's go, my people!
Yes ma'am!
Prepare to fire the main artillery.
Ammunition type: Armor-piercing!
Armor-piercing ammunition loaded!
Aimed!
Kana-chan, give the signal!
Yes ma'am.
They are starting to attack!?
Shoot!
Aimerais-tu, en ce monde, voir quelque chose, s'effacer
Would you like to see something, in this world, erase itself
Et que l'air soit plus pur, le coeur des hommes transformées
And that the air be purer, the hearts of men transformed
Et pourtant tout est si fragile ici, sur la terre
And yet everything is so fragile here, on Earth
Il n'y a rien qui soit futile, tu sait
There is nothing that is futile, you know
It's Kanata-neechan!
Takemicaduchi?
They can use the past's technology to this extent!
Notify all the tankers!
Try your best to stop them from escaping!
Start attacking!
You won't be able to pass here!
No war anymore!
Don't make trouble for the sisters!
D'un cote, beaux ou bon est quelque fois, prodigieux
From one side, beautiful or good is sometimes, prodigious
If you want to go anyway, you must beat us!
O-Oh.
So, what will you do, God of Vingt?
Et de l'autre, laid ou pauvres est bien souvent, monstrueux
And from the other, ugly or poor is often, monstrous
Qu'importe ce que ton coeur te dictera, souvient toi
Whatever your heart dictates to you, remember
Que la différence naît dans tes yeux
That the difference is born in your eyes
Dissolve!
Join the troops in the back!
Chante toutes les couleurs du monde
Sing all the colours of the world
The Maidens of Flame protect the lives.
Sans manquer une seule note
Without missing a single note
We're all depending on you, Kanata-san.
Chaque choses à sa place ici
Everything has its place here
Once upon a time,
Before the world became like this,
Chaque émoi... forme la symphonie... de notre vie
Every excitement... forms the symphony... of our lives
God sent angels to punish the world.
These angels became wounded, so they rested their wings in a town at the end of the west.
Savoure l'harmonie du ciel
Savour the harmony of the sky
It was the Maidens who lived in the town's fortress, at the edge of the world, that saved these angels.
Vois que tout est essentiel
See that everything is essential
Those whom the Maidens should have destroyed.
But, the Maidens felt sad for those angels,
Il comprend que toi aussi
He understands that you too
So they borrowed power from the huge spider,
Tu veut écrire, la mélodie
You want to write, the melody
and hid the angels at the bottom of the valley.
In order to stop the bleeding, they took turns holding the angels' heads.
And in return, the angels gave them the Golden Horn.
Voudrait tu, de ce monde, pouvoir revoir l'écriture
Would you like to be able to see the writing of this world again
But, in the end, the townspeople discovered the angels.
They set fire to the bottom of the valley.
Et choisir ses couleurs pour faire ta propre peinture
And choose the colours to make your own painting
The Maidens burned in the fire; the angels lost their heads.
Prendre le bien, le mal et sans trier, accepter
Take the good with the bad, and accept it
They died.
Sans couvrir tes yeux, tout regarder
Don't cover your eyes, look at everything
At that time, the angels' troop was discovered. The town's skies were covered.
But, why was that?
Joie et malheur ne font qu'un
Joy and misfortune are one
Suddenly, the sound of the sky started to be heard.
The angels were gone.
Tout est dans leur destin
Everything is in their destiny
It was the Golden Horn, which was sounding for the maidens who gave their own lives to save everyone.
De chaque rime naît un chagrin
In every rhyme a sadness is born
Dans chaque voix... dans chaque petit bruit
In every voice... in every little sound
Vit l'infini
Infinity lives
Hey, do you remember that girl?
You are pushing it too hard.
That girl will probably die.
Everyone! Prepare to attack!
We have to do this. We're soldiers.
Attack!
What!?
What is that!?
Those are our own people!
Whose troop is it?
It belongs to Platoon 1121.
It's the cease-fire signal!
No.
It's the Roman military's signal!
Commander-dono!
You want to retreat from here!?
Prepare to fire the main artillery!
No, we can't stop them.
Platoon leader!
Kana-chan!
That girl!
Hey, what are you doing!
How's the attacking! Shoot! Shoot!
You, drop your weapon!
We have been sent by the Grand Duke of the Republic of Helvetia, who ranks second in line of succession.
The fiancée of the rightful Roman Emperor, Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
With the name of my father, the Grand Duke of Helvetia, and the Roman Emperor, I tell you:
Peace has been made.
You shouldn't fight at all!
Both sides are to retreat as soon as possible!
This is the order!
As Emperor of the
Roman Empire and (as)
Prince of the Helvetian Republic,
I(we) hereby declare
that peace has been established
between these two nations.
On Behalf of the
Grand Duke of the
Republic of Helvetia
and the rightful Emperor
of the Roman Empire, we
hereby declare peace
between our two countries.
If you dare to disobey, under the name of both kings...
The First Division of the Imperial Guard of Helvetia will bring you a crushing defeat!
It can't be...
Then, we...
Don't need to fight any more!
Girl! Girl!
Sergeant-dono!
It's totally spring now!
By the way, what was in the letter from Aisha a few days ago?
My wounds are healed, and I'm practicing the trumpet every day.
Translate it!
I'm fine. I'm practicing the trumpet.
Really? That's great.
Well...
We received a letter from Rome, but not from the capital.
They must be busy. Senpai is the princess!
But, the battlefield was surrounded by the Imperial Guard so quickly, that we couldn't say anything to her.
That's the sound of Klaus-san's bike.
He's there, he's there.
I've been waiting so long, and worried!
I really will...
She's there.
From today on, I, Second Lieutenant Rio Kazumiya Arkadia, am assigned to be a member of Platoon 1121.
Captain Felicia Heideman, please approve my arrival.
Approved.
Here, we don't have to use rank to address people, Rio.
Well, the Roman Emperor really understands people.
Besides stopping the war, he said he would accept whatever I wish.
Well...
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Rio.