I'm sick of walking!
Hang in there.
Don't wanna!
Carry me!
Hey, Inaba.
Come on, Taichi!
Can you give me a hand?
She's going through an episode.
I don't wanna walk anymore...
Not my problem. You deal with it.
Hey, Inaba!
Hey, why are you guys fooling around?
Yaegashi...
If you use this trip as an excuse to do
unspeakable things to Nagase, you'll pay dearly.
You make it sound as if I'm the bad guy!
Taichi!
Carry me!
Isn't there something else
you care about just as much?
Nagase! Cut it out!
Hey, Inaba!
Help me out here!
Inaba!
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
Quit beating
around the bush!
How about laughing more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
That comic was pretty cool.
Time for some curry.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi Academy
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Curry hot pot
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
me yui
We should get married
I love youuuuu
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
The whole world
Let's go
to Disneyland
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry, I can't
go out with you.
Seriously.
Done tomorrow's
homework?
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
I can't believe we have to use this dump.
Sorry. It's my fault for
losing at rock-paper-scissors.
Well, it's okay.
Yaegashi, your punishment
must be more severe.
What?
Watase, can you think
of a suitable punishment?
I'd love to!
You look happy.
Now, now, now.
One day we'll all look
back on this and laugh.
Right, Inaban?
I seriously doubt that.
Putting Into Words
Burnable Trash
Separate
Your
Garbage!
Uh, I'm sorry.
How can you be so bad
at rock-paper-scissors?
You couldn't beat Iori or Watase either.
Oh, according to my daily horoscope,
I'll have the worst possible luck today.
Maybe that's it.
Yikes.
The fall would kill you.
With your luck, you need to be extra careful.
The only reason I'd fall is if I were to jump off.
Why are you smiling?
You were depressed a second ago.
Well, it feels like it's been ages since we just chatted about nothing.
What? You don't have
to be so upset about it.
Be quiet!
Are the three of them doing okay?
They're probably fine now
that Inaba is recovering.
Anyway...
You look great!
There's something about girls
with long hair in aprons.
I'm actually impressed you're
so laid back about all this.
What does it take to never have to worry?
You're pretty good, Nagase.
I do a lot of cooking at home.
Oh...
Yours look a little rough, Inaba.
Oops!
Don't make fun of me!
I'd be great at this if I just tried!
Wanna see?!
Wh-Why are you so excited?
Are you having an episode?
So what if Taichi gave you
a little compliment, Iori?!
You shouldn't be too happy with yourself!
How did I get pulled into this?
Let's race to see who can chop these faster!
A-Am I supposed to do that too?
Don't ask me.
I got the rice.
Oh, you're getting along just fine.
I was right to assign all
of you to the same group.
How do you figure?
Can we start, Fujishima?
I'm starving.
Not yet. Wait a little longer.
Hurry up!
The other groups already started eating!
It'll be a little longer.
I just added the last original spice.
Huh?
You're pretty picky about your cooking.
Not always.
Only when it's curry.
Why?
Okay, it's ready!
Delicious!
Hunger is the best spice,
second only to love!
Hey, are you listening to me?
I'm too busy eating this good food!
I was listening to every word!
Love is the answer!
You don't mean love in a weird way, do you?
Who knows?
Anyway, Nagase...
There's rice on your cheek.
It's okay! It's okay!
I can get it myself!
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Let's focus on eating.
That was so good.
Yeah.
I wouldn't mind going on a picnic every day.
I guess.
Say, Inaban...
Hey, Inaba!
Are you bleeding?
Look here!
Oh, I didn't notice.
How did you not notice?
What if it gets infected?
I can wash my own hand!
Does anyone have a band-aid?
It's fine. I brought my own.
I'll be back in a bit.
Wait, Nagase!
Man, they need to mind their own business.
Wh-What is it, Iori?
Inaban, are you...
Huh?
Are you in love with...
Wait, Inaban!
She knows!
She knows! She knows!
Separate
Your
Garbage!
Where did Nagase and Inaba go?
Separate
Your
Garbage!
Separate
Your
Garbage!
Separate
Your
Garbage!
Inaban!
Tell me why...
Inaban...
Are you in love with Taichi too?
Why?
You kept trying to push
Taichi and me together.
You always said that you
wanted us to be together.
I knew that you cared about him.
But wasn't that only as a friend?
Why were you trying to get us together?
Did you want to let me have him?
Inaban...
Explain yourself, Inaba Himeko!
Iori, are you having an episo—
What's that mean?! What's that mean?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
If you don't give me an explanation,
I'm no longer your friend!
But... But...
That's the only way the five
of us can stay together!
Why would you think that?!
Well, when you have a
group of boys and girls,
and love comes in and complicates things, there will be arguments.
Friendships fall apart.
Aoki loves Yui,
and despite what she says,
Yui doesn't mind his attention.
You're looking for someone to support you,
and Taichi's naturally inclined to do that.
If the two of you get together,
everything will work out.
Then the five of us
will always be together.
Are you stupid?
Everything will work out?
I never realized the Inaba Himeko
I knew was such an idiot!
I was always alone.
Always by myself.
But in high school, I made
friends for the first time!
I didn't want to lose those friends!
I didn't know what else to do!
I don't care about that!
If you feel lonely, you should say something!
If you're worried, say something!
Not everyone is as smart as you are!
If you want people to understand you, you should say something!
Even if you're worried that
you'll embarrass yourself,
you should still say something!
I can't do that!
If I show people how weak I am,
they won't need me anymore.
I didn't have a choice!
What else was I supposed to do?!
You didn't need to do anything!
I don't believe that!
A worthless, unwanted failure like me...
Don't say "like me"!
Don't talk about yourself like that!
But it's true!
I'm not a good person like the rest of you!
How do you think that makes me
feel for liking Inaba Himeko?!
I really like you a lot, Inaban. A lot.
If you don't realize that,
I'll say it a million times.
I love you. We all do.
But that's the fake Inaba Himeko who's strong and knows what she's doing.
I'd like you no matter what a mess you were.
You're wrong.
You're wrong, Inaban.
You're a much better person than you realize.
No, that's not it.
That's not the point.
You can't label people as good or bad.
It's not that simple!
Trust me!
If you...
If you think I'm a good person,
then you should believe me!
It's okay, Inaban!
You don't need to do anything.
I'll always be your friend.
No, that's not quite right.
I want to always be your friend!
Please let me be your friend!
I've...
I've always wanted to
hear someone say that.
But it's too late now.
I'd only be a third wheel.
And I don't want to ruin the SCS bond,
so I can't go back to the clubroom.
Why not? What makes you think that?
Well, it would be really awkward.
Everyone would feel uncomfortable.
Remember what you just said?
If Taichi and I got together,
everything would work out?
But wouldn't it also work out if you and Taichi got together instead?
But you and Taichi are a good match.
And I didn't really care about
Taichi in the beginning.
Er, I still don't, really...
Why are you still lying to yourself?!
I'm not lying.
You were trying hard to
protect our friendship, right?
But you love Taichi so much now that you can't hold yourself back!
The Inaba Himeko I know
would fight for both!
She would never give up,
no matter the odds!
Arrogant and patronizing!
Using people to her advantage!
Willing to do whatever it takes
to accomplish her goal!
That's the Inaba Himeko I know!
Besides, the friendship between Nagase Iori
and Inaba Himeko isn't going
to end because of one guy.
That's what I believe.
So you don't need to worry.
You can come back to the clubroom.
Okay, okay.
But don't blame me if you regret it later.
I'm no pushover.
If that's how you want it,
I'll be going all out.
You're going to be crushed.
Just so you know,
I don't plan on losing or giving him up.
And do you really think you can beat me?
There are plenty of ways to beat a girl who's got nothing but a cute face.
Ouch...
Anyway, you were pretty intense.
Was that really me?
Huh? When did my episode—
Iori?
Well, I want to set the record straight.
What the hell?
Why did you show up now?!
Well, I wanted to tell you that this unleashing of desire business is about to end.
End? Is it all over?
But there's been an accident,
and I thought it would be more amusing,
or maybe better to let you know—
What the hell are you talking about?!
Yaegashi fell.
Huh?
Fell?
You mean he fell off that cliff?
Taichi!
This isn't like what happened with Nagase.
I didn't do a thing.
So why did he fall?
That white knight
is really something.
Ow...
Geez, don't make us worry like that!
We ran over here for nothing!
Yeah!
Yui and I were having some
quality time cleaning up together.
That's irrelevant.
Oh, Inaba.
You look really pale.
Wasn't Nagase with you?
Listen to this.
Taichi did something stupid again.
He was trying to help a kitten
that was stuck in a tree.
And he ended up falling down.
What about the cat?
It's fine.
It's a good thing that
neither of you were hurt.
Sorry about all the trouble.
Honestly, you and your false alarms.
Well, at least we get to laugh it off.
Inaba?
What's wrong, Inaba?
Don't make me worry, you idiot!
Hey, that was uncalled for.
Er, I'm sorry!
Don't cry!
I don't know what's wrong,
but it was all my fault!
I'll apologize!
So stop crying!
Inaba, you don't need to cry.
Look, Taichi's fine.
What? Were you really that worried?
You can stop crying.
Stop crying, Inaba.
I finally made it back.
Iori, where did you go?
Yeah, I'm not really sure.
Um, what's wrong with Inaban?
Actually, we're not sure either.
Inaba, I'm not sure
what's wrong, but I'm sorry!
It was all my fault!
Inaba, Inaba.
You can stop crying.
Taichi's fine, Inaba.
Inaban, Inaban? What's wrong?
Yamaboshi
Academy
So these episodes of unleashing
our desires are over.
Starting tomorrow, it's back
to working on the paper.
Is it really over?
Yeah, it might be something else next time.
No point in worrying about that now.
We should just enjoy the freedom we have!
Honestly...
What does it take to never have to worry?
Huh?
What happened to Taichi and Inaba?
No idea.
Maybe Fujishima's yelling
at them about what happened.
You think?
Oh, in that case...
We should head home then.
H-Hey, Inaba.
You wanted to talk?
Wh-What is it?
I love you!
Oh, uh...
Er...
I-I'm...
I'm happy to hear you say that.
I truly feel honored, from
the bottom of my heart.
But right now,
I'm in love with Nagase.
I already knew that.
But "right now" means that I still have a chance to change your mind.
Uh, that wasn't what I meant...
Since you and Iori aren't going out yet,
there's plenty of room
for me to worm myself in.
And I already told Iori
about this beforehand,
so don't worry.
We're going to have a fair fight,
so you can do whatever you want.
W-Wait! You're moving too fast!
What do you mean?
It almost sounds like the two
of you are fighting over me...
You took my first without asking.
Another one can't hurt, right?
I'll see you in the clubroom tomorrow.
I'm so embarrassed I could die!
I kissed him!
I'm heading out.
What's going on, Himeko?
You usually leave without saying a word.
Shut up, stupid.
Next Time
A Story That Began As We Realized It
I see you're busy shakin' out that thin red velvet cloth
But before you take your leave, might I ask where you're off to?
Me, I'm headed for the morning, travelin' to the west
Then may God be with you
Your eyes, reflecting up to me from the teacup
look just like a rabbit's in a cage
Must be because we forgot to add the sugar
But who cares about that
Your love is sweet enough
I cry out, again and again to the dawning sky
Are there really things in this world that I truly cherish?
This aching in my heart, and the place where I belong
Maybe even those are things that I hold dear all the same
Cry out
Nagase Iori
Tune in next time!
Laugh more
Rice? Bread?
me yui
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
Let's go out
Screw that
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow