This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old.
Her debut single as Full Moon,
"Myself", is now on sale.
She thought the debut would cause an uproar in her class...
...but the rumors going around were different.
She was really disappointed.
But, with my loud voice, I managed to advertise for her.
Now that she's befriended her classmates,
she's really happy now.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Mitsukinchin, who'll come?
My grandmother originally planned to come.
But she caught a cold this morning.
So, no one will come.
Ah, I see.
Who is that..?
Could he be...
Don't tell me...
...The Prince?
Eh?
See? Don't you remember?
From Route L...
The Prince?
Who's that?
He's so cool!
Wakaouji-sensei...
Dr. Wakaouji, he really stands out in a place like this... definitely.
He reeks of medicine.
I Wanted You to Listen
Mitsuki-chan.
Sensei, why are you here?
Well, your grandmother is ill today,
and I heard that you had a Parents Day...
...so I came here instead.
Thanks.
Who's he?
Your dad?
You never told me that your dad was so cool.
No, he's not.
He's not?
Well, Wakaouji-sensei is a friend of my dad.
I see, so that's how it is.
Am I troubling you by posing as your father?
Not at all!
That's not the case...
I admit that you really stand out.
Eh?
Oh my!
He's looking this way!
Prince!!!
A Greeting Always
Brightens the Mood.
Wakaouji-sensei, I listened to your story.
It was really interesting.
Not really.
It's just my past.
I felt very proud today.
Attention everyone!
Next up is this month's latest rising star.
With her big hit, Full Moon is next with "Myself".
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
She said it's a big hit!
Just like I told you, right?
Ahhh!
Shhh!!
Yes, this is Wakaouji.
Hey, what's that all about?
Right while her song was playing...
...he just had  to pick up the phone.
Yes, right.
Tomorrow we meet at the Taujo Hotel, right?
Here, show him the CD.
Yes, I'll leave the rest to you.
So if you'd excuse me...
Sensei.
Hmm?
Want to hear some music?
Here, this one!
Ah, sorry.
This car is not equipped with a CD player.
Well, how about if I give it to you... so you can play it at home?
See, she's really pretty, right?
I'm sorry.
Hmm?
The thing is... I never really
listen to this kind of music.
I'm already an old guy.
What are you talking about?
Just listen to it.
I think it's a very good song.
Really?
You like listening to music.
Yes.
Maybe, if I become a singer...
...I think this is the kind of song
that I'd want to sing.
That's why I want to know what you think of this song, Wakaouji-sensei.
Please listen to it.
I see.
You want to become a singer.
That's right.
You told me countless times.
Right.
Ah, by the way, about the meeting today...
...that was a first for me,
so I was very nervous.
Hmph.
Eh... um...
Uh... um...
Mitsuki-chan, what is it?
It's nothing.
Why are you like that?
Stupid.
For showing up at school today...
...I thank you for that.
Mitsuki-chan!
Sorry, did I say anything bad?
No, you didn't.
Really?
W-Well...
You should tell me if
it was something I said.
Nothing at all.
Is that... so?
That's right.
With a cold guy like him,
there's no use telling him.
Sensei, you're cool... and you're smart as well.
You're perfect.
There's nothing to complain about.
Mitsuki-chan.
Ah?
Ah...
I really am an old guy... I can't even understand a girl's feelings!
Ahhhhh!
Grandma...
I've brought you some tea.
Ah, thank you.
You must be hungry, Grand...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Ah, that's the radio in Tanaka-san's room?
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Mitsuki-san.
Y-Yes?
It's irritating.
Could you turn it down, please?
S-Sure.
My heart's beating so fast.
Tanaka-san?
Mitsuki-chan?
Your earphones are not plugged it.
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I lost way too much back then
I could hear it throughout the house.
Oh, darn.
My fault, my fault.
Nani mo utae-
I couldn't sing...
Hey, hey, we have a job today.
Yes.
Yay, we're going out, we're going out!
Eh, you're going to see the doctor?
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
The thing is... I never really
listen to this kind of music.
What, I have to stay?!
Meroko, you're annoying.
Are you serious?
It's really boring here!
Mitsuki-chan is not the social type...
A mature love is usually the key.
What... what?
Girls look for a father figure.
That's so moving.
Huh, that can't be... like that...
No, Mitsuki-chan is not like that.
For the love of knowledge, I'll keep a copy.
Well, this is for my love of knowledge...
Man, this is so boring!
I can't take it anymore!
Thank you very much.
Wasn't that a good session?
Especially that tune.
Yes.
Here, what do you think this is?
What is it?
The song's such a big hit,
stores keep asking for more!
I see.
It's really selling.
What is it? You're not happy?
No, that's not the case.
You don't seem very energetic.
No, I'm fine.
I see.
It's really selling.
Well, we'll split here.
Take care on your way back.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
You're worried about something.
Why do you say that?
"Why?"
It's written all over your face.
The doctor and your grandmother...
They won't listen to my song.
So now I'm sad.
Really?
Stupid, I don't mean literally.
Eh?
It's a big hit, isn't it?
But, I...
I kept thinking about it,
but I wanted to be happy.
My dad composed a song...
...I passed the audition with it...
...and now I'm a singer.
However, despite that fact,
Wakaouji-sensei won't listen to it.
Somehow...
...I feel like even Dad wouldn't
recognize my song.
I don't think so.
Eh?
You have a good voice.
You put your best effort into that song.
Even so...
That proves it.
W-What is it?
Takuto, you don't know anything about music.
That's why you said those things so easily.
Ah.
S-Sorry, I went over the line.
Um...
I'll go first.
I...
I was a musician in the past.
Eh?
Papa, over here!
Wait a second.
Takuto.
What did you just say?
I was a musician in the past.
In the past?
When I was a human, I used to sing too.
Eh, Takuto used to be a human?!
Hmph, I wasn't born as a Shinigami from the start.
Eh, no way!
I never knew.
Well, how about Meroko?
Was Meroko a human, too?
I don't know her that well.
But, I think so.
So that's how it is...
Sorry... for saying that you didn't know anything about music.
That's alright.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go.
Eh?
Where to?
Your song.
You want him to listen, right?
Dr. Wakaouji is out for a meeting today.
Yes, right.
He has a meeting.
Now that I think about it...
Yes, tomorrow we meet at the Taujo Hotel, right?
Alright, we're going to the Taujo Hotel!
Ah, w-wait!
Eh, was I wrong?
Yeah.
He said something about a special favor and he sent someone else instead.
I don't see him.
We came here uninvited... won't we be bothering Sensei?
How could you say that?
We won't know until we try.
But...
If he really doesn't like listening to music, what should we do?
Aw, geez!
Don't hesitate now!
Let's go in!
Have more confidence in yourself!
Right, right.
Meroko?
What are you doing here?
That's because...!
You two always go out!
Being by myself is so boring!
But, what about...
It's alright.
Since your grandmother
has a cold, she won't check.
Today, she'll be bedridden all day long.
We won't get discovered.
Medical
Meeting
The Topic
on a
Breathing
Machine
Ah, there it is!
Who are you looking for?
Um, I'm looking for Wakaouji-sensei...
I'm really sorry.
If you're not on the guest list, you're not allowed to go in.
Tsk, and we've already gotten this far!
I was pretty sure he'd be here.
I know!
I'll make Dr. Wakaouji listen to the CD.
But, but...
Meroko, not again...?!
Anyways, we just want him to listen, right?
Meroko!
Ah, where are you going?
Takuto, what'll we do?
Heh, this should do it.
Geez, that Meroko...
Where did she go?
Darn her.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
It's Meroko!
How could you say that to me?!
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
No, I'm certain of it?!
Hey, what's going on here?
There's some weird music for the meeting upstairs.
It's a wonderful song, nonetheless.
Let's go see!
Sure.
Now's our chance!
Well, this background music is pretty good.
Where is he...?
I don't see him.
It's very good.
Ehhhh?
Hurry up! Just ask someone!
Okay.
What was that all about?
I wonder if this music is
part of their service?
Excuse me, I'm sorry...
Where's Wakaouji-sensei?
Oh, Wakaouji-kun?
He's not attending the meeting today.
Eh?
Where did he go?
How was it?
Today was perfect, right?
Hmm, if only that doctor was here.
Eh, he's not here?
Oh crap...
Did you get the place?
Yeah.
Let's see...
This place is...
Is it a place you know?
Yeah.
I came here once before.
Really?
Why do I...
...have this feeling?
Ah.
Wakaouji-sensei!
It's been ten years since you left.
Your daughter now is twelve years old.
She's a strong girl.
Just like Hazuki-san.
This is Dad and Mom's...
If not for you two, I would've always run away.
Every time I see Mitsuki-chan, she reminds me more and more of Hazuki-san.
It's almost like going back in time.
This is too painful for me.
Mitsuki-chan is now looking into the future.
I can't let the wounds of the past haunt me.
I hope you two can give me the strength to get through all of this.
For a long time, I kept silent...
...about my music.
The thing is... I never really
listen to this kind of music.
I'm already an old guy.
So what he said that time...
You want to become a singer.
That's right.
You told me countless times.
I thought that I'd never have to deal with music ever again.
But your daughter wants to become a singer.
I guess she's just like her parents.
As your daughter continues to grow...
I kept getting reminded of you.
Both of you, together with me...
...please protect her.
He's coming this way!
She couldn't be...
Wakaouji-sensei, thank you.
Dad, Mom...
Mitsuki has debuted.
Please cheer for me.
I...
...will do my best.
Is Wakaouji-sensei here?
Oh, Mitsuki-chan!
Sensei, can I...
Ah, sorry!
There's an emergency.
I'll be right back.
Geez, he's always busy.
Is that...?
Sensei!
You bought it too!
Sorry...
...for making you wai...
Huh?
Mitsuki-chan?
She went home?
That can't be helped.
Thank you for stopping by on Parents Day!
It was a little bit awkward...
...but I was very happy!
From now on, you can pose as my dad, okay.
From, Mitsuki.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Sensei... I wonder if he's reading the card right now.
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
What is it Meroko?
Grinning all by yourself...
Because...!
Takuto, aren't you glad?
TV appearance! TV appearance!
Look to the right and left, there are so many celebrities!
Darn it!
It's supposed to be her appearance, not ours!
But, see... she's happy too.
Ah, you two!, When will it stop!
Is this gonna be okay?
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The Law of Show Business!?
Look forward to it!