What's an urban legend?!
That black bike!
The headless rider!
The man riding that black bike...
...has no head.
It's completely gone, yet he can still move.
It doesn't sound like that difficult of a job, but be careful anyway.
I don't remember anything about you becoming a crusader for justice.
What the hell are you?
What the hell are you?!
The headless rider?! I've heard of him!
My friend saw him riding around.
Well, I'm not really interested in that.
If that's what you mean, I took a picture.
See?
The headless rider?
That's this guy.
I've heard of that.
I, like, mighta seen it near Sunshine.
For reals?
I dunno, but, like, everyone was freaking out, so it had to be him.
Everyone has a lot to say about her.
It looks like the bike was spotted again.
But, do you really think it's true that he has no head?
That's just ill-spirited gossip.
But I've heard some stories that are pretty believable.
Whoa...
There's no way he could be headless.
Unless he weren't human...
Then it'd be believable.
Apparently, those who know the most about it aren't talking.
Sorry, but I don't know anything about it.
What do you think?
What impressions do you have of this headless rider?
Do you think she's scary? Cool? Unexpectedly kind?
Or...
Do you not know what to think?
I'm going to tell you what I know about the headless rider.
It's a long story, but I'd like you to keep an open mind.
First, let me introduce myself.
I'm Kishitani Shinra, twenty-four years old.
I'm an underground physician here in this town.
To put it more clearly, I'm a black market doctor.
I treat people who've been injured by illegal weapons and
perform cosmetic surgery on people who need to change their faces.
Even though I work in this field, I'm skilled and well respected.
Alright, time to get to the important part.
I'm home!
That's right.
I...live with the headless rider, Celty Sturluson.
I'm home, Celty.
It was a really simple job.
How about you?
No peeking!
Sorry! I didn't mean it like that! I just accidentally...
Umm, you look pretty pissed, huh?
You might need some more calcium.
Are you saying I should eat egg shells?
That might be a good idea.
Well, I'm just a doctor.
I'm not a nutritionist, so I don't know stuff like how much calcium is in egg shells or how well you could absorb it from that source.
I don't even know where your brain is,
so who knows how much you even need calcium.
Shut up!
Hey, Celty, I'll ask you again, but how does the world look to you when you have no eyeballs?
I can't explain to other people what I don't understand.
She doesn't have a head, but can see, hear, and smell.
However, she can't see 360 degrees just because she doesn't have a head.
She has only a slightly broader range of visibility than humans...
This is nothing more than one of my hypotheses,
but regarding that mysterious, shadow-like, sci-fi
substance which keeps emanating from your body...
Do you think it collects information about your surroundings for you by releasing particles into the air and analyzing them when they return?
Of course, then you wouldn't be able to pick up information about things from far away.
I don't care.
I'm fine as long as I can see and hear.
You're always like this, Celty.
I wonder just how different the worlds you and I perceive truly are...
That's all I want to know.
This isn't just a conversation about your field of vision.
It's also about your value system.
The value system of a fairy who just materialized in this town.
I'd like to know what a dullahan thinks is valuable about this world...
What's wrong?
If it's okay with you, let's talk it over.
Did something happen?
Orihara said your job today was easy, but...
I finished the job without any setbacks.
But?
I'm really thankful for couriers.
I'm where I am thanks to you, and you're where you are thanks to me.
I'd rather not believe the last part of that sentence.
Don't say that...
I hope I can count on you in the future as well.
I'd like to get along with you, you know.
From now until forever...
Is it just me, or are you being really creepy?
It's totally just you.
Anyway, do you know what a dullahan is?
Apparently it's a headless fairy in Ireland,
but there's a caricature artist in Yoemi
park who says he's seen someone like that.
I heard he kept talking about how, "She had no head! She had no head," so I wonder if he's referring to a dullahan...
Is he still there?
Hmph. Who knows.
I knew she'd be interested.
Celty Sturluson is not human.
She's a wandering spirit that's termed a "dullahan" by Celtic lore.
Do you know of a caricature artist?
Oh, he's not here anymore.
Hey, didn't that guy say he was moving on to Yokohama?
Huh?
A dullahan holds its own decapitated head in its hands while she rides a two-wheeled carriage pulled by a headless horse called "Koshitabawa."
It visits the houses of people who are close to dying.
If you happen to open the door for it, your life ends.
You're doused with blood from a wash bin.
It'd be difficult to connect her current form to that ominous and bloody legend, though.
Except for the fact she has no head.
Why did she come to Ikebukuro in Tokyo, Japan?
Why is she so concerned about her own head?
I'll tell you about that right now.
It happened twenty years ago.
She awoke one day in the mountains to find that her head was gone.
In that instant, she also noticed that she'd lost various memories.
Things like her personality and memories of her past.
However, she remembered that she was a dullahan, her
name was Celty Sturluson, and she possessed certain abilities.
And the first thing she was surprised at was...
I don't just think about things with my head.
As she said.
She also noticed that she felt the presence of her head nearby.
Assessing the situation, she inferred one thing.
That her will was shared by her body and head,
and that her lost memories must lie inside her head.
She then made a decision.
She was going to get her head back and
remember the meaning of her existence.
That itself became her purpose in life.
It's possible that her head left its body of its own free will.
Even so, she wouldn't know unless she got it back.
He wasn't in Yokohama anymore.
I tried Tama next, then Chiba.
No matter where I went, I couldn't find him.
You should've just waited until tomorrow.
I was desperate.
My head might be there.
I wanted to get it back no matter what.
Even if was only a day earlier...
I don't want to live with only vague memories anymore.
Following that faint presence her head exuded, she came so far...
But apparently her head had left the country.
The ship was headed for Japan.
She decided to stow away and keep following it.
The problem was her horse.
Dullahans possess horse carcasses as their servants.
She could've just made it disappear,
but only her head would know where it went.
Therefore, even though she knew how
to make it disappear, she couldn't do it.
It was then...
That she...
Came across it.
I couldn't find him anywhere.
But...
Hey, I know that guy.
He was in Southern Ikebukuro Park just two days ago.
I see.
You want me to take you to him?
It's got to be inconvenient living like that, right?
There you go.
Amazing!
He drew you prettier than you really are, Arisa.
Hey!
Great job as always, mister.
No, no, I still can't quite draw things the way I envision them.
Thank you very much.
My pleasure.
Come again!
Okay!
I'm sorry, but it's getting dark.
I'm done for the day.
Is it true that you've seen a dullahan?
Huh?
Yeah...yeah, it is.
I saw one in the mountains of Ireland when I was young.
I saw it with these eyes, I'm certain.
What do you mean by, "It lost its head?"
"It lost its head?" That's not it.
It had no head.
I can't draw it right.
Look.
It was a woman, and an extremely beautiful one at that.
She passed by me on a mountain road during a really foggy night.
She was frightening yet beautiful as she drove by at an incredible speed.
I just knew she wasn't of this world.
After I returned to the inn and talked to someone, he told me it was, without a doubt, a dullahan.
Apparently they've inhabited that place since the olden days.
Why don't your dullahans hold any heads?
I can't draw them.
The more I try to draw them, the more they vary.
My memory of that day is so vivid,
yet I can't remember that woman at all.
What color was her hair? Her eyes?
What about her facial expression?
If I knew, I wouldn't bother making pictures of her.
Although, a strange man came by the other day.
He told me that picture was perfect.
He said she didn't have to have a head.
What a weird guy.
Why do you care so much about it?
That experience was the height of my life.
That one night was my whole life.
I want to get back the feelings and the memories I had of that moment.
Thanks, man.
I get it.
You don't remember meeting him at all, do you?
No.
That dullahan may have been you, or it may not have.
Or he might have misconstrued what he saw.
It was definitely me.
I know it.
Alright.
Where was I going then?
What was I thinking and what was my goal?
Do you really have to worry that much about it?
Huh?
You can appear and disappear at will and you're refreshingly unique.
However, you're still quite far away from having your wish come true.
What are you trying to say?
It's simple...
Just give up.
That strange man's probably right.
You might be fine without your head.
Let's stop looking for your head and go somewhere together.
Anywhere is fine.
As long as you wish it, I'll use any means
I can to get you back to your hometown.
I'll go there, too.
We'll be together forever.
I don't hate you, but I'm fine with how things are now.
Don't say that—
I'm fine!
Then...
Try being more feminine—
I've had enough!
So, I guess our values are different after all.
Let's end this intermission and continue with the story.
The story of her—no, us after we boarded that ship.
She was able to talk the crew into letting her on board, but she realized her appearance made her stand out.
After knowing her for a while, I can now say it wasn't much of a shock.
Although, I was surprised the first time I saw her.
I was four years old at the time.
I was returning to Japan with my father.
Dad, Dad, there's a woman in the cargo bay!
To put it nicely, my father—Shingen—wasn't someone you couldn call normal.
After hearing what I said, most parents would just ignore it.
However, my father was different.
Maybe it was because he was a doctor, but it piqued his interest.
Ma'am, this might be presumptuous, but is it true you have no head?
So my father entreated her:
"As long as you let me dissect you once, I'll give you a place to stay."
She assented.
It may have been best for her,
but I'm sure she was still worried.
Apparently she doesn't remember much of what happened after that.
Human anesthesia didn't really work on her,
so I'm sure the shock of it all was quite great.
It seems she can feel pain, but not nearly as acutely as a human would.
She doesn't have a heart.
All her organs are in form only and serve no real function.
She has blood vessels, but no blood courses
through them. Her flesh is the only thing that's real.
It's as if she's just a model.
But, look.
How does she die?
He's a horrible father, right?
He let a four year-old dissect somebody.
Yet, thanks to his teachings, I learned how to be a surgeon.
I don't even know what you could call "fortunate" about this.
What's wrong?
The first time I saw her, I was attracted to everything about her.
My feelings for her haven't changed during the twenty years I've lived with her.
And she continues to search for her head while working as a courier.
I wonder what she plans to do if she ever finds her head?
What will happen to her?
Is her will the same as her head's?
Or...
What're you filming?
Um, you know, I'm filming every
aspect of my daily life to leave to posterity.
Well, whatever you're doing, do it quietly. I can't sleep.
I'm sorry, Celty.
Well, I'll end it here. We'll continue at a later time.
Wow, that's perfect!
Huh? What is? Dullahans are supposed to carry their heads with them.
It's fine if it doesn't have its head, right?
Of course it's not. You can say that
because you've never seen the real thing.
She was an incredibly beautiful woman.
I'm sure.
Hm?
But I still think she looks better without her head.
She's more charming that way.
It's perfect as it is.
Therefore, there's no need for you to worry.
It's fine if you can't draw her head.
Even if you never can...
I'm still going to draw it.
I said it's fine as it is.
You sure are weird.
No, I'm not that weird.
You want to know about my seductive suaveness and heartbreaker lifestyle?
Then take the channel of your heart and tune it in to me, the cool yet shy Kida Masaomi.
Next time: False Advertising.
Don't miss out on this once-in-300-years chance!