We've found the location of our next target, Frank Cloud.
So who are we hiring this time?
We've already chosen someone who will definitely accomplish the mission.
Why are we letting them go again? They overdid it last time.
In order to protect our power and influence.
Their power will become a flame endlessly burning towards hell.
This world will become ours.
Are you hurt?
It's just a scratch.
I will...
kill.
In order to live,
I will kill.
The Awakening
Am I going to die...?
If I don't run, I'll die...
I can't run.
What should I do?
If I can't run, then I can only kill.
Kill or be killed.
This is...
What..is this?
What am I?
Who am I? I can't
remember my name. What is this?
Japanese?
Duffel bag...
This is...me. I'm a Japanese
tourist so I...
What is this? Why can't I remember?
This won't work. The people
who attacked me could be nearby.
Don't always do things alone, Kuro.
Did you forget what a bodyguard is?
Want to come with me?
No thanks.
It's ok. I'm only scouting it out.
I can't let him do everything.
That annoying snake is probably overdoing it.
He's so disgusting.
He's helped us a lot though.
He's just pretending to be a puppet.
Doing anything for success is the Inferno Code.
I understand but, Kuro, you're getting in too deep.
If anything happens, call me.
I'm counting on you, Lizzie.
If only you drove better...
There's an 74% chance of success and an 87% chance of awakening.
He's only been awake for a few minutes and he's already there.
I've said this before.
He's a prodigy.
I'm so going to hell for this.
No, wait, I'm probably already in hell.
Just then, he sensed...
That's instinct for you.
But his is more of a sixth sense.
It's not enough, not enough.
He hasn't reached his full potential yet.
it's your turn now, Phantom.
But don't overdo it.
Yes, master.
If you want to live,
Those eyes...
then fight me like you mean it.
His heart is confused. His life is confused.
His thoughts are confused.
He'll probably live if he tries hard enough.
Whoah.
The people who follow
their instincts are strong.
Those who give up
are weak.
In this world, those people are the ones
that I hate the most.
Well well well if it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
What a pleasant surprise.
How's it going?
Iit'll be over quickly.
Care to join me?
Yes.
This way please.
Who is she?
Why does she want to kill me?
I don't know why I'm being attacked.
Where the hell is this?
Who...am I?
I can't escape.
Theres nowhere left to hide.
I can't run anymore.
You are my...
I'm going to die. Shes going to kill me.
Its starting.
Starting?
Watch closely please.
Why!
If you want to live, fight me like you mean it.
I have nothing.
No past. No future.
Not even my life.
Even so,
I still don't want to die.
Where should I go?
I don't know where I'm from.
I don't even have memories...
How do I find freedom?
What is this empty freedom I get from murdering?
Tell me.
Please...
I'm begging you...
What is this.
This is...
Who the...Who the...
HELL AM I!?!?
Zwei.
Y-You are...
I am Ein.
You are Zwei.
Zwei...
Thats your name.
The name I have given you.
You are Zwei.
Zwei...what is this exactly?
You are mine.
And I am yours.
What do you think?
He really is a prodigy.
His statistics are amazing.
Even without training and experience.
He relies purely on natural skill.
And this is what he did, defeat Ein.
This isn't like you, Phantom.
I'm very sorry.
He's an absolute genius.
He shows his true potential in life or death situations.
It's as if he was born to be in Inferno.
Its the only way he can survive now.
But like this, will he want to join?
We've taken the yolk from the egg.
And now we can't put it back.
He has nowhere else to go.
This is your specialty.
It'll be easy.
The usual drugs and hypnosis
should be enough to erase his memories completely.
Don't worry,
Ms. McCunnen
This is my forte.
It was his own luck that landed him here.
I was originally planning to kill him but
I wanted to give him a chance to prove himself worthy of this new life.
So he came alone from Japan?
Thats bad.
No one will ever be able to find him.
Our plans are perfect.
Ok then.
Scythe Master,
I'll leave this boy with you.
Thank you very much.
Ein and Zwei,
put some effort forth for them.
How long do you think you can treat me like this?
Madam
I am first place. A woman named Ein.
You are second place. A man named Zwei.
Together we are...
What are you still doing?
Its over, Ein.
Go back to work.
Yes, master.
We can't live like this.
We're just empty shells.
I can only live
as Phantom
Welcome back, Master.
Where is everyone else?
Yes, they're all sleeping right now.
Sleeping?
In the middle of the day?
Wh-Who are you?
Phantom.
Inferno's top assassin
and the world's best sniper.
My perfect creations...
And him...
You over did it.
I see...
Is it finished?
With this, two of the five major Los Angeles Mafias have been leveled.
Gentlemen, allow me to show you.
Our new world order.
Thanks to Inferno.
Thank you.
We puppets don't belong anywhere.
Don't think that way, Phantom.
Phantom.
We aren't allowed to live unless we can kill.