I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
I like those shades, man.
Mmm, I like everything you got.
Looking to make some big bucks?
I think you'd fit right in here.
"Herbal Medicine Shop"
You know the first rule of combat?
Shoot them before they shoot you.
Quite an elaborate way
to get acquainted.
I had no idea the legendary
Lady Luck was still alive.
Poker Alice, Queen of Hearts.
They tell tales about you
on every asteroid from here to TJ.
If Alice was still alive,
she'd be over 200 years old.
That's true.
Considering, you're looking pretty good.
Hottest granny in the star system.
Poker Alice never lost a game.
And she never cheated.
She was just a born winner.
Maybe, and maybe that's
just part of the legend.
I understand you've accrued
quite a large debt.
Would you rather deal with the galactic
police or me, Ms. Queen of Hearts?
Prophecy?
So Charlie says,
"Only hands can wash hands."
"If you want to receive,
you have to give."
Something like that.
I wish I could remember the exact words.
Anyway, I think Charlie's
telling us to just do it.
Ha... what do you make of it?
Somehow, I don't think
Charlie Parker'd be quoting Goethe.
Come on, it's just a dream I had.
Lighten up.
I have a feeling that dream's gonna
suck up our last 5,000 Woolongs.
I'm really sorry to mention this...
No smoking in here.
You better not play here.
Your eyes are too sharp.
They'll kick us out
if you win too much.
Thanks, Mom.
But if you didn't want me to win,
then you shouldn't have
brought me here.
Say your prayers.
Thanks for the tip.
Mm-hmm!
Queen makes 21.
Oh, that's just fine.
You mind if I join the game?
He's the one.
That's 21.
The target will sit at your blackjack
table and lose all of his money.
'Course, you'll use your skills
to help him with that.
And he'll give you
his last chip as a tip.
A token for his lovely dealer.
That's great. What about it?
Put that chip in my hands, and all those
ugly debts of yours will disappear.
The final hand.
What a shame. Appears I'm not skillful,
and I'm not lucky either.
- Then what are you?
- I seem to be very generous.
Another blackjack.
You cleaned me out.
All but this one chip.
Think I'll keep it as a souvenir.
Hey, wait! Hey!
Come back here!
- What's going on?
- She hasn't taken all of his money yet.
Hey, you! What happened
to your generosity?
- You're messing up the whole plan.
- Huh?
Don't play stupid, you're supposed
to give me that last chip.
You're pretty brash.
You cheated the whole game,
and I didn't say a word.
- Did you hear that?
- Cheating!
- No wonder I'm broke!
- Unbelievable!
Just give me the damn chip.
Can you come with me
to the office, sir?
- We have some questions.
- Like what?
Bad move.
You punk!
Come on, guys.
I like the fitness program here.
It's a good workout.
Okay, showtime.
Looks like we got a problem.
Got another fight.
Ooh, a fight, huh?
Oh, Spike...
Yes!
- Jet!
- I told you not to win too much.
That's not it.
We gotta split fast! Come on!
I haven't cashed these in yet! Hey!
He doesn't have it.
That chip he was carrying is a fake.
Neither you nor your boss were
told why we cooked up this plan,
but there's a reason,
and that chip is crucial.
If it falls into police hands...
we're finished.
Boss, we still can't find the girl.
Track her down.
Put a price on her pretty head.
Wait a minute,
I brought you guys back here,
I should get a reward for that!
Why are you locking me up?!
Stupid dog.
My dog thinks you smell like money,
and I have the very same impression.
Well, get over it.
Hey, Jet, how much did
you win on those slots?
It must have been 200K, minimum.
And who made you
lose the whole pile?
Hmm...
200K is chump change.
It's nothing compared
to what I've lost.
It's peanuts! And you're
blaming the wrong person!
Right... your little zipcraft
should sell for at least 400K.
You brought this on yourselves.
If you'd given me that chip,
- there'd have been no problem.
- Chip?
Yeah, chip. Are you deaf?
Ew, that's disgusting.
Gordon'll pay a fortune for that,
more than your little brain can imagine.
So why don't we call him.
What do you say?
I don't know anyone named Gordon.
And even if I did,
you don't really expect me to buy
that phony story, do you?
Wait a minute!
Come on, Ein. Let's go.
Where are you going?
Come back here!
- It's a chip.
- 'Course it's a chip.
Not the poker chip, dummy.
There's another chip
inside that chip. A microchip.
Hi, amigos!
You ready for some bounty info?
Big Shot, cowboys,
is coming your way!
- Whoa.
- So Punch, who's up first this week?
A pretty poker player
that's headed for the pokey.
Yo. Hey, Spike.
And the bounty's a whopping
6 million Woolongs!
Yo. Hey, Jet.
Happy hunting, all you cowboys.
I've been waiting for you.
First off, I didn't run away.
My ship was hijacked.
I believe you, of course.
Where are you?
An old fishing ship at the gate.
And they have the control chip, Gordon.
So hurry up and--
What do you want?
Well, we were thinking about you,
and we had a little change of heart.
Why lock a fine young lady
like you up in a place like this?
You creeps aren't getting
any ideas, are you?
On the contrary.
We're taking you someplace where
you'll be very well protected.
Oh, and where would that be?
The police station.
You were right, 200K is chump change
compared to your price...
Faye Valentine.
I don't believe this.
Did they put a bounty on me?
6 million fat Woolongs.
6 million?
Is that all they're offering?
Just how much money
do you owe, anyway?
Come on, have a heart,
take me anywhere but the police.
They're the only ones
who will pay your bounty.
I can't be stuck in one place
for long, it'll kill me!
- My whole family's like that.
- Yeah, right.
We're Romanies. For eons, we've
wandered the stars looking for love.
- It's our way.
- Huh?
You don't know anything, do you.
Romanies are gypsies.
And you know what we call
someone like you? A gaujo.
That means a bumpkin who
doesn't know which way is up.
"Gaujo." I like that.
The wilds are calling me!
You can't keep me locked up!
Save it for the police.
Come on, Jet.
Let's get outta here.
Fine! Look, I'm not gonna run away!
At least uncuff one hand!
I can't even go to the bathroom this way!
Man, you're a real talker, aren't you.
Spike, my friend,
that girl is money in the bank.
Yeah... no penalty for early withdrawal.
It's just like Charlie said in my dream.
"If you want to receive,
you have to give." See, Spike?
You gotta listen to your dreams.
That's how you find your dream girl.
Ow!
Who's that?
I'm not sure who you are,
and I don't really give a damn.
You have my chip,
and I want it back.
Well, I'm not sure who you are,
and I'm not giving you anything.
Are we done now?
It's just a poker chip.
It has no value to you.
Oh, we've become quite fond of it.
And we know what it's worth.
Three years ago, SIT developed a master
decryption program called Crypt Breaker.
Rumor has it that shortly
after its completion,
the programmer turned up dead,
and the program disappeared.
A program with advanced
artificial intelligence.
It can decrypt and unlock
virtually any security code.
But the catch is the program
itself is encoded.
So whoever has it needs
the key to open it.
The key to the key, so to speak.
They say the cops and
the ISSP Special Forces
have been searching every
corner of the asteroids for it.
Guess they never thought
to look in a casino.
Or even if they did, who'd ever
suspect a humble poker chip?
Not bad. You've done your homework.
I used to be with ISSP Special Forces
myself, in another lifetime.
'Course, a casino's a perfect place to
launder large sums of stolen money.
You had the right idea.
You just chose the wrong day.
Now, it's only right that we do our
civic duty and give it to the police,
since, as you pointed out,
it's worthless to us.
It's not worthless if I pay you for it.
300 million Woolongs?
Nah, I'll go easy on you.
Make it 30 million.
Cheap for a magic key, huh?
All right.
Okay. 6 million turns into 30 million.
Our little nest egg's growing.
Just be ready.
Don't get caught off guard.
Okey dokey.
Shh!
Stupid dog!
Sellers who want cash up front
are rare these days.
Yeah? Guess I'm just
an old-fashioned kinda guy.
Beautiful.
Now, we will both count to three.
Then we'll release the magnetic field
and move it up toward you.
At the exact same time,
you will toss the chip carefully to us.
No problem.
I'm trusting you, pal.
Confirm that we have the chip,
then destroy them.
Right.
Let's do it.
One...
Two...
Three.
Hey!
You're supposed to open the hangar!
Hey, "Gaujo."
Hello, "Romani."
- Bye.
- Don't let her go! Fire!
Shit!
Jet, get me outta here!
All right!
Sink them! Destroy all of them!
No way.
She reversed polarity
on one of the missiles!
It's coming back around!
She beat me again.
All this thing is good for
now is one bet.
Might as well use it.
We're starting from square one.
Hey, the dealer's cheating!
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
This sucks. This world's a mess.
Economic recession,
kids blowing their minds...
You been reading the paper again?
Take a look at the Bebop.
It's a bigger mess than that.
Bah, that's nothing.
Check out this news report.
Intergalactic terrorists.
They wanna blow up Ganymede.
- Huh?
- They're "environmental protectionists."
Perfect. They can get rid of
this furball you call a dog.
Next episode: "Gateway Shuffle."
Man, I'm losing it.