This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
An incident in which we could not
enter the house occurred.
It was due to a rock
that was cursed.
Our voice and letters
couldn't reach her.
As I was wondering what to do,
Takuto managed to break the curse.
For a moment,
I wasn't sure what to do.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Okay, we've arrived.
This is Hiiragi-En where today's
mini-concert will be held.
Wow...it's a great place.
What's so great about it?
Just when I finally get a chance
to go out with Takuto...
I hate being in such
an uncivilized place!
She really wanted to come here,
no matter what.
Uh! That's right.
She was raised in an institution,
wasn't she?
My, oh my...
Welcome and thank you for
coming to such a distant place.
It's a pleasure.
Thank you very much
for inviting us.
My name is Ms. Date,
the Home Director.
Everyone, let's greet Full Moon.
One, two, three...
- Hello, Full Moon!
Hello! My name is Full Moon.
It's nice to meet you all.
Eichi?
Mitsuki.
Eichi...
Mitsuki... Mitsuki!
Mitsuki!
Ms. Oshige!
Goodness!
What's the matter with you,
all in a daze like that?
It's because...
It's nothing.
Please pull yourself together.
Hey, give me this.
I'm gonna have
Full Moon autograph it.
Uh, that's—!
That belongs to Sora!
Taiki! Don't be so rough!
Your name is Taiki?
Taiki!
Don't scold Taiki!
Taiki hasn't done anything bad!
Sora.
Sora, let's go!
Okay!
I'm very sorry.
Please don't worry about it.
It's all right.
He must be a little overexcited
because Full Moon is visiting.
Yes, that's certainly true.
All of the children
are very thrilled.
Of course,
I am extremely thrilled too.
When I received this picture,
I wanted to visit, no matter what.
I see...
The child who drew that was
Sora from earlier...
Sora is a big Full Moon fan.
She watches all the TV shows
and reads all the magazines.
Wow, that makes me very happy.
Umm...
Are Sora and Taiki
brother and sister?
No, they aren't siblings...
Sora was a very shy and withdrawn child
and didn't take to anyone.
But fortunately, she's become a lot
more outgoing ever since Taiki came.
And they've become like family.
I believe the connection between those two
is even deeper than just that of family.
Mitsuki, haven't you
written it yet?
I wrote mine to Kuroda of
the Japan Soccer League.
I wrote mine to my mother.
I...
You ought to write to either
your father or mother too, Mitsuki.
But I don't have either one.
Huh! Why?
- Why?
- Yeah.
This is father...
and this is mother...
Hey...I'm passing you the ball!
What's the matter?
Umm...
This is where I live.
Welcome home!
Huh?!
I'm living here too,
starting today.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Mitsuki.
What a pretty name.
I'm home!
I'm home too!
Welcome home!
I'm home!
I'm home.
Is something the matter?
Umm...
Right now...right now...
R-Right now I'm testing
the microphone!
F-Full Moon is that delighted
about singing here!
Right?!
Y-Yes!
I see... That's wonderful...
Of course,
it's about Eichi again, right?
There's one again today...
a keyword...
Confetti, huh.
Confetti?
The stuff that was prepared
for the concert, right.
In any case, we'll be fine if
we collect every bit of paper there is.
Hey, Takuto,
you help with this too.
One of us has to stay with
her or else, right?!
Gimme a break!
Your bags which were delivered
earlier today are over here.
Taiki!
What are you doing here?
Taiki... That was your name,
wasn't it?
If you don't mind,
I'd like to talk to you?
Mitsuki!
Taiki!
Are you all right, Mitsuki?
I-I'm fine...
It doesn't hurt at all.
I apologize for his behavior.
Really, I'm fine.
Your costume's not here!
What?!
Could it be that that boy earlier on...
My goodness! I will tell him to
return it to you immediately.
There's a limit to mischief!
My apologies!
In any case, we must get it
back immediately!
Please wait!
Huh?
We don't yet know if
it's because of Taiki's mischief.
How can you say that?
But it's almost time for
the concert to start.
It'll be fine.
If worse comes to worst,
I can sing without my costume.
But...
I don't want to be suspicious
of that boy.
And even if he did take my costume,
there's probably a good reason for it.
Therefore...
All right, if you're that adamant.
Thank you, Ms.Oshige!
Kindergarten Director,
may I check the stage.
Uh, certainly.
Mitsuki, I'm going ahead of you.
Owww...
Trying too hard.
But...
Are you protecting him because
he resembles Eichi?
It's not like that.
No, maybe it is, after all.
It's a strange feeling.
I'm now Full Moon at age sixteen...
But right here...
Eichi and I from those days
long past are still right here.
Where are you going?
I thought I'd look
for your costume.
What is it?
I was just thinking that you're
a really nice person after all, Takuto!
It's not like that at all.
This is the Death Spirit's job too!
Job? It's never that.
You're always at
Mitsuki's beck and call!
I hate you, Takuto!
Gimme a break!
I tried to build
the stage like this.
Wow... How cute!
Very nice.
Kindergarten Director...
Hello.
Where did that boy go?
So it was his doing after all.
I'm getting it back.
What's going on?
Takuto hasn't come back yet.
All right, everyone.
Let's call her to the stage!
Welcome to Hiiragi Kindergarten!
- Full Moon!
Oh my goodness,
I wonder what happened?!
I'm sorry, Full Moon.
This boy turned off the power!
Taiki?!
I-I hate you!
Let go!
Hey!
Wait, Taiki!
Taiki!
I'm terribly sorry after you went
to all the trouble of visiting.
This is terrible.
As it is, the concert will
be cancelled.
Please wait.
There must be a reason
behind this.
You're still saying that?
I mean, Taiki and Sora
are that close, right?
I can't believe that Taiki
would play mischief
and get in the way of a concert
that Sora was looking forward to so much.
But even if you say that,
the fact remains that it's that kid
who created a disturbance.
It must be that after all...
Huh?
To be honest, there has
been discussion about Sora's adoption.
It is a very good situation for her.
But because Sora has been
looking forward to the concert so much,
it was decided that the adoption
would take place today after it's over.
That means that she and Taiki?
Will they be separated?
They say they simply can't
adopt both of them.
That must be very difficult
for Taiki.
Kindergarten Director!
Taiki and Sora are gone!
- Huh?!
Sora!
Where are you, Sora?!
Taiki!
Hey!
Come back!
Sora...
Taiki...
Where did those two go?!
Meroko!
Please! Please search for the two
of them from the sky!
Hey, we're not your servants!
In the first place, we're very busy
with our job as Death Spirits!
Still, please search!
I truly understand how
Taiki is feeling!
Even though he got
in the way of your concert?
You and your whimsies...
They have to go their separate
ways after the concert,
so he didn't want
the concert to end.
Taiki was desperate!
If you mean the two of them,
they're on top of the hill.
Takuto!
Got it!
On top of the hill, right!
Gimme a break.
Siding with her again!
Where are you going, Takuto?
Meroko, you come with me too!
Yes!
Mitsuki, where are you going?!
Come to think of it...
If I remember correctly,
there's a tree at the top of the hill
which they named
"Taiki and Sora's Tree"!
Hang on tight!
It's a short flight to the hill.
Okay!
I wouldn't mind holding
Takuto's hand forever!
Over there!
Taiki! Sora!
Don't come near!
I'm not letting Sora go anywhere!
I'm not going anywhere either!
I'm staying right here with Taiki!
Please believe this!
It's sad to part but there's
no such thing as forever.
The more strongly you believe
that you never want to part...
the more you will have
the chance to meet again!
How could you possibly
understand how we feel!
Won't we ever meet again?!
You will meet again.
I sing because I believe
that we will meet again.
Believe...
That you will surely meet again...
Therefore...
Even if you and Sora part,
you won't be alone, Taiki.
You will always be together
under the same sky.
The deeper your feelings,
the closer you will feel to each other.
I'm sure of that!
Taiki.
Will we really be able
to meet again?
Yes!
Sora, no matter how far apart we are,
I will never forget you.
Neither will I.
Kindergarten Director, we have
made up our minds.
Please allow us to adopt
both children.
We wouldn't possibly separate the two
of them when it would make them so sad.
Hello, Taiki!
From now on, you'll really
be brother and sister.
- Okay!
I'm so happy for them.
It's really wonderful.
I'm returning...this...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
Is this really okay?
Huh? What about?
The confetti?!
The Manager will be mad at us!
Come, Full Moon!
Let's start the concert again.
Let's go back to Hiiragi Kindergarten!
All right!
I truly believe that
I will see you again...Eichi!
Takuto, hurry, hurry!
We're being summoned by
the Manager of the Death Spirits.
We'll catch hell for it if we're late!
Wait a sec. Is that girl gonna
be okay if we're both away?
You're such a worrywart, Takuto.
As long as we transform her,
Oshige, her manager,
will take care of whatever comes up.
But I heard her manager
has the day off today.
Yikes...
Next time on Full Moon:
"Do Your Best, Deputy Manager!"
- Don't miss it!