Girls!
Yui!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Who is she?
She's Twilight.
Don't worry.
She's... Towa now.
We'll explain later.
For now, let's all rest.
Oh, Princess Twilight!
Let it go, 'kay?
Why, you—
Back to what matters...
where did Lady Dyspear go?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
The Flames of Hope!
Her Name is Cure Scarlet!
Kanata...
Oh, not again...
Don't be so hard on yourself, Towa.
But Brother...
Whenever you fall, just pick yourself up again.
That's the path to becoming a Grand Princess.
I know that full well, but...
I want to become skilled enough to play this song with you!
Towa...
Now, let me try again...
Brother...
This melody!
Towa...
Why do you know that song?
Ah, Madame Siamour taught me!
She said Kanata used to play it.
Kanata even told me how often you two practiced together!
Oh, and this...
belongs to you.
Isn't that... my brother's violin?
Yeah!
I think it's better off in your hands than mine.
Oh yeah, how about we play tog—
Please, stop!
Huh?
I can't bear... to look at that anymore.
And do you know why?
Because to you, it stands for a dream...
that will never come to pass.
Dy—
Dyspear!
H-How?!
Did you really think you could elude me so easily?
Twilight.
Return to me while you still can.
I shall not!
Furthermore, I am no longer Twilight!
But who would wear such a dress...
other than the princess of Dysdark?
Th-This was your do—
You won't call me "Mother" anymore?
Indeed, it was all my own doing.
But the fact remains.
Hope Kingdom hangs on the brink of despair, and your brother...
K-Kanata's totally fine!
Even though I now stand before you?
N-No...
Towa!
Reality is cruel.
And nothing you do...
will bring him back.
If it had to end this way...
you'd have been better served by staying as my daughter.
No...
Your dream ceased to be long ago.
From the very moment you set foot inside my forest.
Now be a good girl...
Come to me... and despair!
No!
Kanata's violin!
What's that?
Towa!
Haruharu!
What's going on?
Towa's inside that!
Such wondrous despair could only be Twilight's.
At least her final act will serve me well.
D-Dyspear!
Final act?
When she is drained of despair, she shall wither away.
No!
Now...
perish!
Guess we're doing it the hard way!
Indeed.
Stay back, you two.
We'll fight.
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Witch of Woe, Dyspear!
Do prepare yourself!
Amusing.
Short style!
So that's all you're made of.
Girls!
Her strength is overwhelming!
And she's getting powered up by that girl's despair to boot!
So...
what do we do?
We save her.
No matter how bleak the odds...
I must save Towa!
Take care of Towa.
But how?
That's it!
That song is the key!
It might be able to save Towa from despair once more!
Sounds like...
that's our only shot.
Go ahead, Flora.
Go and save Towa!
I will!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Frozen Ripple!
Precure!
Full Moon Humming!
So it's Twilight they're after...
Precure!
Mermaid Ripple!
What?!
Bubble Ripple!
Twinkle Humming!
Lys Tourbillon!
Ouch!
Towa!
Not that I think you have any chance of success...
but I've had enough of your mischief,
you children!
Looks like this is it.
The moment of truth.
Stop.
I don't want to hear it.
If I hear it, I'll remember...
my brother, Hope Kingdom, and...
my crimes.
Don't talk like that.
Let's get out of here first.
And do what?
There's no future for one who despaired and transgressed such as I.
I've no home...
and no dream.
Becoming a Grand Princess...
Is possible!
If you wish from the bottom of your heart, your dream is certain to come true.
That's...
what Kanata taught me.
My... brother...
Kanata said his dream was to play the violin with you once more.
And I want to make that dream happen!
So please...
lift your chin up once again!
Brother...
Flora...
I'm scared...
Don't worry.
It's all right!
No matter how many times you fall,
just pick yourself up again.
Whenever you fall, just pick yourself up again.
I know that full well.
Now, let me try again...
A violin?
The two melodies are harmonizing?
They were halves of the same song!
The despair... is vanishing?
Don't forget, Towa.
No matter how hard your path becomes,
you mustn't give up.
Being the light of hope that shines upon peoples' dreams...
is what it means to be a Grand Princess.
Yes, I understand.
I understand, Brother...
Twilight...
Curse you...
How did you escape?
I chose...
to never despair again!
Impudence!
Towa!
The crimes I've committed can never be undone...
But I'll wish from the bottom of my heart...
to live with my crimes!
To bear this burden and strive once more...
to become a Grand Princess!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
Princess Engage?
She's really...
a Precure?
You dare mock me,
Twilight?!
What is this power?
That which expels the dark and shines upon dreams...
The Flame of Hope!
Until the day comes where I can reclaim my brother and Hope Kingdom...
Dyspear! I shall battle you!
Now!
Prepare yourself at once!
Is that...
Brother?
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
This power...
Twiliiiiiight!
Adieu.
The fourth princess, huh?
Where's Dyspear?
Such a strike wouldn't defeat her.
She merely retreated.
Cure Flora.
My brother is still alive somewhere.
Really?
I can feel it through this violin.
So... you'll meet again!
Yes, I'm certain!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
We're taking Towa on a tour of Dreamy Shore!
We'll dine and shop!
Ooh, this'd look great on you.
I mustn't. Until I reclaim my kingdom, I cannot allow myself such festivities.
Don't be like that! Let's all have fun together!
Go! Princess Precure:
Together Forever!
The Four of Us Are Princess Precures!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hokkaido - Miyu (Age 7)
Tokyo - Haruka (Age 10)