Master, another cup of coffee over here.
Um, the truth is, I...
I have a favor to ask of you, Oreki-san!
Huh?
Ah...
A favor?
Yes.
Normally, this would be
my own personal matter,
so I don't really have any
business asking you for this...
So will you please hear me out first?
Well, as long as I'm just listening...
Okay.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
I had an uncle named Sekitani Jun...
The Circumstances of the Classic Lit Club's Scion
and I want you to help me remember
what it was that I heard from my uncle.
I'm not really following.
Ah, I'm sorry,
I'm getting ahead of myself.
I'll take you through this step by step.
As it happens, ever since my uncle
went to India seven years ago,
he has been missing.
Japanese National Missing
Back when I was a little girl,
I was quite attached to this uncle.
He would always answer my questions,
no matter how absurd they were,
and it was as though there
was nothing he didn't know.
When I was in kindergarten,
I found out that my uncle
was in the Classic Lit Club,
so I became interested in it.
I think it was because
the name reminded me
of the vinegar kelp that we always had at home.
sukonbu: 'vinegar kelp'
Kotenbu: 'Classic Lit
Club'
Is that a joke?
One day, I asked my uncle about something
having to do with the Classic Lit Club.
That was the only time he was
reluctant to answer, for some reason.
Reluctant?
Yes. I threw quite a tantrum,
and finally, my uncle answered me...
but when I heard the answer, I...
You what?
I cried. Whether I was scared,
or I was sad, I started bawling.
You cried.
What's more, I startled my mom,
and she came dashing in,
but my uncle didn't do anything
to try to comfort me.
The shock of what happened
back then was so great
that I don't remember anything else.
But once I got into middle school,
I started growing curious about it.
Why did my uncle shy away from answering?
Why didn't he try to console me?
I've tried to do everything
I could since then.
I've tried everything in my power
to contact the Sekitani family,
from whom we are now estranged.
But no matter what I do, I can't remember!
That's why, when I enrolled
at Kamiyama High School.
I figured that the Classic Lit Club
was my last hope.
And that's what your "personal matter" is.
However, I didn't realize that the Classic Lit
Club was on the verge of being closed down.
When I asked in the faculty room,
there weren't any teachers there who
remembered my uncle from 45 years ago.
So, why is it that you're
now turning to me for help?
Well, it's...
It's because you seem like you might
conclude something that I never imagined!
Like you did with the lock, and the book,
and that recruitment note, too!
Knowing you, Oreki-san,
I'm sure you will be able to
lead me to my answer!
I don't want you giving me too
much credit. That stuff was just luck.
Then please let me rely on that luck!
I don't feel like it.
For Chitanda, this is a question which,
not to lay it on too thick,
could affect her entire outlook on life.
And she wants an energy
conservationist like me
to take on even the least bit of
that kind of responsibility?
She must be joking.
Why are you only asking me?
Surely there are others you could turn to.
You could use strength
in numbers to tackle this.
Why don't you ask some
of your friends, too?
Oreki-san, I'm not one to go
around blabbing about my past.
This is not something that I can
talk about with just anyone.
Sorry.
I know I'm asking for quite a lot.
I know that I shouldn't be dragging you
into my memories, too. It's just,
while you may be a lot less
personable than my uncle,
you also answered me.
Well excuse me for not being personable.
Perhaps I saw my uncle when
I looked at you, Oreki-san.
High school goes on for three years.
You can take your time
and search during that time.
I want to remember what my uncle
said before he passes away.
Passes away?
Yes. If it's unknown if someone
is alive or dead for seven years,
I understand that they can
be declared legally dead.
Is that right?
My uncle's family intends to put
this matter to rest at some point.
They say they're going to hold
a funeral, too... at least a small one.
That's why... That's why I want to have
what my uncle told me in my heart...
when I'm at his funeral.
Forgive me.
Hotaro,
I mean, you don't have anything
else you want to do, right?
I'm not going to claim
any responsibility over you.
As such, I'm not saying that
I agree to your request.
But I will keep some mental notes
about what you've told me,
and if I come across anything
that might offer any hints,
I'll be sure to tell you.
If you have any trouble with
my explanation, I'll give you a hand.
Okay.
If you'll agree to that,
then I'll help you.
Thank you very much. I greatly
look forward to your help.
Yeah.
High school life being what it is,
things are never all rosy.
Regular examinations, for instance.
Midterm tests have begun
at Kamiyama High School.
During the testing period,
all club activities are suspended.
Naturally, that goes for
the Classic Lit Club, too,
but we normally don't do anything anyhow,
Library
so honestly, there's not much difference.
So you'd think it would be
okay to carry on as always,
but since the keys weren't being
circulated, there was nothing we could do.
1st Term Midterm Schedule
1st Term Midterm Test
Day 2 2nd Period
Math I
1st Term Midterm Test
Day 3 2nd Period
World History B
1st Term Midterm Test
Day 4 2nd Period
Integrated Science
Okay, that's all!
Whew...
It's over.
1st Term Midterm Schedule
Midterm tests are done.
That's a relief.
"Greetings.
I am currently in Istanbul.
I goofed up a little bit,
and I'm stuck here in
the Japanese consulate,
so I haven't seen inside the city yet."
What did you do, Sis?
"This trip has been fun.
I'm sure that ten years from now,
I won't regret spending this time."
"By the way, how's the Classic Lit Club?
Have any more members?
Anyhow, there's something worrying me,
so I thought I'd write you.
Are you planning to make an anthology?"
"The Classic Lit Club entered an anthology
each year for the culture festival.
Are you still doing that? If you are,
I thought that you might
not know how to make one,
since the Classic Lit Club
anthologies aren't in the library.
You have to look in the club room.
There's an unused chemical locker there,
and the back-number anthologies
are inside. It's not locked.
Okay, once I reach Pristina,
I'll give you a call.
Sincerely, Oreki Tomoe."
A chemical locker?
This timing is too good to be true.
Shouman ('The Greening')
When nature
waxeth full, and limbs and leaves grow lush
Hyouka
Earth Science Prep Room
Really?!
Really. I even brought the letter with me.
So that's it. The chemical locker, huh?
It isn't here.
Ah, now that you mention it,
I didn't see one.
S-So where are the anthologies?
Where are the anthologies?!
Chi-chan, calm down, calm down!
"Chi-chan"?
Chitanda, the letter just said
the chemical locker in the club room.
Sis graduated from here two years ago.
In the meantime, the club room has changed.
I get it. So that's what happened.
So then, Oreki, do you know
where it was two years ago?
I already asked the adviser.
It was the Biology prep room.
Oh? That's unusually
well-prepared of you, isn't it?
Just increasing our efficiency.
You're pumped about this, huh?
No, I'm not. I don't
generally get "pumped."
Well, let's get going!
Oh, come to think of it,
where's Fukube-san?
Ah, Handicrafts Club.
He said something about getting
a head start on the summer fashion scene.
Oreki-san!
Biology Prep Room
Huh? It won't open.
Is there anyone in there?
Hey, sorry about that.
I had the door locked. Are you here
to join the Wall Newspaper Club?
No, it's not that. Um, this is the
Wall Newspaper Club room, then?
Yeah, it is.
What is that smell, cologne?
No, air freshener?
So, is there something I can do for you?
Um, I am Chitanda Eru,
the Classic Lit Club president.
You're Togaito-senpai,
from Class 3-E, right?
How did you know my name?
I saw you at the
Manninbashi home last year.
The Manninbashi home? Hold on,
you wouldn't happen to be of
the Kanda Chitandas, would you?
Yes. Thank you for all
you do for my father.
Er, no, I should thank you.
So, you're a Chitanda...
Why is he so distracted?
So, what did you need?
Right, actually, we heard that
the back-number issues
of the Classic Lit Club's anthologies
are stored here in the Biology prep room.
This used to be
the Classic Lit Club room, right?
Biology Prep Room
Uh, y-yeah. It was back
when I was a 1st-year.
Then... Then do you know
about the anthologies?!
N-No, I don't.
Is that right? Thank you very much.
Don't leave!
Um, excuse me, but they're
supposedly in here.
Please let us look.
Sorry, but I already said
they weren't here.
Oh, no...
Well, let's be going.
Whoa!
Don't you think something's up here?
I do.
Then don't just leave!
Well, sorry I can't help you.
Try somewhere else.
But we followed a trail that
shows that they're here!
If they're not here, then we'll
have to search the whole school!
The whole school?
You've gotta be kidding.
We just need a few moments!
Please let us see inside!
I'm asking, too.
I don't want to let any
non-club members in.
But, Senpai, before this was a club room,
it was a classroom, right?
Who are you?
Classic Lit Club member, Ibara Mayaka.
All right. Fine, go ahead and look.
But don't tear the place up too much.
Kami High Monthly Newsletter Issue 496
Where are your other club members?
Oh, they're off today.
I was brainstorming ideas
for the June issue.
It's called the "Kami High Monthly
Newsletter." It goes way back,
and we're nearing our 500th issue.
It doesn't look like it's in this room.
I guess you're right.
What do we do? Oreki...?
Senpai, when you changed club rooms,
did you all move anything out of here?
Come to think of it, we carried
a number of cardboard boxes out.
Cardboard boxes, you say?
Yeah.
Which means...
But then, getting our hands on it
is a somewhat difficult problem.
Maybe I can trip him up here.
I'm sorry, but there are
so many things in this room,
and it would take a lot of
trouble to search them all.
I'd like to get the adviser's help
to search everything top to bottom.
Would that be okay?
No, you can't. I told you I didn't
want you tearing everything up.
But if they aren't here, we don't
have any other leads on them!
We will be responsible for putting
everything back, so please...
No, I told you!
But...
I'm busy in here!
Don't give me any
"top-to-bottom search" business!
This is not your club room!
Got it?! Now get out!
Bingo.
Senpai, we're just interested in
what's inside a chemical locker.
You're what?!
The anthologies should be inside it.
As long as we have those,
we won't have to trouble you
over anything else.
By the way, we have an errand
to go run at the library.
After we leave, if you happen
to find the anthologies,
would you mind leaving them in the
Earth Science prep room for us?
The door is unlocked.
A-Are you...
Are you saying I...?
Saying you what?
All right. If I find them,
that's what I'll do.
Please do.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, 1st-year!
I never caught your name.
Oreki Hotaro.
I am sorry it came to this.
Hey, Oreki,
why are we waiting out here like this?
We're conserving energy.
What does that mean?
By the way, Chitanda, in what regard
is the Togaito family famous?
Let's see... They have influence
over secondary education...
Their family has a number of
people in educational positions.
That would explain it.
Five minutes have passed.
We should be getting back now.
Earth Science Prep Room
Oh, there they are.
The anthologies.
Hyouka
Hold on, Oreki! How did you do this?!
Did you know something?!
Oh, just a little intimidation.
Intimidation?
Yeah. Ibara, can you keep a secret?
What? If you tell me not to
say anything, then I won't.
Okay.
Well, first off,
when Togaito left the room,
he was clearly acting wary about us.
That's true.
What about inside the room?
The window was open,
and the fan was running,
but the way it was pointing, the paper
on the table was being blown around.
He wanted to air the place out, right?
That's right. So, why was he
so keen to ventilate the room?
To go even further,
why did he lock himself inside,
and even place infrared sensors outside?
J-Just a minute!
What do you mean, infrared sensors?
Yeah. There were small, strange boxes
on either side of the hallway.
Supposing that thing with the antenna
on it inside the room was a receiver,
if someone were to pass by there,
it was rigged to set off an alarm.
I'm surprised you would
know something like that.
Well, I was just inferring
from the situation.
The question is, why would
he take such precautions,
and hurry to air out the room
when someone came too close?
To get rid of a smell?
That's a reasonable guess.
He also had the smell of
air freshener spray at work.
So, for what odor would he go to
such lengths to make sure no one smelled?
Tobacco.
If he's a member of a famous
family in academic circles,
it would mean that he couldn't
be found doing anything illegal,
no matter what it took.
That makes sense.
And, if Chitanda hadn't had her cold,
she would have noticed the
smell at her first breath.
But hold on! Where did the
anthologies end up being?
Inside the chemical locker, duh.
Oreki...!
I-I'm not trying to pull your chain.
The chemical locker had to be
under the makeshift table.
He probably hid his cigarettes
and lighter in there, too.
That's why, when I asked to
search the room with the adviser,
Togaito panicked the way he did.
Hmm?
You really are weird.
How can you say that to
someone so typically ordinary?
Guys!
Heh-heh, sunflower!
Satoshi, we found the
back-number anthologies.
Huh? Oh, you're right.
Huh, so this is what they're like.
When you go all the way back 40 years,
they really have that hand-made feel
about them. What's the matter, Chitanda?
That's because they were
printed on a Ditto machine.
Or more precisely, it's called
mimeograph printing,
and it was invented during the
Meiji period. What's the matter?
They didn't have copy machines
in schools during the 1970s, after all.
Oreki-san...
See? They used copiers for these.
Come here...
What issue is that?
It's this.
Hyouka
Hyouka.
Issue 2
Issue 2.
This is what I found back then.
I took it to my uncle,
and asked him what it was.
Do you remember?
Please look inside here.
This has something about my uncle inside.
Something happened here,
45 years ago, in the Classic Lit Club.
"This year, once again,
culture festival time has come.
It has been a year since
Sekitani-senpai left.
In this last year, he has gone
from being a hero to a legend.
The conflicts, the sacrifices,
and even his smile
are all being swept away
to the far reaches of time.
And it is for the best.
They should not be remembered.
For none of that is to be
found in a heroic tale.
All of the subjectiveness is falling away,
as it becomes a classic in the distance
of historical perspective.
Someday, we in the present
will also become classics
to someone in the future.
October 13, 1968, Koriyama Yoko."
The "last year" they mention
in here would be 45 years ago now.
Which means that the Classic Lit Club's
Sekitani-senpai must be my uncle.
Sekitani-senpai
The answer that my uncle gave to me
had to do with the Classic Lit Club.
Then everything should be fine now.
But I still can't remember. It's so...
It's so close, too!
What was it that my uncle
told me that day?
What exactly happened
to my uncle 45 years ago?!
You just have to look into it.
But it says that it
shouldn't be remembered.
If I look into it,
it might prove unfortunate.
There are some truths that are
better off forgotten, right?
Even if they're 45 years in the past?
Am I wrong?
Yes, you are. It's written
right here, isn't it?
All of it is becoming a classic
in the distance of historical perspective.
Meaning there's a statute of limitations.
Okay.
Besides, when I say look into it,
Issue 2 here talks about "last year,"
so you just have to check out the
first issue... Hey, what is this?!
The first issue is the
only one we're missing!
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "The Classic Lit
Club's Glorious Days of Yore."
The Classic Lit Club's Glorious Days of Yore