Ta-Tama?!
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
Tama...
Tama-chan...
Why?!
So that's how it is.
Tama...
I'm so happy you're okay.
Tama!
But why is she here?
I'm asking myself the same thing, but...
how come Ulith is a Selector now?
Isn't she supposed to be
making your wish come true?
In a manner of speaking, my wish has already been fulfilled.
However...
Then what reason does she have to battle?
You know something, don't you?!
You were lying about Tama...
No, I'm surprised as well.
It's the truth.
Such a tasteless game... that's just like her.
Tama, you poor thing.
You must be scared.
You'll just be hurt again.
The first turn is mine.
Grow.
Battle start!
Please go easy on us, if you would.
Tama! Don't!
Can you please not speak to her?
Tama is my LRIG.
Wish Crisis!
Sheesh, that was strong!
It's happening? It's really happening now?!
Has my rival made her appearance?!
All righty, this is getting me going!
That's no reason to celebrate!
Chorizo In The Fantasy!
Use the proper name of the move!
Cloth Crush Flash!
It wasn't very effective!
Seriously?!
Ow ow ow!
The fight's so one-sided...
At this rate, Chiyori's going to lose.
Tama...
Stop, Tama!
Ruu...
There's no need to listen to her.
She threw you away, after all.
N-No! Ruu was—
Get Bound.
No...
Sh-She's coming!
It seems that Tama is doing fine without you.
She seems to be having fun, too.
She hasn't changed from the days when she still was your LRIG.
Tama...
But I'm different.
You must know, Ruu,
that you're the only one for me.
No...
Tama, you're not having fun, are you?
Eldora. Grow! I'm calling up Kozame!
Ruu... I'm sorry.
Tama.
Tama was a bad girl.
That's why I had to go bye-bye, isn't it.
Baroque Defense.
Sh-Shiira!
Attack!
...or maybe not.
Oh come on, just do it!
Are you even paying attention to her card's effects?!
This isn't fun.
Why?
Battling was so much fun for me.
I loved doing it with Ruu!
Is it because I'm with Ulith now?
Salvage!
N-No!
Tama's not having fun battling?
Tama...
Sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Tama!
It's true, I really thought I'd never return back when I battled Iona-san!
I thought I was about to become a LRIG.
And I believed that'd be okay if it
meant saving you, Yuzuki, Hitoe,
and all the other girls who turned into LRIGs!
But I was wrong.
Ruuko...
I was lonely!
I was lonely without you, Tama!
I was... lonely, too.
It's my fault.
Everything happened because I didn't tell you how I really felt!
It's all because I made you worry, Tama!
I'm sorry...
I should have talked more with you, Tama.
I should have made sure you understood me!
Because you're my...
You're my precious friend!
Ruuko...
"Friend"...
So why the heck are you crying now?
Because Tama and Ruu were friends!
And now they're facing each other as enemies!
That's so cliché!
Of course I'd cry... I absolutely adore clichés!
I could live off clichés alone for months on end...
I really don't think this is the time to go off on a tangent like this!
What?
Huh?
The next attack will seal our loss.
And then...
Ruu...
Tama.
You're such a bad girl.
Doing it with me, and still
thinking of someone else...
What a turn-off.
Let's finish this.
Arch Aura!
Tama?
Tama...
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Give me back Tama!
If you want her back,
you'll have to battle against me.
No!
Ruu, you can't battle! Never!
I can't wait for my battle against you...
and you, Iona.
See you again, scum.
Tama!
Ruu...
Ruuko, are you alright?
Yup, I'm fine.
Now I know that Tama is okay and that she feels the same way I do.
Hitoe, Yuzuki, sorry I made you two worry!
Now those are some nice plot twists!
A friendship torn apart and the appearance of a rival!
I'm burning up with excitement!
Chiyori-san?
Wait, you're still here?
It's just all so really, really cool!
Forget about that...
Listen, you!
We warned you so much about not battling any more.
Don't you care about what's going to happen to Chiyori?
Now, now. I did talk it through with her in depth, you know?
I really did, but...
Let's see...
There it is!
Lookie here!
What's that?
Chorizo de Ibérico Mark 2!
Huh?
"Chorizo"... as in the sausage?
Wrooong!
It's my name for when I become a LRIG!
You see? All it did was make her even more excited.
But... you already lost to me.
And you lost to Ulith.
So you've lost twice already?
That's bad!
But I also already won three times!
My wish could come true any moment!
But if you lose one more time,
your wish is going to be reversed!
The heroine in the novel loses twice too,
but then she ends up beating her rival!
And then, before she knows it,
she finds herself at White Garden...
"White... Garden"?
Yup! A hyper-dimensional white space!
White?
Could it be...
that white room I visited when I became a LRIG?
Hey, that room gets mentioned in the novel?!
Man, I even gave you a copy!
So you didn't read it, huh?
Ah, well... no, not really...
What's this about?
Chiyori-san, do you mind letting us read that novel?
"WIXOSS: The Wings of Lamentation Mark the Dream of the Ruined Country"
Futase Fumio
Futase Fumio...
In a not too distant future,
mysterious beings by the name of "LRIG" appear all over the world.
They cross paths with young girls who all hold special powers
and become the manifestation of their wishes.
In order for a wish to come true, they need to defeat other LRIGs
and gather WIXOSS factors from them.
A young girl meets a LRIG and is drawn into the battle for wishes.
Finally, after she wins all the battles that await her,
she finds herself lost in White Garden, the labyrinth of time.
White Garden must be the room with the white windows, right?
They don't use the word "Selector,"
but everything else is identical.
It's just really romanticized...
There! You've finally gotten to her part!
Cocoon, the Dark Queen of Atonement!
Yoink!
She's the ruler of White Garden!
The almighty being in full control of all WIXOSS battles!
So she's like the final boss or something?
I can't deal with this cliffhanger...
I want more! Hurry and give me more!
Uhm...
"Cocoon"...
Isn't that the English word for Mayu?
Mayu!
A white room, and now Mayu...
That must...
That must be it!
The Empty Flame Chants the Forgotten Victory Song
The author must know something.
Futase Fumio
Article
Talk
Futase Fumio
Futase Fumio is a Japanese author.
Her residence is in Tokyo.
Contents
1. History
2. Personal
3. Publications
4. External links
History
Futase Fumio was always an avid reader, and shortly after entering high school began writing in earnest.
Although the content of her work was written based on her own preferences, the web release of her novel
caught the attention of Full Moon Books and she was contacted by an editor to write professionally.
After several revisions, she finally debuted with "WIXOSS: The Wings of Lamentation Mark the Dream of the Ruined
Country" (it wasn't originally written to become a series, but due to the high sales despite being from a new author
a continuation was confirmed). Although the second book was highly rated, the continuation has yet to be released.
Personal
"Futase Fumio" is thought to be a penname, although the specifics are still unknown.
Futase's picture, age, gender, and other information are completely private.
Futase Fumio.
It says here that it was first
published the on the Internet.
It was just written for fun, but it caught a publisher's attention.
Then the first volume got published...
But then the series went on hiatus after the second?
That's what it says.
Do you think they're a Selector?
But why would they romanticize it this much?
If they know about the white room,
then they should know what happens if you keep on battling, too.
I want to meet this person.
We could probably find out a lot from them.
Like what?
About Mayu... and about Tama.
Yuzuki, you said something about how Tama could be a "special girl," right?
Not all Eternal Girls are normal girls.
Among them may be special girls who hold mysterious powers.
I'm not sure, but...
I feel like I know how to make the LRIGs return to normal.
That's what Tama told us.
I want to save Tama.
I want to save everyone!
Come to think of it, where's Chiyori-san?
Gyaaa!
And that was the sixth win in a row for Grandma.
Nooo... you're too strong...
If you don't try harder, you're not going to get any.
Could you be the Blood Sorceress?! The WIXOSS Danger Zone?
Queen of Innocence!
Who knows?
I might tell you if you win, Chiyori-chan.
Oh,
do you two want to join us?
Uhm... maybe later.
Ruuko
Ah, look!
That's the website of the novel.
It's still online.
"Dear Futase Fumio,
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
Dear Futase Fumio,
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are
aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe.
please excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We've read your novels,
and we'll be upfront with you.
We're Selectors.
It is our belief that you are aware of them as well.
If so, please grant us an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruuko and Uemura Hitoe."
Does that sound about right?
Yup.
Send
See ya laters!
We'll let you know when we get a reply!
Be sure to come with us, okay?
Absolutely!
Will we get a reply, though?
There're a lot of things we don't know.
Like how Akira-san and Ulith-san became Selectors recently.
It can't be a coincidence that
Tama became Ulith's LRIG, right?
And Yuzuki ended up with me, too.
Mayu...
Did she do this?
Yeah, she must have!
But why? Why would she do such a thing?
I know, right? It's like she's trying to throw us into disarray.
What are you saying?
Why are you girls battling at all?
You're simply being misled by her incomprehensible rules.
She's playing with you all.
Selectors, LRIGs... they're nothing but her dolls.
To her, it's like she's playing with dolls.
Playing with dolls?
She greatly enjoys pitting
her dolls up against each other.
That's all there is to it.
If that's true...
Then I can never forgive her!
I'll be going now.
Okay.
H-Hey, you know...
A lot's happened today, but...
I'm really happy you got to see Tama again.
Tama's at her best when she's by your side, Ruuko.
Yeah...
Let's do our best so Tama-chan can return to you as soon as possible.
Hitoe...
Yuzuki...
Thank you!
See you!
Good night!
Good night.
How disgusting.
These two are making me feel nauseous.
They disgust me.
Akira, Iona-san's here for you.
How has Akira-san been doing?
I really have to thank you for
helping her get back on track.
Don't mention it.
Hello, Akira?
Oh, that girl... But please, come on in.
Excuse me.
Would you help me again?
Of course...
I'll do anything...
You're adorable,
Akira.
It's truly disgusting...
That smile.
Regarding Selectors
Futase Fumio
This is where Futase Fumio-sensei lives?
That's what it says in the e-mail...
I... I can't take this!
Nervous! Nervous! I'm su-per-ner-vous!
Sorry! My girl's actually quite shy around strangers!
Oh gosh, oh boy, oh gosh, oh boy...
Uhm... this is Kominato.
I sent you an e-mail yesterday.
U-Uhm...
Uhm, excuse me.
Hello...?
What now?
White room...
Mayu...
Large windows...
White room...
MAYU
Mayu...
Large windows...
White room...
Uhm...
Mayu...
Large windows...
Are you Futase Fumio-sensei?
Yes.
I'm Futase Fumio.
That
Delusion
Is
Raging
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
Don't you know more than what's written in the novels?
I'll tell you everything I know
if you can defeat me in battle.
How much do you think she knows?
What's with that form?
This
Irritation
Is
Disillusionment
This irritation is disillusionment.