9th Street
“Charge! Clash of the Buytans”
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
People arbitrarily assign value to things and then treasure them.
But as time passes, these objects become vessels for lost souls,
and become what we call “artificial spirits”.
This is a tale of people under the spell of such beings.
A man sold his pocket watch, and bought a brush for his wife.
The wife sold her beautiful hair to buy her husband a chain for his pocket watch.
What a sweet story.
I wish my work here was that exciting.
Those kinds of things only happen in books, I guess.
Welcome.
I'd like to sell this, please.
This is a beautiful vase.
But I can't afford to pay that much for it.
Any price is fine.
I'd be more than happy to just get rid of it.
Thanks for your business!
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Price is Negotiable
Hey, that's—
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Pardon me, but did my wife sell a vase to you?
I did purchase one from a woman yesterday.
I knew it! How dare she sell off MY collection!
How much is it? I'll pay whatever you ask!
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Thanks for your business!
Sorry to trouble you, but would you please take this off my hands again?
Sure, thanks a bunch.
Excuse me! Please sell me that vase!
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
'Preciate it!
I'd like to sell this!
Sure thing.
I'll take it!
You got it.
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
I can't take this anymore!
Please see to it that this vase is sold far, far away!
HEY!
D-Dear!
Quit screwing with my collection!
Quit obsessing over this piece of crap!
It's a free country, dammit!
How much money have you wasted on this!?
It's the money I'VE earned!
Can't you try so see things my way!?
No! I'm not backing down!
What do you love more, me or this stupid vase!?
Anyway, I'm taking this home with me!
Keep your mouth shut, woman!
Let's see, that was five round trips, so here's what you owe.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
“Clash! The Faerie vs. The Reaper”
from Vol.4 Chapter 32
It's said that everyone has their own special talent.
But there are many who go their whole lives unable to find it.
Those who do realize their gifts however, may simply be blessed with good fortune.
Sanada!
Got it!
Donkey Kong!
Is that supposed to mean me!?
Don't just make up nicknames on the spot!
Sorry, man.
Asai, you idiot! What are you doing!?
Don't make Sanada look bad!
What'cha looking at?
Oh, the boys, huh?
I wish that was our test.
So, who's winning?
Huh?
Umm, good question.
Weren't you watching the game?
Okay, nice job!
All right, next... Arashiyama!
Yes ma'am!
Ahh! Coach!
Don't stand right in front of the landing mat! That's dangerous!
Look behind you, Arashiyama.
BEHIND YOU!
Huh?
Did I warp or something?
You're not extending your left arm fully, so you can't dismount properly.
Okay, you're free to go play ping-pong.
What the heck are you doing?
Just checking to see if the space here is distorted or not.
“Careless Miss” and “Hairless Miss” sound similar.
Finished your test, Tattsun?
Yup. A perfect landing, naturally.
Ta-da! Let's play some ping-pong!
You and me?
Well, why not?
Starbucks and Star Tours sound similar.
Guess I could humor her for a bit.
Here goes!
What?
Here.
Hey—
I'm pretty good, huh?
Yup. You've got a gift.
Take that!  Man, I'm good!
You think I'm a prodigy?
Well, do ya?
I'm just going easy on... YOU!
My quick visual reflexes can easily spot the fast-approaching sphere...
However!
Whether or not I can react in time is a different matter all together.
That spike... you haven't lost your touch at all, Tatsuno.
Haribara...
There, there.
That was mean! It really hurt!
It was spherical!
The shape has nothing to do with it.
How about a match for old times' sake?
Arashiyama's not even a challenge for you.
HEY!  I was using this tab—
Unbelievable!
I never thought I'd witness a match between South Middle #3's twin aces!
OW! What the hell!?
I was also in the ping-pong club back then.
But now, I'm in the film club.
They were feared as the Faerie and Reaper of South Middle #3!
No kidding...
So what about Kon, then?
She went to the same school, right?
Futaba Kon...
It's said that the villagers froze in their tracks upon hearing the name...
What villagers!?
She-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named was a whole different beast.
The demoness of South Middle #3...
A.K.A. Satan incarnate...
or even Darth Vader...
The Sith Lord!
She had many fearsome nicknames.
Only such names could truly describe her ridiculous strength.
She's that good, huh?
Tatsuno opens with a killer serve!
Whoa! It's like the pro matches on TV!
She's good. Tatsuno's not your average player!
You wouldn’t guess she hasn’t played in over a year!
Impossible! Her biggest weakness, her footwork, has been corrected!
She's not getting tired!
Mind if I start playing seriously?
This reminds me of middle school.
I'm starting to enjoy this!
I've been going all-out from the start!
That stance!
Is she going to do it?
Do what?
There it is!
Haribara Special: The Reaper's Scythe!
Special!? Reaper's Scythe!?
Ever since one student fell and was
knocked unconscious trying to chase it,
it's been called The Reaper's Scythe...
...by me!
You just made it up!?
Now... time to die!
She returned it!
But Tattsun's lost her balance and can't recover in time!
You're mine!
I win! I've defeated Toshiko Tatsuno!
I'm gonna lose!
Sanada's watching me...
I will not...
...be defeated!
Okay, pack it up, guys!
Naito
Dentistry
My whole body aches.
So who won, anyway?
I don't really get the rules and stuff.
I lost. There's no way I could've beaten someone who still plays.
Hmm... learned something new today.
Lil' Miss Fried Chicken
When I become a genius detective,
my job will be finding out who the perp is, not catching him.
So why would I need stupid gymnastics skills?
You too, Tattsun.
If you're gonna be Sanada's wife, who cares about ping-pong?
You've been making fun of me this whole time, haven't you?
Or are you trying to console me?
Your heart is a black hole of emotion!
I've always been “good” at everything, but never “great”.
I mastered the basics of stuff like the violin and ping-pong no problem.
I could make it pretty far with almost no effort.
But then I hit a wall,
And the truly hardworking geniuses overtake me.
I'm forever doomed to be second-rate.
Go on and laugh...
I can't tell if you're tough or a coward.
It's said that everyone has their own special talent.
But there are many who go their whole lives unable to find it.
But the truly perceptive can find it where they stand out.
Did you see that match, Sanada?
Yeah.
She's in a class all her own, huh?
Shake... Shake...
They were like water balloons... her boobs.
Don't say that.
It's unbecoming.
A portrait of the sun.
Year 2, Class A. Hiroyuki Sanada.
Now, let us merely observe the sunset in silence.
Burning its shaking image...
...into our hearts.
“Collector's Frenzy”from Chapter 71
Nothing is impossible if you persevere.
Even the most difficult of endeavors.
Unrelenting quests, fueled by strong emotion, have changed the course of history...
And made dreams into reality.
People call these phenomena “miracles”.
Mori's Japanese Confections
Welcome.
I thought I'd grab a bite before I head home.
Thank you. We'll be closing the shop at the end of the month, unfortunately.
My Mother and I really loved these...
I guess the colors turn most people off from them...
They're just not selling well enough.
It can't be true! I can't imagine life without these.
I'll take every single thing in this store!
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Mori's
Rainbow Delight
This is delicious!
Hey grandpa...
What were those multi-colored snacks from Mori's?
Huh? Oh, some passing stranger gave it to me.
Did you eat one?
Nope. He only gave me one.
There's no way I'd eat something that nasty lookin'.
I've never heard of Rainbow Delights before.
Have you, grandpa?
Ah, come to think of it, didn't I see those back in the day?
Nope.
Maybe the convenience store has them.
If they do, I'll clean 'em out tomorrow.
Kameido Antiques Buy & Sell
Did you eat breakfast today, Kon?
Yeah.
You wouldn't shut up about it, so I wolfed down a
processed, fat-ladened hunk of bread this morning.
Why do you have to have such an attitude about it?
Shizuka, up early? Now that's a rare sight.
Yeah, I guess.
You girls ever heard of Rainbow Delights?
Rainbow Delights? No, I haven’t.
So it's not one of those new kids’ snacks...
What is it? Is it good?
It's really good.
It's blue, pink, and bright green...
Crunchy, but soft and chewy too.
Is it actual food?
I went to three different stores, and none of them had it.
“Love Letter” and “Predator” sound similar.
Maybe it's from one of the mom and pop places.
“Mori's”, hmm?
I wonder if I can order some.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please hang up and try a—
It hadn't expired yet either... right?
That's really strange.
Moriya's Rainbow Delights
Web
Images
Maps
Videos
News
Books
Other
Your search - Moriya's Rainbow Delights - did not match any documents.
Suggestions:
• Make sure all words are spelled correctly.
• Try different keywords.
• Try more general keywords.
• Try fewer keywords.
Rainbow Delights
Web
Images
Maps
Videos
News
Books
Other
Your search - Rainbow Delights - did not match any documents.
Suggestions:
• Make sure all words are spelled correctly.
• Try different keywords.
• Try more general keywords.
• Try fewer keywords.
C
C p
C pr
C pre
C pref
C prefe
C prefec
C prefect
C prefectu
C prefectur
C prefecture
C prefecture M
C prefecture Mi
C prefecture Mih
C prefecture Miha
C prefecture Mihas
C prefecture Mihaso
C prefecture Mihasor
C prefecture Mihasora
C prefecture Mihasora c
C prefecture Mihasora ci
C prefecture Mihasora cit
C prefecture Mihasora city
C prefecture Mihasora city s
C prefecture Mihasora city sn
C prefecture Mihasora city sna
C prefecture Mihasora city snac
C prefecture Mihasora city snack
C prefecture Mihasora city snacks
Web
Images
Maps
Videos
News
Books
Other
Your search - C prefecture Mihasora city snacks - did not match any documents.
Suggestions:
• Make sure all words are spelled correctly.
• Try different keywords.
• Try more general keywords.
• Try fewer keywords.
That's ridiculous...
There's no city by that name in C prefecture.
I've never heard of it before either.
What's going on? Why the phony address?
Some passing stranger gave it to me.
“Gave” seems like my only clue.
At the very least, this mysterious third party isn't made up.
Eel Bowl
with Miso Soup
yen
A city that doesn't exist.
An unused telephone number.
The only lead this fake packaging offers is an out-of-city zip code.
The zip code is used in C prefecture.
Guess I'll ride around the area and check all the confectioneries.
Here's your eel bowl.
Umm, excuse me...
Yes?
Would you happen to know of a confectionary called “Mori's” around here?
A candy store, or a Japanese treats store kind of place.
Don't tell me, Rainbow Delights?
You're the third person to ask me.
You're asking if it's made somewhere around these parts, aren't you?
Sorry, but I've never heard of it.
You from Tokyo, dear?
Must be something if you've come all this way for some.
Bed and Breakfast Tagame
I'm sorry for bothering you this late at night.
Not at all. I just run the inn on the side,
so it's not so strange to have guests come by around this time.
I don't have any dinner for you, though.
I ate before coming, so I'll be fine.
By the way, you wouldn't happen to be
familiar with Rainbow Delights, would you?
Hmm?
If you're still hungry, you can have this.
Here's some hot water.
Ogata Ken sounds like Kai Ken.
So there's been others who asked
about Rainbow Delights at that shop.
And both of them are from Tokyo too.
Emergency
Flashlight
I bet they had one as well.
One of those addictive little multi-colored treats...
They must have eaten one and tried to find more.
Did that man just walk around Tokyo handing them out to people?
But why would he do that?
My mind's buzzing more than it does when I'm writing.
Of all the things to be obsessed over...
Wait, am I just imagining it?
Did I really eat that?
Please Miss... right this way.
Is this...
Is this Mihasora City?
I've finally found Mihasora City!
That was close.
I almost wound up in some weird fantasy novel.
That's not it.
None of the ingredients written here turn blue or pink even if you fry or bake them.
I know that, but still...
Are you sure you didn't dream that?
You went all the way to C prefecture and nobody had it, right?
This has to be some kind of snack made with futuristic technology.
Excellent deduction, Future Frames!
I've discovered the secret behind this wrapper-ow!
Who the heck are you calling “Future Frames”!?
The expiration date only has the last 2 digits of the year, right?
So this isn't from the year 2010...
...but maybe the year 2510 instead!
It's totally possible for cities we've never heard of to spring up hundreds of years from now.
There you have it, so let's give up on trying to recreate them.
It's just not possible in our time.
I've eaten so much that my stomach hurts.
Yeah, me too.
First it's fantasy novels, and now it's sci-fi...
Mori's Japanese Confections
Time-Traveller Ryosuke Moriaki
Welcome Home
A.D. 2310
You've become the first man to successfully travel through time. How do you feel?
Hard to say. I'm still getting over the time lag.
Now that you're home, what's the first thing you want to do?
I really liked this snack called Rainbow Delights.
I could sure go for one right about now.
That long trip through sub-time gave you a craving for the common man's food, huh?
Common man's food? You've heard of it?
Time-Traveller Ryosuke Moriaki
Welcome Home
Rainbow Delights, right?
They sell 'em practically everywhere.
I've got one in my briefcase. If you want it, go right ahead.
If you're fine with just one, you can have mine.
With 300 years of determination, miracles can come about.
You conducted several experiments during your trip to the 2000's.
How did they turn out?
They were a big success.
Safety-pin sounds like Mandolin.
Welcome.
Hey, Shizuka, would you buy this please?
Sure, but you won't get much for it.
That's fine. Better than just throwing it out.
Hey, does anyone else in your family want this?
If anyone did, I wouldn't be here.
Then I don't either.
Why!?
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living for rock!
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
Living lonely, blasting my music.
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Kyou mo Kare ni wa Nasake Kokurezu
and I still have yet to tell him how I feel.
Toppuu ni Inochi wo Sasage Ashikoshi wo
Putting our lives in the hands of a tornado,
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
we train our legs by playing drums.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We're the Maids, yeah!
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Chiisai no wa Zessan Eigyou Chuu
The little one's working inside, making a profit!
Thank you very maid for coming!
Do you ever think Macaroni is just the hollow part itself?
I've never once thought that.
But that's the best part of it, don't you think?
Now that you mention it, maybe...
If you think about it, your life until now feels kinda empty too, doesn't it?
The other day, I tried making hole-less macaroni.
How'd it go?
I just ended up with thick spaghetti.
Café Seaside
Next time: 10th Street.
10th Street“The finger-pointing geriatric”
The finger-pointing geriatric.
Round and round, all sexy-like.