[YUZUKI] And yet,
she did grant my wish.
Holding up her end of this
perverse contract, I suppose.
And I became an Eternal Girl.
To repeat the cycle.
Get it now?
That's the ugly truth
behind this game!
[RUKO gasps]
[HITOE gasps]
[YUZUKI gasps]
[HITOE screams]
[YUZUKI] Hitoe!
Hitoe!
Oh my gosh! Are you okay?
[YUZUKI] Ruko!
Go get help! Call an ambulance!
But I don't have
a cell phone!
Come on, think.
[YUZUKI] Hitoe has
one! Just hurry!
What? Oh, right!
[RUKO] Yeah, nothing serious.
The doctor said
she's stable now.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, they called them.
I hope this is okay, but,
I, uh, I wanted to wait
with Hitoe a bit longer.
You know, until her
parents show up at least.
[HATSU] Sure. That's fine.
Of course you can
stay with your friend.
I'm just glad you called.
But--how are you? I'm worried.
No, don't. I'll be okay.
I'll call again if
anything else comes up.
Mm-hmm...
[YUZUKI] Why didn't
I listen to you?
[RUKO gasps]
I should've stopped
while I had the chance...
Oh, Yuzuki...
Do you know how this happened?
I think so.
I won the battle and then,
well, it was strange.
[VOICE] And now...
You become an LRIG.
[YUZUKI] Where am I?
What's... going on here?!
[VOICE] Nice to meet you.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[VOICE] Yuzuki.
Who are you?
My name is... Mayu.
That's insane.
[YUZUKI] It was like some sort
of weird initiation.
She told me all about
Selectors, LRIGs,
and how Eternal Girls work.
If you become an LRIG,
then apparently
you wake up there.
[RUKO] You think Hanayo went
through the same thing?
I would imagine so.
Mayu...
A white room...
[RUKO] Wh- Tama?
Do you know something?
My memory is
still too fuzzy.
[RUKO] So, who is
this "Mayu" girl?
I dunno, she didn't
talk about herself much.
I see...
[YUZUKI] I know
what you're thinking.
That Hanayo was tricking me
this entire time.
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA] Huh...?
She didn't mention a word
about her taking my place,
or any of that.
If what Mayu
told me is true,
she's out there living
my life right now.
All that talk about
helping me with my wish.
Figured she was laughing
at me the whole time.
Don't say that!
Well, that's what I thought.
But...
[YUZUKI] Hanayo.
How could you do this?
We were friends!
[MAYU] Don't blame her.
LRIGs are not allowed to share
the truth with their Selectors.
[YUZUKI] Why do you know
this and nobody else?
What is this place?!
What the hell are you?!
[MAYU] If this rule is broken.
If their Selector learns the
truth and refuses to battle
anymore, that LRIG will
forever lose her chance
to escape the world
inside her card.
Then you're doing it too.
You're trying to
trick poor Hitoe.
It's not that simple.
I'll try to explain.
[HITOE gasps]
Nice to meet you, Selector.
[YUZUKI] I couldn't believe it.
Hitoe became a Selector
again and I was her LRIG.
I didn't know what to do.
Should I hide the
truth from her?
Was it my job to
force her into battle?
At the very least, I knew I'd be
stuck in this card if I didn't.
But after what happened.
Let's be friends, Hitoe.
How do-- How do
you know my name?
Who are you?
[YUZUKI] Well, let's just
say I'm magic, okay?
[YUZUKI] Even though we
didn't know her for long,
I still felt like we
were good friends.
But after her wish
was corrupted,
she really did forget about us.
I'm your LRIG now,
so take good care of me!
[HITOE] LRIG? What?
[YUZUKI] For starters,
can you tell me your wish?
[HITOE] My wish...?
[YUZUKI] Yeah, if you have one,
I can make it come true.
I'm Yuzuki, by the way.
I think you and I
will be good friends.
Yu... zu... ki...
[HITOE whimpers]
[HITOE]
[YUZUKI] "I've gotta fight
my way outta here."
"Even if I have to
hurt Hitoe to do it.
I need to see Kazuki again."
That was all I could think.
Hey, don't be shy.
You must have a wish.
[HITOE] I-I don't know.
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe?
You okay? Did something happen?
Talk to me, Hitoe! Please!
[YUZUKI] I knew her wish
was already dead.
But what could I do?
This was the only
chance given to me.
I had to take it.
But then...
[YUZUKI] Just as I was starting
to think I'd have to give up,
I guess I got lucky and
something happened.
Hitoe?
[YUZUKI gasps]
[HITOE grunts in pain]
[YUZUKI] Oh my gosh.
Are you okay?
[HITOE screams]
If it hurts, why are you
putting yourself through this?!
I don't know why.
I just... feel like...
This is something important.
[HITOE] But I think,
maybe, I do have a wish.
Huh?
I wanna have friends.
And for some reason that hurts.
[YUZUKI] After all the horrible
things she went through.
All that pain and confusion.
[YUZUKI] She still asked
for the same thing.
[HITOE whimpers]
[HITOE] Can I have friends?
Can you do that...?
You have my word.
I promise I'll make
your wish come true.
[YUZUKI] How could I say no
to a crying girl, you know?
Whether it was right or not,
I guess I got caught
up in the moment.
[YUZUKI] Will Hitoe's wish
turn out like mine?
Even I can make it come true,
is it really worth the cost?
Makes me wonder if Hanayo
went through all this, too.
I wonder if she felt as
lost and hurt as I do now
And if her wish came true...
[YUZUKI cries softly]
[YUZUKI] Hanayo...
[YUZUKI sobs]
[YUZUKI] After that,
I started to rethink things.
[YUZUKI] Hey, Hitoe?
If you want your
wish to come true,
we'll have to find a battle.
Okay, I'll try...
[YUZUKI] I intentionally
had her battle you.
And then told you the
truth in front of her.
So it's not quite
what it looked like.
I was hoping she'd refuse to
fight after she heard that.
But, if she quit,
then you'd be stuck in the
card forever, wouldn't you?
That doesn't matter.
[TAMA gasps]
She's my friend.
If I have to sacrifice her, then
I might as well just disappear.
And besides, if I can't live
as Yuzuki Kurebayashi anymore.
If I can't even love
Kazuki as myself anymore,
then what's the point?
I give up...
Yuzuki...
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe?
[RUKO] Uh, hello!
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Oh, Ruko!
Where's Hitoe? Is she okay?
Uh, yeah, everything
is just fine.
Mostly, at least.
Seems like she's
calmed down now.
The doctor's with her.
You can go inside.
[HITOE'S MOTHER gasps]
[groans]
Oh, no. I'm all right.
I'm just scared...
[RUKO gasps]
Hitoe was... She was
so sweet before...
But now, I don't know
what's going on in her head.
It's terrifying...
What am I supposed to do?
What can I do?
It's like I don't even
know her anymore...
I'm at a loss...
[RUKO sighs]
Hey, Yuzuki.
Can I take you to
my place for now?
This is all my fault...
Huh?
[YUZUKI] I was the one
who made her battle.
[RUKO] Well, yeah.
But... you just wanted
to help, right?
Even though the truth was
more than Hitoe could take,
your intentions
were still noble.
[YUZUKI] Thank you, Ruko...
Ah! I just realized.
This'll be the second
time you've stayed over!
[YUZUKI] Oh, um...
[RUKO] Hm?
Actually, before we go back,
can we stop somewhere for a sec?
Is this good?
Can you see from here?
Yeah...
[LANDLADY] Well, if it
isn't Yuzuki and Kazuki.
Are ya steppin' out?
Just to the
convenience store.
[LANDLADY] Looks like we've
got snow coming, so be careful.
[HANAYO (Y)] Yes ma'am.
[KAZUKI] See you later.
Yuzuki, something
bothering you?
[KAZUKI grunts]
What's this about?
I want to be
boyfriend and girlfriend.
[KAZUKI gasps]
[RUKO gasps]
[YUZUKI whimpers]
[HANAYO (Y)]
This is the only time
we can be together as lovers.
Mom and Dad are still
upstairs watching TV.
No one from school's
here to see us.
In weather like this, if we
happen to share an umbrella,
no one will bat an eye, right?
What now?
[RUKO gasps]
Aw, isn't it beautiful, Kazuki?
Snowing, just for us.
You really are
strong, huh?
Uh?
[KAZUKI] You've been like that
ever since were little.
You always protected me.
Kept me on the right path.
I should've told you...
For my entire life,
I've loved you...
Thank you.
But I want to protect you, now.
As your brother...
...and your boyfriend.
[RUKO gasps]
[YUZUKI whimpers]
[YUZUKI] She made my wish
come true, didn't she?
Even though she took my body,
she still kept her word.
[YUZUKI cries softly]
[YUZUKI] Thank you, Hanayo.
You were my friend...
Yuzu... ki...?
[URITH] Setting your little
plan into motion, are you?
That's right.
[URITH] I wonder...
You think she'll really come?
[IONA] Oh, don't worry.
She'll come.
She's the same as me.
I suppose that's true.
And by that, I mean you both
have WIXOSS on the brain
and not much else.
Nothing personal, of course.
[URITH laughs]
[URITH] Though I wonder if two
of you might be one too many.
[YUZUKI] That doesn't matter.
She's my friend.
If I have to sacrifice her.
Then I might as
well just disappear.
[RUKO] We're all still friends.
[YUZUKI] She made my wish
come true, didn't she?
Even though she took my body,
she still kept her word.
[RUKO] If my wish
came true, then...
"My wish?"
Ugh...
Oh, Ru.
Is something the matter?
Uh, no, I'm fine,
just spacing out.
So, what are you up to
out here, Grandma?
[HATSU] Nothing exciting.
It started to snow,
so I'm trying to dry off the
potatoes I left outside.
Here, let me help.
Hey, Grandma?
[HATSU] Hm?
All my life...
I never really wanted to
be anything or do anything.
And I didn't really care
if I had friends or not.
I guess that's
not really normal,
so I can't blame
you for worrying.
But I've changed my mind now.
[HATSU] Hmm...
I made friends...
And realized I was wrong.
We had fun.
I was happy.
I wanted to, I mean, I want to
stay with them forever.
So I mean, I guess
what I'm asking is
if there's anything
I can do for them.
I'm sure you'll come up
with something on your own.
Huh?
I have faith.
You are my Ru after all.
You can do anything.
Heh. Grandma.
Now, let's see...
Guess we can't put
them back outside.
No, but maybe over there, where
they can still get some sun.
Okay!
[RUKO] Tama?
You're acting weird...
What's wrong?
I wonder if you were like
me when you were a real girl.
Bet you had all sorts
of friends, back then.
It'd be fun to find out
what kind of wish y--
[TAMA] Stop it!
I don't know, okay?
I don't remember
any of that stuff!
I'm sorry!
[TAMA] I didn't know
that other stuff either!
Not about Selectors
switching with LRIGS
or wishes or the weird room!
I wouldn't lie to you!
Please believe me, Ru!
I just wanted to battle
together, I promise!
Of course I believe you.
[TAMA] You mean it?
[RUKO] Uh-huh!
You're my friend!
We have to trust each other.
Guess you're right...
[RUKO grunts]
It sure has been
a long day, huh?
I'm going to bed!
[RUKO] Night-night, Tama.
[computer keys
clacking sporadiccaly]
[RUKO grunts softly]
Wha...?
[RUKO groans]
[GIRL 10A] Hey,
did you see this?
[GIRL 10B] Yeah, the Iona
fan event thing, right?
[RUKO] Ah...?
[GIRL 10B] But on the ad,
it said it's only for
"select" people.
[GIRL 10A] Do you have to win
a contest or something?
[GIRL 10B] It didn't seem
like it, but I dunno.
[GIRL 10C] There's no
address listed either.
[GIRL 10A] It doesn't list
anything but a contact.
[GIRL 10D] Oh yeah.
I sent them an e-mail about it,
but I didn't get a reply.
[GIRL 10C] What the heck?
[YUZUKI] Ruko!
[YUZUKI] We gotta
find that thing.
Do a search for it!
Try typing: "Iona Fan Event."
[RUKO] Uh, right.
[TAMA] What is it, Ru?
[RUKO] An Iona fan event,
just like they said.
"To those who are
forced to select."
"To those who do not
refuse to select."
Then it has hashtag
"Selector" at the bottom.
So, what do you guys
think she's trying to do?
She's calling us out.
[RUKO gasps]
[YUZUKI] She's bringing
the Selectors together.
[RUKO] It's happening
really close to here, too.
[TAMA] Is something wrong?
[HITOE] I don't want to hear it
and I have nothing
to say to you.
[RUKO] I'm sure my
plan is gonna work.
[TAMA] No! I don't want to!
[RUKO] I finally
thought of a wish.
[RUKO] Next time:
"The Summer of Dreams."