From yesterday's me to today's me.
"You will lose your memory every thirteen hours."
"It's the result of a traffic accident that happened four years ago."
"I'm sorry to tell you that you also lost your left eye."
"Please accept what has happened is real."
"Here, I will write down what you need to know for you to live on."
"First, please, without fail, read this diary every morning."
"This is your memory."
"Everything of yours is here."
"Second, please make sure to write in the diary."
"What you did that day, the conversations you had, medical records, etc."
"Please write them down as accurately as you can."
"Third, if possible, please avoid coming into contact with strangers."
"Due to this handicap, you might have a hard time or might trouble the person you've met."
"In case you meet someone,
please write down that person's exact characteristics and information in the diary."
At first,
I wrote down that you're a small, older guy in a school uniform, who came to the station around three o'clock.
Older?
Because for me, time stopped four years ago.
Ah, I see.
If you wore plain clothes on holidays,
or if I met you before three o'clock, I wouldn't recognize you.
So that's how it was.
That's as far as you can read.
Ah, sorry. This is a diary after all.
No.
This is the real me.
Thirteen hours. That's the number of hours you can remember.
I remember from when I get up at seven o'clock in the morning until eight o'clock in the evening.
But, after that, an hour of my memories disappears as each hour passes.
At twelve o'clock midnight, my memories from before eleven o'clock in the morning will be gone.
And then at seven o'clock the next morning,
my memories before six o'clock, the previous evening, will be gone.
In that case, when you get up in the morning,
you'll have forgotten all about your encounter with me...
Nah, I will remember.
I think back upon things that are important to me. Many, many times.
If I manage to recall them, I'm able to remember them for the next thirteen hours.
At nine o'clock in the evening, before I go to sleep, I read the dairy
and think back upon the things that are important to me.
If I do that, I'm able to remember them even the next morning.
The fact that I had fun with you,
and the fact that I have a memory defect.
I live a peaceful life right now.
I don't go to school, and since I don't have anyone whom I can call a friend...
I'm really doing nothing at all.
If I space out at the station, then I won't have anything I need to remember.
It's a worthless life, isn't it?
If I let go of everything, life will be very easy.
That's not true-
I don't have anything.
Therefore, if I can, my goal is to live a life without troubling others.
However, that's difficult as well.
As long as I'm alive, I will trouble someone.
And then I'll heartlessly forget that I troubled them.
Renji-san.
I'm going to tell you a joke.
Eh? A joke?
A
The furigana next to it says "Rinjin," which means "Neighbor."
I'm home.
Welcome back. Dinner is ready.
Come to think of it, Renji, you got the career interest survey, didn't you?
How do you know?
I heard the other mothers talking about it in cooking class.
That's pretty early. You're still a first-year student.
Yeah.
What will you write down?
I don't know.
It's fine if you just write down what you want to be.
If I could decide, I wouldn't be stressed over it.
Oh yeah, there's something I'd like you to deliver to Kuze-san after this.
Kuze-san is back?
Yeah.
The pot on the stove is his share. Bring it to him.
Kuze-san.
Oh, if it isn't Renji.
It's been a long time.
You're as short as ever. Have you been eating properly?
After three months, is that the first thing you've got to say?
Oh, is that my usual share?
Yes. My mom told you to enjoy.
I accept it gratefully.
I wonder what today's dish is.
Erm, can I come in?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Yeah, if you don't mind that there's a girl on my bed who's wearing nothing.
Excuse me for interrupting you.
It's okay. We don't mind.
I do, so forget about it.
Well, you're right.
Worrying over something?
No, it's not a big deal.
That's all right then.
I'll visit your place with a souvenir next time.
After you're finished with the pot, please leave it in front of my house.
Thank you for everything.
Good night, Renji. Sweet dreams.
Welcome back, Kuze-san.
A
The furigana next to it says "Mujun," which means "Contradiction."
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
The same peaceful day as usual.
I feel that way because I remember my usual life.
I was happy to see Kuze-san yesterday.
That's because I remember Kuze-san.
But for Chihiro,
both the day she lived and the people she met disappear from her memory after thirteen hours.
I went to see Chihiro simply because I wanted to see her.
But Chihiro has to be mentally prepared to meet a stranger like me.
I bet she feels anxious and scared.
Yet...
See you tomorrow.
Yes. See you tomorrow.
Is it all right for me to go and see Chihiro with such an irresponsible attitude?
If you want to stay by Chihiro's side, you have to be prepared.
Am I just being half-hearted about Chihiro?
She won't be there today.
I'm going to tell you a joke.
A joke?
Every day I think about how I can disappear without troubling anyone.
But I've given up on that idea.
I'm not afraid of disappearing.
The feeling of being afraid will simply disappear as well.
It's just that...
Just that?
What I'm truly afraid of is not the disappearance of my own memory,
but disappearing from the memories of everyone else.
I see. Surprisingly, I'm quite a coward.
A joke... eh?
Isn't there something I can do for Chihiro?
Something that a knight can do to protect his princess.
Something that will make her happy.
I have a dream.
A dream?
I want to write stories.
Even if it's just a single story,
I want to complete one as my current self.
A
The furigana next to it says "Yakusoku," which means "Promise."
How come you're here?
I'm the messenger.
Chihiro caught a cold. "Since I couldn't come here today, I'm sorry," she said.
Is she all right?
It's just an ordinary cold.
To be safe, she's forbidden to go out today.
I... see.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
You two made a promise, right? "See you tomorrow."
Chihiro was here till midnight.
To make up for her memory loss, Chihiro makes sure that she keeps that kind of promise.
To her, "see you tomorrow" is an important promise that connects the her of that day to the her of a different day.
I guess she was happy.
Even though I came to pick her up, she told me she had made a promise with you.
How stubborn.
Since Chihiro cannot confirm her own existence, she listens to everything people tell her.
It seems she still has some human qualities left in her.
I... didn't even realize that.
You're not the one to blame.
Chihiro's inflexibility about her common sense just means I'm not qualified to be her guardian.
Yeah.
That's all.
Ah, Onii-chan.
Yo. Practicing by yourself this morning?
Nah. Everyone is too slow, so I left them behind.
Let me have a sip.
Aside from that, what's wrong? You're up so early.
I finished the script through sheer willpower.
I just brought it to the editing department.
If I fell asleep, I wouldn't be able to wake up, so I thought I'd head straight to school.
What kind of wind is blowing?
Is it going to rain too?
I can't guarantee I'll be awake during class though.
Then it's meaningless!
You drank all of it...
Well, I commend you for your solo efforts.
Good work, Onii-chan.
What was that about?
Guess who.
Now, who am I?
Hey you...
Don't be mad. It's just a cute prank that's done all the time, right?
Normally you only cover the eyes!
Normal is no fun.
You can't kill me for a reason like that!
But I'm glad you're here.
Why?
Because, if you weren't here...
The lock to such a wonderful hiding place couldn't be opened.
Ah, I see.
Hey, will you give that to me?
No.
It's an important souvenir my elder sister gave me as congratulations for being admitted to this school.
Even a duplicate key is fine, then.
There's no way I'm gonna share my precious space, where I can be alone.
By the way, Hirono-kun. What about your job today?
If you don't finish your script soon, will your editor beat you up?
I wouldn't come to school under such circumstances.
Really? Let's go, then.
W-Wait a second. Where are we going?
Somewhere that's not h-e-r-e.
Somehow, it looks ordinary.
What do you mean by "ordinary"?
It's like it came out of a textbook.
This kind of film is commonplace.
We made it to look ordinary.
It looks too much like Impressionism if we combine your shots together.
What's wrong with that?
Works that are too individualistic won't be considered for the special prize.
If you plan to go after a high-ranking prize, a solid production will work better.
Kyosuke...
As I thought, even simply taking a walk in Otawa is fun.
I've been living here forever, so I'm tired of seeing it.
There might be a difference in the scenery you usually see when two people walk together.
Not at all.
This Otawa town had ordinary Japanese scenery before as well.
It was all wiped out by the earthquake.
It was also burned to ashes during the war. What an unlucky town.
Maybe that's why...
They built a town that was completely different from before.
You don't need to hold back. I have money with me.
I stayed up all night, so I can't eat that much.
The weather is nice.
There's no way I'd feel like attending class on a day like this.
You skip school regardless of the weather, don't you?
Yeah.
Do you hate school?
Nah.
Why, then?
The town is way more interesting than lessons.
Huh?
I don't hate school. I just hate being bored.
In any case, isn't it better to choose the interesting one?
Even though I shouldn't be the one to say so, it's bad not to go to school.
If the world was restrained to common sense, life wouldn't be fun.
You should also do things that you think you'd enjoy.
Hiro-senpai!
Hayama.
Hiro-senpai, what are you doing at a place like this?
What about you?
I'm shopping.
For my supply of shoujo manga.
You really like manga, eh.
Hirono-kun, who's she?
Ah. She's my kouhai, Hayama Mizuki.
A
A "kouhai" is a junior at school or work.
Nice to meet you.
She's my classmate, Miyamura.
Miyamura... erm...
What?!
Hirono-kun.
I order you to call me "Miyako" from this very moment on.
What's that?
My heart is thoroughly scarred because you forgot my name so quickly.
I have no idea what I should do anymore.
Say, Hayama.
Do you think this is a threat?
It's your fault.
Besides, it's weird to call your girlfriend by her last name.
Hiro-senpai is such a shy guy.
She's not my girlfriend!
E-Eh? Really?
I thought that if you got a girlfriend, the available Kei-senpai would be mine.
How come even Kei is now my girlfriend?
Where's Miyamura?
You got dumped.
As I said, she's not my girlfriend!
Kyosuke.
I know how you feel, but try to understand.
Everyone worked hard to win at this Cinema Festival.
You guys always talk about that.
The only thing you care about is the evaluation.
You should stick to what you want to do.
How about you?
Are you sticking to what you want to do?
No idea.
"No idea"...
Somehow, I'm bored lately.
Peeking through the finder.
What does that mean?
I can't see what I want to do.
Say, Kyosuke.
What?
Let's break up.
Somehow I don't understand you anymore.
You're right.
Can you fill out the notice that I'm leaving the club, President?
Kyosuke...
The site of the earthquake, eh?
It's still here.
You can't stay here.
There's no need to look back at the wreckage of a past that's already over.
I only look forward all the time.
Oh? Aren't you unable to see what you want to do?
For now.
But I decided what I wanted to do a long time ago.
I...
I take the shots I want to take.
What's that?
What I want to take is...
A dream.
The cold is nothing serious, but Himura-san won't let me go outside.
Even though, I want to go see Renji-kun.
You have to listen to what Himura-san tells you.
If you get worse, it'll be bad.
Mizuki?
Hirono-kun, you idiot.
Hey, Onii-chan.
Don't yawn while watching someone practicing. It's rude.
I'm on a different timetable than you.
Humans should sleep at night and wake up in the morning, right?
Manga artists are creatures who really live outside the confines of human nature.
It doesn't matter.
What do you want to talk to me about this early in the morning?
You skipped school yesterday, didn't you?
Y-Yeah. My body couldn't stand it after staying up all night.
I went home to sleep in the afternoon.
You liar.
I know.
You were with Miyamura-senpai, right?
I heard from Mizuki. You ran into her, didn't you?
You know Miyamura?
She's famous.
You're about the only one who doesn't know, since you don't come to school.
Really?
Because she's pretty, the guys always talk about her.
She's a habitual school-skipper,
and even when she attends class once in a while, she completely ignores what the teacher says.
When she's called on, she doesn't answer.
Your attendance record is already dangerously bad.
She didn't know the circumstances, yet she just took you out as she liked.
What an annoying girl.
Stop bad-mouthing someone you don't really know!
Do you know Miyamura-senpai well, then?
I don't.
T-The first time we met was Christmas.
It hasn't been a month yet.
Christmas...?
Is that true?
Onii-chan, you broke your promise to me because you met Miyamura-senpai?
I entrust the feelings that I want to convey in the story.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories: Honesty.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?