HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Crisis at the Great Heart Tree!
The Precure Take Off!
I'm scared. I'm scared of the operation.
So scared!
I'm so afraid!
I know that deep down you have the
courage to surpass your fears, big brother.
Hah!
How ridiculous!
How could a coward ranting on about how
scared he is possess even a scrap of courage?!
If you're going to use the weakness in people's hearts to fulfill your own heinous ends...
then the darkness in their hearts shall be illuminated by my light!
She's strong...
Don't give in, big brother!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Now we've got yet another annoying Precure to deal with! Sheesh!
Itsuki?
I met this girl in my dream.
She tried her hardest to encourage me when I could do nothing but run away.
She seemed to sparkle so very beautifully.
Like the Sun.
I'm sorry you had to see me like this.
I've always admired you, big brother.
And I always will.
In the language of flowers, a chamomile means "to endure hardships."
It's great that he's regained the courage
he needs to go through with his operation!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
I searched high and low but was unable to pinpoint its location.
I apologize for my failure.
The Great Heart Tree is connected to the Flowers of the humans' Hearts.
It cannot have gone far.
Professor Sabark! We've got trouble, huge trouble!
A third Precure's shown up!
What?!
She's a tacky golden Precure!
She's just a newbie, but she sparkles so brightly that it's a total eyesore!
Professor Sabark...
Yes.
We must seek out the third fairy
that was at the Great Heart Tree.
Go, Dark Precure!
Sir.
Operation in Progress
Thank you so much, you two.
Now that there's three of us, things are looking up!
What's going on?!
The Great Heart Tree ish calling for me.
Huh?
The Great Heart Tree is heading toward us!
Huh?!
It'sh over there!
Over there... You mean in the sky?
We need to get there as soon as we can!
Get there? How?
Just leave it to us!
These are... capes?
I'm not sure they're particularly fashionable.
It'sh because you were born, Sunshine,
that the Great Heart Tree has come back.
Ichuki, will you pleashe help me protect the Great Heart Tree?
Of course I will.
I'll help you to the best of my ability.
Anything you want to protect, I'll gladly protect as well.
I love you, Ichuki!
All right then!
Let's fly!
Okay!
This cape is totally awesome! Yahoo!
Erika, you're a good flier!
This is so fun!
What are you doing, Tsubomi?
I... really don't like heights...
Don't worry! I'm here with you, so you won't fall!
I know I won't fall, but...
It's still scary!
If you're holding onto my hand, it won't seem as scary, right?
R-Right! Thank you.
Being able to smile always gives me courage
And sometimes, even my tears seem like little blessings
You see, what lets me press on, no matter how worried I am
is knowing that you're all here for me
It's only once you truly believe in what you're capable of
that you'll be able to protect those important to you
When we're born, our flowers remain shut
without any life within them
But by showing strength and true kindness
they'll bloom within our hearts
And that's when we'll become the flowers of the future
That'sh the Great Heart Tree!
Nice to meet you. I'm Hanasaki Tsubomi!
It's nice to finally meet!
Yahoo! I'm Kurumi Erika!
The Great Heart Tree says, "It's nice to meet you too."
Huh?
The Great Heart Tree can sense your emotions and feelings.
I see.
Just what you'd expect from the Great Heart Tree, huh?
But it sure is big! It's just like it was in the dream.
The dream?
Could you possibly mean the dream
about Cure Moonlight fighting here?
Huh?!
That's right!
You've had the same dreams, right, Itsuki?!
Do you mean you had them too?
If you'd told us that sooner, we'd've figured out you were a Precure earlier than we did!
I knew from the very shtart.
Right...
It's strange, but every time I had that dream, I thought the same thing.
When its flowers fell away, I wondered whether we could make it bloom with beautiful flowers once more.
Look! There's a flower bud growing over there!
There are flower buds over here too! And over there!
The Great Heart Tree is connected
with the Flowers of people's Hearts.
It's because you two have worked so hard to
keep the Flowers of people's Hearts in bloom
that the Great Heart Tree has recovered so well.
I see. Looks like our hard work paid off!
Yeah!
I can't wait to see the Great Heart Tree's flowers blooming again!
This sensation...
It couldn't be?
I've finally found you.
Dark Precure?!
Why is she here?!
She must've followed us!
That's Dark Precure?
What do you plan to do with the Great Heart Tree?!
Whatever I please.
Get out of my way if you value your lives.
Sheed of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Stay away!
Sunshine!
Are you all right?!
Yes...
But those movements... She's something else.
She's not special just because she can fly!
We can do that too! Coffret!
Roger!
The bud...
You mushtn't hurt the Great Heart Tree!
Potpourri, look out!
How could she?
If the Great Heart Tree withers, then the heart of man will also wither and become a desert.
You've hurt both Potpourri and the Great Heart Tree...
I've had it up to here with this!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
No way...
Dark Power, Gather!
Dark Tact!
Blossom, Marine!
Disappear.
Dark Forte Wave!
Sunflower Aegis!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
What are these?!
Now!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
You're better than I thought.
But if that's all you have, then I'm afraid...
Light, come forth!
Protect the Great Heart Tree!
Hurry, hurry!
So this was your goal?!
Like hell I'll let you!
Damn you...
Damn you!
Huh? Isn't this...
It's the hill in our neighborhood.
What about the Great Heart Tree?
It's flown shafely back up into the shky.
Then that means...
The Desert Apostles won't be able to find it anymore!
We'll be able to rest easy for a while!
Satsuki!
Mother...
Grandfather...
The operation was a success.
Everything's going to be okay.
Itsuki... I'm back!
Welcome back, big brother!
Thank god...
Satsuki, you really pulled through.
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble.
Ichuki's shmiling.
She has a nice smile, doesn't she?
Yeah.
It's warm, almost like the Sun.
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Itsuki, we're all packed and ready to go!
Together with everyone from the Fashion Club...
...we're off to the endlessly summery seaside!
Refresh yourself in the midsummer Sun!
New designs will appear before your very eyes!
As we run together across the beach...
...our beautiful friendship will only sparkle ever brighter!
All right, let's make ourselves some fantastic memories!
Yeah!
HeartCatch Precure:
Let's go to the Beach!
Itsuki's Exciting Summer Camp!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!