I'll do it.
I'll take care of Cal.
Are you trying to die?
Not really.
You need to prepare our escape.
We don't have a lot of time.
I don't want to get held up by Cal and waste it.
Therefore I'll handle this...
I asked you the same question before,
but can you point your gun at her?
About that...
Please...
Give me just a little more time.
Alright.
But I need your answer today.
If you can't make up your mind, I'll kill Drei.
And I will also...
...save Mio.
I can't let Elen point her gun at Cal.
I have to be the one to settle this.
I...
Reiji...
Reiji, I want to be with you.
Reiji-kun.
What is it?
Want to have lunch together?
Because you're so occupied with Mio,
it's a rare chance for you to eat lunch with us.
There's not many we can eat with today.
Mio and Elen are both taking the day off.
Elen?
She went to school with me this morning.
She left early.
She said she wasn't feeling well this morning.
You didn't notice?
Hey! Wait a sec!
Tell us how far you've gotten with Mio.
Elen!
The number you have dialed is out of range or turned off.
Found you.
Don't run, answer me!
How far have you and Mio...
Hold on, this isn't the time to...
Why are you so freaked out?
Are you that worried about Elen?
There's a limit to how siscon you can be...
You two.
Fifth period is about to start.
Ah, jeez. We're going back to class.
Hey!
You have to turn it off during classes.
That's common sense.
Now, let's go back.
This is a mailbox service center. You have a message.
You might be angry with me by the time you hear this message,
but I really think this is for the best.
You must not fight Cal.
I'm the one who got Mio involved.
I will save her even if it kills me.
That's why...
...you have to escape ahead of me.
After I've saved her,
I will follow you.
And if...
If I don't show up on time,
please consider me dead.
That was today at 2:15 PM.
Please don't do it...
Don't do it, Elen.
I don't want to lose anyone anymore.
I don't want to get anyone hurt anymore.
Anyone...
That's Ein.
Our prototype.
We must report to Master.
You're putting up with this pretty well, huh?
I thought you'd cry or be more upset than this.
I'm not an animal.
You were tricked by him and dragged into this.
You should be furious.
Are you furious?
About Reiji-san.
Don't talk big.
I just can't believe it.
How can you hate someone so much?
You're not the only one who suffered.
He must have suffered too.
What do you know?
I know.
How can I not?
If you're truly in love with him, then...
You're such a liar.
That's right.
Both you and Reiji are liars.
Is everyone in this country like you?
Have you ever frozen out in the cold?
Did you get beaten up?
Did you survive for three nights without food?
Who do you think you are?
Do you really think nothing in this world could hurt you?
Do you think it's normal...
...to be the one fawned over by everybody else?
You live in comfort and wealth in this foolish country...
What do you know?
You can't possibly know...
...about the suffering of others.
No, stop!
You see, I only had a single dress.
It was burnt to ashes.
What food were you eating to have such smooth skin?
Tell me, little princess.
I'll teach you...
...the true meaning of despair.
Helplessness engulfing your own ability to do anything at all...
...will be carved into your body.
Like a wound it will stay deep in your heart for the rest of your life.
I've been waiting for you here all this time.
You said you'd come home for sure.
You promised me that.
So for a long time...
...I was waiting for you.
For a long time.
Reiji.
Is that you, Shiga?
I'm sorry to disturb you this late at night.
I'm guessing you have bad news.
This matter pertains to Fujieda Mio-san.
As I arrived late, she has been subjected to her current hardships.
We've reached the height of the conflict.
I'm fully aware of my responsibility in this matter.
However, before anything else, saving Mio-san is my primary objective.
For that I ask your permission to mobilize the Godou family's retainers.
Are the ringleaders those Americans?
Is Mio still alive?
Yes, it was confirmed.
Then it's not necessary.
Don't mobilize the Godou family.
Leave the matter to the foreigners.
B-But...
If the clan moves out, we might as well announce it to all of Japan.
Why would the Goudo clan be in frantic disarray for the sake of a single girl?
People would want to know the reason.
You couldn't do anything about it. Taking responsibility isn't necessary.
But, that means...
I said no, Shiga.
There is no relation between the Fujieda household and ourselves and it must stay that way!
Neither now...
...nor in days past.
Listen now, don't take any action until Mio is safe.
As long as we aren't told a ransom or threatened as a clan, there's nothing we can do.
I thank you for your concern.
Shiga, being part of the mafia is nothing but a heavy burden.
Especially when you try to protect something.
Guns and blades can only slay and smash.
They can't protect.
Understood.
I'll keep it in mind.
When I appear in a play I've written,
I always act my own part.
Play and stage have passed the climax and are about to reach the denouement.
The creation of the perfect soldier.
Ein was my first piece of art.
The experimental ones were Zwei and Drei.
Brought forth by them is the final product, the actors presenting the epilogue.
The Zahlenschwestern, devoid of fear or mercy.
They are machines carrying death like faithful hounds.
Both the Godou clan and Inferno are nothing but my tools.
I will dispatch them once Drei is cornered by Ein and Zwei.
The chapter where they all appear will come to pass.
You, the Zahlenschwestern, are included in the play.
I await the moment...
...when the bell announces the curtain call.
Ein?
Drei, I assume.
What do you want?
Let's meet where nobody can disrupt us.
I'll put an end to everything.
Yeah, that's right.
Leave him behind, just the two of us.
My cellphone.
Is she talking to Reiji-san?
Okay, that place is fine. 3 AM.
Do you know those rundown buildings opposite Shinokura High School?
The old girl's dormitory.
Yeah, that's the one.
You can find Mio there.
Bring some clothes.
So you've woken up.
Forget everything.
I'm not a woman you should have a grudge against.
Even without you there are already plenty of others who hold a grudge against me and can't forgive.
I probably won't live long.
When my time comes, I will go straight to hell.
Bye now.
Mio?
Where were you? I was worr-
I'm Mio-san's classmate.
She took the day off, so I came over to bring the printout.
Mio took the day off?
Here.
Okay.
Well then, I'm leaving again.
Goodnight.
Umm, you're...
No, it's nothing. I'm sorry.
Goodnight.
She couldn't be...
Elen!
It's Ein.
There is no longer a reason to keep it a secret from you.
So please call me "Ein".
"Keep it a secret"?
What do you mean?
I brought you a change of clothes.
Why?
Who did...
Drei.
Drei?
Are you referring to Cal?
People have called her that as well.
What are you people?
You heard the story from Drei, I assume.
Is it really true... that you and Reiji-san... ?
Yes. We are assassins.
No way... it can't be true...
I'm sorry, but can you go home by yourself?
You can call the cops with this if you want.
I'm leaving.
Cal left before.
She said something about putting an end to everything.
She's probably trying to kill Reiji-san.
I know.
You do?
Then, she was calling...
Are you going to fight her?
Is there nothing I can do?
I love Reiji-san!
I'd do anything for him.
Is that still not enough?
Can't I be together with him?
Your emotions might be real.
But you cannot defeat Drei with your feelings alone.
If I don't kill Drei, she will kill Reiji.
Preventing that is my responsibility, not yours.
If you want to be useful for him, stay here for a while longer.
If you do that, his chances of survival will increase.
Reiji-san...
Did he lie to me?
No, he did not.
The one who dragged you into this is me.
Reiji isn't someone who can fake crying or laughing.
If you have ever seen him laugh or cry,
they must have been his true feelings.
Ever since you called me Elen,
my life has been devoted only to protecting you.
I want you to live, I want you to stay alive.
If you survive, that would be proof...
...that I ever lived.
This is fine, isn't it?
At least it would be if I could find the unlikely salvation I dream of.