Once in America, Mitsuki
is reunited with Ms. Kazumi,
who gives her the address of her contact
who may know how to find Eichi.
Mitsuki is so excited to be
on the verge of finding Eichi,
and both her throat checkup
and visit to the TV studio go well.
No keywords have appeared
in the Death Spirit Handbook.
Looks like this is
going to be a great trip!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Thank you so very much
for everything.
No problem. Be careful.
Take care, Mitsuki.
Yes, Ms. Kazumi.
Now we're finally free from babysitting.
Right, Takuto?
Huh? Yeah, that's right.
What's the matter, Takuto?
You're sad about leaving that kid, huh?
Bye bye, Nick!
Thank you for everything.
I'm definitely going to see Eichi!
And this time I will definitely
tell him how I feel!
Oh, I feel so free now that
we're without the baby!
Really, what's been up with you?
W-What?
You're acting a little strange today!
I-I'm not acting strange.
I'm not acting strange.
It's only natural.
She's a human and
I'm a Death Spirit.
Even if I could communicate my feelings,
what would happen?
I can't make her happy.
And...she likes Eichi.
There's no need for me.
That's right. It's only natural!
It looks like there's time
until the next bus.
So, what should we do?
Huh?
Do you even need to ask?
Sightseeing!
All right. Time to make
some dough for today.
We're here!
Wow!
It's amazing!
That's Eagle Valley!
Come on! Let's ride that
down to the valley floor.
Wow!
Ms. Oshige, I wanna go too!
What? You too?
But you can't go alone.
You really don't get it!
It'll be fine since I'll be with her!
Stupid! That's what worries us!
I see, Takuto is going too. Then there's
nothing to worry about, I guess.
What's that supposed to mean?
Thank you, Ms. Oshige.
Let's go, Takuto.
All right.
Hey, wait!
Whoops!
I'm so sorry!
Wow...
It's like a Baumkuchen.
Yeah, I wonder how long
it takes to get like this?
Ahem!
This is called a "stratum," and it takes
approximately 43,000 years to form.
This dramatic gorge formation
started two billion years ago,
and the erosion
continues to this day.
Oh, is that so?
You know so much, Meroko!
Ahem!
Hmm, I wonder.
W-What?
Are you just making stuff up again?
How rude! It's not made up.
I'm just relaying what's in here!
But nature can be really huge!
Oh, I know.
Let's take a picture since we're here.
That's a good idea!
Yeah!
Do you want me to
take the photo for you?
Huh?
You can't take a souvenir photo
by yourself, can you?
Here, give me it to me.
Oh, yes, please.
All right, Takuto, Meroko.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- Yup.
Are you ready, young lady?
Yes!
It's a cheap and worthless necklace,
but I'll make it the start to my work here.
All right, smile!
Thank you very much.
Don't mention it.
I'm sorry, are you all right?
Y-Yes.
All right then.
Thank you.
Mitsuki, shouldn't we be
going back soon?
Yeah, we should.
It's gone.
What's the matter, Mitsuki?
It's gone! It's gone!
What's gone?
The pendant is gone!
What am I gonna do?!
Without that... Without that...
Calm down!
Calm down, Mitsuki!
What should we do, Takuto?
Well, we won't make it in time
if we don't go back now.
Takuto, Meroko, you guys go back first!
I'll stay here and look for it.
I'll go back after I find it!
You know we can't do that!
B-But... Without it...
What should we do?
Is it that important?
All right, I know.
Mitsuki and I will stay here
and look for the pendant.
What?!
Hey Takuto! Are you serious?
Yeah. So you go up and let them
know about this. Let's go, Mitsuki.
J-J-Just a minute!
Why am I left behind again?!
Jeez! Forget them!
It left.
I wonder what happened
to Mitsuki and them.
You don't think they've gotten in
an accident or something, do you?!
Let's go look for them.
Even though I said what I said,
I just can't leave them on their own.
Why am I so admirable?
And that idiot Takuto...
Lucky! Perfect timing!
Hey! It's awful, just awful!
Hey, are you listening?
I said, it's awful!
Oh yeah...
So that's what happened.
Really, Meroko?
Yup.
Then we need to hurry
down to get them.
You're right, let's hurry.
You had it on when
we took the picture, right?
Yeah.
Let's look for it again
on the route here.
Come on.
There's no use getting depressed, right?
Let's look for it.
Yeah.
Let's go back to where
we took the photo again.
Takuto...
Please!
As I've said, all the drivers
have gone home for the night,
and there's no way
we can operate it.
No way!
Isn't there some way?
I'll go.
Axel...
Will you be all right, Axel?
Thank you so very much!
Leave it to me!
It's not here after all.
We don't need to look anymore, Takuto.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you're giving up so easily?
Well, it's already so late.
It's something important to you, right?
Yeah.
Eichi gave me that pendant.
O-Oh, I see!
But it's all right!
Because I get to see him soon!
It's too bad I lost it,
but it's all right!
B-But...
We've already made Ms. Oshige
and the others worry, so let's go back.
Takuto, thanks for
looking for it with me!
What?! This is terrible!
Takuto, what do we do?
I guess there's no choice.
I'll carry you and fly up.
Are you Mitsuki?
Huh? Oh, yes.
Huh?
No.
Don't come any closer!
All right, let's go.
I don't want to!
Hey, you!
Get away from Mitsuki!
Oh, there's someone with her.
Takuto!
What are you planning
to do with Mitsuki?!
I wasn't planning to do anything.
You come with us too.
Now, hurry up.
Wow, it's like a Western!
It's from the pioneering days.
Thank you very much.
Sorry for surprising you earlier.
No, sorry for jumping to conclusions
even though you had come to rescue us.
It was a pretty good tackle.
After we eat, we'll sleep.
We'll go back first thing
tomorrow morning.
Okay!
We'll look for your lost item
again tomorrow.
Takuto?
Man, I'm such a loser!
Damn it!
What am I supposed to do?
At this rate, I'll eventually...
Takuto?
S-Stupid!
It's dangerous to walk around alone!
S-Sorry.
But since you went out,
I followed you!
Can I sit down?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
About what?
For not being able to
find your pendant.
No, it's really all right.
You looked really hard
for it too, Takuto.
Hey, Takuto?
Huh?
I'm really glad that I met you, Takuto.
What?
Because I met you,
I was able to become a singer.
And I was able to come
all the way to America.
I didn't think I'd be able see Eichi again,
but I'm gonna get to see him soon too.
Even though sometimes when
I talk about Eichi, you get moody.
Th-That's...
But whatever happens, you're always
on my side, and you always help me.
Th-That's...
Why?
What?
Why do you always
do so much for me?
Th-That's...
That's because...
That's because you're a little loser,
and you can't take care of yourself!
What?
I'm going back!
Wait for me, Takuto!
I wish we had a better
hideout than this.
Oh, good morning, Eric.
Did you guys drink all night?
Get it together!
We need to make some dough today too!
Oh?
That guy...
What's the matter, Eric?
O-Oh no!
Run!
That man... I think he's...
Just as I thought!
He's the thief that targets tourists!
I see! So she didn't
drop the pendant!
He stole it back then!
Huh?
Otherwise, he wouldn't run away!
W-Wait!
Wait!
I can't keep going!
M-Me neither.
Wait!
- What?
- Huh?
- We've been spared.
You can't get away now!
All right!
Give us back the pendant!
Takuto!
What're you gonna do?
A-All right. I'll give it back,
so forgive me!
Here you go!
Damn it!
Takuto!
What an idiot.
Takuto! Takuto!
What do I do?
Takuto is... Takuto is...
What're you crying for,
you little loser?
You're so stupid, Takuto!
Takuto?
Stupid, stupid!
You're so stupid, Takuto!
What the... I got it back for you!
Aren't you happy?!
I am happy! But why did you
do such a reckless thing?!
When I go back to this form, I can fly,
and besides, Death Spirits can't die!
That's not the point!
I was worried!
Takuto, where are you?
Why? Why do you always act so tough?
You did such a dangerous thing!
Oh, enough, enough!
Answer me, Takuto!
Why should I, you little loser?
What did you say?!
Takuto!
I-It's... It's because I like you,
of course!
Hey, Takuto, what are you doing
telling her you like her?!
Gosh, you're so annoying!
Don't call me annoying!
Takuto, you're a Death Spirit and
she's a human! It's forbidden!
And... And...
Eichi's gonna be in
the picture soon too,right?
You don't have to tell me twice!
Next time on Full Moon:
"To the Town Where Eichi Lives!"
- Look forward to it!