Madam?
We must hurry.
Another intruder...
Directly ahead of us.
If we go this way, we'll run into him.
Understood.  We'll detour to the north.
Madam?
It's...
Kotomine Kirei.
Kotomine Kirei?
Maiya-san, Kiritsugu ordered you
to keep me safe, right?
Yes.
But...
But what?
We absolutely cannot let
that man reach Kiritsugu.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
Madam, how did you―
What a coincidence.
As it happens, I feel the same way.
Kotomine Kirei probably poses the
greatest threat to Kiritsugu.
We must keep him at bay.
Right, Maiya-san?
I apologize.
Please ready yourself, madam.
I will.
Don't worry about me.
Just focus on the task before you.
Rather than follow Kiritsugu's orders,
do what you believe to be
the right course of action.
Yes.
What is it?
The human heart is a
funny thing, isn't it?
Repeating the same
ineffective attacks...
Scalp!
He penetrated Volumen Hydragram's
autonomous defense?
No...
His childish trickery made me
lower my guard.
I'll defend myself more quickly
and effectively next time.
You disgrace of a mage.
You worthless thug!
You will pay for spilling my blood,
with your life.
After that attack, he knows
how powerful this weapon is.
The same tactic won't work twice.
He'll probably pour every bit of mana
he has into defense.
Of course...
That's exactly what I'm counting on.
An illusion?
Maiya-san, don't!
Madam...
No!
This may surprise you, woman,
but it is not my objective to kill you.
I know that, Kotomine Kirei.
I know your true objective.
But I'll tell you nothing.
You will not reach to Emiya Kiritsugu.
We will stop you.
Here.
Madam!
He is an Executor...
A special agent trained to kill mages!
Normal magic won't be enough
to defeat him!
Kiritsugu's taught me more
than how to drive.
He's taught me how to live.
And how to survive!
Shape Ist Leben!
Madam!
That won't work!
Maiya-san!
Do it!
No way...
Son of a...
All this effort, yet we still
have no opening.
This has gone from annoying
to downright frustrating.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds his Noble Phantasm,
our tactical situation will not improve.
I see.  So that's it.
Knocking that book
away from its gaunt owner
still means breaking through
this wall of monsters.
Lancer, are you willing to try an
all-or-nothing gamble?
The thought of being
forced to it chafes me,
but fighting these beasts
is just as galling.
All right.
I'm in, Saber.
I shall clear a path, but we will
have only one chance.
Lancer, can you run on the wind?
I understand.
It will present no problem.
Have you said your final prayers?
You will know terror...
Hopelessness.
Superior skill can do only so much
against overwhelming numbers.
Isn't it mortifying?
You'll die, suffocated by a
host of spirits and devils,
with neither honor nor valor.
No hero could abide such humiliation.
Ah, that beautiful face...
I want to see it twisted
with pain, Jeanne!
Strike Air!
Prepare yourself!
Pierce through, Gáe Dearg!
Damn you...
Damn you, damn you, damn you,
damn you, damn you, damn you!
Damn you!
How about that?
If Saber still had the use of her left hand,
this would have been the result.
Prepare yourself...
heretic.
Ridiculous.
I did not enter the Holy Grail War
to fight these kinds of battles!
Where is he?
Found you.
You filthy rat.
You aren't really planning to use
the same tactic again, are you?
Scum!
Don't delude yourself that
this wound resulted
from any brilliant strategy or scheme.
It was merely an absurd coincidence,
and you are about
to learn the difference.
It won't be quick, either.
I shall continuously heal
your lungs and heart,
as I shred your flesh from head to toe.
You will suffer, despair, and
languish as you die.
And in your final moments,
you will curse your cowardly employers,
the Einzberns, for making a
mockery of the Holy Grail War!
Fervor Mei Sanguis!
I knew you'd try that again, imbecile!
Fight all you like.
How cowardly can you be?
Lancer.
Is something wrong?
My Master is in danger.
It seems he's left me here,
while he attacks on the castle.
I'm certain my Master is behind this.
You should go, Lancer.
Save your Master.
King of Knights...
I am in your debt.
No.
We swore, on our pride as knights,
to finish our battle honorably.
Let us abide by that oath.
In the end,
has everything gone as Kiritsugu planned?
Your origin lies in severing and binding, kiddo.
Cutting and connecting.
The nuance is a bit different from
destroying and regenerating.
If you cut a thread and
tie the ends together again,
the thread will be thicker
where you tied it, right?
In other words, the change
is irreversible.
I ground up part of your ribs,
and put some in this bullet.
Your origin will manifest in
anything you shoot with it.
It will be especially effective
against mages.
You see, if they try to
deflect it with magic,
your origin will cut their Magic Circuits,
then haphazardly tie them.
The more capable the mage,
the worse the Circuits will
misfire and short out.
Of course, the victim will never
function properly again...
Neither as a mage nor as a person.
This will be for your Mystic Code, kiddo,
the origin shot.
I made sixty-six rounds.
Use them wisely.
You do know how easily I could
spear you right now,
Master of Saber?
So that's how it is...
I will not let my Master be killed.
Nor will I kill Saber's Master.
Neither she nor I wish our battle
to end this way.
Do not forget,
the only reason you leave this place alive
is the honor of the King of Knights.
One question, woman.
It appears that you two faced me
with the intent
of protecting Emiya Kiritsugu.
But who ordered you do so?
Without any Command Spells,
you are not the Einzbern Master.
I assume
you are a homunculus, assigned to
protect the Grail Vessel.
Not someone, in my estimation,
who would be foolish enough
to appear on the front lines.
So I ask you again...
Who ordered you to fight?
Kirei-sama...
Caster, as well as Lancer and his Master
have withdrawn from the forest.
Saber closes on our location.
You are in danger here, my Master.
Interesting...
So it really is red.
Is it possible?
Could these women have tried to fight me
of their own free will?
No.
Emiya Kiritsugu is like me,
an enigmatic, isolated man.
A man filled with emptiness.
He must be.
Irisviel...
Irisviel!
Stay with me.
Saber...
Don't speak!
Just stay awake!
I'll get Kiritsugu.
Hold on until I return!
Where's Kirei?  The man who attacked us.
He escaped.
Had I been here but a moment sooner,
this would not have happened.
How is Maiya-san?
She is badly injured,
but her life is not in danger.
We must worry about you!
You've lost so much blood...
Irisviel?
But, how?
I want you to take Avalon.
But this is a Noble Phantasm
that heals its owner's wounds.
Shouldn't you carry it?
No.
Unless its original owner, Saber,
is close enough to provide mana,
the scabbard's power won't activate.
You will be the one working
alongside Saber from now on, Iri.
Keep it inside you, as a
Conceptual Armament.
Also,
tell no one else about it.
Not even Saber.
I felt Avalon's healing power
from the moment you touched me.
Thank you, Saber.
Kotomine Kirei...
That Executor is as dangerous
as we thought.
Or perhaps, even worse.
We were lucky tonight,
but there's no telling
what will happen next time.
One thing is clear.
I cannot allow him near Kiritsugu.
But I'm not the only one
protecting Kiritsugu.
Right, Maiya-san?
We'll win next time.
Together, we'll keep Kiritsugu safe.
Episode 8:
The Mage-Slayer
My Master is in danger.
Battles must be fought with dignity.
I cannot agree to that.
Please give me your Command Spells.
Lancer is not so obliging!
Next time:
Master and Servant