I did it!
I sold a copy of
the manga I drew, yeah!
If it comes to this now,
I'm going to draw more and more!
What, even though
you have 29 copies in stock?
But to be honest,
the printing cost is tremendous.
You're always wearing
really cute clothes.
Justice makes them for me.
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
So can I ask about now?
What is it?
Why aren't you saying hello to Najimi?
Because we're following her.
If you could explain
in a way I can understand...
A job?
Ah, no, no. Thanks, though.
You were saying how you
needed to make money for printing.
To tell the truth, I already found one.
What kind of job?
That's...
...a secret!
4th Edition
Please stop, Master.
I get it.
That definitely makes me curious too.
That's why we're going to follow her
and find out where her new job is.
Roger!
But is it okay?
It's fine. She's just
a little shy about it, and...
...the truth is she seemed
like she wanted to say it.
On top of that...
Najimi is an M.
M?
I get it!
If it's a job that she's
embarrassed to say...
...when people find out,
it turns into pleasure.
Bingo.
Although, if she's selling herself when
she's not supposed to be selling it...
Again?
You were the one that was just
misunderstanding the other day, Justice.
I cleared it up for you, right?
No, with the happiness
of selling one book...
...Najimi has been possessed
by the fascination of dojin.
As it is weakening
her ethical decisions...
...then it could be possible
that she chose that kind of job.
That's when I, Justice, will...
...bring her back to the right path!
I thought you would have
waited for me at the platform.
We would have lost Najimi.
More like, you and Najimi are a little alike.
Thank you very much.
I'm not speaking well of you.
But how did you know we were here?
It's thanks to these marks.
Beads?
You placed these on the ground
as you walked, right, Sora?
Yeah.
Thank you, Sora!
Justice!
I'm just going to go ahead.
Oh, bummer...
It looks like she just came to buy
some games or erotic books again.
This is strange.
From what I've heard,
it's about time for her job to start.
You think she skipped it?
Najimi even tried to pick up a
1-yen coin that was dropped in a puddle.
There's no way she would
do such a wasteful thing.
Then, she has to be
an employee here.
If that's so, it's strange
that she's hiding it.
Cat Ears Café.
Welcome home, Master...
I-I'm home...
What did you guys come here for!
This is not a Tsundere Café.
How do I say this...
It's like a broad interpretation
of a sensitive part of a girl's heart.
You followed me, huh?
Well, I guess that's what
it's turned out to be.
It's not "I guess"!
It's...
I'm sorry.
It's okay. We aren't
worried about it at all!
I'm worried about it!
I wish I hadn't seen this.
You...
Luna-chan!
Yes!
Luna-chan?
Stop being so loud!
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Najimi, that was not nothing!
Luna? What is Luna?
Master, it's making things difficult for
me, so would you be please be quiet?
Just for your information, the reason
why I'm working here is because...
You like those kinds of clothes?
Sora.
Listen, at times like this,
even if that's what you think...
To make money for printing, you
chose a place with a good wage, right?
Yes, but could you please hide that...
..."I'm being told to say this"
feeling a little bit more?
On top of that, the reason why
I'm working here is because...
I give up.
Okay, two coffees and
a rice omelet. No problem.
But the truth is she wanted to
wear those kinds of clothes, right?
Well, there were most likely
other places with good wages too.
Ah, meaning Najimi is
a very shy person, right?
Very shy person...
That's a dirty play.
Welcome home, Master!
I-I'm home...
One person in non-smoking, right?
Yes. Thank you.
If I'm right, that guy is...
The first customer of Najimi's book.
Najimi, may I have a moment?
What is it?
It seems like you're used to it,
but does that guy come often?
Hoshi-kun?
Yeah, every day.
Every day?
Yeah, a couple of times a day.
Seems like he started working
on the floor above here.
So he comes here
every break he gets.
When did he start working?
Maybe about two days after
I started working here, I think.
Luna-chan!
Yes, be right there!
That's what it is...
It's hard to believe that their jobs
were in the same place by chance.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah, rice omelet!
I can write an illustration or message
with the ketchup. What would you like?
The illustration is, you know,
so a message please.
Then what message
do you want me to write?
What should I do?
Tsuyuri, you can decide.
Let's do...
Najimi Osana is...
Najimi is...
Yes, and then?
A perverted girl.
Wait, why do I have to
write about myself like that!
About yourself?
I thought you were Luna-san, right?
Okay, I'll write it.
A perverted girl...
On top of that, a super masochist.
That's your ulterior motive?
Ah, hurry up and eat and go home!
By all means, this is not a Tsundere Café.
She's definitely tsundere!
Justice, you want some too?
I can write a message or do
an illustration with chocolate, but...
...what would you like?
W-Well, if it's... if it's okay with you...
If I could ask your real name...
But I can't do such a drastic thing...
What? I'm sorry.
I can't really hear you.
Don't flatter yourself, kid!
Oh my god, you scared me!
I was just requesting
a message from Luna-san.
More like, what's with you!
I am her childhood friend!
That's unfair!
I have even taken a bath
together with her.
Hey! Put "when we were
still young" at the end!
W-Well, I can put a
magic spell on Luna-san!
A magic spell?
Luna-san, can I get the service
for the melting-away magic?
C-Certainly.
Um, he can get a souvenir photo
taken with just the two of them.
Puni puni, puni puru,
it's melting-away magic, meow!
If you have something you want
to say, say it! Actually, don't say it.
Get a little closer, please.
What is with this sense of defeat?
I'll take care of this.
Okay, kitty!
You said your name was Hoshi-kun, right?
I'm heading out before you.
We'll meet again somewhere.
Is that so? I'll be here every day,
so whenever you would like.
Every day?
Do you hear me? From this day on,
you should stop chasing her around!
Chasing her around? How rude!
Najimi is most likely annoyed!
Is that right?
Beauty Love-san's real name
is Najimi-san, huh?
What a wonderful name.
This is what you call losing
the game but winning the match.
Well, goodbye.
See you another time, Najimi-san.
Thank you very much.
Najimi! You have to quit
this place right now!
I will not allow you to
go marry a man like him!
What are you talking about?
The reason why I'm
working here is because...
...if I go upstairs,
there are a lot of references.
I-If I know what kind
of book is selling, then...
...I can research what kind
of book people want.
So that means...
That's right! I thought it would be a
good environment to draw dojinshi!
So I won't quit!
So you could draw dojin...
Najimi!
It wasn't just the clothes, huh?
But if it was that, you should have
just worked upstairs normally.
Don't come see me too much.
It's a little embarrassing
to see acquaintances.
Okay, we'll stop coming to see you.
We won't come see you,
but we will come work.
Where's the manager!
We'll have them hire us right now.
S-Stop it!
Najimi, get out of the way.
Don't come into the kitchen!
There is something I have to do!
Thank you very much.
We'll be waiting at the Akiba's Tora.
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Did you find out about the
cruel tease in the subtitles?
5th Edition
Let's do it with the two of us.
Please be fooled by it a little longer.
5th Edition
Let's do it with the two of us.