Hishigata Clinic
Welcome to the white sands of Omoto Beach.
Dive deep below.
Watch the schools of fish swim.
Is that a person or Hiruko?
I'm sorry, Hizuru.
I said I wanted to meet yer friends.
But when they came...
Ya don't need to do anything ya don't wanna.
I just like being with ya.
Yer not like the others.
I'm not?
People run when they see me, but ya ran toward me instead.
There was a way to go upstairs in the old clinic 14 years ago.
Rumor has it that there's a ghost in the old clinic.
That's why I'm told not to meet ya.
Who told ya that?
Shide!
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Shide?
Who's that?
I'm not supposed to say, but I guess I can tell ya a little.
Shide is always full of greed,
so he's got four arms!
Four arms?
"Shide"...
Shide
Four arms
As in "four arms."
Paper streamer
Or "paper streamer."
That's the four-armed monster!
Oh, right. I brought it.
Here.
Wow!
This is it!
Thanks, Hizuru.
I was wondering how it tasted.
I'll be the mom!
I'll be the sister.
This must be another day.
Shinpei, is she really Haine?
I don't know, but let's watch this memory to the end.
What's wrong, Hizuru?
I cut my finger.
Are ya okay? Show me.
Hey.
Haine?
That tickles.
I hate being so hungry.
I hate it.
Ya don't look well.
Do ya eat anything besides what I bring?
Haine?
So many died of hunger.
Adults died, and we couldn't catch fish.
Come the summer, Father, Mother, my siblings, and everyone...
They all died.
Hizuru?
My shadow...
S-Stroke my shadow too.
Please.
Yer hand's so warm.
Ya can tell from the shadow?
Yeah.
I'll bring more food next time.
Thanks, Hizuru.
Please stay my friend ferever.
It's summer now.
Hey.
Are ya the Minakata girl?
What're ya doing here?
Walking.
I can see that.
This place is dangerous.
Beware of snakes!
There are snakes 'round here.
Then why would you be safe?
I ain't safe.
That's why I'm working here.
Yer in the way.
At least use the path.
What? Snacks?
Yeah. She just bought a bunch.
Aren't ya having a party?
Yeah, but she said she was going to Koba Mart and never came back.
What? She said she was sharing with a friend.
That ain't y'all?
What?
Koba, she really said that?
Mt. Takanosu!
Sis!
I hope she has water.
What if she passed out somewhere?
She even forgets to breathe when she gets too focused.
What?
Who was that?
A red kimono?
Who is it?
I have a bad feeling.
Is it that day?
Is this the "friend" Sis told us about?
Hey.
No, Ryuunosuke.
Stay back!
Are ya okay?
Do ya feel sick?
Ms. Nagumo!
Is someone there?
What? Did she hear me?
Just my imagination?
"Ms. Nagumo"?
Oh no. She can't hear me anymore.
What was that light?
Ryuunosuke...
Why, Haine?
Did ya do this?
Hizuru...
No...
Not me.
Not me!
An eye?
It's Haine's right eye!
Was that...
It hurts...
It hurts!
Ryuunosuke?
Ryuunosuke!
Why?
Why did this happen?
Haine!
Strays!
Who?
Who are those guys?
Here. Go on.
The hunter.
The hell is this?
What the—
Watch out! Stay away!
M-Me?
I-It can't be.
Sis...
No way!
Wh-What are ya?
What the hell?
Are they immortal?
S-So there ya are.
I was looking fer ya.
H-Hey!
Sis, I got enough water fer ya too.
Today is our birthday, Sis.
He's inside Hizuru.
She has a shadow's physical skills!
Ryuunosuke's data burst out of Haine and went into her!
So it's Ryuunosuke who's moving Ms. Nagumo right now.
What was that?
Sorry, Sis.
I might've dislocated yer shoulder.
H-Hey!
Are ya okay?!
Stay with me! Hey!
Hey!
Hizuru
Asako
Since we're friends, I'll let ya go this once.
The next time we meet, I'll kill ya!
Ow...
You... came back.
This is before we went inside Koba Mart.
D-Don't do it.
Don't go in.
I'm at home.
Ushio hit Shinpei's neck and looped.
Daddy, what time is it?
Let's see... it's six o'clock on the dot.
Last time, it was before the funeral.
The starting point is getting later.
Maybe it's starting later because
Shinpei's power is getting weaker.
I see.
Each time he dies, the amount of time he can observe decreases.
This is a good discovery.
In that case, let's give him what he wants and make him loop over and over...
until he reaches his limit.
So we kill Shinpei until he can't loop anymore, at which point he'll die for good?
Exactly.
Let him use up his life one bit at a time.
It's easier than capturing him alive.
Right, Shide?
Yes.
Asako.
Seconds, please.
Summer Time Rendering
One hour later
Are you hungry?
I brought you this.
You're a strange man.
You somehow managed to cook in this situation.
On that day, Ryuunosuke entered you.
I was surprised at first, but I got used to it in time.
Ryuunosuke is strong like Ushio,
and you've saved me many times.
I'd prefer to fight myself.
I don't want to bring out Ryuunosuke.
You care for your brother, don't you?
Why do you think so?
I have a sister too, so I understand.
You don't want Ryuunosuke to fight shadows and suffer again.
You're overthinking it.
Am I?
I'm only looking after myself.
If he fought with all his power,
my body would be torn to shreds.
On that day, when my shoulder was
dislocated and my ankle was sprained,
I was in bed unable to move for five days.
What a royal pain, right?
Oh, did you not like spicy food?
No, this is great.
It reminds me of eating at Bistro Kofune.
Every 22nd, Mio's shadow was at Bistro Kofune, but tonight, she'll likely come here.
Shadow Mio pretty much ignores Mio.
She has an order that overrules her instinct to kill her original.
It's an order from Haine.
We can use that to our advantage.
Yes.
With this mark, can Haine know my location too?
We'll find out.
Since the enemy loops too, we must move quickly.
If Ushio shares her memories,
others will feel like they looped.
We'll attack at full combat capability from the very start.
Sorry I called ya a monster.
Ya were fighting as hard as ya could.
Oh, at the summer festival?
No worries.
Ya ain't exactly wrong, anyway.
I'm not upset at—
I thought I'd never see ya again!
Mio, don't cry so much.
Sis, lemme fight.
I can't just watch y'all protect me.
Mio, we brought ya here to keep ya safe.
Shin, I'm ready to fight back.
Alain's not picking up.
He's usually home by now.
Shinpei?
Are ya okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm just a bit nervous.
Do I gotta do this?
A mission needs a leader.
Everyone wants to hear from you.
I don't think I can be the leader.
You're better at that.
Yer the only one fer the job, Shinpei!
If it weren't fer yer powers,
none of us would be here like this.
O-Okay... Well...
For as long as I can remember,
I've taken a bird's-eye view of things.
It felt like another me was looking from high above and thinking.
I was able to see myself amidst my surroundings.
Even if I messed up, it didn't feel personal.
I thought I was being smart by living like that.
But after Ushio died, I was left with regrets.
I should've at least called her once.
I could've come home for New Years.
I should've made her that curry one last time.
I thought I saw everything, but I missed that.
I've made so many mistakes.
It hurts me to regret things I can't fix.
I'll probably have regrets again,
but I don't want to ever feel like this.
So I'll avoid doing anything that I might regret.
I decided to run away from it.
Run away?!
But that doesn't mean I don't have to do anything.
If I'm going to have regrets, I'll do something about it.
That's how I feel now.
In other words, even if I fail and end up dead...
I want to think that I gave my whole life for this.
I know you guys saw how Ushio fought
the shadows all by herself before she died.
She lost her life trying to save Shiori.
She must've been disappointed... truly disappointed.
I'll finish what she started.
I won't let the end of that summer festival repeat itself.
If we all work together, I believe we'll be successful,
but don't take my word for it.
Don't, huh?!
I can't guarantee we'll survive.
I don't know even know if we'll win.
But I'm not giving you the choice to leave either.
I know I'm being selfish, but I don't want any regrets.
I'm forcing everyone to stay because I don't want to regret not doing it.
Please take a weapon and fight with me.
Okay, when and where will they appear?
Oh, a snake.
Yer crazy!
Ya want us to die fer yer sake?!
We're not yer pawns!
Shinpei loves this island.
Not to mention, everyone on it!
Sure, he ain't good with words, but Shinpei's on yer side.
And there ain't nothing wrong with taking the side of people ya love!
I'll fight!
M-Mio?!
Me too, Shinpei!
I'm always on yer side!
That'll never change!
Are y'all aware how many shadows are on this island?
We've got no chance.
Even more so if Haine is looping.
Shinpei is trying to get us all killed.
Tokiko!
That's right! Ya tell him!
But...
I've already died once.
My life is yours now.
What?!
Our only choice is to exterminate them.
Damn, this can't...
Fine, let's do this!
I'm a man of action! Damn it!
Thanks, everyone.
What?
I'm at home.
I'm back?
I looped.
Did I...
die?
When?
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Lights, Camera, Action