The Shimogamo Shrine is located in the triangular area between the Takano and Kamo rivers.
Lake Biwa
Although there are mountains of shrines of noble lineage in Kyoto,
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine is one of the foremost among the ones that existed prior to the Heian period.
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Kamo River
Takano River
Shimogamo Shrine
Though scores of visitors
go there throughout the year
to receive matchmaking and all kinds
of other blessings from the gods,
God of
match-
making
Aioi
Shrine
few know that a small ramen cart
appears in the vicinity each and every night.
It's called Neko Ramen.
The rumor is it uses actual cats
to make the broth,
but whether or not that's true
cannot be ascertained.
However, the taste is unmatched.
You are a person of
Shimogamo Yuusuisou, yes?
In fact, I am a resident of Shimogamo Yuusuisou.
Yes, and?
I also live there.
Shimogamo Yuusuisou is a boarding house behind Eizan Demachiyanagi Station,
and according to what I've heard,
it's exactly the same as when it was rebuilt
after it disappeared during the violence of the final days of the Tokugawa shogunate.
If it weren't for the light leaking out the windows,
it would be no different than ruins,
and when I visited there at the introduction of the university co-op at the start of school,
I could have reasonably thought that I had strayed off and stumbled into Kowloon City.
Ah, that's it!
I remembered that I have seen this queer, curious fellow quite a number of times.
I am a god of Shimogamo Shrine.
My proper name is Kamotaketsunuminokami.
K-Kamotake...?
Kamotaketsunominokamo.
Don't make me say it twice.
But the second time was different...
You didn't know?
I know everything about you.
Your parents' names, how you were always
throwing up and making sour smells as a baby,
your nickname during elementary school, the middle school cultural festival,
your fleeting first love during high school, the first time you watched an adult video,
your life as a ronin, and your lazy, idle days
spent after entering college.
You've got to be kidding me!
After suffering heartbreak in the club of your dreams, you closed yourself off,
and before long, you started getting in the way of people's path to love.
And why have you spent these
two years in such a warped state?
That's because Ozu...
I accept that you have had your soul
somewhat dirtied by the influence of Ozu.
But that is not all, is it?
The past two years went rambling through my brain like swaying paper lanterns.
At the sacred woods of
Shimogamo Shrine, of all places,
my delicate heart was seized by
nothing but painful memories, and—
Ahhhh!
...is what I wanted to scream out,
but I restrained myself like a gentleman.
N-None of your business.
It's got nothing to do with you.
It will soon be Kannazuki.
I must travel to Izumo once again.
It is our job, yes, but it is quite a lot of work,
and don't make light of the train fare.
In this age, we just throw
the matters we bring with us
into the "already inspected"
wooden box with hardly a look.
And yet, as I am a serious fellow, I can't help
but to be deep in thought, scratching my head
thinking about which two people
would be most suited for each other,
almost like a matrimonial agency.
Woe is me.
Don't you think?
I don't follow in the slightest.
When fall comes, we gather at Izumo
and decide the relationships
of man and woman.
Here is the name of Akashi-san, whom you know.
And here are the names of yourself and Ozu.
Do you understand?
Understand what?
You're even stupider than I thought.
As a god of matchmaking,
I am trying to decide the fate of
this woman you know: Akashi-san.
In other words,
it's between you and Ozu-kun.
If you desire, come to my room.
Shimogamo Yuusuisou, room 210.
This strange fellow is saying he is trying to tie Akashi-san to either Ozu or me.
When I was in high school,
I didn't participate in any club activities,
and I just stayed cooped up with a bunch of other layabout guys.
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Will you take up
Sumo?
Dance Dance Dance
COSPLAY
Judo
Club
Dance Dance Dance
Singing for everyone!
But now, as a brand-spanking-new freshman university student,
countless doors to the mystical treasure known as "rose-colored campus life" lay open before me.
I was half-swooned with glee.
And the one I chose was...
Cupid
Among the raven-haired maidens working up an invigorating sweat,
I would begin the rally of love!
...is what I, an idiot beyond
all redemption, had thought.
The first summer.
My still-as-of-yet rose-colored self was
cut to the quick by that which is called reality.
Making 100 friends wouldn't be so bad,
or so I frivolously thought,
but I soon realized just how difficult
casually getting to know other people could be.
My wish of a rally unfulfilled,
I was not even able to hit back,
and my serves were left unreturned.
I tried presenting myself
as sociable and easy-going,
but I wasn't part of the
conversation to begin with.
By the time I realized I had to be sociable
in order to be included in the conversation,
it was already too late.
I had lost my place among the circle.
It was then that an ominous man
stood beside me with a face of ill portent.
Are you some messenger from hell
that only delicate little me can see?
You say some pretty mean things.
There's no need to worry. I am your compatriot!
That was my first contact with Ozu,
as well as my worst contact.
Anyway, it's quite a contrast, isn't it?
Maybe I should mix it up over there myself.
The place below the Shimogamo Shrine where the Kamo and Takano rivers join
Shimogamo Shrine
is called the Kamo River Delta,
Party Area
Us, Concealed
and it is widely used as a location for parties
from spring through summer.
Party Area
Us, Concealed
Ozu is in the same year as I am.
Eight in ten people to meet him at night
would mistake him for a youkai,
Hates vegetables
Grades
dangerously low
Selfish
No pride
Lazy
and the remaining two would be sure of it.
Picks on the weak
The Devil
Sucks up to
the strong
Doesn't care as
long as it's funny
Fast at
running
away
Worthless
character
Eating the unhappiness of others
as a topping on his rice,
he's a man with seriously
not a single point to praise.
My soul would have surely stayed unblemished
were it not for having met him.
Hey, are you gonna turn on me?
I'm just joking with you.
Stop touching me!
But the night breeze is so chilly...
You lonely bastard!
Dammit... Why does it have to be you
next to me instead of a raven-haired maiden?
Oh, look. Akashi-san came too.
See, over there.
Let me see!
She's in the engineering department,
so maybe she's designing
for Birdman or something.
Hey, maybe we should call it off for today...
I don't want to get Akashi-san
mixed up in this.
What are you saying? What happened to your pride as a Black Cupid?
Well, sure I have my pride, but to someone from the outside, this just looks like—
Your conviction will bend under the watchful eye of the world?
Well I, who have dedicated both my
body and soul, am not such a person.
Are you not here today precisely because you bear this loneliness and isolation?
They are the ones who
have lost sight of reality!
You must bring the hammer down upon those who have lost themselves among frivolous dreams!
Now, without further ado!
Hear ye, hear ye!
We are the ones who hinder love!
We will now rain the heavens down upon you merrymaking ladies and gentlemen!
"Id...iot..."
Yes, we may be idiots,
but you should watch out for us!
Bottle rockets are for the purpose of shooting up into the night sky.
Doing things like holding them
in your hand, aiming them at people,
or using them over rivers to bomb people having a peaceful party are quite prohibited.
Hold your ground! Counterattack!
Oh?
You damn barbarians!
That's one shallow river!
We're gonna smack you good!
Hey, Ozu, they're not all out!
Hey!
Since I met Ozu, it had just been
cutting, cutting, and more cutting
the red threads that stretched across the circle like at Yasui-konpiragu.
At these activities, Ozu was ingenious, and there were soon villainous rumors
that there was no personal information we didn't know and make use of,
and that we would scatter oil
and then light fires,
and whether or not
that was true, it spread around,
making it an environment
where we were set up as guys
who constantly enjoyed blazing
scenes of carnage inside the circle,
like some incarnation of evil,
a disgrace among all Homo sapiens.
Even after we were kicked out of the circle,
we did not let our activities slacken.
We expanded globally,
cloaked as gods of death,
and the evil name of the Black Cupids
roared throughout the land.
If there was a maiden in love in the East,
we'd say, "Give up on that freak,"
or if a man in the West worried about one-sided love,
we'd advise, "Just give up, it's no use."
If the spark of love was kindled in the South,
we'd immediately pour water on it,
and it's said love in the North is impossible to begin with.
After one victim almost drowned me
in the canals of Lake Biwa,
with the boarding house surrounded, I could
barely breathe at a manga café in Kitashirakawa,
when I spoke too frankly to a passerby on Konoe Street and made them cry...
But I didn't lose. I couldn't lose.
Even though I was sure that losing would have let me and everyone else be happier!
Except for Ozu!
I couldn't care less if he's happy!
As I was walking, catching my breath
after having run all the way to Kiyamachi,
under the overhang of someone's house,
I was caught by an old woman who
emitted a suspiciously ghoulish aura.
This unplaceable aura was persuasive, and thinking logically,
there was no way that the fortune-telling of a creature who emits such an aura
could be anything but spot on.
What do you want to know?
Your face is a face of extreme impatience...
You are dissatisfied.
I feel that you are not blessed by a situation
in which you can make the most of your talents.
Yes, that's exactly right!
I can sense your fiercely earnest talent.
Quickly did I tip my hat
to the old woman's keen insight.
To perceive my good sense and talents in an instant, and yet be so very unassuming,
like how a master always hides their true ability.
It made me even forget where I was.
Anyway, I sense there is an opportunity
you can't let pass by.
An opportunity?
As in an excellent chance.
Yes, I know what it means...
This opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
You must grab this opportunity and act on it.
It's still somewhat vague.
Can you be more specific?
And if you do not!
You will walk this life as you are now,
ever unchanging.
That'll be 1,000 yen.
But you haven't answered anything yet!
Playing the little lost lamb?
A friend of yours, Ozu-kun?
You shameless bastard!
How the hell are you popular all of a sudden?
Now that's just uncalled for.
Force-feeding me such a bundle of fungi?
What is with these ribbed bits?
She's the dental hygienist at the dentist I go to.
She looked totally drunk
and asked me out for drinks.
Dentist?
And what about you?
I bet you've never had a young lady stick her fingers in your mouth in your entire life.
Don't bring me down to your level.
Oh, yeah? I know you visited the god of matchmaking at the Shimogamo Shrine.
I just wanted to do it once for fun!
Speaking of which,
what do you think of Akashi-san?
In other words,
it's between you and Ozu-kun.
What do I think?
I had thought I was the only person
unfortunate enough
to actually be able to comprehend
a human being as dumb as yourself, but...
Shush, you.
I think she might go out with you.
This is an opportunity!
Now, look here.
I'd much rather have a beautiful angel-like raven-haired maiden
than someone who is able to
comprehend a person such as myself.
Why so selfish?
Don't tell me you're still hung up on being dumped by Kohinata-san as a freshman?
Say not that name in my presence.
Then I'll become happy in your place.
I'll take this opportunity.
Now, see here.
Akashi-san is not interested in you.
Don't give me that depressed look.
I pray for your victory.
Shut up!
Thanks to you, I've wasted my perfectly lovely college life!
Oh? I think you're also to blame for that.
After all, it doesn't matter which path you take.
You'll keep ending up
right where you are now.
At any rate, once I met you,
I put all my efforts into making you no good.
Why do you haunt me so?
It's the way I show my love!
We're connected by the
black thread of fate, after all.
The Japan Trench
A chill went down my spine
as a fearsome phantom rose into my mind.
Senpai, if you want to eat any more, please hurry.
Akashi-san, why are you here?
You really are pretty dense, aren't you?
This is the usual place
for the after-party, yes?
The Birdman Circle is camped out over there.
I haven't eaten meat in a while,
so if you don't mind...
Meat after a party? Do they have
no pride as an agricultural people?
Where's Ozu?
He already ran out the back door.
You escape too, Senpai.
That bastard's left me behind again!
I'll handle the bill, so head out the back.
That's what I came to say.
I'm in your debt!
Forget about the debt,
just keep your promise.
Never mind. Hurry and leave.
I have to get back.
I met Akashi-san the previous year during
a part-time job at the Shimogamo used book fair.
A year younger than I, said to be in the engineering department,
and meticulously prepared for
anything and everything she did,
it felt like just one stare from her eyes
would make a shoplifter stay their hand.
Oh, really?
What do you do on vacations, Akashi-san?
Why do I have to tell you
something like that?
After that, she was not someone
who was asked her weekend plans.
I sent her off a fiery cheer of
"You just keep doing things your own way!"
Good evening.
What are you doing?
Don't just barge into my room!
How dare you just stroll on in...
It's a castella.
You can have it, so chill out.
You giving someone something? That's rare...
You can't get any lonelier than
eating a giant castella all by yourself.
Pining for a taste of someone's love...
Get out! I'm busy!
Is this really necessary?
Leave!
He probably came to visit the person
in this boarding house known as "the Master."
This castella is surely the leftovers.
Nevertheless, just as Ozu said,
a castella like this is to be eaten with someone.
Most definitely not Ozu.
Perhaps with Akashi-sa—
Even I was surprised that
Akashi-san's name came to mind.
Could that strange man who called himself a god
and said he was heading out to Izumo
to decide the relationships between man
and woman seriously be telling the truth?
Kannazuki. In other words,
the tenth lunar month.
The myriad gods gather at Izumo, leaving vacant all the lands.
Izumo
This is quite well known. Even I know that.
And among the gods, there's got to be some of suitable peculiarity. That is not the issue.
What I have often pondered is for what reason
all those gods would gather at Izumo.
And written right there it says that, at Izumo, after a boisterous and outspoken argument,
the myriad gods decide the relationships
between man and woman!
Don't they have anything better to do?
Now that I'd ascertained the truth,
it would be best for me to climb the stairs
and see this god face to face.
But if that god from yesterday went...
"Ha ha, I got you good!"
...or something, I couldn't stand it.
I'd surely end up cursing myself and spending the second half of my life in a right mess.
Even if that man is really a god,
it's not like I'm burning with passionate love.
It's against my beliefs to seek the comfort
of a stranger from this transient loneliness.
Is it not because I scorn
those inexcusable students
who cannot bear the isolation and greedily seek out others,
that I ran to the name of limitless notoriety
as "one who hinders love"?
This guise of a barren,
agonizing, wretched life...
Haven't I finally reaped the victory close at hand
from the endless number of defeats?
Would I, the one who hinders love,
forgive myself for changing the way I live?
Or will it end with me
providing entertainment to the gods
as the spider's thread to which I cling snaps?
Then I'll become happy in your place.
Although I don't think Akashi-san would be fooled by a freaky finicky youkai like Ozu,
I feel like her compassion may be deep enough to find a monstrous man like him intriguing.
If this continues and Ozu and Akashi-san become friendly with each other,
this would no longer be
a problem of my own love.
It would become entangled with Akashi-san's future.
I felt like even my reasoning was
crumbling to pieces like the castella before me.
I'm not gonna lose!
I'm not gonna lose to pining for love!
The taste is definitely unmatched,
but, unfortunately,
no one knows where he'll set up.
It's a ramen stand that
comes and goes as it pleases.
You go there quite often, then, Senpai?
Well, I have a good nose.
When I'm hungry, if I cock my ear,
I can hear Neko Ramen's wind chime.
I would like to try eating there as well.
Let go! Let go, Akashi-san!
I s-s-squished it... I squished it...
Now, now, calm down.
I apologize. I am not fond of moths.
These are called Mochiguman, and they come in sets of five, but I have lost one.
Worry not! As this earth is round, you are sure to meet once again!
Or if you'd like, I'll help you search for it.
I'd rather you take me to Neko Ramen.
If that's what you want.
Then it's a promise.
Promise? Ah, that's it.
After careful analysis of all possible courses of action,
I was slow to reach a perfect conclusion.
Or rather, I'm a man who doesn't hesitate to analyze to the point
where a perfect conclusion becomes out of reach.
Analyzing the number of different patterns
of Akashi-san's life and my life,
I quickly came to a conclusion to who
should become happy and who should not.
But the most vexing question of all was whether I,
as one who had hindered the
path of love for countless others,
could at this juncture
change the way I live.
As a result of the life-or-death struggle
between love and reason that occurred within me,
I stumbled in my sleep-deprived state
to knock on door 210.
Yeah?
You can't give her to Ozu!
Give Akashi-san to me!
Right. Good, wait here a moment.
Oh? Understood, yes...
Meet me before 8 p.m. on the east side of the Kamo Bridge.
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Stopping on top of the bridge is dangerous!
Oh, so today is Gozan.
Now you will cross the Kamo Bridge.
When you do, Akashi-san will
come walking from the other side.
Strike up a conversation about something and ask her out on a rendezvous.
I can't! I refuse!
Stop your whining.
Something isn't right here!
Weren't you going to Izumo
to be a matchmaker?
This sort of preparation is also important.
This is nothing but a frontal attack!
Stop complaining and get out there.
Everything until now
is water under the bridge!
Now's the time to push forward
toward that rose-colored campus life!
Senpai, good evening.
You escaped safely last night?
Thanks to you, yeah...
Here for Gozan?
Yes, yes.
Bye!
That went well.
That's enough for today.
To come this far despite learning not even the slightest about the ways of romance!
This was plenty!
Oh, hey!
You just thought something like,
"That's enough for today," didn't you?
Don't defy the words of a god!
Hurry up and run along the path of love!
Are you saying this was all your plot?
You made a wish to the
god of matchmaking, right?
I don't want your help!
Now's the time to grab this opportunity!
If you don't make a serious move now, I'm jumping!
Wait a second!
How does my love life have
anything to do with you jumping?
I'm not too sure myself.
Ozu-san! The river is swollen.
You'll die if you jump in.
You damn traitor!
You've got nowhere to run, Ozu!
Revenge for the fireworks? But this is...
Ozu-senpai, have you done some more mischief?
You evil, good-for-nothing...
Ozu!
You're a friend of his?
Me? I don't know Ozu at all...
Don't!
I can't shake off the feeling of regret
for choosing the tennis circle Cupid in front of that fateful clock tower.
If I had chosen some other circle, I would have surely spent quite a different two years.
I might have grasped the mystical treasure known as rose-colored campus life.