No way I'm gonna let this end so easily...
Y-Yeah!
Class A wins.
What's going on? Rep?
Huh?
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Note:     What you're seeing here is a fantasy; not what's actually happening.
The ESB is over and a new morning has arrived.
Could these be...
Yeah, they're drawing boards and mats.
Thirteenth Period
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
And I thought cardboard boxes were the bottom of the barrel.
There's no end to the worse.
I never imagined this happening.
Sorry, Himeji.
Don't be. You really don't need to apologize.
I had a lot of fun from the ESB.
Himeji...
Cheer up, all of you!
It's not like we can do anything about losing.
These drawing boards are definitely usable.
Well, they say you can get used to living anywhere.
It's like we're in art class. It's not that bad.
What's the matter, Mizuki?
Well, umm...
I can't see the bottom of the board.
Where are you going, Minami?
Do you really need to ask? Of course I'm going to request another ESB!
Just give up, Shimada!
We're banned from doing so for another three months!
But... I just don't want to use these boards anymore!
Well, your breasts won't get in your way, so these are a perfect fit for-
My joints don't work that way!
Somehow I haven't felt this in a long time.
What do you mean "these are a perfect fit!?"
Almost... Almost... Just a little...
You're burning! You're on fire, Voyeur!
Wow, it got put out by his blood!
Oh, wow. Is that all it takes to bring you down, Voyeur?
Kudou...
I even wore a bra just for you today.
A really cute one.
So what?
The body never lies.
Don't worry! I feel for you, Voyeur!
Awaken!
Oh, sorry... I forgot that the bracelet broke.
A
Note • Voyeur
Where are you going, Voyeur!?
Please grant summoning permission to Akihisa.
For what reason?
To remove a bra.
I'm afraid I cannot, then.
So I guess that's as far as our strength goes.
Well, I guess so.
But I can't accept losing like that.
Well, a defeat is a defeat.
We focused more on pragmatism than scoring high on tests.
The same goes for them.
They were smart for attacking instead of being distracted by the situation.
We lost because we let our guard down.
But...
You can't change what has already happened.
Results are everything, after all.
What's the matter, Aki?
You said that effort is nothing but a means to an end, remember?
Yes, I do.
I couldn't do what I needed to do.
Perhaps I'm just an idiot after all...
Those who boast of their own efforts are the most foolish.
But having someone else praise you for your efforts isn't necessarily a bad thing.
Sis...
I believe you tried your very best.
You make me proud to be your sister.
Thank you, Sis...
It's all right to grieve over your defeat.
Don't people normally say to do the opposite?
It's important to admit when you've lost.
Not being able to do so makes it impossible for you to climb back up after a fall,
and even more impossible for you to move forward.
So go on ahead and grieve to your heart's extent.
But after you're done grieving, be sure to set your eyes upon your next goal and move toward it.
Okay.
I will comfort you as much as I can when you're grieving.
Would you rather sleep with me or take a bath with me?
No thanks...
Don't be like that.
We're related by blood.
That's exactly why I don't want to!
Once you're done grieving, move forward, huh?
Forward?
Does that possibly mean I could still do more?
All right, I've made my decision!
So we'll be taking a bath together, right?
No, I meant something else.
That's all for the ESB results.
Who is it?
Yoshii, what the hell are you doing here?
I have a request to make.
Please allow us to compete with class A one more time.
I'm afraid I'll have to turn that request down.
Just wait another three months.
We can't wait that long!
That's the rule. I can't break it.
Please!
I can't let it end like this! Please!
Consider it a request from the rest of us as well.
I cannot accept such a cowardly victory.
Even though we technically won,
I hate to admit it, but they had the upper hand during the fight.
Kinoshita... Kirishima...
You girls...
That victory is an insult to the top class that represents this school.
I don't think the rest of the classes will accept this so easily either, so...
I'll send in my request too.
Do you kids know why the Exam Summoning Battle system was implemented into our school?
I can't give way regarding the rules, but...
I still owe you a favor from when the system went berserk.
And I'm responsible for the fact that you were using the prototype bracelet.
I guess I can make an exception just this once if you're this serious about it.
Exception?
Do you really want to exchange facilities that bad?
If so, there are other means of achieving that.
What!?
A rematch with class A?
We really can?
That old bitch allowed it?
That's great, Akihisa!
Yeah...
Hell yeah! We'll beat them into the ground this time!
Let's hurry and form up a new plan.
Well, Yuuji... It's a bit different this time.
WHAT!?
You're going solo?
Yeah, against class A's rep in an exam battle.
Class A's rep? You mean Shouko?
We can't exchange facilities if I win,
but the principal promised to grant my request.
But you're going against the valedictorian!
Can you win?
Are you sure?
Don't worry, I won't pull you guys down with me.
Akihisa, so what'll happen if you lose?
The other side gets their wish granted-
If I win, you'll have to return my marriage contract.
It isn't yours!
You bastard!
"I won't pull you guys down with me." Yeah, right!
This is my life you're fucking with!
Life
That isn't important!
We're going on a honeymoon right after the match.
Hell no!
Yuuji, I want to make children with you.
Akihisa, you have to fucking win this, no matter what!
Shouko, take it easy on him, please!
I thought you said not to hold back?
Holy shit! My life is over!
So you're saying that I'm gonna lose for sure.
But I guess he's right...
They granted us a rematch, but there's no way I can beat Kirishima by myself...
Mr. Stupid!
Oh, Hazuki.
Here, this is a present for you.
Wow, you baked cookies!
I learned it from home economics class.
Though I don't think they're that good...
Thank you very much, Hazuki.
Yay! So do you feel a little more confident now?
I see. Thanks.
I feel a lot more energetic now.
These are good.
You'd make a great wife.
Thank you!
I didn't really quite get the hang of it, so I burned a few batches.
But I didn't give up and kept trying and I succeeded!
All right!
What's the matter?
I'll make sure I don't give up either.
It's not like I have anything to lose, so I'll give it everything I've got.
Thank you, Hazuki.
You're welcome!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Aki.
I don't know what I can do with the time I have...
But I'll try my best to get even a single point more.
This is a specially permitted rematch between class A's rep, Shouko Kirishima, and class F's Akihisa Yoshii.
We'll go by the "Sudden Death Rule."
Sudden Death Rule.
Sudden Death Rule
The exact same question will be given to the contestants,
and they are required to solve it at the same time.
The battle ends whenever one of the
contestants answers a question wrong.
The loser will be the one who answered it wrong.
In other words, whoever's the first to get a question wrong loses.
We're dealing with an endless series of questions here,
but they'll keep getting harder and harder as they go along.
That means the beginning will be decisive.
Akihisa...
All right, let's begin!
Good luck, Akihisa.
Yuuji...
I believe that you can win.
You have to believe in yourself and do your best!
FIGHT ON!
He only cheers people on if it benefits himself.
Question 1:
Please answer the question with an idiom that contains the given meaning.
"Failing at something you're good at."
That's an easy question.
Unless Akihisa is literally mentally
retarded, he can't screw this one up.
He looks like he's having trouble!
What!?
What about this?
Even monkeys fall from trees
Quandoque bonus dormitat Homerus
Yippee!
Both answers are correct.
Don't fucking scare me, bro!
I was nervous! I couldn't help it!
Question 2:
How do you calculate the area of a circle?
Radius × Radius × Pi
Yeah! She got it wrong!
Wait, why!?
How did you even get into high school?
Radius × Radius × Pi
Next up, question 3.
It's edible, but still a long way from what it should be...
I bet Aki is trying his best now.
It'd be great if I could cook
him something as a reward.
I've got to try my best as well.
Q-Question 30...
When was the 12 level ranking
system of officials implemented?
Both answers are correct.
Good going, bro!
You can do it!
I managed to make it this far because I had a feeling these questions would show up...
She's not gonna screw up that easily...
I can't let my guard down for even one question.
Question 31:
Who was the conquerer that began his
conquest of the Persian Empire in 334BC
and defeated the last king of the Achaemenid Empire?
Another history question...
This is a tough one.
Akihisa...
Alexander the Great
Alexander the Third
Both answers are correct.
Oh, he got it right!
Good job, Aki!
I'll never get this question about
Alexander the Great wrong ever again.
The easy questions are coming to an end.
Answering is only going to get harder and harder for Akihisa.
Akihisa...
Question 32:
The name of Japan's first era was "Taika."
Which year of the Common Era did the reform of the Taika era take place?
That question is...
That's a gimme.
Both of them will get this one correct.
The showdown is delayed until the next question.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
S-So when exactly did the Taika reforms happen?
What!?
You dumbass! How could you forget after we've been through all that crap!?
That's exactly why I'm confused!
Don't fuck with me, you fucking faggot!
I only remember it according to the "uneventful reforms"...
"Uneventful reforms"... 645AD? 625AD?
Which does "uneventful" refer to?
Uneventful reforms... Uneventful... Uneventful...
Akihisa...
Aki.
Which one? Which one is it!?
It's all over if I get this wrong.
Aki...
Akihisa...
God dammit!
Aki?
Akihisa?
I'll fucking murder him for giving up so easily...!
He, he hasn't yet!
That's...
That's Striker Sigma V!
Go!
Stop it, you dumbass!
Their answers are different!
What!?
Shit, my life's over...
The winner is class F's Akihisa Yoshii.
What the hell!?
I guessed it right...
Good job, Aki!
Nice one, Akihisa!
Akihisa!
Shouko, what happened?
I made a promise with you...
...that I'd never forget.
I'm sorry.
Moreover, I already got what I wanted.
What?
I'm going to go register now.
How the hell did you...!?
A kind soul gave it to me.
Don't tell me...
No harm in doing a good deed here and there.
I can't believe you won.
Principal...
As promised, I'll grant you your wish.
Thank you very much.
Wish... What did you ask from the principal, Akihisa?
Well...
All right then, Himeji.
You're free to take the placement exam again.
Akihisa, don't tell me you...
This is the reason I declared the ESB to begin with.
Even if we don't deserve it ourselves,
we want you to study some-
where that's fitting for you.
Then...
You can now go to the class that matches your ability.
Isn't that great, Himeji?
No... Akihisa...
Why?
Akihisa, is this what you really want?
It's gonna feel a little lonely, but this is the best choice to make.
Really?
Thank you, Akihisa.
All right, begin.
A lot of people in this world thinks that grades equate to everything.
But no matter what, a person's ability can only go so far.
Those who only care about themselves won't be able to live a fulfilling life.
When I was a kid, we all helped each other out as a matter of course.
Something achieved through only one
person's effort isn't really worth that much.
If they understand that, then I can rest easy.
Time's up.
Looks good.
Now you'll be able to go to class A.
Thank you.
I'll give you your results later.
You can go home now.
Excuse me!
What's the matter?
I messed something up big time.
Could you allow me to change that?
The time allotted is already over.
You can't change your answers.
But...
Don't worry, I'm sure you did fine.
Please!
I have to... I have to amend that no matter what!
Good morning, Aki.
Morning, Akihisa.
Morning.
Good morning.
Yoshii...
Hey, Kirishima.
We went to get registered, but we got rejected.
Shouko Image
County Clerk
According to the Japanese Civil Code, the male must be at least 18 when he registers for marriage.
That's unfortunate...
Akihisa.
Aki, have you seen Mizuki yet?
Nope, not yet.
Really...
It's going to be hard for you two to see each other now that she's in a different class.
I guess.
Have you heard, Akihisa?
About what?
Himeji's score on the placement exam will definitely get her into class A.
Really?
Are you sure that's fine?
Yeah.
Himeji doesn't belong in class F.
She should be studying with the
amazing facilities class A has to offer.
If that's what you think, then okay.
But Akihisa, I don't think things are going to go your way.
Good morning, Akihisa.
Himeji... Why are you here? Did you forget something?
No, this is where I belong.
But aren't you accepted into class A?
Well, actually... I forgot to write my name.
So I got a zero on the test.
That's why I'm here back in class F.
Himeji...
Let's have fun like we used to, okay?
What's the matter, Aki?
Joys of tear?
That's great, Akihisa.
Happy end.
That goddamned old bitch!
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
You bitch!
Mango-chan was too lazy to actually translate this but it's a bunch of words saying that season two of this show was announced.
Watch your mouth, you little brat.
That's not fair!
Why did Himeji get a zero?
Well, obviously because she
forgot to write her name down.
You're kidding me!
She was the only one taking the test, so it should be obvious that it's her!
Are you guys blind!?
You idiot!
Wow, I never thought I'd live long
enough to hear you call me an idiot.
Anyway, give Himeji's points back!
If you can't, then let her take the placement exam again!
I'm starting to think you're a real idiot.
Huh?
What a dumbass.
You're stupid.
Idiot.
Stupid.
You're truly one giant idiot.
Idiot.
Akihisa, you're really stupid, aren't you?
You're the last one I'd expect that from... Why?
Stupid!