I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
My feelings have become stronger,
since what I've always believed in is resonating more than ever now.
I don't want to stop
trying to communicate,
because I can't stand it when
someone is left in the dark.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
I can't stop thinking about her...
The girl who looked my age,
who had such deep, beautiful eyes...
I'm sure we'll just fight if we ever meet again, but...
But...
Episode 6
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Knock it off, already!
Ever since that day, you keep spacing out when we're talking!
I-I'm sorry, Arisa-chan...
Don't apologize!
If talking to us really is that boring,
then just go ahead and zone out by yourself!
Let's go, Suzuka!
Arisa-chan...
Nanoha-chan...
It's all right, Suzuka-chan.
It really was my fault this time.
I don't think that's really true...
I think Arisa-chan went completely overboard just now.
I'll go talk to her for a bit.
I'm sorry about this...
I guess I made her angry...
I'm sorry, Arisa-chan...
Arisa-chan... Arisa-chan!
Arisa-chan!
What?
I kind of understand how you feel,
but you can't get angry
over things like that.
But it really annoys me!
It's so obvious that she's worried about something!
It's written all over her face that she's
in trouble and doesn't know what to do!
But... no matter how many times we ask
her about it, she won't tell us a thing.
She's lying when she says
there's nothing wrong!
Everybody keeps secrets,
even from their closest friends.
If Nanoha-chan wants
to keep it a secret,
don't you think all we
can do is wait for her?
That's what annoys me so much!
I'm sure we could help her,
even just a little!
Whatever it is, I'm sure...
Even if we can't do anything about it...
at the very least, we can all worry about it together!
Arisa-chan, you really do care a lot
about Nanoha-chan, don't you?
Of course I do!
Because she was there for me,
I wasn't alone anymore...
That's right...
It was the same with me...
Because Nanoha-chan was there,
we were all able to become friends...
Nanoha-chan, we're sorry,
we both have lessons today, so...
You'll be gone till late tonight, right?
Take care and do your best.
Arisa-chan...
Ah, I'm sure everything will turn
out all right, Nanoha-chan!
Yeah. Thanks, Suzuka-chan.
Now that I think about it...
it's been a while since I walked home alone.
I guess I'll make a stop before I go home...
because I don't want anyone
to see my face right now.
When we all first met...
I was a lot weaker
than I am now,
and I could never say
what was on my mind.
No matter what anyone
said or did to me,
I could never stand up to them...
And I think I was a really awful kid.
I was selfish, and a bully.
I always made fun of our classmates
and joked about everything...
because I was a weak person.
Ah... that's mine...
U-Um...
I was weak back then, too,
and I couldn't say what I wanted to...
That it was really important to me,
and if you could please give it back...
Even after you told me to stop, I didn't listen...
because I thought that if I listened
to what someone else had to say...
I'd lose for some reason.
What was it Nanoha-chan said back then?
"Does that hurt?"
"It hurts a lot more when someone takes
something precious away from you!"
That's right...
After that, I got into a big fight
with Arisa-chan, didn't I?
And the one who stopped us was...
The incredibly quiet girl who decided to be brave.
Stop it!
Back then... it was because
I was so desperate...
After that, we slowly began to talk more
and more to each other, didn't we?
Yeah... just the three of us.
So? What did you want from me,
after bringing up that old story?
I think you already know.
I at least understand that she doesn't
want the two of us to worry about her,
which also means that there's probably not much we can do to help.
If all we can do is wait, then...
I'll just stay angry while I'm waiting!
Angry over the sadness of not
being able to understand her feelings...
and at myself for not being
able to help my best friend!
You really are stubborn.
Hmph!
I see... so you got into a fight.
That's not it. Arisa-chan just got
mad because I was zoning out.
She's one of your best
friends, isn't she?
Yeah. Almost since
I first started school.
Here you go.
This is your half.
I don't have cram school today,
so I should be able to do some Jewel
Seed hunting, at least until dinnertime.
Let's do our best.
Yeah, let's...
The food in this world...
Well, it's not that bad!
Now then, let's see what my little princess is up to.
Oops, can't forget this!
You haven't touched your food again!
That's no good... you have to eat.
I had some of it...
I'm fine, don't worry.
Shall we get going, then?
I've been able to get a rough idea of
where the next Jewel Seed should be.
And I don't want to keep Mother waiting for too long...
Well... you are my
master after all, Fate...
and because I'm your familiar,
if you ask me to go, I'll go, but...
Oh, we can go after you finish eating, if you'd like.
Th-That's not what I meant.
I'm worried about you, Fate.
Using wide area search magic
uses up a lot of stamina...
yet you're hardly eating anything,
and barely resting...
and your wounds aren't
exactly light, either.
I'll be fine, because I'm strong.
Fate...
Now then, let's go.
Mother's waiting for me.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha!
Hey, Kyouya...
about Nanoha-chan...
Has she been worried about something recently?
That's how she looked to me earlier,
and Suzuka's pretty
worried about her, too...
I wonder... She has been going
out a lot at night recently...
I might be prying a bit too much,
but do you think maybe I should try talking to her?
Thank you for the offer, but...
I don't really think she'll talk about it.
So I'm no good?
Ah, that's not it!
That's definitely not it.
I didn't mean that she won't talk to you specifically,
but that she probably won't talk to anyone about it.
She's always been like that whenever
she'd be worried about something.
I see...
Well, I'm sure there's nothing to worry about.
I'm sure she'll be able to
figure it out on her own.
I see.
It has so many features,
it'll surprise you every time! Just look!
Ah... I might be out of time...
I should head home.
Don't worry about it. I'll stay around
here and search a little longer.
Okay... but will you be all right by yourself, Yuuno-kun?
Yup. Go home and get
some dinner, okay?
Okay.
Arisa-chan and Suzuka-chan should be on
their way home from their lesson right now...
You have no
new messages.
I'm pretty sure it's
somewhere around here,
but I can only get
a rough reading.
Yeah, I bet. Searching through
all this garbage must be a pain.
This is a bit rough,
but I'll force it to activate by
pouring mana into the area.
Ah, wait a second.
I'll do that for you.
Will you be all right?
You'll be pretty drained afterwards...
Just whose familiar do you think I am?
Then, I'm counting on you.
Here goes!
A forced activation spell inside the city?!
This is bad, I gotta hurry!
Raising Heart, please!
Found it!
But it looks like she's nearby, too.
Let's finish quickly, then.
Bardiche!
Sealing Form, Set up.
Nanoha, can you see the activated Jewel Seed?
Yeah. It's really close.
That other girl's really close, too.
Seal it before she does!
Got it!
Lyrical Magical!
Jewel Seed Serial XIX!
Seal!
Device Mode.
Stop it!
When I first met Arisa-chan and
Suzuka-chan, we weren't friends...
because we couldn't talk with each other...
because we couldn't understand each other...
Arisa-chan got angry with me this morning
because I couldn't tell her
what was on my mind...
All right! Nanoha, hurry up and capture it!
Like we'll let her!
Because we both have the same goal...
we might not be able to
avoid fighting like this...
But I want to know!
Last time, we weren't able to
introduce ourselves properly...
I'm Nanoha! Takamachi Nanoha!
I'm a third-grader at
Seishou Private Elementary School.
Scythe Form.
Why does she have such lonely eyes?
Flier Fin.
Sending mail to Nanoha?
Yeah. Telling her we just
finished our lesson.
Well, let's get going.
Ah, yeah! Wait a second.
NEW MESSAGE
T9 Word     SEND     Options
To:  Takamachi Nanoha
l
\
/
-
I just got done with my
lesson. I'm going to go
home and have dinner
now. Arisa-chan isn't all
too upset, so everything
is fine. Nanoha-chan, I
hope you're okay.
I hope you get through
what's troubling you soon.
Do your best. We'll always be
cheering you on. Suzuka.
Sending
message...
Flash Move.
Divine Shooter.
Defencer.
Fate-chan!
You said nothing would
change by just talking,
but I'm sure there are things we can't get across without talking!
We might not be able to do anything
about competing with each other like this,
but I can't stand fighting like this
without knowing anything about you!
Originally, I was just helping Yuuno-kun search for the Jewel Seeds,
because he needed to gather them
and return them to where they belong!
So I was there to help him!
It was just a coincidence that I ended up helping him,
but now I'm gathering the
Jewel Seeds because I want to!
Because I don't want the people
around me or my city to be in danger!
That's... why I'm doing this!
I...
Fate! You don't have to answer her!
You don't have to answer some random person just because they were nice to you!
She's just trying to use you!
We're just here to
capture the Jewel Seeds!
Nanoha!
I'll be fine!
Suzuka, what's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing...
You have no
new messages.
Geez, I'm starving.
Let's head back home already.
Ah, yeah.
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
An explosion that big...
this is seriously dangerous!
But... Mother's waiting, so...
The true nature of the
Jewel Seeds, and a new mage!
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 7
A Third Mage!?
Episode Seven:
Lyrical Magical, I won't lose!