Commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is everyone.
Hello everyone!
Um, Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika final episode,
My Best Friend audio commentary shall begin!
With the role of Madoka, it's Yuuki Aoi!
And—...
Um, I have come here again, it's Urobuchi Gen.
(lol)
And!
Ah—
Aoki Ume... is me.
It is!
(lol)
Cute! ＞＜
You're cute right from the beginning.
...
And!
Ah—
Um, Series Director Miyamo–Miyamoto.
Yes, I look forward to working with you—
I look forward to working with you.
Look forward.
And with the role of Akemi Homura, it's Saitou Chiwa.
And (lol)
I look forward to working with you!
I look forward to working with you! *clapclap*
Look forward~
So like this, on the final episode...
we feature the staff-sama.
Yes!
Mou, I don't know what to ask.
desu yo~
It's a pretty big crowd, isn't it?
Ne~!
Right, right.
Yes!
Right before this, all the actresses gathered together.
That's pretty flashy, isn't it.
It was a set of mahou shoujo.
What do we ask this time?
What to ask, we can really ask anything, after all...
That's right.
What's coming my way? I'm a little bit fearful.
(lol)
Yeah...
Well, we're on the final episode, um, what do we ask first, Ao-chan?
I wonder what I want to ask...
I wonder what I want to ask~!
There are a lot of things I want to ask, though!
A lot of it is stuff I can't put into words correctly, though...
Um—
Was this type of ending-style for the final episode decided on from the very beginning?
Ah, that's right.
Well, for the scenario itself, there weren't any major alterations.
Yeah.
Um, right...
For the scenario itself, it was pretty much entirely used.
All together, there were a large number of canon-style scenes.
Ne? Stuff like "A space with nothing in it" and "In space" weren't exactly written.
(lol)
Ahh, is that right!
The ones who had a hard time were the people who made the content, though.
(lol)
(lol) "How's that?"
We have a person who here's really laughing about it, too!
Nah, I have to truly praise them.
(lol)
So then, what kind of feeling did that script have?
Right, well Sasaki-san created quite a bit of the content too, but...
笹木信作 (Sasaki Shinsaku) - Storyboard for episodes 4, 6, 10, and 12.
Before Madoka☆ Magika, he was mostly known for work with Studio Ghibli, as the key animator for films such as Mononoke Hime.
Well, um... it was basically like "What do we do? What do we do?" (lol)
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm truly sorry for the trouble.
Ah, I don't mind, I don't mind.
I didn't make it easy on anyone, mou (lol)
Nah, you gave plenty of guidance, you know.
Nah, even if you say that... Yeah...
Somehow um, Madoka☆ Magika's sekaikan... including backgrounds and such, they're a bit unique, right?
They're different from an ordinary everyday style. Somehow, there are a lot of wide open areas, aren't there?
That's right, ne.
Was that something that was understood clearly in the concept, from the beginning?
The wide open areas are, um...
Well, the fact we wanted them was already established, but it was very unclear to what extent.
For that part, really... Inu Curry-san had their influence in it.
Yeah.
Amazing, they're very charming.
Mou, t–this then white background comes, ne~
That's right, ne!
Well, it has that "Final episode!" feeling, you know?
Like "There's no opening!"
Truly! Right, right, right.
Amazing, isn't it?
Ah, then Madoka's final, um, that...
Her request, was it decided from the very beginning that she'd erase witches?
That's right, ne. Yeah.
So that's right...
Ehh~
Ah by the way, in everyone's opinion, do you feel that Madoka's final wish was "correct"?
Well, that's right... personally, I don't think that it is mistaken.
Mm! Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
For a middle school girl, it's a considerably significant thing.
It's amazing!
That's right, ne!
That's what I think, though.
Yeah...
(lol)
Ume-sensei, what do you think about it?
Really it's like "She really thought about this!"
She saw various things when tagging along to defeat witches, and such.
She had a lot of various types of conversations, too, I think...
Really, she came to properly comprehend various things within herself by thinking a lot, I feel.
It's extremely heavy, isn't it?
Then somehow, everyone sort of gathers together like this to discuss Madoka's decision, right?
Was this like... companionship?
Well, that's right... she makes her wish, and then speaks with the people who have nothing to do with space and time.
"Ah, this is very amazing!"
Ahh, I got the notebook back!
Something like a final farewell.
Ah (lol)
(lol)
That's pretty embarrassing for me, isn't it!?
Miyamoto-san, what do you think of Madoka's wish?
Ah, I think it's brilliant.
She doesn't really save the future of the world or the universe, but...
She's just saving mahou shoujo.
I think "This is nice."
Ahh, that's right, ne.
Ao-chan, what do you think of it personally?
Always acting as Madoka.
Me?
I think it's a wish that would've never happened without Homura-chan.
Ah, really? ♡
Well, that's true from the standpoint of the settei too, isn't it?
That's right.
Yeah.
Somehow, this is...
A wish that couldn't have been done it weren't for Homura-chan's repeated worlds before this, and wanting to protect the world...
That's why, it could be done by having someone as a companion who you trusted.
I think so, so it's a pretty cruel, yet very wonderful wish, I think.
(lol)
... Amazing.
When writing the scenario, I was wondering "Is it okay to write such a flashy thing?"
This part is amaz—
(lol)
(lol) That's!
It was a bit on my mind, though...
"Ehh, when they make the content what're they going to do? Mmm—!"
Somehow they didn't become the witches of the world.
Right, right, right.
She gives closure to mahou shoujo.
Really, all the content I wanted was done...
Ah, right right!
But my first time seeing this, there was a conversation with everyone like "Ah, so there's actually tons of mahou shoujo around the world!"
Ne?
It isn't just a story limited to the bounds of Japan.
Nah, QB-san is world-wide. (WWQB)
Ne~?
QB is all over the place, huh?
All over. Yeah.
Uwaaah~!
Scary~!
Amazing.
Then when you understand that everyone was fighting...
This, too, brings about a lot of thought somehow, doesn't it?
It makes you think.
If it was just us fighting, then it'd sort of be like "Well, what about the rest of the world?"
Ne?
So it's like "Ah, I see, throughout the entire world everyone was fighting..."
Ne~?
That's an amazing thing, isn't it?
Then she saves them one by one.
All of the mahou shoujo of the past, too, right?
The past and the future, all of them, you know.
Right.
Around the world.
Right—
But somehow, you know seeing the mahou shoujo of the past, like Jean d'Arc... that deeply moved me!
"So this does come!?" I thought.
Ne? You thought that might have happened, right?
I thought about it a bit, yeah!
I think that is amazing.
I see...
The art somehow gets sublime, it's deeply moving to me (lol)
Yaa, Madoka-san is doing some hard labor, huh?
(lol)
Since she has to go one by one, you know.
She splits up though, you know.
Iya—
Mm, amazing I really love Ao-chan's warm style of acting here...
Mm, so kind.
That's right, I didn't want to overdo the megami feel...
goddess
Somehow, I thought "If she were a girl, this would be painful."
Somehow, from a story standpoint I thought it might be good if she didn't feel too adult-like,
I thought that the art would surely feel a lot softer.
I saw it was extremely soft and there was that bright light!
That image—
It worked out.
Right (lol)
Then, that's amazing.
It was time to stop being immature.
Did that...
Ya, she suddenly becomes an adult...
These frames have some pretty cool art, huh.
It's quite moving, isn't it?
Ne?
It's cool, ne?
Right!
Yeah.
Truly~
Somehow, you know... I had really wanted to see this sort of thing.
(lol)
She has such a megami-feeling.
Yeah.
Homura-chan is constantly bleeding though (lol)
It's flowing out.
(lol)
Somehow, Homura is...
Um, before this, during the commentary with everyone, all of the actresses, I didn't get to talk about this enough, but...
Really in episode 11, I had that feeling of "It's the first time Homura has confessed to Madoka!"
Those long lines about "I came from the future, you know."
I really love that part.
Then, the Homura that I had been doing up until that point said everything there...
But really Homura is Homura, and her words would stop mid sentence.
That's right, ne~
Somehow it's like dot dot dot [...].
And she does that hug, you know.
"You are..."
Right.
"To me, you are..."
That dot dot dot.
So it's like "Just say it!", but...
She can't just say it, that Homura's feelings... I felt like they all came out right there, after so long...
Anyways, somehow it's really... personally, somehow...
I think that probably Homura conveyed everything that she wanted to. Maybe not all by words, but she conveyed it.
So then, surely, Madoka chose this type of end...
She was trusting Homura in doing so. There is cruelty in it, but she was leaving the future to Homura...
Somehow, amazing, I feel like that requires more trust than anything else.
Somehow, it's like "You're my beloved!"
(lol)
It sort of has that feeling though. Regarding that,
how was the feeling in that?
Right, it was originally thought that this will end as a "Madoka and Homura" story, yeah.
Especially around episode 10 that's true, yeah.
The thing from just before, the words that Homura uses in episode 11 where she conveys everything...
Then just after this, Madoka is like...
"Everything... truly." Where she able to see everything, right?
During that moment, I was happy (lol)
Right, me too!
"Thank goodness!"
Good for you, Homura!
I certainly thought that.
(lol)
This clothing!
Cute! ＞＜
That's right, truly when everyone saw this... it was deeply moving.
For that design,
we had worries if it'd be okay since it only makes an entrance once, but...
Afterwards it became quite an existence, huh?
Amazing, isn't it?
Just from that one cut, too.
That's cause it's Hyper Ultimate Madoka!
(lol)
Right, right, right.
I was moved just from the screenplay!
That was written there, wasn't it?
I might have had something to do with that, you know.
No, no, when I saw that, I was like "What's that going to be like!?"
When I saw the settei scenario I was like   ( ﾟ∀ﾟ)ﾉ UWAAAA~
Then after the actual thing I was like   ヾ( ﾟДﾟ)ﾉ゛ HUWAAAAA!
Right, right, right.
That skirt is like a whole universe, huh? (lol)
Everyone really, really wanted to see that, at the time!
There's a whole world under that skirt!
Amazing.
Somehow, seeing "Hyper Ultimate Madoka" in the settei, it was something like the ultimate weapon Madoka.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah, that's right, ne.
It was left there when I was writing eccentrically, yeah.
It was quite like "This is it."
How did the staff work with that?
(lol)
How did you know what to do?
What was it? How was it decided to be like that?
The design was done by Aoki-sensei.
Yeah.
Is that right?
The clothing, right.
Like the clothing and that hairstyle, and the colors and such.
I just did what I wanted.
I thought it might be troublesome when actually animating...
But I was told to do as I pleased, so...
What's this, was it troublesome?
That's right, Kishida-san really gave it his all, I think.
It was like "how to do this part?" and "How should her hair flow?", Then...
He was constrantly drawing pages worth of sketches...
For just that one cut.
(lol)
（　・∀・） Hiii!
It's very extravagant, after all.
Extravagant!
Truly.
Drawing that art!
This kira-kira scene with both of us, you know.
During our after recording sessions, it had a leopard print design.
(lol)
(lol) Really. It was like "So it's a leopard print design...?"
Like right here, right?
Yeah.
Even though it was a leopard print design, it was supposed to be kira-kira.
It was supposed to be kira-kira, right, Ao-chan?
Right, "shining" was written...
"Leopard print?" (lol)
In the final version, this will be a bit uncensored.
Ohhh!
Half uncensored, though.
Is that right...
Uncensored (lol)
Mou, for us, truly, somehow...
The art acts as a guidepost.
So for us, during the after recording the art was acting as a guidepost...
Mou, anyways...
It's just for a short time, but these two are able to experience each other's feelings, so...
At the end, Madoka is able to see everything, but...
Homura was somehow... properly still thinking of Madoka, mou...
"What's with this!?"
"Just how dedicated are you!?" I thought.
But she's doing such a kind thing, yet she's basically telling Homura-chan "You alone can definitely not forget about me."
"Understand that!"
It's somehow very cruel of her, isn't it?
You might be able to think that!
Right. But, I thought "So the smile she gives is this gentle?"
It's relieving, isn't it...
Ahh.
(lol) Sorry.
I'm going to cry watching this, though...
Truly... somehow, ne...
For Madoka, around episode 1, she would basically only say things like "I don't help anyone and I have no worth," you know...
Well, that's right, ne.
You couldn't say that she didn't help anyone now (lol)
(lol)
I'd say she changed the world.
That's right.
Somehow... she was able to become an extremely special existence,
because of Homura's emotions she became a special existence herself...
It's truly thanks to Homura, I think.
Now she's leaving her own traces behind (lol)
(lol)
That's right, she doesn't want her to forget about her, right?
Isn't that actually more lonely!?
That's what I think.
That's right, amazingly, ne...
I sort of feel like this was able to be done because of friendship between girls. Somehow, you know...
During episode 10 I believe? I talked about this with Ao-chan a little bit, but...
Umm...
If this were a ren-ai relationship, it would have changed a little bit, I think.
That's right, ne.
If this were a girl and a boy, I believe that they'd think of themselves a little bit more, like "I want them back!"
But these two are constantly thinking about each other. Madoka in a bigger way, though...
Seeing that sort of thing, it's sort of like a girl's—Especially a main girl's...
It isn't really putting yourself in a pretty place, but what to say...
It's like "She's a good person."
Conversely if they were guys, they wouldn't be together like those girls, right?
It'd have a bit more of a rough feeling.
In place of that feeling, it'd be something like "GOOD LUCK!"
Ahhh.
Right, right, right.
Just like Gurren Lagann, you know.
(lol)
The way they're hugging is a bit girly, I think...
That's right, somehow...
Somehow, generally you'd say that guys have a stronger sense of justice than girls, but...
For girls around this age, they haven't developed their sense of justice yet, so they can become an adult at any moment,
because when they get hurt, they grow up through that pain.
Why do you understand that when you're a guy?
(lol)
That's right,
it sort of makes me think "Urobuchi-san is...?"
Right, right.
Then the sense of dependence that girls around this age have, too, you know.
Somehow, that's there too. It's amazing, you know.
Well those kinds of girls are loved, they score points with the guys, you know.
That's why she helps the whole world.
Ah... ha!
So profound~!
(lol)
I see!
Sayaka-chan's somewhat reckless feeling and such... That feeling where she's always rushing, it's amazing, you know.
Right, right.
You might actually be a girl, you know.
Ehh, seriously!? Uwaah!
What's that?
(lol)
Then—
Really, everyone had that conversation a great number of times.
That's a bit...
Ehh–?
But Urobuchi-san is QB.
So that's it!?
QB, that's right.
That's shock treatment!
It's impossible to understand!
He comes out right at the end.
(lol) This...
Then there's this guy.
This guy.
(lol)
Right, that's that.
Sayaka's end, for it to really develop like this, you know...
Right, in the end the fact that she couldn't really save the people who were holding themselves in importance...
That must certainly irritate Madoka. Right...
But I think she must be satisfied.
Right...
"It is youth." That's what we'd say during after recording (lol)
ما هذا؟
"This is like our youth."
It's like a first love, right?
The violin's polish looks super real, doesn't it?
Yeah.
(lol)
Amazing.
This part, you know... It was written to show the entire audience sitting down...
"This'll be troublesome for the art, huh?" I thought (lol)
(lol)
We made use of copy, though.
Thank you very much!
(lol) Ah, is that so.
Ah~
Then, these–these members is fairly... it's somewhat unexpected.
Ne?
Well, in episode 10 this sort of thing was kind of there, though...
Somehow, it's a mysterious collection of members.
They're the most unrelated characters.
That's right, ne.
Right.
So it's like, it ends up as these three...
Actually they are the ones who never became witches.
So that's like that. Yeah.
That's right, ne.
Cute, huh?
Cute~!
I was somehow really happy at that line...
Agh. (9999 damage critical)
She's cute.
(lol)
Madoka is answering now, isn't she?
Cute, "Finally friends—" Uwah!
(lol)
Mou, she's truly soothing at any time.
She started out as a brutal character, huh? Kyouko.
Ne?
Kyouko—
Cute~!
Those two feel for each other.
(lol)
This is no good.
No...!!!
Mm.
Mou, it's sorrowful, you know...
Sorrowful.
This is also sorrowful!
It's very sorrowful...
It makes me think "You remembered?"
But, for your parents to forget, there might be viewpoints where that seems really cold, but...
All of the actresses talked about this before, but it's just that if Madoka's parents had remembered her...
That's too painful, isn't it!?
Rather than remembering, this might be more like seeing, you know?
Yeah.
It's a little bit like a cat in the corner of the room.
I see.
I see!
So really, despite the fact that she shifted up a level, Madoka is really still around?
That's right, ne.
She can't be with everyone but she is still there?
I see!
Probably because this child is still very small he can perceive that kind of thing, you know?
Yeah. When common sense tells him that such a thing can't exist, he will forget.
I'll remember, Ao-chan!!!
I'll remember!
It's all right.
(lol)
I'm not lonely!
No, I'm lonely~!
(lol)
I'm lonely!
I'm lonely, so remember~ (lol)
Somehow, for episode 12 I really love how everyone is in it again, you see a bit of everyone's actions,
I really love that, it makes me so happy...
Mm, somehow...
Everyone's future is properly portrayed,
and that's all something that Madoka did.
Well, that's how it is. Yeah.
That's right, ne.
Mm, everyone finds happiness.
There is something like that.
But, somewhere... somewhere it has a lonely feeling to it, too.
That's also left behind.
Somehow, the things you sacrifice... Well, I don't know if "sacrifice" is the right word, but to remember...
If it pains you, then conversly that'd make Madoka suffer, so...
Somehow, being able to think that even that is fine, makes her feelings genuine.
Yeah.
Right, I definitely couldn't do that.
(lol)
Amazing, isn't it? It's truly an amazing choice.
Amazing.
She took on so much pain and she's still like that...
And then...
(lol)
And—
I was wondering how to assess the writing of this scene, since it's a fairly suspenseful scene, you know.
With this, what does it mean will happen?
Well, right...
Umm......
To QB, um, it's since his methods of the past have lost their merit...
So then you'd be able to say a relationship of cooperation is acceptable.
Yeah.
The interests for him changed, so he can just become a regular ally.
Really, Madoka erased mahou shoujo—witches, but then a new enemy to fight appears?
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
Madoka did not erase curses themselves.
And Incubator's thoughts of obtaining those were also left behind.
Yeah.
Somehow I think that's extremely nice in its own way...
The fact it isn't entirely happy with everyone living in peace...
That's right, ne.
Like there's still a bit left behind.
Mm, that's there.
Well, that's right. Yeah.
That's really right, isn't it?
Life isn't that pretty of a thing.
It makes me sort of think that, though...
Conversely since it isn't essential for them to avoid each other anymore...
It's okay for these two get along with their own rules in mind.
So it's like that sort of thing is finally open to them.
Yeah.
But this world's QB-san is really, um...
He probably still makes contracts without telling people that their Soul Gems disappear, huh?
I think he'd probably say it, actually.
In short, that's why he says things to a careful extent.
I see, to say they disappear—
It's troublesome if you don't carry them with you, so.
Ah I see!
You might disappear from this world.
In exchange for that, he will grant your wish?
That's right, ne.
Yeah.
That's—
It's still going to be necessary to put in some hard work.
He's still giving you hard labor, you could say.
Yeah.
I see.
Amazing, huh?
That means that she'll continue to fight.
I think she must be tired from fighting so much, though!
Yeah.
I think Homura was truly glad that Madoka was around!
Well, that's right, ne.
Thank you very much.
I think so!
Well now, we're really at the end of the end.
Regarding this work, you can say whatever you'd like!
Let's hear what everyone has to say, starting with Miyamoto-san!
Ah... well I'd like to decide on season 2 as soon as possible. Right now people giving it their all until they die are helping with that...
While we still have staff that can work...
Please~
Then, as for you, Ume-sensei?
I was really only useful until around the middle, but...
This was a fun anime, and I'm really glad I was able to be a part of the design staff myself.
Then, on the way a lot of really hard things happened, but...
For that reason there were a lot of really helpful people.
I feel truly thankful for all of the staff-sama, and all of the viewers who watched. Thank you so much!
Yes~
Then, Urobuchi-san, give us some words, please!
That's right, mou...
I've only just started writing for anime, but...
The fact I was given the ability to do what I wanted from the beginning makes me really happy.
That's why to show all of the staff that let me do as I pleased my gratitude...
To repay everyone...
Um, I'm frantically trying hard to think of the next thing.
Season 2!? Season 2!?
Season 2!?
(lol)
Season 2? What'll happen to Madoka?
Ah, mamamadoka.
I think I can announce someday, but right now I'm frantically racking my brain.
Yeah, I'll keep at it.
It doesn't necessarily have a parallel to this world,
but surely there's a different type of ending, right?
Well, there's a lot that could be done, you know.
That would probably have to be the case, right?
The possibility to see that kind of world...
How interesting~!
Yeah. I feel that it hasn't ended here.
I really want to see one where I can Madoka love-love...
(lol)
I want to be happy!
I want to be happy~
Yaa... I wonder what to do.
I've shown Aoki-san a little of the plot, haven't I?
Urobuchi-san doesn't give out happiness that easily, so...
AHHHHHHHHH
No...
Yeah.
Well, that's right.
(lol)
Mou...
No but, I was able to create happiness to this extent, you know.
Yeah, I have the proof for that.
(lol)
I wonder if there'll be happiness? (lol)
Well then, we're really at the end of commentary.
That's right, ne.
I want to give our opinions too.
I've truly said this time and time again...
Truly doing this piece of work and acting as Homura—
Ah, Urobuchi-san thank you very much.
Urobuchi-san's voice is the reason I was able to!
I'm truly glad for it.
To an extent where I don't think I've ever done anything that brought me this much happiness in my career as an actress.
Thank you very much!
I think it's truly a wonderful piece of work, thank you very much.
Ao-chan!
In doing Madoka, there was a lot of hope in a different meanings...
Somehow there was a lot of hardships and experinces to go through but none of it was bad at all.
I think I was truly able to grow through doing this!
I truly, truly love Madoka, magic, and this piece of work!'
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you very much.
So then, to everyone who cheered us on to the end, truly:
Thank you very much!