Homura-chan, I'm sorry.
I'm going to become a magical girl.
Madoka...
That's...
I finally understand.
I found the wish I want granted.
Therefore, I'm going to use this life for that purpose.
Stop it!
Then...
Then for what purpose have I...
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Up until now, I've always... always, always been protected by Homura-chan...
I believe that your desire is why I am here now.
I'm truly sorry.
This is the answer that I've finally found.
Believe in it.
Because I absolutely will not make everything you've done up until today meaningless, Homura-chan.
Madoka...
The fates of numerous worlds are bundled together.
For you, the singular point of their karma,
no matter what kind of ridiculous wish you have, I believe it can be granted.
That is the truth.
Now, Kaname Madoka... with that soul as the cost,
what do you wish?
I...
want to erase all witches before they are born.
In every universe... The past and the future, every single witch, with this hand...
That wish is...
If that wish were to be granted, it wouldn't be on the level of something like time interference!
It's committing treason against the law of cause and effect itself!
Do you truly intend to become a god?
God or anything else is okay.
Everyone who has fought witches up until today... The magical girls with hope and trust...
I won't let them cry.
I want them to keep smiling until the end.
As for any rules which are a hindrance to that,
I'll break them.
I'll alter them.
This is my prayer.
My wish.
Now, grant it!
Incubator!
Final Episode
My Best Friend
Kaname-san, do you understand just how terrifying that wish is?
Probably.
In the past and the future, for all of time...
It means you will have to continue fighting for all of eternity.
If it happens, then surely the individual that you call "yourself" won't be preserved.
It isn't anything simple like death.
Until the end of eternity, you will be anchored to this universe, playing the role of every witch who was destroyed.
It's fine.
That is my intention.
If I were told something like "embracing hope is a mistake," I'd say that such a thing is wrong.
I would repeatedly say that any number of times.
I would surely insist on saying it forever.
Isn't that fine?
If it's something you can do, give it a try.
You've found a reason to fight, right?
"Not to run away" is something you've decided by yourself, right?
Then there's no helping it.
At this point, there's nothing left to do except charge in at full blast, y'know.
Yeah.
Thank you, Kyouko-chan.
Well then, I have to return an item that was entrusted to me, don't I?
Here, take this.
You will not fulfill any hopes.
You yourself will become hope.
The hope for all of us.
I won't let your prayers end in despair.
None of you will curse anyone.
You won't haunt them.
I will accept all of your karma.
So please, until the end, believe in yourselves!
It's okay now.
It's okay now, all right?
It's okay not to resent anyone anymore.
It's okay not to curse anyone!
Because before you take on such a form, I will endure and stop it for you!
This place is...?
The universe is being reorganized due to the new laws that Madoka has brought about.
That's right. You too were another user of magic that could transcend time.
Well then, shall we watch together?
The conclusion of the existence called "Kaname Madoka."
That is the Soul Gem brought about by her prayer.
That's...
To compensate for the fulfillment of that excessively grand prayer,
do you understand the number of curses Madoka will be burdened with?
There is hope equal to accomplishing the production of a single new universe.
Namely, that means enough despair was brought about to end a single universe.
That's natural, right?
No, it's all right.
My wish means that all witches will be erased.
If that is truly to be fulfilled, then even I...
Do not have any kind of reason for despair anymore!
Madoka, with this, your life...
no longer has a beginning or an ending.
Any evidence of you having lived in this world, and memories of that too, can no longer be found anywhere.
The existence called "you" has shifted up a single level, reducing you to a mere concept.
Nobody will be cognizant of you anymore, and likewise, you will be unable to interfere with anyone.
You will cease to be a member of this universe.
What is that?
Are you saying this is the conclusion that Madoka desired?
You think this style of ending will repay that girl!?
Don't joke around!
Compared to death, this is even...
more awful... It's awful...
No. That isn't right, Homura-chan.
You know, the current me is able to see everything in the past and the future.
Universes that formerly were,
and universes that someday might be. All of them.
Madoka...
That's why, you know... I understand everything.
The vast amount of time that you persevered for my sake.
Anything and everything.
No matter how many times you cried, even when you were completely covered in wounds...
Even still, for my sake...
I'm sorry for never noticing it.
I'm so sorry.
Since I became as I am now, I can truly understand everything you did.
I had such a very precious friend here the whole time.
So I'm happy.
Homura-chan, thank you.
You were my best friend, you know.
But even still, if you stay as you are now, you won't have a place to return to!
You'll grow more and more detached from the people you love!
You're saying that you'll be left behind, alone in a place like this for eternity!?
I'm not alone.
Everyone... I'll be together with everyone forever.
From now on, you know... I'll be anywhere at any time.
That's why even if you don't see me or hear me, I'll be by your side, Homura-chan.
Madoka, is that fine with you?
Even though I'll forget about you?
Even though I'll never be able to even perceive your existence again, Madoka!?
No. It's still too early to give up.
Homura-chan, you were able to accompany me all the way to a place like this.
That's why, even if you return to the world from before...
It might be possible that you won't forget about me.
It'll be all right.
It'll surely be all right.
Let's believe.
Madoka...
Because magical girls grant hopes and dreams, after all.
Surely if it's really small, a true miracle could happen.
Isn't that right?
Madoka, don't leave!
I'm sorry. I have to go welcome everyone.
Someday, I'll be able to meet you again once more, Homura-chan.
Until then, it's just a little farewell, okay?
Madoka!!!
Number 25, Kamijou Kyousuke.
The set piece is... Ave Maria.
Somehow...
I cost you a lot of time and trouble, didn't I?
No. I'm the one who is sorry.
Sayaka-chan, for me to rescue you, it means that anything and everything will not have happened.
If that's so, it means that this future will disappear too.
But, I believe that's probably...
not how you desired things to take shape, Sayaka-chan.
Sayaka-chan, your prayer, and how hard you persevered for the sake of it...
I think they those things are very precious, and I certainly don't want to make them meaningless.
That's why...
Yeah.
This is fine.
That's right.
It seems that I just simply wanted to listen to his performance once more.
I wanted a larger and larger crowd of people to listen to that violin.
Just remembering that... is enough.
I have no regrets anymore.
Well, that is... it's a little vexing though, you know.
There's no helping Hitomi.
She's such a good girl that it's wasted on Kyousuke...
The ability to be happy...
will be given to him, you know.
Yeah.
Well then... shall we go?
Sayaka?
Sayaka is...?
Oi, what happened to Sayaka?
She has left...
Guided by the Law of Cycles.
Miki-san... used all of her power in that single blow earlier, you know.
Freakin' idiot...
What're you going to do now that you've vanished for the sake of the guy you fell in love with...
Idiot... even though we finally became friends...
That is the fate of a magical girl.
We should understand that when we take this power into our hands, right?
Before karma balances the hope we sought by causing us to bring a curse to this world...
We have no choice but to disappear like that.
Madoka...
Akemi-san?
"Madoka"...?
Who's that?
_____m
_________a
__________d
____o
k
..a
Madoka! Madoka!
Yeah. That's right.
It looks just like her.
Hey! That's not allowed, Tatsuya.
You're not allowed to pull a woman's hair.
Madoka! Madoka!
Excuse us. Are you all right?
No, I'm the one who's sorry for disturbing you.
Madoka.
Madoka... is it?
Yes!
Here I go!
Now, come!
Whoa!
Well, um...
That child's imaginary friend he plays with when he's alone?
It's something that happens frequently during childhood though, you know.
Yes. I remember her as well.
This "Madoka"...
You know of her as well?
Is she a character from an anime or something?
I wonder... I'm not sure.
It's like I remember hearing about her, but it's like I don't.
Ah, is that so?
I wonder if I saw her together with Tatsuya somewhere, you know...
Every now and then...
There are times when I think it sounds really nostalgic.
Madoka...
Is that so?
That ribbon is really cute, you know!
It's completely in line with what I'd like.
So much that I'm kind of surprised!
Shall I offer it to you?
It wouldn't suit an old woman like myself.
Well, what if I had a daughter or something?
I might've had her wear that, you know.
Hm... I see.
Your story would certainly serve as one logical hypothesis.
It isn't a hypothesis. It's the truth.
Even if that's the case, there's no evidence.
If the rules of the universe were rewritten like you say,
then right now, there's no way for us to do anything like ascertain that fact.
If you're the only one who carries those memories,
then there isn't any distinction between them and a story you dreamed in your head.
Right.
Well, certainly... "Why do Soul Gems that are purified get annihilated?"
Even we haven't been able to clarify that fundamental truth.
Concerning that point, the concept of a witch, which you brought up in your story, is considerably intriguing.
As far as methods for collecting human emotional energy go, it certainly is fascinating.
If there was a method that amazing, I believe that we, the Incubators, would be using a much different strategy.
That's right. You guys are those kinds of things, you know.
In the world you talked about that has witches,
there wasn't any existence similar to the evil beasts we're fighting now, right?
As far as curse collection goes, isn't that a much faster method?
It's not as simple as that.
When it comes to our relationship with you, it was rather grim.
In the end, I can't comprehend them at all... human values, that is.
Even if this is a world where witches are not born,
that doesn't mean that the curses on this world's people have disappeared.
The forces that strain the world have changed shape,
and even now, they take aim at humanity from the depths of the shadows.
The obstinate miasma is thick tonight, isn't it?
Those evil beasts are springing up one after the other too.
No matter how many we defeat, there's no end.
There's no helping our complaints.
Now, let's go.
Consisting of nothing but reoccurring sorrow and hatred,
this is a hopeless world.
But even if that's so, this was formerly the place protected by that girl.
I remember that.
No matter what, I'll never forget.
So for that reason, I will...
continue to fight.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the
promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes
and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇
振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the
darkness that has
closed in on me,
I move forward
いつになったら
なくした未来を
The future I had
lost at some point...
私ここでまた見る
ことできるの？
will I be able to
see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing
shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いて
この世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as
many times as necessary
while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた
時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking
of time now announces
a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged
feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した
未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint
the future where I'll
start running
難しい道で
立ち止まっても 空は
Even if I come to a standstill
on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも
待っててくれる
is always waiting for
me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what
happens, I won't be crushed
Keep it up.
Subtitle notes, runes, and extras @ http://tri4.net