Please !
Einzbern Consultation Room
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room.
Part 2
I'm a lawyer for Masters and Servants who have lost their way!
And this is the Einzbern Consultation Room!
Saving people tired from the Holy Grail War with love and attention,
our law office is now open for business!
Why are you so quiet, Zecchan?
Um, it's just that I don't think anyone's made a classroom their office before.
Oh, I see.
You saved me because you save people all the time!
You see, although I set up an office,
I haven't had a single customer.
My income is zero.
You're my first customer, Zecchan.
That's no business.
That's more like a law office that only offers consultation sessions.
We should make a signboard.
A signboard?
Wait for me just a bit.
I happen to be good at making them.
Bing
Bang
Boom
Bing
Bang
Boom
Bam
Crash
Yeah! I went ahead and made one.
Please see if it's to your liking later.
Ooh, my my!
Instructor Iri, I have a question concerning Magi today.
According to the textbook you gave me, Masters are all practitioners of magic...
But what's magic?
That's a difficult and really annoying question.
To put it simply, think of it as the opposite technical system from physical and consumer culture
among schools passed down from antiquity.
You've lost me already, Instructor.
It's basically magical arts, okay?
And Magi are those who keep those arts to themselves, away from the general public.
Those born to a family of Magi inherit what's been passed down over generations of family heads,
acquire new spells during their time, and pass them all down to their children, the next generation.
Do you remember what Kayneth said?
About how bloodline is everything to a Mage.
He didn't mean it in a conventional way.
Magi really do become more powerful
with the accumulation of generations.
So the magic used by each family is different?
It also depends on culture and race, but the foundations of their magic basically differ on how they approach it.
Einzbern
Makiri
Alchemy
Sorcery
The Einzbern use alchemy, while the Makiri use sorcery.
With time, different attributes came to characterize each family.
Put simply, they have their own features and traits.
Is it like being good at running or being good at calculating?
Yes.
But while they do have only one prominent trait each, its general usability grows weaker with time.
In the magic world, omnipotency is proof of nobility.
It's known as blue blood.
Blue blood...
Are Magi like nobles from medieval times?
"Be elegant", and all that.
Most of them are, yes.
Magic
Because magic is expensive to pursue, naturally, only wealthy and distinguished families remain.
They also seek to monopolize areas of knowledge.
The Magi of Western Europe are
particularly keen on exercising control,
so they typically value styles and traditions in practicing magic.
That would apply to Kayneth-sensei and Tokiomi-san.
But this Kiritsugu guy isn't magelike at all.
Instructor, you mentioned how magic was the opposite of consumer culture.
But this guy mainly uses modern weapons.
It's fine!
Kiritsugu's just fine the way he is, Zecchan.
He breaks conventions in everything.
Each Mage has his own style.
There are those who value tradition
and those who deviate from tradition.
Let's take a look at the Magi who are taking part in the 4th Holy Grail War.
Champions of Tradition
Tohsaka , Archibald
Deniers of Tradition
Kiritsugu , Ryuunosuke , Kariya~n
In the Middle
Waver  ,  Kirei
That's nice and clear, Instructor!
So we have a dichotomy of traditionalists and reformists in the 4th War!
Huh?
Isn't Waver-kun a denier of tradition?
He's part of a new age that values tradition,
but also feels certain areas of it can be revisited.
Old
New
Magic
Ryuunosuke-kun never knew the rules of the magic world to begin with.
Kariya~n eschews magic itself.
I see.
So that's why the scruffy priest was looking with disgust when Tohsaka-san was using the occult auto-writer to communicate.
He even told him to use the telephone.
Scruffy?
Oh, you must be talking about Priest Kirei.
He's not a Mage to begin with, so
his values differ from Tokiomi-san's.
Different values...
Wouldn't the Kiritsugu guy be the most extreme case of that?
His use of guns and explosives
almost has nothing to do with magic.
That's why he's known as the Mage Killer.
Because Magi regard magic as absolute and focus only on defending against it,
they neglect guarding against modern weapons.
While weapons weren't commonly used as of late, they
proved to be very effective against Magi during the 4th war.
Kiritsugu has no dignity for himself as a Mage,
so he's a Master who'll resort to any means once he grasps his opponent's weaknesses.
His readiness for battle is earnest, but I do think he lacks respect for his opponents in battle.
Victory should come from defeating
your opponents while respecting them.
I guess.
Kiritsugu does go by efficiency too often.
Call it cowardly, but he has no choice.
Zecchan, do you dislike Kiritsugu?
Nope, I can't hate someone I haven't even met.
Plus, I don't think any human's better than the other.
It's all about how you live your life. Yeah!
Ooh, you're so cute!
I wonder if Ilya'll become just like you six years later!
Huh?
Hmm?
Too easy.
Too easy!
Instructor, what is it?
Maybe I'm just imagining things.
Do you understand the rules of the Magi?
Well then, this comes next!
Battle Royale
Seven Masters
and Seven Servants
About how the Holy Grail War is a battle royale, right?
Magi summon Servants that represent them in battles and defeat the other participants.
That's right.
The Grail will appear in front of the last
surviving team, giving them the right to use it.
From legends and tales of the past
Spirits of Heroes
By the way, Servants are summoned spirits of Heroes from legends and tales of the past integral to the establishment of their people.
In the magic world, they'd be familiars of the highest rank.
So Magi are called Masters precisely because they summon Servants to do their bidding.
Huh?
From legends and tales of the past
But wouldn't that mean I'm not a Master?
I'm sure you just haven't summoned one yet, or you were separated from it.
Zecchan's Servant should be, let's see...
...a young and amiable girl. I think that'd be great!
I'd rather have a tiger or something strong like that!
By the way, Instructor.
From legends and tales of the past
Spirits of Heroes
Why are Servants referred to by simple titles like Saber and Lancer?
Well, part of the reason would definitely be to conceal what Heroic Spirits the Servants are.
So the class names of the Servants aren't their true names?
Like how Rider just suddenly revealed his true name to everyone...
Was that supposed to be an NG?
That normally never happens.
This fight is a battle royale.
It's not as simple as simply defeating the enemies you come across.
When you reveal data about yourself in order to defeat B,
your next opponent will use that data against you.
Can you see how this gradually places you at a disadvantage?
Yeah.
What's more, the more famous the Heroic Spirit, the more
weak points and details on how they died are recorded in legends.
True Identity
Weakness
How They Died
It's not something you want revealed when
you still have five groups of enemies around.
How They Died
Weakness
It'd really hurt your chances.
I see.
So the established tactic in the Grail War early stages is completely concealing your Servant's true identity
while collecting data on your opponents.
That's right.
But while Saber, Lancer, and Archer have top ranks in
actual combat, collecting information is not their forte.
That's why Lancer baited himself to lure out the other Servants,
and why Saber attempted to expose her opponent's trump card in battle while concealing her own.
I see.
So Caster would be weak in battle but specialize in collecting information.
Simply being strong in battle isn't enough to win.
Battle Royale
Seven Masters
and Seven Servants
That's the battle royale involving seven camps...
That's right. Screaming "I'm strong!" and thrashing about won't work.
Yes.
No matter how powerful your trump card is, if you use it
in your first battle, it will be countered against in your next.
That's why you need to be prudent in using your trump card.
Good! Very good, Zecchan!
Since you've been chosen as a Master, you need to know this established tactic of battle to survive.
Of course, there are strategies that take
advantage of this tactic, but that's something else.
By the way, Zecchan, how would you go about the early stages?
Like Lancer, I'd challenge other Servants to one-on-one fights...
...is what I'd like to say, but I'm not confident enough in myself, and I have no pride I must protect.
That's why I'd start by searching for Caster and defeating him.
Oh? What's the basis for that?
Firstly, I'm probably a Master specializing in combat.
Secondly, if I let him be, he'll read all the cards in my hand.
Thirdly, if I take him one-on-one, I'll likely win.
I'm going from those three points. Yeah!
You pass!
You've become such a skilled Grail War beginner that I wouldn't be embarrassed to show you to everyone!
I'm happy for you as your instructor!
Yeah! But I'm still a beginner.
I'll continue to work hard and
repay your kindness, Instructor Iri!
Oh, my!
You're so close to turning me into a lesbian!
All right, now that we have the
basics covered, let's go out, Zecchan!
The night starts here!
We'll sneak into Tokiomi-san's house and enjoy his wine!
It'll be too easy!
Whoa, Instructor!
I'm still underaged!
Also, that's a death flag, a death flag!
A death flag, I'm telling you!