Sasami
Sasami Report...
Sasami Re
Report
Chapter 3.
CHAPTER 3
The second draft.
THE SECOND DRAFT
In this country, gods reside in everything.
...reside...
These gods are called the Yaoyorozu:
the Eight Million Gods.
From the pebbles on the streets to the architecture,
craftwork, animals, grass,
the weather and even the laws of physics...
they reside in and control everything.
...control...
There are rankings of divinity.
The gods with higher divinity control
lower-ranked gods and alter them to their will.
...called "Alteration".
This is called Alteration.
The highest ranked god, she who controls
all the others, is Great God Amaterasu.
Sasami Report Chapter 3,
Second Draft
All gods alter themselves
according to Amaterasu's wishes...
"Alteration" "Alteration" "Alteration"
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO SEARCH?
OPTION (O)   SEARCH (S)
...so that they could form the world
in the exact way the Supreme God desires.
YOU WILL BE ELIMINATED.
OPTION (O)                      SEARCH (S)
the way!
That great power was once inherited,
maintained and controlled by me.
by me.
However...
...the power of Amaterasu currently resides
inside my big brother, of all places.
In other words, it's no exaggeration
to say my brother is God.
"Supreme God"
So when my brother wishes for something,
the Yaoyorozu conduct alterations
in order to make him happy at times.
The disaster which occurred on
Valentine's Day was one of them.
The gods turned my body into chocolate
and made me implore him to eat.
But fortunately, thanks to the Yagami sisters,
Tsurugi, Kagami and Tama,
the Alteration was stopped and brought under control.
It's not clear who they really are.
But I'm sure that they're psychics with
a very high-ranked divinity.
In conclusion, continuous surveillance is needed
for not only my brother, but those girls as well.
The end.
Sasami Tsukuyomi
Sasami Tsukuyomi.
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
Deatta kouya no hana
Kowakute yasashikute
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
EPISODE 2                                              Ganbaranai
"SECURITY PERSONNEL AT HOME"
Yes! I won!
Shut up, you idiot!
First of all you're so childish for getting
excited over winning a game, you idiot!
Yawn.
You're so loud; shut up.
We're in class, you know.
Look at your delinquent behavior.
As a student and as your younger sister,
I'm embarrassed.
As a teacher and as your older sister,
I don't want to hear that from someone
who's been sleeping up until just now!
I finished the drill a long time ago.
But I don't have anyone who'd
go through all the answers with me.
You know what? Don't we have too many absentees?
It's been like this for a while now.
Oh, is that right?
Pay attention, will you? You're a teacher, aren't you?
We teachers aren't as concerned about
our students as you students think we are.
I didn't have to know such a harsh reality.
Jeez, you're so irritating! Can't you speak clearly?
Obviously it's strange, right?!
Why are so many of them absent?
Under Year 1 - Right Class
Hi!!
Hi!
CHAT LOG
Yesterday
was fun...
Got more SP!
Yesterday
was fun...
I wish I was
that high level
Roger that!
Take a look at this.
What's that?
This is the Yamata no Orochi SNS, which is
super popular right now among young people.
"Yamata no Orochi SNS"?
Put simply, it's the sword & magic academy
fantasy Social Networking System.
Basically, this one, this one and this one are
the students who are absent from school today.
She's sleeping.
Teacher is coming.
Seriously???
They're playing in this
internet world all day at home.
Is it that fun?
I don't know.
Three years ago they were going to shut it down
because it wasn't profitable enough
due to the fact that game balance was
totally off and the game system was so lame.
But for some reason the popularity
picked up again so they're still here today.
I guess I'll give it a try too.
Oh? So you're interested in it?
Is that an Alteration?
Tsukuyomi, your sister has a computer, right?
Yes.
She's got about ten of them.
So let me borrow your computer.
Stuffed animals!
Yawn.
This is pretty nice.
I'm not going to nag you about
not coming to school, so help me out a little.
YAMATA NO OROCHI
User ID
Password
How many computers does one person need anyway?
I bet you don't have that many purposes for them.
I do.
I use them for games, surfing the net, watching videos,
listening to music, games and games...
How many times are you going to say games?!
I use different ones for different things.
Let's see... I've never done anything like this before.
You know a lot about the internet, right?
Why don't you join us, Sasami?
What? N-no, thanks.
I don't understand the point of stuff like that anyway.
Don't tell me you're hikikomori on the internet, too.
Note: Hikikomori are socially withdrawn people, or shut-ins.
I can never tell them that I'm a hardcore gamer who's
logged thousands of hours on Yamata no Orochi SNS
and created this, the most powerful character
equipped with super rare items!
S-so tell me what's happening
on that Yamata no whatsit?
I'm not sure.
But we should shut down anything suspicious.
I don't want to wait until it's too late.
It'd be bad if this turned out to be like
the Valentine's Day Disaster.
Crap...
What if they determine Yamata no Orochi
is corrupted and shut it down?
What's going to happen to my
experience points, gold and Orochi rank,
all the items and all those hours that I've spent on it?
I must stop it from happening no matter what!
All right, it's done! Let's get it started!
Welcome to Takamagahara Academy!
Before we let the entry ceremony begin,
will you tell me about you?
Wh-wh-wh-what am I supposed to do?
First, you have to create a character.
I want to advance through the game quickly
so I'm going to be a Fighter.
Job Options
Next
Oh? Your real job is this one, isn't it?
What?
You're lucky, Big Sis.
That's a rare message that doesn't pop up often.
You'll get to pick a rare job.
Really?
Tsurugin's real job is... This one!
NAME: TSURUGI
HP: 80
SEX: FEMALE
DEFENSE: POWER
DEFAULT
EQUIPMENT: CIGS X 3
JOB: BANCHO
SPECIAL MOVE: YELL
JACKET
AGE: 16
RIGHT HAND: WOODEN
SWORD
TRIBE: HUMAN
It's Bancho!
Note: Bancho is the leader of a group of delinquents at school.
What the heck?!
Is "Bancho" even a job?
Enjoy your school life!
Oops!
My hand slipped!
Oh no!
I broke the router!
Connection interrupted.
Check your network connection.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm sorry! You can't use the internet anymore today.
You have nothing to worry about.
I have my own high-speed internet.
Mine is complete too.
I figured that we need at least one healer.
REGULAR ELECTRIC
ENERGY METER
Shikaku Electric Co., Ltd Made in 1988
Are you a nurse?
I'm a vet.
I'm not interested in ordinary humans.
NAME: KAGAMI
HP: 50
SEX: FEMALE
DEFENSE: UNIFORM -3
NURSECAP -3
AGE: 16
EQUIPMENT: ANESTHETIC x3
JOB: VETERINARIAN
SPECIAL
MOVE: ANESTHETIZE
RIGHT HAND: SYRINGE
TRIBE: ELF
DEFAULT
Can a vet heal humans?
You go to sleep whenever it's
inconvenient for you, don't you?
I'm sorry! It looks like the breaker is tripped.
You guys didn't save the game, did you?
You might as well give up for today and...
Tama did it too!
NAME: TAMA
EQUIPMENT: NONE
HP: 50
SEX: FEMALE
DEFENSE: MAID
UNIFORM
AGE: 16
RIGHT HAND: KNIFE
TRIBE: MAGICIAN
JOB: PATISSIER
SPECIAL MOVE: CUT INTO
STRIPS
DEFAULT
My job is patissier!
I'm going to make all the sweets I want and eat them!
Oh no! Everyone's using a laptop with a battery...
I still hadn't saved my report!
Hey, Tsukuyomi, go turn on the breaker.
Yes, right away.
Hurry up! We're waiting!
Yes, I'm going to do it right now.
Oh, it looks like it's timed out.
Can't you even pick an option on the game?
I'm sure you're a slow person who can't decide
anything on your own in real life either!
I bet you wish to fulfill your relationships
with others on the internet,
but things aren't that easy here, either, you moron!
Have I done anything to make you treat me this way?
Stuff like this is perfect for a moron like you!
Yamata no
Orochi
Online
NAME: KAMIOMI
SPECIAL MOVE: SERVANT
HP: 20
SEX: MALE
DEFENSE: NONE
AGE: 16
RIGHT HAND: NONE
TRIBE: HUMAN
DEFAULT EQUIPMENT: NONE
JOB: LOSER
Your job is... Loser?
I'm not even wearing anything?
Big Brother... You're lame in the game, too.
Enjoy your school life!
Chat Log
All right! The real game starts now.
Guys, don't overlook any symptoms of the Alteration.
I couldn't stop them...
To think Project Blackout, Project Birdlime,
Project Swooning-Madame have all failed...!
So, what's next?
There's no rule.
You can do whatever you please in this world.
Where's the fun in that?
Isn't it fun enough to do whatever you please
in real life, not in the game world?
Only you would think that.
By the way, you can't even serve me
some tea around here?
Stop doing whatever you please here!
I'll bring it right away!
It'd be great if you have some snacks like potato chips.
Be more modest!
Tama wants a chocolate parfait!
Make your own, you patissier!
Thank you for waiting.
Thanks. I didn't mean to press you or anything.
You DID press him!
What's that?
Don't you touch it with those dirty fingers!
You're getting potato chip grease on the keyboard!
Big deal.
No! Use chopsticks!
Don't be a pain in the butt!
You can't be that way, Big Sis.
Hikikomoris have their own rules, too.
For instance, you're supposed to
break potato chips like this.
If you eat it directly from the bag,
you don't have to use your fingers.
You're so smart!
All right!
What are you doing?
It'll be okay as long as I eat it within 30 seconds.
I'm not talking about potato chips!
Chopsticks come in handy!
Vacuum! Vacuum!
Aren't you awfully quiet?
Nothing much is going on.
Is something wrong?
Nothing!
Let me see it.
No, don't look!
I told you not to look...
I don't care! Just turn it off!
You have these manga?
I've been wanting to read it!
For the last time, don't you touch it
with those greasy fingers!
Same difference as long as I can read it.
That's the first edition!
You're lowering the premium value!
Whatever. It doesn't make any difference.
Don't you throw the sleeve away!
Oh? I haven't watched this movie yet.
Don't you open it without my permission!
I haven't even opened it yet!
Hey, what am I supposed to do with this?
"Would you like to turn it back to the
factory setting"? What's that?
There!
Setting the machine
back to factory setting
Please wait a while
Machine Reset
Oh, no! My party!
I can't... I can't endure these
simultaneous terrorist acts all by myself.
My biggest blunder!
The moment I let these people in here,
the outcome was already decided.
CHAT LOG
Maintenance outage
expected from 11pm-12am
Hey, you!
Keep it down
during class, will ya?
CHAT LOG
Headquarters:
500-People-Campaign
Accomplished! 7 Wonders Event
"Art Room" is now open
It hit ME! I was just listening to the class!
Chat Log
Kibamaru: Hey
Kibamaru: You
Kibamaru: Keep it down during class, will ya?
Kamiomi received 2 damages.
Kamiomi has died.
Oh...
I DIED?!
Oh, boy, Kamiomi. You're dead?
Someone take him to the nurse's office.
Is that how you handle this?
Let's revive Mr. Tsukuyomi.
So what are we supposed to do?
MINI GAME
Mini game, "Naughty Nurse's Office" has begun.
NAUGHTY
NURSE'S
OFFICE
CHAT LOG
Kamiomi has died.
Minigame "Naughty Nurse's Office"
has begun.
What?
Try different things within a limited time and revive him.
Let's see...
How about this?
CHAT LOG
Tama cooled Kamiomi's head.
That's what you do for a cold!
CHAT LOG
Tama cooled Kamiomi's head.
Kamiomi was revived.
Kamiomi has revived.
Why?
Tama, you saved me!
CHAT LOG
Tama cooled Kamiomi's head.
Kamiomi was revived.
Kamiomi's likeability went up by 20 points.
Likeability? What's that?
When your likeability goes up,
you can marry another character and
create a kid character together.
What? You can make babies?!
If that's the case I need to get in on that!
The bed in the nurse's office is a spot
where naughty stuff could easily happen!
Come on, Tsukuyomi! Take off your clothes!
What? Me, too?
You're no young girl,
so shut up.
You're right. I'm no young girl, but I don't think
the story should go that direction.
I'm scared! I'm scared!
Big Sis Tsurugi and Papa-lin
are doing strange things naked!
Please stop traumatizing the elementary school student.
Just give it up! Give it up!
Don't be so cruel, Miss Tsurugi!
I understand this is just a game,
but please don't go any further!
The more you refuse, the more excited I get!
How do you like this? Take this!
What do you think you're doing to my big brother?!
Wh-what's that?
Is this you?
She looks super strong!
I can't believe you, Big Brother!
I understand it's just a game,
but I wish you'd resisted her a little more!
Moron! Pervert! Hmph!
Just go ahead and fall in love with
a game character and get married to her!
You always-in-heat good-for-nothing SCUM!
Sasami is inside the game.
SCUM!
And she's being a cutesy tsundere
while she's yelling at me.
Get away from me!
CHAT LOG
Kamiomi's likeability
went up by 20 points.
Sasami has logged in
Sasami: Scum!
Kamiomi received 9999 damages.
CHAT LOG
Kamiomi's likeability went up by 20 points.
Sasami has logged in.
Sasami: Scum!
Kamiomi received 9999 damages.
Kamiomi has died.
So have you been playing Yamata no Orochi SNS
while skipping school all this time?!
No, actually I was shopping online, watching videos
and reading net idols' blogs, too...
It's the same thing!
But I'm not the only one hooked on this game.
Here's what I learned upon hacking the site operator.
It seems that about ten thousand people
have gone hikikomori because of this game.
I wonder what the purpose is.
I don't know. I have no idea what the enemy is after.
Big Sis Tsurugi...
I just discovered something really big!
What happened?
I have to...
I have to go to the bathroom!
You should've gone earlier!
I want you to come with me, Big Sis Tsurugi!
You're in elementary school. You should be
able to go to the bathroom by yourself.
I know this is a tragic truth, but...
Humanity hasn't reached that level just yet!
I don't get it!
We'll be right back, so you guys go on without us.
So, what are you going to do?
We should keep going for now.
First, let's go back to the classroom...
What is this?
What happened?
Check it out.
Those lights... Players' psychic energy?
That thing is absorbing the psychic energy...
It's the Demon King's troops.
I feel this powerful force coming from them.
It has extremely high-levels of divinity...
Kagami?!
Aargh! Owww...
Oh? Where am I? What just happened?
Oh, no! Big Brother, get out of here...
Owww...
PLAY
HARD
This is mind-boggling.
It seems that our consciousnesses
have been sucked into the Yamata no Orochi SNS.
So that means the Alteration really happened?
Yamata no Orochi...
Its divinity level is way too high.
It must've grown bigger by eating
the players' psychic energies.
No way...
At any rate this is beyond comprehension.
It's grown that big, but why isn't it doing anything?
If it's a god of ill intent, it could manipulate
the players and infiltrate the real world...
But all it's doing is devouring sacrifices and nothing else.
It's a mystery.
With that power, I'm sure it could invade
the real world and build its own kingdom, too.
He's not interested in reality.
He just wants to maintain this world. That's all.
He hopes that this alternate world is eternal.
That's all he exists for.
What does that mean?
He smells like us.
This level of divinity indicates that
it's some kind of Supreme God.
In other words, it's a monster
Sasami unintentionally created.
I learned something after checking your profile.
You've been playing here for the past three years, right?
In order to escape from the harsh reality...
In order to escape the hardship of your daily training,
you've been playing here, right?
You wished for something.
Three years ago this place was on the verge of collapse,
but suddenly it started growing rapidly.
The timelines match, don't they?
He's been protecting this playground you found.
Is that what I wished for?
Is this what I wished for and created
when I still possessed the Power of God? Really?
I see...
He's been protecting this world all this time.
You know what to do, right?
Yeah.
His job is done.
You need to let him know that.
In the name of Sasami Tsukuyomi I order you!
O raging god...
You will calm yourself!
Diffuse and melt into the world and go to sleep!
I'm okay.
I have a pretty happy life!
So I want you to know that you don't
have to work so hard anymore, either.
WHEN YOU WAKE UP,
I WANT YOU TO
SLEEP IN YOUR BED.
IMPORTANT MESSAGE TO OUR CUSTOMERS
Yamata no Orochi SNS is temporarily down
due to system issues.
Now it's time for you to get up on the stage, Sasami!
I'm going to make sure you sing this time!
Here, here, grab your mic.
Are you ready? Here, come on!
Oh no? You can't even respond?
You seriously don't want to do this, do you?
Ah, the song started....
At this rate this is going to be a broadcast error.
But don't worry! Your beloved Big Brother
is going to hype it up for you!
Yeah!
Come on!
Cha-cha-cha!
Yo!
Hoo!
Hoo, I say!
I did my best...
I shouted with all my heart!
But you still don't seem up for it...
You'd better do something about this
otherwise this project is a bust!
Oh yeah! Why don't I ask the Yagami sisters
to help me out next time?
WEATHER FORECAST
It's time for Ganbaranai weather forecast.
I'm going to stay home from morning to evening,
so I don't care about today's forecast.
TODAY'S FORECAST
I'll be home at night, late night and tomorrow
morning, too, so I really don't care.
But the sunlight wakes me up when
it's nice outside, which is very annoying.
Whoever invented blackout curtains is a genius.
Next time, Episode 3,
"You work, you lose"
Episode 3
"You Work, You Lose"