Deleted.
Onii-chan...
Hirono-kun, you aren't here?
Hirono-kun...
Oh, Miyamura-senpai. What can I do for you?
"Wh-What"...?
Where's Hirono-kun?
Onii-chan is sleeping right now.
Can you be quiet?
Let me see him! I have something important to tell him.
Let me see Hirono-kun!
It will no longer reach him.
I won't let it reach him.
Because I'm always by Onii-chan's side.
It's already over.
Good afternoon, Renji-kun.
A-Ah, good afternoon.
What's in the obento today?
I'm hungry.
It's delicious. I always look forward to your obento.
How many points does it get today?
It's so delicious that it can't be scored with points.
R-Really?
Please teach me how to cook next time.
Teach you?
My sister is practicing her cooking right now.
I want to be able to cook something too.
I see. Let's try something simple then.
Okay.
The number you have dialed is outside your calling area, or the phone might be switched off...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
A
She most likely means to say "naisoku sokufuku jintai sonshou 【内側側副靭帯損傷】 which means "Medical Collateral Ligament Injury."
So, what did the doctor say?
Let's see... naisoku sokusoku... jintai sokusoku?
A
She most likely means to say "naisoku sokufuku jintai sonshou 【内側側副靭帯損傷】 which means "Medical Collateral Ligament Injury."
That's nothing but "soku."
It kind of sounds like that.
At least remember the name of your own injury.
He told me to rest and not move it until it doesn't hurt anymore.
Really? Then you can't play basketball for a while.
Yeah.
There.
Thank you.
How's your tendonitis?
Same as usual. If I rest my arm, it will get better.
Maybe I should slow down my pace.
Eh?
Since you have to rest your knee too.
Should I keep you company for a while?
Yes.
A
The furigana next to it says "Chigiri," which means "Vow."
"The girl began to look at the painting a lot."
"When she stared at the boy in the painting, she had a strange feeling."
"'Let's marry.' She somehow had that idea."
"In the books, there were an unusual number of stories relating to marriage."
"It was described as something important in people's lives."
"She began to study the marriage system in detail."
A
The furigana next to it says "Inori," which means "Prayer."
Renji-kun, have you decided about your career?
You got a career interest survey, right?
Yeah. It's hard to decide.
You should become a novelist too.
It's fun to write stories.
I do yearn to become a novelist, but...
It's impossible after all.
Why?
After reading what you wrote, I don't think I can catch up at all.
I don't have the talent after all.
That's not true. It's not like that.
It has nothing to do with talent or anything. What's important is doing it.
You taught me that.
Thanks to you, I'm about to finish writing a story.
Even though I thought I couldn't possibly do it.
Chihiro...
Even though my memory only lasts thirteen hours...
Even though my life experiences haven't progressed since I was twelve...
You taught me that there are things I could do.
Therefore, please don't give up.
If you have a dream, please don't give it up, and try your best.
Yeah.
It's still there.
That's wrong.
Eh?
This here has to be more like this.
Yeah, you're right.
It's weird. What am I depressed about?
Things are back to how they were.
I can still go wherever I want freely.
This is not a place you should come or return to.
Leave me alone.
Even if you trap yourself in the ruins of the past, nothing good will come of it.
Where should I go?
You know about warmth.
As long as you remember the feeling of tenderness, you won't choose the wrong path.
I don't have such a faraway memory.
But don't you already remember it?
It might have been better if we hadn't met.
I wouldn't remember warmth then.
A
The furigana next to it says "Surechigai," which means "Passing each other."
Chihiro's condition has improved?
Yeah. Even though it's little by little, her memory is better than before...
That's impossible.
But...
It would be a different story if a miracle happened.
But miracles don't exist in this world.
There are only inevitabilities and accidents, and what someone has done.
That's it.
Do you remember what I told you?
Forget about it. It may be too late already.
The number you have dialed is outside your calling area...
That Miyako.
Hirono Hiro-kun of grade 2 class D,
and Miyamura Miyako-san of grade 2 class A,
please come to the career guidance room after school.
What did they say, Onii-chan?
They asked me what I planned to do with my career interest survey.
Miyamura-senpai too?
She skipped school.
I see. Isn't studying better than working after all?
Yeah. Maybe I should take this opportunity to rehabilitate too.
Oh, yeah. Let's go somewhere and have fun after this deadline. I...
Yes, this is Shindou Nagi.
Oh. Well, I'll make it somehow.
A one-shot?
Okay. I'll give it a try.
I'll send you a plot outline this week.
Yeah, see you then.
Is it about work?
They asked me to draw a one-shot.
Something other than the series.
Are you going to do it?
Yeah, it's an opportunity.
No way. You said you were going to rest just now...
If I decline, there won't be a next time.
If a newcomer likes me doesn't seize every chance that passes by, he won't succeed.
Really? Then do whatever you like.
Where are you going?
Club activities. If I don't move, my body will become dull.
You idiot. You were told to rest, weren't you?
Same goes for you. You're not going to rest, even though your arm won't get better, are you?
If you really damage your knee, you won't be able to play basketball anymore.
Same goes for you. If you get really hurt, you won't be able to draw manga anymore.
If I stop drawing, some other artist will seize the opportunity!
Same goes for me, I have to fight to be a regular!
Anyway, you won't be able to be a regular with that injury.
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Did I fall asleep just now?
How many hours have passed?
How long have I slept?
Nah. Only around five minutes.
I... see.
Aren't you exhausted?
Not at all. I'm not tired at all.
Really? It's all right then.
Yes, I'm all right.
He really is an idiot.
He's taking on more work, even though he doesn't have enough days in attendance.
What is he thinking?
You can't demand planning from him.
Why did you start playing basketball?
I liked it from the beginning.
It feels really good to attack swiftly, shake off your opponents, then shoot the ball.
We're the same.
Eh?
The moment you capture a video that moves people's hearts from time and space gives you the best feeling there is.
Hm...
It's the same for Hirono.
He's way ahead of us.
That's why it's a lot harder for him than for us.
But he's an idiot after all.
You two are really clumsy.
What do you mean?
Hm... nah, nothing.
It's unfair not to finish your sentence.
When you film the life of a wild animal,
the film unit must not interfere with the behavior of that animal.
You have to shoot wildlife just as it is.
How does that relate to us?
If I cut into the conversation between the two of you, I would be interfering.
Don't compare people to animals!
Geez. Please don't talk like you know everything.
I do.
If I look through the finder, I can see everything.
Hmm?
Chihiro. Chihiro.
What's wrong?
Ah, I was just thinking about something.
In the middle of the meal?
I'm sorry.
11:50. I arrived at the library.
Renji-kun came four minutes later.
We had lunch in the courtyard.
The menu of the obento consisted of fried white fish, Japanese-style salad, and other things.
Dessert was strawberry jelly. It was delicious.
I always look forward to Renji-kun's obento.
"How many points does it get today?"
"It's so delicious that it can't be scored with points."
"Please teach me how to cook next time."
"Well, let's try something simple then."
It's only three o'clock.
It's okay. I can still remember.
What are you doing?
You're still sorting your memories this late?
Before going to sleep, didn't you read over the necessary parts again?
Yes, just the summaries.
Summaries?
I only wrote summaries into the diary.
I wrote the fun moments as fun moments.
However, why they were fun, and how I felt, I couldn't write any of that down.
That's why you're thinking back about it?
If I skim through this, I'll be able to remember in detail.
In that case, I'll be able to remember things for longer than thirteen hours from now on.
By the time I meet Renji-kun at noon, I'll be able to remember everything until now.
It will take you till morning to do that.
Yes.
Can you keep up with that?
It's because I don't want to lose my time with Renji-kun.
I'm just a normal girl too.
Is it okay now?
I don't have much time left.
What are you doing?
It's useless, even if you do something like that.
It's not useless.
There's no way you can keep doing it.
Don't force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself.
Listen to me. It's bad for you.
Please give it back to me. Give it back. I beg you, please give it back to me!
Inside that... inside that, is my Renji-kun!
I won't forget this.
I'll never forget about this!
I understand.
I'm sorry for saying something selfish.
Don't overdo it.
A
The furigana next to it says "Genzai," which means "Present."
How was it when we first met?
I want to retain the important past in my heart one more time.
Chihiro...
You were looking at the sky.
You kept gazing at the sky. It gave me a strange feeling somehow.
Sky, eh?
I think I was indeed looking at the sky at that time.
But now it's more fun to look in front of me than at the sky.
Erm...
What is it?
Renji-kun and I...
Erm, if it's okay with you...
Can we hold hands?
It's fine if we can't.
I don't really want to force you.
I was just thinking of trying to hold hands for a bit.
Can... we?
Sure.
Let's hold hands.
Okay.
Chihiro! What's wrong?
Chihiro! Chihiro! Chihiro!
A
The furigana next to it says "Kurayami," which means "Darkness."
"The girl married on the next day."
"She found a dress in the castle."
"She pretended to ask herself, 'Do you vow to marry?' in her mind, and she pretended to answer 'Yes.'"
"And then she kissed the boy in the painting."
"It tasted like oil."
"She threw the flowers that she picked as a bouquet."
"She prepared a bigger meal than usual."
"It was a party after all."
"But she had leftovers, because the dress was too tight around the hips."
"The girl tossed the bouquet, the dress, and the leftovers to the bottom of the dump site and went to sleep."
"And thus the wedding ceremony was over."
It's you, eh.
Erm...
Come in.
You heard me, didn't you?
Is Chihiro all right?
Strain and lack of sleep, plus mental stress.
She kept straining herself, so she broke down once she felt relieved.
I tried to wake her up several times, but it didn't work.
She passed her time limit already, so just let her sleep quietly for now.
Time limit?
Chihiro.
Onii-san, who are you?
Eh? Why am I...
Eh? Eh?
Why? Why have I grown up?
What happened to my eye?
Chihiro...
Where's Onee-chan? Where's Kei-onee-chan?
Where's Hiro-onii-chan? What happened to me?
Calm down, Chihiro.
You already...
Why? Why?
What happened to me?
Wait!
No!
Chihiro, do you recognize me?
Himura... onii-chan?
You still remember me, don't you now?
Now you understand, right? This is Chihiro.
This girl is stuck at twelve years old and thirteen hours.
Forever.
Yes, this is Hirono.
Hello?
Hello, can you hear me?
Is this Miyako?
Bingo.
Miyako...
What, so you do remember me.
What's wrong? I was worried because I couldn't get in touch with you.
Turn on your phone!
So I didn't disappear.
I still haven't disappeared yet.
If you don't know about pain, you will face a more painful tragedy.
Next episode, ef - a tale of memories:
Forget me not.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?