I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
W-What the hell
are you doing here?
Waterfall...
Do you know this place, Ed?
I think I know...
I don't think I know...
I don't think I think I know...
I don't think I think...
Which is it?!
Come on!
Dammit, Ein!
Hey, Spike, where the devil are we?
- It's Earth, isn't it?
- Earth?
This ship was headed for Mars!
What are we doing on
Earth all of a sudden?
- Don't know.
- Oh, shit! This isn't funny!
While we're wasting time,
our bounty head's getting away.
This was our best lead in months.
- How do we just get off course and--
- Jet.
The girls are gone.
What?
All right, I promise.
If you lead me to that waterfall place,
I'll give you something good.
Oh! Good thing, what?
You'll see. It's something
wonderfully, tremendously good.
All right!
Something wonderfully,
tremendously good for Ed!
Hot!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot...
Over here!
Waterfall!
Right... listen to Ed...
What was I thinking?
Hey, look! I found Ed!
So Edward is found?
Do you know these kids?
35 point 38 point 1...
Look it!
Cool, huh? Look!
- Can I please have your nails?
- Nails?
I'm collecting them. Can I?
Just the pinky
would be all right,
but anything you could give me
would be great for my collection.
What are you doing?
Children!
Oh... Edward!
Is that really...
Is it you, Edward?
I'm sorry about all that.
I'm afraid it's the only way I can get
the kids to pay attention sometimes.
It's all right.
Is Edward...
Is she from this place?
She wandered in
about five years ago.
Before I knew it, she was eating here
as if that's the way it always was.
Then about three years ago,
she wandered away again.
Like a cat, you know?
I've often wondered how
she's been getting along.
But I didn't think that she
would suddenly appear like this.
Children, let's eat!
Our Father in heaven,
you know we're here...
so I'll leave off the rest.
Eat hearty, kids!
Thanks, amen.
- Hey, I can eat faster than you can!
- Get your elbow out of my face!
Uh... I'm afraid I have to go now.
Why, dear? You're welcome here.
Actually, I'm looking for something.
Ed knows where it is.
We just came here 'cause
there's good food, Faye-Faye.
You little rat.
You have to give me something good!
Oh, that's right...
There's something good
in my desk drawer.
- I've been saving it for you, Edward.
- Something good?
- See for yourself.
- Something good for Ed?
It's in the top drawer.
No, not that one.
Yes, that's it. Open it up.
- It's your father.
- Ed's father?
Mm-hmm. He came here looking
for Ed about two months ago.
He said he forgot that he
put her in a daycare center,
and that he'd been looking for her for
seven years, hopping around the world.
Oh, he's not your
model father, I suppose...
Still, I do hope she finds him.
In this world, people must
cherish whatever ties they have.
Yes!
Are you... Faye?
You are! Impossible!
It's me, Sally Yung!
I was in your graduating
class in high school.
Are you okay?
I was so surprised.
I thought you were
some kind of ghost.
You look just the same as before.
They say they appear in places
where they have regrets.
Of course, I remember now.
They put you into cryogenic
hibernation after that accident.
- That's why you still look the same.
- Accident?
Faye, don't you remember it?
Maybe...
Grandma! Hey, Grandma!
Grandma, we have to go back now.
Is it time already?
Do you know who this nice lady is?
You'll never believe it, dear.
- But the fact is that she's--
- a ghost from beyond.
Goodbye, take care.
All right, you two!
Changing course without asking...
Our plans have been completely
screwed up because of this.
I don't appreciate these
kinds of stunts, Faye.
Hey, Ein, I got us something.
Wanna smell?
What's with them?
It's like they got a
big secret or something.
Better let it be.
Maybe they're just
too hungry, you know?
It's a known fact that human beings
go insane if they don't eat.
It's 50 million?
Huh, that's pretty big.
Appledelhi Siniz Hesap Lutfen.
You want one? Huh? Macinroe?
It's Macintire, and I'll take a pass,
Mr. Appledelhi. Thanks.
You sure?
Sucking eggs is good for you.
Give you power and charge.
That's what counts.
Telling you, Macintosh.
It's Macintire, actually.
I know I'm just your assistant,
but you could remember
my name. It's not hard.
Don't sweat the small stuff, my friend.
- Hurry, Macin... whatever!
- Macintire!
Hey, watch where you're going!
- Uh...
- What?
- I'm sorry.
- You're... sorry?
Yes.
I have to go.
Are you going out?
Where are you going, huh?
Edward...
I finally remember
where it is that I belong.
You belong?
Yes, Ed. You have someone
waiting for you, too.
There's somewhere that
you belong, Edward.
- You should go and find out where.
- Hmm...
It's the best. Belonging is
the very best thing there is.
This is gonna be a piece of cake.
50 million in the bag.
If the girls could eat some
sukiyaki with meat, then--
Jet, Faye took off again.
Oh, swell. Where'd she
go this time, Arcturus?
A woman's heart's as fickle
as the skies of Ganymede.
Appledelhi.
We'd like you to come
along with us, all right?
A little basic cooperation here,
and you won't get hurt.
Who are you guys? We got
work to do, and you're in the way.
Work to do?
Since the gate accident,
chaos rules the Earth.
Now how do you think
we can regain peaceful peace,
- and non-chaos in the cosmic sense?
- Huh?
Only through maps. That's right!
The Earth has changed, so we map
those changes to understand them.
We're creating maps of the newly altered
planet Earth so we can save it.
That's great. Only the meteor showers
change the terrain every two days.
So what you're trying
to do is impossible.
Bah, that's exactly why
we travel around so much.
We chase down every major meteor.
Then we update the maps,
thus changing chaos to order.
All right, I've heard enough.
I wasn't expecting a match.
- Edward!
- Hey, hold it!
Françoise!
Yay!
'Round and 'round we go!
- Higher! Higher!
- Upsy-daisy!
This is the father-person.
F-Father?
You mean your father?
You have... a father?
This is Spike-person
and Jet-person, okay?
Okay.
No, these are Ed's friends!
I stay with them, okay?
Oh, that's different.
Thanks for taking care of my son.
Or, uh, was it my daughter?
Well, either way,
you guys are all right.
Little token of my appreciation.
Ed, don't tell me,
did you put that bounty
in the computer or--
Fifty point zero, zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero.
Only 50 Woolongs?
So, Françoise, wanna stay with me now?
Hey!
Wow!
Whoa! Let's go, Macindingle!
It's Macintire!
Hey, hold on!
Father-person gone.
♪ I close my eyes and
I keep seeing things ♪
♪ Rainbow waterfalls ♪
♪ Sunny liquid dreams ♪
♪ Confusion creeps
inside me raining down ♪
♪ Got to get to you ♪
♪ But I don't know how ♪
♪ Call me, call me ♪
♪ Let me know it's all right ♪
Hey, dinner's ready!
♪ Please, won't you call and ♪
♪ Ease my mind ♪
Spike. Food.
♪ Reasons for me to find you ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
♪ What can I do ♪
♪ To get me to you ♪
♪ I had your number
quite some time ago ♪
♪ Back when we were young ♪
♪ But I had to go ♪
♪ Ten thousand years I've
searched it seems and now ♪
♪ Got to get to you ♪
♪ Won't you tell me how ♪
You can't come with me, Ein.
Edward is going
someplace far, far away.
Ed might not be coming back.
So you better go back to the ship, Ein.
Oh...
Do you wanna come with Ed?
♪ Come on now, won't you ♪
♪ Ease my mind ♪
♪ Reasons for me to find you ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
♪ What can I do ♪
Come on, let's go!
♪ To get me to you ♪
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
Everything has a beginning and an end.
Life is just a cycle
of stops and starts.
There are ends we don't desire,
but they're inevitable.
We have to face them.
That's what being human is all about.
It's been a fast trip for Bebop.
Only two episodes left.
But make sure you pay
close attention to the end.
Next episode:
"The Real Folk Blues, Part 1."