Tora Dora! Episode 7 English Translation by KloneDesu
() Are notes/information for the timer/editor.
What would you do if I revealed my true self, Takasu-kun?
Huh?
Would you fall for me?
Well?
W-Wait a second...
I—
Taiga! Were they there?
Taiga?
Uh oh, looks like I'm in trouble.
I guess I'm bad at timing things.
T-This isn't what it looks like.
Ta-i-ga!
Minorin! It looks like no one's here.
Where did they go off to?
Oh? I wonder why you're covering it up.
Could it be that you don't want to acknowledge it?
The fact that he let a woman other than you into his room.
Stu—Don't say it in such a suspicious way!
What? But—
It's not "but"!
Hurry and tell her the truth!
The truth? Oh my, Takasu-kun.
T-Taiga?
Taiga?
Good mornin'.
Did something happen Taiga-chan?
Nothing at all; not to me anyway.
I wonder what today's meal is.
It's steamed rice. You like it right?
Oh? You should have made it steamed bean rice...
Wha—?
Right ugly-bird?
Ug—?
H-Hey, Taiga, about the thing that happened this afternoon.
Kawashima was just messing with me.
I mean... it seems to have made you feel bad so I'm sorry.
Oh no! Why are you apologizing?
Ryuuji's quite a strange one.
I-Inko-chan?!
Hang in there Inko-chan!
Keep your head straight!
Taiga, wake up!
Crap, there's not much time!
I-It hurts…
Huh?
S-Sorry.
What?
More importantly, we're late!
Just hurry and get ready!
What's for breakfast?
Why did you wake me up like this today?
There's no breakfast or lunch prepared.
If we don't get out in five minutes, we're going to be late!
Aww man! If we don't go to the convenience store, we won't have any lunch!
Hey, are you listening, Tai—ga?!
I'm listening you perverted dog! The convenience store right?
What's the matter with you? It's just food—
Ow!
Made it in time!
Oh, you're finally here!
Thanks for everything you did for me yesterday.
Wha—? Uh-Ye-Yeah...
What was that?
Could it be that you were entranced by my summer outfit?
Just kidding.
You're blocking traffic, stupid chihuahua.
O-Oh, you were there too Aisaka-san? Good morning...
Good morning Kawashima-san.
Thanks for being in heat so early in the morning.
Hey. You guys—
Oh, is that it? Sheesh.
Don't get jealous over something like that.
That was just your misunderstanding.
You don't understand well either. Yesterday was jus—
Hurrah!
Good morning everyone!
Woah! This might be a bit of a challenge!
Minorin, stop strength training with me.
Alright. Tomorrow is the pool opening that everyone has been waiting for.
I'll be going over the rules now.
When you think of summer you think of a step forward in love.
It's my last chance in my 20's.
Aww, my belly's going to be a problem.
Yeah, for me it's my thighs.
I'm telling you, mine is more worse.
How can you guys say that? Isn't being young good enough, damn it?!
What? We have to take swimming class with the boys in this school?
Oh no, I'm so embarrassed.
Why the hell would you be? You're insanely cute.
You're a freaking model. What's so damn embarrassing?
What, huh?! What? What? What the hell man!
Teacher, how about we end homeroom now?
Alright, do the call!
Stand!
Taiga, come on, hurry!
No! I'm not buying any swimsuits!
You don't have a choice; you let last year's rot.
You have to immediately wash and dry swimsuits after you use them.
I said that I don't want to!
And why is "that" thing here too?!
That's because this is the only store that sells swimsuits.
I-I-It's not like I asked her to come.
Hey-hey. I think this would look perfect on Aisaka-san!
Hmm, it might look "too" good.
Calm down Taiga, people are looking!
Takasu-kun, what do you think of this?
Um. I-I think it looks really g-good—
Hey! How do you think this looks?
It's not weird is it? Does it make me stand out in an odd way?
What's up with those long legs?!
You're standing out like crazy!
What? Is that true? But I chose this dull swimsuit too.
K-Kawashima-san. What brand is that swimsuit? Where was it?
Over there. Oh, do you want to wear the same one?
No, please don't! Let me off the hook from that!
Kushieda?
Hey-hey!
I'm like way, way, way too cute!
Isn't it unbelievable? I'm even wearing this dull swimsuit!
How far can it go? This cutness, this beauty, this great style!
Isn't it like pretty much a crime to hide it?
Right? Don't you think so too Takasu-kun?
Huh?
Hey, are you okay Tai—
What the hell are y—?!
I don't know what to do anymore...
What is it, what's wrong?
I can't make it work no matter what.
What is it that you don't like?
The only colors you can use are black or navy blue.
That's not it, I can't find the right size!
You could—try the kids' sizes.
I'd rather die!
Stop saying the same thing as that stupid chihuahua.
This one looks pretty small.
The price is just right and the material seems durable enough for a dryer.
Have you tried it on?
Well...
I did try it...
I guess that one was somewhat okay.
But... How do I put it? Umm...
Then this should be fine. Right?
Yeah. I suppose.
Taiga! What do you want for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want to eat.
Oh yeah. Did you prepare for the pool?
Don't forget to bring a towel, a bath towel.
Shut up.
You're so—
What's your problem?
Is it the swimsuit?
Don't tell me that you're still mad about the other night.
No!
Then what is it?!
I can't swim.
That's my problem.
Stuff you can say so easily isn't the real problem.
Oh no! I'm late, I'm late!
Hey, wait a sec!
At least drink this.
Thank you Ryuu-chan.
It's hot.
What's that?
It's Ryuu-chan's specially made soy-milk.
There's Isobom-bom or something in the soybeans that can make your breasts bigger.
It's Isoflavon.
It'd be a major problem if they shrunk, so it's my precaution.
I'm so smart.
Taiga-chan you're so perverted, sketchy, one-touch~!
Stop sexually harassing people's parents!
I'm heading out~!
Sheesh, that was a bother.
What's wrong with you?
Something's odd.
Beans...
Hey!
It's nasty! Give me another!
What in the world are you doing?
I want some Isobun-mum too!
Why would you want—?
The swimsuit sizes... Isoflavon...
Taiga, could it be that you're—
No! Don't say it! Don't say anymore than that!
Are you flat-chested?
Sheesh, is it something to be that worried about?
It's just breast size.
Thanks for waiting.
Y-Yeah.
How is it?
It's flat isn't it?
I'm flat-chested right?
No... w-well...
What about the cup?
It went in but... i-it's concave...
It went in, but... i-it's concave...
That's why I don't like pools.
A-Anyway, put something on.
You'll catch a cold.
What's this?
If you see that, you'll understand my sorrow too.
This is... harsh.
It says pathetic chest, pathetic.
They thought my chest was so flat that it was pathetic!
Well, no, this is just the opinion of the person who wrote this.
Of course I made red rain pour over the picture club this came out of.
Now that I think about it, the picture club disappeared abruptly.
To think that I have to show my pathetic self to Kitamura-kun...
I can't stand it... I can't stand it...
Hey, Taiga.
Alright. I'll do something about it.
What?
So that you can proudly show yourself in front of Kitamura.
I'll do something.
It's alright; you can just go home and sleep.
No, I'll wait here until it's ready.
I'll stay up until you're done, Ryuuji.
Hey.
I-I bluffed and acted weird...
Um... I'm sorry.
How is it?
I'll definitely take it with me when I wed.
Maruo!
Maruo, you look so much better without glasses.
You should wear contacts.
Is that so?
Definitely!
I'm not wearing glasses.
Yeah.
See you later, Aisaka-san. I'm going ahead.
Taiga?
Come on, hurry. I'll help with your head.
Uh-yeah.
Maya-chan, I'm sorry.
I just couldn't get my hair together well.
Sorry for the wait.
Ami-chan! Wow, leave it to the model!
Your style is so great.
What?
I'm so moved!
That's not true.
You're totally on a different level from us.
She's a goddess!
Now, now.
You're damn right; I'm so cute today! I'll allow you plebeians to bow before your angel!
Go on, lick my shadow. Isn't it the most exquisite meal for you?
Don't tease me Maya-chan.
Takasu-kun.
Minorin, don't run!
My hair's going to fall apart again!
Alright, let's go straight to the warm-up exercises.
Time to run; sike!
Minorin?
Kushieda?
I've already figured it out!
Huh?
As long as I'm in this pool, no one will see my belly!
So I'll be swimming now. Ciao!
Minorin...
Oh my, Aisaka-san, you're finally here?
I thought that you might have been unable to come out because your swimsuit was too big.
Huh? What are you talking about? Are you sleep talking? Are you asleep?
Sheesh.
Oh man. I hope I don't get sun-burned.
It's perfect.
You were able to get this far in one year? Well done!
I'm for Taiga after all.
Sheesh, that's just average. The scale's wrong as usual though.
I did it!
Yeah!
Ginyu Special Forces.
She knows.
As expected of Minorin.
Aisaka?
Huh? Aisaka? It's you right?
I can't see well since I'm not wearing my glasses, but, that size is Aisaka.
Why are you hiding it?
I like that hair, it's like a mouse.
Go away!
What?!
Did I say something wrong?
I-I don't know.
Hey, show me your arm muscles.
Like this?
Wow, that's amazing!
He's the only one—
that's so popular!
We'll question society!
This is a summer drop!
Hey.
Let's do it.
It's a "free" class as usual, but, isn't this a bit dangerous?
Hey Tai—
Kitamura-kun... said my hair's cute...
No, he said he liked it, but—
We've found our prey!
Here we go my softball companion!
Alright, let's head to the next one!
Right, boss!
Haha~ they dropped you!
Yeah, it seems really fun doesn't it, Aisaka-san?
Y-You—
I'm just playing around.
I don't want you to get mad for real.
Hey, you could have gone a little easier on her!
Come now, I was just playing around.
Hey, you alright Taiga?
Taiga?
She—
I can't swim!
Could it be that—
She really can't swim?
No way!
Hold on a second.
Taiga!
Teacher!
No!
Calm down Taiga!
What should I do? It came off!
Only one side!
Hey, isn't that pretty bad?
Aisaka.
Taiga!
Aisaka!
Not now!
I'm coming!
Taiga!
Damn it!
If that's the case—
Taiga.
Humiliation...
I told you I'm sorry.
I didn't know that you couldn't swim.
Come on, everyone left. Cheer up already.
It's not something that can be fixed by apologizing.
Because you did such a senseless thing my... b-breas-b-b-b—
Anyway. Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize!
Well, I guess we can't go to places like beaches or pools if Aisaka-san can't swim!
Hey Takasu-kun. I have a villa out by a beach.
Would you like to spend your summer with me?
Hold on a second. Weren't you apologizing to Taiga?
Oh, then would it be alright if Yuusaku was with us?
Hmm? Is something wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you do something selfish like this again, your 100 impersonations video is going into circulation.
Oh wait, was it 150?
If you did something like that, I might sue you for copyright infringement.
Even the great palm-top Taiga wouldn't stand against the hammer of law.
Hey, you guys—
Stop yourselves!
You'll scar your knuckles.
Oh, but-but, Minori-chan, Aisaka-san was about to—
It's this stupid chihuahua's fault!
Hey, what are you saying?!
In the first place—
Shut it!
If you want to nurture your friendship with knuckles don't fight...!
Compete in sports!
S-Sports?
A battle for Takasu!
Ami-tan VS Taiga?!
Why is it that he gets to always being in such a delicious situation?!
Oh, fight over me too! Just mess me all up!