What is it?
I'm going to become one
fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
with the gently floating
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラめく遠くの空と
and glittering distant sky.
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
The wind will carry me at its will
kaze yomi kimama na
風読み気ままな
to my destination far beyond.
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
Won't you come with me?
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう？
I take a deep breath and bask in
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
the world's Spring Breath.
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
We all gather in the sunlight
taiyou ni atsumaru no
太陽に　あつまるの
with radiant smiles.
minna no egao
みんなの笑顔
Between "good morning" and "good-bye,"
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
it'll just be us.
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
We can do anything.
nandemo dekiru ne
なんでもできるね
The translucent sunlight,
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日射し
and the newborn sky,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
and the Morning Arch where we promised to meet.
machiawaseta yakusoku no Morning Arch
待ちあわせた　約束のMorning Arch
As you wave your hand at me,
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
I'll give you this new day I've been saving,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
and we'll chat the day away.
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
Carbonation
Run!
What is it?
About yesterday...
Right.
Run, you dropped your notebook!
The new volume went on sale, right?
Really?
Megumi
Akiba Shingo
Azuma Atsuko
Watanabe
Machino Takuya
Togawa Haruna
Suenaga Tetsuya
Kisaragi Hitomi
Katsura Aki
Sasaki Yuu
Ueno Kyouko
Shimokawa Kazuki
Nagai Akemi
Kubota Motoko
Kobayashi Mari
Morikawa Jun
Ari Rika
Rina
Makita Kaori
Shouko
Kubota Motoko
Kyuuno Shino
Satou Youko
Nagai Akemi
Ueno Kyouko
Sasaki Yuu
Maisonneuve
Klaus
Sonya
Sanju
Engi
What's up?
I-I-I-I-I'm sorry!
I'll forget all about it, so please don't kill me!
I'm sorry...
What are you talking about?
This notebook.
It's that one used to curse people you have a grudge against, right?
No, it's not.
This is my exchange notebook with Tooru.
That's one of Tooru's pages.
Then what are all these names for?
A memory test!
We're seeing who can write down the most names of people they've met.
Why, exactly?
But man, her memory's good.
I'll bet I couldn't beat her.
Not to mention, all the names turn foreign-sounding halfway through.
Did Tooru live abroad at one point?
Uh-uh.
Starting there are characters from manga she's read.
Oh, that explains the strange names.
Justine, Michelle Richard
Justine?
Ooh. Michelle Richard.
Jule Auguste Gianne.
Marie-Françoise Victoire!
Oh?
Dovoch Hekenovich.
François Poronac Haque.
Michel Bomparnasse.
O'Brien Vukovich.
Alessandro Galexon.
Paul Ginades!
Andreas Banderas!
Grakios Andretti!
What's this?
Salvadore Andrea!
Heisel Poncho!
Yuuko.
Velázquez!
What is it?
So what did Tooru say?
She said she had something to show us, so come over.
I wonder what it is?
But I've never been to Tooru's place before, so I'm pretty excited!
Neither have I.
Wonder what kind of place it is?
You'll see soon.
Right here!
That's quite the nice apartment she lives in.
Let's go!
Right.
Gosh, that Tooru. She didn't have to go home early just to clean up.
Maybe there's something she doesn't want you to see?
What's wrong?
This feels like a foot massager! It's so nice!
Quit acting like an old lady and hurry up!
Tooru! We're here!
It's open! Come in!
Okay!
Pardon the intrusion!
Tooru! We're coming in!
So messy!
Is Tooru bad at cleaning up?
Uh-uh.
She's usually obsessively neat.
In other words, this must be...
A ransacked room.
Its owner, missing.
And the windows, locked from the inside.
A locked-room murder!
Except the front entrance was open.
Oh?
She wasn't just being a slob.
Take a look. The trash in the trash bin just got scattered around.
In other words, the trash went for a walk.
It's not like they have legs.
Oh no! A human is coming!
It all makes sense!
In any case, should we clean up?
Yeah.
I doubt it's what you were thinking, Run-chan.
Sorry it's so messy.
This little guy was tearing up the room.
Little guy?
So cute!
Where'd you get this cat?
I picked him up this morning.
It seems he was abandoned.
I get it! Cats have legs too, don't they?
I have no idea what you mean, Run.
A cat could be personified, too!
What are you talking about?
And then, I bet it'd be Tooru!
Tha-
... I think I could live with that.
Right?
What's that supposed to mean?
See you!
See you tomorrow!
Say bye to the kitty for me!
See you later!
It's gotten colder. You okay, Tooru?
Yeah.
That's right!
Want to grab something to eat on the way back?
Sure. I'd like something sweet.
Then we could go to a family restaurant.
Let's head through the shopping district.
The shopping district, huh?
In that case, can we stop by somewhere on the way?
If I remember, it was somewhere around here...
Where are we headed?
I want to buy a collar.
Ah, I see.
While we're at it, some cat toys, and various other stuff.
Toys?
In that case, I know a place!
Toys
I'm sure they'll sell them here, no problem!
Adult Toys
They'll sell them, no problem.
But there's a huge problem!
Welcome!
A white cat, so...
what color would look good?
Red? Blue?
Look at how serious she is.
You must really care for that cat.
I really care for you, too, Run-chan.
I know~
That tickles...
Welcome to G-N's!
Thank you for your patience.
Please, have a seat.
Tooru, you can have the sofa seat.
No, you have it, Run-chan.
Then let's just sit together!
Ah, oh yeah.
About my cat.
I can never decide at the drink bar.
How many flavors are you putting in?
Five-delicious-flavors-at-once mixed juice!
So you haven't decided on the cat's name yet.
Yeah...
I can't come up with a good one.
Why not name it after a sweet or a juice?
Since you like them.
Ah, that's a good idea.
What I've got here right now are...
cola, cider, ramune, ginger ale, and melon soda, so...
putting them all together, you get...
"Carbonation"!
We're back!
How've you been doing?
Starting today, you'll be named "Carbonation"!
He's very well-behaved.
He runs wild now and then, though.
Carbonation, that collar looks good on you!
Such a cutie!
Hm?
Are you hungry?
We'll feed you right away.
Oh, we got you some toys, too,
so let's play after you eat!
Run-chan.
Let's talk about something.
I ended up not getting any attention from Run-chan.
Good morning, Carbonation.
It's that late already?
I'd better change.
Bad boy. You'll get fur on my uniform.
I don't have time to play with you.
Temperatures will be very low this morning, continuing throughout the day.
The chance of snow this afternoon is high,
so please be prepared as you leave home today.
Oh, all right.
I'll be off, then.
Morning, Tooru!
It's gotten even colder today.
Apparently it's going to snow today, Run-chan.
Well, according to the forecast.
Really?
Wait just a sec!
What was it?
Deluxe
Strawberry
Ta-dah!
I brought syrup!
For the snow?
Yep.
Yuuko-chan, morning!
Good morning!
Another cold morning today.
Yeah.
Morning.
Morn-
Nagi! What's with that outfit?
The forecast said snow, so I made suitable preparations.
You look like an assassin! How cool!
Don't you mean a pervert?
Honestly.
Why do we have to come to school in this blasted cold?
It's only natural. We're students.
Don't you think they should make it winter break from the end of fall to the start of spring?
You must hate winter.
Despite constantly ranting about how hot summer was.
When the snow comes falling, I just lose the will to live.
What's with the depressing talk?
Snowy days are full of fun things!
Like making snowmen, or making igloos,
or having snowball fights!
Nagi-chan, you should pray for snow, too!
Huh?
Did you even listen to a single thing I said?
1st
per-
iod
2nd
per-
iod
3rd
per-
iod
4th
per-
iod
It's not going to snow.
I'm sure of it.
Haven't given up yet, I see.
Well, I've half given up.
Just completely give up.
Whoa! It's started snowing!
Huh?
What?
Awesome!
Cool!
It's the first snow!
It's true. It's snowing!
Ugh.
The weather changes on a dime.
Run, isn't that wonderf-
Huh?
She's gone!
It's here!
Lunch! Lunch!
Eat your bento, not snow!
Looks like it'll pile up.
It's coming down hard!
If a lot piles up,
I've always wanted to try this once!
Get buried so deep, you can't see the bottom!
Just like in a manga.
If I jumped from here, I bet I could do it!
What?
That's a little...
Ah, then what about from the roof?
I don't think it'll work.
It piled up!
Amazing!
All right! Let's go!
Yay!
Run-chan.
Did she die?
She's eating it!
Run-chan, don't do that!
Hey, let's all jump in!
Gosh, don't do that so suddenly!
What was that, out of nowhere?
That's dangerous, you know.
Huh? What?
Yuuko-chan, that's a funny pose!
Nice one, Yuuko.
Gosh!
Snow...
Huh?
Snow is...
quite warm.
Nagi?
Nagi, are you okay?
You look cold.
That's right!
Huh?
Nagi-chan, we'll warm you up!
What are you doing, Run-chan?
I'm making an igloo for Nagi-chan.
Ah!
I hear those are warm!
I'll help!
There we go.
Nagi-chan, it's done!
Looks cramped.
Nagi, feeling warmer?
Yeah, better than outside.
Thank goodness.
You're wide open, Yuuko-chan! Hi-yah!
Here I come, too!
Now you've done it!
My heart dances for joy at the snowflake on the forecast.
The cold doesn't mean a thing.
Come on, let's pray.
If, from the sky above,
snow falls, we'll be Lucky. On a whim, let's make a Snow man.
Leaving behind footprints,
let's pretend to dive right in.
Pile up more and more!
Keep snowing forever and ever!
After playing around so much outside,
I'm surprised I didn't catch a cold.
"I caught a cold. -Yuuko"
Why did you catch one?
Oh.
"I've got a fever of 38 degrees. -Tooru"
"Looks like I've caught a cold. -Run"
I think
I think I
I think I aatggt
I think I baught
I think I caught
I think I caught mm
I think I caught nn
I think I caught on
I think I caught ond t
I think I caught one t
I think I caught one tmm
I think I caught one tnn
I think I caught one too
I think I caught one too.
"Sending"
The tall shadows
akane ni narabu
茜に並ぶ
line up in the sunset
seitaka kageboushi
背高かげぼうし
at the end of another happy day.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きない　お喋り
Our chatter goes on and on,
and I still have more to say,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but it's about time we headed home.
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね、明日ね
I'll text you!"
meeru suru kara
メールするから
On today's page, everyone's
kyou no peeji ni minna
今日のページにみんな
wearing matching smiles.
osoroi no egao
おそろいの笑顔
"See you again tomorrow!
jaa ne ashita ne
じゃあね、明日ね
Thanks for everything!
itsumo arigato
いつもありがと
I'm so glad we got to hang out together again today."
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒にいれて　ヨカッタな
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
ru-ru-run
ル・ル・ルン・
My heart hums with the wind.
kaze to kokoro hamingu suru
風とココロ　ハミングする
At the next street corner,
tsugi no kado de
つぎの角で
we'll turn around, and say, "Bye bye."
furimukinagara baibai
振り向きながら　バイバイ
Come here.
Nice and warm.
S...
So cold...
Okay, everyone!
Let's shovel with all we've got!
Yes ma'am...
Next time
What did we do last winter?
Yutaka was tutoring you for high school entrance exams, Miporin!
You liar!
Next time on A-Channel!
"Birthday"!
Everyone, good luck with your exam studying!
Do you even know what month it is now?
See you next week!