I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a twist of fate changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
The encounter that
led me towards magic...
was it just a coincidence,
or was it fate?
I'm not quite sure right now, but...
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
The Lost Logia are around here, correct?
They're in the form of blue jewels...
referred to as "Jewel Seeds."
That's right.
I'll have them soon enough.
Episode 4
A Rival!? Another Magical Girl!
Come on, Yuuno... c'mere, c'mere!
Good, good.
You're so smart, Yuuno.
Nanoha, are you ready yet?
Ah... sorry!
Just a little longer!
Huh? Are you two going
somewhere today?
Yeah, to the Tsukimuras's.
Apparently Suzuka-chan
invited Nanoha over.
Ah... I see.
So... I suppose you're going
over too, to see Shinobu-san.
Well... I thought Nanoha might need
someone to walk her over, so...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let's go, then.
If we leave now, we should
be able to catch the bus.
Okay!
Yuuno-kun, come here!
Well, have a nice time.
Yep.
We're off!
We made plans to have a tea party
at Suzuka-chan's house today.
I'll be spending the whole day with
Arisa-chan and Suzuka-chan.
And Onii-chan is coming along to see
Suzuka-chan's older sister, Shinobu-san.
Oh, it's nothing, really.
Is that so?
Master Kyouya,
Miss Nanoha, welcome.
Thank you for the invitation.
Hello!
This is the Tsukimura family's
head maid, Noel-san.
She's a little reserved,
but she's beautiful and really cool!
Please, come in.
Right this way.
Nanoha-chan! Kyouya-san!
Suzuka-chan.
Nanoha-chan, welcome!
This is Falin-san.
She's Suzuka-chan's personal maid,
and she's like a cheerful and kind older sister.
Kyouya... glad you could make it.
Yeah.
Onii-chan and Shinobu-san have been
classmates since high school.
And they're still really close to each other even now.
Allow me to prepare some tea.
Which type would you like?
I'll leave it up to you.
And for Miss Nanoha?
I'll leave it up to you, too!
Understood.
Falin.
Yes. Coming, Onee-sama.
Well then... Kyouya and I will be up in my room...
All right. I'll bring the tea up to you when it's ready.
Good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
Suzuka's sister and Nanoha's brother are as lovey-dovey as ever!
Yes.
Ever since Onee-chan's gotten to know
Kyouya-san, she's seemed really happy.
As for my older brother... who knows?
But I think he's lightened up a bit
from how he used to be.
He smiles a lot more now.
I see.
Before I forget,
thanks for inviting me today.
Not at all. It's my pleasure,
so thank you for coming.
You seem to be in high spirits today.
Nanoha-chan, you've looked
a little down recently, so...
If you're worried about something,
maybe you could talk to us about it?
At least, that's what the two of
us were talking about earlier.
Suzuka-chan...
Arisa-chan...
Yuuno-kun!
Ai, stop that!
Here I am!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I brought you some strawberry
milk tea and cream cheese cookies!
Falin, watch out!
Safe...
Suzuka-chan! Nanoha-chan! I'm sorry!
There she goes again...
She's quite a handful at times.
But anyway, your house sure
is cat heaven as usual, huh?
It's okay, since the kittens are so cute.
Yeah!
But some kittens are already getting adopted, so I'll have to part with them...
I see...
I guess that's kind of sad, huh?
Still, I'm happy the kittens will be
able to grow up big and healthy.
Yeah.
You're so cute...
There, there.
Nanoha...
Yeah... it's really close.
What should we do?
Um...
Uh...
I know!
Yuuno-kun?
Huh? What's gotten into Yuuno?
I think he found something.
I-I'll go look for him.
Should we go with you?
I'll be fine. We'll be right
back, so just wait here.
It's been activated!
There's a good chance of us being seen.
I'll put up a barrier this time!
A barrier...?
The same kind of space I made when I first met you.
Inside the barrier, time flows slightly
differently than normal space.
It's one of the few types
of magic I'm good at.
I can't make it very big, but...
If I only need to cover this immediate area,
I should be able to manage.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Th... Th... Th...
That's...
P-Probably...
That kitten's wish to become
big... was granted literally?
I... I see...
But things will get dangerous if we
don't return it to normal soon...
Y-You're right.
It'd probably be a big problem for
Suzuka-chan if it stayed that size.
It doesn't look like it'll come after us,
so if we just seal it now, nice and quickly...
Well then... Raising Heart!
Bardiche. Photon Lancer - Electricity.
Photon Lancer. Full auto fire.
Wha–?!
Light from magic...
That can't be...
Raising Heart... please!
Stand by, ready. Set up.
Flier Fin.
Wide Area Protection.
A mage...
I'm a little less surprised every
time I see what she can do.
Maybe there's nothing more I can teach Nanoha.
Another mage, just like me...
She's also searching for the Lost Logia.
There's no doubt about it now...
She comes from my world.
And this girl... she knows the true
identity of the Jewel Seeds...
Another Intelligent Device,
just like my Bardiche.
Bardiche...?
The Lost Logia... the Jewel Seeds...
Scythe Form, Set up.
Forgive me,
but I'll be taking this one.
Evasion.
Flier Fin.
Arc Saber.
Protection.
Nanoha!
Why?
Why are you doing this so suddenly?
Even if I answer...
it probably won't mean anything to you.
Device Form.
Shooting Mode.
Divine Buster, Stand by.
Photon Lancer, Get set.
I'm sure she's around my age...
She has such beautiful eyes and hair...
But... this girl is...
I'm sorry...
Fire.
Nanoha!
Sealing Form, Set up.
Capture!
Order?
Lost Logia... Jewel Seed Serial XIV.
Seal.
Yes, sir.
Sealing.
Captured.
When I woke up, the evening twilight
had already stained the sky.
Yuuno-kun went and got my brother and everyone else.
I lied a little and said I tripped and fainted
while I was searching for Yuuno-kun.
I made everyone worry...
and I really regret doing that.
That staff, those clothes, and how she used magic...
She's probably...
No, I'm sure of it.
She's from my world.
Yeah...
I wonder... if we'll run into her again...
while gathering the rest of the Jewel Seeds?
Strangely, that thought doesn't really scare me...
But... I'm sad, and filled with
so many confusing feelings...
There was a bit of a hindrance,
but everything turned out all right.
Jewel Seed... Serial XIV...
I wonder... how many she has?
It'll be all right.
I won't stray from my path.
Wait for me, Mother...
I'll return to you soon...
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
Sometimes students and
working people need a break!
And with that said,
we're all here,
at our local
Uminari Hot Springs!
Who's this causing trouble, just when we started to relax?!
And what's that mysterious
magical girl after?
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 5
This Is a City of Hot Water, the Uminari Hot Springs!
Episode Five: This Is a City of Hot Water, the Uminari Hot Springs!
Lyrical Magical,
doing my best!