Huh?
Kurumi-chan!
Ri-san!
Mii-kun!
So...
this is where I'm going to die.
Kei...
I'm sorry,
I'll never see you again!
Broadcasting Room
There it is!
NO!
No!
Taromaru?!
Broadcasting Room
Taromaru!
C'mere, Taromaru.
You like my hat, right?
I knew you remembered.
You're really hurt...
You're bitten.
You're so cold.
I'm sorry.
I can't do anything for you.
Everyone remembers.
Even if their hearts are gone,
there's something deep inside them that does.
That's why they keep coming back here.
Right, Megu-nee?
It's time to go home.
Attention students on the school grounds,
please make your way home quickly.
Do you like school?
I love school.
You might think I'm weird,
but school is amazing!
The science room has all kinds of weird devices.
The music room has lots of
pretty instruments and spooky portraits!
The broadcasting room
makes the whole school your stage!
School has everything.
It's like one big country!
No other building can compare.
I love school.
I don't like studying, but I like the teachers.
When you forget your homework,
someone shows you theirs.
When you fall asleep in class,
the teacher gets mad.
Sometimes you get along with your classmates,
sometimes you fight with them.
But we're all here together as one.
There are so many happy times
and so many sad times.
That's why...
I love school so much.
Yuki
Lovely~
And you love it, too.
You've loved it for so long.
That's why you're all here.
But all good things...
must come to an end.
It's kinda sad...
that it can't go on forever.
But I think it's better that it ends.
So, school is finally over.
I hope we can meet again.
But today, it's all done.
To everyone here at school:
Hello.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
Shh!
Kurumi-chan!
Kurumi-chan! Kurumi-chan!
There, there.
Morning.
Good morning...
Kurumi!
Welcome back, Kurumi-chan!
I'm back all right.
Thank goodness.
Taromaru?!
Ri-san, Taromaru's gonna get better, right?
Right?
I gave him the shot.
But he might've been too far gone...
Taromaru?
Do you remember me?
Hey, don't push it, save your strength!
Maybe Taromaru's hungry.
See?
He really does nothing but eat.
I'll go get some.
Taromaru
He should only have a little bit at a time.
Right.
Senpai, bring me some water!
Right!
Just wait one sec, okay?
Here, have some water.
Welcome back, Taromaru.
Yuki-senpai told me that you saved her.
You're such a smart dog.
You led Senpai to me that day
in the mall, too, didn't you?
And you helped her save me, too.
It's all thanks to you, Taromaru.
But it's alright.
We'll be together forever now.
Taromaru?
C'mon, what?
That should be good.
Yes.
Miki-san?
R-right.
Hey.
Can I put this in, too?
Sure. I think he'd like it.
See ya...
Shall we say goodbye, then?
You ready?
Yeah.
Mii-kun, are you okay?
I'm alright.
Taromaru saved me.
So I've got to say goodbye with a smile.
You don't have to.
You shouldn't try to hold back all the sad things.
Because you'll forget the important things instead.
I'm so glad I was your teacher.
I'd forgotten Megu-nee's last words.
So it's okay to be sad when you're sad.
It's okay if you're not okay.
Yuki-senpai...
So don't forget Taromaru's last words, okay?
Last words?
Taromaru didn't...
He did!
He looked right at you!
And said, "Thank you!"
I-I wanted to...
thank him, too...
There wasn't a lot of food underground.
Our refrigerator isn't working anymore,
Let's all graduate!
so we need to eat our perishables quickly.
We'll start with the frozen stuff then, huh?
Okay, first come, first serve!
Yay, I found a ton of Unmaibo!
Those aren't frozen!
Yuki-senpai's still Yuki-senpai.
Aww, I can't have them?
Okay, I'll just go with another snack.
Can we still use the stove?
You can have snacks later! Later!
We can until the emergency power runs out.
I don't think it'll last very long, though.
Our water's running pretty thin, too.
Yes.
The water collection ran on electricity, too.
So we'll have to leave this place after all, huh?
But there probably isn't a place like this
where we'll have all the necessary facilities.
Actually, about that, take a look.
I found it when I was rereading the manual.
Maybe this symbol marks an evacuation area.
Wait, did Megu-nee put this here?
It's a little far, but...
But we've got the car we used for the field trip!
Megu-nee really cared about what you
should do after you graduate.
That's right.
She was our teacher, after all.
Yeah.
Let's see, the closest is this one, St. Isidrus University.
The Randall Corporation here is pretty close too, huh?
Dude, that's kinda shady.
Guess we have to choose between
work or college, huh?
Hey, maybe there are other people who are safe there.
You're right.
There has to be.
Will they take us in?
True, we don't know what kind of people they'll be...
They could be worse than the monsters
if things go badly.
We can't deny the possibility of that happening.
Hey everyone,
look at this!
What're you bothering us a-
Hey, what'd I say about snacks?!
Forget about that, look!
There's a bite mark on it.
I don't care how hungry you are,
Senpai, that's just wrong.
I-it wasn't me!
You're right, it doesn't look human.
Was it Taromaru?
They're too small to be Taromaru.
That means there's another dog down there.
I'd always wondered about that!
Why Taromaru was down in
the emergency evac area!
Yeah!
Maybe he went to go see his friend!
Yeah, that's gotta be it!
Why else would he go down into
such a dangerous place?
Taromaru went underground
'cause he was worried about them?
Yeah! Taromaru's such a good friend!
But I didn't see anything down there
when I went earlier.
Yeah.
Maybe it ran outside.
So maybe it's still okay.
Of course it's okay!
Because Taromaru was there for it!
You're right, that's right.
Taromaru was so brave.
Hey, back to what we were talking about earlier...
let's not worry too much about what we're
gonna do after we get out of here.
Taromaru'll make fun of us.
Right.
So it's goodbye, school.
Hey, before we leave...
Let's have a graduation ceremony!
Let's all graduate!
A graduation ceremony?
That's right. A graduation ceremony.
Even now, Senpai's just...
Senpai.
Wait, what, what does that mean?
It means you're fine just the way you are.
Wait, is it okay if I graduate, too?
Biscuit Animals
You're really smart, Mii-kun, so you'll skip a grade!
My goodness, Senpai.
I'll show you the biscuit you deserve.
It's "respect."
Alright, so our last activity as the School Living Club
will be the graduation ceremony!
Yeah!
Diploma
Yuki Takeya
This diploma certifies that…
Graduation
Hey, Yuki!
What?
Megurigaoka
High School
Graduation
Ceremony
I'd like to formally begin the
Megurigaoka High School Diploma Ceremony.
First, a farewell address from our
underclassmen representative, Miki Naoki.
Right!
The days and nights have gone so fast.
It feels like only yesterday that I met you all,
and now it's already time to graduate.
A great big future is waiting for us out there.
When I think of myself about to set sail
into the squalling sea of society...
I'm so proud of myself,
and at the same time, so very worried.
You invited me to join the School Living Club.
There, I learned to work hard and believe in myself.
The courage to stand up and face hard times.
To never let the happiness in my heart waver.
I'm not worried anymore.
Thank you all so much.
Underclassmen representative, Miki Naoki.
Next, our graduating class representative,
Yuki Takeya, will reply with a speech of her own.
Right!
Naoki-san, thank you for your
wonderful farewell speech.
Mii-kun, ah, Miki-kun, er, Miki-san, we're all so...
Just call me Mii-kun.
Sorry.
We're all so happy to have met you.
You were with us, and so was Taromaru,
and Megu-nee, too...
Some of them aren't with us today.
But, even so...
I'm so happy we can all graduate together.
I hope you stay with us after we graduate, too.
Graduating class representative, Yuki Takeya.
We are deeply indebted to our teachers
And our years at this school have passed
As we think back, we realize how time has flown
Bow to our teacher.
School Living Club is AWESOME!
– Kurumi Ebisuzawa
We would not be here if it were not for you.
Thank you so, so much.
– Miki Naoki
– Yuri Wakasa
To Sakura-sensei
We’ll be together, even after we graduate!
– Yuki Takeya
Thank you for all your help.
With that, the Megurigaoka High School
As we think back, we realize how time has flown
Now it's time for us to part
To Sakura-sensei
Graduation Ceremony now comes to a close.
Now it's time for us to part
Now we say goodbye
Thank you.
Ri-san, hurry up!
Okay, let's go!
We're off!
Did you forget something?
Not really.
They're really gone, huh?
They all went home.
You think so?
I feel a little sad leaving school. Is that weird?
It is.
But I understand how you feel.
What is it?
Nothing.
I was just thinking,
we all really love school.
Graduation Ceremony
Kei:
I’m glad I’m alive.
Hey, so this is kinda like a graduation trip!
You're right. Where should we go?
America!
Overseas?!
Where do you wanna go, Kurumi-chan?
On a graduation trip?
Maybe Kyoto?
Kyoto... So you wanna be a ninja!
What?!
Or a geisha?
Huh?
You thought about it for a second, didn't you?
You guys!
Houkago nara atarimae no koto
Saa sa, atsumare!
Kossori kaeruna! (Kora!)
Bukatsu dou dane? Katsudou shichau ne!
Asonderu nja arimasen
Tadaima tte ano ko ga iu yo (Okaeri!)
Minna de ireba daijoubu (Bu!)
Everybody say: tomodachi de iyou ne
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Daisuki (Hai!)
Watachitachi wa tanoshinderu
24 jikan hashaideru
Okujou ni wa akana taiyou
Kanari sakendemita (Genki desu!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
We're doing fine.