Youth is a hoax.
It's evil.
People who make a big deal of their "youth", are just inviting trouble.
They try to keep up with everything going on around them.
For them, if there's something that's to do with their "youth", they jump at it without second thought.
From normal daily life, to rebelling against the views of society.
If you fall in with them, lies, secrets, failure, and even crime await you.
But for them, it's just the spice of life.
And if failure is also the mark of "youth", then...
Could it be...
Isn't it ironic, that a person who has failed to make any friends, is also technically leading his "youth".
Though I wonder if they'd agree.
Everything runs on their schedule.
Then let me be clear.
The people who enjoy their "youth",
will eventually fall apart.
I'll be waiting here for you
Waiting in this sunlit room
The Romantic
Comedy Of My Youth
Is Wrong, As Expected.
By the time you've noticed,
you've been mesmerized by that old sight
But we aren't even staring at the same thing
I wonder when my heart
started yearning for all those hues
The shrouding mist hides everything and the light is warped by it
The cold rain which pours down from those clouds
A tint of that distant spring gust bursts past
Searching hard for an ornament
Waiting for that warm garden
Take me with you
Just do it
What my happiness drew,
though it's not a fairy tail
I know
Even still
I want to be there right now
Eventually fall apart?
I'd say that's you.
Say Hikigaya,
What was the topic that I handed out in class?
Lets see...
A short story about High School life.
So why did you write this shallow stuff?
What's this?
How did it end up like that?
Man.
Your eyes are like a dead fish's.
Does it really look that rich in DHA?
You sure are sharp.
Listen carefully.
I, um, I'm just trying to portray high school life accurately.
Don't you think my essay resembles high school?
You little brat, don't try to be smart with me.
Don't call me little...
Well, then again, from someone your age—
Were you never taught not to comment on a woman's age?
Sorry...
I will rewrite—
Come with me for a moment.
Hiratsuka-sensei.
I believe I've asked you to knock before entering.
Even if I knocked, you wouldn't have answered.
That's because you'd come in regardless.
So, what's with the clueless guy?
I..
...know this girl.
National General Course, Class J.
Ninety percent of the class is female.
The facilities are good, and it's known as a flashy class.
And within that class, lies a girl with great talents—Yukinoshita Yukino.
She's famous and known throughout the school.
He wants to join.
I'm a second year from Class F.
Hikigaya Hachiban.
Lets see.
Wait, what do you mean by "wants to join"?
As punishment for your half-assed report, you'll be joining this club.
I won't take no for an answer.
So that's basically the gist of it.
He has a rotten heart to go with those rotten eyes.
Those two things make him pathetic and lonely.
To help him get over that, I'd like him to join this club.
That's my request.
I respectfully decline.
I feel that I would be putting myself in danger being near someone with rotten eyes lead by a rotten heart.
I ain't looking at you!
Like I would, with that flat chest.
That's the truth... I think.
Don't worry, he may not look it, but he's trustworthy.
He wouldn't do anything that'd get him arrested.
Put your faith in the fact he's a spineless hooligan.
I'd like to say that I'm not that spineless.
A spineless hooligan?
I see.
She isn't even listening to me.
Well, since it's a request from a teacher I can't really say no.
I accept.
I see.
Then I'll leave you to it, Yukinoshita.
Hold on, is this for real?
What's with this atmosphere?
It brings back some sour memories.
Can't we just be friends?
Being friends? She didn't even talk to me after that.
Well for me, romantic comedies don't work.
I'm specially trained for this. I wouldn't fall for some comedy trap like her.
Women are only interested in hunks..
They befriend people only to forget them later.
In short, they are my enemies.
Can't we just be friends?
I wanted to be hated so I'd never experience that pain again.
I've decided. Instead of being friendly, I'll intimidate her.
Why don't you take a seat.
Oh, uh, yeah. Sorry.
What is it?
Well, I'm a bit confused.
What does this club actually do?
Take a wild guess.
It must be a literature club.
And how did you get that?
The condition that this room is in. There aren't any distinctive features.
All you do is sit here and read books.
Incorrect.
Then tell me what club this is.
I'm doing some club activities right now.
I give up, I have no idea.
Hikigaya-kun, how many years has it been since you last talked to a girl?
If memory serves me right,
it was 2 years ago, in June.
Isn't it super hot?
More like hot and humid, right?
Huh?
The one who possesses skills shall grace those without them.
Those people are called volunteers.
They reach out with a helping hand to those in need.
And that is what this club does.
Welcome to the Public Service Club.
I will fulfill the task given to me,
by fixing all your problems.
You should be grateful.
You pompous bitch.
My problems?
You know, I'm quite talented.
I scored third in the Practical Japanese test.
I'm also good looking.
I have neither a girlfriend nor friends, but that's only because of my high standards!
To say such thing with such pride, you really are something.
You weirdo
and creep.
Shut it.
I'm not here to be ridiculed by you.
From what I can tell, the reason you're alone is because of your character.
In regards to your appearance and your intelligence,
looks aren't everything and academics don't win you friends.
So then it would seem that my analysis was perfect, don't you think?
That's one hell of an analysis, but I think it's incomplete.
Now then, our talking with another human being simulation has come to an end.
What?
If you're able to talk to a girl like me, you should be able to talk to anyone.
In fact, I think I've fixed you a bit!
Listen here! It's not like I can't make conversation!
I just loathe talking about pointless crap.
I don't need your "fixing".
I think it'll be bad for you on a social level if you do not learn and change.
Yukinoshita, I'm entering.
Knock before...
My bad.
It seems like you're having some problems handling Hikigaya.
It's because he won't admit his faults.
That's not it.
I just, uh, don't want others to keep pushing change on me.
You're running away, aren't you?
Isn't changing yourself the same as running away?
Why can't I just keep living like I always have?
If you do... If you do then your troubles will never go away.
I won't be able to help you.
Calm down you two.
We'll settle this like a Shounen Manga, I propose a challenge where society will benefit!
What are you talking about?
In other words, a challenge where the most helpful person wins!
Did she just force her idea on us?
The winner can order the loser to do anything they like.
How does that sound?
When she says anything, does it really mean anything?
Gulp.
I refuse.
I don't feel safe betting that against him.
Hey, that's sexist!
Guys don't always think about perverted things.
World peace?
That's not exactly something I think about too often...
So you're afraid of losing are you?
I thought you'd be more confident that you'd win.
Even though I feel foolish for being provoked,
I will accept.
Then it's settled!
What about me?
Hello.
I didn't think you'd come.
Could it be that you're a masochist?
No.
So then you're a stalker?
Why are you making it seem like I have feelings for you when I don't?
Am I mistaken?
You are.
I really have to look out for your over confident attacks.
Say, don't you have any friends?
Let's see, can you please define what a friend is in your dictionary?
Right, that's enough.
That's the kind of thing you say when you don't have friends.
I know your type, you're the kind of person that doesn't have friends even though people would kill to talk to you.
What's up with that?
You wouldn't understand.
I've always been cute.
Males would approach me with thoughts of romance.
You were always alone yet you had a face that could be loved by anyone.
It seems you have a love affair with being alone.
Then again, maybe it would have been better to just be loved by anyone.
Huh? What do you mean?
I had to look for my slippers 60 times in grade school.
Of those 60 times, it was girls who hide them 50 times.
Thanks to that I had to make sure that my slippers were with me when I returned home.
Sounds like it was tough.
Yes it was.
All because I was cute.
But that's just how it is.
No one is perfect.
Humans are low and weak. We fall to envy easily.
So it's hard for a talented person to live a simple life.
Isn't that strange?
I plan to change all that.
To change this world.
Your faultless image has been broken.
It's better then being a spineless crybaby like yourself.
I hate it that you're so laid back and easy going.
She posseses everything, yet she has problems.
Normally, it isn't a big deal to just carry on in life, hiding those problems from the world.
It's what everyone else is doing after all.
Yet, she refuses to.
She refuses to lie.
I guess there's something in common between the two of us.
It's not really my thing but, somehow I ended up thinking that way.
The silence was soothing.
The rapid pace of my heart, begging to burst out and move forward.
Maybe... She and I...
Say Yukinoshita, I wonder if I could be your frie—
Sorry, that's not possible.
I haven't even finished yet.
Come in.
E-Excuse me.
Hiratsuka-sensei told me to come here...
W-Why is Hiki here?!
Well, I am a member of this club...
Wait, Hiki? Is that supposed to be me?
Besides, who is this girl anyway?
You're Yuigahama Yui from Class 2F aren't you?
Have a seat.
So you know me?
I think the entire school knows you.
No, I'd never heard about you up till now.
Right...
Don't worry.
If are worried then I'll just pretend that you aren't here right now.
I have a weak heart you see.
What is that? Some kind of consolation?
It's called irony.
So then... This is a fun club!
Hikki, you sure talk a lot don't you?
Huh?
Well, uh, how do I put this?
You're sorta different here compared to when you're in class.
How to say it... You're a bit weird at times.
You damn bitch!
What?! I'm not a bitch! I'm still a virg—
Whoah, nevermind!
That's not embarrassing is it? I mean at this age...
Hold it! What are you saying?!
It's still embarrassing!
Aren't you an advocate for girl-power?
What a sensless value to advocate.
You sure sound like a bitch when you say girl-power.
You said it again!
You're seriously calling me a bitch?
You sure are sick.
Me calling you a bitch and me being sick are two separate topics.
And don't call me Hikki, bitch.
You really are sick, the worst I've ever met!
Huh, cookies?
It seems like she wants someone to eat her homemade cookies.
But, since she has no confidence, she wants us to help her out.
That's something you ask your friends for help with.
But I... Um... Um...
I don't want my friends to know about it.
I can't be this serious with my friends either.
I see.
Anyway, I heard from Hiratsuka-sensei,
that this club fulfills the wishes of the student, doesn't it?
Nope.
We, The Service Club, only lend others a helping hand.
We don't just hand the starving a fish, we teach them how to catch it themselves and to be self sufficient.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's all twisted, don't you know how to wear an apron?
Sorry, thanks.
So, what about me?
You can tell us how they taste.
How did they come out this bad?
It looks like some kind of charcoal.
I think it's poisonous too.
It is not!
Actually it might be...
You don't want to die?
Now then.
What can we do to make them better.
Never let Yuigahama cook again.
That isn't going to solve anything!
Maybe I'm really not cut out for cooking...
A talent...?
I don't really have one.
You have to work hard to solve a problem.
You just said you didn't have any talents, correct?
You have to understand what that means.
People who don't work hard don't have the right to be envious of the people with talent.
People fail because they don't understand the hard work necessary to be successful.
But you know, they also say you shouldn't force something you can't do.
Maybe I'm just not cut out for this.
Could you stop forcing that idea onto yourself?
It's very disturbing.
Trying to justify your failures, foolishness and screw-ups by getting others to agree with you?
Aren't you ashamed?
C-Cool!
You don't sugar coat anything!
I think that's pretty cool!
Did you even hear what I said?
You do realize I just said some very harsh things to you, right?
I understand that.
But I know that you meant what you said.
No one's ever been so straight forward with me.
Sorry, I will do it properly next time.
Teach her how to do it properly, would you?
I'll show you once, just follow my lead.
Not even close...
How am I supposed to teach her?
Say, why are you trying to make delicious cookies?
What are you talking about?
Give me ten minutes.
I'll show you how to make real homemade deliciousness.
Now it's my turn.
These are your idea of real homemade cookies?
These aren't delicious!
I see.
Sorry, I guess I'll just get rid of them.
W-Wait.
They aren't that bad!
They're your cookies after all!
Don't you think it's the same with your cookies?
What do you mean?
This is the story of my friend's friend.
There was a girl who would talk to him about everything.
"She totally digs me!", I thought.
I mean, he thought!
So he planned to hear her out.
Just tell me who you like!
Just give me his first initial.
H.
H?
Then...
Could it be me?!
Huh, what are you saying. You're totally gross.
Stop it will you.
Hold on a sec.
So then, what part of your experience—
I told you it's the friend of a friend of mine!
So, what part of that story has to do with your cookies?
In short, guys are simple.
They get the wrong idea when you call them.
But they'd be very happy if you gave them your homemade cookies.
So it's perfectly fine if they taste terrible.
Taste terrible?...
Shut it!
Well, as long as he knows you worked hard on them,
his manly heart will be as soft as pudding for you.
I wonder....
Are you the same, Hikki?
Yup, I am.
Wait, don't call me Hikki!
So, what are you going to do, Yuigahama-san?
I'll keep trying till I succeed.
Thanks a lot, Yukinoshita-san.
I really hope it worked out for Yuigahama-san.
I wonder about her request from last week...
That came out of nowhere.
I think it's important to challenge yourself. It helps make you a better person.
At the end of the day, it makes her a better person.
Hard work betrays none,
but dreams betray many.
Huh?
Working hard alone doesn't assure you that you'll achieve your dreams.
Actually there are more cases where you don't.
Even so, working hard and achieving something is some consolation atleast.
All that is is self satisfaction.
Very naive, you disgust me.
Hey!
What is it?
Sorry, it seems like I'm not invited in.
Yukinoshita-san, do you hate me?
It's not that I hate you,
I just have a hard time dealing with you.
You just sugar coated it!
So, what brought you here?
As thanks for your help,
I made cookies for you.
I don't have the appetite right now.
Well it sure is fun just trying stuff out.
Next I want to try making a Bento!
Say Yukino, lets eat lunch together in this club room.
No, I like eating all by myself, so...
And don't call me Yukino, it's weird.
Say Yukino,
I'm free after school, I can help you with your club you know.
It's also my thanks to you.
Hikki?
It's my feelings of thanks towards you.
You helped me too after all.
Sure is confusing.
Somehow it looks omnious,
I will accept this if she meant to thank me but...
She keeps calling me Hikki...
The waves reflect the blue of the sky.
An Airplane, flying far beyond the reaches of the sky
The waves crash up against the shore
Of course I can confide in you
I don't see that ever changing
I'll be by your side till the end
You tried to get away from it, but we're connected
I won't let you go
I can hear your voice echoing like it did before
I'd express my love if you were here
Woah
Like a fish out of water, I can't escape it
Soon we'll be together again
Hello Hello Alone