Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
NERV HQ, TEST SITE NO. 2
22 DAYS AGO
Initiate activation.
Connecting main power to all circuits.
Main power connection complete.
Booting activation system.
Will reach operating threshold
in 0.5, 0.2... Threshold reached!
Proceed to activation system stage two.
Pilot interlink has started.
Start system phase two.
Inserting synapses, beginning interlink.
-Broadcasting signal pulse.
-All circuits nominal.
No abnormalities in
preliminary contact phase.
Sending power to left
and right brachialis muscles.
All neural links nominal.
Checklist cleared through item 2-5-5-0.
-Prepare for level three connection.
-Entry 2-5-8-0 cleared.
Absolute borderline in 0.9.
Zero point seven. Zero point five.
Zero point four. Zero point three.
Neural pulse flow reversing!
Critical error in stage three!
Rejection has also begun
in central neural elements!
Abort contact.
Open all circuits up to no. 6.
Negative! Signal not getting through!
We have lost control of Unit 00!
Abort the test. Cut the power feed.
Yes, sir!
Unit 00 has switched to auxiliary power.
Total system shutdown in 35 seconds!
You're not safe there! Stand back, sir!
-Automatic ejection system activating!
-No!
-Total shutdown in ten seconds.
-Specialized Bakelite! Now!
Eight. Seven.
-Rei!
-Six.
Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Zero.
Rei! Are you all right?!
Rei!
Good.
Rei Ayanami, age 14.
The first subject chosen as a result
of Marduk Institute research findings.
The First Children.
Designated operator of Evangelion
experimental prototype Unit 00.
Her past is a blank slate.
All records erased.
So, what was the cause of that accident?
Still unknown.
But one strong hypothesis
is unstable pilot mental state.
Mentally unstable? Rei, of all people?
Yes.
The readings were
unbelievably unstable for her.
-What caused it?
-I have no idea.
But... Maybe...
You have an idea?
No. That couldn't be possible.
Dismantling of Block D-3 complete.
Please submit all data to
Technology Department analysis team.
So this is our enemy?
Well, well.
Except for the core,
it's almost perfectly intact.
It's a perfect specimen.
-This is useful.
-So, does this mean you learned something?
What's that?
The error code that indicates
analysis failure.
"I have no idea," you mean?
Yes.
Angels are composed of matter
that displays the properties
of both particles and waves,
just like light.
But it did have a power source, right?
Something resembling one.
But we can't begin to fathom
its operating principles.
So the realm of the unknown
keeps on expanding.
This world is full of mysteries.
For example, look at this Angel's
wave pattern fingerprint.
What about it?
Isn't that...?
Yes. Despite the difference
in the component elements,
the signal sequencing and locations
are very similar to human DNA.
There's a 99.89% match.
A match of 99.89%? But that means--
It drives home how superficial
our understanding is.
Okay! Hold it!
This is the core?
Where is the rest?
It was so badly degraded that it would
be problematic for research.
-Fine. Dispose of the rest.
-Yes, sir.
What is it?
No, it's nothing...
Look. When you say "It's nothing"
with a look like that on your face,
you're practically screaming,
"Pay attention to me! Worry about me!"
Er... It looked like there were burns
on my father's hands.
Burns?
I was wondering how he got them.
Burns? Do you know anything about that?
Before you came, Unit 00 went berserk
during an activation test.
-You've heard about that, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
When it happened,
the pilot was trapped inside.
The pilot? You mean Ayanami, right?
Commander Ikari got her out.
The hatch was burning hot,
but he muscled it open.
He did that?
The burns on his palms are from then.
Go, go, go!
-Go for it, Hideko!
-Lose, lose!
-Here we go!
-No, you don't!
Okay, we'll get the next one!
They've all got such great knockers...
When Suzuhara looks at me,
I want to take a shower!
Yo, big guy!
-Who are you staring at?
-Um, nobody.
Could it be... Ayanami, maybe?!
No!
Hah, as if!
Talk about suspicious behavior! Right?
Ayanami's breasts... Ayanami's thighs...
-Ayanami's calves!
-...calves!
I wasn't, okay?
What were you looking at, then?
You can't pull the wool over my eyes!
I was just wondering why
she's always alone.
Oh. Now that you mention it,
I don't think she's made any friends
since she started here last year.
Something about her
makes her hard to approach.
Maybe she's just got
a really nasty personality.
You're both Eva pilots.
Shouldn't you know her better than us?
He's right.
I guess we don't talk all that much.
Eva-01 now beginning
level three cooling cycle.
Cage no. 6, please shut down
all systems up through phase three.
Previous harmonics and synch tests
returned no abnormal results.
All numerical targets met.
Roger. Forward results to Balthasar.
Roger.
Copying full range of entry plug
personal data to Melchior.
Sending now.
Melchior, roger. Circuits connected.
Starting level three cooling cycle.
CBL circulation commencing.
Direct waste water to
level two water treatment system.
Condition of all protein walls nominal.
All sections show green.
T minus 1,050 minutes
until Unit 00 reactivation test.
What on earth is this?
Curry.
It's always instant food with you.
Dinner guests don't get
to complain about the food.
And you, Ms. Misato?
I'll be having this.
Ta-dah!
Put it in here, and give me plenty!
Are you serious?
Sure! It tastes great!
If you say so.
You can't get this kind of flavor
with curry-flavored instant ramen.
Let's eat!
The trick is to cut back on
how much water you add.
Misato made this, didn't she?
-Yes, ma'am.
-You can tell?
From the taste.
How can someone ruin boil-in-the-bag food?
The next time you invite me,
could you do it on Shinji's day to cook?
Shinji, you should move out.
Don't ruin your life by picking up
bad habits from a roommate.
I'm already used to it.
Besides, moving would be-- Oops.
Shinji? Could you get me another beer?
Yes, ma'am.
The paperwork would be a huge pain.
I mean, Shinji just got
his official security card.
Right, I almost forgot.
Shinji, could you do me a favor?
Sure, what?
This is Rei Ayanami's renewed card.
I keep forgetting to give it to her.
I'm sorry,
but could you drop it off at her place
before you come to HQ again?
Yes, ma'am.
What's the matter? You sure seem
captivated by that photo of Rei.
No, I--
-Hey, don't tell me you...
-I'm not!
You're not fooling anyone!
You're all flustered!
Now you have an official reason
as an excuse to go to her place.
Cut it out, stop teasing me!
You get wound up so easily,
it makes you fun to tease!
Just like you, Misato.
It's just that we're both Eva pilots,
but I hardly know anything about her.
She's a really sweet girl, but just
like your father, she's all thumbs.
All thumbs? At what?
At living.
AYANAMI
Hello?
Is anyone home? It's Ikari.
Ayanami? I'm coming in.
Are these hers?
I...
I didn't mean to--
Could you move, please?
I...
What?
Er, I... That is...
They asked me t-to...
To do what? Your card!
Your card's been renewed,
so I was supposed to drop it off.
That's... That's why I...
I wasn't trying to...
Ms. Ritsuko said that she
forgot to give it to you.
Honest! Nobody answered the doorbell,
and the door was unlocked, so I...
Central Dogma access
is currently available.
Category 3 visitors,
please use direct access gate no. 4.
GOOD MORNING
Here's your new card.
Ms. Ritsuko asked me to give it to you.
I'm sorry for earlier.
About what?
Um, your reactivation test
is today, right?
I hope it goes well this time.
Say...
Aren't you scared of getting
into your Unit 00 again?
Why?
I heard you were hurt really badly
during a test a while ago.
So I was curious if you were worried.
You're Commander Ikari's son, right?
You don't have faith
in your father's work?
Of course not!
Have faith in a father like him?!
Um...
Rei? Are you all right?
Rei.
When it happened,
the pilot was trapped inside.
Commander Ikari got her out.
The hatch was burning hot,
but he muscled it open.
The burns on his palms are from then.
-Rei, do you read me?
-Yes, sir.
We will now conduct
Unit 00's reactivation test.
Initiate level one contact.
Main power supply connected.
-Operating voltage threshold crossed.
-Roger.
Format, proceed to phase two.
-Initiate pilot contact with Unit 00.
-Connecting circuits.
Neural pulses and harmonics, all nominal.
Synchronization, all green.
All neural links established.
Central neural elements
show no abnormalities.
Recalculating.
No error corrections needed.
Checklist cleared through item 2-5-8-0.
Reaching absolute borderline
in two point five.
One point seven. One point two.
One point zero.
Zero point eight.
Zero point six. Zero point five.
Zero point four. Zero point three.
Zero point two. Zero point one.
Passed. Borderline cleared.
-Unit 00 is now activated.
-Roger.
Will now proceed to interfacing test.
Ikari, an unidentified flying object
is heading this way.
It's probably the 5th Angel.
Suspend the test. All personnel,
go to condition one battle stations.
You're not going to go ahead
and deploy Unit 00?
It's not combat-ready.
What's Unit 01's status?
We can have it ready in 380 seconds.
-Launch it.
-Yes, sir.
Rei.
The reactivation was a success.
Stand down.
Object now passing over Tounosawa.
Now preparing to launch Unit 01.
Release lock bolt no. 01.
-Release confirmed.
-Roger.
-Release secondary restraining frame.
Target has entered airspace
over Lake Ashi.
Eva-01, ready for launch!
Launch!
I'm getting a high energy reading
inside the target!
What?!
Don't tell me it's...
No! Take cover!
Shinji!
TO BE CONTINUED
Shinji survives,
but his injuries cause him to act spoiled.
Rei pushes him away.
Meanwhile, Misato attempts
a point penetration against the Angel.
Next episode! "Showdown in Tokyo-3"!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming