Romero.
I'll take you away from here.
To the place you were looking for.
A place where no one will pursue us.
And with enough speed to shake off the past.
To the other side.
A job at such a late hour...
My job doesn't have work hours.
Have you lost interest in becoming an assassin?
Not at all.
I might be back late.
Go to sleep without me.
I'll stay up.
I picked up an old video recorder this afternoon.
I want to see if I can repair it.
You could just buy a new one.
That's a waste of money, the recorder might still be usable.
Still usable, huh?
I guess you're right.
I hope you return soon.
Yeah.
It's a promise then.
I promise.
I don't want to be separated.
I want to stay beside you.
If I get back in one piece...
...it's time to quit.
Whether I choose to quit or to run,
either way, the organization will...
You're late, Lizzy.
Lizzy?
Alright, freeze.
Lizzy.
Sorry.
I always make trouble for you don't I, kid?
I heard about it, kid.
You're Phantom.
No wonder my youngsters were killed so easily.
No need for pretense.
We brought your publicity picture.
Look.
That picture...
Who took it?
Was it her doing?
What's up?
You won't do anything?
Mr. Godou, this is a misunderstanding.
That photo is...
Before you defend yourself, listen up.
I know you were ordered to do it by an executive.
All we want to know is who pulled the strings.
The three times you attacked us...
...Claudia was behind it.
Isn't that right?
Are you certain?
Do you have any idea how hard Claudia worked to have you join Inferno?
I can't say I hate loyal followers,
but you shouldn't follow that woman blindly.
We have been tricked into this.
You and us both.
Shut up.
Hey, Miss...
This isn't the first time we've met here.
What?
Don't you remember?
It was a memorable night.
That's right, almost a year has passed now.
A year?
What organization are they with?
The cargo!
We did it!
Not yet, brother.
Just go!
Aye!
I see.
It was you people.
You were working with Scythe.
I have no idea who Scythe is.
It was Claudia who set it up.
No...
We were having a lot of trouble...
...when that woman suddenly proposed a deal to us.
"Steal 500 kg of cocaine."
She provided the plan and the backup.
She even asked:
"Do you want to have some fun in Los Angeles?"
Why would she do that?
After the Godou clan had escaped its straits,
we were to join Inferno.
We had trouble understanding at first,
but when we found out about her position, we agreed.
She wanted to create an organization inside Inferno loyal only to her.
If she had stayed solitary, she would never have risen in position.
The story of how we would get shipments from elsewhere...
...is complete bogus.
I'm the one that built the Godou clan's market during this past year.
It was based on the cocaine we grabbed from you guys.
Then, Claudia sold out Scythe...
Yeah.
There was some idiot who got creamed by the plan.
Was that the Scythe you're talking about?
It's me.
Sudden change of plan!
Scythe has betrayed the organization.
He used Phantom to attack Inferno's cargo hold.
The organization is currently looking for them with all its manpower.
Neither have been found yet.
At that time...
A way to prove your innocence...
...and take Ein back.
You should know...
...how to use this.
She was behind...
...all of it.
Scythe.
Because of that, we were hurt...
...and cried.
It seems you realize what she has done.
Phantom, is that true?
Even the invincible Phantom is defeated by a woman's charm.
But you know, there's still an epilogue to this story.
That woman will throw Shiga and I away in the end...
...and seize control of the Godou clan.
It shuts our mouth...
...and along the way she takes care of her rival.
I can't believe how cold-hearted she is.
That's the truth.
You know that.
We were used like tools by that woman.
I don't care about Inferno or anything any more.
If I keep quiet about this, then I'm not Godou Daisuke.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe a thing you say.
You filthy bastard!
Die!
A sniper...
Where are you hiding?
It's her.
Hop in, Phantom.
Go ahead!
Phantom!
Elen...
E-Elen...
Impossible.
You're alive?
But why?
Why, Elen?
Why are you doing this?
Don't call me Elen.
I'm Ein.
From the days of yore until now, simply Ein.
Hurry up and run.
Inferno will hunt you soon.
This time there will be no mercy.
Inferno will...
Elen, wait for me!
Elen!
I'm Ein.
From the days of yore until now.
Is it him?
That man.
Scythe Master.
A splendid performance.
The Godou clan, Claudia McCunnen and Inferno's Isaac Wisemel.
With those three as sacrifices,
you took revenge on the enemies who once betrayed you.
One after another, they have brought ruin to themselves.
No.
That's not all.
The truth behind all of this was relayed to Inferno by me.
They will make their move soon.
They will kill the traitor, Claudia McCunnen,
and her trusted subordinate, Phantom.
The organization is after me...
If so...
Cal.
So you've been accepted on recommendation.
I'm happy for you, Mio.
I wanted to tell you immediately.
I came suddenly, am I interrupting your work?
Don't worry about that.
But isn't import-export business hard?
Well, it is.
The day after tomorrow I will have to go abroad for a while for work.
What do you want for a souvenir?
No, you always give me one.
If I get too much from you, mother will find out.
I see.
I suppose you're right.
I have a date with my friend.
Have fun.
See you later.
Okay.
Even though we're related,
Mio is different from me or the boss.
But the blood of the Godou's demon is flowing in her veins.
If someone wants to exploit that...
Mio, who doesn't know anything...
I wouldn't be able to protect Mio.
No matter if her position or family name changed, she's still my little sister.
She's my precious little sister.
Shiga.
The mountain we have to climb this time is tall.
If I don't come back to the clan alive...
When that happens...
I understand, brother.
I will watch over Mio's path until the end.
Sorry about that, Shiga.
My stomach and shoulder...
Then...
...I will survive this hell.
Carnage... is my path.
Hey there!
Who survived?
We're annihilated.
I see...
It's you and me who survive in the end.
It's been like that for a long time now.
No matter where we fought, you were beside me.
With my courage and your intelligence, we will always...
What will we do?
Nothing in particular.
What about Claudia?
Inferno will take her life.
We should be thinking about us, the Godou clan.
Inferno won't let our transgressions slide after we worked for that woman.
War will come.
What about Inferno?
I'll make them pay for deceiving us.
Their battle of penance has come.
Hey, Shiga.
Let's slaughter them all!
It won't be necessary to go so far.
Huh?
With one more man's death,
the game will end.
Everything...
Shiga?
After all this, you probably won't believe me, but...
...brother, I truly love you.
Shiga...
Shiga!!
With the death of its founder we have proof of the Godou clan's loyalty.
I will report that to Inferno.
Mr. Shiga, the Godou clan is safe after this.
Giuseppe.
I have a strong urge to kill you right now.
Will you shoot me?
It seems we can communicate as well.
We can be friends, Mr. Shiga.
Clau...
Where are you, Clau?
Where are you?
Where are you now?
Give me some sort of reason, Claudia McCunnen.
Run, Reiji!
Stay alive!
Are our pursuers already...
Cal.
Don't you get bored listening to it?
Never.
You really like that song, do you?
I love it.
Because it's a present from the person I love most.
I thought I had nothing.
I never had what normal people have.
That's why I thought I would never have them.
Thank you, Reiji.
I want to stay beside you.
Cal?
Cal!
Cal!!
If this world isn't the hell of dreams,
it's only because you're alive.