Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
-Hey, have you seen her?
-I sure have!
-Seen who?
-Haven't you heard about the foreigner?
Foreigner?
Yeah, she transferred into
8th Grade Class A! Last week!
Is she hot or what?
PHOTO PRINTS, 30 YEN EACH!
I heard her name is Asuka Langley Soryu!
Wow, she's so cute!
She grew up overseas, right?
I wonder if she, um, matured early.
You don't get it! I bet she went through
a rough breakup back in Germany!
Everybody's talking about her...
"Asuka" this and "Asuka" that.
-If only they knew.
-Pleasure doing business!
Too bad her personality
doesn't show up in these pictures...
Hello, Shinji!
Guten Morgen!
Gooten morgun...
Geez, you look all mopey,
and it's first thing in the morning.
I did you the favor of talking to you.
So maybe you could try to look happy, huh?
She's here, right? The other one.
Other what?
What kind of idiot are you?
I mean the First Children! Who else?
Oh, you mean Ayanami. She's...
Hello!
So you're Rei Ayanami,
the prototype's pilot.
I'm Asuka. Asuka Langley Soryu.
Eva-02's pilot. Let's be friends.
What for?
Because it's best for everyone that way.
For various reasons.
I'll be your friend if I'm ordered to.
You're a strange one.
Seriously, is it just weirdos
that get picked as Eva pilots?
-I think you've lost some weight.
-Oh?
-You're in love, but it will end in tears.
-Really? And just how do you know that?
Because people with a mole along where
tears flow are doomed to a life of tears.
Is this your opening seduction move?
I wouldn't do it.
There's a mean old lady
looking right at us.
-It's been a long time, Ryoji.
-That it has.
I must say, you're off your game.
He's just as stupid as he ever was!
You've finished overseeing the handover
of Unit 02, so go home already!
New orders came in this morning.
I'm here until further notice.
The three of us, together again.
It will be just like old times!
Together with you?! Dream on!
An Angel attack?!
Report from cruiser Haruna in patrol.
"Large submerged object encountered
off coast of Kii Peninsula.
Relaying data."
Cross-checking received data.
Wavelength pattern, blue.
Confirmed as Angel.
All personnel,
condition one battle stations!
Tokyo-3's intercept systems
were badly damaged
in the last attack.
We're only back up to 26% capacity.
In actual combat, that's effectively zero.
As such,
we're going to hit it just before
it comes ashore this time.
Units 01 and 02 will
engage the target in turns
in close-quarters combat.
-Roger.
This is my debut battle in Japan.
Why won't she let me fight it on my own?
It can't be helped. This is her plan.
Just so we're clear, don't do anything
that will cramp my style, got it?!
Um, okay...
Why was somebody like him
chosen to be a pilot?
I don't like this two-on-one stuff.
It seems like cheating.
It's not my thing.
We don't have the luxury of choice.
We do what we have to do to survive.
Here it comes!
Commence attack!
I'll go first, then! Cover me!
-Cover you?!
-Ladies first!
Geez, you don't have to be so bossy.
I was here first...
I've got this!
I'm impressed...
See that, Third Children?
A battle should be quick and clean!
Hey, that's playing dirty!
At 10:58:15 a.m., Unit 01
was attacked by Target Alpha,
half of the original target
that had split in two,
and was flung two kilometers
into Suruga Bay, where it sank.
At 10:58:20 a.m., Unit 02 was
rendered inoperative by Target Bravo.
The Project E Director
had the following to say:
How appalling.
My precious debut fight
got ruined because of you!
What are you talking about? It happened
because you pulled that dumb stunt!
Dumb stunt?! How does a wimp like you
get to talk to me like that?
You've got some nerve!
Come on! This mess happened because
you were in such a rush to beat it!
Look at yours, it's like a drowned--
At 11:03 a.m.,
Nerv halted further operations.
Command was transferred
to the UN Second Army Group.
Those two made us look like fools.
At 11:05 a.m., the target was hit
with an N2 mine.
We'll have to revise the maps again...
It succeeded in incinerating
28% of their mass.
-Is it dead?
-No, only delayed.
It will resume its advance eventually.
Well, we should count our blessings
that it bought us time to regroup.
Listen, you two.
Do you understand what your job here is?
-To pilot the Evas.
-No! It's to defeat the Angels!
Nerv does not exist in order
to make buffoons of ourselves.
To do your job,
you must work together to--
Enough.
Why does everyone here
get angry so easily?
Adults don't like being made to look bad.
Um, where is Ms. Misato?
On aftermath detail. It's the job of
the person in charge to take the heat.
Complaints and damage assessments
from all related agencies.
And this is the bill from the UN.
Complaints from Public Affairs, too.
Make sure you go through them all.
I already know what they're going to say.
"If you're going to fight,
do it in Tokyo-3!"
Very perceptive.
They don't need to tell me that. Once that
wreck is dealt with, we'll fight here.
I'll defeat that Angel, no matter what.
The Deputy Commander is furious.
If you make him look bad again,
he'll demote you, mark my words.
I guess the one silver lining
is that Commander Ikari isn't here.
He would fire you on the spot.
Even without seeing this pile.
So, you come bearing ideas
that will save my hide, right?
No, just the one.
That's my Dr. Ritsuko Akagi!
Good old friends are great blessings!
I'm flattered, but I'm not
the old friend who's saving your hide.
This is Ryoji's idea.
Ryoji's?
TO MY HONEY
DHU
ARTA MOVING CENTER
I'm home!
Not that anybody's here
to hear me say it...
What is all this?!
Don't be rude! Those are my things.
W-What are you doing here, Soryu?
-I'm surprised you're still here.
-What do you mean, "still"?
You got sacked today.
I'm going to be Misato's roommate.
Well, considering which of us is better,
it's the natural choice.
Admittedly, I'd rather be
living with Mr. Kaji.
How come Japanese rooms are so small?
I could only fit half of my stuff in here!
SHINJI'S ROO--
And how come Japanese people
have zero sense of caution?
How can you live in a house
with rooms that don't have locks?
Unbelievable.
That's because we Japanese try to be
perceptive and considerate of others.
-Ms. Misato!
-Misato!
Welcome home. You two seem
to be off to a good start already!
For what?
Preparing for our next battle.
What do you mean?
The 7th Angel has just one weakness!
A two-point attack to its core unit
while it's divided in two.
There's no other way.
In other words,
it has to be a perfectly
coordinated attack by both Evas.
And to do that, it's essential that
you two work in perfect unison.
To that end, you two are going
to live here together, starting today.
No way! They say boys and girls mustn't
sleep in the same room after age seven!
The Angel is regenerating as we speak.
It will attack again in six days.
We don't have time.
This is ridiculous...
And so, here is how we turn
the ridiculous into the possible:
To achieve perfect unison,
you're going to memorize
an attack pattern that's set to this song.
You have six days to do it.
The sooner, the better.
Humph!
I wonder what's up with Shinji.
Yeah, he's missed school
three days in a row.
-It's the Class Rep.
-It's two thirds of the Idiot Trio.
So what are you doing here?
I'm here to check in on Ms. Soryu.
What are you two doing here?
Checking in on Shinji.
Why are you stopping here?
-Coming!
Y-You dirty traitor!
They're wearing matching outfits again!
Rubs me the wrong way!
Ms. Misato says that Japanese start
with the form and the rest will follow,
This is so indecent! Both of you!
It's not what you think!
Then it must be even worse!
Hi, everybody.
Would you mind explaining this?
You should have just said so
in the first place!
So, is the unison training going well?
See for yourself.
What do you expect?!
It's never going to work if I have to
force myself down to Shinji's level!
This whole thing is flat-out impossible!
So, you want out?
There's no one else, is there?
-Rei?
-Yes, ma'am?
-Give it a try.
-Yes, ma'am.
From the looks of it, it might be better
to change the plan and use Rei instead.
Screw this! I'm out of here!
-Ms. Asuka!
-"Even a demon's eyes can shed tears."
Shinji!
Go after her!
-Um...
-Don't say anything!
I know, I have to do this.
Piloting the Eva is all I've got.
I'll do it.
No matter what it takes,
I'm gonna get back at Rei and Misato!
Get back at them? For what?
Why are you so clueless all the time?!
You call yourself a man?
They're gonna... pay for wounding
my pride! With interest!
TWO DAYS LEFT
ATTACK TOMORROW
-Where's Misato?
-At work.
She called and said
she'll be there all night.
Right. That means it's just
you and me here tonight!
This doorway is the impenetrable
Wall of Jericho!
Sure...
Putting so much as a toe
over this line is a capital offense!
And don't stay up past your bedtime, baby!
How can Japanese people
sleep on the stupid floor?
Unbelievable!
Mommy...
You're just as much a kid as I am.
-Who's watching?
-Who do you think?
Look, we're not involved anymore.
Don't do that again.
But your lips didn't tell me to stop.
Which should I believe?
Your lips or your words?
Here you are.
Thanks.
You're not drinking tonight?
-Yeah, well...
-So, which is it? Work? Or a man?
A little of both.
I wonder, is the attraction still there?
Don't be ridiculous!
Like I'd still have feelings
for a jerk like him!
I can blame it on being young and foolish,
but being in a relationship with that guy
is the biggest regret I have in my life.
I was talking about Ryoji's feelings.
Did that catch you off guard?
Now, look here--
Getting angry only proves my point.
Try being more honest
with yourself this time.
Things are different from eight years ago.
Nothing has changed. Not one bit.
He hasn't grown up at all.
Well, back to work!
Tomorrow is the big day!
Target has breached
Goura Absolute Defense Line.
Here it is.
We're ready for you this time.
Raise your A.T. Fields
as soon as the music starts.
Follow the plan from there.
Got that, you two?
-Roger!
Target has entered the mountains.
Listen up! We're going balls to the wall,
full speed ahead from the get-go!
I know. We'll finish this in 62 seconds.
-Target is about to reach Point Zero!
-Jettison external power plugs!
Launch!
TIME REMAINING
Both Evas accounted for!
-Oh, geez...
-How appalling.
Hey, what do you think
you're doing to my Unit 02?!
What?! You're the one
who came barreling into me!
You're the one who lost
the beat at the end!
You have your head
up your ass all the time!
And what were you doing
last night instead of sleeping?
I was doing visualization training
for today's battle!
You're full of it! I know you tried
to kiss me while I was sleeping!
No way! You were awake?!
That's horrible!
I said that as a joke,
but you really did? You kissed me?!
No, I didn't! I stopped myself!
Pervert! Weirdo! Freak!
I can't believe you!
You're the one who sleepwalked over
and started talking in your sleep!
They're making us look like fools again...
TO BE CONTINUED
An unhatched Angel slumbers
within the crater of Mt. Asama.
Nerv attempts their
first capture of an Angel.
Outfitted for localized combat,
Eva-02 plunges into a red-hot hell.
Next episode! "The Magma Diver"!
Tune in next time
for lots more fan service!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming