I'm like, super pooped, for real.
Something wrong?
I've got this article for work,
so I had to go to this one place and eat tarako spaghetti,
but I hate that stuff.
Can't tell if it's Japanese or
Western or what.
What's wrong with tarako spaghetti?
It's perfect for a model who lives on convenience store food like Dumb-chi.
Shut it!
Damn, my manager's worthless...
I'm going to slowly pick at one of her moist scabs when I get a chance.
You're only saying this because you've never had delicious tarako spaghetti.
What!?
Delicious tarako spaghetti!?
There's no such thing in this world!
Yeah, yeah!
Don't pretend like you're a foodie when you're just low class.
How about it? Shall we go have some delicious tarako spaghetti?
Well, might as well humor the stupid dog.
A perfect way to kill time.
Lumpy and Delicious - Viva Tarako Spaghetti!
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for Foodies
Gobbling Up Little Lives
Here we are!
Welcome.
You can sit wherever you want.
Delicious! Give me another!
Minorin!
Oh, Taiga! Amin!
What a coincidence.
Did you watch the shopping special last night?
Sure did.
They were selling a white dryer.
Can't believe that it doesn't come with a water tank.
I wanted to buy one, but I was denied.
Makes sense.
I'll make Ryuji buy it.
Good idea.
My name came up in the conversation,
and Kushieda is still ignoring my presence!
So what are you up to?
Oh, that's right.
This stupid dog and Dumb-chi wanted tarako spaghetti.
Yes, yes, yes.
The tarako spaghetti here is great.
I'd give it three stars!
Fool!
Yeah, yeah!
R-Right...
Boy, you don't know jack about tarako spaghetti!
I'm gonna teach you what real tarako spaghetti is all about!
Open your eyes good and wide and watch carefully!
It's on!
Hey, why is there spaghetti with meat sauce when we're comparing tarako spaghetti?
And you're going so fast that I don't understand why we're having a contest.
We'll start with my selection, the ultimate Jonny's tarako spaghetti!
Delicious!
So delicious that my hair's standing on end!
My, that was quite scrumptious.
Naturally, tarako spaghetti can't be found in Italy.
However, Italy is known as one of the few
European countries to eat octopus.
Italians are generally viewed as a cheerful people,
but there are differences between northerners and southerners.
Southerners are cheerful and active,
while northerners tend to be more reserved.
A difference that may arise from the difference in climate between regions.
Tsk, lecturing us like you're some kind of geography professor.
You weren't even the one who made this.
Hah! The weaker a dog, the louder he barks!
Now!
Try some of my Jonny's spaghetti with meat sauce!
Delicious!
So delicious that my hair's falling out!
My, that was quite scrumptious.
Meat—I'm talking red meat!
But it doesn't end there!
In English, it can be used in the daily context of meating with others!
And then you have a meating for the first time and meat in the middle!
Hands meating! A competitive meat! Meat the parents!
Sight! Sound! Touch!
And so on!
There is no limit to the number of possible meanings!
Be amazed!
Tsk, that was too long.
- Think you're from New York or something?
- You aren't even the one who made this.
So which one wins?
Hmm, this is hard...
Shazam!
An impressive showing by both sides!
A certain tribe in Laos follows the practice of bride kidnapping.
So when the couple is in love, the woman still must put up a fight and kick and scream!
Which means this contest is a draw!
Tarako spaghetti!
Deep stuff!
Deep!
Too deep!
Hey, what does SOS stand for?
Isn't it strawberry on shortcake?
Convenience store cakes are pretty good these days.
Do you eat the strawberry last, or first?
Inko Today
Sho-Sho-Sho...
Short-Short-Short...
Short-Short...
Pants!
Chopin! Chopin! Chopin!
Pan-Pan-Pan...
Panties.
To be continued