Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
I haven't put on my uniform in a while.
It's Kona-chan.
Kona-chan!
Good morning!
My...
Kagami-san.
Tsukasa-san.
A very good day to you.
Why, Tsukasa-san...
Your ribbon is crooked.
Thanks.
Gonna hurl.
What brought this on, Kona-chan?
Yes.
I have become hooked on Marimite.
Marimite?
Are you a kid?!
Image
Hey...
Don't start copying their costumes, too.
Um...
Is that called cosplay?
I wouldn't go that far.
You mean it, right?
I already do plenty of that at work.
Oh, yeah...
You work at one of those places...
But if Kona-chan was a high-class lady...
Feels so wrong that I can't even picture it.
Baseball games have been going over schedule too much recently.
Why do the people watching new anime get shafted?
If you want to watch anime that badly...
...you could get cable or something.
Aren't there specialized channels for that stuff?
If I could...
God knows I want to...
But the cable guys were all like...
You can't get cable...
Yuki-chan.
Good morning.
Good morning, Tsukasa-san.
You look kinda down, did something happen?
Actually, I went to have my cavity taken care of.
You went to the dentist.
Impressive!
Why are there so many follow-up trips
after a visit to the dentist?
I totally know what you mean!
And it isn't just one or two trips!
Miyuki-san.
Good day.
Konata-san.
Have you been well?
Thank you for asking.
I'm pleased to see you looking well.
Yuki-chan's so amazing.
She's talking the same way...
...but it doesn't feel weird at all.
And she isn't even questioning the way Kona-chan's talking.
This is the first time I've seen a person say "good day" in real life!
Really?
It appears to be a regularly used greeting...
...at the girls' school my friends go to.
A real school for rich girls is something else.
How refined.
Kuroi...
...told me to collect summer homework for her.
Excellent work, Sebastian.
S-Seba—
Butlers must be named Sebastian, do you not agree?
You do get that impression.
Tell us a funny story, Sebastian.
Ain't happening!
Okay.
Vacation just ended...
...but you got no time to be mooching around.
Schedule
for
Second Semester
Start thinking about your future...
...and put effort into studying.
By future, does she mean choosing a major?
I guess high school is only a temporary stopping point.
But you probably haven't done
much thinking about the future, right?
Why?
Don't insult me!
'Cause...
You chose liberal arts to be in the
same class with everyone else, right?
Tsu-Tsukasa!
You blabbed!
Ah, sorries.
And you told her...
...o-of all people!
Come on...
You should have just been honest.
You hate being lonely, don't you?
There, there.
Shut up!
Hey!
I'm back!
Cousin Yui...
For my summer homework...
I did as you told me and wrote down
random stuff when I didn't know the answer...
...and now I have to redo it all!
Save me!
O-Okay...
But...
If you get help from me, you might have to redo it again...
...if you know what I mean...
She got out of it...
An extension on homework without
an extension on summer vacation...
Maybe I should borrow Kagami's notes.
The sound of cicadas puts me to sleep.
Huh?
I see...
The schedule's off because the baseball game went over.
I guess it can be useful sometimes.
My recorder's off!
Huh?
Where are your glasses, Yuki-chan?
Actually...
They broke this morning...
I forgot that I left them on the chair...
...and accidentally...
I'm terribly sorry...
...but could I borrow your notes for today later?
Sure.
You still got the clumsy thing going.
Konata's Notes
Konata-san...
Horrible handwriting.
So hard to read.
Your handwriting is a mystery to me.
Tsukasa's Notes
Tsukasa-san...
So detailed that
she didn't get
everything down
Hang in there!
They sure are useless.
Here.
Thank you so much.
Good thing we have the same teacher.
Um...
But please keep this a secret...
I don't wish to ruin their good intentions...
I'm starving!
Yuki-chan!
Let's have lunch!
Tsukasa-san.
Konata-san.
Thank you for letting me use your notes.
Nah.
No need to thank us.
I never expected Yuki-chan to borrow my notes.
Well...
It's not happening again.
STARE
U-Um...
Is there something on my face?
In games, when a character who wears
glasses shows up at school without them...
...they suddenly become popular...
But I guess that doesn't happen in real life.
I-It really doesn't.
Unfortunately.
Don't chocolate cornets kinda look like drills?
D-Drills...
D-Didn't we discuss which side of a chocolate cornet was the head?
Like how the thin end looked like the bottom.
On second thought...
...the fat end looks more like the bottom.
Bottom?
That's one big bottom...
And layers of stomach.
When the lower half of your body gains weight...
...it becomes difficult to buy skirts and the like.
That's right!
If you use your waist measurements, you can't get it over your hips.
If it fits your hips perfectly, it's loose around your waist.
You have no choice but to buy one that's too big for your waist...
...and when you walk around in it,
your skirt starts spinning, doesn't it?
That's right!
A body with layers of stomach looks like a cornet...
If you turn it on the side...
...you can play it like a cornet.
If you turn it again, you can...
...put it on your head like a cornet.
Was that supposed to be funny?
Weren't you dieting to make up
for your added summer weight, Sis?
But my weight went down...
...without my waist or hips changing.
No, Kagami.
I can see the fruits of your diet.
Really?
It's plain to see.
They say that when you diet, you lose
weight in the places you don't want to first.
Okay already!
Stop right there!
When reading literature...
...the trick is to keep the theme in mind...
...and understand what the author is trying to convey.
I get it...
I heard that people with poor eyesight end up
with nasty expressions that scare other people...
...but I guess...
...it depends on the person.
Hey, you!
When you said it depends on the person...
...you glanced over at me, didn't you?!
I've heard that thinner eyes make you look prettier.
It makes you look more mature.
Hey.
Stop that!
She's late!
Stupid Konata...
What's she doing?
She's here!
Sorry!
I'm late.
Way late!
Someone who's always complaining
about night games lasting too long...
...shouldn't be so loose with time!
Well, you know...
All the games have been going over schedule lately, so...
I guess it infected me.
Like it's contagious!
So?
Why were you late?
Overslept?
No way.
I'm not a child.
Then give me an adult reason for why you were late.
Well...
There was still plenty of time left when I finished getting ready...
So to kill time...
...I started playing games and couldn't stop...
You suck.
You're worse than a child.
Oh, yeah.
There are a bunch of cultural festivals and
sporting events during second semester, right?
And we have tests soon.
Kona-chan is really athletic so she can do well in sporting events.
I don't like sporting events 'cause they make me tired.
Pretty rare to see such a lazy athletic type.
I wonder what our class will do for the cultural festival.
There isn't anything I'd want to do.
These things...
...can never be decided...
...unless someone wants to do something.
And the person who brings up the idea usually gets put in charge...
...so nobody's willing to talk.
And you have to stay after school to prepare.
You won't be able to watch evening anime.
Knew you'd say that.
It's my turn to cook dinner tonight.
Have to stop by the store on the way home.
What are you going to make?
Everyone's favorite chicken curry!
Everyone in our family loves chicken.
Curry, huh?
Sounds good.
I've heard that letting curry sit overnight makes it taste better.
It works well.
Then I'll make some extra and bring it for lunch tomorrow.
Since there'll be leftovers anyway.
Yes.
This is the Hiiragi residence.
Tsukasa?
Kona-chan!
Why are you calling so early?
The curry...
Curry?
The curry I made yesterday...
I let it sit overnight, and now it's spoiled.
No way.
Really.
Why?
Curry usually doesn't go bad in one day.
Right?
Did you put in anything weird?
I didn't.
But...
...there was mold in it this morning!
So?
Another cornet today?
They taste good, so it's okay.
If you say so...
Oh, yeah...
I just noticed...
...but the difference between when your lunches are...
Mini Hamburger Patties
Fried Eggs
Bacon Sauté
with broad beans and onions.
Salted Asparagus
and Carrots
Made
Properly
...made properly...
Made
Frugally
Grilled Salmon
Okra
(Just boiled and sliced)
Pickled Vegetables
And nothing else...
...or made frugally...
...is really obvious.
Ts-Tsukasa and I take turns making lunch...
I'm not good with housework...
So, it always ends up being simple!
Well, sorry that's the case!
What?!
So you're the type of person...
...who can blow up pots when they cook?!
Nobody in the world can do that.
Yuki-chan's lunch looks wonderful again today.
Not at all.
Today's lunch is just leftovers from last night.
Dinner at Miyuki-san's place...
Is really fancy...
And these are just the leftovers.
Um...
What's inside these fried eggs?
We had some eel leftover last night, so I added it in.
You don't usually see leftovers for eel.
The only thing that's ever leftover at our house is moldy curry.
Your house isn't normal.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Yo!
Look! Look!
My parents bought me a cell phone!
Good for you.
'Cause I did well on my practical exams for once.
Give me your number.
I'll give you mine.
What is my number again?
Um...
Hold on a second!
Um... Um...
Konata.
You have a cell phone?
But I usually forget it at home.
Since Dad's the only one who ever calls.
Doesn't that defeat the purpose of having a cell phone?
You think?
Keroro!
Isn't it cute?
They bought it for me with the cell phone.
Oh, yeah...
There was a girl in our class who
had a bunch of straps on her phone.
They weighed it...
...and the straps alone were 800 grams.
That much?
That's heavy, man.
Once she took the straps off...
...her stiff shoulders were cured.
Sounds like making a phone call would count as weight training.
Isn't it exciting how you never know
when you'll get a call on your cell phone?
Really?
I hope someone calls me soon!
There's no need to get so excited over a cell phone nowadays.
By the way, did you find your number yet?
Not yet!
In England...
...there was a large struggle between the
House of Lancaster and the House of York.
The two houses fought wearing red and white roses respectively.
Thus, this war was known as the War of Roses.
It lasted from 1455 to 1485.
This...
M-Mine?!
It's my phone!
Somebody finally called me!
Who's this?
Okay.
Confiscated.
Pick it up in the faculty office after school.
What a relief!
She gave it back!
But junk mail already?
Dad?
Still at school.
I was talking with Konata and Miyuki and lost track of time.
It's okay.
We'll be home soon.
Bye.
Just a little late and look what happens.
Yes?
Dad?
I'm still at school.
I'm with Kona-chan and everyone.
You'd think he'd get the idea after calling one of us.
Fathers are always worried about their daughters.
We sure get a lot of junk mail these days.
It's better to make your address hard to guess.
That's how I did it.
Hard to guess?
In what way?
My e-mail address is in roman letters.
iluvgiriswithglasses.
I wanted to go with maids or something...
But maids and shrine maidens are popular and easily...
Hold it right there!
We get it already...
...so don't talk so loudly around the general public.
Your conversation is a bigger problem than the junk mail!
Good morning!
Yo!
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
My cell phone...
My cell phone...!
She left it in her pocket...
It's gone to a better place, huh...
I wonder if they'll buy me another one...
This boy was safe.
Tenacious little guy.
Then the e-mail last night...
The one that said Kagami wanted her notes back...
That was the last one you sent?
Yep.
Did you reply?
Um...
You never respond immediately when you get an e-mail, do you?!
I don't reply to people I can talk to whenever I want.
Reply to e-mails through e-mail.
We see each other every day.
What's the point?
You're going to lose your friends.
Oh, well.
Wasn't that big a deal anyway.
Don't decide that on your own!
And she didn't return my notes.
Tsukasa!
I'm coming in!
Sis.
Wh-What is it?
What's wrong?
This manga I borrowed from Kona-chan moved me to tears.
Good morning!
Thanks for the manga, Kona-chan!
It was great!
Wasn't it so stupid and hilarious?
I-It moved me to tears!
I find it hard to believe you're talking about the same manga.
Here.
If you cry, you're with Tsukasa.
If you laugh, you're with me.
I'm not gonna read it!
I don't want to be classified with either of you.
But I wanna see how Sis reacts.
Is it wrong to want to know more about your friends?
In that case...
Did Attack No. 1 make you cry or laugh?
Laugh.
Cry.
Then what's your favorite manga?
Sgt. Frog.
I can't tell if these two are similar or not...
Why don't you join a manga club, Kona-chan?
Since you love manga.
Well, I'd be willing to do it...
And it'd be a good use of time...
Draw. Draw. Draw. Draw.
D-Did you even try on this?!
Incidentally, Konata-san...
What is this a picture of?
This is Tsukasa.
This was me!
This is Miyuki-san.
Well, I could really stretch and say that you captured her spirit...
This is Kagami.
So I can breathe fire.
My...
It fits Kagami-san's image so perfectly.
What a frightening child.
Cut that out already!
There's a new volume of FMP out.
Right, I guess there's a release date coming up.
I'm heading to Gamers.
Wanna come along?
Sorry.
I'll just stop by a local bookstore today.
I have some other stuff to take care of.
You're supposed to come with me as a sign of our friendship!
What is it?
You sure are clingy today.
Besides, you shouldn't be using words like friendship.
Well, you know...
I wanted you to give me your
purchase points as a sign of our friendship.
So that's your idea of friendship.
I can almost get
the item I want
You've waited so long for me!
It's quiet...
Is she mad about how I mixed up the
ribbons on my pigtails with sunflowers?
Me?
Me?!
To Akira-sama?
You sure?
Understood.
Uh.
Uh...
It started already...
No choice!
Before they change the channel...
Go—
Good lucky!
Just kidding!
Just wanted to say it.
W-Well, we're on another episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm Minoru Shiraishi!
Akira-sama's in a bad mood so...
You said your own name before Akira Kogami.
Do you not understand what natural order is?
No, that's...
Looks like those pigtails of yours have been
getting ridiculously popular in certain places.
I-I wouldn't call it popular...
Don't be getting full of yourself!
I'm terribly sorry!
Besides...
People were expecting Project
Fashionable Akira to show me in pigtails, right?
So what's this?
It's just as you say!
I'll go with twin drills!
T-Twin drills?!
Don't underestimate the Getter's speed.
No. 2, huh?
The age of pigtails is over!
The new thing is twin drills!
Isn't that what Konata said?
Drills are like a man's romance.
Is it now...
Well, everybody!
You can catch the rest of this on
the radio show and our home page!
L-Look forward to next time.
Bye-bee!
Say...
Yes?
About those pigtails...
Ah, the ones I had?
The ones in the real life picture.
Yes?
You had sunflowers on, right?
I did.
That looked awfully familiar...
You can't mean...
How many years ago was it?
H-Hold on a sec!
In one of my...
Eew! Eew!
I was so nervous.
It was cute and wonderful.
Isn't it so nerve-wracking when you're singing your first song?
You wonder if your voice can be heard and stuff.
Miyuki's next, right?
Sing us something full of memories.
Why?
May I have the mic?
Here.
Go for it!
Um, I'm not used to this kind of thing.
Please forgive me if it offends your ears.
Don't worry.
Go for it!
Manly.
I get it.
This ties in to the other Miyuki.
PLEIADS IS IN THE WIND.
Even her singing is manly.
THE MILKY WAY IS IN THE SAND.
Is this a new kind of moe?
You're so cool, Yuki-chan!
WHERE HAS EVERYONE GONE?
I NEVER SAID GOODBYE.
PEGASUS IS IN THE PRAIRIE.
VENUS IS ON THE STREET CORNER.
WHERE HAS EVERYONE GONE?
I CAN NO LONGER WATCH OVER THEM.
NOBODY REMEMBERS THE STARS ON THIS PLANET.
PEOPLE ALWAYS LOOK UP AT THE SKY.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Tsukasa.
Er, I'm already out of time?!
「Don't Need Me
to Have a Blast」
Next time:
Don't Need Me to Have a Blast.
Look forward to next time!