We won't let you fight the Eastern Federation!
Do you think our lives are worthless?
Come out, you stupid king!
We know you're working
with the Federation!
...So...
What are we all here for?
I told you after we
won yesterday, didn't I?
Demand two:
You, elf.
Fiel, I'm taking the right
to alter your memories.
...Wha—
You want us to spy for you, right?
...Spy...
The reason we bet Imanity's
Race Piece is that we knew you,
the spy working with Elven Garde,
would form contact with us.
And we beat you in the game.
You thought that, by giving me
your memories during the game,
you could bring me to your side without
having to use the commandments, right?
However, while I
did agree to help you,
I didn't see anything in your memories that'd lead me
to believe you can beat the Eastern Federation.
Do you really think you can?
We'll be fine.
Anyway, I've brought you here
for a very important reason.
There's only one thing
we need to do now.
Something we need to do
in order to fight together.
Fight Together
What is it?
...You mean...
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Introductions!
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Education
Preferred Type
Blood Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Introduction
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
Best Feature
Preferred Type
Hobbies
Zodiac
mawaritsuzukeru haguruma ni wa narisagaranai
I never wanted to become just another cog in the machine
heikin enjiru tanjou kara hajimatta jigoku
I was pretending to be average in a life that had always been hell
asobihanbun de kami ga michibiita
But then God frivolously took me to a new stage
danjou no sekai no no no game no life
To the world of no game no life
nurui heion wo bassari kirisutete
Where I can do away with my boring everyday life
eikou e no kaidan ni sonzai kizamunda
And engrave my name on the stairway to glory
me ni utsuru no wa kanzen shouri no unmei
I now see a destiny of flawless victory for myself
nani mo kamo keisan doori kaete yaru
I'll change everything precisely the way I want
somaranai kuuhaku de
As an untainted blank
we are maverick kyuusai nante iranai
We are mavericks who need no savior
donna rifujin osoou to mo kateba ii dake no hanashi darou
Whatever challenges come our way, winning is all that matters
kakehiki to sainou ga muhai izanau
We'll put our strategy and talent to work and stay undefeated
umarenaoshita inochi de tanoshimu sa
We're enjoying our new lives to the fullest
jibun dake wa jibun shinjiteru
Believing in ourselves
Introductions?
Blue Rose
Why would we do that now?
I'm Clammy Zell.
It's nice to meet you.
Huh?
Is that all?
Don't you have anything else to say?
Nope.
That's not a problem, is it?
She's eighteen years old, same as me.
158 centimeters tall.
...Her three sizes, from the top, are...
Hey!
That's not fair!
...And she pads her bra. She's actually—
F-Fine, fine! I'll do it
for real! Just stop it!
But I can't do that
without introducing Fi first.
Hello there! I'm Fiel Nilvalen!
You're all free to call me Fi,
except for that demon over there.
My, it seems you don't
like me very much at all.
I wonder why. How mysterious.
...Because...
When I think of
how many of my people
died in the attack by a certain
...Flugel during the great war...
Defendant Jibril, what is your plea?
I don't know what to say.
If you had only known your place and avoided
placing anti-flight wards above your cities,
then I never would've
even noticed you.
You got what you deserved.
Thanks to you, I fell from
the sky and bumped my head.
I don't see how you could blame me
if I accidentally let you all die.
Judge! The defendant, Jibril, is guilty!
Why?
Fi, since we'll be working together,
I don't want any hard feelings.
What does Jibril have to do
to earn your forgiveness?
That's a very difficult question.
...Fi...
We need her power for Sora's plans.
I ask you too.
Fine.
If you lick my feet and say,
"Please forgive me, O' great Fiel",
then I'll forgive you.
Excuse me?
You long-eared forest mongrels
are as cocky as can be, aren't you?
Jibril. Guilty.
Punishment.
I... I really have to lick this animal's feet?!
Punishment!
I really don't want to,
...but if that's my masters' order...
Please wait a moment.
Please forgive me, O' great Fiel.
Okay, I forgive you!
That's all it took?
Ma-Master!
Licking this vulgar animal's feet and apologizing
has to be the ultimate humiliation!
But why?
Why is it that, when I think that
I'm doing it because you ordered me to,
I get so excited?
Who is Blank, that they're
capable of doing this to a Flugel?
Do you know what's behind
this shocking discovery?
...Um...
If we're talking about hard feelings,
then I have my share too.
She used magic to
cheat and defeat me!
It's your fault for being deceived.
Oh, he's just cold-blooded and uncaring.
Fi is my childhood friend.
More specifically, she's my master.
Elven Garde is a democracy,
but they maintain a hierarchy and
promote the binding of lower-ranked races.
Basically, they have a slave system.
...So Clammy is...
Yes.
We've been slaves of the
Nilvalen family for generations.
I was born and raised in Elven Garde.
The Nilvalen family is one of
the most famous in Elven Garde
and has served in the
Upper Diet for generations.
But Fi was the only one
...to treat me, a slave...
Do you want to eat together?
Fi, don't be nice to me anymore.
If you treat a slave
...like me as a friend...
...as a friend....
Though she can't show
any signs of it on the surface.
I really don't like that!
Since the last head of the
family passed away last year,
Fi is the de facto
leader of the family.
So, from society's perspective,
our relationship has gotten
even more complicated.
Wait, so Fiel, you're acting
as an Upper Diet member now?
An Upper Diet member
...planning to free the slaves...
Isn't that treason?
That's really surprising, isn't it?
Yeah, it was. Steph, were you
really able to follow all that?
That's what surprises you?!
Are you fine with this, Fiel?
Helping us could lead to
the destruction of Elven Garde.
I'm fine with anything so long
as Clammy doesn't get hurt.
I don't really care
about my family at all,
and I've even thought it would be faster if
the whole country would just up and vanish.
You're surprisingly brutal.
Clammy starts crying whenever
I take my eyes off of her,
so I want to stay by her side.
I... I don't cry! I've never cried!
Actually, when you
lost the battle for the crown,
you were bawling like a baby.
No! That's not what happened!
I knew it!
I told you, I didn't cry!
Just because you've
known me since I was a baby
doesn't mean you can
treat me like a kid forever!
Clammy tries to
push herself too hard.
There, there.
She's more like a mom than a best friend.
Leave me alone!
There, there.
Anyway!
We need to focus on the
Eastern Federation now!
When their ruler,
the "Shrine Priestess", appeared,
they became the third-largest country
in the world in just fifty years.
Nobody knows how great
a threat they truly pose.
Not to mention that the Werebeasts
have an ability called Blood Destruction.
Do you have any sort
of plan to deal with that?
I'm thinking.
If we're going to fight together,
we need teamwork.
Bonds.
We need to get to
know each other better!
...And to do that...
I'm not taking a bath with you.
How... How did you know?
Did he forget that he
gave me all his memories?
Well, too bad.
Clammy, it's important to get to know
the people we'll be fighting alongside.
That's right!
In the world we came from, Japan, there was
a traditional ritual for getting to know each other,
...and it was...
hanging out while naked!
I'm having you work with me because of
mutual trust, not because of the commandments.
My only hope is to resort
to traditional culture!
All you're relying on is worldly
desires and ulterior motives.
Jibril, explain to the girl.
Ahem.
The idea of associating while naked
dates back to the Japanese civil wars,
...when carrying weapons was—
30 Minutes Later
In other words, because both the
ancient Romans and modern Japanese
shared this concept of a public bath,
it became a major hit
and a nationwide phenomenon.
So, do you understand now, Clammy?
I... don't even know what
we're talking about anymore.
Very well, then.
I'll refuse for you.
This is what Clammy is trying to say.
...Uh, thank—
She doesn't want to take a bath with you
because she lacks confidence in her proportions.
That's not it!
It's fine, Clammy.
A woman's worth isn't
determined by her breasts!
Fine!
I'll take a bath with you!
That's what you want, right?
Aw yiss!
Couldn't you make this
shampoo a bit easier to use?
Clammy?
I didn't know you
had such a nice figure.
Well, I'm the type who
looks smaller with clothes on.
Master, did you expect that?
But of course.
Fi, I mean, Fiel,
is the magic you're using on
Clammy's breasts an illusion,
or did you actually alter them?
Looks like he found out, Clammy.
I think it's rude to use our magic like that
when we're supposed to be baring ourselves.
What sort of magic would you prefer?
Glad you understand!
Ahem.
Can you turn me into a girl?
That way, I can enjoy the
paradise spreading out behind me.
Of course I can!
For real?!
I won't be able to
turn you back, though.
Is that okay?
No.
They sure are a fun bunch.
It's fun to think that there are
still Imanity willing to challenge us.
Isn't that right, Ino?
Indeed.
But they're the only ones
who should have fun.
You have but one job.
Do you understand, Izuna?
Hey!
We didn't even get
a chance to talk today.
Where did he disappear to?
Sora!
So this is your strategy to
defeat the Eastern Federation?
You're not taking this very seriously.
Honestly, this is Shiro's area now.
It's beyond me.
I'm just helping.
I've just been looking over
the footage from the bath earlier.
If you're expecting me to react like
Stephanie Dola, it's not happening!
I don't quite believe that when your face is
bright red and you're covering your breasts.
You're here to ask if we
can really win, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I've looked over your memories,
and all of your victories have been close calls.
And, like I said earlier, this time
you're fighting the Eastern Federation.
One misstep and you're doomed.
I don't think you can win like this.
So I just have to avoid misstepping.
Can you really be sure you
won't make a single mistake?
No way.
If it were just me,
I'd be sure to screw it up.
But Blank is different.
If I make a mistake, Shiro is there.
That's how Blank always wins.
Don't you want to be
friends with me, Clammy?
That's not it,
but if they find out about us
...and something bad happens to you...
You and I are different.
If I make a mistake, you're there.
And I want you to
be always by my side,
so I don't make a foolish mistake
and lose the person I care about.
...Fi...
Did you pull that line
from my memories?
Who knows.
Anyway, I understand.
The reason I think you can't win
is that I only have your memories.
You've found your wings, haven't you?
Hey, Shiro.
...They say people can change...
...but is that really true?...
Pretty embarrassing,
but I kind of like that thought.
There's no need to be ashamed.
Shut up!
It's hard to have
such a talented sister.
You've got your pride
to think of, big brother.
Get out of here, already!
If you stay too long in Elkia,
they'll get suspicious!
Tomorrow's the day, isn't it?
I'll believe in the
potential of humanity.
Of course you will.
You're human too.
Hey!
He's coming out!
You mad failure of a king!
You're insane, leaving
by the front gate like this!
There's a riot happening!
This didn't just happen. I started it.
What do you mean?
Well, they made a path
for us, so let's get going.
We're heading for Izuna's house!
Why are you ignoring me?
We've been waiting for you.
Please wait here until the game begins.
Make sure you let the audience in.
All right, Shiro.
How are you feeling?
All green!
How about you, Jibril?
Flugel are the ultimate weapons.
How we feel has
nothing to do with it.
I will give you my all
at a single word.
My stomach hurts.
By the way, Steph.
Yes?
You remember that I still have one demand
left after our bet in that last game, right?
Huh?
Jibril, can you keep the Werebeasts
from hearing what goes on in here?
Yes.
I'm able to cover you and Dola in spirits
to keep the sound from getting out.
Okay, Steph. I'm going to
put a special spell on you.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Players, please sit here.
I will now confirm
the terms of the game.
The Eastern Federation wagers
everything it owns on the Lucia continent.
The kingdom of Elkia
wagers its Race Piece.
In other words, all the rights
of the Imanity, their territory,
and everything they possess is on the line
in a game designated by the Eastern Federation
between the representative
of the Eastern Federation
and the two rulers of Elkia,
joined by their two attendants.
The game will be conducted
with these five players, one vs. four.
And as always, if the Federation wins,
all memories of the game itself are to be forgotten.
This includes all players and
all the Imanity viewing the game.
Now, the rules will be
explained once the game begins.
So if you decide to decline
after hearing the rules,
your memories of the game will be taken,
but the contest will be voided.
Are you sure this is okay with you?
Sure, no problem.
But there are two things
I want to make clear.
Firstly, if we do decide to drop out, then the
only memories we lose are of today's game.
If your plan was to
give us an impossible game
to make us drop out and then rob us
of all our memories, give it up now.
And secondly, if we catch you cheating during
the game, it's grounds for an immediate loss.
That's a major premise
of the ten commandments,
and as long as you don't forget it,
we'll have no problems.
I'll take that as an agreement and
ask you to swear by said commandments.
Aschente (I swear by the commandments)
Aschente!
Aschente, please.
Let's do this, Izuna.
I won't lose.
Hey, Izuna.
What, please?
When was the last time
you thought a game was fun?
Are you all ready?
Okay, Shiro.
Don't let go of my hand.
You too, Bro.
Let's begin the game.
...I sense magic...
Clammy Zell?
What's she doing here?
...And...
You're trying to act
like you didn't notice,
but your ears moved
when you sensed my magic.
Fi, it doesn't look like we can
interfere with the game from here.
I know that.
What's important is the
fact that we're watching.
This means the Eastern Federation
can't use any obvious cheats.
Let's see what you can do,
Sora.
He's sharing information with the elves?
Just how cautious is he?
But even so, we Werebeasts
can't possibly lose at this game.
Are we really okay?
I don't think we can win this.
Steph, it's the same as the
answer to your earlier question.
Why did I make the people riot?
Huh?
Why are you talking about this now?
I don't need the trust of anyone
who's sure we can win.
They're watching closely to
make sure we don't deliberately lose.
As a result, it's harder for the
Eastern Federation to use obvious cheats.
There's no more trusted observer
than someone who suspects you.
That's impressive, Master!
They'll try to use cheats
and Werebeast abilities
that we aren't expecting
so they can overcome our observers.
What determines our victory is how
...quickly we react to what we expected—
and to what we didn't expect—and
how we reflect that in our strategies.
Wh-Where the heck are we?
It's an illusionary world that
I've never seen or heard of before.
...Master, where are—
What's wrong, Master?
We're doomed.
We can't do this.
Sorry. Imanity's finished.
Wh-What do you mean?
After all that buildup?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't expect it
to be set in Tokyo.
I can't do anything here.
It's our home,
but we're the away team.
We can't help you, so I'm sorry,
but please handle this
yourselves. We can't do it.
...No way...
dare ni mo ienai
With a loneliness
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That I could share with no one, I was crying all alone
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, deep inside our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshiyatte
We pushed away the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura wa kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furun deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By finding and piecing together the fragmented expressions
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuite ikun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
As we pray to the sky
douka eien ni
For this moment to last forever
Killing Giant
No doubt in my mind!
I believe Shiro!