So, Aki, how many
people are going on this trip?
Akihisa Yoshii is
being put in a tight spot.
N-Nine people, including you...
Is that a problem?
If we rent a van, it'll
be fine, but seven is a lot.
Who did you invite?
F-For example, you know
these guys, too, right?
Yuuji...
Hideyoshi...
Muttsulini...
Who else?
Th-The others are...
Th-This isn't good. She forbids me
from being close friends with girls.
For Kirishima, I can probably get by
by telling Sis that she's Yuuji's fiancée.
But Himeji...
Minami...
Kudou... If she realizes they're coming,
too, I don't know what she'll do to me!
So, who else?
Huh? Well, H-H...
You've already mentioned Hideyoshi.
H... It's a secret.
Aki, please clench your teeth.
I'm sorry! I was just joking!
If you're honest with me,
I'll reward you with a kiss.
The remaining four
people are space people.
Aki, close your eyes.
Argh! Wait a sec!
I clearly lied to you, didn't I?!
In a sense, humans are space people, too.
Wait! I apologize! Stop! Stop!
Why...? To think that
you refuse that strongly...
Ah... I'm sorry. But a
brother and sister kissing...
It's arousing, right?
A perv! A hopeless
perv stands before me!
Please don't take it
seriously. I was 30% joking.
Oh no... So she was
more than half serious.
To start with, it was your fault that
you tried to weasel your way out by lying.
Ack!
Why did you try weaseling out of telling me?
You won't get upset?
Of course not. Unless you're bringing girls,
I won't get upset or
make you wear girls' clo--
Where are you going, Aki?
I don't wanna be
scolded, beaten, smashed,
and forced to wear girls' clothes!
I see... So you invited girls, too...
I-It's not like that! It's just that...
Himeji and the others
help me out with my studies.
Also I'd feel bad not inviting them
when we always do things together.
I didn't know it'd turn out to
be an overnight trip, either, so...
Seriously, what will I do with you?
Okay, then.
What?! Th-Then...
Just this time, okay?
However, if I see you engaging
in illicit sexual activities...
...your entire family will be killed.
Err, that includes you, Sis.
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"Episode 1
Me, Everyone, and Swimming in the Ocean!"
And, today is the day of their beach trip.
It's a good thing the
weather is nice, huh, Yuuji?
Yeah. Everyone was able to make it, too.
I was so excited about this trip
that I had a hard time sleeping.
Come on, Mizuki. You aren't
an elementary school kid.
I got a new swimsuit for today, too.
I thought you bought a new one just recently.
That one... uhm... didn't fit.
A-ha... Could it be
that you gained weight?
Just a little! Just a little!
It was just a little bit of a lot...
So which is it?
It's not like that.
I'm sure my weight gain was
caused by my hair growing, that's all!
Geez... That's because
you let your guard down.
As for me, I even lost
weight due to the heat.
What?! That's not fair, Minami!
That's a harsh betrayal!
Yeah, I did lose weight...
starting with my breasts.
Himeji, Shimada, aren't
you guys worrying too much?
I don't think you two look
much different from before.
Well, excuse me! I know my
breasts grow slower than yours!
My breasts don't grow!
You don't have to be nice to me.
I know you'll get huge boobs
and leave me in the dust!
You have such a busty figure.
You can't understand our worries!
I'm a guy! Calm down!
What's with you two today?
It's just...
I envy her breasts.
I envy her slim waist.
Indeed, Akira is dangerous.
I have to keep a sharp eye on Yuuji.
Yeah, she's got such a nice figure.
It's amazing! It seems like she'd look good
in those string bikinis you
see in dirty magazines, huh?
Oh? What's the matter, Kouta?
I got a little carsick.
It's not often that
carsickness causes nose bleeds.
Aki, could you get the motion
sickness medicine from my bag?
Okay!
Hm? The zipper doesn't open.
One, two... Oof!
Okay, it's open. Hm?
A school swimsuit (old type). Wow...
Sis! This is "out"!
What's with you, Akihisa?!
What do I do, Yuuji?! I've got a
hopelessly pathetic person in my family!
I think the pathetic one is you,
holding that school swimsuit tight.
Well, this is my sister's swimsuit and...
I see. You have an interest in
your sister's school swimsuit, huh?
That is hopeless.
You got it wrong! I won't allow this!
You were worried about being
embarrassed, so you asked me to wear
something that exposes as
little as possible, right, Aki?
I'm sorry! Compared
to the embarrassment
of walking with my own sister
in this swimsuit at her age,
your exposure was nothing!
Change! Change the swimsuit!
As your brother, I can't
allow something like this!
In other words, are you saying that
this swimsuit exposes too little skin?
Oh, think whatever you like.
Akihisa, you should
watch your naughtiness.
Ahh! Muttsulini, the king of
naughtiness, called me naughty!
Don't cry, Akihisa. You call
others idiots at times, too, right?
Does that mean that
I'm the king of idiots?!
I guess it can't be helped.
I'll wear a different swimsuit.
Actually, it was tight around the
bust and my breasts fell out, so...
Bust... Bust... Breasts fell out...!
Wow, what a nice view.
The breeze feels nice, too.
This location is perfect.
All right! Let's go
quickly change and swim!
Okay!
Today's the day that I make sure
everyone realizes that I'm a guy!
This time, I was careful to
purchase guys' swimming trunks.
I won't let anyone complain!
Yahoo!
I changed in the car!
The tan I got from my swimming club
swimsuit doesn't match with this one.
This is also sexy, isn't it, Muttsulini?
If you wanna take pictures of me,
you can take as many as you want.
I don't mind.
Don't flatter yourself, Aiko Kudou.
Huh?
I haven't the slightest
interest in your swimsu--
This is caused by sunstroke.
You really hung in there, Muttsulini.
You lasted 28 seconds.
It's amazing! You beat your old
record for holding back your nosebleed!
Are you okay, Muttsulini?
Ahh... If you get
closer to him, Kudou...
The sunlight is... strong...
Muttsulini!
I wish to be reincarnated as a bird.
Oh no... Don't even joke like that!
And I wish to be able to peek on
the girls' locker room from the sky
as much as my heart desires.
He didn't learn anything
from his death in this world.
Woosh... Woosh...
--I didn't know that lemon juice goes surprisingly well with sugar.
--I'm sorry to keep you guys waiting!
Thanks for waiting.
Is Tsuchiya okay?
He's stable right now.
Aiko, don't tease him too much.
Well, I didn't do anything, though.
You look so cute in that
swimsuit that Tsuchiya got excited.
There has not been
any confirmation of that.
Excited?
Yes. He's a guy, too, after all.
I see...
--Scissors.
--Arrrrrrrrgh!
What'd you do that
for all of a sudden?!
You have to get excited by
watching me in a swimsuit, so...
You didn't have to do that.
You both are pretty
and have nice figures.
Oh... stop it...
"Pretty"? I'm embarrassed.
Thank you, Yoshii.
I know I don't have
a nice figure after all!
That's not really true. You're slim
and the right places are protruding, so...
Yeah, yeah. My bust is slim
and my belly is protruding!
No one said that!
Hey, guys! Sorry to keep you waiting!
You! What're you doing?!
What is it?
Why aren't you wearing your top?!
Because this is a men's swimsuit.
A girl shouldn't wear a men's swimsuit!
Well, I'm not a girl.
Anyway, come with me!
You're mistaken!
Listen to me! I'm saying, wait!
Oh, Minami, did my
brother make a blunder?
What's the matter, Minami?
It's okay. I know I'll never
be able to beat that.
Akira, excuse me a second.
Amazing!
I'm sorry! Please excuse me, too!
Beaches are cruel, aren't they?
It's God who's cruel.
I'm sorry I took so long, everyone.
Is something wrong, Hideyoshi?
You seem to be down.
Please don't ask me about it.
Beaches in summer
are cruel in many ways.
Idiot Test!
Akihisa, it's more to your right.
That's not true.
It's actually more to your left.
Yoshii, keep going straight ahead.
Who's telling the truth?
Aki, it's 32 degrees
left at a distance of 4.7m.
It's actually at the opposite direction.
Everyone's giving me
different instructions. What do I do?
What about Yuuji?
Yuuji, what do you
think of this swimsuit?
Nothing, really.
I saw it before, didn't I?
That's because you aren't seeing it
carefully. You should see it up closer.
Hey! Don't get so close!
All sorts of things are touching me!
It's... right... there!
Bite me!
That was close!
Tsk! I missed it.
I'm sorry, Yuuji.
I thought it was a watermelon.
It looked as if you
dashed with no hesitation.
What're you saying, Hideyoshi?
That's a terrible misunderstanding.
He's right, Hideyoshi. All Akihisa was
doing was looking for the watermelon.
Now, it's my turn.
What's the matter?
Let go of the bat, Akihisa.
You tried just a little earlier and failed.
The first round is over. It's the
second round now and I go first, right?
It's just fair to do it in the
opposite order in the second round.
Uhm, we don't really want to smash
the watermelon, so why don't we stop
the watermelon cracking game now?
Don't worry! We're definitely
not gonna crack the watermelon!
What're you guys going to crack?
Ahh... I'm exhausted.
I haven't even swum yet.
Why am I so exhausted?
You asked for it.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
We bought lunch.
Sorry that it took us a while.
Was it crowded?
No, but...
Well, we got hit on.
I really don't like stuff like that.
Me, neither.
I see. That must've been a hassle.
You can just laugh it off, right?
Yeah, he's right.
Hey, both of you.
That kind of attitude isn't good.
Huh?
Geez, you don't get how
women's minds work, do you?
That's right. You should
be more worried, Yuuji.
Huh?! About wha--
Argh! My bones...!
I wish Akihisa got jealous
over us, too, even just a little bit...
Oh yeah, why don't we
make him worry a little?
Yeah.
Guys like that are everywhere.
It's such a pain, right, Mizuki?!
Yeah, they're always bothering us!
Oh? Do you two often get hit on?
Yes! We get hit on all the time!
Yeah! We get hit on everywhere!
But, you guys seemed
like you weren't used to it.
What?!
Th-That's not true! Since it happens
all the time, we were just disgusted.
That's right,
though you may not get it since
you're dull and a stranger to relationships!
How rude! If we're talking
hitting on girls, I, too, can easily...
--Easily what?
To start with, there's no
way you can hit on girls, Aki!
That's right! Hitting on
girls doesn't suit you, Akihisa!
I don't think it'll work, either!
You shouldn't put up a front!
You don't get a woman's heart either,
Yuuji. That's why you're unpopular.
How dare you say
something like th-- Argh!
Everyone has his or her
strengths and weaknesses.
You're not suited for relationships.
Damn! I can't take it!
I feel like I was unfairly scolded.
How can they say we're unpopular?!
Yeah! If I get serious, I can
hit on as many girls as I... Hm?
"Argh"
What's wrong, Akihisa?!
I-I saw an unbelievable sight...
...is being hit on...
Huh?
Muttsulini is being hit on by girls.
That's ridiculous. I keep telling
you to cut it with the nonsense talk...
You're a genius at
taking pictures, aren't you?
Oh, this is nothing special.
Oh, you're being shy,
aren't you? How cute.
This can't be happening...
Why is Muttsulini...
Yuuji...
What is it?
This is just hypothetically speaking...
but could you and I be the only
ones among us who're unpopular?
Don't be ridiculous!
That can't be right!
Yeah! There's no way
that's the case, right?!
At a glance, Muttsulini
looks completely harmless, so...
It's just that he's a different
type from us, that's all, right?!
Yeah, so it'd be premature
to think that we're unpopular!
That's right, right?! How dare they
say that there's no way I can hit on girls!
I'll show them what I can do!
That's the spirit, Akihisa! Let's show
what we can do when we get serious!
Yeah!
"Thinking back on it,
something must've been
really wrong with us at that time."
In any case, how do we
go about hitting on girls?
The quickest route would
be to imitate a successful guy.
Let's follow Muttsulini's example.
We target those who're
trying to take pictures?
Yeah, the first person will start
by creating an opportunity, saying,
"I can take your picture if you like."
I see...
Then, if the second person
gets a conversation going,
the rest will go without a hitch.
So how do we get a conversation going?
That's something the second
person has to think about.
So if the whole thing fails,
it'd be the second person's fault, huh?
You jerk, Akihisa! Why are
you running like a maniac?!
You too, Yuuji!
What's with that crazy running?!
You take your time and come later.
You should do that!
I'll create an opportunity, so...!
I can't trust you! Just leave it to me!
Not a chance!
Thanks for waiting!
Well then, I'll take your picture!
"Gasping, gasping... Gasping, gasping..."
Miss... you're pretty.
If you like, I can take...
a picture of you in a swimsuit...
I never thought that
they'd call the police...
Using pictures to create an
opportunity might be tough, huh?
Yeah... Unlike Muttsulini,
we're not good at taking pictures.
Okay then, let's change the approach.
What're we gonna do?
How about we praise the target's
looks to thaw the ice and get close?
Yeah, people like being praised.
But how do we praise them?
Use figurative expressions,
like telling them they resemble
some showbiz person or athlete.
If you compare them to someone
and get the conversation going...
...it'll be a piece of cake!
Thanks.
Uhm... you're pretty, Miss.
What? Really?
Yeah, you've got an outstanding figure!
I think so, too! It's really nice!
Oh, you guys are good at flattery.
No, it's not flattery!
That's right! We really think that way!
Yeah! You've really got a
nice figure. You're just like...
Yeah, you're just like...
You're just like one of the
nude models in dirty magazines!
What a right hook she had...
She could be a world champion.
I bet that lady is a future champion
because I even feel it in my legs.
Oh? Where have you two been?
Gulp!
Your faces are swollen.
What happened?
N-Nothing, really, right, Yuuji?!
Y-Yeah! We just fell,
that's all. Right, Akihisa?!
Yuuji! Let's go back to
the swimming competition!
Yeah! I'm not gonna lose this time!
We were finally close to succeeding!
But since you said
something uncalled for...!
That's because you said stupid stuff!
What'd you say?! Are you
trying to pin this all on me?!
You jerk... Are you picking a fight?
Let's not. Fighting won't get us anywhere.
Yeah.
You know, I was thinking...
Don't you think things go bad
because we're not really serious?
Huh?
I mean, since they're not our types,
we're unconsciously holding back.
True... If we can't get serious,
then what can we do, right?
As if...
That's an uncool excuse, isn't it?
What's the matter, Yuuji?
All right, then! Why don't
we try one last time with them?
Yeah, let's do it.
E-Excuse me...
A-Actually... we got lost.
W-Well, we're looking for the
swimming beach, do you know where it...
Idiot! This is the swimming beach!
You said we got lost,
so without thinking, I just...
Hm?
Her hair color... changed?!
I'm always like this.
Sh-Shouko...
Oh shoot!
Huh?
Sorry, Akihisa...
Muttsulini?! Why...?
They were giving off a vibe that
I was going to be killed if I refused.
I-Is it possible that you guys
knew we were hitting on girls?
They said just the right arm...
Just the right arm, huh?
It sounds painful.
I don't wanna go back.
They said they'd spare just the
right arm and break everything else.
Akihisa, please stay where you are.
I'm going to give you a full-course
punishment today. Be prepared, Aki!
Your sister feels sad...
about losing her little brother.
Run, Akihisa!
These three are serious about hurtin--
Akihisa... We had a lot of fun together.
Noooooo!
Yuuji...
Yes, Ma'am.
Sit in a formal way.
What? But we're in the...
Well, we're in the ocean so...
Are you going to make me say it again?
Sit in a formal way...
Question 2.
Aside from water, what is the
primary component of seawater?
Tears of regrets and penitence.
What happened?
Next episode!
"Me, Yukata, and Festivities!"
This will be on the test.