Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I see you've bonded with a new friend,
which has allowed you to obtain the Priestess Arcana.
The disaster looming in your future is claiming human lives as it draws ever closer.
But there is nothing to fear.
You already possess the power to fight back.
When you truly need us,
the door will open, and we shall offer you our assistance.
I'm looking forward to it!
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
I'm hot! I'm on fire!
What should I do with my melting hot body?
I'm so hot.
I'll just have to thrust...
deeper in!
Off I go!
Dude, did you see that?
I did.
So you saw...
I sure did.
Want a copy?
Hell no!
Incredible! We actually went inside the TV.
Oh, yeah. This is Yukiko's first time coming here on her own.
What? You don't know where Tatsumi Kanji is?
Well, I can smell that someone's here, but I can't figure out where.
Why not?
I think it's because I've got so much on my mind!
Like where did I come from?
Who am I?
I can't seem to figure it out.
How could you? Your head's totally empty inside.
Well, what can we do? Our hands are tied if Teddie can't find him.
So like, wanna call it quits this time?
Of course not!
We can't?
Wha— Narukami?!
Maybe I could find him if you gave me a hint.
Got anything with his scent on it?
I'm sorry,
but he hasn't been home since yesterday.
It's been dangerous out lately, so I notified the police.
You must be worried.
Indeed.
He always leaves without saying a word, but this is the first time he hasn't come home.
That's surprising. I figured he'd usually be out at night fighting.
Hey, watch it!
It's okay. I'll admit he can be a little rough.
A while ago, he got into a fight with some biker kids.
You mean how he beat up an entire biker gang?
But that was partially my fault.
I couldn't sleep because of their loud bikes.
That made him angry.
So he beat up a biker gang for his mother?
Talk about an aggressive momma's boy!
Can I help you?
Uh, is that guy in?
The one who lives here?
Yep! Um, see this?
That's...
I borrowed Sana's cell phone strap with a doll on it,
but I lost the doll and couldn't find it anywhere.
And then...
Pipe down! There's no use crying over it!
What's it like?
Huh?
I can't make an exact copy, but I could make something like it.
Really?
Yeah. Just apologize when you give it to her and ask for her forgiveness.
I'll go with you.
He even made one for me to match Sana's.
Does that mean Tatsumi Kanji made that strap from scratch?
Yeah.
May I see it?
Yep.
Amazing! It doesn't even look handmade.
H-How cute.
I'm not sure what to think of Kanji making something like this.
No way! It defies my image of him.
Everyone has their thing.
Sana forgave me because of him, so I wanted to thank him.
Say, could I ask you for a favor?
Those kids...
His scent should be on it if he made it.
Yeah!
Huh? Didn't we see him yesterday?
So we meet again.
Yeah, what a coincidence.
Did you hear? Tatsumi has gone into hiding.
Uh, yeah.
Come to think of it, what did you and Kanji talk about yesterday?
Why do you need to know?
Uh, just curious.
Fair enough. I'll tell you upfront since you seem to be in a hurry.
All I did was ask him about his recent activities.
What? It was just small talk?
Pretty much.
But now that I think about it, he was acting a little peculiar.
Peculiar?
Yes. And I bluntly told him as much.
I said, "You're weird."
That made the color drain from his face.
That's surprising. He doesn't seem like the type to care.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
He might be struggling with some sort of complex.
A complex?
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff.
This bear acts like a dog!
I think I've got Kanji's scent down.
Now to pick up the trail!
Don't fail me now, nose!
Sniff, sniff! Sniff, sniff!
Oh, I think I found something!
It feels like our target! Is this it?!
Follow me!
H-Hey!
Is Kanji here?
Is it me, or is the fog here different?
My glasses are fogging up.
Man, it's hot in here! It's just like a—
C'mere, pussycat.
Such well-defined pecs!
There's no need to be scared, so just relax.
W-Wait a sec! I don't wanna go!
Yeah, it's too risky.
Hey, Teddie, is Kanji really in there?
The nose knows!
So we're really going in.
Wait! I seriously don't want to!
It's way too risky! There's no turning back once we're in!
I might lose something important!
Shut up! We're going!
Ouch! Lemme go! No!
I'm not ready to give up my pure body!
I should just leave him.
Narukami, let's go.
Okay!
Damn, it's hot. This sucks!
I wanna leave so badly.
Should we split up?
Satonaka and Amagi can charge in while you and I go home.
Great idea!
Like hell it is! You're not going anywhere!
We're here to save Kanji, remember?
Try to keep that in mind.
Sure thing.
He's not as bad as I thought, so we gotta save him.
My, my. Thank you for your attention!
I'm Kanji!
Hold it! Not so fast!
Yeah, right! We're gonna snap if we don't get this over with quickly!
We're coming at you live from the Suspicious Tropical Paradise!
The hot steam is making my heart go wild!
Hey! Not you too, Chie!
Sorry. He was pissing me off.
See?
Since everyone's burning up, let's move on to the next segment!
No Girls Allowed!
Take the Plunge?!
It's the Steamy Paradise of Love!
This is bad... in more ways than one.
This is just like it was with Yukiko.
No way! Mine was nothing like this!
So, do the people who get thrown in here create these images?
Mine was like this? No, that can't be true.
Well then, in my hunt for more love,
I shall thrust...
deeper in!
Here I go, dammit!
Hold it!
Here they come!
Is this how it was with me?
That... That...
That pisses me off!
Persona!
You're up, Jiraiya!
Ouch!
Don't use your fire spells when it's already this hot!
It's too damn hot!
Now I'm freezing. How about a little moderation?
Now I see what Hanamura was getting at.
We'll go crazy if we stay here too long.
The next time he creeps me out, he's toast!
Sounds good.
No, it doesn't! You can't do that!
Why not?
Dammit, what is this place?!
Is someone there?! Show yourself!
Tatsumi Kanji's a violent delinquent and a bum.
What was that?!
He trashed a biker gang and became their boss.
He thinks he's "King of the Mountain"!
Cut the crap! I never became their boss!
Aren't you the one stealing kids' money at school?
No, I'm not! Don't assume it was me!
Clearly Tatsumi Kanji did it. He's that kind of guy.
Fuck that!
How dare you make that shit up?!
Come out so I can kill ya!
That's why you put on the scary delinquent act.
"Cut the crap"? You're such a liar.
Who is it this time?
Kanji, the strong and scary delinquent.
Talk about manly!
That's how you want to be seen, right?
But that's not you.
You're me?!
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Kindly
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Average
A
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Strong
Understanding
Kindly
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Average
A
Welcome to Tropical Paradise
He's in here, isn't he?
Yeah, no doubt about it.
Okay, let's go all out.
Yeah, but keep your cool.
You're one to talk!
Yeah, well, no one should lose their temper!
First, we need to rescue Kanji. Then, we gotta save Kanji!
Chie, those two objectives were the same thing!
Uh, that was intentional.
Huh? It was?
Obviously!
Amagi, I seriously don't get you.
Why aren't you opening the door?
Yeah, about that...
Do we really have to? I bet we're in for an eyesore.
I can just picture it.
Yeah. What should we do, Narukami?
Let's just leave.
That's not happening!
This is when you guys take the lead!
Go on!
What?! Wait!
Go on! I said, go!
W-Wait! Why me?!
Oh, wow! You're so gentle!
Cut it out, you bastard!
It's simply sublime!
I told you so.
Wha— You guys?! Why are you here?!
We, uh, came...
...to save you.
Why do you sound so unmotivated?!
Upsy daisy!
I won't let you interfere! Hmph!
Huh?
What's this? Is this supposed to slow us down?
Chie!
Are you guys okay?
What are you guys doing?
What is this?! It's slimy!
It's so gross!
I can't get up.
Narukami, got a video camera handy?
Shit! I don't!
What do you think— Whoa!
Bastard!
Why don't you drop the charade?
Huh?!
What's wrong with just saying what you want to do?
I'm what you really want, aren't I?
Hell no!
No, don't listen to him!
Jirai— Whoa!
Hanamura!
Master, I'll help— Oh, no!
Oh, how I hate girls.
They look at me and say, "You like to sew? What a queer!" or "Painting is so not you."
Punk, if you don't shut up...
"But you're a man! Why don't you act like a guy?! Why aren't you manly?!"
"But you're a man! Why don't act like a guy! You aren't you manly?"
What does it mean to be manly?
Girls are so scary.
I ain't scared of 'em!
Men are much better!
They'd never say those awful things.
Yes, I vastly prefer men!
Bullshit!
But it's true.
Why, you're me, and I'm you.
Like hell you are!
No! Don't say it, Kanji!
There's no way in hell that you're me!
You're me, and there's no denying it!
I am a Shadow... The true self...
Oh, my, my, my!
That's enough shit outta you!
Don't interfere!
Kanji!
Are you okay?!
Hang in there!
I want to be honest with myself.
And I'll get rid of anyone who gets in my way.
I can't believe this is how Kanji truly feels.
This isn't how he feels!
His emotions are just going haywire.
Get him!
Oh, yeah!
Hey! Come on, baby!
Wh-What the hell?!
Oh, nice!
No way!
What's going on?
Hey, Teddie! What's the big deal? We've got some real weirdos here!
They must be a part of Kanji's Shadow.
My, what a stud!
Ch-Change!
H-Huh?
Oh?
Hold me tight!
Ch-Cha—
I could just eat you up!
You too!
I'm dead.
The monster! He broke their spirit!
Crap! The guys are down!
It's okay. They aren't interested in us, I think.
Hmph!
Huh? What is it?
Such vulgar red!
What?!
Give me more!
Calm down, Yukiko!
Wh-What is it?
Say something!
Feeling so good!
Girls, calm down!
They weren't any trouble at all.
What a hoot!
You sound lovely! It's making my heart race.
Huh?
But you're an eyesore!
You're...
Well, it's time for one last hustle!
At this rate...
I've been waiting for you.
The time has finally come.
It's time for you to awaken your wild card's true power.
Awesome!
They merged together!
Oh, goodness!
I don't dislike this! Not at all!
Ecstasy!
Oh, no!
I'm so cold!
Isn't that...
Didn't you make it?
What? Got a problem with that?
I made it even though I'm a dude.
No, I think it's cute.
Huh?
It's cute.
Cu—
I-I-It's cute?!
It's super-duper cute! I love anything cute!
You're so persistent!
Yeah, that's right.
What is?
I love cutesy shit!
Oh!
Accept me!
He defeated his own Shadow!
Uh, it made me happy when you called it cute and accepted me.
He... He's coming back for more!
You must really find him unbearable!
Won't someone, anyone, accept me?!
Accept me!
I said to cut the crap!
Damn, the mere thought that you've been inside me is disgraceful.
Kanji...
It ain't about men or women.
I'm just scared shitless of getting rejected.
I'm a total pansy who tries to make everyone hate me!
Yeah, I already know.
You're me, and I'm you, dammit!
Mmhmm.
That's Kanji's Persona.
It's pretty masculine!
Persona...
You okay, Kanji?
Are you okay?
Kanji!
Honestly, anyone would be surprised if they found out you made this.
Drop it! I'm over that already!
Right.
I owe you.
I'm surprised you're being so polite.
Well, you guys are my seniors.
More importantly, who was the jackass that threw me into the TV?
That's what we're trying to find out.
You're searching for the culprit? Can I help out?
I gotta pay him back ten times over!
For real? That'd be great! You'd be a huge help.
Yeah. Is that okay, Narukami?
Of course.
Thanks!
I, Kanji Tatsumi, will risk my life for you!
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
Adachi was telling me
that you were hanging out around Tatsumi Textiles.
What were you doing there?
A friend took me there.
You aren't getting into any funny business, are you?
You guys fighting?
No, we're just talking.
Really?
Yeah.
This is really good!
two
Ta-da! It's our new early summer release!
Hey, didn't you accept me?
Not at night.
Done already?
Narukami!
We've lost something important again.