When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Do people definitely marry after marriage meetings?
What is this out of the blue?
Well, um... You see...
Saki went out for drinks with her friends two nights ago.
And since it was late, she stayed at her parents' house.
Then, she came home yesterday morning and...
Oh, you're back already?
Since you went all the way home, you could have enjoyed the stay.
No, I didn't want to make you worry, so I came back early.
I said I wasn't worried.
By the way, at last night's party, there were men, too.
Why should I care?
My mother suggested I have a marriage meeting.
That's great.
Oh, Mom? Get the arrangements moving at once.
Yes, by any means.
What? Saki!
Okay.
Therefore, tomorrow, Sunday, I will be having the meeting.
So I will be asking for a day off.
Is that fine?
And she went out this morning.
That's a surprising turn of events, but she's having the meeting because she has a desire to get married, right?
I see lots of very selfish disapproval on your face.
Fine, I'll listen to you.
So, a marriage meeting, eh?
Bunch of places to jab.
I have yet to see a marriage meeting with my own eyes.
Then how about we all go on a marriage meeting tour?
Yes! That's a great idea!
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet started!
I don't care about that!
It's no time for that!
Saki might disappear, you know?
They must be at the site by now.
A marriage meeting now-a-days has a classic feeling and is nice.
Let us leave the area to the young people.
Yeah.
No~
Please forgive me, my lord.
What's the problem? What's the problem?
Someone help meee!
What could I be thinking?
That's not what goes on at a marriage meeting.
Marriage meeting?
What the heck is that?
This is one of the super-expensive Japanese restaurants in Tokyo.
Just so you know, it's not Isumi's house's cels being recycled.
To think that Saki and some unknown man are having a marriage meeting here...
I figured it out!
They are following standard practice and are now in the "young people only" phase.
What the heck is that?
Basically the two take a stroll in the garden
and blab about each other's hobbies and stuff.
So it's like a husband and wife comedy show.
J... Just the two of them, alone?
However, this garden is so large,
it's called the Forest of Ambivalence,
and a woman who came for a marriage meeting is currently lost in it.
What?!
Maybe they've turned into bones by now.
We'll find her no matter what!
They won't turn into bones that fast.
No, it's more fun to have high tension like this.
So juicy~
N-Nice to meet you!
My name is Kaoru Kyounosuke.
I'm a teacher at Hakuou Academy.
My name is Kijima Saki.
Allow me to explain.
Kaoru Kyounosuke has been appearing as a sub-character, but his lines total count is practically nil.
He'll be talking like a machine gun now.
I'm sorry I had you come to a place like this.
No, likewise.
Um, so what are your hobbies?
What am I doing? I don't have any intention of marrying, but I just came here in the heat of the moment.
I have lots of Princess ********!
About 300 ******. It's not enough to brag about.
I'm being so rude to him.
Although it's ****, it's only the ***** model.
It's Elm***, the phantom of sol***n that was feared in the federal state by the name "Cone Hat".
However in the original Gun*** kit,
it was packaged as Elme** like in the show.
I remember, I was young in those days.
Let me take that back.
But I guess I'll have to explain why all of this is happening.
Cheers!
So, how's it been going lately, Saki?
Yeah, how's it been?
"How"? That's what I want to ask.
Both of you, what happened about getting jobs?
Are you going to say that being a NEET is a crime?
We're on a search to discover who we really are!
I-I'm sorry. I won't ask again.
We don't care about that.
When girls get together and ask "how's it been going lately", it's got to be about men.
What, I don't need a boyfriend.
Besides, the job keeps me busy, and I don't have time for that.
You'd only hear that from a person with a life.
You won't get any attention from good men if you're like that.
No need for your concern.
I am already in a good man's hands.
What? What? What does that mean?
So you do have a boyfriend after all?
No, ah...
Give us the details!
So... ah...
Rats, I didn't expect it to be this late.
There are no trains going to Nakano Sakaue at this hour.
I guess I'll call Sir so he won't worry about me
and then stay at my parents' house.
Oh, so you won't be back?
Huh? You sound happy.
Do I?
I'm not thinking things like
"I won't get yelled even if stay up late".
In any case, sorry I made you worry.
Huh? I wasn't worried about you.
But for a girl to return home
in the early morning after drinks is-
I think I can have a peaceful sleep tonight.
Thank you for the food.
Saki-chan, do you always eat meals with a grumpy face like that?
I was born with this face.
How could you say that?
How could he not worry about me when I'm returning home in the early morning after drinks?
Because nothing happens, as you see.
I'll go back now.
Hold on, Saki-chan.
What?
Um, Saki-chan, are you interested in a marriage meeting at all?
In addition!
Figures do not come with this kit.
But, it includes ********'s ********.
If you hear "marriage meeting" at that time, anyone would...
And the scale is 1/550.
Um, was my G****m trivia boring?
I-I'm sorry, I was thinking about something.
I can tell from your sad face.
Um...
I'm already twenty-eight,
so my parents are bugging me all the time.
They keep telling me to get married,
so I'm here for this marriage meeting without a choice.
It's the same for me!
Should I say by force, or by impulse...
I'm sorry!
It goes for both of us.
Rather than that...
Where... are we?
Where are we?!
Where could they be?
Beasts really could be living here.
Rest assured! I will protect you with my body!
Which way do I go!
But Wataru, what happened to Isumi?
Oh.
Why are you bringing Isumi up?
Yeah, if you follow the standard relationship plot,
when you waste time unable to confess love to your significant other,
marriage meetings tends to pop up for your partner.
It's nothing like that!
Then leave Saki-san alone.
She's at a good age; she has a right to become happy.
Y-Yeah, but...
You still don't get it?
Not that I really care, but in the first place,
it's strange for me, your fiancée, to be listening to you.
Then fine! I won't ask anymore!
I found Saki-san!
What?
Where are we?
I don't know.
Let's find our way back.
Who is he? He looks familiar.
That's Kaoru-sensei.
Oh, that Ga*-Pura geek.
I can't hear what they're saying,
but it looks like they're in a good mood.
Yes.
Damn, Saki. Is she serious about him?
But, can't we somehow hear what they're saying?
I doubt your almighty butler can do something about that.
Leave it to me!
Leave it to me, Milady.
I will use the lip-reading technique acquired from S** to read their conversation.
To be honest, I have someone I like.
To be honest, Saki, you are the one I love.
Someone... you like?
Yes.
I... love you, too.
So the person you like is?
A childhood friend of mine.
She used to be very cute, but...
That's the perspective of the guy in love.
She's broken down as she's gotten older.
Well... she was broken to begin with, but...
So what do you like about me?
How you'll be a young wife, cute,
and I want to make you go crazy. I want to break you.
But, you like her right?
Then do as you like to me?!
I don't know what she's thinks of me,
but emotions are hard to change, you know.
You're right, they are hard to change.
I'm more of a technician than I seem,
and I'll be sure to make you feel good.
Yes, if it feels good-
I can't take this anymore!
Saki!
You moron!
You'll only be hated if you dash in without a plan.
Yeah, she's got a point.
Th-Then what do I do?
How about a smack from behind with this to knock him out?
I'm not sure about that.
How about a globally standard way?
Cause a crisis, jump out once we see how insignificant the man is, and then solve the crisis.
Th-That's my Hayate. You're smart.
No, not really.
That's getting too typical nowadays.
We're in the 21st century now.
Even Wataru won't go with-
Hayate! You're amazing to come up with such an idea!
Right? My butler is a genius!
Yeah, he is!
Please...
I don't think Wataru-kun watches dramas with these stereotypical turnarounds.
So if we are to use these stereotypical turnarounds, how do we make the crisis?
We'll use Tama.
Tama?
What is he doing here?
He came after hearing what Maria was mumbling.
So I have to watch the house alone.
Well, I'll take the chance to sing my lungs out.
Ka-kun yori Kino-ppi
Ka-kun yori Kino-ppi = Kino-ppi over Ka-kun.
Pitan osuki desuka?
Pitan osuki desuka? = Do you like pitang?
I guess I'll go clean the entire mansion.
It made me even more lonely.
What?
That's the story, so you jump out of the bushes and scare them a little.
Sure, but what do I get out of this?
Let's see...
How about I sell you to a circus
as a tiger that speaks if you don't do as I say?
Fine! Damn you.
Tama agreed to it.
You can talk with tigers?
Well, yes.
As expected from my butler!
Seriously!
Man, Hayate can be really cruel when he has such a cute face.
Seriously...
That's when Tama noticed a fearful killing intent.
Wh-What is this presence?
I'm told that animals can instinctively tell when something stronger than them is near, but...
My instincts still haven't forgotten that?
Th-This beastly presence...
I can't move.
I'm sorry I made you come to a marriage meeting and had you listen to my personal issues.
It's fine.
She's selfish and whimsical, and I often get angry at her,
but the more she's like that, the less I'm able to ignore her.
Selfish and whimsical and makes me angry?
To tell you the truth...
I also have a person I can't leave alone, as well.
I'm jealous.
I'm jealous of the person you care for so much.
Kaoru-san!
That's fast for Tama.
Now Wataru! Get your ass moving.
Y-Yeah!
Saki!
Are you all right, Saki?!
Sir!
What are you doing here?
Wah... Well... "What"?
Forget that, we need to get out of here!
But we can't leave Kaoru-san behind.
Don't worry, I'll go save him.
Good, good. It's turning in a good direction.
Yeah. Being stereotypical isn't bad once in a while.
I was trying to pounce on them, but then I sensed the presence of a really strong beast.
So I felt danger and came back.
What's wrong, Hayate?
Um, that beast we just saw was not Tama, apparently.
Th-Then what's over there?
It could be a real beast.
What?!
Sir! It's dangerous!
You get out of here, Saki.
Sir!
Come out, beast.
And let got of Kaoru-sensei.
Otherwise, I'll have to exterminate you!
Wataru-kun, it's not Tama, but a real beast hiding there.
You idiot!
Sir!
Bo** Conquest!
Saki.
Katsura-sensei!
Y-Yukiji... What are you doing here?
I was here since yesterday for a marriage meeting party, since the drinks were free, but they said "enough" and kicked me out!
I got lost in the woods,
and now I'm hungry and not in a good mood!
Of course she'd get kicked out.
I haven't had nearly enough to drink!
Yeah...
So, we're going to go to Kabuki-chou to drink some more.
And you pay!
H-H-Help me! I want to go home!
Did you come because you were worried about my marriage meeting?
Th-The shop's busy, so let's end this meeting and go home.
Come on.
You're right. I don't think I can get married for a while.
Obviously not, you idiot.
Geez, he's like a little brother that needs a lot of attention.
Yes.
But, does he like Isumi or Saki-san?
For boys, there are many forms of "like".
I don't really get it, but boys can be complicated, too.
Yes.
By the way, Hayate. Was your lip reading accurate?
I'm pretty confident about it.
After the rain comes fair weather.
I don't really care about others' happiness.
And next week, we'll fight against suspense.
Ayasaki Hayate, huh?
That boy has quite a bit of potential.
That boy...
With this and that kind of clothes... and with cat ears...
Geez! Kuzuha-sama!
What's so good about him?
Don't be so jealous, Shion.
Wouldn't you want to make Ayasaki cry, as well?
Kuzuha-sama.
So, how long should I wait?
I'll get to you,
Mysterious Dark Butler One.
Defeat Ayasaki Hayate and bring him to us!
Yes, Ma'am.
Please, Kuzuha-sama.
Feel the wrath of the hitmen I send you.
What a peaceful day.
It's my turn!
Wh-What are you?!
My name is Duel Butler.
My turn!
Draw!
Wh-What's this?
Eh? This is...
Fight me, Ayasaki Hayate!
I don't really get it, but here I come!
My turn! Draw!
Magic card!
Summoning the White Hair Demon, Klaus and attack!
They'll come back even if you crush them.
The toughness is the fearsome part of my deck.
Activate Shield Trigger!
I won't let you!
Another draw!
I'll end it with the rare card, Ayasaki Hayate!
Let's do this, partner.
Yes, my other me.
I died in single turn?!
What?
Damn you! You better remember this!
What was this about?
"This week's"?
You mean this will continue?
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
You summoned me so here I am, Sanzenin Nagi.
And Ayasaki Hayate's here.
And I'm Maria.
What? What are you doing here, Maria-san?
When the story takes place outside of the mansion,
I do not receive enough screentime, so they put me here today.
I see, it's that serious a matter.
But the majority of people watching this show want to see me, so I'm sure there's no big problem about that.
What? You think so?
I want to see more Maria-san in the show.
Oh my, Hayate-kun.
See you again.
Boo.
She's dead!
But I have already narrowed down who the culprit is.
What?
Will always come to the absolute truth.
Appears to be a tsundere and has the brain of a NEET.
Her name is Detective Nagi!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
The Pretty Lady Detective has Witnessed.
The Female Teacher Murder Case at a Hot Spring.
There will be plenty of service shots.
Please enjoy it with your entire family.
Did you know? At a high rate, it's the third or fifth person in the cast that's the criminal.