Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
'Kay!
Everyone, have a seat!
Happy New Year.
The year just flew by, didn't it?
Let's have another good'un.
'Course,
I'll be biddin' farewell to some of y'all in three more months.
Guess who I'm talkin' about.
Teacher!
You don't mean me, right!?
Savory Day
I can believe, right!?
People always talk about the New Year's mood...
...but I guess there's kind of a weird atmosphere.
But it changes the second school starts.
Unfortunately...
Well...
It's true that New Year's wields a mysterious power.
Despite the fact that I spent the first three days of the year busy working at home...
...I gained weight!
New Year's magic, huh?
The cold weather makes it difficult to burn off your fat.
I did a lot of moving around, though.
Three days of busy work as a shrine maiden.
But you ate just as much, didn't you?
Shrine maiden. New Year's food!
Shrine maiden. Zoni soup!
Shrine maiden. Snacks!
Snacks! Snacks! Snacks!
Something like that.
But the pictures of having fun during New Year's...
...usually include badminton...
...One Hundred Poets...
...and kite flying...
...but I've never actually seen someone do those.
Well...
These days, it's dangerous with stuff like electric lines and cars.
I just watched TV and read books.
After those first three busy days.
Um...
I did those.
I enjoyed badminton, One Hundred Poets, and Pin the Tail on the Donkey.
Doesn't match your image.
My family follows western customs,
but our relatives in the country are more traditional.
We wore kimonos and went to the temple on New Year's...
...and I had fun with my cousins.
An omnipotent god...
Way more Japanese than I am!
More traditional than my family!
Wait, why Pin the Tail on the Donkey?
In One Hundred Poets...
...they're all 31 syllable poems, right?
Yes.
You read out the first verse...
...and look for the card with the rest of the poem.
You must have skills...
Not at all.
I'm just a beginner.
The experts snatch up the cards in a flash.
Well, more like...
I can't stand playing a game that makes you feel like you're studying.
People like you who view mental games as a chore are why Japan's going down the drain.
Why couldn't they use One Hundred Poets for like a card battle?
You could summon a monk.
Think there was a Semimaru!
Semimaru uses a shining attack!
Ono no Komachi uses a lovely strike!
Doesn't that sound fun?
Back to your world, huh?
But wouldn't more physical games have helped you lose weight?
Be quiet!
It was those stupid rice cakes...
Rice cakes are loaded with calories, aren't they?
One as big as a matchbox...
...is equivalent to a whole bowl of rice.
Which means that Kagami's eating a bowl of rice with each bite!?
Hey!
You also ate rice cakes, didn't you!?
[zoni soup: a broth eaten with rice cakes; New Year's meal]
My mom's gone, so I've rarely had zoni soup and that stuff.
Actually, I don't really eat rice cakes.
That's a waste.
With zoni soup, sweet red bean soup, soy flour rice cakes...
There are so many fun ways to eat them.
Looks like she's gonna lose to the rice cakes again next year...
...Kagami.
What do you have to eat for New Year's...
...instead of rice cakes, Izumi-san?
Stuff like pizza and pasta.
Our year starts with raw pasta.
My dad cleans out the pasta machine at the end of every year.
Did you know?
That thing rusts if you don't use it for a while.
If you use it without cleaning it first,
the pasta ends up all black and stuff...
So we clean it out...
...and make pasta and pizza!
Sounds very thorough.
Well, Kagami's house probably orders pizza and their pasta consists of cup noodles.
More like...
We don't have pizza or pasta on New Year's...
No way!
It doesn't go with traditional foods.
Sure it does!
It goes great with roast chicken!
That's a traditional New Year's food?
Sure it is.
Under western traditions.
That's how it works?
What did you have for New Year's, Miyuki-san?
Me?
Your family sounds all wealthy and western,
so you probably didn't have traditional stuff or rice cakes.
Maybe you had a full course French dinner!
Not at all.
I ate traditional foods...
...and I was unable to bite through a rice cake...
...and it stretched like whee!
What's with this walking pillar to elements of moe?
Rice cake goes whee!
But New Year's goes by so fast.
Yeah.
Winter break goes by fast, too.
It's supposed to be a long vacation,
but after cleaning, writing New Year's cards, and homework,
you don't have much time to relax, right?
Hold it right there!
You didn't do New Year's cards this year!
And you copied my homework yesterday!
Uguu~
Oh, yeah.
Did you have your first dream of the year, Kona-chan?
Isn't it supposed to be a good omen if you dream about certain things?
Yep, yep.
Usually, it's one: Mt. Fuji, two: hawk, three: eggplant.
Officially, you would add...
...four: fan, five: tobacco, six: blind man.
It goes all the way up to six!
But you know...
Who ever dreams about that kind of stuff?
What kind of dream would that be?
And why a blind man?
Pretty much...
Hey.
Do you have to dream about all of those at once?
If all of those showed up in your dreams, you'd be really blessed...
...but I believe that just one will suffice.
I thought you would have to dream about a hawk twice and an eggplant three times.
And quite frankly...
Who really remembers what they dream about?
People who care about that stuff are having way too much fun with New Year's.
You have a point.
In my first dream this year...
...I opened my shoe locker to find my shoes missing.
So I had no choice but to take shoes from someone else's open locker...
...but the size was wrong.
I looked up the meaning of this dream in the encyclopedia for dream fortune telling...
...and it said that it's a sign I am pursuing skills useful to society...
...but it will take a while before I accomplish that goal.
The shoes apparently represent societal standing.
Cheesecake?
Miyuki-san's...
...pretty ambitious.
It's like I kinda understand, but kinda not...
Another person was goofing off on the stage...
...during the coming-of-age ceremony.
Don't they realize they're representing Japan?
Makes you wonder why they even bother going.
No kidding.
I wouldn't want to go to a boring coming-of-age ceremony.
And this girl's gonna grow up to be a bad person.
What are you guys going to wear to your ceremony?
Might as well go with a long-sleeve kimono...
What about you?
Well...
My dad's probably going to have me wear a long-sleeve kimono.
I can see him doing that.
Yahoo!
But...
When you wear one...
...you'd look more like a little kid going to the festival.
Happy New Year!
Hope ya had fun!
Happy New Year, Yui-neesan.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Well, my husband was here.
And a lot happens during New Year's.
Oh, and my sister had a fever.
She's got a weak body.
Whoa!
It definitely wasn't because I didn't give her any New Year's allowance!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Only a cop would reveal what she was really thinking before I've said a thing.
A One Hundred Poets tournament is currently under way...
...and it's been one crazy ride so far.
Oh, yeah.
What did you do on New Year's when you were a kid?
When I was a kid?
Well, I did all kinds of stuff...
Let's see...
Um...
Dot.
Sorry.
I forgot.
No clue.
She really just goes with the flow.
I've never heard her say anything serious.
Guess I outgrew my memories!
Tsukasa's always cooped up under the kotatsu these days.
'Cause it's cold.
I know what you mean!
Kotatsu are so wonderful.
Going to the bathroom's a pain, though.
Yep, yep.
But you shouldn't say that so loudly...
But we have a sure-fire way to get a person out of a kotatsu.
How does it work?
Konata?
If you stay under the kotatsu too long,
you'll get stuck.
So your dad doesn't need a kotatsu.
He likes them as much as the next person.
It's just like a warning.
'Cause we've both fallen asleep together under the kotatsu before.
I know what you mean!
But they say that you'll catch a cold if you fall asleep under a kotatsu.
Yeah.
So we turn it off once someone notices.
It's like a mix of heaven and hell.
Like right before you turn it on...
..and after you turn it off, it feels even colder.
I totally know what you mean!
And doesn't it really suck when you get out of bed in the morning?
While we're at it, it's totally freezing after you get undressed and before you get in the bath.
But not enough to make you run.
You might slip and fall.
And doesn't it suck when you need to go to the bathroom in the middle of the night?
I hate that!
Hey.
This is our stop.
And the trip from the bus to the classroom is also hell.
It's almost Valentine's Day.
It always gets a lot more exciting this time of year.
It kinda tickles me how everyone can get so worked up every year.
Having someone special on this day...
...and confessing your feelings...
...and having them reciprocated...
...is a beautiful thing.
You're such a girl.
I just see it as a conspiracy by the chocolate industry.
Well, I guess you could say it's also a special time of year for me.
They have a sale on the unsold chocolate afterwards...
...so I'm looking for chocolate to use in making my own.
And you, you have no dreams.
Money can't buy love!
At least, that's what they like to say...
...but isn't Valentine chocolate a way of showing love through money?
I guess someone who's only experienced love in games has some harsh views.
Well, in games, it's all about upping your relationship level before the day comes.
I don't do anything special for Valentine's.
Guys dream too much.
Nobody managed to trigger the Kagami flag.
What about you?
I'm super popular!
Right...
In your game.
When you talk about flags and relationship levels,
I seriously get worried about your future.
You can't limit yourself to events in games.
I can't stand those narrow-minded people who don't know what they're talking about.
So I'm wrong?
Lately, events only take a few hours in game time...
...so Valentine's Day is usually over in a flash.
So what?
But this year, I'm planning on giving chocolate to someone.
Seriously!?
Someone playing the same online game as me.
A friend from your game?
You're giving it to him in person?
I'm not actually going to meet the person.
It'll be in-game.
Since the characters are still human.
Does that even count?
So you just meant a game character.
How dare you insult my bride!
Bride?
We're married in-game, and my character's male.
What?
Wait a sec.
So the guy is giving the girl chocolate?
And wouldn't it be like a girl giving a girl chocolate?
If the other person's a girl...
Don't worry.
The other person's a guy in real life.
Guess it doesn't matter as long as you're having fun!
Got that right.
I wanna go overseas.
That came out of nowhere.
Well, yesterday, Miyuki-san was, like,
"Females giving chocolates on February 14th is a Japanese custom."
Miyuki-san!
In western society, people of both genders...
...give chocolate and cards to friends and people they like.
That's what she said...
...so a girl like me could still get lots of chocolate!
I guess you could interpret it that way...
...but you sure have a lot of confidence in yourself.
Like you already know for a fact that you'll be popular.
Don't worry.
In foreign countries, little girls...
Okay, stop!
No risqué statements allowed!
Uh...
Will you accept this!?
Happy Valentine's Day!
Here, Kona-chan.
Incredible wrapping...
...for a uniform...
And the inside's all cool and heart-shaped!
I put some effort into it.
Tsukasa's always enthusiastic about this kind of stuff.
She was making them until morning.
And it's only friendship chocolate.
Tsukasa.
You shouldn't give any friendship chocolate to guys.
They'll definitely get the wrong idea.
What?
Anyway, here.
Kagami's giving me chocolate!
Tsukasa was making hers...
...so I just joined in.
You don't want it?
Kagami's looking like she's good at everything when she actually sucks, so when she secretly works hard, it turns me on.
Zip it!
Shut up and put it away.
Huh?
Kagami?
Here.
This is for you.
Just so you know, it's just a friends thing.
Friendship chocolate.
S-Sorry the shape's funny.
Silly.
The shape isn't important.
What matters is that you made it for me.
S-Stupid.
I told you it's not like that.
Nothing like that?
No.
Just shut up and put it away.
This is my first time.
The first time's most important.
So did you give anybody chocolate, Miyuki-san?
I gave chocolate to my father and a relative.
I gave chocolate to everybody I'm friendly with.
I gave chocolate to you, Tsukasa, and Miyuki.
Sheesh.
You guys sure had a boring St. Valentine's Day.
Don't need to hear it from someone who lives in an online game.
Oh, yeah.
Your cousin was accepted to Ryouou, right?
She was.
It's pretty far from her home...
...so she'll be living with us starting next month.
She's always been like a little sister, anyway...
...so we've been in touch.
Really.
But next to you...
...nobody would be able to tell who's younger.
No, like I said...
She's like a little sister in more ways than one.
She's that small!?
But if she got accepted to our school...
...your cousin must be really smart.
That just sounds like you're being really presumptuous.
Since you're a student here.
But I barely passed the exam.
Exams, huh?
We'll be taking our exams next year.
Guess I'll be spending the whole year studying.
Sounds awful.
Exams...
Should I even take them?
I haven't even picked a major.
You seriously need to start thinking about your future.
Studying, manual labor, and me just don't mix.
What kind of future do you have in mind?
I design games. 'Cause it's my hobby.
Use a hobby to make a profit and make games...
Be a self-proclaimed manga artist who can only sell at Comiket...
Megas smoked cheese-nyoro.
Or perhaps, indulge your curiosity and become a professional writer.
There can only be one truth!
And this isn't it!
No, maybe just a novelist who aims for a niche market.
Since you like computers, I guess art design might work.
Maybe a scenario writer who uses random material instead of an actual story writer.
Or she doesn't go to college...
Or they're all the same thing!?
What?
What is it?
Manager!
Legendary Girl A...
...has returned!
What!?
She shook us off last time!
Manager!
Today!
We will absolutely make sure she reaches the goal known as our register!
Giro.
She seems to be at a loss.
Then allow us to...
...help her find her way!
Okay, everyone!
Let 'er rip!
Okay!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Aw yeah!
Manager.
Attempting to determine Legendary Girl A's objective for the day.
Okay.
Countin' on you.
What's the newest comic out?
Yes.
Volume 14 of Sgt. Frog, sah!
Okay!
Raise the height of our goods to the appropriate level...
...to bring them to the attention of Legendary Girl A!
Okay!
And deploy the flyers!
Tama!
Deployment complete!
Sah!
Okay.
Keep an eye on her movements.
And as Legendary Girl A approaches the register...
...deploy our best-selling goods!
Roger!
Sah!
Okay.
Manager!
Legendary Girl A's objective isn't the comics section!
What!?
Manager.
Switch target to the DVD section.
Okay.
Just to be sure...
...block all side paths so Legendary Girl A...
...heads straight to the new DVD section!
Roger!
Sah!
So sorry!
Tama! Tama!
Oh, my!
Forgive me!
Gero-gero-gero-gero build-up!
Tama-tama-tama-tam build-up!
New
Okay, okay...
Manager!
She's...
...picked up the item!
I've finally become a winner today!
Comrades!
Let us have a wild celebration tonight!
Yes!
Sah!
It was a feint!
culously Cheap!!
I'll have to bring out my trump card!
Come...
Bring that bargain, super-rare, out-of-print DVD to me.
Manager.
She is heading for the register.
Okay.
Keep going!
What a beautiful scene!
The crowd inside me is cheering with applause right now!
We did it!
Sah!
Your total comes to 1,785 yen.
I'm short 3 yen.
Sorry.
Please put that back.
We'll be back!
Good lucky!
Okay!
Let's kick this into gear!
We're already on the thirteenth episode of Lucky Channel!
Okay.
As you already know, I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And...
Yes.
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
D-D-Drill!
D-Drill!
It's a pleasure!
That's right.
D-Drill!
We're on episode 13.
Into the second season.
D-Drill!
It's like we've reached the fifth station on Mt. Fuji, right?
Mt. Fuji?
You can drive up to the fifth station.
That's true...
That's right!
I've climbed Mt. Takao before!
Don't you have something else to talk about?
D-Drill!
That's true...
Mah, uh...
Akira-sama's twin drills look wonderful!
What's so wonderful about them?
The way they go round and round like a shell.
Well...
Uh...
We have a special announcement today.
The results for the Lucky Star figure poll!
Let's have Akira-sama announce the results!
The characters that will soon be getting figures are Izumi Konata...
Akira-sama, do a proper job!
Congratulations!
Sheesh, everybody knew this would happen.
What a joke.
No, no, no...
Just means that the higher-ups think the actual show is more important than this corner.
Of course not, right?
Look.
The producers agree.
Yeah.
I'll just fall for your little trick.
I'm already used to being backstabbed.
Little trick?
That's an awful thing to say.
And don't tell me that it says you're going to have a figure made.
Of course not!
Okay.
We'll be making a figure of Izumi Konata-san this time.
And the popular Shiraishi Minoru will also get a figure!?
The hell is this!?
U-Uh...
It's time to say goodbye!
So please send us any suggestions or comments you have!
You can leave them on our home page.
Right, Akira-sama?
Er, what?
I'm leaving.
W-Wait!
B-Bye-bee!
Akira-sama!
Wait up!
Okay.
All the staff members can go home.
D-Drill!
Clap for no reason
wa-wa-wa-wasure mono
F-F-F-Forgot something.
ore no
Forgot...
ore no wasure mono
Forgot my something.
ano hi ano toki okizari ni shita kioku no kakera
That fragment of memory I left behind on that day.
keichimattano sa
It's disappeared.
ano ko to tomo ni
Along with that girl.
akai yuuhi ga yake ni mabushii
The red sunset was so brilliant.
He's annoying
Don't look him in the eyes
koi no jougashima
On Romantic Jougashima.
Couple who readily agreed
to be in the production
baka na yatsu da to waratte okure
Go ahead and laugh at me for being an idiot.
sore ga ore ni wa oniaii sa
That's how it should be.
Unsurpassable Wall
dakedo
But...
Unsurpassable Wall
toki ni wa
Every now and then...
yasashiku daitekure
...give me a gentle embrace.
Shiraishi couldn't have!?
Coward
Next Episode
Well, next time on Sgt. Frog:
No!
You mean, next time on Lucky Star!
Giro-giro.
Comrade, I have a good idea!
Japanese anime is now a global industry.
If we use it to brainwash the people on Pekopon...
...we can complete the invasion of Pekopon in no time, sah!
You're a genius, Sarge!
Worthless.
A solider should act like a soldier and use brute force!
Shut your mouth, you red dharma doll!
In this age, whoever controls information controls the battle!
Well, your prehistoric mind wouldn't understand that.
You better watch yourself!
In any case...
「 Under One Roof 」
Next time:
"Under One Roof."
Look forward to next time!
G-Gero!