Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Okay.
Everyone please be seated.
Happy New Year's.
Last year went by so fast,
but I look forward to taking care of you this year, too.
Of course,
there are some who will only be in my care for another three months.
I wonder who they could be...?
Sensei!
You don't mean me, right?
Savory Day
I can trust you, right?
People usually talk about the New Year's mood,
but I guess there is an unusual atmosphere going around.
And when school starts again, that atmosphere changes.
Unfortunately...
Well...
A mysterious power does seem to be in effect during New Year's.
Despite the fact I spent the first three days of the year working so much at home...
I gained weight!
New Year's magic, huh?
The cold weather makes it harder for your cells to metabolize.
I moved around a lot, though...
Busy for three days with my job as a shrine maiden.
But you ate a lot just to make up for it, didn't you?
Like shrine maiden, New Year's food.
Shrine maiden, zoni soup.
Shrine maiden, snack.
Snacks, snacks, snacks!
Something like that?
But when you picture New Year's, usually things like...
...badminton,
One Hundred Poets,
or Kite Flying...
...come to mind first,
but I've never actually seen people doing them.
Well,
nowadays, those things are dangerous because of stuff like electric lines and traffic.
I watched TV or read books myself.
Except for those first three days I was busy with work.
Um...
I did those.
I enjoyed Badminton, Hyakunin Isshu and "fuku warai".
Whoa, that doesn't fir your image.
Indeed, our family is rather Western...
...but our relatives in the country are more traditional.
We even wore kimonos and went to the first temple visit of the year.
And I played with my cousins.
Chihayaburu / Kamiyo mo kikazu...
She's more Japanese than I am!
More Japanese than my family!
But what does she mean by "Pin the Tail on the Donkey"?
The Hyakunin Isshu is composed of thirty-one syllable poems, right?
Yes.
You read the first verse...
...and then race to find the card with the rest of the poem.
You must have some skill...
Oh no, I'm no good at all!
The really good people can find the right cards in an instant!
Well, it's more, like,
I can't stand a game that makes you feel like you're in literature class.
It's thoughts from people like you that emasculate educational games, contributing to the decline of Japan.
Why couldn't you like Hyakunin Isshu more like a card battle?
You know, summon a poet and all that.
Someone like... Semimaru, was it?
Semimaru uses "Shining Attack"!
Ono no Komachi uses "Lovely Attack"!
Doesn't that sound interesting?
You always go off in that direction...
Perhaps you would have lost a little weight if you had played more physical games, Kagami.
Shut up!
It must have been the mochi...
Mochi certainly is high in calories.
I hear one ball the size of a matchbox...
...is equivalent to a bowl of rice.
So you mean Kagami is eating as many calories as a bowl of rice with every bite!?
Hey, you ate mochi, too, didn't you?
I don't have a mom, so we hardly eat zoni soup and stuff like that.
Rather, I don't really eat mochi anyway.
Whoa, what a waste!
With zoni soup, sweet red bean soup, soy flour mochi,
there are so many ways to enjoy them.
Looks like you're on your way to losing to the mochi again next year, Kagami.
What do you have for New Year's then, instead of mochi, Izumi-san?
Eh?
Stuff like pizza and pasta.
Our year begins with raw pasta.
My dad brings out the pasta machine at the end of each year.
Did you know?
Those things rust if you don't use them for a while.
If you use it without cleaning it first,
your pasta comes out all dark and such.
So clean it out,
and make pizza dough and pasta in it!
That sounds so authentic.
Though I bet at Kagami's house the pizza comes delivered and the pasta consists of dried noodles.
More like...
Who eats pasta and pizza for New Year's, anyway?
No way!
It doesn't go with the traditional foods.
Sure it does!
It goes perfectly with roast chicken!
Is that a traditional New Year's food?
S-Sure it is.
Perhaps under Western traditions.
Eh, is that how it is?
What did you have for New Year's, Miyuki-san?
Me?
I have the image of a wealthy, Western-style house,
so you probably didn't have traditional New Year's food or mochi.
Perhaps you had a full course of French dishes?
Not at all.
I ate traditional foods,
and I had a hard time biting through the mochi.
So I stretched it as far as it goes.
What's with this walking pillar of moé!?
Mochi *uno~n* stretch!
But New Year's goes by so fast.
True.
Winter break goes by fast, too.
Even though it's supposed to be a long vacation...
...between cleaning, writing New Year's cards, and doing homework...
There isn't much time to relax, is there?
Wait a sec!
I didn't receive a New Year's card this year!
And you copied my homework last night!
Uguu~
Speaking of which,
have you had your first dream of the year yet, Kona-chan?
Oh, the one that's supposed to be a good omen if you dream about certain things?
Yep, yep.
Usually it's first: Mt. Fuji; second: a falcon; and third: an eggplant.
Officially, you could also add four: a fan; five: tobacco; and six: a blind man.
Really?
There are six.
But you see...
What kind of dream would have all of that stuff in it?
Who ever dreams about that kind of stuff?
And why a blind man?
Pretty much...
Hey, do you have to see them all at once?
If you dreamt about all of them at once you would probably be very blessed,
but I believe just one would suffice.
I thought you had to see two falcons and three eggplants.
But honestly,
most of the time you don't even remember your dreams the night before.
People who actually care about that stuff would probably be out enjoying New Year's.
Indeed.
My first dream this year was...
...opening my shoe locker to find out that my shoes were missing.
So I tried to go home wearing a pair of shoes that were in someone else's locker...
...but the size didn't fit.
I tried to look up its meaning in a Dream Fortune Telling Dictionary,
and it said that I was becoming more socially knowledgeable and active,
but that it will take time.
The shoes apparently represent social status.
Cheesecake?
Miyuki-san...
You're pretty ambitious.
I kind of understand, but then I kind of don't...
It seems there was another ruckus at the stage...
...during the coming-of-age ceremony.
Don't they understand they are now representing the face of Japan?
Makes you wonder why they bother to go all the way up on stage to go crazy?
Seriously!
I wouldn't want to go to something as boring as the coming-of-age ceremony.
And you're going to become a bad adult in your own way.
What are you guys going to wear to your ceremony?
Since it's a once-in-a-lifetime chance, I'll probably wear a long-sleeved kimono.
Speaking of which, what about you?
Probably a long-sleeved kimono, per my dad's request.
He would do something like that...
But...
If you wear one,
it'd seem more like a kid's Shichi-Go-San festival than a coming-of-age ceremony.
Happy New Year!
Good times this year as well!
Happy New Year, Yui-neesan.
It's been a while.
Well, I had to take care of my husband, and a lot of things happen at New Year's.
Oh and, my little sister had a fever.
She has a weak body, huh?
Whoa!
I'm definitely not trying to avoid giving you a New Year's gift!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Only a policewoman would give the answers before the questions are even asked...
"A Hyakunin Isshu competition is currently underway...
...and it's been a crazy battle thus far."
Speaking of which,
when you were little,
what did you do for New Year's, Yui-neesan?
Hm?
When I was little?
Let's see...
I did all kinds of stuff but...
Um...
Dot dot dot dot...
I forgot.
Can't remember a thing.
Nee-san, you really just live life as it comes...
I don't think I've ever heard her say anything serious.
I guess I've left my memories in the fast lane, too!
Tsukasa's been living under the kotatsu these days.
Because it's so cold.
I know what you mean.
Kotatsu are so nice!
When you're in a kotatsu you don't even want to get up to use the bathroom.
Yep, yep.
But maybe you shouldn't say it so loudly...
But we have a surefire way to get someone out of kotatsu.
Eh?
How so?
Konata.
If you stay in the kotatsu too much, you'll get stuck.
Your dad doesn't need a kotatsu?
He enjoys it, but maybe he's doing it as a warning.
Because we've both fallen asleep under the kotatsu before.
Yep, I know what you mean!
But I heard you can catch a cold from sleeping under the kotatsu.
Yep, yep.
So we try to turn it off when we realize it.
It's like combining heaven and hell together.
Eh?
A kotatsu that isn't turned on seems even colder than not having one at all.
Yep, I totally understand!
And isn't it hard getting out of the futon in the morning?
Yep.
And when you go from the shower to the bathtub, it's totally freezing.
But not enough to make you want to run on the tile.
Because you might slip and fall.
And what about when you need to use the bathroom in the middle of the night?
Yeah, I hear you!
Hey, we're getting off now!
Getting off the bus and walking to class is hell, too...
Yep.
It's almost Valentine's Day.
You can really feel the love in the air during this season.
Every single year...
Everyone tries to act normally, but you can feel the tension in the air,
it makes things so awkward.
On a day like that, having someone special...
...and confessing to them,
then having those feelings reciprocated...
...is a beautiful thing.
Tsukasa, you're such a maiden.
Though personally I'd say it was a conspiracy by the chocolate industry to sell candy.
Well, I guess it's a special time of year for me, too.
Eh!?
Every year they discount all the unsold chocolate afterward...
So I go after the chocolate powder to use in making my own.
As for you, you simply don't have any dreams.
"Money can't buy love!"
Or so they say,
but aren't Valentine chocolates a form of expressing your love through money?
This coming from a person who's only experienced romance within games.
Well, in games, it all depends on how much you can raise their affection level before the day comes.
Nothing really changes for me, even though it's Valentine's...
The guys dream too much.
I guess no one managed to raise the Kagami flags.
What about you!
But I'm so popular!
Sure, sure...
Inside your game, right?
I seriously worry about your future at times...
...when all you talk about are flags and affection levels.
How can you live by game events?
Geez, I can't stand people who criticize without even knowing what they're talking about.
Oh, am I wrong?
Lately, a lot of games take place over a really short period of time...
...so they don't even touch Valentine's Day.
So what?
But I do plan on giving chocolates to someone this year.
Eh?
Seriously!?
A person who plays the same online game as me.
Eh!
A friend from your game?
Yeah.
Don't tell me that you're handing it to him in person!?
Nah, I'm not actually going to see the person.
You give them chocolates through your characters in-game.
Since there is a human playing each character.
Does that even count?
So you meant just the game character.
How dare you insult my bride!
Eh?
Bride?
Yep.
We're married in the game, and I'm the male character.
Eh~?
Wait a second.
So they guy is giving chocolate to the girl?
Or more like, a girl is giving chocolate to a girl?
If the other person is a girl...
Don't worry, the other character is really a guy.
Huh!
Huh?
Well, whatever floats your boat!
That's right!
I want to go overseas.
That came out of nowhere.
No, yesterday Miyuki-san was saying,
"It's unique to Japan that only girls give chocolates on February 14th."
"In Western societies, people of both genders exchange gifts,
giving chocolate and cards to people they like."
Really~
Is what she said...
So a girl like me should be able to get lots of chocolate, right?
I suppose,
but putting simplicity aside, where is this confidence coming from?
It's like you already assume you're going to be popular.
Don't worry about it.
Foreigners really like little gir-
Okay, stop!
No dangerous comments allowed!
Umm...
Here you go!
Happy Valentine's Day, Kona-chan!
Here you go.
What incredible wrapping...
For a uniform.
And the inside is all amazing and heart-shaped!
I put some effort into it.
Tsukasa really puts a lot of time into this kind of stuff.
She was up all night making one after the other,
even though they're just obligation chocolates.
Tsukasa.
Don't give any to the boys.
Even if it's just obligation chocolate.
They'll take it the wrong way.
Eh?
What?
Anyway, here.
Kagami is giving me... chocolate!?
Tsukasa was making some,
so I thought I might as well.
You don't want it?
The fact that you seem skilled in every field,
yet actually so awful that you work hard behind the scenes...
...makes you so moé, Kagami.
Just shut up and put it away!
Huh?
Kagami?
Here.
This is for you.
Let me tell you, it's just an obligation, okay?
Obligation chocolate.
A-And sorry if they're shaped funny.
You're so silly.
The fact that you made them for me,
is more important than its shape.
I-Idiot.
It's not like that.
Nothing like that?
There isn't.
Just shut up and put that away.
This is my first time doing something like this.
The first time is the most important.
So Miyuki-san, did you give chocolates to anyone?
I gave it to my dad and my relatives.
I gave it to everyone I'm friends with.
I gave one to you, Tsukasa, and Miyuki.
What's this?
All you guys sure had a boring St. Valentine's Day.
You shouldn't be talking, denizen of the gaming world.
Speaking of which,
your cousin was accepted to Ryouou, right?
Yep, she was.
It's a long commute from her place,
so she's moving in with us starting next month.
She's always been like a little sister to me, so we get along really well.
Really?
But next to you, we wouldn't be able to tell who's the little sister.
No, like I said,
she's like a little sister in more ways than one.
She's that small!?
But if she got accepted into this school with ease, she must be pretty smart.
Depending on how you take that, you sound presumptuous.
You're a student too, right?
But I know I barely made the cutoff.
Exams, huh?
We have our exams next year, too.
I guess I'll be studying all year...
That sounds awful.
Exams...
I wonder if I have to study.
I haven't even thought about my future.
You should seriously start thinking about your future.
The words "study" and "manual labor" don't exist in my dictionary.
What's going to happen if you keep on going like this?
She'll become a game creator for work as well as a hobby.
Actually I design games because it's my hobby.
Or a manga artist who can only make a buck at Comiket...
Megas smoked cheese nyoro~n!
Or perhaps she'll indulge a curiosity and become a professional writer.
There can only be one truth!
No, maybe just an author that focuses on a niche market.
Nowadays, light novels are the thing to do!
She's really good with computers, so maybe a web designer?
This is the only thing I won't give up!
Or maybe a scenario writer for scripts that pull more gags than actual story writing.
And that's another one down!
Don't tell me... college?
They're all the same thing!
What?
What is it?
Boss...
That Legendary Girl A...
Has returned!
What!?
Last time she slipped right through our fingers...
Boss!
Today...
We'll make sure the Legendary Girl A reaches the goal known as our register!
Giro...
It seems she's troubled.
Then let us help her...
...find her way!
Okay everyone, let's put all our effort into this!
Oh!
Let's go!
Oh aww yeah!
Boss, I'm investigating Legendary Girl A's target item for the day.
All right, I leave it up to you.
What's the newest manga release?
Volume 14 of Kerero Gunsou, sir!
All right!
Correspond the display height of the goods to Legendary Girl A's level!
Bring them to her attention!
Roger!
On top of that, deploy the flyers!
Tama!
Deployment complete!
Sir!
All right, let us observe for a while.
On top of that, deploy some of our best-selling goods...
...between here and the register.
Roger!
Sir!
Okay.
Boss!
Legendary Girl A's target isn't the comics section!
What!?
Boss.
Target has switched aim to the DVD section.
All right.
Just to make sure this goes according to plan...
Block off all side routes so that...
...Legendary Girl A goes straight for the new releases section!
Roger!
Sir!
Oh, I'm so sorry...
Tama... Tama...
Oh my...
Forgive me!
Gero, gero, gero build-up!
Tama, tama, tama build-up!
New
Good, good...
Oh!
Boss!
She's finally...
Picked up an item!
Finally, on this day...
...I have become a victor!
Comrades, let us celebrate tonight!
Okay!
I will!
It was a feint!
culously Cheap!!
Now it's time for my trump card!
Now,
bring that rare, bargain, out-of-print DVD to me.
Boss...
She's moving towards the register.
Good, keep moving...
What a moving scene!
Right now I am filled with joy!
We did it!
Indeed.
1,785 yen, please.
I'm short 3 yen.
I'm sorry.
Can you put that back for me?
We'll be back!
Lucky Star
Lucky Channel
Oha-lucky!
We're coming at you full of energy today!
It's been quick, but we're already on the 13th episode of Lucky Channel!
As you already know, I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
And...
Yes, I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
D-D-Drill!
Thank you very much.
That's right, it's already the 13th episode...
D-D-D-D-Drill!
We're entering the second season now.
D-D-Drill!
How do I say this...
It's like we reached the fifth station at Mt. Fuji.
D-D-Drill!
D-D-D-D-Drill!
Right, Akira-sama?
What's that?
Mt. Fuji?
You can go up to Station 5 by car.
W-Well that's true, but...
Oh, yeah!
I've climbed Mt. Takao before!
What?
Don't you have other things to talk about?
Right...
Um, right.
Akira-sama, your twin drills look wonderful!
What's so wonderful about them?
Like how they go round and round like a shell.
Well...
Oh, right.
Today we have a special announcement.
The Lucky Star figurine poll results!
Now Akira-sama, please take it away!
The person turning into a figurine is Izumi Konata-san...
Akira-sama, do a proper job!
Congratulations!
This is a joke.
Are they trying to say that the actual series...
...is more important than this corner?
That's not true at all, right?
See?
The producers agree, too!
Fine, whatever.
I'll let you trick me into this again...
...since this isn't the first time I've been betrayed.
T-Trick... that sounds so bad.
Don't tell me you were thinking that you might actually get your own figure.
Oh, not at all!
So this time around,
we're going to make a figure of Izumi Konata-san.
And the popular Shiraishi Minoru will also be getting a figure-
What the hell is this!?
U-Uh...
Ah!
It's already time to say goodbye!
So please, send us any comments or suggestions you have about our show.
We're accepting them on our homepage, too.
Right?
Akira-sama?
I'm going home.
H-Hey!
B-bye-bii!
Akira-sama, please wait!
Okay.
All the staff, pack up.
Drills!
Clap for no reason
wa-wa-wa-wasure mono
F-F-F-Forgot something.
ore no
Forgot...
ore no wasure mono
Forgot my something.
ano hi ano toki okizari ni shita kioku no kakera
That fragment of memory I left behind on that day.
keichimattano sa
It's disappeared.
ano ko to tomo ni
Along with that girl.
akai yuuhi ga yake ni mabushii
The red sunset was so brilliant.
He's annoying
Don't look him in the eyes
koi no jougashima
On Romantic Jougashima.
Couple who readily agreed
to be in the production
baka na yatsu da to waratte okure
Go ahead and laugh at me for being an idiot.
sore ga ore ni wa oniaii sa
That's how it should be.
Unsurpassable Wall
dakedo
But...
Unsurpassable Wall
toki ni wa
Every now and then...
yasashiku daitekure
...give me a gentle embrace.
Shiraishi couldn't have!?
Coward
Next Episode
And next week on Keroro Gunsou is:
No!
It's next week on Lucky Star:
Giro giro.
Comrade, I have a good idea!
Japanese anime is now a global commodity.
If we use it to brainwash the people on Pekopon,
we can complete the invasion of Pekopon in an instant!
You're so smart, Sarge!
Pfft, weaksauce.
If you're a military man, act like a soldier and do it with brute force!
Shut up, you red dharma doll!
Right now, we are moving into an age where those who conquer information conquer their enemy!
Well, your old-fashioned way of thinking would never comprehend this.
Why you...
In any case...
「 Under One Roof 」
Next week: "Under One Roof."
Look forward to it!
G-Gero!