This isn't the first time you're experiencing July 22nd.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
You must've repeated the day many times.
In other words,
you're a time traveler.
Yes.
I see.
But it probably wasn't me who revealed my name to you.
Did you meet my brother?
Next up, we have a report from Kinokawa City.
Let's hear about delicious
Wakayama treats for the summer.
Please tell us all about that—
It's time, Ryuunosuke.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
3rd loop
Tuesday, July 24th
Wake up
Eat breakfast (egg sandwich)
Help at restaurant
with Mio
Lunch service ends
Think in my room about
what to do
Read through a few
of Ms. Nagumo's books
Forbid Mio from going
out alone
Toki comes over to do
Mio's yukata.
Sou and Mio come to my room.
Mio, Sou, and Toki and I go
to the summer festival
I see.
Interesting read.
Enemy
It could even be the plot of my next novel.
It's awfully confusing.
Went right over my head.
This book is proof that you believe me.
Swamp Man is a true story.
The "Swamp Man" in this story is exactly like the shadows,
and the protagonist has the same name as you.
Fourteen years ago, I met a shadow on this island.
It killed my family.
That's the reason why I believe you.
But... Th-That's...
I won't say anything more.
It would reveal who I am.
If I told you and you were copied,
a shadow could learn who I really am.
Shadows go after the family.
Since Hizuru returned to this island, they'll be after her too.
Family.
Is that why Ushio, Mio, and I were targeted?
Wait...
What about Alain?
Don't worry, I already took care of Alain's shadow.
His shadow will no longer be able to return.
It's just like chickenpox. Ya develop an immunity.
If yer shadow is killed,
ya can't ever get shadow sickness again.
S-So if you kill your own shadow, you can't be copied again.
Yeah. That's why I got immunity.
My shadow won't exist.
Ya can trust me.
But Ms. Nagumo, you don't have immunity.
Why'd you risk coming back?
I can't tell you that, either.
But I came to save you, that's for sure.
Although you might not want to trust me too much.
No, I...
What's your plan?
We have 54 hours until everyone is killed at the summer festival.
That four-armed shadow...
It seemed to control all the other shadows.
My step-sister Mio is in danger.
Will you help me defeat Mio's shadow?
Your notes said Mio's shadow will appear at Bistro Kofune at 9 p.m. tonight.
Yes.
Fine.
But I need to handle one thing before that.
The Kobayakawas, right?
You're bound to fail.
What'd ya say?
I saw Shiori's shadow at the shrine on the 24th.
So you're saying that I'll fail to kill Shiori today?
Yes.
So let me come with you.
It's my enemy too.
Even if we fail again, I can find out why.
Okay.
However, I'll be the only one who'll enter the house.
What is she doing?
She's been listening to something.
Hizuru's memories ain't just transferred over.
Huh?
Roger that, Sis.
The famous Arakawa peaches grown here in Momoyama, loved by people all across Japan, are in season now!
Hi, Hizuru!
Hey, did I catch ya... I mean, you at dinner?
I had some gifts from Tokyo to give you.
Oh! Ya shouldn't've!
Let her in.
Come in.
Thank you.
This is my husband Tatsuo and my daughter Shiori.
Hello. Make yourself comfortable.
I hope I'm not interrupting, Asako.
Can I open my luggage here?
Of course!
Hizuru, why don't ya stay fer dinner?
We have so much catching up to do.
I was wondering...
What is it?
Does Ms. Nagumo have a split personality?
No, thank you. I won't be staying long.
The shadow itself is flat, so a body blow won't hurt it.
Mommy?
It's merely the eyes of the body that's looking at me.
If they knew I could kill them,
they'd be cautious and avoid me.
So it's best to kill them both now.
Asako!
I only reeled in one.
Split personality?
Why do ya say that?
She asked if I met her brother.
Doesn't that mean...
Well, ya ain't too far off, but that's not it.
C-Can she really handle this alone?
We wait here.
Ryuunosuke has the power to battle shadows.
Ryuunosuke?
Yeah. Ryuunosuke's a tough one.
Lemme be clear. I don't get yer loop or whatever.
But if ya go inside, it might change
the reason Shiori's shadow escapes.
Ryuunosuke's trying to find the cause of the failure.
Listen up.
She trusts ya.
Ya said she's not dying today.
If that was a lie, I'll never forgive ya.
Yes.
Ms. Nagumo certainly was strong.
So that was Ryuunosuke.
Mr. Nezu, can you tell me about Ryuunosuke?
I guess it wouldn't take much to find out.
Hizuru had a twin brother.
His name was Ryuunosuke.
He was found dead on Mount Takanosu 14 years ago.
I heard Hizuru scream, so I ran over.
It was a hideous sight.
Daddy? Mommy?
This can't be real...
Why?
Why kill them?
He was eaten.
Chunks of his body were bitten off.
People thought it was wild dogs.
Hizuru claimed that it was murder.
Along with those bite wounds, he had strangulation marks.
I missed.
No, I felt contact.
But no one believed Hizuru.
The body was cremated that same day.
Mr. Nezu, that sounds exactly like...
Yeah, ain't it similar?
All this could be related.
There are monsters on this island.
I want to kill every single shadow on this island,
even if it costs me my life.
Can ya say the same, Shinpei?
Yes.
You're dangerous.
Ya know how to kill us.
Is that traitor on your side?
I see ya could follow Mommy and Daddy's movements.
And ya move quicker than shadows.
Are ya really human?
Copy me and create my shadow, and then you ask it.
So smug.
Fine, I'll do that.
After I kill ya.
Ya old hag!
How dare you stab yourself just to hurt me?!
Did I not strike deep enough?
Strange.
That first hammer strike should've been fatal.
Something is different about that shadow.
Sorry, Sis.
I hurt your body.
So it went to the third floor.
It's exactly like Sis said.
Asako and Tatsuo are eliminated. Shiori got away and she's on the third floor.
I'll chase after her, but things may turn out as Shinpei said.
I-It's from her.
Asako and Tatsuo are eliminated. Shiori got away and she's on the third floor.
I'll chase after her, but things may turn out as Shinpei said.
Change to plan B.
Plan B.
Now it's our turn.
Here.
Let's see how serious ya are about this.
Summer Time Rendering
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
South balcony
Bathroom
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Closet
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Bedroom 1
Stairs to 2nd floor
Closet
Bedroom 2 (kids' room)
North balcony
Third floor, went through north window.
Roger.
Third floor, went through north window
Diary
Kobayakawa Shiori
It's useless.
After you release the light to copy me, you can't move for a few seconds.
I guess it takes quite an effort to scan an entire human's worth of information.
Do you think I'll waste those few seconds?
The moment you try to copy me,
I'll kill you.
And this time for sure.
No fun.
Bye-bye.
It's Plan B!
The third shot!
Bring it!
Running away? Get over here!
Damn it!
Shinpei!
No... Stop...
Was... Was it you?!
Get off me, scum.
Did you kill Ushio?!
Ow!
That's enough. Let it go, Shinpei.
It can't move an inch anymore.
One or two ain't gonna be enough.
Ya gotta nail it in three spots.
Then the shadow gets stuck in place.
In other words, ya can capture it.
C-Capture it?
That was your intention from the start?
Yeah.
I-I didn't know!
Well, I didn't tell ya.
I didn't expect ya to be helpful.
The fact that we captured Shiori is huge, though.
It'll change the future.
Once the body is pinned down,
I guess the shadow can't escape.
This is a new discovery, Shinpei.
Thanks to you, we didn't lose it.
If it were just the two of us, we would've failed.
Ya sure got some guts for a youngin'.
Good job.
What's so funny?
This shadow is different from the others.
I chose Plan B to examine it.
Huh? Different?
First, let's get it to answer Shinpei's question.
Did you kill Kofune Ushio and create her shadow?
Oh.
Ushio, huh?
Yep, I killed her.
I strangled her to death.
Ya killed her?
Why?
Why kill Ushio?!
Y'all kill people and take their places!
What do ya want?!
It's the end.
It'll be done after this summer.
We're going home.
Our whole family is going home.
What?
What're ya talking about?
Don't be so afraid.
Ya misunderstand me, Shinpei.
My human self was killed by a shadow, yes,
but the shadow made a perfect copy of my body, mind, and memories.
So I'm Kobayakawa Shiori.
I was just reborn.
Don't lie!
Yer not Shiori!
Ya killed Shiori and her family!
I wish you'd become a shadow soon too.
Come with us.
Become my big brother, will ya?
That's more than enough.
Talking to a shadow for too long can confuse you.
D-Damn it!
It was a tough one.
How'd ya kill Asako and Tatsuo's shadows?
The usual way with one strike using the hammer.
If we strike a blow to a fair percentage of the flat shadow, it's fatal.
We don't have a large enough sample size to prove my sister's theory wrong yet.
It was saying strange things about its family going home.
Copies acting like the same humans?
It said it was reborn.
How is a perfect copy different from the original person?
That was the theme of Swamp Man. Right, Ryuunosuke?
Huh?
What do you think?
I told him about the split personality.
Is that right?
Well then, nice to meet you.
I'm Minakata Ryuunosuke.
I was Minakata Hizuru's brother.
So, are you the author of those novels?
Oh, no.
That's my sister.
I'm not a good writer.
I come out when she's in an interview, or when she has to be social.
You've read her books, haven't you?
Well, actually...
This guy's totally obsessed with her books.
Is that right?
That wasn't in the recordings.
I guess she was too embarr—
Wh-What're you doing?!
Don't get the facts messed up.
I'm not embarrassed, and I'm not hiding anything.
I just leave out unnecessary information!
Ms. Nagumo, your nose is bleeding!
Ya okay?
I'm not okay. You have no vocabulary!
Does letting down her hair bring her back to Hizuru?
Don't let the words and the appearance of shadows affect you, Ajiro Shinpei.
They might appear as a friend or a
family member, but don't hesitate.
Contemplate about the sameness of copies and originals after we're finished with everything.
It was too late for the Kobayakawas.
However, there's still time for you.
Can you really kill Mio's shadow?
We'll wait outside until it's time.
Let's exchange numbers.
Tell me if something unexpected happens.
Act the same as you did before and assess the situation.
You're an observer.
Got it.
I'm home!
Sorry for being late... Mio...
Welcome home, Shin.
N-No way.
What's with this onion?!
It's making me cry so much!
I can't see anything!
What? Are ya cooking?
Ain't it obvious?
I wanted to stir-fry some onions
and chicken I found in the fridge.
Oh, be careful!
This is strange.
Mio never cooked in the past loops.
Why are ya...
Ya didn't look too good in the morning, so I thought I'd make something for ya.
I see. Thanks.
But leave the rest to me.
I don't wanna see ya cut yerself.
Don't worry.
I feel fine.
I-I'll go wash my face!
Thank goodness. Mio isn't a shadow.
And I can still make curry with this.
She can be so cute.
What am I thinking?!
Nothing can change!
Oh, right. The way I acted already changed Mio's behavior tonight.
I'll make curry, and everything will be the same.
Well, Ms. Nagumo and Mr. Nezu are waiting outside, armed and ready, so one thing is different.
Besides killing the shadows,
I need to do exactly the same things.
Any changes will cause the others to change too. It's all connected.
The future I've seen will become useless.
Wow, Mio. That was a loud rumble.
Are ya really that...
hungry?
Yeah.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Memento