Street Number 6
Pandora Maid Service
There is no shame in ignorance,
only innocence.
One will learn eventually.
But until that day, there is no need to know.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
七色の黄昏おりてきて
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
風はなんだか涼しげ
The wind is kinda refreshing
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Saturday night is lively
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
Minna ukiuki
みんなウキウキ
Everyone can't wait
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait.
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
http://FurukawaPan.net
#FurukawaPan@irc.rizon.net
Encoder: Xarda
Edit + QC:
lalala
Xarda
Kayshin
Liasion
Translation: crazybob
Timing: SiegN
Xarda
Typesetting:
[Pandora's Box] From Volume 3 Story 20
Hotori?
How did you know?
You've taken a step back with a hand over your agape mouth.
So detailed!
The Guardian Spirit told me.
Shizuka, when did you get such powers?!
Just kidding.
A mirror.
You were looking through the glass.
Such an elementary trick... but you couldn't see through it.
You couldn't even be my assistant.
I came today to get a present for Tatsun's birthday.
To a second hand goods shop...
Huh?
This scale...
I have the perfect amount of sugar for this coffee.
This could work!
Note: 6500 yen is currently about $78.85.
But it's expensive.
Shizuka, is this good?
What a vague question.
Well, it's certainly...
The ranchu goldfish is the pride of Japan, poko~
So, buying it?
No discount?!
Oh yeah.
Changing the topic...
I visited Africa a few days ago.
Oh. So that's why you're wearing those weird clothes.
It comes out of the walls, poko~
Here. Your souvenir.
Yay! I'm so happy!
What the hell is this?!
Repugnant! Revolting! Repulsive! The three 'R's!
Those three 'R's...
Really just mean the same thing, right?
Somehow...
A wealthy local tried to get me to marry him,
and gave me his family's heirloom mask.
Anyway, with the mask's power
you can find out where you should be.
Ahhh, I don't want it...
Now, now.
Think of it as a matchmaking charm.
Stop it...
I just thought of a present for Tacchan!
It's Tatsun.
It's something romantic.
See ya!
I feel like I've been used to get rid of some trash.
What is that?!
Mice actually hate cheese, poko~
It's two days early, but...
Happy Birthday!
Thanks. I haven't had a birthday party like this since elementary school.
This is a little something from my place.
It's a dish called Fresh Sea Salad.
Thank you! I'll take good care of it!
No, you should eat it right away.
In other words,
this is a Sanada Sakana Salad?
(Fish)
You're rhyming too much.
I didn't think anyone would make that complaint.
Catalog
Other things you've received: A basket of vegetables from the grocery store,
two vouchers for free cleaning from the dry cleaning place,
and various bottled drinks from the 100 yen store.
I bought you a cake.
Be grateful.
Th-Thanks.
And now, with the party in full swing,
here's today's main event!
The party just started.
The main event was Tatsuno's birthday.
You're a terrible host.
D-Don't give up!
Okay!
This is my present for Tatsuno.
Thanks.
A worn box?
There's something inside.
I see!
I'll open this box in two days on my birthday.
Sorry, but that wish can't be fulfilled, Tatsun.
Huh?
There's no key.
When Kameido from the second hand goods shop got it,
the key was lost and the box left unopenable.
It's kinda romantic because you can't open it.
Try pondering about the contents of the box on long Autumn nights?
...and she said it'd be okay if I said that.
Huh? No way, that's creepy.
Josephine Joe Star Jojo. Just wanted to try to say it, poko~
Ah, but isn't it nice?
Let's have a birthday party again sometime.
It's not like anyone comes to this cafe anyway.
Sanada, when's your birthday?
February.
That's so far off! You're useless!
Grandma, when's yours?
April.
Senpai?
Don't worry about me.
Huuh? Why? Don't be shy!
We'll give it our best here at Seaside to celebrate it.
When's yours anyway?
Mine's in May.
Girls born in May are wise!
"Wise" is a bit much.
So, when's your birthday?
Speaking of May...
The topic's changed, you know.
Score. I found your student handbook.
Stop it! It's gonna be really bad if you open it!
Alright. September 8th.
That's today.
You didn't want to say it.
What the hell did you do?
What are you gonna do about this awkwardness?
Do something.
Co-Congrats!
Ha. Ha...
Happy birthday to you...
Right! A present! I'll go to the cheap sweets shop!
I don't need your cheap sympathy!
It'll be taken away if you play too much, poko~
The only thing I have left for a present is a matchmaking charm...
Oh? I'd rather have that,
than this Pandora's Box.
Then, the romantic box goes to Kon,
and the matchmaking thing goes to Tatsun.
Mmm.
Looks like everything will be fine.
You'll have to settle things now before that happens.
Senpai, we'll celebrate your birthday right next year.
I'll remember your birthday,
September 8th, Kon Futaba, Birthday
Hateful September memory, Kon Futaba.
No one could forget this!
Stop screwing with me!
Cup ramen is best cooked 45 seconds less, poko~
— Next Day —
Ah. It opened.
No way! Crazy. You could be a phantom thief...
and then I'd catch you.
But your sidekick would be senile, and not care about catching me.
And now, what's in the box?
A charm?
What? Boring.
This is a matchmaking charm.
That Tatsuno. I think this charm would've been more useful.
It's just an empty box if you open it.
Pandora's Box just turned into an old box.
How is this a matchmaking charm?
I'll just end up married to a wealthy African.
Excuse me!
Ah. You're Hotori's friend, Tacchan, right?
Tatsun. I mean, Tatsuno.
I heard you'll buy old things off me.
Yup. Show me what's in the box.
[Traveling Maid Service] From Volume 2 Story 17
If you upload the assignment it'll end up on the website,
and you'll be able to manage it there so please submit your work.
Hey, does "upload" mean up a road on a hill?
No, jeez.
Can't you just be a little bit helpful?
I'll put in the tags. Can you get materials?
Thanks Suzuki.
I should've been in Suzuki's group!
Why did I pick a jock for a partner...
I'm good at weightlifting and that's about all.
You don't have to try so hard.
Just copy some page and change it a little.
I've finally typed up the title.
Maid Café Seaside
When this webpage goes live, we'll get more customers.
Ahh, nice. Two birds, one stone with the assignment and advertisement.
Arashiyama.
This is the illustration you asked for.
Wow, thanks! It's perfect!
Alright, here's the Tatsun maid pictures I promised.
Marvelous!
If we make a big deal with the illustration..
You're going to get busted for fraud.
You just told me to copy some page before.
Guess I can't be a hypocrite.
Alright, this will be due in two weeks.
I didn't get anywhere today!
Thanks for waiting.
Uhh, the curry was...
Who was it for?
Well, whatever.
Share the curry!
So cruel! You're worse than any normal waitress!
Store
And you just had to write the one word I didn't want to think of while playing hooky.
You're turning out like grandma.
Alright. You're all taking responsibility for that so you're gonna get salad and coffee.
You dumbass! Look what you did!
Don't hurt the maid's feelings!
Hey, Tatsuntsun.
The nicknames are getting worse.
Do you have a computer at your place?
Yeah. My little brother usually plays games on it though.
Let's work on our assignment after this is over.
Ahh,
but today it sounds like Kon stayed home with a fever.
She lives by herself,
so I thought I'd go over and take care of her.
No way. They say idiots don't catch colds.
Bad timing.
Colds? I don't really catch them.
Last time I got sick was... in middle school, I think.
You liar. When you were in middle school
you were bragging about how you were never absent.
So you got the perfect attendance award.
You guys don't catch colds either, eh?
Hey, so is Sanada home right now?
Hiroyuki? He's home.
Good.
And with that said,
Plan B - can I go to Sanada's place to do my homework?
What are you talking about? You're in the middle of work.
It's also advertising for this place!
Well, no one is here anyway. Go ahead.
Yay!
Your customers are right here!
Ah. You're here everyday so I thought you were part of the seats.
Cruel! Grandma is a hundred times more cruel!
She cuts differently.
Her words are sharper than the tip of a knife!
Hold on! You going to Sanada's place?
Because he also has a computer.
You go too.
Hey, wait up!
Huh? Weren't you going to go see Kon?
Let's do that after.
Oh, PC?
Sure. When?
Now?!
We're going to get you something.
How about a potato croquette?
We're at the butcher's after all.
The butcher?
Even if they buy a croquette it'll be only a few minutes before they arrive!
And isn't the potato croquette the cheapest thing?!
Get me a cream puff from "Romando".
What? Guess I have to.
When did you get so fancy?
You're just taking advantage of me.
Good. I bought myself 20 minutes.
Ah! Shit!
There's a ton of porn under the desk!
We're coming in!
Made it.
Ahh!
The computer they're going to use
has my internet porn collection...
What's this folder?
Sanada's a pervert!
It could happen!
So the only option is to delete it all.
It's no contest.
We're here.
Yo.
Sanada, are you tired?
I feel like I've conquered the dark side to become a Jedi.
What are you saying?
Here, your cream puff.
Sanada, sorry for coming so suddenly.
No, it's completely fine.
I want to put this picture on our website's splash screen.
I can't do it - don't have a scanner.
Scanners?
Note: Scanners is a movie. "Scanners" in the movie are people with telekinetic powers.
Didn't you say you wanted to be a Jedi?
Wait, that's not what we were talking about.
A "scanner" is a machine you connect to a computer to scan pictures.
I thought you could do anything with a computer?
You're like an ancient woman from a bygone age.
What a waste of time!
We're going back, four eyes!
Four eyes?
I deleted everything for no reason?
Huh? Isn't that the book I lent you?
Can't believe you stuck it there. I'm taking it back.
Nooo! You can't go there!
Guess you can't polish a turd.
He's the worst! From now on I'm going to call Sanada "perv-yuki."
At this point, guys without any porn
are the creepy ones.
C'mon, let's get to Kon's place and then go home.
"Yo no naka ne, kao ka, okane ka nano yo" is a palindrome, poko~
Huh? Kon Densuke?!
So she was a guy after all!
Guys are dangerous! Guys are pervs!
She's living by herself,
so her dad's name is on the plate.
Wonder if she's sleeping.
It's open.
How careless.
Senpai! We're coming in!
Careless. Careless.
Care...Less less le-less less.
Let's go!
Tatsun's cool!
Quiet! We're in a sick person's room!
But you started it...
Strong fever.
Senpai, you alright?
Her cold is worse than I expected.
Cover her up.
I'm going to make a water pillow.
Ok.
Everyone in Arai Kazutoyo's family looks the same, poko~
She's kinda cute when she's sleeping quietly like this.
It hurts. I'll die, mama.
Mama?
Senpai! You have to sleep!
Now I'll have to kill you.
Calm down!
Yikes!
You were mumbling in your sleep,
but we don't know what you were saying!
Really?
Really!
I see.
Senpai, please go lay down.
Ah, sorry.
I'll be fine if I just sleep through it.
Yeah, yeah.
Hotori has also fallen off her desk, poko~
The fever has gone down a bit from the sweating.
I'll make something to eat so sit still.
What are you making?
Spring onion and egg rice porridge.
Sounds so good.
It's not for you.
Fine then. I'll have the cream puff from before.
H-Huh? Gone?
What are you talking about? You gave it to Sanada.
Crap! So I gave it to perv-yuki for free.
The day both girls discovered the porn magazines was a day to remember.
Today's cream puff is bitter.
There's enough CDs here to open a store.
She really loves music.
A guitar!
But the strings are thick and I think there's not enough strings...
Is this a newbie guitar?
It's a bass.
Every bassist in the world will want to punch you for that.
Ho-ho. So this is a bass.
Huh? Sound's not coming out.
Augh, you're so annoying.
It's because the amp isn't turned on.
The sound comes out of the huge speaker?
Wh-wh-what?
Nothing at all.
Alright, let's go to sleep.
But you flipped the switch!
We're back.
Sorry for being late.
Hey, welcome back.
Yo.
Hold on!
You're still playing hooky from work?
Don't you feel weird being here till it closes?
I left and came back again.
Hiroyuki got really depressed.
Did something happen?
Your perv-yuki is unhealthy, isn't he?
Damn kid! Did he do something to you?
Like I'd let him!
(Cough) Huh?
We're done for today, poko~
Next Morning
Tatsun is staying home today.
I wonder if she caught Kon's cold.
Now that you mention it, my dad wasn't looking too well last night.
The cold's getting around.
I'm also kinda tired all of a sudden so I'll be going home.
Huh?
What's wrong, grandma?
Oh, it's Hotori.
It's been a while since I caught a cold.
It's not a big deal.
I don't want you to catch it so go home.
The cold is quickly spreading.
I'd better watch out.
Idiots don't catch colds.
Huh? Do I have a cold?
I'm way too healthy!
What should I do?!
Hi,
1,
ひ、
Fu,
2,
ふ、
Hi, fu, mi, yo
1, 2, 3, 4
ひ、ふ、み、よ
Taikutsu ya
Living alone is boring,
退屈や
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
My pufferfish cheeks
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
Pulls the town into chaos.
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
I didn't confess to him today.
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
I play the drums to train
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
My body for ping pong.
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
But this band isn't a fake!
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
The members aren't playing rock!
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
We're not trying to lead the song!
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
We're not looking for Nirvana!
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
We're maids! Yea!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
メイド姿で参上！参上！
acho-!
アチョー！
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
They're maids! Yea!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
acha~
アチャ～
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
kanchoooO!
enemaaA!
かんちょぉぉお！
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
Next episode
And then the two eloped to a faraway place no one knew.
Ahh, soaring away from everything is so romantic.
Sounds like he was a delinquent when he was young.
That guy wasn't a delinquent.
When you decide to get away by air, it's called flying away.
Really? Then what would you call getting away by sea?
Swimming away?
Like you'd elope by swimming away.
Street Number 9  [Lover's Midnight Escape]
Next time, Street number 9, "Lover's midnight escape."
We're gonna be lazy all over, poko~