Looking at the moon, I remember...
Looking at the stars, I think back on
the days together with my loved ones.
The sun shines only on the past, and the future is shrouded in mystery.
No matter how often I look into the mirror, all I see is the present.
I will never forget
the golden rice fields,
and the children's gleaming smiles.
Let us dream for now.
Let us dream until the day of our homecoming.
You're such a poet.
That was a lot of words,
but aren't you making that place up?
Or maybe you were dreaming, master.
My beloved little Koto.
You're one of the few who might make it there.
What's this?
Keep it.
It glimmers like nothing else.
It's perfect for you.
Slow down, master.
You've never been a brainiac.
Look who raised me.
Touché, Koto.
The Background and Difficulties of a Certain Family
Chapter One
Past
Our story begins on a beautiful and auspicious spring day.
Distant Past
The monk Myoe fled from the bustle of the city
to study sutras in the hills of Takao.
He had a certain problem.
Flashback
I only drew what they wanted to see.
Life is unfair.
This temple is full of monsters!
The head monk is a beast too!
It's not like he harmed anybody...
Girls
Yeah...
He's half human, half fox through his parents.
Father
Monk
The head monk is a magnificent person.
However...
Occultist
I heard he's in league with occult gods.
Please keep us out of it all.
They're getting pretty freaked out over some moving drawings.
Don't you agree?
It seemed he had no one but his dog for company,
Koto
but someone else kept watch on him from the shadows.
The rabbit which he had drawn.
Koto
He had named the black rabbit Koto.
He had drawn it on a whim as the capital's god.
He kept drawing a fictitious version of the city and its people even after he left voluntarily.
Simply looking at his drawings allowed it to look deep into his heart.
It thought he was quite handsome too.
Something was watching the rabbit in turn.
The buddha on the altar.
The bodhisattva knew full well what the rabbit desired.
I shall let you use my body.
But does your present body not limit you terribly?
I doubt you will ever make progress as it is.
Do you think Myoe will ever know how you feel unless we intervene?
It's Myoe we're talking about.
Thanks for the comment.
Something about Myoe is wonderfully skewed.
I can only see what is to come;
I cannot peer into the past.
The love you bear is the very thing that can save him.
Who are you?
Koto.
What turned you human?
Love!
Love?!
Love?
Love!
Yep!
Hold it!
I don't think I follow.
Don't worry.
I will remain by your side until you understand.
It was love.
Love-rador
Sometimes my love rises
The rabbit was eccentric to say the least,
but as they lived together, affection budded in his heart as well.
to cheer me up
Yakushimaru!
Youngest:
Yakushimaru
In time, their little family grew.
What is it?
This here is all I have
Nothing.
It seemed like a good idea.
I don't think it is.
Neither do I.
Even the rain is beautiful
Now, now! Don't fight!
The droplets dance
Kurama!
like the rain
Eldest:
Kurama
Everything is so much fun here
The baked potato's done.
I'll pass.
Want me to bring it over?
I'll pass!
A world of music
I feel like I've started
Be merciful, Kurama.
to listen to everyone
Yase!
Middle:
Yase
with a smile
Middle:
Yase
Why did you make me real?!
I can accept this place as my home
Don't eat him, Yase.
I hate you too!
Let's say goodbye
Takayamayoshi Family
Father: Monk Myoe
Mother: Koto
Child: Yakushimaru
Child: Kurama
Child: Yase
Night falls to draw me in
This wild world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
They were certainly a peculiar family, but they lived happily.
meet and laugh once more
Shrine
That man is...
...a real problem.
We went to a lot of trouble...
...to chase him into the mountains.
Our reputation is in dire peril.
We await your decision, head priest.
We have little choice.
What's it say?
You don't have to crack jokes.
They're complaining that we're making trouble for the capital.
I bet it's your fault.
It was Kurama!
No.
I'm home.
What now?
It was just a matter of time until they'd complain.
They have their duties.
The ways of the world.
Dad...
I've been thinking that Yase and I could just go back to being drawings.
Yakushimaru's a human anyway, and if only Mom is left otherwise, you should be able to sort it out.
Just erase our drawing and redo it.
You can do that, can't you?
Dad!
I can't.
I won't, Kurama.
What if we all go to the world you drew in the back room?
Are you serious, Mom?
Interesting.
Fantastic idea!
I love you, Koto!
We'll be fine.
I think.
No, I'm sure.
What's the name of that capital?
It must have a name.
Let's just say it's Kyoto too.
At least come up with different characters to write it.
And thus the family moved to the other side of the looking glass,
and mankind did not see them again.
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
Chapter Two
Past
Mirror Capital     Capital
The monk and Koto ran the capital, and named it the Mirror Capital.
Humans and fantastic creatures lived there side-by-side.
Master!
Survive, I beg you!
What? You're alive?!
I shot the sin in you.
All things the monk had drawn were continually reborn,
and all broken things regenerated.
Not "A"!
Not "O"!
The family kept living in the mountains,
Not "A"!
Not "O"!
but the children could now play freely in their enormous garden.
Kurama Temple
Yase's Village
You're as beautiful as the sun!
The moon!
The flowers!
I love you!
Will you be the mother of my children?
We're going home.
Life in their wonderland was happy and carefree.
Peaceful, uneventful days came and went.
This place is weird.
Nobody dies and nobody is born.
Everything here is as the monk and Koto decide.
I guess it's a good thing there's no war and bloodshed.
But something else bothers you?
I wasn't implying that.
Calm down.
I am calm!
You think this is normal?
How long will we have to stay children?
Geez! It got away again!
You sure seem to be having fun all the time, Yase.
Of course!
I just want to be with Mom.
I like how broken things just fix themselves.
Sometimes new stuff shows up too.
There's the station opening too.
What don't you like?
Nothing in particular.
You dislike that there's nothing to dislike.
Koto.
Did you have that dream again?
What would you do if you left?
Do you want to be a rabbit again?
Dream Diary
I think you know how I got this body.
I had an agreement with a bodhisattva.
I kept this body out of selfishness until today.
Why would you rush it this far in?
I'm just a rabbit from a drawing.
A bodhisattva's mercy is all that permits me my human body.
The agreement was to return my body once my feelings were returned.
I knew!
I knew that I would eventually bring ruin to this world.
And yet, spending time with you and looking at the faces of our children,
I kept postponing going back and told myself I'd stay only one more day...
The eyes of a bodhisattva see the truth of all the worlds.
It's only a matter of time until my nightmare comes true.
You knew all that, yet feigned ignorance?
How inconsiderate.
Says you?
Yes. We're the same.
I knew, yet couldn't act.
I was terrified.
The chance of losing you paralyzed me.
Let's go together.
I will not leave you alone.
It was a sudden farewell.
The children were left behind by their parents in the Mirror Capital,
and had nothing left but memories of the time they had spent together
and a promise of uncertain reliability.
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
Chapter
Three
Present
/
Mirror
Capital
XRSWEKXXUIEZDGFJSADHGF
XRSWEKXXUIEZDGFJSADHGFKZRFS
Takayamayoshi Family
Father: Monk Myoe
Mother: Koto
Child: Yakushimaru
Child: Kurama
Child: Yase
I don't understand why they're not getting bored of this.
Obviously there's nothing to report on anymore.
Will you shut up?!
See this? See it?
I know you want it.
If you want it, get it!
That's taken care of.
I'm surprised you still remember that.
I want to always cherish the memories of us together.
They tell me all the time
that I'm basically the same person even though my body changed so much.
Yeah...
You've grown tall, Yakushimaru.
You totally left me behind.
I'm sorry, Myoe!
Force of habit.
I don't mind.
You should.
Changes always occur for a reason.
Your name changed for a reason too.
I'm happy you still come to hang out with me, though.
Of course I do.
All right!
Calm down, will you?
I'm not irresponsible!
You guys are just taking it way too seriously!
Yeah, I'm listening.
Just don't pester me.
Yeah. Yeah. Until tomorrow.
Did you ditch the meeting again?
Being the head monk Myoe must be tough.
I don't mind.
I'm just a substitute.
You sure protect those prayer beads.
Why don't you ditch everything for good if you hate it so much?
Can't.
Tried it?
Of course.
Didn't end well.
I'll tell you one day.
You're gonna love it.
Regardless, the prayer beads are mine now,
and until they come back, I'm duty-bound to wonderland.
Sounds rough.
Is that sarcasm?
Our place in society is way too different for me to understand.
I also happen to like this place.
Good for you.
Darn! You poor man, Myoe!
It really is tough, huh?
Will you comfort me?
Am I good enough for that?
Only you are.
Do you tell that all your girls?
Nah.
Want to stay at my place?
No, I'll just... take a nap...
I hope one day someone will take you out of here, Myoe.
We'll be back with the beginning and the end one day.
I promise. Wait for us, Myoe.
Myoe! Look outside!
Where are the analysis results?!
What's going on now?
Did someone open the gates of Hell?
Can't you get anything done, dammit?!
You might not be too far off.
Get your lazy ass to work!
Then again, they might be the gates of Heaven as well.
So pretty.
I want a thunderstorm too.
Will someone bring me a thunderstorm?
Kurama, please!
Give me a lift!
I can't! It's broken!
That's why I'm asking you!
This is very strange.
No idea! How should I know?!
Yeah, just my gut! I just know it!
Come on!
I know that light.
I've seen it together with him before.
Are you back, monk?!
No luck, sis!
It's not here!
Crap! And I was sure we got it this time!
I'm gonna chase it to the end of the galaxy.
Hey, dude, you a local?
I'm from Shrine.
Seen a rabbit?
Black one. Red eyes.
Had ears.
And a mouth.
Legs too, right?
Shrine?
You don't know?
Huh?
What backwater dimension is this?
Be polite!
Hey, what's this place called?
Come on!
I'm asking which plane this is!
What, are you mute?
Kyoto.
You write it "Mirror Capital" and read it Kyoto.
I don't know what planes you're talking about.
No one's been admitted into this place for centuries.
It's not the place for a little kid without her guardian.
Who the hell are you?
Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
I'm Koto.
First Plane, Central,
General Agency: Shrine,
team Inari under direct command of the head priest.
I'm here looking for my guardian.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
Hey, when you move to a new place, don't you recall stuff from long ago?
I always end up remembering stuff I was glad I'd forgotten.
I guess I remember some nice things too.
I wonder how the guys at Shrine are doing now.
Think they're missing us?
I sure hope they're not happy we're gone!
Welcome, Little Sister
Next time: "Welcome, Little Sister".
Behold the little sister!