Yuriko!
Muroto?!
Stop right there!
Oopsies.
Moritani!
What's going on?
Who's that?
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
Stand By Me
Moritani, are you hurt?
I'm okay. Just a little bump.
This is all my fault.
Kotoura?
Your arrest, the attack on President Mifune,
Muroto's injuries.
They're all—
all my fault.
Because I have this power.
Because I have this disgusting power, I hurt everyone.
No. It's not my power that's to blame.
I shouldn't exist in the first place.
What are you talking about?
How is any of this your fault?
That psycho's hurting people, not you!
Manabe told you the same thing.
Hey, yeah, Manabe!
Why is he missing now of all times?
No! Don't call Manabe!
You still haven't gotten over your fight with him?
That's not it.
Even after the fight, he still...
Kotoura is such a klutz.
Please don't let her do anything too reckless.
Screw it.
She's got me so worried about her, I can't even eat.
Why can't they just catch that damn criminal?!
Then Kotoura won't do anything dangerous.
He still kept on worrying about me.
Selfish, stupid me.
Constantly.
That's why I just can't let him get hurt.
Kotoura.
I'm sorry, President Mifune. Muroto. Moritani.
I'm so sorry, Manabe.
For the love of—! Why is it always like this with you?!
Oh, what now?
Crap! My parents!
Hello?
Yeah. What? Yeah.
I know that. I'm not a little kid.
What? Pick up miso and soy sauce on the way home?
You seriously called just to give me errands?!
Unbelievable.
Sorry, Kotoura—
And she's gone. Why does this always happen to me!?
Nope, can't do it anymore. Gonna get angry now.
This is the park I came to with Tsukino.
Huh? Kotoura?
Eh?
We keep on running into each other, huh?
Tsukino.
What is it?
Wait! You're hurt!
Hey, what's wrong?
Checking for new messages...
No new messages.
Damnit!
How long is this going to keep up?
I'll never get through that thick head of yours.
I hate you!
She hates me, she says.
But I never thought she'd actually want to use her power.
It could put her in real danger.
Where did I go wrong?
Come on, who is it at this hour?
Shut up! Nobody's home today!
Keep it down! What time do you think—
Hi.
Demon!
I'm real sorry for the mess, but come on in.
First we need to take care of that leg.
Uh, right.
Okay, all patched up.
Thank you.
No police officer could ignore an injured schoolgirl
crying alone in the dark.
Righto then, shall we have some dinner?
Just you sit tight and I'll whip something up.
Oh, I should text Moritani.
I'm sure she's worried.
I'm at Tsukino's apartment. Everything's fine.
I'm sorry for running off on you again.
Send.
Wh-What happened?!
I'm so sorry.
The truth is, I can't cook to save my life.
Um, shall I make something?
You can cook? Seriously?!
S-So, am I being taken away for execution?
This sure brings back some memories.
I can't believe it's only been three years
since we graduated from this elementary school.
So this is where you're going to slaughter me?
That psycho attacked President Mifune.
What?
Don't worry. She's okay.
Muroto shielded her. Thankfully he wasn't hurt too badly.
Phew. That's a relief.
Wait! What about Kotoura? And are you okay?
Huh? S-Sure, I'm fine.
I'm just fine. Kotoura, too.
Don't make her an afterthought!
But Kotoura's run away again.
She feels my arrest,
the attack on President Mifune,
and Muroto's injuries were all her responsibility.
Damnit, she's thinking like that again?
Why does that moron always assume that everything is her fault?
It's how she is.
You must remember. You told me that yourself.
She's never once asked me for help.
She locked all her pain away inside herself.
And you, her knight—
Sulking in your room! What the hell are you thinking?!
Ow! What are you doing?!
That's what I'm asking you!
Why weren't you there when Kotoura was in danger?
Why did you abandon her over a petty argument?
I agree, she can be completely infuriating.
But that's exactly why
you have a duty to stay with her, no matter what happens!
That's all Kotoura needs!
I'll stay with you.
No matter what happens, I won't leave.
What the hell.
How could I have forgotten my most fundamental promise?
Hey, Manabe, can I tell you something embarrassing?
What?
I love you, Manabe.
Oh please. This is no time for joking aro—
I've always, always loved you.
I'm sorry. Kotoura has all my love.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
So that's that.
Aww, I got turned down.
This might sound weird after that confession,
but seeing you and Kotoura just feels so right.
I love watching you two.
Moritani.
Even when you were fighting,
I couldn't bring myself see it as my chance. I was just worried.
I'm not sure why,
but it really bothers me when you two aren't together.
So...
Go and get her, right now!
Wait, where is she?
Huh? How should I know?
Find her yourself, lover boy!
Wh-What?!
Kotoura!
Moritani.
Wh-What?
Back when you were bullying Kotoura...
Kotoura looked into you, and what she saw was so foul it made her retch.
I shouldn't have said that.
I've felt guilty about it this whole time.
Why are you digging up ancient history?
And anyway you were even more horrible to me after that.
You said I was a bug.
I'm sorry!
Well, enough of the teasing.
I'd better send him Kotoura's text.
So your family owns a dojo?
Y-Yeah.
Wow! That's so cool!
Manabe Yoshihisa
What? Why?
I knew it would end this way.
Why am I crying?
Muroto?
Eh? Have you been crying?
Shut up!
Oh, good. Looks like you're okay.
Don't you "oh, good" me!
..What possessed you to go and...
Sorry. Everything was my fault.
Not just what happened to you.
If anything had gone wrong, Kotoura and Moritani
might also have been victims of my selfish quest for vindication.
I was so scared.
I was so scared you'd never open your eyes again.
I was so scared you'd leave me like my mother did.
Don't do anything like this again!
I can't bear to see you get hurt on my account!
My mom says, "unfaithful bitch, untrustworthy whelp!"
Don't let us see you at school again!
Let her be!
You again?!
You're a real pain in the ass!
H-Hey, let's go.
Shall we head home, Mifune?
Please.
Pleading with me will only make the next time harder.
Because not matter how many times it happens, I'll keep on doing the same thing.
You've always been like that!
Why are you so damn set on protecting me even when it hurts you?
Because I'm Mifune Chizuru's daughter?
I certainly do respect your mother's legacy.
But if I had to choose between her and you, I'd choose you.
Wh-What do you mean?
I'm saying you're more important to me than your mother.
I won't tell you to leave off anger, or to lay aside your revenge.
But I couldn't bear to see you sacrifice the joy you have now.
Joy?
Yeah.
You look so happy when you're with Kotoura and the others.
Like you've forgotten all your cares and burdens.
But. I've always lived to avenge my mother.
We're in the same boat now.
I'll stay with you until we reach port.
No matter how selfish you may be, or how risible your overacting may become.
What do you mean, risible?
I'll use any means to achieve my objectives.
That's the kind of person I am.
Ahh, Kotoura, won't you marry me?
I'm afraid that's not really feasible.
Aww, shucks.
Well, now that we're all full—
is it true that the criminal knew your club president's name?
Yes.
Any idea how?
All right. I'll discuss it with Yama tomorrow.
You can stay here for tonight.
But wouldn't I be a bother?
What did I tell you?
No police officer would turn a blind eye to you.
Thank you. I do appreciate it.
Sorry again for the mess.
Pretty much no one comes here.
I may have a big body, but I've always been pretty timid.
Everyone bullied me when I was a kid.
I got tired of it, started training, and got really strong.
But that just scared people off.
I still wound up alone.
So in the end, I used that strength to become a detective.
She sounds a little like me.
But you're so lucky, Kotoura.
You have friends in spite of your power.
Righto then, leave the cleaning to me.
You just make yourself at home.
O-Okay, thank you.
She may be ditzy and blunt, but she's not a bad person.
Still, I feel a little sorry for her.
Something smells fishy here.
Fishy?
The place we ran into the random attacker
was the exact spot from which that detective warned us away.
What's so fishy about that?
Telling people a place is forbidden generally just makes them more curious.
Well, sorry to be curious.
There's something else too.
The criminal knew your name and where you'd be.
There was only one person with all that information.
The daughter of Mifune Chizuru.
I see.
The clairvoyant's daughter.
What did she want?
She warned us to stay away from the alleyway off 2nd Street. It's not safe.
The text Moritani forwarded me earlier said...
Kotoura's at that detective's place right now!
Yuriko!
Oh, my phone.
Huh? It's gone.
How did it get over there?
Aw, shucks. I missed.
Tsukino.
No. Who are you?
Come on, don't give me that look.
Haven't you been chasing me this whole time?
You mean, you're...
Bingo! I'm the criminal!
I hate looking at you.
That mind-reading is a real nuisance.
I'll crush you!
Hey!
You think you can escape me?!
Hey, wait up!
I don't understand why this is happening.
I bet people call you a klutz, right?
I mean, you're trying to escape by going up the stairs?!
President Mifune! Muroto! Moritani!
Manabe!
Kotoura?!
Did something happen, Manabe?
No, nothing.
More importantly, haven't you found that detective's address yet?
The police said it was too dangerous to tell us,
so Muroto's looking for it right now.
Hang tight!
Damnit!
What are you gonna do if we're too late?!
Where are you, Kotoura?!
Why?
Why did you attack those people?
Why would you want to hurt anyone?
To let off some steam.
When you were talking to this woman earlier, didn't you wonder
why she was constantly laughing like a silly cow?
She's always been a spineless coward,
so she crammed all the resentment she couldn't express into the recesses of her soul.
And that's how I was born.
Jealous of those who seem happy,
hateful towards those who have friends,
wishing destruction on all those who enjoy the things she can't!
And especially on those who remind her
of the hell she lived in as a student.
Things were that bad for her?
So all this time, I've been burning off the stress
she didn't even realize she had.
It was going so well until today.
I never expected to encounter an inhuman monster like you.
Oh, did that hurt?
But it's true: a mind-reader is nothing but a disgusting monster.
No! Stop it!
Yes, that's right.
She smiled at you so placidly, but in her heart she hated you.
Guess I can't blame her.
A monster who found everything that she couldn't?
Well, honestly I couldn't care less about her feelings.
I'm just here to have a good time.
But I can't do that if I'm caught, so...
bye-bye.
Until very recently,
I thought the world would be better off if I'd never been.
Sometimes I was sure I ought to die.
But...
Kotoura!
I don't want to die! I don't want to die!
I want to live! I want to live!
Manabe!
Y-You?!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Kotoura.
Manabe!
You psycho!
Sorry. Didn't I promise?
I'll always stay with you.
Manabe.
Oh, give me a fucking break!
If you won't get out of my way, I'll just have to—
Tsukino, stop this!
Maybe I am a monster.
But I met people willing to reach out to me.
Big damn deal!
No one ever "reached out" to her and no one ever will!
That's what I thought too.
But I was so wrong.
I'm sure there are people who'll stand by you.
So please don't give up.
Kotoura!
Hey! What are you dragging your heels for?
She's just a damn kid talking nonsense!
I can hear your voice, Tsukino.
It's okay. Even I was able to change.
If you don't finish this, they'll just call you a criminal!
I'll keep helping you!
So stop! Stop!
Stop!
Sorry to scare you like that.
Tsukino?
Kotoura!
You guys.
Are you okay?
Yeah, just a little shaken.
Wait, Tsukino!
I need to answer for my crimes.
Tsukino.
So there you have it.
Let's move. In the car with ya.
Yama.
When you're out, look me up.
I'll treat you to some dinner.
Can I get the big set?!
Damn lug! You're only gettin' the kiddie meal!
Kotoura, let's head home.
Come on, hurry!
Yeah!
When something trips you up,
how do you stand again?
Can truth be found by thinking
about the days to come?
When we are born, we all come into this world alone,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
ESP Society, assemble!
Present!
We've reached the final episode,
so let's do the last preview together!
One, two...
Kotoura will live on in our hentai folders forever!
Episode 12
The Things I Want to Tell You
NOOOO-hoo-no-o!