It was the first time...
What?
...I was able to say what I really felt.
You were the first, Hanayo-san.
Yuzuki...
Thanks...
...Hanayo-san.
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
Ru-chan, you're going to be late for school.
Oh no!
Grandma will clean up the rest.
Okay!
Morning, Ru.
Good morning, Tama.
Is it time to go to school already?
Tama, you're such a sleepy-head.
S-Sorry, Yuzuki!
I'm leaving!
Good morning.
Oh, are you alone today?
Where's Yuzuki-chan?
Huh? Oh, um, nothing...
Is Akira still missing?
Yeah. A girl from her school said so.
She hasn't come home at all.
It's been about a week, right?
Ru, the train's going to go. Ru?
Yuzuki...
That's right... We're...
Let's... not be friends anymore.
We're... not friends anymore.
I won't battle anymore.
Yuzuki won't quit battling
until her wish comes true.
That's what we decided.
Yes... decided...
You serious?
Kurebayashi, in the second-year class...
You mean the twins?
I heard they're going out together.
What?
Wait, isn't that ince--
No way?!
So, the rumor was true?
I wonder if they "did it" already...?
--What'd you think? They live together.
--No way...!
It's not your fault, Honoka.
Really, don't worry about it.
And I thought he was cool...
Gross...
Did you spread it to everyone?
What do you mean "spread"?
It's your fault for doing stuff that would spread.
I-I just said that you were acting strange.
I just discussed it with the others...
Honoka was worried about you.
I felt sorry that you and Yuzuki-san
were being misunderstood.
I'm fine. But, I can't forgive
anyone who insults Yuzuki!
C-Can't forgive...?! That's so mean!
You're so terrible.
That's why everyone is saying
you're both making out and stuff.
Apologize!
What a loser.
It's your fault.
--Aren't they like, brother and sister...?
--That's why it's freaky.
Too bad. I thought she was cute...
There you are.
Yuzuki...
I heard you told the others not to insult me.
Yeah...
I'm so happy. But you don't have to worry.
After all, it is true.
What do you mean "true"?
I...
...love you, Kazuki.
Huh?
I've loved you... ever since we were kids.
But, I thought saying that
would make you feel sick about me.
That's what I thought... for the longest time.
I guess Goto-kun in the second class...
That sounds okay.
I don't know about that.
Huh...
As I got older, all the kids
around me had others they liked...
Hey, how about you Yuzuki?
Huh?
Everyone said who they liked,
so it's your turn next!
Who do you like?
I... I'm not into boys now...
Aw, quit lying.
Really. There's no one that I like at all.
You're still lying.
No, really!
C'mon, tell us.
I'm telling you the truth.
I couldn't tell the truth to anyone...
Um, do you know if...
Kazuki-kun has a person he likes?
H-He was saying that he thought
things like that were creepy.
Even when he watches TV, he said those
love stories were boring and unreal.
I lied to my friends...
Even to the person I love... Kazuki.
But, I was thinking maybe it's best like this...
What? You're fine like this?
Yeah.
But, I'll still love Kazuki forever.
Even if he gets a girlfriend,
and marries, and has kids...
I'll continue to lie my whole life.
Even when I'm old and single,
I'll love him forever.
But... that day...
A card game?
It's pretty fun.
What's the matter?
Huh?
Are you the Selector?
What...?
My name is Hanayo. Nice to meet you!
The card... talked?
The card did what?
Can't you hear her, Kazuki? This card just...
Don't bother.
Our voices can only be heard by Selectors.
S-Selector...?
My wish... can come true?
Right. Whether you
believe that or not is up to you.
You have a wish, right?
Not like you'll lose anything.
Go ahead, tell me.
I... love Ka--
What?
I... love Kazuki.
Kazuki? You mean... your brother?
I... love Kazuki...
Kazuki...!
I love Kazuki! Love... Love...!
I love him!
I know... This isn't right...
This isn't forgiven!
But, I want to be with him.
I want to be with Kazuki forever!
No... I want to be Kazuki's...
I want to be his girlfriend!
Okay, let's make it happen.
We'll make that wish come true.
So, your wish is...!
I was really doing my best...
...being straightforward.
Straightforward in what I did...
Straightforwardly hurt...
Straightforwardly hurt others.
It was the first time...
What?
...I was able to say what I really felt.
You were the first, Hanayo-san.
Yuzuki...
Thanks... Hanayo-san.
If I could be with you
no matter how hurt I was,
no matter if the entire
world were against me,
or even if I lost everything,
it wouldn't have mattered.
I love you, Kazuki.
Kazuki?
He hasn't come back from lunch yet.
Thanks.
She's here...
Pretty creepy...
A wish...
A wish you want to make come true,
even if it means hurting yourself,
even if it means hurting someone else.
The next time we meet, I'll be a new me!
Me, as Kazuki's girlfriend!
That kind of straightforward
feeling can't be stopped.
I... don't have a wish.
It can't be helped.
That's what we are about...
Me... and you.
No...
I'm...
Ru?
Ru? Lonely?
Huh?
Because Hitoe and Yuzuki
aren't friends anymore?
But, Tama is Ru's friend.
Battle...
Even if we don't battle... Always friends!
Tama...
I like to battle, but...
But, I can... stop!
Thanks... Tama.
Ru.
Excuse me...
Hitoe?!
Hitoe? Why are you...?
Wait. Do you remember me?
Ru!
Hitoe has an LRIG!
LRIG?
You're... a Selector, right?
Please battle me.
What...?
It can't be... You're a Selector again?!
Please... battle me.
No...
No... Why...?
I'm sorry... I'm not battling anymore...
Right, and you're still
hanging around with Tama.
Yuzuki?
I guess that can't be helped.
You're both really close to each other.
Yuzuki?!
But if so, why not listen to
a favor from your former friend?
Where...? Where are you, Yuzuki?!
Yuzuki...?
Long time no see... Well, not really, I guess.
Yuzuki... an LRIG?
This can't be real... This...
This can't be...?
Well, it's actually pretty real.
That scrunchie...
Looks like the three of us got together again.
But, this feels so weird.
Yuzuki...
What happened...?
Really, there's a lot to talk about,
but before that...
...battle Hitoe.
I can't! I can't do that!
It's for Hitoe's sake.
For Hitoe's wish... For me...
My wish...
Please, Ruko...
For Hitoe and Yuzuki?
Okay...
Thanks.
--Open!
Hitoe... Yuzuki...
Tama! Grow!
Okay!
Tell me, Yuzuki! What happened?!
I won my battle.
And... my wish was approved.
Your final attack... your final call. Together...
Now, together with me.
I accept...
I... accept!
...the laws of the Selector.
And...!
--...now, a new Eternal Girl will be born!
--Adamasphere!
What...? Then, the Yuzuki now is...
Yuzuki.
Hanayo-san...
...became Yuzuki?
The girl whose wish was approved
becomes an Eternal Girl
and gains the power
to make wishes come true.
But...
...the wish is granted to...
It's the drawing I made during pre-school.
The princess is me.
The black scribble next to her...
Do you know who that is?
What?
I drew you as the prince.
I wanted to be your bride.
But, I learned that was a bad thing...
I tried to make it go away,
over and over again.
I colored over it so hard.
But, I couldn't make it go away.
"Go away"...
I... I couldn't make
my feelings go away, either.
I love you too...
I love you too, Yuzuki... I love you...
I've loved you for so long...
We were family. That wouldn't be forgiven.
I deceived myself all this time.
I tried to not notice my feelings...
But, I don't care what happens anymore.
I don't care what others think!
I don't mind losing everything
and leaving this place together!
I love you, Yuzuki! I love you! I love you!
I... love you too, Kazuki.
Finally.
The wish...
...came true.
That... That can't be...?!
The LRIG... gets the wish?
You...
...will become an LRIG.
The replaced Selector...
becomes another person's LRIG.
Nice to meet you, Selector.
And when that person is led
to victory, and is replaced...
...the LRIG can come back
out in the world again.
The wish will come true...
But the wish comes true,
not for me, the Selector...
...but instead for Hanayo-san, the LRIG.
That's the Eternal Girl...
That's...
...the truth behind these battles!
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
Hanayo-san...
I don't know anything!
Tama don't know.
Hanayo-san... you're so horrible.
I don't know...
Thanks... Hanayo-san.
"That Stranded Emotion."