When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Shoot!
SIGN: Little Haruhi's U2
What is the matter?
I forgot to return this
DVD to Wataru's store.
Then I shall go return it.
How long have you had it?
Roughly 2 years.
What?!
No, it may be closer to 3 years by now.
Hurrying at this point is moot, but
I just have to get this returned.
Why a potted plant?!
I have a feeling luck's not with me today...
Closed due to special circumstances
Luck really isn't with me today...
But then, it's not like
anything unfortunate happened.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
The Young Sir does not understand
what is in a woman's heart.
Honestly! Young Sir, you cur!
Teehee.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
I've Never Had the Trouble
of Being Too Popular
I have returned.
I'm sorry, Hayate! That DVD was actually...
My apologies. Wataru's
store was closed today,
so I left it in the return box.
Oh, no, about that...
Oh, welcome!
Hello.
Shoot! I let my guard down
and didn't prep a joke!
To what do we owe the pleasure today?
You have to ask "to what"?!
I came to check on Nagi, 'cause I heard
she hasn't been to school at all!
Now that you mention it!
No more of this needless conversation!
The wonderful tea will get cold!
It's ice tea!
The lingering summer heat is
still ruthless, after all.
True.
Considering how hot it is now in September,
I wonder how hot it'll get
in October and November.
Why would ya wonder that?!
But that was good. Keep it up!
Having said that, it's
actually autumn already.
When it comes to autumn,
it's the season of eating.
Yes, yes, because it's the season
where you get beat a lot.
Autumn, the season of beating!
Just kidding.
Falter and ya lose!
Have confidence in yer own material!
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Speaking of which...
Ya got a new openin' line?
Opening line?
Or is it a new careless thing you did?
Yes, my stole...
Your stole?
Yes.
It is a new stole, but
somewhere, I carelessly...
You left it and forgot it?
Oh, then I'll go look for it.
Oh, no, I do not really care
if it is lost for good.
It only cost about 50 million yen, so...
I'll go look for it right
away, on the double!
He is such a kind person.
Well, of course! My Hayate is the
world's most kind and dependable man!
As I recall, Isumi was resting
in the guest bedroom.
Today sure was rough.
It's best to sleep on days like this.
Ooh!
And right as I was saying that,
here's a stole that'll
make the perfect blanket!
Let's see...
I think I'll pick it up with
these claws that shred cloth!
No, Tama! That stole cost 50 million and...
Don't touch Isumi's stole!
Thinking of touching Isumi's personal
belonging, when you're only a pet?!
You've got some nerve!
Wataru? When did he get here?
Sheesh!
Even I don't often get to touch
Isumi's personal belongings...
Her personal belonging...
Wataru?
What are you...?
H-How long have you been
there, you butler-in-debt?!
I've been here the whole time...
D-Did you see that just now?!
By "that just now", do you mean...
S-S-So, you know...!
Oh, that almost pathological
behavior unique to adolescents
where you happen to come upon
an object that was worn by the
girl you like and you get
the urge to sniff it?
That's normal when you consider
what 13-year-olds do.
You gonna tell them?
Huh?
Like tell Nagi and Isumi what you saw?!
Not to worry.
What?
A Sanzenin butler does not do things
that would embarrass a guest.
But a Sanzenin pet would do things
You bastard tiger!
Tama, you...!
Wait, weren't you not going to speak,
because it would ruin your image?!
It's for the girls that I
don't want to ruin my image.
Good grief
In fact, I want to ruin my image for boys!
Rarr! Rarr! Rarr!
This anime is geared towards boys, though...
So, I'm gonna get right to
telling the young ladies
about this stinking brat's weird behavior
using a dying message from Conan!
W-Wait, if Isumi finds out, I'll...
I had no idea Wataru was
that kind of person!
How filthy!
He is worse than an insect!
Not to worry. Please leave the rest to me.
Th-Thanks, butler-in-debt.
I'll be counting on you.
Yes, sir. Incidentally, what
are you doing here, Wataru?
What?
Oh, I'm here because that
idiot Nagi returned a DVD
that I'd gone to the
trouble of giving to her.
So I came to give it to her again.
What?
Oh, I'm so glad! Then...
All right! First, I'll
spread the rumor on the net
and build it up so the Miss hears about it.
I've started numerous threads
that went on to become famous.
No worries! I can do this!
I'll build up the hype myself
by using different IPs
and make the thread really popular.
Tama, enough with making
trouble for our guests!
Or I will show you no mercy,
even if you are the Miss's pet.
Y-Yessir!
It seems Tama has reconsidered.
But I still can't face Isumi,
so you give it to her for me.
I understand.
Also, um...
Thank you for helping me.
Not at all. I am honored to be of service.
Then please excuse me.
Ayasaki Hayate... If I
could be a man like him...
Little Wataru kept his steady
gaze on Hayate's back...
Here you are, Isumi. Your stole.
Aren't you glad he was
able to find it, Isumi?
Yes, it is all thanks to my dear Hayate.
That reminds me, where's Sakuya?
She left just earlier,
complaining she had no one to make jabs at.
Then, I shall be taking
my leave soon as well.
Well, please be very
careful on your way home.
My dear Hayate, you seem
rather happy for some reason.
I am. A certain person thanked
me for a little something.
Oh, my.
I've had a string of mishaps lately, so...
Like this morning, I got ran over by a truck
and people were giving me unfriendly looks...
It made me feel a bit down...
Oh...
But I think it was just
my imagination, after all.
Unfortunate things have happened
to me ever since I was little,
so I think it was just a coincidence.
My dear Hayate.
Yes?
What?
What?!
I-Isumi?!
Smooch.
Uh, um...
This is my thanks for the stole.
What?
I think this will make
things somewhat better.
Then, good day to you.
I want you to know that I
love you, my dear Hayate.
What?!
The romantic comedy turn
of events to be continued!
Real love.
(Riaru rabu.)
Brassiere complex!
(Burajaa konpurekkusu.)
I-Isumi...
I want you to know that I
love you, my dear Hayate.
A dream...
I know! Maybe it's just that kids love me!
It turns out that we have
a wholesome protagonist,
who doesn't consider kids to
be possible romantic partners.
Have you been awake this whole time?
Yes...
When I saw them yesterday, it looked
to me like they were embracing, but...
What in the world was that?
If it bothers you that much,
why not ask them yourself?
But...
If I ask and Isumi really does love Hayate...
With Hayate already in love with
me, it would mean hurting Isumi.
I-I see...
But it may be some kind of misunderstanding.
There is a high probability that
Isumi has fallen in love with Hayate.
After all, Hayate is the
coolest man in the universe.
Whoa...
Then it will be a serious problem
if the coolest man in the universe
were making a pass at Isumi.
That would never happen!
For Hayate to pursue some
girl other than me...
For him to make a pass at Isumi...
For him to fall for some other girl...
Such a thing...
I-I'm going to go see Hayate!
A-All right.
Hayate!
Wh-Wha?!
What is it, Miss?!
I have a little question for you!
Y-Yes, Miss?
Hayate, do you, um... love Isumi?!
What?
Yes.
I do love Isumi.
A-Are you serious?
Yes!
Are you seriously in love with Isumi?!
What?
Answer me! After what you did yesterday!
W-W-Well, I don't think I'm
actually in love with her...
Then are you just playing?!
Are you saying you were just toying with
Isumi when you did that yesterday?!
If anything, I play with
Sakuya more than Isumi.
Oh, but I would like to
play more with Isumi, too.
M-Miss?!
J... J...
Hayate, you jerk!
That hurt...
I shouldn't crack eggs using my head. Yeah.
I misjudged you, Hayate!
Are you all right?
Um, did I do something?
What? I-I wouldn't know...
Could it be because Isumi confessed
to me that she loved me?
I-Isumi said that?
Yes. It's so cute, isn't it?
It might be that kids just love me,
so maybe I'd make a good
preschool teacher or something.
What?
Uh, perhaps...
I must... do something about this...
Video Rental
V Tachibana
DX Animation
Tama's Sinister Design!!
Honestly!
Why do men want to watch such things?!
You've been looking at it for some
30 minutes yourself, though...
The Young Sir is still a child, so
I'm sure he has no interest in girls,
but will he eventually want
to watch things like this?
No! I'm sure only a portion of men do this!
Surely, the Young Sir will not...!
Do Not Enter
But he has not set foot
outside since last night...
What in the world could he be...
I-I am sorry, we are not open yet...
Miss Nagi!
I'm coming in for a bit.
No! Isumi couldn't possibly have
feelings for the butler-in-debt...
But then...
How can you sleep there like
you've got no problems?!
N-Nagi, what the hell are you doing here?!
What am I doing?! I've run away from home!
Huh?!
Heartbreak!
And in despair, the girl ran away from home.
Oh, you guys can go home now.
But don't tell Maria about this.
Yes, Miss!
I'm running away from home!!
Don't look for me!!
Nagi!!
Wh-What shall we do?
Well, we'll have to look for her.
Understood!
Oh, uh, Hayate!
I'll go to Isumi's place first!
Oh, uh, wait!
Uh, um, if Miss Nagi has run
away from home, does that...
She will be staying here for a while.
By the way, Miss Saki Kijima.
Yes?!
Miss Nagi is the one and only
granddaughter of the Sanzenin family
and she is to be spending time here.
If something should happen to her...
You understand, I hope?
You will not go unpunished.
Anyway, we'll get nowhere if we
just keep fighting like this.
You're right.
Let's go to Isumi's place...
...and ask her how she feels!
Oh, my, Nagi has run away from home?
Yes, do you have any ideas?
Well, it is probably...
What is the matter?!
Oh, no, some dust got in my eyes...
A-Are you all right?
Hey, isn't it possible you were
mistaken about what you saw?
Well, it's true, them embracing would be...
I can't get it out...
Hayate!
M-Miss, so this is where you were!
You came to see Isumi the
moment I disappeared?!
What? Uh, yes, I did, but...
Isumi can just take you for 150 million!
What?! M-Miss!
Why, Miss?!
Shall I take him?
What?!
Shall I take my dear Hayate for 150 million?
Wha?!
Miss!
Miss Nagi!
Thus, the romantic comedy has grown
into a muddy, icky, quagmire
of a love-hate drama.
In the meantime, as for Maria...
I have to do something about this, but...
Wait, what? Huh? I've been left
alone somewhere along the way!
Video Rental
V Tachibana
Shoplifting is a crime
I swear! What the heck is the big
idea of renting such boring DVDs?!
Huh?
Besides, what's with these?
They're all just hyped up pieces of garbage.
Th-That's my decision to make...
Shut up! Quiet!
Now you listen to me carefully!
Time is limited!
There are countless masterpieces
in this world that must be seen!
You are decisively lacking in "Gundam"!
Sieg Ze*n
G-Gundam?
That's right! "Gundam"!
So, I'll loan you all of it from
the original series to "00"!
What?! All of it?!
Just don't sleep, got it?!
Don't sleep and watch it all,
like your life depended on it!
"Char's Counterattack" and
"Turn A" are particularly...
Like he even understands!
Don't randomly loan out my DVDs!
I am not doing it randomly! I've
selected masterpieces to loan out!
What the hell are you doing here anyway?!
It's because I've run away
from home, of course!
The reason you didn't want
to be at home to begin with
was because that butler-in-debt
was there, right?!
Then, get your butt home already!
Because that butler-in-debt's
not at your house anymore!
Not there...
Hayate's...
...not there...
YOUNG SIR!!!
What are you doing bullying the Miss?!
I-I wasn't really bullying her...
At the rate you are going, Isumi
will come to hate you, too!
Doooom
Wait...
I'll just burn this damn store!
Let it all burn!
You cannot do this! Young Sir! Miss!
Right around then, Saki was at the
mercy of two heartbroken children.
And now, next time, they
will fight against a robot.
Wataru and Tarutaru
I'm a kitten. I don't have a name yet.
The sky's so high up there again today...
Look, look! So cute!
Oh, wow, a kitten!
It warms my heart!
Hah, don't just let your heart be warmed.
If you've got any compassion, feed me!
Wait, you're really leaving?!
Coldhearted bastards! Hypocrites!
Darn, the rain in the city is cold.
But man, I'm hungry.
Wataru
Hey, that's milk!
Hey, you bastard!
You weren't gonna give it to me, bro?
Mouth-to-mouth feeding?!
C-Come on, bro...
H-Hey, you okay? You got a cold?
Oh, my, Wataru, so this is where you were.
Oh!
So you found the kitty.
I'm so glad for you.
You've been worried and out looking for
it every time it rained, after all.
Bro, you've been looking for me?
There, there. There, there. There, there.
Bro, what's your name?
Taru.
Oh, so this kitty's name is Tarutaru.
What?!
What a cute name!
I-It's kind of lame, but
I'll just let it lie.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Best of luck tuning. I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm Sakuya.
But don't ya think I get too
little screen time on this show?
Some characters show up every
week for no good reason.
No, that's because you upstage
the others when you show up...
Butler-in-debt, ya aren't
gonna gloss it over so easily.
Saku's the character that gets forgotten.
What was that?!
Oh, well, whatever. Here's
a risqué sexy shot of me.
Well? Did ya sear that image into yer eyes?
Bye-bye!
Preview
Someone like me deserves to
get abandoned by the Miss.
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
Being allowed to work in a
grand mansion like that...
It was like a dream to begin with.
Hayate probably hates me now.
Then why don't you just test his love?
Test his love?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Hearts Wavering".
Are you planning to fake a kidnapping?!
You should not do that!
Hearts Wavering
The clouds of war call to Hayate.