What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
It's so cold...
So tired...
Should I really keep these?
It's probably a mistake...
Good morning, Mukae!
Morning!
Good morning, Kaoru.
Cold today, isn't it?
Good morning.
Morning, Ritsu!
Morning!
That's right.
Not gonna get my hopes up again.
I've already been rejected once.
Can I get the usual, Ma'am?
Sure thing. Here you go.
Thank you!
You're looking beautiful as always, Ma'am!
Oh, it's you.
What's with the long face?
Let me guess.
You're in shock over the news that Yurika eloped?
It's all over the school!
D-Did you tell him about it?!
Oh, Kawabuchi?
Yep, I told him this morning...
I don't think he's in class!
I didn't expect to hear anything like this...
I wonder how he feels.
Ah, that's the piece that won the Governor's Award.
We'd better take it down now.
You take that side.
Um, what are you doing?
The school doesn't want to display a painting done by someone involved in a scandal.
We were told to remove it.
And what's going to happen to it after you take it down?
You got me.
W-Wait!
This painting is important!
Please!
What's she to you, anyway?
Had eyes for her, did ya?
Wha—
Let it go, Richie.
Sorry about that.
You can take it away.
Sen...
Hey, Sen! Why?!
You don't care about it at all?!
Hey!
W-What are you doing?! Let go of me!
What are you laughing at?!
Your stupidity must be contagious.
W-What?
Seriously, how stupid are you gonna be for somebody else's sake?
It's ridiculous.
Wait.
What about her painting?!
Oh, I already said goodbye to it back there.
I feel much better now.
Sen...
Did a certain someone give you a gift recently?
Like something that was knitted maybe?
Yeah, sure did.
I knitted Sentaro a sweater and used the leftover yarn to make your mittens!
So cruel...
It figures...
Look! It's called Lily-yarn or something.
I got it from Sachiko yesterday.
Anything else?
Nope. This is it.
But what am I supposed to do with a string?
Huh?
Strike!
What the heck?!
You!
You're gonna get it!
Wait up, Richie!
Richie!
U-Um, these are really warm...
Thank you.
Ow! Dammit! What are you doing?!
Hey, I'm over here!
Nope, over here!
Come to think of it, we'll be changing classes again soon.
I guess third-years are split up by their grades,
so you probably won't be in the same class as Kaoru.
Goin' for college entrance exams, right Richie?
Y-Yeah...
I intend to go to college, too.
I'm thinking about becoming an elementary school teacher.
So you're gonna be a teacher, huh?
What about it?
Long time ago, you said you wanted to have a bakery or a cake shop.
What?
When was this?
Come on, don't you remember?
You were a glutton.
So you wanted a shop!
I never said that!
Kaoru, where do you want to go to college?
Oh, I haven't decided yet.
As for me, never mind about college.
I might not even make it to next year.
I see...
Wait, what did you just say?!
All right, it all comes down to the next makeup exam.
Start with these basic problems.
I'll make you some flash cards in the meantime.
You take care of that.
Hey!
I'm just not cut out for studying.
What are you going to do if you fail this?!
Oh, I'll just quit school an' get a job.
You must be jo—
It ain't a joke.
I've thought about my family.
I can't afford to repeat a year.
No way!
I won't let that happen!
I'm not gonna let you flunk this test!
I'm tired.
I need a break!
Wait! You're right in the middle of these!
I can't take anymore...
If you're going to rest, it'll have to wait 'til you're done with these problems!
I can't! My head's gonna explode!
B-Bro...
Jeez...
Hey, Sen...
You always look so happy when you're surrounded by children.
W-Where'd that come from?
I bet you're going to have a big family of your own,
with lots of kids around you.
It'll be a warm...
Chi'ko wet herself!
What?!
Yay, Chi'ko!
The bath's over there.
My mom will dry your pants, so relax for a bit.
This is an unusual setup for a bath...
Sachi?
You're out of soap, right?
Here...
S-Sorry...
I-I don't understand.
Isn't this Sen's bath?
We share a bath with Sentaro's family...
Y'know... I wish I had given the mittens to you earlier...
It's almost spring, so you won't need to use them anymore...
Oh, that doesn't matter...
I'd wear them all year 'round, since you knitted them for me.
Cold!
Condensation?
Happens all the time.
Sentaro lets out a yelp once in a while himself.
Say, Ritsu, why did you give me those mittens, anyway?
W-Why?
Why me and not him?
I mean...
If you've liked him all this time...
Richie!
How about havin' dinner here?!
Your pants aren't dry yet anyway...
I'm going home now.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Wait, your hair's soakin' wet! You'll catch a cold!
That's enough!
Sorry.
Well, see you tomorrow...
I didn't mean to say that to her.
But I couldn't get it out of my mind...
She probably still has feelings for him...
Sen, how did the makeup exam go?
Oh, you passed?
Yeah.
Good for you.
It's thanks to Richie.
I gotta thank 'im proper.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Richie-rich much lately.
He passed out in class with a fever the other day,
so he's restin' up at home.
You didn't hear?
Nope, Ritsuko didn't say a thing.
"Someday My Prince Will Come?"
N-No!
That was just...
Ri'ko. Wanna come with me?
Look at it.
Huge, ain't it? That's Richie's house.
All right, go on.
Thank Richie for me, for helpin' me study.
But...
Sentaro, wait!
Go on by yourself.
Why?!
Let's go together!
Kaoru, one of your classmates has come to wish you well.
E-Excuse me...
Hey, Ritsu.
Um, is your fever down?
Yeah. Sorry to make you worry...
I see. Good.
Oh, that's right. These are for you.
Eat them if you're up to it.
Oh, thank you.
Did you go out of the way to buy them?
Um... No.
I didn't buy these. Uh...
Sentaro did...
Ritsu...
He came here with you, didn't he?
I saw you two from the window.
He should've come in with you...
Kaoru?
Never mind. I understand.
What are you talking about?
It makes sense.
You two have been together since you were little.
There's no way I could be a match for him...
Unlike me, he's strong and built...
And he's so handsome, he even takes my breath away once in a while...
You're better off with him, y'know...
Enough already!
I know what you're saying, so please stop.
I'm going home now.
Kaoru, don't you like me anymore?
Or is it
that you just don't have any confidence, so you're trying to keep your distance?
Kaoru, you told me to have confidence in myself.
Those words have saved me a number of times.
But if it looks like you don't have confidence,
I have a feeling I'll lose mine, too.
Huh? What the heck am I doing?
What I've wished for all this time...
Oh, you're leaving already?
Excuse me.
Oh, boy! I bet something happened between those two!
Ritsu!
Kaoru!
Don't come here...
I'll go over to you!
Ritsu...
Let me tell you how I feel about you once more...
I love you!
I love you, Ritsu!
I love you! I love you! I love you! I—
K-Kaoru!
P-Please!
Your family can hear!
Let them!
I'm not muscular and maybe I'm not as manly as I could be,
but when it comes to my feelings for you, I'm second to none!
I might get you sick...
I won't mind.
Kaoru!
Hey! You're burning up! And you're heavy!
Excuse me! Somebody!
That was really something...
Kaoru! Anyone, please!
It's summer already and I haven't made any more progress with Ritsu...
Even though I was so bold when I had a fever...
What's wrong with me when I'm not sick?!
I want to touch...
Touch what?
How long have you been in here?!
I just got here.
Did you hear anything?!
Like what?
Nothing!
Both of you!
Take a look at this!
East High
Newspaper
"The Olympus Has Thrown Down the Gauntlet"?
What is this?
"The Olympus is going to win at this year's festival.
It seems there are still some old-fashioned jazz musicians around,
but this is the era of rock 'n' roll."
They were handing this out all over the school.
What are you gonna do?
I mean, you can't take this sitting down, right?!
You two are gonna perform in the festival, aren't you?!
Huh?
I've been thinking...
Me too.
We start with "Moanin'" to fire up the people who saw us last year
an' fake 'em out thinking we're gonna do the same routine.
But then we move into some other songs that we want to play.
I was thinkin' the same thing!
All right, let's choose our next song!
Startin' today, we'd better practice every day!
Absolutely!
How about this one?
I'm home...
Welcome back, Bro!
Hey.
Welcome home!
Look, I got big news!
Dad says he's comin' home!
This way, the whole family can live together!
Sachi...
What are you doing here all by yourself?
I can't say that I'm actually scared...
Scared?
See, our Dad was working really far away.
And he's coming home tomorrow morning.
Richie, I'm one of those that ain't got a place in his own home, too.
Richie?
I'm home...
Hey, you're back late, Sachiko.
What's Richie doin' here with you?
I see.
Unlike with Kota and the other little ones,
you remember how scary Dad was when he was drunk.
But don't worry, Sachiko!
Ma told me that Dad worked really hard an' quit drinkin' over there.
Really?
Yeah. You got nothin' to worry about, Sachiko.
Now how about comin' inside an' we can get ready together?
Yeah!
Sen...
Oh, thanks for lookin' after her.
You're the one I'm worried about, Sen.
Dope! What're you lookin' so serious for?!
What?! I am serious!
Richie. Don't worry so much.
I'll be fine.
Bro, look!
Comin'!
Sen!
Are you coming to practice tomorrow?
Yeah. After all, playin' jazz with you is the most fun I have.
Bro, what are you writin'?
Hmm... Nah, that's no good.
It's not comin' out right.
Ah, well. Let's get to sleep.
Richie.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
I was looking forward to the festival, too. I wanted to perform.
Be good to Ri'ko.
Take care.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change