Aw, she's being bullied.
And the bullies are so awfully clichéd.
Right turn!
Well then, start talking.
Let's hear about the human experiments you're helping with.
It was me.
It had to be.
I wonder where I was headed?
I found...
my love!
Spare me your excuses.
Or will you be the "raw material"?
Give up.
Maybe it's fine to not have a head.
You always lose the important things, right?
Like the umbrella you just bought.
But you still have a ton of that vinyl crap.
Well, I don't care if it's an umbrella, but when you put your winning lottery ticket down
and can't find it afterwards, that sucks.
And then you always find other things when you're looking for something else.
Maybe we just think that the things we lose are really important.
Evening!
Are you guys looking for something?
Sometimes I think...
that my head might be awake while my body's asleep.
Ever since my memories became hazy,
the time passing by has felt ambiguous as well.
I wonder how long it's been...
since I've seen myself as a whole, even in my dreams?
Here and there...
What will I see on the other side?
What am I seeing?
In this ever-repeating dream
that I'm trying to decipher.
However, the dream never changes.
Selty!
I've got great news!
Last night, you said you didn't have to work today, right?
After some calculations, I've found out that it's your first day off in 265 days!
Your face doesn't look happy.
He reads my mood on the face I don't have.
I heard that people dream because their brains are sorting their memories.
Is this true?
What's with that sudden question?
You want to know why people dream?
Simply put, it's still unknown.
There are still many hurdles that medical science has yet to cross.
Especially in neuroscience.
The term "REM" comes to mind when talking about dreams.
You often dream during rapid eye movement.
He's a doctor.
To be precise, an underground doctor.
I don't know what he really does though.
It's all thanks to him that I can both continue my job as a transporter and have a place to stay.
Well, first we have to answer the question, "What are memories?"
Are you listening?
I'm grateful to him.
And lately, when we're together,
I've realized that I'm in love with him.
However...
Well, you think your memories are in your head, but we don't know that for sure.
They're definitely there. Duh!
More importantly...
Let's get changed.
We can go out somewhere.
I'll take the day off too.
Look, I'm turning my cellphone off.
I'll unplug the network cable as well.
I swear I won't even check my mailbox!
We've got the whole day to ourselves!
So, where should we go?
A ride on your horse to the vast sea?
Or perhaps a trip to the spa?
I don't want to go anywhere.
Why not?
Well, since we're taking the day off, and as thanks for taking care of me, I'd like to cook for you.
Oh my! Home cooking?!
What would you like to eat?
I'll look for a recipe.
I'm so moved, Selty!
I wonder what's good.
Thanks for letting me borrow this, dude.
You're a real life saver.
Stupid me overslept this morning.
No worries, young man.
I figured the fatigue of coming all the way to Tokyo was catching up to you.
Yeah, you could call this a "hunter's chance"!
You sit shoulder-to-shoulder with your pretty neighbor and look at the same book.
And?
No necktie? Or did you forget that too?
Are you all right?
You sure you didn't forget your wallet too?
No way...
It's yummy!
Russian Sus—
Simon!
Have you seen Yumacchi?
Oh, Karisawa!
Do you want some sushi?
I haven't seen him.
So he wasn't here...
Dengeki Bunko's Accel World came out today.
We bought it together, had some tea, and then headed home.
But then the maid in the café told me that he forgot his cellphone.
Hey, don't ask customers then.
Hello? Excuse me.
What are you looking for?
I said, "I'm looking for Yumacchi—
Who are you?
Lost things?
Write what you're looking for on this.
Come on, tell me.
Are you going to walk around the city with that all day?
I'm asking everyone around.
My cellphone!
Welcome back!
What am I searching for?
Everything's cool now that Kaztano is safe and sound.
Even though I promised not to dig deeper...
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals...
It's said that they're working behind-the-scenes with the Awakusu Group,
and that they're connected to the North American Nebula Inc.
Either way, I'm not going to learn anything by standing here.
Have you seen Karisawa-san?
No.
Oh...
How about some Russian sushi?
Ah, Selty!
Use a kitchen knife, okay?
This is yummy!
Way too yummy!
Delectable!
Hold on! Why are you crying?
Crying?
They're tears of joy.
It's truly great.
This extremely sweet burdoc,
and the bitterness of the miso soup.
Something's not right...
No, no. Your cooking is just divine!
It's just like you!
That's not a compliment!
Okay, I understand. I got the taste wrong again.
It's all right. Don't force yourself to eat it.
That's not true.
It's so tasty.
Don't eat it!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Hey, honestly, you're a good cook.
So what if you don't have watermelon cells?
What? Watermelon?
I'm talking about your sense of taste.
The brain can't understand tastes that aren't in your DNA.
But since you don't need to eat,
it doesn't seem to be an issue with the brain.
Come on, cheer up.
Let's play a game, 'kay?
Don't treat me like I'm a child.
That annoys me the most.
I'm not treating you like a child.
It's true that you've taught me many things,
but I have memories that stretch back 100 years.
And my head has even more...
Do you need memories from 100 years in the past?
What do you mean?
It's like I always say...
You're fine the way you are.
Do you know how I feel?
It's like I'm forgetting my own face!
Please wait!
I'm sorry!
Selty!
You came back?!
You can't do that, Doc.
We couldn't contact you during an emergency.
What's wrong, Sonohara-san?
They're not here.
"Not here"?
What?
What did you lose this time, Mikado?
Her shoes are gone.
What? Again?
Some people are so spiteful.
I have a pretty good idea who did this.
Kida-kun.
All right!
Hey, Kida-kun!
Kida-kun was a bit scarier than usual.
Really?
Sheesh, he just ran off.
When I was a kid, I often lost things.
I used to cry and shout, "It's not here!"
And my mom would always help me find it.
Sounds like you have a kind mother.
Yes, my dad is too.
I'm fine.
I'm going to go home.
Thank you for helping me look, Ryuugamine-kun.
Forget it, Kida-kun.
Nope, she went home already.
What? No idea.
Me?
I'm still looking for them.
Anyway, catch you tomorrow.
I found them!
What the hell am I doing?
Strange, isn't it?
I can't remember.
Vacant lots are pretty strange.
When it's gone, you just forget what was there.
There was something here not too long ago.
Something really big...
What am I doing?
I get irritated when Shinra tells me to stop looking for my head.
But having a job and friends...
Do those make me feel human?
So, didn't you want to talk to me?
I remember!
Wasn't there a tall, thin, blue building here?
Oh, that old one?
There was an old woman selling cigarettes on the first floor.
Good catch, transporter.
I can feel my head in this city...
Hello! How is it going?
Me?
I'm searching for beautiful Japanese.
Please tell me what you're desperately looking for.
Can I take a look?
Okay.
I wonder if she met him.
I looked for many things today.
I managed to find some of them, but not all.
Since his bag was gone, I assumed he was at work.
But...
something felt different.
Fireworks?
Yeah.
With a lot of bang.
We put him back together with help from a lot of people.
Just fireworks?
You got some harsh staff.
It's a real pain.
He was blabbering some nonsense.
Apparently his girlfriend was kidnapped,
and she could only remember this place.
He wanted to know what we did to her.
Well, that isn't nonsense; it's the truth.
Can you make it
so that he won't remember anything about us when he wakes up, Doc?
You can't erase memories that conveniently.
Besides, I'll remember him.
We'll send him back.
Maybe to his home, maybe somewhere else.
Doc, the chief and I put our trust in you.
You're still keeping our secret.
Oh yeah, you're living with a rather eccentric person, right?
At that moment, I forgot...
about my head,
and the memories of several hundred years as a Dullahan in my head.
I wasn't thinking of anything.
Just... Just...
Hey, won't you come with me?
If I ask for seats for two people, the restaurant won't complain.
I know a great place.
Please, Selty.
Eating alone is terrible.
What's with this mysterious, avant-garde dish?!
Karaage sushi, cheese sushi, mabo sushi,
prosciutto sushi,
and this is our sour cream sushi.
You don't have to make sushi out of them!
What are you saying?
This is a special set!
It's great service!
So, we got fortune cookies for dessert.
Oh boy.
They have a fortune inside.
Open it.
This is yours.
Let me see.
This means you'll find what you're looking for.
I didn't know you'd be that happy.
I'm so happy, Shinra!
What does yours say?
Mine didn't have one.
I can't cry.
I wonder if my head cries when I'm sad?
Thank you.
I hope not.
I hope I'm smiling.
What's wrong?
You're still afraid...
We're alone.
There's no one there.
Can you remember anything?
You don't have to.
I told you, didn't I?
I don't need your past or future.
Just stay as you are.
We're in the eternity now.
I love you, Selty.
That night, after a long time,
I had a dream where I was whole.
I am here.
Right here.
My love is different.
It's different from the love where the more you seek for it, the more you get spoiled.
It's something more complete.
Next time: Love and Care.
I am what Seiji needs.