Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
2015 A.D.
At 12:30 p.m. today, a special state
of emergency has been declared
for the Toukai region
and the surrounding mid-Kanto area.
All residents, proceed to your designated
evacuation shelter immediately.
I repeat, at 12:30 p.m. today,
a special state of emergency
has been declared
for the Toukai region
and the surrounding mid-Kanto area.
Proceed to your designated…
How could I lose track of him
at a time like this?
I don't believe this…
All phone lines
are currently disabled due to
the special state of emergency.
I can't reach her?
I shouldn't have come.
I'll never make it.
That's that, then.
Might as well head to a shelter.
Unidentified object is continuing
its approach to this facility.
We have visual on target.
Sending to main screen.
It's been 15 years.
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
It's an Angel.
All missiles, direct hit!
Sorry! Been waiting long?
Target unfazed. It is continuing
to advance towards Tokyo-3.
Local air units are unable
to slow its advance!
This is total war. Launch all units
from Atsugi and Iruma as well.
Commit everything we have!
Crush the target at all costs!
This makes no sense!
Those were direct hits!
Our armored battalion has been wiped out.
Guided munitions, bombs,
and artillery are having no effect.
Damn it! This kind of firepower
isn't getting us anywhere!
An A.T. Field?
Yes. Standard weapons
will be useless against the Angels.
Yes, sir. We'll deploy it
according to plan.
They wouldn't…
They're gonna use an N2 land mine?
Get down!
We did it!
Sorry, but your services
weren't required this time.
Shock wave incoming.
Are you okay?
Yes, but I got some sand in my mouth.
Glad to hear it. Okay…
Here we go!
One, two!
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without you.
No, I should be thanking you,
Ms. Katsuragi.
Call me Misato, okay?
It's nice to meet you, Shinji Ikari.
Thank you.
Target's current status?
Target status unknown, EMI too strong.
You saw that explosion!
It must have been obliterated!
Sensors coming back online.
Energy readings at ground zero!
What?
Visual feed back online.
That was our ace in the hole…
This can't be happening.
God-damned monster!
Yes, not to worry.
His protection has top priority.
So have the car shuttle train standing by.
The direct service line.
Right. Well, I am the one
who said I would go meet him.
Man, what a day!
I just had this car restored,
and it's trashed already!
Repair fees, on top of another
33 months of car payments…
Plus, my best outfit is ruined!
-Um, Ms. Misato?
-I got all decked out for today…
-Excuse me, Ms. Misato?
-Yes, what?
Was it okay for you to do that?
Oh, don't worry about it!
This is an emergency!
I had to get the car moving, right?
And I might not look it,
but I'm an international civil servant.
So it's perfectly legit!
Oh, lighten up.
For a kid with such a cute face,
you sure are uptight.
Am I?
Oops! Are you mad?
I'm so sorry! You're a boy, after all.
Actually, you seem a bit childish
for someone your age, Ms. Misato.
As we predicted, it's regenerating?
If it couldn't, it would be worthless
as a standalone weapon.
Very impressive. It's even capable
of enhancing its abilities?
And it's getting smarter.
It's only a matter of time
before it resumes its advance.
Gates closing. Please stay clear.
Special Agency Nerv?
Right. It's a secret organization
directly attached to the UN.
My father works here, doesn't he?
Yup. Do you know
what your father does here?
A teacher told me that he has
the important job of protecting humanity.
As of this moment, you have been
given command over this operation.
-Let's see what you can do.
-Understood, sir.
Ikari, I'll admit that our ordnance
is ineffective against the target.
Can you defeat it, though?
This is what Nerv is for.
Don't let us down.
Target status has not changed.
Current intercept capacity is at 7.5%.
The UN Forces have given up, then?
What do you intend to do?
We'll activate Unit 01.
Unit 01? But there's no pilot.
Not a problem.
The spare pilot will arrive shortly.
Will we be going to see my father?
Yes, I think so.
Father…
Oh, right! Did your father
send you any ID forms?
Yes.
Here.
Thanks.
COME HERE!
-GENDOH IKARI
Read through this, okay?
"Welcome to Nerv"?
My father's work…
Am I supposed to do something at Nerv?
There has to be. Otherwise,
Father wouldn't have written to me.
Oh, I see. Dealing with your father
isn't your strong suit, huh?
Just like me, huh?
Wow!
-A bona fide Geo-front!
-That's right.
Over there is our secret base,
Nerv headquarters.
The key to rebuilding the world,
and the last bastion of humanity.
I could swear it was this way.
Closed Central Dogma passages will remain…
Wearing skirts in this place
is a bad idea.
I wonder where Ritsuko went?
I'm sorry, I don't have my bearings yet.
We passed through here already.
Well, not to worry!
Nerv has systems for this very situation.
Paging Project E. Dir., Dr. Ritsuko Akagi
of Technology Division Section 1.
Dr. Ritsuko Akagi.
Please contact Capt. Misato Katsuragi
of Operations Division Section 1.
I don't believe it.
She's lost again, isn't she?
Oops! Hi, Ritsuko!
Where have you been, Capt. Katsuragi?
We're short on both manpower and time.
Sorry!
This is the boy?
Yep. He's the Third Children
reported by the Marduk Institute.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, yes, ma'am.
That's another way
that he takes after his father.
A total lack of charm.
Take care of things here.
They haven't seen each other
in three years.
Deputy Commander,
the target has begun moving again.
Very well. All personnel
to condition one battle stations.
I repeat, condition one battle stations!
Prepare for ground intercept.
-Hear that?
-This sounds bad.
So, how is Unit 01?
It's being cooled down
in its Type B Configuration.
Is that thing really going to work?
It's hasn't worked once, right?
Success rate of activation is
0.000000001%.
Calling it the 0-9 System
was certainly appropriate.
Doesn't that mean it won't work?
Don't be rude. It's not 0%.
Sure, numerically.
Ah, well. We don't exactly have
the luxury of accepting failure.
Um, I can't see a thing!
A face? A giant robot!
You won't find this
in the orientation book.
This is the ultimate multipurpose decisive
combat weapons system created by man.
The Artificial Human Evangelion.
Unit 01 of the series.
Built in complete secrecy,
this is mankind's very last trump card.
-This is part of my father's work?
-Correct.
It's been a while.
Father…
Launch the Eva.
Launch the Eva?
But Unit 00 is still grounded!
Wait, you want to use Unit 01?
There's no other choice.
Wait just a second!
Rei's in no condition for that!
It's got no pilot!
He just arrived.
Are you serious?
-Shinji Ikari.
-Yes?
You're going to pilot it.
But it took even Rei Ayanami seven months
to synchronize with her Eva!
He literally just got here!
He couldn't possibly do it!
All I ask is that he sit in the cockpit.
Nothing more.
But…
Repelling that Angel
is our number one priority right now.
For that, we need anyone capable of
synchronizing with an Eva to try,
however remote the chances.
I shouldn't need to tell you this,
Capt. Katsuragi.
You're right.
Father… Why did you send for me?
For the reason you're thinking.
So you want me to get inside this
and fight that thing out there?
Correct.
I don't want to do that!
Why send for me after all this time?
I thought you left me
because you didn't need me!
I do now, so I sent for you.
But why me?
Because it's impossible for anyone else.
It is for me, too. I've never seen
or heard of this thing before.
I can't possibly do it!
Learn how.
That's… That's impossible!
There's no way I can pilot this!
If you're going to pilot it, do it.
Otherwise, get out!
That bastard must have figured out
where we are.
Shinji, we don't have much time.
Get in.
No way. I just got here! This is crazy!
Tell me, Shinji. Why did you come?
Don't run away! Not from your father,
and especially not from yourself.
I know! But there's no way I can do this!
Fuyutsuki.
Wake up Rei.
Is she viable?
She isn't dead.
Understood.
-Rei?
-Yes?
The backup isn't working out.
I need you again.
Yes, sir.
Rewrite Unit 01's core system
for Rei! Reactivate!
Roger. Suspending current tasks
and initiating reactivation.
I knew it… No one wants me.
Look out!
-The Eva moved!
-What the hell?
Its right arm broke free
of its restraints!
What? That can't be!
It doesn't have an entry plug inserted!
It's incapable of moving!
It reacted without any
interface connection?
Or was it trying… to protect him?
This will work.
Don't run away.
I'll do it. I'll be the pilot!
-Cooling cycle complete!
-Right arm reattachment complete.
All gear inside cage
is in docked position.
Shutdown signal plug extraction complete.
Roger. Inserting entry plug.
-Plug locked in position.
-Initiating level one connection.
Flooding entry plug.
Huh? What is this stuff?
Don't worry,
once your lungs are filled with LCL,
it will feed oxygen
directly into your bloodstream.
You'll get used to it in no time.
This is so gross.
Deal with it! You're a big boy!
-Main power connection complete!
-Feeding power to all circuits!
Roger!
Initiating level two contact.
Cognitive configuration
base rules set to Japanese.
Initial contact shows all green.
Opening bilateral circuit.
Synchronization rate at 41.3%.
-Amazing…
-Harmonics are all at normal levels.
-No signs of a runaway.
-We're good to go!
Prepare for launch!
Release lockdown bolt no. 01!
Release confirmed!
Initiating umbilical bridge retraction!
Release lockdown bolt no. 02!
Retracting primary restraining frame.
Removing secondary
restraining frame, as well.
Disengaging safety systems one through 15.
Internal power source, fully charged.
External power source connecter
shows green.
Roger. Transport Eva-01 to launch bay.
Launch path clear! All stations green!
Launch preparations complete!
Roger that!
-Do we have a go, sir?
-Absolutely.
Unless we defeat the Angels,
humanity has no future.
Ikari, you're really sure about this?
Launch!
Shinji… don't die.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
The Eva defeats the Angel,
but that was just the beginning.
Shinji runs away from his father.
Misato's arrogance makes her
decide to try to save him.
Next episode! "Unfamiliar Ceilings"!
Tune in next time
for lots more fan service!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming