A... ki... ra...
That was nasty, Aki-lovely.
Milulun's so scared.
I have to... continue battling...
Huh?
Selector battle...
Oh...?
What's your wish?
For Urith's... scar...
...to heal quickly...
No problem-lun!
Aki-lucky...
Taken and granted,
ideals are repetitious games that slip through
My daily life is so shot with holes
that I can barely stand
Empty theories without conclusions
Dance steps along invisible rules
The final bell holding together
the crumbling day rings
In the scene I imagine
you're there
with a smile
No forgiveness? No desires?
And still
We cry "OPEN"
A future to get back and a world to destroy
A wish to open. GOT IT?
Now cross
I wish you don't cry
The future of light and dark,
let's believe in the "future"
so that they overlap to gain color again
Hitoe, are you all right?
"Re: Sorry for making you worried"
Does it hurt anywhere?
No, I'm fine. I was just surprised back there.
I'm sorry. It's my fault...
No, I'm sorry, too.
--Ruko, I made you go through all that pain.
--But...!
I brought back Iona-san's
bitter memories, too...
How softhearted can you get?
Huh?
We were originally made by Mayu.
So you can say that we created Selector battles.
But in the first place, Mayu--
You girls have every right to hate me!
And yet, the words you say are...
This Mayu person shouldn't be forgiven...
...I think, but...
Before becoming friends with Ruko and Yuzuki,
the days I spent were excruciating.
When I took a stroll, everyone
around me seemed happy...
...and it felt like I was the
only lonely one in the world.
But, after hearing what Iona-san said...
...I understand now, how Mayu
couldn't even feel what loneliness is.
That's it...
Maybe that's it...
About what?
Mayu's... real wish.
Real wish...?
It... felt weird to me...
...as to why Mayu made the rules to
the Selector battles like how it is now.
The girl who wins has their wish
taken away, and is sealed into a card.
That's horrible, but it felt
a bit different from revenge...
Well... things are fine when
we're talking like this, but...
...being in the card is... pretty lonely.
Really...
...lonely.
Maybe Mayu wants to have everyone
know how it really feels to be lonely...
Yuzuki...
I'm sorry I made you feel like that!
Yuzuki, from now on I'll hold you
close to me, even when I go to sleep!
Aah! I'm okay!
C'mon, stop holding me!
Iona...
Unbelievable...
Huh?
With all that everyone went through...
...no one is thinking badly about Mayu.
Well, that's not entirely true...
I think we feel like how we feel now...
...because of Tama and you, Iona.
I mean, if Tama and Iona
together is like Mayu...
...it's hard to imagine
Mayu is really a bad person.
Tama... and me?
Tama and Iona are our friends, right?
Then I believe that Mayu would
understand if we spoke from our hearts.
My heart... aches...
It must be from this feeling I hold,
despite being the LRIG of dark.
But, even if it aches, this feeling...
...is so warm.
I want to embrace this feeling...
Weird... Weird...
This is so weird!
Kuro's not the same anymore.
Selector battles...
...need intense light and deep darkness.
Let's burn the useless LRIG card of dark.
Okay, Shiro?
I can't believe the pampering...
A private hospital room for this measly wound?
As expected from the Urazoe Family...
Are you okay, Urith?
It's just a small wound.
Say, mind if I ask you something?
Huh?
Iona passed through many
Selectors' hands as an LRIG of dark.
Where were you until you
ended up as Ru's card?
Well, Tama was...
...with Ru before I knew it.
I forgot about Mayu and
everything that happened...
...but after meeting Ru...
...I felt that Tama was born
because I wanted to meet Ru.
I see...
I know just how Mayu feels.
Huh?
You're like vomit, so Mayu
wanted to get rid of you.
She was disgusted by the hypocritical desire
for light that clung like scum to her heart...
That's why she put you into Ruko's hands first.
After all, she is a terrifying girl.
A girl who can destroy everything...
Chiyori? What next?
What do you mean?
Even if I know the truth behind
the battles, I'm not giving up-y!
I'm gonna go to the next battle-y!
Aren't you going to do your usual stuff?
Such evil...
Huh?
Chiyori pretty much knows how
these Selector battles work now!
Win or lose, only hell waits...
You're the type who can
calmly toss someone into
that kind of inescapable,
incessant hell, Eldora!
Heheh... Well, you've got to protect yourself.
But, come on, remember what you said?
Chiyori, your wish is to enter
the world of WIXOSS, right?
Works out perfect, you know?
You're right...
But if Chiyori loses again,
I won't be able to battle anymore...
Well, no use dwelling on it.
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it.
I guess...
Speaking of, you were
once a human, right Eldora?
What was your wish then?
Huh?
Aah...
...I forgot.
Liar!
Yeah, I'm lying.
Like, I don't want to tell you, Chiyori.
Why you...!
Yup, nothing special at all.
Now that I think about it,
the wish was really nothing.
But, I guess I was serious about it back then.
In any case, we need to
speak with Tama-chan, right?
But, Hitoe...
...are you okay meeting Urith?
That's right.
Ruko and I can go without you.
No...
After all, this is to meet Tama-chan.
That's--
"New Mail"
"1"
Maybe it's Urith!
Please battle me!
Huh?
It doesn't matter which of
you two I face, so please!
W-Wait! Chiyori-san,
if you lose once more, then...
Justice will prevail!
So... that means, I'm evil?
You still don't understand after seeing Fumio?
Well then...
...how about doing it with me?
Come on...
...battle me...
I sense an unusual, evildoer aura...
A-Akira-san!
Oh, okay.
Huh?!
C'mon, let's do this.
Hey, Eldora! What are you doing,
making a call without the Selector!
Oh? Are you scared of losing?
Heck no!
All right-y then! Let's battle!
Chiyori's gonna win this easy!
No...!
No way!
No!
Wait... Wa...
Wait the hell up!
Bastards...!
What?
Akira-san isn't going to... chase us, right?
Hey!
What gives?!
Why'd you get in my way?!
But...!
If you really want to battle,
then we won't stop you...
...but at least be a bit more
selective of who you--
It doesn't matter who we face.
What?
Yup! No matter who I face,
Chiyori's gonna win, y'know?
Oh? Pretty bold, coming from
someone who lost twice already.
Hmph! Once Chiyori wins,
it's gonna be bye-bye to Eldora!
Oh yes, that's good news indeed!
Wha...?! Why you...!
I'll... battle Chiyori-san.
--Wha...?!
--Huh?!
Chiyori lost twice already! Anymore and...
...you know what's going to happen, right?
A reversal of her wish.
Hitoe...
I understand.
I'm going to do this, because
Chiyori-san is only one loss away.
What?
Don't tell me you're
planning to give her a win.
No.
Before my wish got reversed with
my third loss, Midoriko said to me...
Hitoe!
Please! Get rid of me!
Midoriko... wished for me
to be with friends forever...
...at the cost of having
a chance to be human again.
My wish...
...is a wish that I thought would
make me happy when fulfilled.
But, Chiyori-san's wish is...
Aah! Just shut it!
"Shut it" is my line!
Once Chiyori becomes heroine of the WIXOSS
world, your time of punishment will come!
Oh, yeah? Bring it!
I see. If seeing Fumio didn't get
through to her, then we may as well...
If Chiyori-san wins,
then it's another story, but...
...if I win, I can prevent her wish.
Well, it does bother me what would
happen if her wish got reversed...
Chiyori-san's wish is based on
her attachment to WIXOSS...
...so if it's just a matter of
her forgetting about WIXOSS...
...then it shouldn't make
her situation any worse.
Augh! Now Chiyori's mad!
I'm gonna win for real! This'll really be
the last time I'll be with you, Eldora!
Whatever.
--Um...
--Huh?
I can battle you, Chiyori-san.
Huh?
Yay! Battle-y!
Finally, finally!
The historic moment to be inscribed,
the first step to the birth of a heroine
of the WIXOSS world!
"Authorized construction workers only"
Let's begin.
I can't wait!
Open!
A battlefield opened...
Looks like there are others who, at
this very moment, are seeking battles.
Are you... going to battle?
Doesn't it hurt?
Well, of course it hurts. Just a little.
But soon the pain will go away.
I'm... going to win the battle.
I've stacked sufficient wins, so just
one more will make my wish come true.
I'll become an LRIG again.
And you...
...will gain Urazoe Iona's
body and come outside.
Tama... into Iona...?
You want to be on equal terms
as friends with Ruko, right?
Isn't that your wish?
If so, our interests are mutual.
If we win the battle,
this body will be yours.
You can be friends with Ru, not as an LRIG,
but as a fellow human being.
Here we go!
Chiyori Moonlight Chorizo!
Say the correct name of the move!
Not bad, Chorizo!
Are you okay, Yuzuki?
No problem!
We can't lose this battle after all.
Yup.
Yuzuki! Grow!
Both Eldora and Yuzuki are strong.
But the match is pretty much decided...
Yup...
Yuzuki's deck is red-themed, and contains
cards with the ability to shave Ener.
The odds are really against
Chiyori-san winning, right?
Chiyori probably doesn't know that.
But... there's no way Eldora,
as an LRIG, doesn't know that.
Wait...
No... I'm going to lose...
If this keeps up, I'm going to lose...!
Chiyori! Your command!
B-But, but...
It's okay even if you lose, y'know?
Huh?
You're going to retire from Selector battles...
...and go back to being a normal girl.
Eldora-san...
I knew it... Eldora was thinking
of the same thing as Hitoe!
To save Chiyori-san from the painful battles...
Wh-What are you saying, Eldora?!
Excuse me!
Um, I know it's out of place
to ask this during battle, but...
...even if I lose, can you be friends with her?
Wha...?!
She's dressed loony now, but back when
I first met her, she was, like, super modest.
H-Hey! Eldora!
Th-The card spoke...?
My name is Eldora.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Hm?
So cute...!
Super cute!
Shh...!
Say, look at this! It's so Eldora!
Trying to mimic me?
That, "I gotta be like the other girls"
mentality is kinda creepy.
Aww, come on. If you don't like that,
then wear something else, Eldora!
I'm just paper, so... nope!
Okay! Then Chiyori's gonna use
a marker to draw... your clothes!
Haah?!
Time to draw!
Stop it!
She can be a handful,
but I was glad she was my Selector.
She's a bit soft on the top,
but she really isn't bad or anything.
Eldora...
From the very beginning... you were
planning to lose, weren't you?
E-Eldora?!
I thought we couldn't win, that's all.
Not like LRIGs can sway
the end results or anything.
That's mean! You didn't tell Chiyori that!
Here comes the evil you again, Eldora!
--Why you...!
--Sure, evil. Like you said, I'm evil.
--Take this!
That's why...
...we shouldn't be together.
Huh?!
I was glad I became your LRIG, but only once.
You're so optimistic, stupid, dim-witted...
...and really carefree.
Eldora...?
I...
...just want you to stay like that, y'know?
Eldora...
Now then, Yuzuki-san.
Let's get this over with!
What's next? Orochi?
You've got enough of them Eners,
so how about going all out with Arts?
Hold it!
Chiyori...?
It's... It's not over yet!
Chiyori's brain, get working!
Think of a way to turn the tables!
If I don't, then...
...I'm gonna get separated from Eldora!
Ah...! I got it!
Huh?
Check their Life Cloth with Spell: PLUS RUSH!
Direct damage using Arts: Cloth Crash Flash!
Chiyori... that attack...
Go...!
...is meaningless.
Huh...?
Our attacks aren't going to
get through to Hitoe-san now.
If Chiyori doesn't pull a Shiira
within 3 turns, Hitoe-san will win.
Eldora-san...
Now hold on! Don't you try
to make yourself lose here.
I want to return back into a human, y'know?
But, if I'm stuck with an
unskilled person like Chiyori...
...that'll never come true.
Eldora...
Now, let's keep going, Chiyori.
If you can put a Burst into play,
there's a chance of winning.
Turn end.
Orochi! Echidna!
Attack!
Eldora!
It's your turn, Chiyori...
No... No! Eldora!
Chiyori's not going to forget...!
Turn end.
I'm never, ever going to forget!
Because, Eldora...!
When Chiyori gets inside WIXOSS,
I'm making you Chiyori's subordinate!
Orochi... Attack...
Eldoraaa...!
Chiyori...
Hurry...
This is the last turn...
N-No...
Chiyori!
Chiyori...
I really... liked you.
Turn end.
This is the end.
Now, to wait for the finishing blow...
You're late, Aki-lovely...
That ain't me now...
Right now, I'm Aoi Akira...
The one who will beat and save you...
"That Abrupt Separation"
...Aoi Akira.
Life...
A city of mazes with no exit
and the sound of bells ringing
I do...
Leave the "now" handed to me
as I begin to walk in the morning
In a world where light and dark intersect
catharsis begins to awake
I swore in my shaking heart
that I won't lose anyone anymore...!
Even if my tears flow tomorrow
I'll run through the wind
Release myself towards the future I selected
to regain it
I won't give up on my wish
Shut up... Shut up... Shut up...!
What...? That's wrong...
That's absolutely wrong!
Otherwise, that's absolutely
and completely wrong!
"This Warmth Is at Its Limit"
This Warmth Is at Its Limit.