When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
My name is Hayate.
The Earth is under attack.
And so is your life.
Hey, it's Isumi.
You were surprisingly fast.
I was worried that you might have been lost again.
I am sorry I made you worry.
But I did get lost, so no concerns there.
Ah, I see.
The person, who I presume
is your new butler, brought me here.
You met Hayate?
He was wearing a brand new cashmere jacket.
Yes, that does sound like Hayate-kun.
But if you do not hurry, he might die.
Did Hayate get caught up in another mess?
It's highly possible.
Oh no, Hayate is in a pinch. We need to go save him, Maria.
Maybe I shouldn't have made him wear something he wasn't used to wearing.
U-Umm...
Because he's sick...
Cashmere jacket, eh? Let's go, Maria!
Yes, indeed.
It's the biggest crisis he's faced yet since becoming a butler.
Man, I have to do something about this jacket,
or else I won't be able to go back to the mansion, ever.
Maybe I'll borrow some money and get a new jacket.
No, that won't solve anything.
Hey, Ayasaki!
It's been a while.
Y-You're...
The very kind people who tried to take me to the southern paradise.
Don't say such embarrassing stuff out loud in the middle of the city.
So you were still alive, eh?
Y-Yes.
But you know, business aside, I like people like you.
Well, this must be some fate, so how about I treat you to lunch-
There he is!
Hey Ayasaki, what are they?
Don't even have to ask. They're mafia.
I see. Same bunch as us.
I knew you were suspicious from the beginning; so you were associated with them.
No!
Hey four-eyes. You got something to do with our son here?
When did I become part of you?
I see. So you're eager to see some blood, are you?
I don't know what group you're from, but you've got some nerve.
Hey, I just noticed, but aren't I in big trouble here?
At this rate, I'll be scolded not by Maria-san but by the government.
Above all, I might cause trouble to Milady.
I must get out of this somehow.
Hey, where do you think you're going, Ayasaki?
You're not planning to abandon
your group to get away, are you?
So when did I become a part of your group?
What? Abandoning your group to get out of the mess unscathed alone?
You call yourself human?
What a cold-hearted guy.
I'm going to get criticized from that side, too?
Looks like we have...
...No choice but to do him in.
Ah, I see.
I'm going to die today.
Today is a great day.
If I knew this was going to happen, I should have apologized to Maria-san when I'd made it back to the mansion.
Yeah, if I can make it out of this alive, I'll apologize to her.
Get him!
Here I come!
What are you stalling for! Let's go!
We're talking about Hayate here. If we don't go fast,
he might get stabbed by many swords!
That can't possibly happen.
But the new jacket must be torn to pieces.
It can't be. Don't underestimate Hayate.
No, the jacket already is torn apart.
I see. That's indeed our Hayate.
The jacket got ruined because of me,
yet he looked quite troubled.
He must take his job as your butler that seriously.
After hearing that, we can't scold him
too much for ruining the jacket, can we?
I wasn't planning to from the start.
Speak of the devil. He must be back.
Oh well.
Thank goodness. I made it back alive.
You can't yell at Hayate, okay, Maria?
We need to welcome him back warmly.
If you say so.
Come to think of, did Hayate say anything about me?
Like, "cute" or "adorable" or...
Let's see... Um...
If I remember correctly,
"Little, stubborn, selfish, and sometimes goes wild..."
I've just returned.
Milady-
Wh-Why?!
Why are you shutting me out, Milady?
Shut up! Idiot! Idiot!
Seriously. What's wrong with him.
"...But kind and cute."
I think it's better to say that earlier.
And so the debt-filled butler's life ends.
P-Please, don't joke like that.
It's hot.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
38.9°C.
He definitely has a fever.
Even though the cold front came in all of a sudden, to catch a cold...
You can't possibly be that weak.
I am not sure if he is weak or not,
but after getting shut out under the cold sky with the drenched clothes for hours,
I'm sure anyone would catch a cold.
~stare~
*stare*
Wh-What? You talk as if I'm the bad person!
Are you in pain, Hayate-kun?
Very.
*stare*
~stare~
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Don't stare at me like Kenshi*** that awakened from the Dream Reincarnation style.
You can't do anything about catching a fever. Get a good rest.
Ah... Yes.
It's a milk shake.
It'll warm you up.
Thank you very much.
Oh no. Although Nagi shutting you out was the final blow,
I was the original cause.
In Isumi's mind, she's supporting Nagi.
Yes, Milady did give me the deathblow, but...
So you go to the same school as Milady.
I'm sorry about the great misunderstanding I had.
Please don't worry.
Thank you for this.
Yes, I hope you like it.
Wow, this is really good.
I'm glad you like it.
You made this, right?
You must be a good cook.
I'm not sure if I am good or not,
but I am a girl, after all, so...
It's wrong to think that you have
to cook because you're a girl, Isumi!
With such an old concept,
you can't live in this world of information.
Whenever you use complicated words, you're trying to mislead someone.
You know her well.
Anyways, 21st century has all sexes treated equally and no borders for all.
With that said, you haven't had lunch yet, have you, Hayate?
Ah, no.
Then I shall put all my effort to specially cook you porridge.
Eh?
You have a problem?
Are you saying you don't want to eat my cooking?
No, I meant my heart is filled with gratitude.
Good. Then prepare yourself as you wait.
I've read all of Mr.**** and Go****,
so there is no dish that I can't cook!
Come, Tama!
What's with that worrisome noise you're making?
Then I'll go get you a digestive medicine.
Good luck, Hayate-sama.
Y-Yes.
And this is how Lady Nagi's nursing started.
Since Milady is so full of confidence,
nothing that bad will come out, will it?
Hayate didn't feel like he would get better anytime soon.
Hey Saku, you were still here?
I was absorbed watching Down Town's DVD box, so I became hungry.
Then I'm about to start cooking, so I'll let you have a taste of it.
Oh yeah, I had other DVDs I had to watch.
Where are you going?
But since I'm going through the trouble of cooking, I'd like to make it a unique taste; one you can't find anywhere else.
This is the first mistake that people who suck at cooking fall into.
Something with a distinct taste...
Vinegar's good for the health, right?
Crap. No matter how many lives I may carry, Nagi's cooking would take them all away.
Hayate might just die.
What do you think, Sakuya?
What?
I'm sorry, Isumi-san.
I mean, for Hayate-kun causing trouble in many ways.
Oh please, trouble?
But he indeed is the person Nagi chose.
He was so kind to me.
Did Hayate-kun give her a virus more complicating than fever?
Irasshaimase Goshujin-sama!
Irasshaimase Goshujin-sama! = Welcome, Master!
Mah, mah, mah. = Now, now, now.
Mah, mah, mah.
It's ready, Hayate.
I'm confident about the result, so enjoy it.
Hey, it actually looks good.
This might just be...
Ah, thank you.
Th-This isn't anything like the level of too salty or too much vinegar or not cooked completely.
I detect a faint odor of dish detergent.
What's wrong, Hayate?
You can't call this food...
Um, could it be that it's not good?
At times, men have to tough things out.
It's delicious.
Audience in front of the TV, you must not copy him.
Because dish detergent is neither food nor drink.
R-Really? That's great!
I didn't taste it myself, so I was worried,
but it's good, eh?
Yes, it's perfect, Milady.
The tiny bit of oil that I added must have done the job.
Oh, I see.
There's plenty more, so dig in.
It's great!
Oh my ********!
You're such a glutton.
To meet the master's expectations.
That's a butler's job.
Did she add this thinking it was oil?
To meet the master's expectations.
That's a pet's job.
Th-Thank you for the food.
Wow, you ate it clean.
You must have been really hungry.
I'll go clean this out, so you go back to resting.
Y-Yes, Sir.
I've gone through a lot of misery in my life,
but today, it's worse than ever.
If you push yourself too much, you'll really die.
Maria-san.
Really, I'm amazed that you ate all of that.
She added dish soap instead of oil, didn't she?
Well, yes.
But it was a dish that Milady made for me,
and I was happy to be nursed.
Your mother wouldn't nurse you when you got sick?
Whether I was sick or injured,
my mother would ignore me and invest in her dreams.
Envelope: Lunch Money
Wow...
How can he tell such a story so casually?
In any case, have a good night's sleep.
Yes, my eyelids are closing.
Then goodnight.
Hayate.
Thank you.
Um, what are you doing, Milady?
Um, if you're so up close to me, it's hard to fall asleep.
Shut up! Idiot Hayate! Idiot!
What? Milady?
Shut up, idiot!
You often hear kind people die sooner, but I think I see it now.
That concluded the poverty stricken butler's worst day ever.
However...
After a good night's sleep, I'm all better.
I couldn't do anything yesterday, so I've got a lot to do today.
Good morning.
Eh?
Ah... Yes, good morning.
It's a nice day outside, so it's a perfect day to do laundry.
Eh? Ah, yes, it is.
Look at this. You're the Sanzenin butler, and you have a crooked tie?
You must be mindful of your attire
so you don't embarrass your master.
Well then...
Good da-
U-Um!
Who was she?
Suspicious person inside the mansion?
Yes, she was wearing a maid outfit different from yours and had glasses on.
Any other traits?
Let's see...
She looks really capable at glance,
but she's definitely an all-natural character.
Ah, I see.
You don't need to worry about her, so please get started with your morning cleaning duties.
Oh, and I think there's another guest around,
so if you see him, please take him to the guest room.
Y-Yes, I will.
Tachibana is here?
Yes. Saki-san seems to be here,
so security must have let them through.
Klaus, it's me.
We have unwanted guests in the mansion.
Send them out.
Yes, by all means!
If it means no fatalities, then I allow you to use guns, as well.
Um...
Anyways, eliminate them right away! That's all.
You don't have to kick them out...
But I don't want Hayate to know.
She said there's another guest, but...
I wish the Earth would come to an end.
Wh-Who is this boy that's mumbling something really dangerous?
U-Um...
Uh? Who are you?
Don't talk to me with that poor-man's face, idiot!
Um... Um...
Oh, I get it. This snobbish brat must be
the guest Maria-san was talking about.
This sucks.
I'm so bored, so could you dive into this lake?
Sure.
Ehhh?!
Gotcha.
If you're a butler, be able to dodge that.
If you're that weak, you can't protect your master.
H-Hold on a moment please.
What, you have a problem with me?
No, I was told to see the guest to
the guest room when I found him.
Wow, you've not going to get mad after I did this to you?
I'm used to it.
Sir, this is where you were?
Why do you care where I am?
Sir?
By the way, Sir, a question.
If you want to ask about this guy, I don't know anything.
No, I wanted to ask what that machine behind you is.
Robot: Security 8801
What? It's floating in the air.
M**** Drive?
Target confirmed.
Eliminating at once.
Elimination.
Elimination! Elimination!
What is that thing?
I asked you because I don't know!
I don't know about the Sanzenin's stupid robots!
Target confirmed!
Crap, from the front, too.
I don't know what's going on, but as the Sanzenin's butler, I must see the guests to the guest room safely.
Hold on tight!
You-
Please don't worry. As the Sanzenin's butler,
I will assure your safety.
I mean, don't hold us with your soaking clothes!
Y-Yes.
T-To touch a girl's body so nonchalantly...
You're so lecherous!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please, don't move around so much in mid-air.
I did ask you to bring them to the guest room, but...
You didn't have to bring them though the roof.
I-I'm sorry.
I said it's cold.
Please let go of me already.
What are you going to do if I can't get married?
So, who are these two?
He's Tachibana Wataru-kun.
He's Nagi's...
...fiancé.
Heh?
The boy who visited Nagi.
Wataru, and his maid, Saki.
And Isumi.
Is Wataru really Nagi's fiancé?
The plot is starting to move.
Next time, we'll be fighting against the Tokyo Underground!
Oh, hold on, forgot one person.
You got to be kidding me.
Why the heck!
To be continued.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Hello, I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
This corner that started today. What exactly happens here?
This corner is meant to follow Hayate's endeavors in fighting against evil as he becomes a great butler.
Great evil?
By the way, what's the song in the background?
Yes, this is my image song made by a famous composer.
It's filled with my resolution to protect you.
Is it? Well I'm counting on you, Hayate.
Yes, Milady.
Bye bye.
You're Nagi's new butler, right?
Yes, my name is Ayasaki Hayate.
How about a little duel before we have breakfast?
Um, is dueling a standard pre-breakfast activity for celebrities?
I'm not sure, but he probably just wants to show off.
Just deck him good.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Man's Fight.
You ready, stupid butler?
Take this!
Lots of fan service next time, too!