[YOKO]
It's not so... bad.
I thought it was kind of
a weird name to begin with.
[YAMAJI] And if any boys so
much as look at Miss Yoko
--the wrong way...
--[YU] Yoko!
[YAMAJI] ...they'll have
to answer to my trusty bat.
[FUTABA]
Look, there it is! The ocean!
[YOKO]
It's so beautiful!
[FUTABA] It's not really summer
until you go to the beach.
[HAYAMA] This was so
worth waking up early.
I've never taken a
train to the beach before.
It makes it feel more like we're
on an adventure or something.
You usually get here by limo?
Or helicopter?
What'll we do
once we're there?
Lie on the beach and
look up at the clouds!
Make sandcastles and
catch up on some reading!
Eat ice cream and watermelon!
[ALL laugh]
Or maybe not.
Not so much.
[FUTABA]
Well, ladies...
I guess it's time
for us to get to work.
[SHINO] It's summer.
Summer means the ocean.
The ocean means a good
old fashioned beach hut.
So I present to you,
Secret Garden, beach hut style.
Have a bite of paradise.
[ALL sigh]
I can't believe we traveled
all this way just to work.
At least the
scenery's nicer here.
[SHINO]
We should be pretty busy.
Thanks to Mitsugu, I was
able to get a prime location.
[FUTABA]
Of course it was him.
[HAYAMA]
He does "live to serve," eh?
[SHINO]
We're still setting things up,
but it should be ready
to open tomorrow.
[HAYAMA]
Awesome. Can't wait.
[FUTABA]
I'm curious, though.
What are you going to call
it now that it's out here?
'Cause it's not really
a garden anymore, right?
Secret Garden: Beach-Hut Style!
[FUTABA, HAYAMA]
Well... Uh...
[HAYAMA]
I'm not so sure about that.
Doesn't have a great ring to it.
Do you think it's
a good name, Yoko?
Be nice or it's back
to the bread crust diet.
Uh, well... It's not so bad...
I mean, to be totally honest,
I thought it was kind of
a weird name to begin with.
It is a classic story,
and I can't believe
you've never heard of it.
Well, if that's
what you're going for,
Little Shop of Horrors
might be more appropriate.
Or maybe Little Women .
Very funny.
Can we all please move on now?
We were only
trying to be helpful.
Yes, that's all.
I don't need
your help, thank you.
[YAMAJI laughs]
You can forget about
changing her mind,
because she's as
stubborn as she is tiny.
Oh, Yamaji.
So you're not a fan
of the name either?
No.
It's always seemed
strange to me.
I never got what a garden
had to do with cakes.
Let's just drop it.
We're opening the beach hut
version of Secret Garden,
and that's that.
[YOKO]
Um... Sorry.
I do still have one question,
if you don't mind.
You keep saying "beach hut."
What's that?
[BOTH gasp]
[HAYAMA]
Are you serious?
[FUTABA] You've never
heard of a beach hut?
[YAMAJI]
Let's be nice!
It's not her fault she
doesn't know these things.
[SHINO] The rich are oblivious
to the world around them.
It's not that I've never
heard of a beach hut before.
I simply don't know
what one is exactly,
or how it's supposed to look.
It's up to you to tell me
precisely what a beach hut is!
Using interpretive dance!
I am waves.
I am wind.
This is hopeless.
I can't form a
picture in my mind.
How can I work at a
place I don't understand?
[SHINO]
Sand! I am the sand.
[HAYAMA]
I'm totally lost.
[FUTABA] Just when you thought
she couldn't get weirder.
Well, um, we came
all the way out here
to work, right?
I don't know about you two,
but I was kind of looking
forward to the extra money.
I suppose I'll just
do my best, then.
[HAYAMA] Now that that's
settled, let's get changed.
[YOKO]
Yeah, that's a good idea.
[FUTABA]
I brought some cute outfits!
I gotta tell ya, I'm not
totally the biggest fan
of this stupid beach
hut idea of yours.
I don't see what's
so great about sunburns
and sand in your shoes.
And if any boys so much
as look at Miss Yoko
the wrong way, they'll have to
answer to my trusty bat!
Will they?
I'm sure they're terrified.
I dunno, what do you think?
What should I do?
[FUTABA]
Yum! What is this?
It's delicious! Wow!
It's like a party in my mouth!
Mmm! I don't know.
Should I try the melon
or the orange next?
It's impossible to decide.
I want them all!
I wonder what that
girl's eating over there.
[GIRL 6A]
Whatever it is, I want some!
Please! Could she
be any more obvious?
You should have let me
be the fake customer.
I would've done a better
job than that ham.
I appreciate her enthusiasm.
[YAMAJI] There are bound to
be a bunch of handsy boys
flocking to Miss Yoko.
I'm going to need
all the help I can get
keeping them at a safe distance.
Somehow, I don't think
that's gonna be an issue.
[SHINO sighs]
[YOKO]
That was a pretty big sigh.
Is something bothering you?
Well, you don't
exactly look like
I thought you were going to.
[YOKO]
I don't?
No. I was thinking more...
[SHINO]
Summer!
Splashing under the bright sun!
Three girls reveling in
their youthful bodies!
[SHINO] The sweet lure
of unblemished flesh.
Rivaled only by the sweetness
of the shop's wares.
Secret Garden, beach hut-style!
Open this summer.
Come and join the fun! Mwah!
You know, something like that.
[YOKO]
No way!
As if I would let you
flaunt her body like that!
And that whole
disguise bit at the end
was just plain embarrassing.
Could you at least wear
a cute little tank top
or shorts, maybe?
[YOKO] And wind up with
funny-looking tan lines?
I'll pass.
Someone needs to
compensate for the lack of skin
Miss Yoko is showing.
Hayama, I'm changing your
uniform to a bikini!
[HAYAMA] If it's so important,
change your own outfit!
[FUTABA] You keep calling
this place a beach hut,
but it feels more
like a fancy café.
[SHINO] Beach-hut inspired,
with a more elevated cuisine.
Gelato, frappes, and
other fancy desserts.
[FUTABA]
What about ramen?
And curry! And fried noodles?
[SHINO] That would be silly.
We're a dessert shop.
I eat fried noodles
for dessert all the time.
[SHINO]
You would.
[YOKO] Come to Secret Garden:
Beach-Hut Style!
[HAYAMA] Open today!
Secret Garden: Beach-Hut Style!
[FUTABA] Secret Garden:
Beach-Hut Style!
Drop on in!
[FUTABA]
Ah, man.
The name's just too complicated.
No wonder people
aren't interested.
Maybe we should try
a different spot?
[FUTABA]
What's that?
[YU]
Yoko! I'm coming!
Yoko!
[GIRLS]
Uh...
[GIRLS shriek]
[YU]
Yoko!
Why're you here?
I heard you were
working at a beach hut,
and I wanted to show my support,
so I came as fast as I could.
I'll take one of
everything, please!
I don't know if
you want to do that.
There's a big menu and it's
all frozen desserts.
[YU]
Oh, really?
I dunno if I could eat it all.
[FUTABA]
I can help you with that!
She's not kidding.
She eats like a pig.
[YU yells]
Is there such thing as
a permanent brain freeze?
Why not take a break?
You don't have to finish it all.
No!
You made this with
your own hands
and I won't let all your
hard work go to waste!
Sorry it took a little
longer than expected.
It was you?
But I thought Yoko was
making all the desserts.
Nope.
[FUTABA]
What a child.
Messing with a little kid
like that is so immature.
[YAMAJI]
I dunno.
If you ask me, there are worse
things than being immature.
Like being tiny and
evil, for example.
Or like being a stalker.
Or an obsessive
creep with no life.
[SHINO] Since today was
only our soft opening,
I decided to close
the shop early.
Thank you all for
your hard work.
I was happy with our sales,
especially considering
it was just a half-day.
Working on the beach is harder
than I thought it would be.
It's so hot, too!
Stylish turtleneck, by the way.
[SHINO] I thought it would be
nice to celebrate our success
and keep our spirits
high for tomorrow.
How does a barbecue
sound to everybody?
Awesome!
Yeah, thanks!
[YU]
Sure, count me in.
You think that's the
best idea at this point?
[YU]
I'm a man.
This much food is
nothing to me. It's fine.
Especially if you're the one
doing the cooking this time.
All right, everybody!
It's time to eat! Who's hungry?
Jerk!
I think a little barbecue
will brighten your mood.
You really are a jerk.
What was that, ladies?
Did you say something?
If my cooking isn't to
your liking, Master Yu,
I'd be happy to whip
something else up.
[YU] No, don't bother.
I'll just sit this one out.
One more bite and I'd
probably puke, anyway.
Well, I say
bring on the meat!
What about you two?
Absolutely! Bring it on!
[YOKO] There's nothing
better than a good meal
after working all day!
[HAYAMA]
Mm-hmm!
All right, Yamaji! Load me
up with some more veggies,
meat, meat, meat, meat,
meat, meat, and fish!
[YAMAJI groans]
So much for today's profits.
[KOU]
Teru!
Wow, you're grilling?
That looks like fun!
[HAYAMA]
Why are you here?
I figured it must be hard
work getting a new business
up and running.
So I thought I'd come
and offer to help out.
We're done already.
That was nice of her to come
and check in on us, though.
[SHINO] Would you like Mitsugu
to put together a plate for you?
[KOU]
That would be great. Thanks!
The little cutie's here!
[YU]
Hi again!
You're not eating anything?
That's not good.
A young boy like you
needs plenty of food
to keep your strength up.
I know! You wait here.
I'll make some for you!
[stomach gurgling]
Uh... Thanks.
That sounds great.
Poor thing.
I think this might
be what breaks him.
[FUTABA] Eh, it's just
a little barbecue.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
[YAMAJI laughs nervously]
[KOU] It's actually better
to eat meat raw.
You get more vitamins that way.
[ALL]
Ugh!
[YAMAJI] I'll call an ambulance
and have them on standby.
[FUTABA] Come and cool off at
Secret Garden: Beach-Hut Style!
[HAYAMA]
One mango frappé.
Can I get you anything else?
Our last day of work.
I didn't think we
were gonna make it.
[HAYAMA] It was tough,
but we survived.
[FUTABA] It sucks that
we didn't get to relax
while we were here.
I mean, it's the beach!
We didn't come for a vacation.
We came to work.
It would've been a lot
harder without you two here,
so thanks for letting
me drag you along.
No problem.
Glad we could help.
[YOKO]
Wow, Futaba. You sure are tan.
[HAYAMA]
I was gonna go with "burned."
Well, it's summer, isn't it?
[YOKO]
So what?
Summer means curry, right?
And now I kinda look like curry.
[HAYAMA] You say that
like it's a good thing...
[FUTABA] Anyway, I've got
a farmer's tan now,
and I want to even it out.
Since we won't
be working tomorrow,
I say we go hang out
on the beach!
We haven't been swimming
even once since we came here,
and that's just plain
unacceptable if you ask me!
[YOKO]
That's a great idea!
[HAYAMA] I'm pretty much
done with my homework,
so I'm ready to chill
for the rest of the summer.
Uh, homework?
What is this mysterious word?
I don't think I've
heard it before.
Of course not.
You'd have to pay
attention in class
to be familiar
with that concept.
[SHINO] Since you'll be enjoying
your day off tomorrow,
why don't I make
lunch as a thank you
for all your hard work?
[FUTABA]
Really?
[SHINO] Is there anything
in particular you'd like?
[FUTABA]
Barbecue!
[HAYAMA] We already had that
the first day we were out here.
[FUTABA] What's the
beach without barbecue?
They're a classic pair!
[HAYAMA] Well, there's
the sand and the ocean.
[FUTABA]
Fine, then curry.
[HAYAMA] Not after that
comparison you made earlier.
Leave it to me.
I'm sure I can come up with
something everybody will like.
[FUTABA]
Aw!
Let's just focus on
enjoying the ocean tomorrow.
Good idea!
I bet I can catch me
a fat fish or two.
Not the point!
Woo-hoo! Tomorrow is
gonna be awesome!
Ocean, here we come!
Huh...
Shark can be tricky,
but if it's fresh and
you've got a hot grill...
You're crazy, aren't you?
[FUTABA]
No fair! Go away, shark!
I wanna go swimming!
This really is too bad.
It would have been so much
nicer if it was a dolphin
instead of a shark.
[HAYAMA]
Yep, sure would.
[YU]
Hey, Yoko!
[YOKO]
Yu!
You're not working
anymore, right?
So does that mean you
can have a little fun?
We were hoping to,
but the beach is closed.
Shark sighting.
[YU]
No problem!
[YU] I can get us
into the hotel pool.
How 'bout it? Wanna come?
[YOKO]
If you're sure it's all right.
[YU]
Yeah!
What about lunch?
Can we barbecue there?
You look like you've
already been barbecued.
--[HAYAMA, YOKO] Wow!
--[FUTABA] Wow! It's huge!
[HAYAMA]
And so pretty!
[YOKO] Thanks for bringing us,
Yu. This is perfect!
[YU] Not the ocean,
but it's still nice, right?
[KOU]
This'll be fun!
How long has it been since we've
gone swimming together, Teru?
[HAYAMA]
Um, awhile.
Remember, no running or
diving in the shallow end.
Here's your floatie!
Y'know, suddenly I'm
not so jealous anymore.
[FUTABA] Does anybody
know where Sonobe is?
[YOKO] I guess the cooking's
taking longer than expected.
She said she'd meet
us by lunch, though.
'Kay, last one in the
pool's a rotten egg!
[SAKURA]
Futaba!
Hi!
That's Sakura.
Y'know, suddenly
I don't feel so good.
Yeah, I bet you don't.
She kinda has that
effect on people.
My parents took me
here on vacation.
How about you?
Hey!
Hi, hunk! Smooch!
I think the damage was more
psychological than physical.
I hope it's nothing
serious, poor kid.
[FUTABA]
Wait, where's Sakura?
She didn't go with him, did she?
He's been through a lot.
Next time you see him,
give 'em a kiss on the
cheek or something.
[YOKO] I guess I owe
him that much.
Okay, there's a big,
beautiful pool waiting for us.
Let's go!
[YOKO]
Right!
In honor of our fallen warrior.
[KONDO]
Woohoo!
Can you believe
how awesome this is?
Hotel pools are the best!
Would you stop the
running and squealing?
It's embarrassing.
[KONDO] If you stop
being a party pooper
and have a little fun!
I mean, you are dressed like
you're ready for a good time!
This? It's just something
I had laying around.
Anyway, thanks for inviting me.
It's pretty cool that you
were able to score tickets
to this place.
[KONDO]
Someone gave them to me.
Oh, really? Who?
[KONDO]
Hayama's older sister Kou.
[NISHIYAMA] But why would she
give them to you of all people?
It was kinda random.
[bell ringing]
How am I gonna
carry all this?
[KONDO]
Excuse me.
I can help if you need it.
That's so sweet!
You helped Hayama's sister.
[KONDO] Yep, and then she
gave me some tickets she'd won.
[NISHIYAMA] How am I
supposed to enjoy myself
knowing that's how you got them?
Well at least it isn't like
the evil one herself is here.
Hey, look.
That's Hayama over there.
Are you kidding me?!
It seems like they're
having a lotta fun.
Who cares? Ignore them.
[KONDO]
Maybe we should say hi.
[NISHIYAMA]
Not a chance.
Look what I found down there!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Whoa, where'd you come from?
I'm practicing.
In case I ever go
deep sea fishing.
[NISHIYAMA] How is that
like deep sea fishing?
And, you know,
you might get in trouble
if the hotel people
see you doing that.
Well, that wouldn't be so bad!
[YOKO]
It's your friend, Hayama.
What are you doing here?
You always show up
wherever I am.
Are you following me?
Sorry, but I don't
like you that way.
I'd rather go out with
a rabid dog than you.
[KOU] Hey! You're the nice
girl who helped me before!
Thanks again for the tickets!
This place rules!
It's a freakin' party.
[KOU] I don't think you've
mentioned this friend
before, Teru.
This is Nishiyama. I'd consider
her more of a classmate.
How great!
Since you're here too, why
don't we all hang out together?
Uh... No! I can't!
There're already some
friends here I have to meet.
You've got other friends?
[NISHIYAMA]
Come on, let's get out of here.
[KONDO]
Wait for me!
Well, I guess I can go
finish my sandcastle now.
Come on, Teru!
Don't you want to take a
dip in the pool real quick?
[HAYAMA] No, I don't.
And you should know why!
[FUTABA]
That explains the floatie!
You can't swim.
[YOKO]
I never would've guessed that.
Swimming's a pretty
important skill to have.
Like, what if you're
on a boat and it sinks
in the middle of the
ocean or something?
That's a good point!
Why don't you let us help you
work on your swimming today?
You never know when
it might come in handy.
When do you think it
might come in handy?
Now!
Thanks a lot, Sis!
[screaming]
Huh...
They're so different,
yet so similar.
[HAYAMA panting]
[KOU] Get back in there
and keep on trying.
You'll get better if
you give it some time.
[HAYAMA]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I just don't
understand why anyone
would hate the water so much.
[HAYAMA]
Mainly because it can kill me!
I've lasted this long not
knowing how to swim.
And I really don't see
any particular reason
to change that now,
because I think
I'm perfectly fine
just the way I am.
Of course you are.
Totally.
[KOU] Come on! We'll go
practice in the kiddie pool.
[HAYAMA]
No!
[FUTABA]
Good luck!
[YOKO]
I know you can do it!
[SHINO]
Hey, everyone!
[KOU]
Hi!
[SHINO] Hope you're hungry.
I come bearing lunch.
I've never been so relieved!
[YOKO] You took a lot
longer than expected.
[SHINO]
I know, I'm sorry.
I was working with
some new ingredients,
so I needed a little extra time.
Here you are.
I hope you enjoy it.
[FUTABA]
This is so exciting!
[YAMAJI] It was my first
time too, and I gotta say,
it was pretty exciting.
[HAYAMA] Y'know... you guys
aren't looking so good.
What happened to you?
What can I say?
It was a pretty wild ride.
And harder than expected.
But we were able to get
hold of a rare ingredient,
so it was worth it in the end.
What do you mean by
a rare ingredient?
[YAMAJI] Let's just say
I don't think that shark
will be bothering us anymore.
I would still skip
the swimming, though.
Tons of jellyfish out there.
Hold on, I'm still confused.
Are you saying...?
--Yummy!
--Did you really just eat that?
[FUTABA gasps]
I think I got a fin.
That's cute, isn't it?
Being in the sun all day
can really wear you out.
You can use me as
a pillow if you want.
I don't mind.
That's what big sisters are for.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'm good.
And what about you?
Want a shoulder to lean on?
I would feel silly sleeping
in public like that.
Fine, just one more bite.
[giggles]
I'm not surprised.
[YOKO]
Was she sleep talking?
Oh, sure.
She's probably having a feast
in her dream right now.
If I go to sleep, will I get
to dream about having a feast?
[HAYAMA]
That's not really how it works.
Go to sleep, Yoko.
Close your eyes and sleep.
Go to sleep.
I don't think it'll work
if you're trying that hard.
Sleep's kinda more
about relaxing, ya know?
[YOKO]
You must sleep.
[HAYAMA]
Um, Yoko...
[YOKO] You must sleep now.
Eyes closed. Deep breath.
Sleep. Go to sleep!
[FUTABA]
I can't eat another bite.
But I can. Probably.
[HAYAMA]
Seriously?
[YOKO] I cannot.
I cannot eat anymore.
I will take the rest to-go.
I cannot?
[whines]
[HAYAMA]
A nightmare.