At this rose garden
that overlooks the ocean,
we meet Mr. Sanada, who can see
Death Spirits just like Mitsuki can!
Mr. Sanada is a gentle man who
seems to have accepted his destiny.
And on his fated day, Mitsuki
has a heart to heart with him
just as his soul
is being collected.
I wonder how she felt back there.
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
What?
Everyone?
Ms. Oshige? Dr. Wakaoji?
Takuto? Meroko?
Why?
The reason's simple.
You're going to die soon.
It was a dream?
What's wrong?
It's still night.
It's nothing.
I'm okay.
Hey, Mitsuki.
Mitsuki?
Ow, ow...
What're you doing?
I've been calling you many times,
but you act like you don't notice.
Ta-dah. Look at this.
Orientation for advancement
into junior high school?
Yeah. We're finally going to be
junior high school students next spring.
Next...spring...
The school uniforms we've longed for.
Wonderful upperclassmen...
Let me tell you though, the studies are
going to be tough in our junior high school.
Why did you say such
a pessimistic thing?
Say, Mitsuki. How about joining
the Judo club with me in junior high?
A manga study club
would be nice too.
Wait, we need to ask Mitsuki
what she wants to do.
That's right.
What do you want to do?
You haven't decided, yet?
N-No. Not yet.
I see. Then take your time
and think about it. Okay?
O-Okay.
By next spring, that girl will...
Grandma, may I come in?
What do you want, Mitsuki?
Oh... Umm... I...
It's nothing.
Good night then.
Jeez, what's with that attitude?!
She makes me mad!
Whoa. C-Calm down, Meroko!
I'm calm!
How is this calm?!
Since I won't be able to talk with
Grandma after next spring,
I wanted to reconcile with her
while I had the chance, but...
I failed!
Mitsuki...
Good morning.
- Good morning!
Oh, Ms. Oshige!
Excuse me,
do you have a moment?
Sure.
You go on ahead.
Okay.
You're going to die soon.
You're going to die.
Mitsuki!
Are you okay?
Umm... Umm... I...
THE GREEN TOWN
"Summer Vacation Special Drama."
Half a year from now, huh?
Her health is an issue,
so I have to consult with everyone.
If you're scared, say so.
Takuto...
Mitsuki, it's okay to say
you're scared if you're scared.
Because wanting to live
is human instinct.
Huh?
Th-Thanks, Takuto.
But I'm fine.
Fine?
I'm really fine!
Hey, I'm going to change,
so go outside.
What're you thinking,
saying such a thing, Takuto?
It's good that she isn't
as scared as I thought.
But what would you have done
if she said she was scared?
There's nothing we can do.
Do you really think
she's not scared?
What?
She's scared.
She's gotten scared!
Of course she is.
She's still 12 years old!
But even so,
she's working as hard as she can.
Takuto...
She tries really hard...
to say she's not.
She's saying she's fine,
so isn't that okay?
I don't care about Mitsuki's feelings
in the first place.
Meroko...
This is why I didn't want to
get chummy with a child.
It just makes the job painful.
Are you being serious?!
A-Anyway,
I don't want to do this anymore!
Meroko!
Dammit!
How complicated.
They're on bad terms.
That's perfect.
With this, there will be more
chances to get close to Mero.
She's too good for Takuto.
But you snubbed her
when she hit on you!
Let me out! It's dark!
Good work today!
- Good work today!
Yes.
Yes. Of course we're happy to accept.
We look forward to working with you.
What were you talking about?
I accepted a drama job for you.
Drama?
It's a good offer.
It's half a year from now,
but they're saying you'll be the star
and your third single will be
the main theme song.
Half a year from now...
It'll be okay!
I'll find a way to make it happen,
no matter what.
You'll be in a drama,
make the song a hit,
and we'll do our best together half a year
from now, a year from now, and forever!
Okay, Mitsuki?
Ms. Oshige...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
A friend of yours delivered this while
you were out with Ms. Oshige.
What?
It's about the club activities
we were talking about yesterday.
I'm sorry I asked you to join the Judo club
with me without thinking about your health.
We asked the teacher, and there are
lots of activities that you can do too.
We're writing them down here in hopes
that there'll be an activity you want to do.
Personally, I think you should
do the manga study club.
Jeez, you guys!
I wonder if I was too hard on Takuto.
I guess I should head back.
I-Izumi?!
W-What did you come here for?!
You'd know if I said I'd only
come to the human world
for one reason other
than work, right?
Stop it!
You used to follow me
around so much.
That was then, this is now.
I think nothing of you now!
I'm dedicated to Takuto now!
Do you like Takuto that much?
Takuto's heart has
been stolen by Mitsuki.
A-Anyway, just go on home already!
You're the best, Mero.
You're really the best!
Mitsuki, where are you going?
It's almost time for dinner.
Y-Yeah, Dr. Wakaoji called me in.
Anyway, I'll be back.
Mitsuki!
What's all the ruckus?
Oh, Mitsuki said she was called in
by Dr. Wakaoji. Umm...
Leave her be.
Don't rush so fast.
You'll trip and fall!
But...
Mitsuki!
Dr. Wakaoji.
What's everyone all flustered about?
What the heck is going on?
Well...
Is that true?
I got an email from Eichi?
It's true. An email was sent to
the Full Moon official homepage.
Here, look.
I was surprised when
I heard the song.
Mitsuki, you made your dream
of becoming a singer come true.
I'm doing my best in America
to make my dream
of becoming an astronomer
come true.
From Eichi.
It was sent with a free email address,
so we don't know where he is.
But now we can get a lead
as to where he is.
I can't believe it.
Eichi...
You should ask him when
he's coming back to Japan.
Right!
All right! With this,
Mitsuki's dream will come true.
And what's more,
it'll be just the two of us.
We'll be madly in love!
Oh, Takuto...
To think that even the color of
the sun would look different
just by getting
an email from Eichi.
It's a wonder.
More, please.
Oh, again? You've got quite
an appetite this morning.
I got up kind of early,
so I got hungry.
This is a surprise.
Am I getting worse?
No, just the opposite.
You've gotten a lot better.
That's the Eichi effect.
The Eichi effect?
It seems there are many cases
of incurable diseases
being cured by strengthened immunity
due to being happy and laughing.
I'm a doctor, and I've been put to shame.
I surrender to Eichi.
Strange.
Even though it looks like
her sickness is going to be cured,
no keywords are appearing.
I wonder if this means that
there are no particular problems.
Meroko.
Huh?
Doesn't that email bother you?
Why?
No particular reason, but...
He probably listened to the CD that
the teacher from the orphanage gave him.
Why don't you just be happy for
Mitsuki, who's doing her best?
Okay, I have a meeting,
so you go on ahead.
Yes, all right.
What?
Huh?
Wasn't the dressing room up?
That's strange.
Anyway, let's try going down.
Why won't it stop?
It keeps going up.
The roof?
I've been waiting.
W-What?
What is this?
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh no.
I-It doesn't look like she's here.
W-What did you come here for?
Everyone asks me the same thing.
It's boring always giving
the same answer, so...
Let me see. I guess I'll say something like,
Mitsuki, I've come to take your life early.
B-But my life isn't over yet!
So I'll just take a reservation.
Take the Death Spirit Seal, Mitsuki.
N-No!
She's not here yet.
I really wonder where she went.
N-No!
Why? You're going to
die next spring anyway.
Then it shouldn't be a problem
if we do the seal now.
N-No.
No!
No! Eichi!
Meroko! Takuto!
Let go of Mitsuki!
Let go of her!
Takuto!
Mitsuki, are you okay?!
Oh, it seems you've caught me.
You little... Don't be so rash!
We're in charge of her!
It's because you guys work slow.
What?!
After all, she's actually
getting better, isn't she?
Because of Eichi's email
or something.
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me that you...
Insightful, master detective Mero.
Mitsuki!
We were looking for you, Mitsuki!
Izumi!
Well, I guess that's enough for today.
See you again soon.
Adios.
That Izumi...
Mitsuki! I have wonderful news!
W-What are you so flustered about?
And what are you doing here, Dr. Wakaoji?
A new method of treatment has
been discovered in America!
With that method, we can operate
without harming your vocal cords.
What?!
You'll be able to keep singing
if the surgery is a success!
You can keep on living, Mitsuki!
Is that true?
Yes!
Isn't that great, Mitsuki?
Eichi's email,
this news about my throat...
I feel like so many
good things are happening
that something bad
is bound to happen.
Mitsuki?
But if something bad happens,
I'm ready for it.
I feel like I'd have no problem
at all dealing with it!
That's the spirit, Mitsuki!
Get better and see Eichi!
Oh no, what was I thinking?
Sorry.
She doesn't know that Eichi's email
was Izumi's doing.
What should we do, Takuto?
She's so happy.
How do we tell her the truth?
Hey, Takuto. I think we should tell her
that the email wasn't really from Eichi.
No! She's so happy!
Plus, she's in a contest for
the Best New Singer Award in America!
I know! But isn't it crueler
to make her happy with lies?
I know that too. But...
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Best New Singer Award."
- Look forward to it!