This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
She's made it to her debut day,
but at her first performance,
she got nervous and doubted her ability
to even sing in front of people!
Well, she is in grade school...
Who can blame her?
But...with everyone's support,
she was able
to give a great performance!
Up next is MY Full Moon Meroko Debut!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes
and it sounds almost sad.
Up to now who was supporting me?
I realize, now that I'm far away,
what was supporting me.
"Myself" By Full Moon
IN STORES NOW
It's so pretty...
Was that really me?
You're the new face that
Seed Records is really pushing,
so we went a little bit further with
the promotional video.
But I wonder if everyone will buy it.
It's no good to lose your confidence
after it goes on sale.
There is no doubt that it's a good song,
and from now on it's going
to sell like hotcakes!
Jeez, that's annoying!
Stay still for a minute!
I can't calm down until I hear from
Ms. Oshige about the CD sales.
C'mon, spare me!
Hurry up and call, Manager!
It's her!
Hello?
Yes... Really?
I understand.
- How...
- Was it?
Well... Uh...
Don't get so depressed
if it didn't sell.
It's just went
on sale yesterday, right?
The battle has just begun, right?
I did it!
It's selling like crazy!
They were bombarded with orders!
She said it's going to keep selling!
What was that?
How could you make us worry?!
This means that a lot of people
are gonna listen to my song!
My intuition tells me
it's going to keep selling and selling.
It will definitely sell a million copies!
I'm so happy!
That's great.
Yeah!
Today, everyone at your school will be
talking all about Full Moon, right?
I know!
Take a CD to school today.
What?
You can brag and say
"I have a Full Moon CD."
I can?
That would be good if I really can.
I'm looking forward to
everyone's response.
Ah, that's right. If we do that,
we need to practice our autograph.
Hey!
It's not you, it's Full Moon who's—
Wouldn't it be cute
if I wore a ribbon?
Meroko, quit it already!
Speaking in such a loud voice,
it's disgraceful.
Good morning.
Good morning!
What's wrong?
I get excited and nervous when
I think about what everyone is saying.
Are they really listening to "Myself"?
Everything's fine.
After all, it's selling like crazy, isn't it?
Have confidence.
I know. Try taking a deep breath.
Right.
I've calmed down a little bit.
Well good!
Yeah!
Good morning.
Oh, Mitsuki!
Morning.
Morning, Kumi.
You're super early today, Kumi.
Isn't that okay?
But more importantly, hey!
Did you hear that new song
that went on sale yesterday?
Huh?
I heard it.
The vocals are the best, aren't they?
- It's by Fu...Fu...
- Fu...Fu...
Full Moon!
- It's Full Moon.
Furuta?
Of the Guitar Fighters?
Yeah, that's it!
Tomoe, that's just what I'd expect from
a member of the broadcast club.
Naturally! I'm on top of
all the new releases.
Well then...
What is she doing?
She should get into the conversation.
That's right.
Hey, yesterday on TV...
I was surprised.
She was so pretty.
Oh, that. The thing that was
on the entertainment news?
Norika Matsushima's Commissioner
for a Day !
What happened, Koyama?
Are you not feeling well again?
I-It's nothing.
Thank you.
Really?
I guess that's good then.
Nobody was talking about it.
If you're so concerned about it,
don't worry so much about gossip.
You should just ask them.
Yeah, but...
Is it possible that
you don't have any friends?
There's no reason for that!
It's been two years since
she changed schools.
Yeah...
Takuto is right...
I was absent for a long time
because I was sick.
When it comes to Gym,
I have to sit out and watch
and I'm not allowed to watch a lot of TV.
It's hard to make close friends,
with nothing to talk about.
I see... I'm sorry.
That's okay!
I was told that it's selling,
it was wrong to think that
everyone should have heard it.
I'm sorry too,
that I made you worry.
We HAVE to do this!
What is it, all of a sudden?
Look!
School lunchtime program.
Now accepting requests?
What's that?
During lunch break,
a member of the broadcast club is
a DJ who plays songs and chats.
It's pretty popular.
- That's why!
- Oh, I get it!
Huh?
You're so dull.
If nobody's heard it,
we'll make them listen to it.
What?
Do it.
You should take your CD
to the broadcast room.
Yes, but...
But...
Oh c'mon!
You're so frustrating!
If you hesitate too much,
you'll turn into a fly.
It's easy to give up,
but before you do
you should try a little bit harder.
That's right!
You worked so hard
for your debut, didn't you?
You're right.
I'll give it a try.
No, not "I'll give it a try."
Just go for it!
W-Wait a minute!
I'm still in the middle of thinking about
whether I should request it or not.
Are you saying those things again?
Aw, if it's come to this.
Mero-Mero Magic!
Hey! My CD!
I'm going to go request it!
Meroko, wait!
I can't believe it, that fool.
I said wait!
Stop, please!
Look at that.
Isn't that Mitsuki?
What a sight.
She's strange.
She's so funny.
Oh... H-Hello...
Everyone's laughing
their hearts out at me.
She did it, that Meroko.
Meroko, stop!
Stop, Meroko!
That's the broadcast room.
- Don't stop so suddenly!
Oh, Mitsuki?
What are you doing there?
Tomoe?
Okay? Hand it over to
the broadcast club member
say that you'd like to request it.
It can't be helped.
Prepare yourself!
Are you okay?
I, uh...
U-Umm...
Oh!
Come on!
W-What's this?
Everything's fine, just be quiet.
Play "Myself"!
No, I mean would you play it?
Please?
Meroko?
I wonder what Mitsuki's doing.
I wonder if she's fighting
with Tomoe or something?
S-Stop it, Meroko.
But you have to request it.
It's okay...
So just stop it!
Um... Mitsuki...
What's going on?
I'm sorry!
Oops!
M-Mitsuki, are you okay?
If I keep doing
these strange things,
it's gonna get even more
difficult to talk to people.
I didn't hand over my CD,
all I do is make blunders.
It was a disaster.
That's true.
Whose fault do you think it is?
Tomoe.
Here's your chance.
It's another chance to ask for your request.
Should I?
Yes you should!
Fine, fine...
Uh, Tomoe?
Yes, hello...
Well, maybe she went to buy "Myself."
If you keep saying things like that
you're just building up expectation!
But, look at that.
Oh, "Myself" by Full Moon?
See!
It's completely...
no good, no good.
- What?!
- What?
Yeah, that's right.
And tomorrow I'm going to
Shibuya with my mom.
I'm looking forward to it.
No good...
What does she mean by that?
I'm home.
Oh...
What happened?
You're injured.
This...
Lately you've been laughing so loudly,
it's like you're too giddy.
You've got to worry about your health.
From now on,
please be careful.
You understand, don't you?
Yes.
This taiyaki is super delicious!
See, see! It smells good, right?
How about it?
No, thank you.
What are you talking about?
It's filled with bean paste right down
to the tail!
It's from that bakery called Shunpu,
in front of the train station.
If you don't eat it, you'll regret it.
See, see!
See!
Aw, c'mon!
If I say I don't want it, I don't want it!
Yes...
Ah, Mitsuki?
It's Oshige.
"Myself" is making a huge impact.
We're getting one supplementary order
after another from the CD shop.
It's the first big hit for a talent
that I'm responsible for.
You say it's a hit, but is that true?
Of course.
The radio and TV stations are saying
that they want you to perform soon!
Can you hear?
And my phone keeps
ringing off the hook.
Really?
But nobody knows about it...
What?
Mitsuki... Hello Mitsuki?
It's nothing. Goodbye.
Your manager will worry.
But nobody's heard it.
How can it be called a hit?
That's ...
B-But there was
so much advertising...
Even if there's a lot of advertising,
it's no good if nobody hears it.
And...
"Myself" by Full Moon?
Oh, it's completely... no good, no good.
Sorry...
Please leave me alone...
and don't come to school
with me anymore.
I'm going now.
Good morning!
Somehow, it's painful to go in.
You came this far,
so what are you saying?
Takuto!
Sorry...about yesterday
That's okay.
More importantly, if you get
disheartened over that,
you won't be able to do
what's ahead of you.
But I thought I'd be able to talk
to everyone about Full Moon.
I felt so ill at ease with everyone.
Hey!
If you want to hear a song,
you sing it yourself, right?
Friends are the same.
If you can't try to fit in,
you can't make friends.
The same as singing?
What I'm saying is that...
Before you worry about things like
not having a friend or
that you can't make conversation,
you just have to laugh and
talk to someone!
I see...
It's the same as singing.
That's right.
Anyway, give it a try.
I wonder if I can do it.
I taught you yesterday, right?
At times like that...
- take a deep breath!
That's it.
First, I'll smile...
Well then!
Come over. Take a look!
Ah... That voice?
- Meroko!
Lined up here we have
the new song that was just
put on sale yesterday!
Right now, it's a super big hit
on the streets!
It's really hard to get your hands on!
I'm secretly offering
the special "friend" discount!
C'mon, buy it, buy it!
That's my CD.
What is she doing?
Did Mitsuki's personality
just change?
I didn't think
she was this kind of person...
She's totally different from her image!
That's horrible, horrible, Meroko!
What do you think you're doing?!
Well...
I kind of felt bad about yesterday.
If you're reflecting on your conduct,
why would you act like that?
If everyone listened to Full Moon,
it would be a good plan for Mitsuki
to get close to making some friends.
Well, there's a problem with
the way that you did it!
I thought that would
be the quickest way!
You know...
It's okay, Takuto.
What?
It's okay...
Meroko was just doing it for me.
On top of that, I haven't had friends
since the beginning,
so it doesn't change anything now.
I have to go.
I thought it was a good idea.
She's here, she's here.
We were looking for you, Mitsuki!
What?
Is it okay if I use this CD for
the lunchtime broadcast?
What!
But yesterday you said "Myself"
by Full Moon was completely no good.
That's right!
They weren't selling it anywhere,
I couldn't get my hands on it.
I was thinking that I'd have to go
to Shibuya and buy it.
It's really popular.
The lyrics are good and
the singing is the best.
Especially that one part...
Why do I like you so much?
It's different, it's like this.
Huh?
Something's different.
Is it?
I'm sure it's like this...
Why do I like you so much?
It's different.
You think so?
Isn't it like this?
Say...
Huh?
Isn't it like this?
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice is enough
to make me sad.
Oh...I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have done that.
Wow... Amazing!
Mitsuki, you're like the real thing.
That's cool!
Oh...really?
Yeah. Mitsuki you're really good
at singing.
It's not just singing.
That sales technique from before...
Yeah, that was funny.
- Umm... That was umm...
- We didn't know you were that interesting.
From now on, let's chat more.
And teach us songs.
Yeah.
If you're okay with me,
I'll teach you as many as you want!
Mitsuki! Oh, is it okay
to call you Mitsuki?
Shall we go to
the broadcast room together?
I'll give you a tour, and show you
how to do a broadcast.
C'mon, c'mon!
Okay, I'd like to go and see it.
You can call me Tomoe.
Thank goodness, with that,
the case is closed.
Meroko, I'm sorry I said such
a horrible thing.
Takuto, thank you.
Mitsuki, everything okay?
It's nothing, I'm coming.
Of course!
It's thank to me.
If it weren't for me there would
be no Full Moon, right, Takuto?
Don't let it go to your head.
They're waiting
for a new shipment.
It's really selling.
Production can't keep up.
You can believe that everyone wants
to hear Full Moon's songs.
Yes, I know.
That's why!
Huh?
Yes, I understand well.
A lot of people are listening to it.
I'll work hard from now on!
With a deep breath and a smile!
Hmm, I guess it's okay then!
Takuto, what's the matter?
That Dr. Wakaoji, I don't know
what he's thinking.
He won't listen to "Myself"
even with Mitsuki's prodding!
Huh?! I wonder why?
It's such a good song!
I know, right?
Well, he did say he used
to be a musician!
Is there something going on
we don't know about?
Next time on Full Moon:
"I Want You to Hear It!"
- Look forward to it!