Amazing...
This is cooler than Kamizakura-machi Ginza.
I don't know too much about him, but there are
lots of other dangerous people around, so be careful.
Oh yeah, I saw it today.
That black bike.
We haven't had a teenage girl in a long time.
Yeah, thanks to the info we got.
At that moment, I noticed I was trembling.
Is the reality you perceive truly the only one?
The scenery you're used to never changes...
Congratulations on your matriculation, everyone.
At the moment, unpleasant topics like the low birthrate and the
widening gap between the rich and poor are on the lips of all Japanese.
However, were those people to gaze upon everyone at this ceremony, I'm sure they'd conclude that Japan's future is a bright one.
They'd be assured that Japan is still salvageable.
It would give them strength.
This day will be one you all will remember. However, at the same time...
You don't really believe that an everyday
occurrence is unfolding here right now, do you?
I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
A shy boy who's just come to Tokyo...
I'm Sonohara Anri. It's nice to meet you all.
...a somewhat aloof girl.
I'm Kida Masaomi!
I may look like an adult, but I'm just as fragile and
vulnerable on the inside as any other fifteen year-old.
A boy who looks to be the only happy one in the group.
I'm Kamichika Rio. I hope the year goes well.
A mysterious girl;
These sorts of people are all around you.
Uhh, Harima...
Is Harima Mika here?
Absent, huh...
It was a banal scene anyone could swear they've seen before.
Oh, starting the school year off by being late, are we?
We're in the middle of self-introductions.
Make yours from where you're standing.
I'm Yagiri Seiji. I hope the year goes well.
But, thanks to unexpected developments, another heretofore unseen reality can sometimes peer in on the present one.
Well then, Yagiri, you can sit down now.
I won't need to.
Huh?
I don't think I'll be coming to school for
a while—no, I might not come ever again.
Huh?
That's all I came to say.
Excuse me.
Hey, Yagiri, what in the world...
It is what it is.
It's something that's very important to me.
I have no time to waste with the likes of you.
Please, excuse me.
Yagiri, wait. I said, "wait!"
People are shocked when cracks suddenly
appear in their peaceful, everyday lives.
And one girl here has peered into those cracks.
She should have died two days ago.
This girl was just like everyone else, born into a normal family.
She had no problems or inconveniences in her life.
However, when she became a middle school
student, something arrived at her house.
What was in it?
Pictures.
Apparently my father was cheating on my mother, and they show him with some other woman.
And there was a note, too.
Something like, "Could you forgive this kind of thing?"
I guess it was sent by someone who knew the woman.
Of course your father did something terrible, but that person isn't much better.
I didn't know what to do, so I decided to hide them.
Ever since then, seeing my parents interact seemed gross somehow.
It must have been tough on you.
Hm? Something wrong, Rio?
I endured it for a whole six months.
I figured it'd be better if everything were out in the open.
When it comes to things like that, you shouldn't push yourself too hard.
There are certain things I don't really want to talk about, either.
I'm fine.
I want her to know.
I can't believe they confiscated our cell phones!
But nothing changed.
What?!
I couldn't do anything.
I don't know if my mother just hasn't said
anything or they talked it over while I wasn't around.
That's happened to you too, right, Rio?
Not even my father's lame jokes or the
overly-sweet taste of my mother's boiled vegetables.
So I thought, "Why don't I just try leaving this world?"
That's all I've been thinking for a while now.
That's a lot like me.
I might not be in as bad a position as you, Magenta, but...
What happened?
I was dating someone, but she ended up doing it with my father...
How horrible.
But, the person I can't forgive at all is my mother.
What did she say?
"This kind of thing happens all the time, and we'll just lose face if you make a big deal about it."
She wouldn't say anything about how she felt.
And...I feel like that means our family's
image is more important than me.
But, I guess she could've been thinking about my future...
I don't think so.
I wonder...
She's not thinking about you at all, Nakura.
She's just thinking about herself!
Dinner's ready.
Okay.
Miss Magenta, why don't we disappear together?
If we both die, then maybe they'll understand how we feel.
And what they should truly value the most.
It seems like a stupid idea now, but that's how she felt when she left.
She was spurred on by Nakura's words and wanted to meet
someone who was thinking the same kinds of things she was.
Even if she were being deceived, there was nothing for her to lose.
I'm great with girls, so...
Or so she believed.
Yes?
Are you "Magenta?"
Yes.
Oh, then are you "Nakura?"
Great! I knew it was you.
As soon as she saw his face...
Nice to meet you.
She thought, "This isn't Nakura, is it?"
Please take care of me.
Yet she followed him because she wouldn't be able to forgive herself if she turned back.
It's nice to meet you as well.
Let's go.
Okay...
That's why, even when this happened...
Hello.
Are we in the clear?
No one's around.
Well then, sorry to deceive you!
She was overcome with such emotions as surprise, protest, and regret...
But right before she passed out, she thought...
"This is my fate. It's time."
"I'm going to disappear from this world...without anyone knowing."
However...
You're in a place like this by yourself?
While she was unconscious, the world was still moving...
Well, it doesn't seem like that difficult of a job.
Still, take care.
Without any concern for her thoughts or wishes.
It's no good.
I just can't scrape together that kind of money.
I'm not saying I won't pay it back.
But, if something were to happen to me, I don't know if
Mr. Shiki from the Awakusu Association would keep quiet.
You old fart!
I don't have time for this.
It's not that I'm busy; I just don't want to spend more than 2.5 minutes of my life with you!
Oh, and one more guy you—
Hm?
Hey, I doubt I have to remind an excellent courier like yourself, but...
You don't have to do anything more than I've asked of you.
Just mess up the other guys a bit.
Anyway, I'm counting on you!
The world moves.
Although, not necessarily in the direction
in which the girl believed her fate to lie.
Hey.
Wh-What the hell are you?!
It said, "I was told to take you to a certain place."
The bike made no sound as it moved, yet sometimes whinnied like a horse.
It felt decidedly unlike reality.
However, this feeling of a body pressing against her was unmistakably real.
The girl thought about the person on the other side of that warmth.
What are they thinking? What do they know? What was their life like?
What did she look like in the eyes of this person?
Okay.
Miss Magenta!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nakura.
Are you really Nakura?
I'm the same Nakura who wants to just disappear.
Nice to meet you.
Are you the one who saved me?
Yes, that's me.
Thank you very much.
Were you afraid?
Yes...
It must've been tough on you.
But, how did you know?
Because I'm the one who had you kidnapped, Miss Magenta.
I'm also the one who had you saved.
I don't get it...
You were going to kill yourself, but somehow
regretted being scared when you got kidnapped...
But, if you were to resist, then you'd be contradicting your will to die...
So you decided to accept this as your fate,
but you're actually relieved to have been saved.
I wanted to see the expression on your face after all that.
To put it simply, I wanted to see your expression after I
rendered you speechless by knowing what you're thinking.
Why...?
Why?
Let me see...
I assume my response will sound quite philosophical to you.
So, to avoid that type of explanation,
I'll just say it's because I like humans.
Humans are so interesting, so intriguing.
Oh, but I simply like humans, not you in particular.
That's the important part.
It...was all a lie...?
Do you finally understand your role?
Come on.
Lots of people have jumped from this building.
Not enough to make it famous, but I hear you'll definitely die if you jump from here.
I mean, look at that splotch down there.
You think you're special, don't you?
Well, you're not. Everyone's the same.
There's no one who can live their
whole life being completely uncorrupted.
I mean, you have at least one or two secrets, don't you?
Have you ever thought about why
you're so good and your parents are so bad?
Well...
If you'd so kindly let me give away the answer, it's because
even if you're cheating on someone or you're being cheated on,
everyone laughs at bad jokes and eats over-sweet boiled vegetables.
Take a look around.
No matter what sort of worries you have,
everyone's just a simple splotch.
Splotches.
No exceptions.
Everyone.
All equal before God.
Shall I let go of you?
See.
I'm glad I could see the full and
awkward spectrum of your emotions today.
I'm not really interested in your personal problems, but how you behave when you're worrying.
By the way, your behavior was as boring as I expected.
I guess that's because I knew from the start that you didn't want to die.
Bye, then. I had fun, Miss Magenta.
She hesitated for an instant.
She figured that by jumping, she could somehow hurt that man.
However, she also thought...
"I may have just been waiting for the opportunity."
"And that man's words are that opportunity..."
But, unbeknownst to her...
Umm...
Why?
I said you didn't have to do that...
The girl thought about her mother and father.
About her father, about his mistress...
About both her parents.
Everyone has their own private time.
Maybe that wasn't as malicious, calculating,
or colored with hatred as she had thought.
Maybe it really wasn't a compromise or a way to cover up weakness.
While looking through her house, she decided to forgive her family.
Ever since that day, she viewed the world differently.
There are as many memories and secrets as there are people.
That realization was finally palpable to her.
Where should we go?
I'll take you anywhere you want to, so pay for my meal.
Alright then, how about a book store?
Well, you can find a book store on any corner...
Even people like these two, whom you can find anywhere, probably have their secrets.
Well, let's go home first, then...
They have thoughts they don't want anyone to hear.
Please, wait!
Yagiri, isn't there something—
I don't know!
Bu-But...being absent your first day of school...
I said I don't know!
Wait!
Umm...
Is something wrong?
I wonder what happened...
I'm such a sinful man.
Huh?
That girl with the glasses is totally into me.
She was totally feeling unsure about the
dangerous and risky days she'll have with me.
Could you speak in Japanese for me?
For him, as well as her, reality isn't necessarily what you see.
And so she thought...
"Will I be able to tell this to someone someday?"
"That the world isn't as terrible as you think it is."
I didn't hear anything about you becoming a crusader for justice.
I thought I'd simply asked an excellent courier to do her job...
As if!
A simple information dealer such as myself isn't that evil.
Although, I don't know if you could call someone who stops a person who wants to die from killing themselves "good."
I had fun, you excellent courier.
Ikebukuro:
He, she, you, and I all come to this town searching for
something, seeking something, wanting to change something.
Next time: Running Rampant
Do you want to eat sushi? Sushi's good.
Long time no see, mister.