The stars are beautiful.
You're even more beautiful.
You're really sexy.
Wait, my heart isn't ready for this...
Wait.
Ouch...
That was...
What am I dreaming about?
To think that the Underwear Club is going on an overnighter.
This is gonna be fun!
Yako-chan, we need to do Underwear Club activities on our overnight trip.
We could plan the Underwear Club's activities.
R-Right.
Don't you ever plan anything?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh, Sensei!
Umm... Let's get your luggage in the car.
Ah- My luggage, right? Thank you.
This is not good. That was just a dream.
Only Amahara-san is left now.
Oh... Isn't she sexy.
Eh?! Are the students sexier than me?!
Thanks for giving me a ride.
Was that her father?
Didn't seem like it.
Boyfriend... maybe?
Oh, you're here.
That's nothing to be surprised of. It's already past the meeting time.
Amahara-san, your face-
That's a kiss mark!
Maybe she spent last night with her boyfriend who just dropped her now?
Yako-chan!
No... It can't be!
But...
Amahara-san is already pretty mature...
No, don't! I must stop!
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Nothing, nothing.
Is that a kiss mark, Amahara-san?
Who knows?
This is delicious!
Yeah, it is.
To think I'm going on a trip with Senpai...
The lovers will be spending the night together somewhere.
N-No, this is just an overnight trip, right?
I'm just here to lead the students!
Sorry, sorry. It's been a while since I last drove.
A-Are you okay?
There's no way I'd be okay!
I'm sorry.
How do you wear a bra with that?
It's a strapless.
I see.
Let us see.
It's flush against your chest.
It comes right off.
There you go.
It's pretty heavy!
How does this feel any different from real breasts?
Don't touch them, Yako-chan!
Komachi-kun, give me that.
I-It's pretty warm...
E-Everyone, there are boys here as well.
I-I'm sorry, Komachi-kun.
Sensei, are you wearing a T-shirt bra?
Y-Yeah.
Looks like you've got sweat absorbing pads as well.
Ah, I bought them on net as they were cheap.
Certainly, a t-shirt bra won't show through your clothes,
and the pads will prevent sweat stains,
but still it has no feminine appeal to it.
Please try something to improve your feminine appeal on this trip.
Did a bug bite you? I've got some remedy to stop the itching.
I see, so it wasn't a kiss mark.
Jewelries used this ryokan a long time ago.
TL Note: A ryokan is a type of traditional Japanese inn.
Jewelries?
It's the name of an underwear brand that my grandmother made.
Could it be... that?
What's an "Under Fellowship"?
Such a weird name.
They couldn't just write "Underwear Appreciation Society."
I guess there's no place for us here either.
I think it'd be troublesome if we attention over here.
I might be true but, it still makes me sad.
Welcome.
Please take care of us.
We look forward to our stay.
Thank you!
You guys must be from the Underwear Appreciation Society, right?
Oh, yes.
We didn't want the other guests to look strangely at you.
So we changed your name on the sign outside of your room.
Sorry for acting without your permission.
She was looking out for us...
You're the granddaughter of Yoko-san, right?
Nayu-chan, was it?
Y-Yes.
Haven't you grown up...
You stayed here before with your grandmother.
You were a baby at that time, so you might not remember about it.
I see, so I came here with grandmother...
The ocean!
Let's swim!
Well, I have work to do.
I'll be back by tonight.
Ah, alright.
Just change already so we can go to the beach.
Hey! If you are going to change, then at least close the door!
Alright, alright.
Nayu-chan's swimming suit is cute!
Yours is fashionable too, Haruka-chan!
Yako-chan, is that a racing suit?
Yeah!
That's awesome! It has cuts in it.
It's kinda visible...
Are you wearing something under it?
Don't pay attention! Don't pay attention!
School swimsuit...
And it's about to burst out.
Didn't you have anything better to wear?
But it's been a while since I've gone swimming.
But still...
I-I'll take off the name tag.
Oh, I have some scissors.
Ah thank you. You came here well prepared.
I thought we could learn about making underwear if we had time.
I brought patterns, fabrics,
and a sewing kit with me!.
If it's cut already, then we should cut it a bit more!
What are you doing?
This will look better like this.
Wait!
We might as well make it a bikini.
I could never wear something like this!
It's as if she was attacked...
I guess we overdid it.
I guess we have no choice but to buy a new swimsuit.
Why am I going with you as well?
We need a man's opinion.
It's cute, but...
Doesn't it look kinda childish?
What do you think, Komachi-kun?!
I can't hear or see anything...!
W-Wait...
Hmm.. Not bad...
No, It looks weird.
Th-They're getting...
What about this one?
We can still go further ahead!
Isn't it a bit too small?
There's no other choice than this one!
Is this hiding or something?!
I-I'm just going with this one!
After all those you tried on, you're choosing this one?
I guess I'll go with white.
Why "guess"?
You know, I haven't gotten married yet.
This is how I want to be, so this is what I'll wear!
Let me wear this!
It's raining.
Run!
It's cold.
Endure it! This is training as well!
Training!
Looks like we won't be able to swim today.
I guess not.
How about we take a bath together?
Okay!
I'll take one later.
You just don't want to bath with the big-breasted duo.
That's not true!
You lose.
Shut up!
I can finally relax.
No matter how much you wash them, they don't go away once they grow up.
I feel kind of dirty.
Why are you saying that?
In my case it's even...
What? You too, Haruka-chan?
Let... me... check.
There's no point in checking it anyway!
I just want to know I'm not the only one!
But still!
Leave me alone!
Huh? I...
This chawanmushi is delicious!
TL Note: Chawanmushi is kinda of a custard made from eggs. Unlike other custards, this one is usually eaten as an appetizer.
You should hurry up and eat as well, Komachi-kun.
I-It's good.
Did they carry me here while I was naked?!
Who put my underwear on?
Did they see me?
Sensei.
Do you mind if I make some adjustments to your white swimsuit?
Are you going to cut it to pieces again?
Oh, no. I thought you might like to put some beads on it.
Ah, It's beautiful!
I thought adding some sparkles to your chest might look good.
What do you think?
It's really wonderful.
Thank you, Hayama-san.
W-What?
Why don't you try putting on some makeup as well?
I've never worn colors like this before.
Just hold still for a moment.
You look beautiful, Sensei.
Thank you.
I've been taught by everyone, no?
That saying stuff like "I'm fine with this" or "I'm fine with that" won't allow me to move forward or mature...
As both a human being and as a woman.
Let's take a photo of that expression!
Ah, that's right. It'll help me when I do my own makeup as well.
Sensei, why don't you try posing?
Try squeezing your arms together.
Next, pretend you're lying on the beach.
Spread your legs a little.
Even Mizuno-Sensei... What exactly are they doing?
Looking good, Tamaki-chan. Next...
I'm back.
What's going on?
Excuse me, may I come in?
Ah, sure.
Sorry to disturb you at night. I just wanted to stop by.
Oh, you shouldn't have gone through this trouble.
Did everyone had chance to relax?
Yes!
I'm not surprised Yoko-san's granddaughter formed an Underwear Appreciation Society.
I have also learned too much about underwear from Yoko-san when I was young.
From grandmother?
When I was working at the house by the sea...
Thank you for waiting.
Your bra strap is showing.
Oh, excuse me.
Would you like to try this sample product?
I'm an underwear designer.
See? it wouldn't be a problem if someone saw these bra straps.
With designs like these, they'll be fashionable when seen.
How cute!
Check out this underwear!
This underwear won't stick out when you wear hip-hugger jeans.
She taught me about the wide variety of underwear.
She also taught me; working women don't have to sacrifice modesty and grace.
She was truly a wonderful person.
Grandmother...
Nayu-chan is carrying on her grandmother's will.
I hope I can be a bit more like my grandmother.
What the hell is that?!
Eh? I can't sleep in this?
What are you going to do if your boyfriend suddenly comes over to spend a night with you?
I'm kinda getting nervous.
Was she wearing that last night as well?
It's transparent, so it must be designed to show off your underwear.
It is even OK to wear nothing underneath it when your boyfriend is around.
But then everything would be in plain sight!
You must be bothered with it as well.
You understand? You do understand, don't you?
She's still severely lacking in feminine appeal.
Aren't you going to swim, Komachi-kun?
I-I'm fine.
Didn't you change into your swimsuit?
But I'm fine!
It's tiny, and digging in deeper!
What the hell is this? I don't remember packing this swims-
"Show them that you're a man. Good luck. From your brother."
How can I possibly show this off...
Come swim with us, Komachi-kun.
I said I'm fine here!
Come on, let's swim.
Leave me alone!
That was fun, wasn't it?
I'm glad we had an overnighter.
We didn't do anything to make it feel like an overnighter.
Weren't we going to plan our club activities for the rest of the year?
R-Right, then how we talk about that right now?
R-Right.
Let's see...
We, the Underwear Appreciation Society...
Should spread the belief more  that underwear is wonderful.
In order to do that, we...
What should we do?
Well, how about we start with the cultural festival?
That's right!
It would be nice to do something for the cultural festival.
We can do something about the protective and aesthetic qualities of underwear, like...
It should be something like this.
"We, the Underwear Appreciation Society, should teach people to appreciate and love underwear..."
"through the functions and history of underwear."
"We should do something suited to the society's regular activities and goals."
You guys!
K-Komachi-kun, everyone's just tired.
I'm... I'm tired as well!
I'm going to sleep too.
How cute.
You were cute, too.
You looked good in that swimsuit.
It was wonderful.
No, Tamaki! You've got to enjoy this blissful moment!
Lately, women's loincloths have been gaining popularity.
What?
They don't feel constricting and are easy to wear.
They could be good for sleeping or wearing a yukata.
Hey, why don't I make us matching loincloths?
Who needs that?
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!