The Rank 9 Advancement Exam was in full swing!
Our mission was to descend into this huge maze
called the Bowels of the Cursed Serpent,
then, using our powers of divination,
find the Arrow Key and bring it to the surface.
There were so many scary traps, one after another,
and some weird oni attacked us, too,
but using our wits and courage and Nono's singing...
oh, and Kon's weird dance and a smelly fox,
we finally found the real Arrow Key!
I'm not smelly!
All we had to do was get back to the surface
and we would pass and become Rank 9 Urara!
That was the plan,
but just at that moment...
Chiya.
Wh-what's happening?
We finally found you.
Disgusting, treacherous child...
Chiya, we're gonna go without you!
Huh?
Chiya?
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Chiya just disappeared?!
The Arrow Key went with her!
I-is this another trap?
Could be something another team set up!
No, what if...
I've taken Chiya-san and the Arrow Key!
Help me...!
If you want to pass the test, then come to my castle!
It's a boss fight!
Mom's the boss?!
Whatever, it's dangerous to be alone in this maze!
We have to find Chiya, quick!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Yeah, me too.
Kon-chan, could you have
the fox spirit look for her again?
I don't know, she seemed really satisfied after Chiya
petted her, so I don't think she'll come back.
We don't have time to stand around thinking about it!
Right, and we're still in the middle of a test.
We have to find Chiya and the Arrow Key!
All four of us are getting out of here alive!
No! Hey, what're you doing?!
Let go of me, please!
Jeez, let me go!
Squish
Stop, stop! Hey!
Y-you can only touch my belly if we're friends...
Let go of me!
Ow, ow, ow...
Where am I?
I have to find everyone.
We won't let you go.
The walls are talking!
Because we've finally found you, Chiya.
Wh-what?
How do they know my name?
Why are you trapping me here?
I'm in the middle of a really important test!
I'm not gonna let you get in the way of that anymore!
Who are you?!
Who?
It matters not.
What to do?
None may betray us.
Betray?
The Dead.
The Vanished.
The daughter of a traitorous Urara is an Urara.
Her name is Chiya.
You are the daughter of the Traitor.
Her daughter.
Wait!
There are two doors?
Which is the correct one?
We should be careful.
There must be some hint
as to which door is the right one.
No! The darkness is scary, it's so scary!
Kon!
Dark is scary, dark is scary!
No, I'm scared!
Oh. I'm out.
Dark is scary, dark is scary!
No, I'm scared!
Huh? Nono?
Dark is scary, dark is scary!
Nono! Nono!
It's scary!
"Her daughter"?
Wait, are you...
Are you talking about my mom?
The daughter of the Traitor, Chiya.
You know about my mom?! Tell me!
Oh, the bitter hatred we feel.
Even cursed, the mere presence is hateful to us.
She is still in this town.
Yami.
The Urara steeped in sin, Yami.
Yami? Yami?
Is that my mom's name?
Wh-what should I do?
I might die if this keeps up...
And just when I found a clue about my mom, too...!
All I knew was that she was in this town...
But I still wanted to meet her so badly!
What am I supposed to do here?
I don't know!
Everyone else would probably find some cool way
to divine their way out of this...
If I had a special divining talent...
I know, Kon!
Use that paper to tell me
what kind of fortune-telling I should do!
Alright, I'll tell your fortune.
But just so you know, it might not be right.
D...
...a...
...rk!
Huh?!
You're the...
The spirit I met in the field!
Then you're Dark?
Thank you for saving-
I-it ate me!
Maybe I really am done for!
But it's soft and warm and feels good...
Huh? I'm okay!
Are you protecting me?
My eyes are getting really hot...
Out of the way!
Out of the way! Who are you?!
The same red eyes as that woman!
Piercing eyes that see through all.
Don't look!
Don't look at us with those eyes!
RANK 1
Curse you!
Chiya, we swear to you...
One day, we will...
Th-they disappeared!
Nono!
Hurry, hurry!
I-I can't go on!
Huh?!
M..Matsuko-san?!
W-wow, Matsuko-san is holding up the ceiling!
Nono! Leave this to me, just get out of here!
While I'm holding everything up!
Her hands don't even reach!
Nono, now's your chance!
Get Matsuko-san!
I know!
My hair!
Matsuko-san's gonna... she's gonna go bald!
I could see so many things I'd never seen before.
It was like my eyes turned into crystal balls.
Now that I think of it,
Tokie-san said crystal ball divination
would show me what I wanted to know.
I'll show you!
Which means the thing just now was divination, too?
Dark divining?
Is that what you showed m-
Don't eat me anymore!
You know...
One thing I saw was a person who looked a lot like me.
That person is Yami...
My mother?
What is it now?!
Are more of those things gonna-
Eh, mic test, mic test.
Hello, students, are you still alive down there?
That's Tokie-san!
Only fifteen minutes left until the test period is over!
Unfortunately, not all of our passing groups
have made it to the surface yet.
Oh, how this maze is just like our fragile lives.
Those who make it through the winding path
will open the door to tomorrow.
Another dead end?! Come on, now!
Those who make it through the winding path
will open the door to tomorrow.
Huh?
Those who make it through the winding path
will open the door to tomorrow.
Not fooling me again!
This difficult test is your key to the future.
Koume!
Koume-chan!
Not even the gods can tell you
the path to your success or failure.
But don't give up!
Show me how you struggle in these
mournful situations, show me even more!
Struggle, struggle, struggle until the very last second!
Then entertain me even more after that!
T..Tokie-sensei, I think that's enough!
Divination
I can't believe that woman.
Captain Saku!
Natsumeya's group still hasn't passed.
Yeah.
Uhh, are they okay?
They're running short on time.
Maybe they...
We don't know.
RANK NINE ADVANCEMENT
EXAM GROUNDS
They're not the only ones fighting for their dreams.
Other Urara have gathered here for the same reason.
With the short time left and the other Urara in mind,
they may have already given up.
But...!
We can't assume that it's impossible for them now.
That's something they must determine themselves...
...right?
Right! Our apologies, Captain!
Captain Saku popped us on the head!
Oh, thank you, Captain!
That's right, the test isn't over yet!
I can't get sidetracked by my mom.
I have to find the others and get out of this labyrinth!
Dark! Please let me use your power one more time!
Find my dear friends, show them to me!
Kon, Nono, Koume...
Jeez! I told you to stop pulling those ropes willy-nilly!
But it's a dead end! I thought it might open up the way!
O-oh no!
I can't get my stomach unstuck!
I told you to cut down on the
Sweet Plum Honey Dango Koume Specials!
N-no, it's not the anmitsu's fault!
And Chiya says it's great that my belly is all squishy!
It's Chiya's fault!
That's a terrible excuse.
I-it's no use...
Koume?
Didn't you hear?
We only have fifteen minutes left.
But we can't find Chiya, and there are
so many traps in our way.
We're going to fail at this rate.
Koume... she was always the confident one...
And maybe I've gained a little weight.
So she was bothered about that.
Don't cry, Koume-chan!
Nono...
Kon-chan, give her one more pull!
I don't have any strength left,
so it might not work, but still...!
Nono...
I don't want to give up yet!
I wanna give it my all with everyone until the very end!
Chiya-chan... she was the one who taught me that.
Don't cry, Nono!
That's right, Chiya always...
Chiya...
Chiya-chan...
Your dream belongs to you, Kon.
Nobody can take it away from you,
so don't give up on it!
You can't, Nono!
We're not gonna let you be alone!
She always...
Everyone!
That voice!
Chiya-chan?
I came to save you!
Chiya?
Yep, it's me!
Sorry about the wait!
A monster!
That's not the Chiya-chan I know!
Wait! No! Don't leave me behind!
It's me, Chiya.
Huh?
Everyone, you now have eight minutes left.
Are you ready to start cowering in the corner?
I'm so glad you were okay, Chiya-chan...
Wh-what is that? A ghost?
It's not a ghost.
This is Dark.
Dark saved me from a scary situation back there.
But we don't have time to sit around and talk!
The test is almost over!
Th-that's right!
We're all here, so let's hurry and get outta here!
Only seven minutes left!
What?! Only seven?!
Now it's 6 minutes and 50 seconds.
Let's go, everyone!
B-but we don't have time!
How are we gonna find the exit?!
It's okay. Leave that to me!
I'll divine where the exit is!
Huh?
Chiya's divination?
You don't have any confidence in me?!
I mean, when we did shoe divination,
you kicked yours off into Bloque 9!
And when we did flower divination,
you ate the whole thing!
And when we did dice divination,
you broke the dice!
W-well, sure, but I finally found
a divination technique I'm good at!
A technique you're good at?
You divined it for me, Kon.
Please, trust me!
Alright.
I trust Chiya.
I trust Chiya's divination!
If you're gonna spout off about it like that,
we might as well have you show it to us.
I trust you too, Chiya-chan!
Chiya, the fate of Team Natsumeya is in your hands!
Right!
Let's go, Dark!
I see it.
The second of the seven doors from the right.
There are four traps on the red carpet.
Follow the middle path.
Go up the stairs, and the final path will be before us.
Nine
We can make it if we run as fast as we can!
Let's run!
Three minutes left!
Two minutes left.
Two passing teams have already made it here.
Three teams have been disqualified.
Will a group be able to find the last arrow
and pass through this door?
Kon...
No, I mustn't! The proctor must not be
allowed to be swayed by her own feelings!
What a fool I am!
I have much more to learn!
I must harden my heart even further...
E-even further, Ma'am?
We're almost there!
We just have to get up these stairs
and we'll see the door!
There it is!
Wow! You're amazing, Chiya!
Chiya-chan, you're so cool!
Praise me more!
After the test is over!
The last door...
If we get through that door,
we'll be Rank 9 Urara... right?
Okay, Kon, open it!
Huh? Me?!
PANIC PANIC
No, no, no, you open it, you found the door!
Aww, but you're the leader, Kon!
Kick it down, Leader!
You open it, Koume!
If we want to be fair,
why don't we do rock-paper-scissors?
Or we could draw lines and follow them to the winner?
Thirty seconds remaining!
It doesn't matter who does it, just open it!
W-wait, let's do that one thing one more time!
Do what?
We all worked our hardest in this exam...
We ran and divined and did so many different things...
but we got here because all four of us worked together!
So please, let's do it together!
Okay!
Let's go!
We can't mess it up this time!
Five seconds left!
One,
two,
three,
go!
The last passing team...
...is Natsumeya!
We did it! We did it!
They did it! They did it!
PASSING
GROUPS
The Rank 9 Urara Advancement Exam is now complete!
Dark's gone.
Chiya, are you looking for that dark ghost?
Yeah, all of the sudden, it was gone.
Maybe it went away, like the fox spirit.
Hey, Chiya.
I have a lot of questions about your ghost,
and your divination technique,
and what happened when you disappeared...
Kon...
CONGRATULATIONS
ON PASSING!
But I feel so light and happy right now
that I can't express it in words!
So we'll talk later!
You got it!
Kon, your eyes are kinda red!
Oh, because I was crying before.
Your eyes are redder than usual too, Chiya.
Were you crying?
Look, look! Nono's red, too!
L-look who's talking, Koume!
We all match!
Yeah, but I'm sure...
SAKU!
Hey, I'm still on the clock!
Everyone passed! I'm so happy!
We're gonna have a feast tonight! I'll make meat and potato stew!
...Nina-sensei's got the reddest eyes of all.
Yeah!
We'll have meat and potato stew tonight and tomorrow!
J-just calm down, alright?!
Just smelling you made me calm down a little, Saku.
Wha-?!
Captain Saku's smell?!
Smells like soap.
Soap?! When did she bathe?!
How hard it is to shake off
the refreshing sweat of youth...
She hides her perverted heart
but cannot hide her clean and pure body!
Let us partake in you, Captain Saku!
C-cut that out, you two!
I won't let you get away with acting like harlots!
Y-you've got it all wrong, Captain!
In any case, we managed to pass...
...the Rank 9 Advancement Exam!
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Baths and Celebrations Sometimes Have Smiles"!
We'll divine what the episode will be!
The answer is...
What do you mean, "sometimes"? We're always smiling!
"Baths and Celebrations Sometimes Have Smiles"
That's what it'll be about!
I hope you're looking forward to it!