It... It can't be possible.
She died.
I killed her with these hands.
Yet, saying that she's alive is my...
...wishful egoism...
...to be forgiven.
Elen.
Explain to me what's going on here.
It was four men during the last deal and another one today.
I've looked after Muroto, the one who was killed tonight, since he was a boy.
What the hell is going on here?
Depending on the answer, I don't care if I face disgrace.
Aye.
Lizzie.
Please don't make a rushed decision.
Mr. Godou,
if we have a shootout here,
it will only make the one who killed Mr. Muroto happy.
Weren't you the one who ordered it?
If you doubt me, I don't mind.
But you have to mete out retribution.
Claudia, you there...
I hope you have an option other than us duking it out prepared.
If you back off and agree to abide by my orders,
I will find the perpetrator within three days.
He will be presented to you.
We shall see...
...how to blackmail Inferno-style.
A counter sniping?
Yes.
That's reckless.
The Godou clan will be invited to Inferno's executive meeting the day after tomorrow.
They will be officially accepted as part of our organization.
Even Wisemel won't be able to lay his hands on them after they have joined.
This is his last chance.
So you do suspect Wisemel after all.
In the last attack and in the assassination of Muroto...
...he's the only one who would gain something.
It will take place on the 5th floor of the Atrium Hotel,
in the conference room with a glass front.
Display targets in a showcase, right?
You will ambush the sniper there.
Even after all that's happened, you still use the Godou clan as bait?
If you succeed, everything will be in good order.
Of course, it can't be done without you. It's a dangerous wager after all.
Phantom.
Ah, he's back!
Welcome home.
I'm back.
I'll warm up the soup, so wait for a bit.
Cal.
I found it when I was cleaning up.
You disassembled it?
Sorry, I'll fix it right away.
Are you good with gadgets?
I used to play around with whatever I could get my hands on by taking it apart.
I wanted to know how they worked.
Okay, it's done.
Put it back where you found it.
Okay.
Work?
Yeah.
Do you want to help me figure this out?
Yeah, I do.
What is it?
On the fifth floor of this building...
...will be your target.
If you succeed in assassinating him, you win.
Are you the one who will do the shooting?
No, not me.
Another sniper.
We must predict from where he will shoot.
You can't do it from just any place.
The sniper will be choosing his spot based on a few criteria.
Criteria?
It must have a certain height and be concealed.
Like a rooftop?
Yeah.
So, like here?
No, that's too close.
If you're discovered, the mission fails.
You need to be at least 400 yards away from the target.
400 yards?
Can you hit the target over that distance?
If you have the equipment and skill, 800 yards is still an effective range.
But that's a huge area.
It's hard to pinpoint a specific location.
Well, old methods are the best.
This is your homework before you go to sleep.
Let's eat now.
How is your task going?
All preparations are taken care of.
Leave it to me.
Don't mess up.
If you fail, I will cut off your Johnson.
Yes, sir!
What's the matter?
Hey, Reiji.
Isn't it uncomfortable to snipe from overhead?
What is?
When you shoot down from above...
How can I put it...
Isn't it annoying?
Did that sound strange?
No.
It didn't sound strange at all.
I agree, sniping like that is difficult.
That means we can ignore buildings that are too high, can't we?
Make sure that it's level with the target and in direct line of sight.
If we consider that, there shouldn't be that many spots left, right?
That's a good answer.
Is my answer correct?
You're correct so far.
Yahoo!
Next up tomorrow is directly visiting the site.
You will come along.
Eh, I may?
I can go out with you!
It's not for fun.
I know.
Excuse me.
Muroto's corpse was sent back home a while ago.
On their way back, Suzuki and Kakinuma will gather the group and head this way.
What about the guns?
Giuseppe is taking care of them.
I presume by tomorrow...
That german bastard...
Are you drinking to his farewell?
Yeah.
Have one too.
Skoal.
That bastard Muroto, he didn't finish his drink.
And not just him.
After I came here, Hamura and Shinjou as well.
Five of my subordinates have died so quickly.
Money is moving in the shadows.
This is the way of things.
They knew that.
That's why...
I'm angry because I didn't provide Muroto with a gun when we were faced with this kind of situation.
I will make sure to have Inferno pay for this directly.
Speaking of which, I suspect the
woman named Claudia.
Let me hear it.
We partly understand the means she has been using.
I think she is trying to break us up now.
Shiga.
That woman is innocent in this matter.
Your proof is?
Proof, huh?
Shiga, what's my nickname?
The five-colored spheres and the ascending dragon.
The dragon on my back is roaring.
Inside that woman lives the same dragon.
Determination keeps her alive just like me.
Hold the spheres and ascend to heaven.
That kind of dragon...
I understand 'cause we're alike.
We can just leave everything to that woman for now.
I can't really explain it with words alone.
Shiga, I depend on your intelligence.
Now you have to believe in my determination.
If you put it that way,
I will be covering your back.
You're here at last.
Well then, what will you do, Inferno?
Let's go!
Sorry, coming now.
It's a rare chance to go out with you, Reiji.
Let's go, then?
Okay.
That's the target building.
On the grounds that we talked about yesterday we can narrow down the spots he can use.
Then we can search the area and find the place he will use.
How do we do that?
Find the wind vanes.
Wind vanes?
Even if he's a pro, he can't shoot without preparation.
Particularly on this side of the building.
Wind?
That's right.
Strong wind will make shooting difficult.
The sniper has to see the wind at any given time.
You can't see wind, right?
Ah, I see.
Usually a sniper leaves wind vanes at different points.
Then he'll use places where it's natural to leave pieces of cloth or a flag.
That's right.
Cal.
Oh, sorry.
There's nothing over here.
Neither over there.
Let's go to the next place.
That's it for today then.
Wait, Reiji.
I feel uneasy here.
Uneasy?
That thing.
That's the place, Cal.
Jackpot.
Yes.
No doubt about it.
His sniping spot is over there.
Hey...
Reiji... will you shoot the sniper from here?
Yes.
Is he Judy's killer?
Possibly.
At the very least, his organization.
Let me be there.
Let me see the moment you shoot him.
A person's death is not something you should be seeing.
Judy...
...was killed before my eyes.
Usually a sniping mission consists of two people.
The sniper will be supported then.
With a different scope he can monitor the surroundings,
and aid in the sniping.
That's the spotter's job.
A role to watch until the end.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Cal, hold out your arm.
What is it?
Today's reward.
This is...
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll cherish it.
I'll cherish it forever.
The enemy is over there.
The sun is behind us.
The backlight will blind them.
That's right.
Clau.
Wisemel is arriving.
Is that so.
There's no sign of Randy Weber.
To leave Randy behind at such an important time is weird.
Something is fishy.
It's the promised day.
I will be interested in seeing that woman's move.
A white suit and a gun.
The perfect raiment for a plunge into hell.
Let's go Shiga!
Aye.
Wherever you go, I will be right behind you.
It seems that there's no one around, Reiji.
Maybe it's a different place.
Calm down, there's still time left.
Welcome to Inferno.
There he is!
There's someone behind the water tower.
Affirmative.
Can you confirm his face from where you are?
He's hiding, I can't see clearly.
I can't even tell the gender.
This is bad, Reiji, he'll shoot.
Hurry!
It's different.
It's not supposed to be her.
Reiji?
She is...
...already dead.
I...
...killed her.
Elen.
Reiji, shoot!
Your face...
Reiji?
Let me see it!
He's coming out!
Reiji!
Did you get hit?
No, it's just a scratch.
Reiji, you idiot.
Why did you do that?
I just wanted to confirm his identity.
You idiot!
You did great, spotter.
He was Judy's killer.
You've had your revenge.
With this, we know who was behind all this.
Next is...
You bastards!
What? What's happening?
There's someone else.
Eh?
No way.
She is...
Mission accomplished.
Impossible...
Yes,
Master.
I don't want to be separated.
I want to stay beside you.
To be useful for Reiji.
To feel necessary.