How my shrine has declined.
The world was once filled with
strife and countless vile wishes.
But their etchings here are long forgotten, and prayers are made here no more.
Rabou...
Yet here I am, alive.
We are gods of calamity.
Where we rise is also where we fall.
Isn't that so...
god named Yato?
Huh?
What?!
Hiyori, you idiot!
Why'd you come with us?!
Huh?
Wh-Where are we?
I have a tail?!
Huh? No way!
What's going on?!
Oh, boy.
I'm glad you could make it.
Rabou...
Looks like you've brought
along an uninvited guest.
You really are an eyesore,
do you know that?
Hiyori!
Huh?
You need to get away from here!
Once again...
Have at you!
Sekki!
Reiki!
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Chapter
A Scrap of a Memory
You will give back...
Hiyori's memory!
We've got him!
Too weak!
Damn! I can't break it from the inside!
Furuhime.
The god named Yato
has not yet returned.
Hiyori?!
Ow.
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah.
But what are you still doing here?!
I told you to get out of here!
Still... Thanks.
No problem.
What is that look?
What is that lax expression?
Where is he?!
Who?!
The god of calamity I know!
Where is Yato,
the god of calamity?!
With those beautiful eyes of depravity...
Where is that god named Yato?
I wish to cross swords with
that god of calamity!
Shut up!
I see.
It's still not enough.
What are you talking about?!
What are you—
Sekki!
Say, Rabou...
What an enormous Storm!
This doesn't bode well.
There's simply no end to the Phantoms!
Kazuma!
Yes?
What did Kofuku-dono tell you?
I doubt a Vent is causing
this particular Storm.
This is most likely the product of a tempestuous god of calamity.
A god of calamity?!
Yukine!
What are we gonna do, Yato?!
You're going to take Hiyori
and get away from here.
Huh?
I'm the one Rabou wants.
I'll keep him distracted.
Take that chance to escape.
But what about you?!
Without me, you'll be
completely unarmed!
Shut up! I'll figure something out!
What's that?!
That ball contains
Hiyori's memories.
Huh?!
What a shame.
How fleeting these things can be.
Hiyori!
Hiyori... Hiyori!
What do we do, Yato?!
Hiyori isn't waking up!
Forget about her, Yato.
She is but a voiceless,
mindless vessel now.
Nothing more than a heap of flesh.
Rabou...
Do you detest me?
Good.
Loathe me, O fierce deity.
Accept and awaken to
your maelstrom of hate...
god of calamity, Yato!
Be quiet.
Sekki!
Yes... Those are the eyes.
Come!
You come to me.
I'll hack that smirk off your face.
Yato?
This brings back memories.
Right now, the sky is the same
as when we truly lived.
We are gods of calamity.
Fierce deities that grant heinous wishes
and bathe the Near Shore in blood.
Rabou...
This is it.
The moment I've been waiting for.
The moment my wish is finally granted!
My name is Rabou.
Bearing a posthumous name,
I don this mask.
I hereby make myself a spirit vessel!
You who bear names that now
assemble cannot defy my orders!
Submit to and obey the mask!
Gather, depravity!
He's... absorbing the Storm?!
Fool.
Have you gone mad?
Merging with Phantoms like this...
Nay. I did it in order to
fight you, god named Yato.
To fight to the death!
Yato! Hey, Yato!
NORAGAMI
What's happening to me?
Me? Who am I?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
What is that smell?
Yato! You okay?!
Yato!
Rabou's coming!
Yato! Yato!
Yato!
It smells nice.
I've smelled it somewhere before.
I...
love this smell.
Stop... crying...
Yato.
Hi... Hiyori...
Hiyori!
Huh?
Hiyori! Hiyori! Hiyori!
Hiyori!
Wh-Wha...
Jungle...
Savate!
She broke free of my
spell all by herself?!
Did she unlock her memories?
How did she...
That's so indecent!
What the heck are you thinking, Yato?!
Hiyori...
You just... called me Yato.
Huh?
H-Hiyori's memory...
is back!
Huh?
Why am I...
Hiyori!
Why?
Why will you not return
to your old self?
We are gods of calamity!
We grant depraved wishes and
live off of human greed and hate—
Like I care!
Quit bringing up the past!
None of that matters anymore!
Let Hiyori go!
So it's you.
You are to blame!
Lowly half-Phantom...
You will serve as a
sacrifice for my power!
Sekki!
Let's take him out, Yukine!
Huh?!
But from this distance,
we'll get Hiyori—
It's just like a Borderline.
Rabou's absorbed a Storm
and combined with Phantoms.
Draw the line between
who lives and who dies!
M-Me?!
It's up to you, Yukine!
We can do this!
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
Yato!
Hiyori!
You okay?!
Let's go home!
Let's hurry and go home...
Yato!
Yato...
Your wish...
has been heard loud and clear!
Yato!
Yato... god...
His face!
Just as I thought.
You used a curse to
forcibly retain your body.
Why?
However many wishes we grant...
people will always fear, loathe,
and forget gods of calamity.
For better or worse,
people's emotions are always fickle.
That is the way of things.
It is our fate to be
slain though abandon.
But when I awoke after
slumbering for 500 years,
I yearned to be eliminated.
Not by just anyone,
but by you, one who
knew and understood me.
What a nuisance.
I'll be leaving first,
god named Yato.
God who shares the
same fate as mine...
I'm not like you.
A god...
...has ceased to exist.
Aw. Well, that was a failure.
I'd better go home and speak with Father.
So you really remember?
You remember me and Yato?
Yep!
But I have to ask, how did you
suddenly get your memory back?
Huh?
It was because of Yato's...
smell.
Hmm? What?
Oh...
It's nothing! Nothing at all!
Yeah, I wonder why!
I really have no idea!
Yato?
Hiyori.
What's with that serious look?
It's...
It's best if you cut all ties with us.
You'll live a much happier life that way.
So...
Hold on, Yato!
I refuse.
I have no desire to cut my ties with you!
Pi
ping
Hot
Oden
Soba-Dango
Shiruko
Sweet Sake
Wow!
You really said that, Hiyorin?!
Whoa!
But how come?!
She's just being hard-headed
for no good reason.
I'm not!
I want to stay with you!
I want to be with you forever!
And yet you tell me to
cut all ties with you?
Gosh! Way to go, Hiyorin!
Huh?
Booze!
This calls for a celebration!
U-Um...
When I said, "be with you forever," I didn't mean it like that!
I'll grant that wish...
for 5 yen!
Your wish...
has been heard loud and clear!
Iki Hiyori...
May our fates intertwine!
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more