Street No. 09
"Smash! Adult Shopping Plan"
And Yet the Town Moves
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
People respect and cherish the value of an item.
However, as time passes,
a spirit will come to dwell in the item
and become a supernatural being called
a Tsukumogami, or so they say.
KING
This is a story of one that became
possessed by the magic of things.
KOTOBUKI
TEA SET
Collection
The husband sold his pocket watch
and bought his wife a comb.
The wife sold her hair to buy a chain for the watch.
Such a great story.
O. Henry
Collection
This is how I want to be as an antique seller.
Isn't there a tasty story like this out there?
Welcome.
I want you to buy this from me.
It's an impressive pot.
But I can't pay very much for it.
I don't care about how much.
Such an ominous thing...
It's plenty that you take it off of my hands.
Thank you!
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
Oh?!
Price: "Negotiable"
This is...!
Let me ask you, where did you
get the pot in the front?
Yesterday, a certain woman came to sell this.
Just as I thought! Why, that woman!
Selling off my collection without my permission!
How much is this?! I'll put no limits
on how much I will pay!
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
Thank you!
I'm terribly sorry...
Could you take this off of my hands again?
Yes, thank you!
Pardon! Sell me that!
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
Thanks!
I'll sell it!
Yes, yes.
I'll buy it!
Sure, sure.
I can't take it anymore!
Please sell this off to a far away place.
You!
Don't do something to my collection without permission!
Well, you need to stop being
so obsessed about this thing!
It's my discretion!
How much do you think you spent on this?!
It's money that I made!
Think about me, too!
I can't let this go!
Which is more important, me or that pot!?
In any case, I'm taking this home!
And you can't say a thing about it!
Well, it went back and forth five times,
and so your total comes to this.
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
They say that people all have some sort of talent.
However, it's not uncommon that one never
notices it throughout one's life.
Those who realize their inherent gift
may be among a select fortunate few.
Sanada!
Yeah!
Gori!
Gori meant me?!
If you suddenly give me a nickname, I won't know!
My bad.
What are you doing, stupid Asai?!
Don't make Sanada mess up!
What are you looking at?
Oh, the guys? To think that's their test... I'm jealous.
So, which side is winning?
Huh? Um, I don't know.
I thought you were watching.
Yup, okay.
Good, next, Arashiyama.
Yes ma'am.
Whoa, Teacher...
It's dangerous to stand where I'm going to land!
Arashiyama, look behind you! Behind you!
Oh?
Did I teleport myself?!
Because you didn't extend your left arm,
you couldn't continue straight.
Okay, you can go over there and play table tennis...
Hey, what are you doing?!
I'm checking to see if there's a wrinkle in time-space...
"Careless miss" and "Aerosmith" sound similar, poko.
Tattsun, did you finish your test?
Of course, I beautifully twirled and posed.
Ta-da! Let's play table tennis!
With you?
Oh, well.
"Canned coffee" and "tourist spot" sound similar, poko.
Note: "Tourist spot" (kanko-chi) rhymes with "canned coffee" (kanko-hii) in Japanese.
I'll let her play around as she likes...
Here I go!
Oh...
Here.
I'm...
...pretty good at this, aren't I?!
Yeah, very good, very good.
See, I'm good.
Do you think I'm good?! Hey!
I'm letting you hit it...
...you know!
Whoa!
To her surprise, boasting 20/20 vision in both eyes,
Hotori's eyes did track the speeding ball!
But...!
Whether or not she can react is a different story.
That drive...
Your skill hasn't deteriorated, has it, Tatsuno?
Haribara...
Aw, there, there.
It's not fair! It's painful! It's round!
Round is irrelevant.
It's been a while. How about a round?
I'm sure Arashiyama is not up to par
to be your opponent.
Hey! I'm using this table—!
I never dreamt I'd see two ace players from Minami Third
Middle School battle it out in a place like this!
What are you... What are you doing?!
I'm from the same middle school as Tatsuno,
and I was in the Table Tennis Club, too.
Now I'm in the Film Appreciation Club.
Those two were feared as Minami Third's Fairy
and Minami Third's Grim Reaper!
Wow...
Oh, then what about Kon-senpai?
She's from the same middle school, too, right?
Futaba Kon...
It is said that whenever someone mentioned
that name all of the villagers shut their mouths...
What villagers?!
That person is in a class of her own...
She's Minami Third's Evil Queen...
or Evil God...
or Darth Vader...
God Warrior!
She took on so many different names,
I wonder if any of those names appropriately
described how insanely strong she was...
She's that strong, huh...?
And we start with Tatsuno's serve!
Wow! It's like the table tennis you watch on TV!
She's tough! Tatsuno's sense is not average after all.
I can't tell that she was inactive for over a year.
How can this be?!
Her footwork, which was supposed to be
her weakness, is now stable!
I can't break her pace!
If I may get a little more serious?
I'm remembering how it was in middle school,
so it's becoming more fun.
I was serious from the get go!
That stance! Don't tell me she's going to do it?!
What's "it"?!
It's coming!
Haribara Specialty: Scythe of the Grim Reaper!
Specialty: Scythe of the Grim Reaper...?!
In the past, there was one who chased that
deadly smash a bit too far, fell, and passed out.
That's why it's called the Scythe of the Grim Reaper...
...by me!
You're the one who named it?
Now, take this!
She returned it!
But player Tattsun loses her balance
and doesn't have a back-up!
Ha! I got this! I can defeat Toshiko Tatsuno!
I'm going to lose.
Sanada is watching.
I'm not going to let it happen!
Okay, let's put everything away!
Naito
Dental Clinic
Seaside
Open
Ohhh, my whole body is sore...
Fried Chicken
So what happened in the end?
I don't know about scoring and stuff in table tennis.
I lost. There's no way I can defeat
someone who's currently active.
Hmm. I realized something today.
Fried Chicken Girl
In regard to becoming a detective in the future.
I'm one who deduces,
and not one who chases the culprit.
Fried Chicken Girl
And so I don't need the skill to jump
over the vaulting box!
You too, Tattsun. Table tennis is
irrelevant to becoming Sanada's wife.
Have you been trying to mock me?
Or are you trying to make me feel better?
Is your heart so twisted you don't even know?!
I've always been a Jack of All Trades.
From violin to table tennis,
if I start, I become really good at it.
Even if I don't work very hard,
I can get to a certain point...
But once I hit that certain point, I stop improving,
and so the geniuses and hard-workers
become better at it than I am.
It's my destiny that I can't escape...
You should laugh at me.
I can't tell if you're being tough or weak.
Seaside
They say that all people have some sort of talent.
However, it's not uncommon that one
never notices it throughout one's life.
However, when it comes to outstanding traits of others,
they can be spotted very quickly.
Sanada! Did you see that match?!
Yeah.
They did stand out, right?!
They were ji... ji...
Jiggling! Her breasts.
Don't say it... You're so tasteless.
"Sunlight Photo," Class 2-A Hiroyuki Sanada.
For now, I just look at the sunset.
I will burn them into my chest,
those jiggling memories.
Sit on a rock for three years...
Be persistent as moss trying to penetrate a boulder.
Note: Famous Japanese maxims meaning that if you want something really bad,
be patient and hardworking and you'll eventually get it.
When the power of a wish is so strong that it can
defy history and change a dream into a reality...
Manju    Sponge
Buns     Cakes
100 yen    120 yen
Note: Famous Japanese maxims meaning that if you want something really bad,
be patient and hardworking and you'll eventually get it.
People call this a miracle.
Japanese Pastries MOURIYA
Welcome.
I thought I should have some before I go...
Thank you very much. I will be closing
up shop as of the end of this month.
What...?!
Both my mother and I loved it so...
It may have been the color,
but I couldn't sell much of them.
That can't be...
From now on, life without this...
Give me all that you have here!
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
Mmm...
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
So good!
Grandpa, did you get this
weird colored snack from a store?
Oh?
I was taking a walk earlier, and a stranger gave it to me.
Say, did you eat it?
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
No, I only got one of them, and I could never bring
myself to eat something colored so grotesquely.
This Bechikoyaki, it's the first time I've seen it...
Did you know about this, Grandpa?
Ah... come to think of it, a long time ago...
I didn't hear about it.
I wonder if they sell it at convenience stores.
If they do, I'm going to hoard them tomorrow.
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
Senpai, did you eat breakfast today?
I did eat.
You were all, "Eat, eat, eat, eat," and being noisy about it,
so I took some bread and spread some
trans fat all over it and ate it.
How can such an expression come out so smoothly...?
Oh, it's rare that you're moving
so early in the morning, Shizuka.
Yeah, well...
Do you kids know Bechikoyaki?
Bechikoyaki? I don't know.
Hm... seems like it's not something
that young people eat...
What is it? Does it taste good?
It's really good!
It looks blue and pink and neon green
and it's crunchy, but chewy...
Is that really food?
I went to three different convenience stores,
but none of them sell any.
"Love letter" and "Predator" sound similar, poko.
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
I wonder if it's a kind of local specialty.
Antiques Shop Kamei Dou
Mouriya... huh?
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
I hope I can place an order.
This number is no longer in use...
...please check the number—
The expiration hasn't passed yet...
Best by
Or has it?
That's so weird.
Mouriya Bechikoyaki
There were no matches for Mouriya Bechikoyaki
Tips for searching:
Make sure keyword is spelled correctly.
Use a different keyword.
Change to a more common keyword.
Use fewer keywords.
Bechiko
There were no matches for Bechiko
Tips for searching:
Make sure keyword is spelled correctly.
Use a different keyword.
Change to a more common keyword.
Use fewer keywords.
C
C Pre
C Prefec
C Prefecture
C Prefecture Miha
C Prefecture Mihasora
C Prefecture Mihasora City
C Prefecture Mihasora City snack
There were no matches for C Prefecture Mihaso...
Tips for searching:
Make sure keyword is spelled correctly.
Use a different keyword.
Change to a more common keyword.
Use fewer keywords.
Super
Kanto Map
That's absurd!
In C Prefecture, there is no Mihasora City...
Come to think of it, I've never heard of it.
Note: A play on words; "Mihasora" sounds awfully similar to the
solfege musical notes "Mi" "Fa" "So" "La."
What's going on? Were both the
snack store and contact info a hoax?
I was taking a walk earlier, and a stranger gave it to me.
C Prefecture
I sense a sort of purpose in that he was given one.
At least that means with this mysterious snack,
there's a third person who handed it to Grandpa.
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
EEL       RIKKE      LUNCH
SPECIALS
EEL BOWL WITH MISO SOUP
1800 yen
EEL       RIKKE       LUNCH
SPECIALS
A city that does not exist...
[Contact information]
270-00XX
C Prefecture Mihasora City 5-A-17
Phone: 047-00-XXXX
MOURIYA
Best by: 10.12.14
A phone number that is no longer in use...
A snack pouch with false information...
The only clue is the area code.
This area code covers C Prefecture.
Tomorrow, I will comb through this area code
and look for that snack shop...
Thank you for waiting, here's your eel bowl.
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Do you know of a snack shop
called "Mouriya" in this area?
It should be a specialty snack store,
or a Japanese pastry store...
Don't tell me, is it "Bechikoyaki"?
You're the third person to ask.
You're going to ask if it's a snack
that's made in this area, right?
I'm sorry, but I've never heard of it.
Are you from Tokyo as well?
You've come all the way from Tokyo so it must be good.
TAGAME INN
Sorry for the short notice.
That's okay.
I'm running this place almost like a hobby,
so I can't make you any dinner or anything...
I already ate, so I'm fine.
By the way... you wouldn't happen to
know of "Bechikoyaki," would you?
If you are hungry, I have this...
Here's the hot water.
"Ken Ogata" and "a large dog" sound similar, poko.
Note: The name of actor Ogata Ken (緒形拳)
rhymes with  "large dog - Oogata ken" (大型犬).
There were customers other than me
asking about Bechikoyaki at the restaurant.
On top of that, they were all from Tokyo...
They may have eaten it too... that gaudy-colored snack...
Emergency
Flashlight
They must have eaten it
because they came looking for it...
Someone was spreading Bechikoyaki around Tokyo?
But why...?
Oh, my mind is more awake now
than when I'm writing a novel...
To think that I'm sticking my nose
into something so strange...
Is this... real?
That snack... did I really eat it?
Miss...
This way please...
Don't tell me
Confectionary Store
Note: The kanji here doesn't mean anything, but it's pronounced "Sha-Fu-To,"
or Shaft, the name of the company that made this anime
Shaft
This is Mihasora City...
I finally arrived in Mihasora City!
Oh no...
I was about to go into something
out of fantastic literature...
Seaside
It's not right...
Um, according to these ingredients, even if you
fry or grill it, you won't get blue or pink.
I'm sure that's true, but...
Did you really eat it?
You went all the way to C Prefecture
and couldn't find it, right?
I'm sure it's a snack made with future technology.
That's it, Future Glasses-face!
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
I figured out the secret of this snack pouch!
Who are you calling Future Glasses-face?!
MOURIYA
Best by
See, the expiration date is only two digits, right?
So this snack may not be from this year, 2010,
but actually from 2510 in the future.
If it's centuries in the future, it's not uncommon
for there to be unknown cities...
And so, let's give up on making Bechikoyaki on our own.
In the present time, it's impossible to cook!
I'm so full I feel sick.
Me too.
Fantastic literature turns into science fiction, huh...
Japanese Pastries MOURIYA
Time Traveler Ryosuke Akimori
Welcome Home!
Year 2310
Time Traveler Ryosuke Akimori
Welcome Home!
How do you feel after finishing your job
as mankind's first time traveler?
Time Traveler Ryosuke Akimori
Welcome Home!
Well... I'm still jet-lagged so...
Now that you have returned,
what would you like to do first?
I used to love a snack called Bechikoyaki...
If I had some now, I would love to eat that.
Ah, after doing something so fantastic
you must miss ordinary foods, don't you?
Ordinary...? Do you know Bechikoyaki?
Time Traveler Ryosuke Akimori
Welcome Home!
Bechikoyaki, right?
They sell it anywhere.
I have some in my bag. Would you like some?
If you're okay with just one, you can have mine.
MOURIYA
BECHIKOYAKI
If you let your wish sit on a rock for 300 years,
in due time it will cause a miracle.
We've heard that you performed many
experiments in our world 300 years ago...
What were the results?
BECHIKOYAKI                                                                                    BECHIKKO
BECHIKKO                            BECHIKO                              BECHIKKO
BECHIKKO
FULL HOUSE
BECHIKO
BECHIKOYAKI
MOURIYA
BECHIKKO
It was a success!
"Safety pin" and "Argentine" sound similar, poko.
Welcome!
Say Shizuka, could you buy this from me?
Sure, but I wouldn't be able to pay you much for this.
That's okay. It's better than throwing it out.
Say, doesn't anyone in your family want this?
If they did, I wouldn't come to sell it.
Then I don't want it.
Why?!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
Speaking of macaroni, don't you feel like you're being
ripped off because of the hole in the center?
No I don't.
But it may have been the tastiest part, you know?
Urgh, if you put it that way, I'm beginning to think that...
Once I started thinking about it,
I felt like I was missing out in life.
So I tried to make some macaroni without holes.
How did it go?
It was just fat spaghetti.
Cafe Seaside
Next, Street Number Ten,
"Old Men and Holes."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 10 "OLD MEN AND HOLES"
Sexily we turn around and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside