The one I like... is you.
You don't have to give me a reply right away.
I just wanted to let you know...
...that there's somebody here who's in love with you.
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
Bon, you're stoppin' again...
Be quiet. I'm going to come back
in here with a cool improvised riff.
It don't mean a thing if you don't actually play.
Looks like you're havin' a good time, Sen-bou.
Mind if I sit in?
Jun-nii!
Oh, you're early!
Actually, I already mentioned this to Ricchan's dad,
but I've got some good news...
Would you cats be up for playing
jazz in front of an audience?
The bar I worked at here asked us to
do a Christmas performance for 'em.
It's a foreigners' bar for the U.S. troops stationed here,
so if we're gonna do this,
we'd better put some spunk into it.
Well? Want to give it a go?
Yes!
Good!
We got just one month before Christmas,
so that doesn't leave us much time!
What'll we play?!
Christmas, that reminds me...
Sen, isn't that on your birthday?
Yeah.
I'm almost 16!
We'd better do a decent performance.
It's been a while, so for starters,
let's try playing together.
Oh, yeah!
This'll be our first session
as a quartet since summer vacation!
One, two, a one-two-three!
Come on, Bon, ain't you gonna play?
What's wrong, Kaoru-kun?
Once in a while, this guy just freezes up.
Kaoru-kun's got a classical background,
so maybe he's shooting for perfection.
Don't think you need to do
anything complicated at first.
All you really have to do is hit the keys.
That's plenty lively for an improvisation.
Try to remember how it felt
when you went wild while we played during summer vacation.
You said it, Jun-nii! Right on!
Go for broke, Bill Evans!
Oh, he looks just like 'im!
Never thought I'd meet Bill
Evans in a place like this!
Now I think we can expect you to play great!
By the way, what were you doing
the other day with Yurika-san?
Huh?
In the back of the art room.
Y-You saw that?
So, are you two already in that kind of relationship?
What do ya mean?
Don't play dumb.
You can't tell me nothing happened
when you were dressed like that!
Don't be a dope!
She just asked me to model for her painting.
No!
Tilt your head more!
Gaze at that twig passionately!
I didn't get what it was about,
but it was over before I knew it.
Oh, is that all?
Huh? Why am I so relieved?
Oh. I see.
That must be it.
Come to think of it,
she told me to model for her every week.
Huh. Sounds like there's hope for you yet.
What will you do next time...
...if she does something like that to you?
Why, you! What the hell
do ya think you're doin'?!
Get back here, Bon!
Hey, who is that Nishimi guy, really?
Maybe the "secret boss."
I heard your nephew got the
top score on his final exam.
That's wonderful.
And besides being a prodigy, he can even play the piano!
Yes, well, I don't like how he has
been staying out late these days...
Oh, you worry too much!
After all, he's the only male
heir in the Nishimi family.
I have to make sure he maintains his grades, so he can go to a prestigious school.
Dad... hurry home already.
Even though I'm surrounded by people...
I'm always alone here.
CHRISTMAS
SALE
Furuya Music Shop
Yamaha Pianos and Electones
Christmas, that reminds me...
Sen, isn't that on your birthday?
I don't see him buying a new pair for himself.
Maybe I'll get them for him,
from one jazz musician to another.
K-Kaoru-san?!
Ricchan...
O-Oh my gosh!
It looks like we both had the same idea.
Oh, no, this is...
Sentaro is a lucky guy.
Oh, I know!
We'll each buy one stick and give them to him as a pair.
Let's do that, okay?
This is a strange development.
Maybe it's okay if things stay this way.
I wonder what Ricchan thinks of me...
Are you okay? Do you have a cold?
No, winter in Kyushu is pretty cold.
I wouldn't be surprised if it started to snow.
Oh, it's not that cold!
It rarely snows here in December.
Look!
Kaoru-san, how did you know?!
This is amazing!
Just like in a movie!
It's so beautiful!
Oh, it melts right away.
This won't stick.
Look, Kaoru-san!
It's...
M-Merry Christmas.
Cut it out, Kota!
You're gonna pay for that!
Rikko-neechan?
Who are you?!
How dare you make Rikko-neechan cry?!
It's Bon, from when we had watermelon!
Oh, what are you doin' here?
N-Nothing special...
Nii-chan! He just made Rikko-neech—
What about Rikko?
I-It's a misunderstanding.
He's the last person I wanted to see right now.
Nii-chan, I have to pee...
Alright, how 'bout we all race home?
The winner gets to have
the biggest piece of cake!
Ready? Go!
Wait!
Look at 'em go.
You wanna join us for cake too, Bon?
Of course not.
Oh yeah, your family is rich.
Bet you have a fancy cake
waitin' for you at home.
Oh, shut up.
Somebody who takes being surrounded
with a loving family for granted
will never understand that there
are people who live in a house
but have no place in it!
Am I jealous of him?
Because he has the thing I wish for more
than anything but can never have?
Go home!
Your family's waiting for you, aren't they?!
When I'm around you, it only
makes me feel more miserable!
Hey! Max Roach!
These are some really nice sticks.
Thank Ricchan.
I just laid out half the money for them.
Oh, so one's from Rikko
and one's from you, huh?
That's pretty clever.
Wha...
Come with me!
What?!
Just do it!
No! Let go of me!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up!
Ow!
Damn it...
Wh-What?
Ricchan...
Why is that kid next to
Ricchan in all these photos?
It's easy to tell when you see
me as a little kid, right?
That I have mixed blood...
Bon, I'm one of those that ain't
got a place in the house too.
Ever since I was born...
Hey, America!
Can't you speak English?!
Don't look!
Sentaro!
Mother! Aren't Yasuko's things in that box?!
I don't care. She's no daughter of mine!
Seducing an enemy soldier,
bearing his child, and in the end,
abandoning her shame here before running away!
I don't remember giving birth to a daughter like that!
What's wrong, Sentaro?
Where's Grandma?
So you didn't see anything either, right, kid?
Sentaro, this is apparently a memento
your mother left behind when she went away.
Sentaro, the rosary isn't a necklace.
Take it off.
You're always wearin' this thing.
Let me borrow it a minute.
Don't touch it!
Hey, that's
Kawabuchi, the kid who went nuts yesterday.
Sentaro! You won't have any friends
left if you keep getting into fights!
I didn't have any to begin with.
My dad lost his job around then and
stayed home gettin' drunk every day.
Couldn't even look me in the eye no more.
Eventually, though, he found
a job in another prefecture
and said he was gonna live an'
work there for a while.
I thought it was my fault.
He's still workin' there now,
and hasn't come home in years.
It's never a dull moment at home,
but once in a while, I start thinkin'...
...if it's really okay for me to be there.
I said too much.
I'm mortified.
I was so convinced this guy had it all.
Those things I yelled at him...
It's like we're children playing around on an organ.
Sentaro!
Yeah? What is it, Kaoru?
Let's practice some more.
Maybe even every day, until our gig...
Dummy! That goes without sayin'!
We gotta knock the socks off them Americans!
I get it.
This is the guy that Ricchan loves...
My love feels so petty in comparison.
Since then, we put our all
into every day's session.
Time flew and before we knew it,
the day had come.
Our first time on stage...
Excuse me...
Foreign soldiers gather to drink here.
It's no place for a young lady like you.
I was invited by a friend to come listen to some jazz.
Oh, pardon me.
You're a respectable customer.
After you, young lady.
Stop calling me "young lady."
It feels like you're mocking me.
Yurika-san...
Ritsuko-chan, long time no see.
All right, just play like we practiced at first,
but feel free to go crazy with
it once you get in the groove.
Let's have some fun.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the Mukae Tsutomu Quartet.
One, two, one-two-three-four...
What's wrong with him?
He's stiff...
Is it because Yurika-san's watching?
Wake up!
Pipe down already!
Hey, stop! Stop it, already!
I can't stand that coon music jazz!
It sounds like a jumble of noise!
At least play something white!
What's he sayin', Bon?
He says he doesn't like black jazz,
so we should play white jazz.
Huh?
What kinda segregation is that?!
What are you tryin' to say, old man?!
Don't do it, Sen-bou! Suck it in!
You can't get through to a drunk like that.
Just ignore him.
I can't play like this!
Kaoru-kun...
Can you play that one song?
"But Not for Me."
Oh... I think so.
At this rate, the party's
going to end on a sour note.
But maybe we can at least
lighten up the mood.
Just the two of us?
Don't worry.
It'll just be like we're playing for fun.
They're writing songs of love, but not for me.
A lucky star's above, but not for me.
With love to lead the way,
I've found more clouds of gray
than any Russian play could guarantee.
Jun-niisan is amazing.
I can understand why Sentaro gets so
excited every time he comes back to town.
It's only natural to admire him.
Anyway, Jun-niichan really surprised me!
You're the hero of the night, Jun-niichan!
Oh, Jun-niichan, pretending you
don't know what I'm talking about!
Damn it! So frustrating!
Thanks to that jerk cuttin' in,
I didn't get to play even
half of what we practiced!
But it was a good experience.
The unexpected is really what
makes jazz fun, isn't it?
Listen to you, soundin' like an expert!
Cut it out!
Am I buggin' you?!
Um, young la... I mean...
It's Yurika.
Yurika, huh?
What shall I call you?
That's right. Sometimes life is like jazz
and goes in an unexpected direction.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.