West Misato High School
Come on, Yuu-chan! Hurry up and get changed!
Don't interrupt me.
I'll do it after I finish eating.
You can eat that just fine while walking!
It's bad manners to walk and eat!
You have a point, but still...
Prepare to be entertained!
Huh?
Yuu, still in your tracksuit?
Haven't had enough of gym yet?
You're not allowed to wear that home, so you'll be in real trouble if the teachers see you.
See? Everyone wants you to change.
Everyone's aching to go home,
but you're holding them up.
Shizuku
Why did you write that?!
This is actually perfect.
I wanted to stop by the vending machines anyway.
Kaede, let's go.
Sure.
Now I can eat until they get back.
glance
nom
I'll change your clothes for you.
Just let me eat!
Stop struggl—
What are you doing, Harupoppo?
Yuu-chan, you too.
I forgot they were still here!
Um, I was just taking off her clothes...
Taking off?
Haruka, can it!
What's gotten into them?
We're back!
Hey, stop playing around and change already.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
What're you doing?!
You saved my life, Yuu-chan!
One more second and I would've drowned.
You saved me
You did it on purpose!
You said you'd come to my rescue if I started drowning, after all!
That's not what I meant!
"Rescue"?
Was someone in trouble?
President Mitsuki!
Be careful not to get hurt.
Okay!
Haruka-san in a swimsuit...
fon
dle
I didn't think you'd actually come.
President Mitsuki...
I just thought it wouldn't hurt
to do this once in a while.
Don't read too much into it.
Is that really the truth?
You didn't come to keep an
eye on Haruka and Yuu again?
Let's all have fun together.
You two...
And, go!
Onee-chan can't swim!
"Swimsuit Fanservice: Accidents Included"
Onee-chan, are you okay?
Thanks, Yuu.
I'm sorry.
M-My glasses!
We've gotta find them.
Wh-Where are they?
I'll find them for you, so just sit tight.
I found them.
You left something way more important than the glasses behind!
Having a blast, girls?
You bet!
You don't mind that it's indoors?
Not at all!
Not many people have pools at their houses.
That's Kotone for you.
Kotone-san organized all this?
I did! Play to your hearts' content!
She may not look it, but she's actually a rich girl!
R-Right...
I had no idea.
There!
Putting that aside, why are we holding the cultural festival after-party at a heated pool?
That's a good question.
You don't know either?
It was Shizuku-chan's idea.
Shizuku-san's idea?
dot
W-Well you see, swimming is a physical activity, so it helps you slim down.
You just seem to be drinking though...
It took all my effort to secure the location.
Wanna swim?
Okay.
President Mitsuki, you don't know how to swim either?
I never learned myself.
Haruka-san is talking to me!
N-Not being able to swim isn't such a big deal, right?
Not acceptable!
I'm going to whip you two
into tip-top swimming shape!
That doesn't sound too bad.
Would you prefer I use this one?
The other one, please.
Come on, kick harder!
Haruka got taken away.
Shizuku-chan, play with me.
Get up, Shizuku-chan.
Hey, hey, get up, Shizuku-chan!
Okay, enough.
Swim with us, Shizuku-chan.
I-I have delicate skin.
I need to take extra care not to damage it.
You're terrible at this, Harupoppo!
The flutter kick is the most basic of techniques.
Same to you, President Mitsuki. Looks like we'll be here all day.
Everyone who can't swim, gather over here!
Coach Kotone's looking at you.
I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
Set me free!
Who cares if we can't swim?!
They need some motivation.
Hello? Please bring them here.
They're wheeling something out!
Her name is Yamada-san.
Yamada-san?!
The next two are Suzuki-san and Tanaka-san.
If you can learn how to swim...
You'll get a reward!
That doesn't make me happy at all!
She sped up?!
Success!
I follow Yamada, and this is what I find.
Shinobu?
Kotone-oneesama, I see you've returned.
Huh? Isn't she...
She's Kotone's grade-school sister.
I'm in middle school now!
Ah, sorry.
Shizuku!
I should've known you were the one invading my house!
It was Kotone's idea to come here in the first place.
Such blatant lies.
Keep your nonsense to yourself!
It's been this way as long as I can remember.
Good afternoon.
Whenever she came over, Kotone-oneesama would always...
Shizuku-chan!
Hey, knock it off.
...start messing with her instead of me!
I for one really wish she didn't.
More importantly, Kotone-oneesama,
Mother and Father are furious that you decided to live on your own.
You've even delayed talks of your engagement.
Starting today, you will be living with us again.
Why'd you stop? Keep those feet moving.
Just wait a second!
Don't touch Chappy-kun with your wet hands!
S-Sorry.
Are you really fine with this, Kotone-chan?
I don't know your circumstances, but the sadness on your face is plain as day.
But...
What about you, Shizuku-chan?
Are you fine with this too?
Yes.
No matter how much time we spend together, I won't be able to make you happy, Kotone.
If there's someone waiting for you,
you should face them properly.
Don't use me as your escape!
Don't kiss me if you're just playing around!
Shizuku-chan!
Calm down, Shizuku-chan.
Is that really how you feel?
I won't give Kotone-oneesama
to a home wrecker like you!
Shinobu!
Stop right there, everyone!
Why don't you settle this with a match?
Has she seriously been doing
that the whole time?
Good idea. We'll have Shinobu-chan and Shizuku-chan duke it out for the right to house Kotone!
Naturally, we'll have a swim race.
Yamada, prepare my swimsuit.
Of course.
Sorry, everyone.
There's something I've been keeping from you all...
I can't swim.
No, we knew that.
Shizuku-chan.
Use this.
All ready over here.
Why is there a stuffed animal on your back?
His name is Chappy-kun!
Chappy-kun is a master of the doggy paddle!
Chappy-kun and I are of one mind and body.
You have no chance of victory.
That's totally unfair!
President Mitsuki actually believes her.
On your marks...
This ticks me off.
Sh-Shizuku-chan, good luck.
Why did that make me happy?
Stupid... stupid Kotone.
But still...
I can't...
The victor is Shizuku-chan!
Excuse me!
It's unnatural for Chappy-kun to get this heavy just from absorbing some water!
You set me up, Yamada!
My apologies.
That's great, Shizuku-chan!
You did it!
Well done!
Congrats!
Did Yamada-san do that for Kotone?
Yuzu, you weren't fazed at all.
There was a serious catfight in the works just now.
A-Actually, I was pretty worried...
I wonder what that kiss Shizuku-chan mentioned was all about.
Wasn't it just that time Kotone kissed her on the cheek?
You really think so?
What else could it be?
You've got an overactive imagination, Kaede.
There's nothing more to it.
Yeah, you're right.
"Swimsuit Fanservice: Accidents Included"
The end
Big Sister
Little Sister
See you later!
It's so chilly...
It was a good idea to wear a scarf.
Haruka!
kyaa!
Yuu-chan just hugged me from behind!
Morning.
But if her nose is running, that means...
"Shopping with Yuu-chan"
Why didn't you wear a scarf or anything?
I had one, but I gave it away.
G-Gave it away?
Hey, Yuu!
I can't see anything...
Yuu, where are y—
H-Hey, it sounds like that person is looking for you!
We should run!
I told you, I have my own scarf...
Oh, it was just President Mitsuki.
Haruka-san?!
I-In any case...
Yuu, you're going to catch a cold.
Wear this.
No.
Why won't you listen to me?
Goodness gracious.
You're studying for entrance exams, so it's worse if you get sick.
That's just an excuse.
Big Sister
Little Sister
I'll be heading to school first then.
Do you really hate that neck warmer that much?
Maybe I should use it instead.
Go for it.
Yay! A hand-me-down from Yuu-chan!
It was originally Onee-chan's, though.
I haven't worn it a single time.
You mean it wasn't yours?!
You never wore it because
it was a hand-me-down?!
You see, the scarf I used to
wear started falling apart.
Then Onee-chan said...
You can use my backup.
You know?
There's one at this shop
that I have my eyes on.
That doesn't mean you should
ignore her goodwill.
You mustn't let things go to waste.
Then I'll give it to you!
Don't let it go to waste, okay?
That's right...
Morning!
Good melody!
Melody!
Yuu brought someone shady along!
It's just Haruka.
Ta-da!
So anyway, did you do the bio homework yet?
Haven't touched it.
Nothing?!
So I was thinking of buying a
new scarf after school today.
Cool.
You got one in mind?
There's this fluffy one...
Good morning.
Hey Shizuku-chan, mo—
That's the one I was talking about!
Wait, but if Shizuku-chan has it, then...
Oh, this?
It caught my eye yesterday, so I bought it.
There was only one left, so I splurged a bit.
Shizuku-chan spent all night
posing in front of the mirror.
So what? It's none of your business.
Haruka...
Are they all gone?
I know! Why don't we go look for an even better one after school today?
I wanted that one!
But Shizuku-chan got to it first...
That's the one I want!
Then...
You'll have to live with this.
Haruka, let's go shopping!
She must really hate it...
Scarf, scarf, so fluffy...
Hopefully they have one left.
Half off
This is so cute!
It's even half off!
Look at how nice this color is!
I might have to try it on.
Scarf!
Sorry, sorry.
They're really all gone.
Isn't this flower-patterned one just as cute?
I wanted the other one.
Want to try some other shops?
They might have something similar.
Let's go, Yuu-chan.
Haruka...
Just try it on already!
Changing Room
The balance is off...
Half  off
If my bust wasn't so big I'd fit an S size too...
Yuu-chan, the S doesn't really fit me right.
What did you think?
Haruka got fat, so we need an M.
Yuu-chan!
I understand.
Gotta shave off those pounds, Haruka.
Y-Yeah...
That's not why!
Oh yeah!
Let's ask if they have any left in stock.
Here's the dress in an M size.
Excuse me!
Yes?
Do you have any more of the scarf
Shizuku-chan bought yesterday in stock?
Yuu-chan!
How is she supposed to understand?
A scarf that was bought yesterday?
It's white, and all soft and fluffy...
She's never going to get it...
Just a moment.
Half off
Think she'll find one?
I doubt she will, even if they have it.
Is this the one?
She's such a pro!
This is it!
It's just what I was looking for!
It's one of our bestsellers.
Take as much time as you need.
We should've just asked her from the start.
Yeah!
Haruka, isn't that one adorable?
Seriously?!
I'll buy this one.
Then wait for me to try this on.
Haruka, Haruka.
I'll be at the registers!
She couldn't contain her happiness.
The
Next
Day
I didn't get enough sleep.
I hope Yuu is wearing the neck warmer I gave her.
It looks like she has it on today.
H-Haruka-san?!
Haruka-san is wearing my neck warmer!
B-But why?!
"Shopping with Yuu-chan"
The end
Big Sister
Thanks for your patience!
Service Extras
It's time for the popular weekly corner!
This is the first time.
First up is President Sonoda Mitsuki.
Is she really related to Yuu?
Noda Kotone's shameless body.
There's too much to be jealous of!
The D-cup Takayama Haruka-san.
Haruka's a C-cup!
Yuu?!
The transcendent cutie, Iizuka Yuzu-chan!
Stop, you're embarrassing me!
The adorable Minami Shizuku-chan.
Her figure's nicer than you'd expect.
The cute and petite Sonoda Yuu-chan.
She covering any traces of her boobs.
Ikeno Kaede.
So short!
It's okay, I know how it is...
Extra
Service Extras
The End
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
Kaedekko, Kaedekko.
What?
I feel like the two of us never get the chance to talk.
It's just you.
Could it be that you actually hate me?
I don't hate you, it's just...
Just what?
I can't overlook what you have that I severely lack!
Next time, Trick 8:
"Sakura-colored Wedding"
"Sakura-colored Christmas"
and "Sakura-colored Christmas".
Look forward to it!
So what do I have that you don't?
I'll never tell.