Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Someone with Shrine shouldn't speak of the end of the world so lightly.
Don't misunderstand me. I care about Shrine and the parallels.
I'm just looking for a compromise here.
Let's Think of a Solution Together
Chapter Twenty Five
Present (19)/ Inari A
No doubt you are aware of this,
but Shrine's duty is to maintain the balance of parallels as representatives of God.
Planetary General
Agency Shrine
The living populate the twelve worlds,
and the dead congegate in the beyond.
That has been the order of things.
Permitting a thirteenth world which
destroys the balance is out of the question.
You were told as well, were you not?
Or did you leave blanks in your memory upon reincarnation?
I didn't do that.
Nobody told me anything.
Let's be serious. There's no way God would interfere.
How else could the Mirror Capital enjoy such a long existence?
If he really were in opposition of it,
why would he simply overlook it all this time?
If its existence opposes both Shrine and God,
how could my master create it in the first place?
Why am I able to spend time with my mother and the others here?
How can that be possible?
Who decides what is permissible? When? Where?
Tell me, priest!
I can't think of this place as dispensable merely because it's not accepted by Shrine dogma.
I don't care whether this proves difficult to manage.
Erasing its existence is clearly the wrong path.
I won't abandon the world I see before me.
I want to know the truth about
myself and the world around me.
Answer me, head priest.
If I wasn't honest with myself here,
I'm sure
that my future
would be dark and dreary.
Koto...
Koto!
Koto! You're wonderful!
You're amazing!
A miracle bestowed upon us!
Master... What's gotten into you?
Listen well now, Koto!
I'm a god!
What?
What do you mean, Dad?
I had these doubts all along, you know.
When the world was made, its rules were made as well.
Back then there were only the three of us: the head priest, our father and me.
Our father couldn't be assed to do anything,
so he's been hiding somewhere ever since.
He just shrugged off a metric ton of jobs and duties to me and the head priest.
That's not the problem, though.
We owe him our existence.
Even I listen to my own creator.
Besides, what else was I gonna do?
The head priest made his organization to oversee and regulate the world.
At first I helped him out with that.
It was fun and rewarding.
It wasn't even called Shrine back then.
They used to have these giant lizards back then!
That was a fun age.
I liked it.
All that is over now.
We got lots of ice and snow for a while, humans appeared,
and my brother and I just spent our days minding our duties.
He's just as serious and good-hearted as he seems.
He took care of his daily chores diligently.
I wasn't as enthusiastic.
It's pretty weird, you know?
Every now and then something new appears that we had no hand in.
Weird, right?
We're left in charge of the world, yet things keep getting decided behind our backs.
I don't mind if it works out, but the appearance of mankind really messed up the world.
They just do whatever they want and complicate everything.
I mean it! Nothing works out.
I've forgotten what a well-sorted world was like.
Everything is just a big, idiotic mess.
Diligently following my instructions like my
brother is way more than what I signed up for.
I decided I'd start doing what I, myself, want.
I promised I'd be around when the shit hits the fan, though.
I suppose I wasn't exclusively helpful, but I did help, right?
The head priest is your brother?
You're unusually talkative.
This is the time for explanations!
You see, the creation of life was originally entrusted to me.
So, you being born by somebody
else was something of an accident.
I was a bit creeped out at first.
To put it delicately, I don't really like myself.
Seeing another me born to somebody else was just an absolute catastrophe.
You're about as much like me as you can be without being me.
But this was, truly, and act of God.
Beyond my power.
Can you feel the tragedy?
It sounds grand when I say I have the power to create life,
but at the end of the day I'm bound to God's will too.
But when I was raising you I realized what a wonderful, smart, and cute kid you were!
You moved me, Koto!
I made up my mind!
"If this crazy little girl grew up the way I wanted her to,
I could live through her!"
You've grown into a person who's surpassed my dreams and hopes.
Koto, you're the other me that I was wishing for!
Lay bare the secrets of Heaven, and tell me all the answers.
Chapter Twenty Six
Present (20) / Inari B
What are you doing?!
She told you, didn't she?
We're turning this into our stronghold and destroying the parallels.
Head priest!
Are you okay, head priest?
Go back to Shrine.
But!
Inari?
Sorry.
Darling!
What did you do to he—
I'm sorry, Koto.
I'll explain later.
Shine brighter than anything.
Your light can put cracks into this warped world.
Are you really the head monk?
Are you so startled that you have a younger sister?
Isn't Koto cute?
I thought you'd come home to us.
I thought we'd all live together again.
I was waiting
for your return.
For a very long time.
I thought I could give you back your name and prayer beads.
We could talk about inconsequential things...
I thought that would've been a good way to end it.
But you—
Why didn't you use it?
That's why I gave it to you.
I just held onto it for you!
You never change!
I never asked for a lease on life nor these beads!
I'm done dancing to your tune!
You promised that this would be the last time!
You said that you'd return with the beginning and the end in tow.
All you ever bring is the end.
Koto!
You're right.
I think I'm only bringing the end once again.
Why won't you, then,
be the beginning?
All the actors have assembled!
The rest is up to you,
Myoue!
Chapter Twenty Seven
Present (21)/ Myoue
Yakushimaru!
Kurama?
Sleeping through the apocalypse?
We should have ditched him!
He's immortal anyway.
Got a problem?
Nothing I could say would help here.
Good grief.
Just what is our dear father thinking?
Let's try to get out.
I want my controller!
What are you trying to do?
Whatever, man.
Are you saying there's something I could do?
They're back and they're the same as ever.
If anything, it's worse than ever.
Even Koto's gone off the deep end.
What now?
Myoue.
We might be better off staying buried here forever.
Myoue!
What?
Get a grip.
Will you stop whining?
Live your own life.
Your world changes with you, and only then.
Stop dwelling on the days of yore.
Older brother
Older sister
We are fake siblings made to comfort you.
Surely you realize this.
Myoue.
You were supposed to rule the Mirror Capital alone, Myoue.
The Council of Three was impotent until you took reign of the world.
It's time for you to leave your comfort zone.
Surely you realize this.
Myoue!
Look at me!
Be strong, Myoue.
The things you ought to do are not in the past just yet.
Look ahead.
Move ahead.
Fear not. Your past remains.
Desiring a future does not betray the past,
Yakushimaru.
Too slow!
Sorry.
At least we brought all the reconstruction materials we could gather.
Good! Let's get cracking!
We have no time to lose.
See you, fake monk.
Assuming I don't vanish with the rest.
I take my leave.
Do as you see fit.
How bring the sun is when you climb out of a hole...
Fascinating.
When was it again?
Sitting under a sky aglow with dusk,
our little boat lingered onward dreamily.
Children three nestled near with eager eye and willing ear.
Long has paled that sunny sky.
The echoes of their laughter and the memories of our joy
have all been slain by autumn frosts.
Where has she gone,
having rivaled the sun itself?
Yase?
Look at that light.
Pretty, isn't it?
Can you bring it here?
No.
Too bad.
You should take shelt—
Oh, right. Where would you?
Don't worry.
I like this place, so I'm staying.
What about you?
Why are you here?
Just happened by.
Oh?
But you don't think this place is so bad, right?
Yase!
You always wished for your own death,
but you never once wished for the Mirror Capital's.
You've always been quite hopeless as a little brother,
but I always felt you'd be a fine Myoue.
In a Wonderland they lie,
Dreaming as the days go by,
Dreaming as the summers die:
Ever drifting down the stream—
Lingering in the golden gleam—
Life, what is it but a dream?
Thanks.
Koto!
Are you crying again?
You never seemed this much of a crybaby.
Guess we have that in common.
Myoue...
Hey.
Myoue?
Myoue, what should I do?
The world's gonna end, and it's all my fault!
It's not gonna end.
I'm not gonna let it end. I hope.
When our father left,
he gave me something beside his word.
He gave me his power of creation.
Myoue...
I don't want it to end like this either.
Sorry I said you bring the end.
Koto... you're the beginning for me.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
This was so long! And so fun! And I'm so hungry!
Can I die now?
Can I go outside now?
I love you, Mom!
Everything's so lively!
Something happen?
It's the final episode, apparently.
No!
Kyousougiga: Comic Movie of Crazy People Living Every Day to its Fullest
Next time: "Kyousougiga: Comic Movie of
Crazy People Living Every Day to its Fullest".
Finishing move: The Grand Finale!