This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
She went to an audition for the part of a shampoo's image character, but...
...she met a very spiteful girl there.
The girl's name is Wakamatsu Madoka.
For some ulterior motive...
...she seems to hold a grudge on Full Moon.
So much that... she put up a huge fuss over the results of the audition.
Ah.. for heaven's sake!
I just want to kick her in the head!
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
For this commercial...
Full Moon-san and Wakamatsu Madoka-san...
We're counting on you.
What's with that?
Madoka-san.
I'm so glad I get to work with you!
Let's do our best together!
Please, just choose one of us!
What?
I can't stand this girl!
W-Why..?
Two Different People
Oh, crap.
That's cause...
...Full Moon-san's image doesn't go well with mine!
I'm really worried!
Can we really make a good commercial?
Like such a weak performance ever gonna deceive anyone!
Hmm...
That is true.
Ah!
Valg... got a sec?
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Well...
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Like I said... the image I want is...
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
But for the characters in a commercial...
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
Mermaid
Tear
Commercial
Audition
Room
...they're totally different.
That's why.
Um...
If you would just calm down...
I'm sure something will...
Madoka-san... why?
Erm... sorry to keep you waiting.
We have come to a conclusion.
We will have a camera test for both of you the day after tomorrow.
After that... we will be able to
make our final decision.
Eh?!
Which means...
...accordingly...
We will choose one person over the other.
Thank you very much.
What?
Well that must suck.
That's all you have to say?
No "Wakamatsu Madoka's horrible!" or...
"Meroko's so cute!"?
Well...
Not really...
Geez!
We're working so hard!
Say something else!
Didn't I already say that it sucks?!
Not that!
Geez!
Huh?
Something with more feeling!
Do you have a fever?
A cold?
That's not it!
'Cause... your face is totally red.
This is... you know...
Yep.
It's totally red.
Takuto?
Y-Yours was too!
Huh?
Never mind.
Where are you going Takuto?
I'm coming too!
Bathroom.
Don't follow me.
The bathroom?!
Shinigami don't need to use the bathroom!
Something must be wrong with Takuto.
It's like he's mad about something...
Eh?
I need to cool myself down...
Losing a hold of myself like that... I just...
I'll have to shape up so her audition will go well.
Maybe Takuto...
...really is against me being in a commercial, huh?
Why?
That's cause...
Takuto was a singer before he died, right?
"Commercials are absolutely
useless for musicians!"...
...might be what he's thinking.
Hey, Meroko.
Do you know what kind of songs Takuto sang?
Takuto used to be a singer...
Where did you find that out?
Eh?
Um...
Takuto said that he used to sing when he was a human...
Why you stupid little kid!
Why the hell are you talking about that for?!
But...!
You think it's fun to poke around people's pasts?!
Besides, something like that has nothing to do with you!
Did you really tell her, Takuto?
That's...
Why did you tell her something like that?
Even worse... to a human...
It's my choice to make!
Choice, you say?!
Takuto, what do you mean?
It's not supposed to mean anything!
Get out of my way.
I'm talking to her right now.
I'm talking to you too, Takuto!
Get out of the way!
No!
I-I'm sorry!
I said too much...
I was just wondering what kind of
songs Takuto sang...
Shut up!
Ah!
Takuto!
Hold it, Takuto!
I'm not done talk...
Takuto!
If something happens to Takuto...
...it'll be because of you!
Eh?
You know... Takuto's wings...
...are still just replicas.
Re-Replica?
It means that they were made...
They're not real.
Takuto isn't official yet...
He hasn't become a full-fledged Shinigami yet.
He's still in training.
This kind of thing is the most dangerous for him.
If he remembers everything from when he was a human...
...his soul will be trapped!
Eh?!
Do you understand?
Without a body to go back to...
...he'll become a ghost!
Ah!
If you understand...
...don't ever say anything that will make Takuto remember his past again!
Meroko...
Meroko!
What should I do?
I've done something terrible...
Ah.
The two of them didn't come back...
Meroko...
Takuto...
Where did they go...?
Mitsuki-san?
Ah!
Ah... yes!
I'm sorry!
You seem kind of tired, Mitsuki-san.
I believe that...
...you are supposed to attend school today.
If it's too much, rest in the hospital.
Ah. That's okay.
I'm fine.
I'll be fine, right?
Before tomorrow's audition...
...Takuto will definitely come back.
Ah.
Takuto?
Tomoe-chan...
Who's Takuto?
Ah... um... that's... well...
Well, now... that's the name of the person you like, isn't it?
Eh?!
I-It's not!
Don't hide it! Don't hide it!
Come to think of it...
You seem so grown up suddenly...
In just two weeks of summer vacation...
Did something happen?
Nothing at all, I said!
Then who is this Takuto?
Takuto is...
Ah.
To me... Takuto is...
Takuto is a very dear friend to me!
Are you okay?
Oh crap!
What are you guys doing?!
Girl's Changing Room
Okay.
Looks like it finally dried.
Thanks, Tomoe-chan.
Huh?
My throat kinda hurts...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Those boys...
I'll use my fist...
...and knock them out good!
It's okay.
You don't have to do that...
You can't go easy on them.
They did something wrong.
They're supposed to apologize.
I see.
You're right.
Thank you, Tomoe-chan!
Mi-Mitsuki...
I'm home!
Takuto?
Meroko?
They haven't come back yet...
Even though I wanted to apologize...
Hello?
Ah. Mitsuki.
Are you watching the TV right now?
Which means that...
...the character for the new Mermaid Tear commercial at the center of attention...
...will be chosen from Wakamatsu Madoka-san here and Full Moon-san.
Yes.
To be mentioned with Full Moon-san...
It's an honor.
Huh...
It looks like Wakamatsu Madoka's
agency set this up.
They're doing this to give her
an advantage tomorrow.
But... it won't do any good, so it's okay.
The one who's supervising, Kuahara-san, won't let that change his impressions.
Please tell us how you feel about participating with the new star!
Okay...
Yes!
In this audition...
...I hope to learn many things from Full Moon-san.
"Congratulations, Madoka-san."
Here you go.
I appreciate this, but...
...something like this won't
change the image I have.
That aura she has...
Full Moon  is the only one... who possesses that, I believe.
No, no.
That wasn't our intention.
It's just that...
Yesterday, Madoka was so nervous... her teeth were chattering...
I thought that I could find out just how much of a chance she really has.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah!
Madoka-chan?!
Hey... are you okay?
Owie!
I messed up again!
Please excuse her.
She let her nervousness get to her again.
No...
Madoka-chan seems like a much more straightforward girl than I thought...
The perseverance our Madoka has... is really heartwarming...
No... it's quite surprising!
Your clients must have seen some unexpected things as well.
Oh, no!
I'm embarrassed!
I'll do anything to become the image character.
Full Moon... there's no way I'm going to lose to you.
Takuto...
The pendant Eichi-kun gave me...
Eichi-kun...
I said something that hurt a very important friend of mine...
So... to help us be friends again...
...please lend me your power.
Eichi-kun...
Takuto...
Where are you?
Come back...
Takuto...
Is it okay for you to not go?
The audition's tomorrow, right?
She doesn't have any work today.
Then... is it just the two of us today?
Ah! I'm so happy!
Let's go have some fun!
Just forget about yesterday, 'kay?
She's really pitiful today, huh?
She can't do anything at all without you around.
She should just be a good girl
and think about her Eichi-kun.
Right, Takuto?
You're so annoying, Meroko.
Can't you leave me alone for a while?
Takuto?
Man...
I trusted you!
The fact that I used to sing...
That you wouldn't tell anyone...
How could that singing fool be interested?
I was just wondering what kind of
songs Takuto sang...
I forgot it all when I died... all of that!
You stupid kid.
I've forgotten it all.
Takuto...
Why aren't you coming?
Even though I want to apologize...
Ice cream's definitely the way to go in the summer.
Madam's going to be home late today...
I can take things easy...
Hmm?
Mitsuki-chan.
What is she doing over there?
Mitsuki-chan!
Mustn't forget!
Mitsuki-chan?!
Mitsuki-chan!
Dr. Wakaouji!
How's Mitsuki..?!
She's running a high fever...
It doesn't look too good.
It'd be best for her to stay under critical watch at the hospital for the time being.
Madam!
Even when I told her not to...
She still went walking around on her own...
She's all I have...
Eh?
My daughter...
Hazuki's child is all I have left.
Even if she's that man's child...
...she is still my granddaughter.
What I went through when I lost my daughter...
I already have too many painful memories!
Where... am I...?
When did it become morning?
I have to get going!
I can't be in the audition like this, though...
No...
Takuto will definitely come!
If I can apologize...
...we can definitely make up.
The day's finally here.
She isn't using the whistle anymore...
She's probably given up, right?
You know...
I've been thinking...
If it's come to this...
I can just tell the Shinigami head office to call you back.
That will probably be for the best.
Let's see...
The procedure for these situations is...
She isn't the kind of person who'd give up.
Takuto...
You can't be...
She's waiting.
I can't just leave her on her own.
Takuto!
Hold it!
No
new
me
ss
ages.
Au
di
ti
on.
Reversed letters again.
Au
di
ti
on.
Madam!
Mitsuki-chan...
Mitsuki-chan isn't in her room!
I have to hurry...
I even rushed back here...
Where has she gone off to?
Man...
Meroko.
I won't let you go.
What are you fooling around for?!
Look at this.
This is...
Au
dition.
Yes.
There's another message about something which will speed up her death.
And... that keyword is...
Audition.
That's why...
You can't transform her...
...and help her go to the audition!
But...
We're Shinigami, remember!
We're here to make sure she lives as long as she's supposed to!
I know that!
No, you don't!
You don't understand at all, Takuto!
Don't concern yourself with that girl anymore.
I...
For you to be with that girl...
I can't stand it anymore!
I didn't want to say this, but...
You and that girl...
...are somehow seem to be related.
If you get any closer to her...
...it'll bring back your memories from when you were a human.
You know what will happen, right?
I love you...
I want to be with you forever...
I don't want you to become a ghost, Takuto...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Wait, Mitsuki.
I'm going to find you.
Takuto...
Why do you keep on getting involved with her?
I don't understand it myself!
But...
...I can't just leave her alone!
No way!
I won't let you go!
Takuto... because you've been with that girl this whole time...
...we have a huge problem on our hands now!
Get out of the way, Meroko!
I don't care what happens to me!
I'm...
I'm going to save Mitsuki!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Run! To the Audition!
Look forward to it!