Heya, it's time for Kaleido Star.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep room your brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Everyone, it's Marion.
Do you love your mom?
My mom died in an accident when I was little,
but she was very good on the trampoline.
She was a star at Kaleido Stage,
and she was a very
beautiful and sweet mom.
Even now, I still love my mom.
I want to be a great woman
like my mom when I grow up too.
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Keep going after your
dream without being lost.
If you do that, I'm sure the road to
being a real Kaleido Star will open for you.
My dream...
Miss Layla knew that
I'd lost sight of my dream.
I was inspired by Miss
Layla to join Kaleido Stage.
When my dream was being
a Kaleido Star like Miss Layla,
all I had to do was chase
Miss Layla with all my might.
For that, I could do anything
no matter how hard it was.
But now,
I don't know what I want to do.
I don't have a dream.
Sora!
Have you seen my dad?
Wow, you look so adorable.
What's up, Marion? You're all dressed up.
I'm going to see my mom.
"Marion's Amazing Debut."
Here it is. Your favorites, Casablanca.
Aren't they pretty?
I bought those at a flower shop
in the corner of Northern Street.
But the store clerk there is so unfriendly,
and she always treats me like a child.
The other day, she made me so mad.
So I told her "As much as I'm paying
you, you could at least be nice!"
Then, she--
Hey, hey, Marion.
If you say everything all at
once, you'll make Mom dizzy.
Oh, that's true. Sorry, Mom.
Jonathan, wait!
The time passes by so
quickly, doesn't it, Cynthia?
It's already six years since you died.
So much has happened.
Marion who was small at
that time is already 10 years old.
Jonathan!
What do you think?
--Jonathan!
--Don't you think she
grew up to be a nice girl?
Grand Screw Jump!
Oh, dear... What's wrong?
I'm scared!
Dracula is scary!
Don't worry. That is just a show.
No! I'm scared!
Hi, little boy, please come see us again.
No!
I'm not coming back!
Thank you so much for coming.
The children are scared?
Yep.
Leon's Dracula is realistic and it's popular,
but it seems the small
children get really scared.
That's too bad after
they came all the way here.
I know.
--Then, I have no choice, but--
--I'm not interested in pairing with you.
Kaleido Stage has to be a place that
both children and grown-ups can enjoy.
The stage which everyone can enjoy...
I get it... that's my...
That's it!
Sora?
Let's try it!
For the time being, I'll assemble
a temporary stage for you.
Oh, thank you so much.
You'll be able to start practice tomorrow.
Is it a show for kids?
Yeah.
It's only for Saturdays and Sundays, between
the matinee and night showings of Dracula.
It's Sora's idea.
We're going to teach everyone
how much fun Kaleido Stage really is.
We already got permission from the Boss.
All that's left is to get the cast.
Kids' Stage?
Between the regular performances?
That's right.
It's a little tough, but if we take
turns, I think we will be all right.
That's ridiculous. Don't do it.
Why?
The audience size is increasing.
We don't have any problems.
I also want children to enjoy Kaleido Stage.
That's why we need a Kids' Stage.
Instead of worrying about that,
improve your skills so that
you're good enough to satisfy me.
That is important,
but I think the Kids' Stage is important too.
Are you going to disobey me?!
I'm not giving up the Kids' Stage.
I can't believe this.
I'm the one who's losing my composure.
Do whatever you want.
What are we gonna do?
Don't you think we will be in trouble?
May!
I want to concentrate on
the role I'm playing now.
Also, in order to be a suitable partner
for Leon, I want to improve my skills.
Why don't you go play with your kids?
Sorry...
Me too. Sorry.
I thought everyone would
participate. Instead...
We can do the show even if
we don't have that many people.
Of course, I will cooperate.
Miss Sarah!
Me too.
Rosetta!
Once a while, I want to
perform in front of many kids.
If you want, I wouldn't mind
doing the trapeze with you, Sora.
Sorry, there isn't a trapeze.
Really?
Then, I will do diabolo.
A mortal blow!
--Chick Style! Peep, peep.
--Excuse me...  If you don't mind...
--Peep, peep. Peep, peep...
--I want you to sing or something.
--Peep! Peep!
--Perhaps you could sing for us...
I want to introduce everyone to
the world's unknown martial arts.
--Um, a song...
--Peep!
You're amazing, Rosetta.
Finish it after that.
It's good.
Oh, I remember.
No gags, please.
How about if I fall on my face,
or something like that?
No.
Here I go, Jonathan!
Here I go!
Huh? Uh, here I go!
I'm really going this time!
Um, um... Here!
He's ignoring her.
Jonathan, give me that ball back.
Jonathan! I'm waiting!
And she doesn't even notice.
Jonathan!
You're terrible.
Marion!
Give me those.
Okay.
Let's have fun, Jonathan!
Here!
--Marion's amazing!
--Here!
--Their timing is also perfect.
You can tell they spend
time together all the time.
So I guess Sora just wasn't
good enough as a partner!
On days when I don't need to
go to the director's meeting,
I'm able to take turns, but...
Then, why don't you ask
Marion to take your place?
Oh, that's a good idea. Very good.
That's right, if there's someone
the same age as them on stage,
I'm sure the kids will be very happy.
I'm gonna do it. I want to do it.
Then, we decided.
Sora, you switch to trampoline.
I will do my best.
Jonathan's a really quick learner.
Not just with a ball, either.
He's also able to spin rings using his nose!
Really?
But if we have a big
audience, he may be nervous.
I will be all right.
I'm fairly strong under pressure.
Are you happy that you'll be
able to go on stage, Marion?
That's not how it is.
Jonathan says it has to be me.
So, I have no choice, do I?
I see...
Here I go, Jonathan!
There!
Why, you!
Wait!
Okay, just you watch!
Well? Do you give up?
I'm so happy being able
to pair with you, Sora.
Pair? Huh?
Marion is jumping on a trampoline...
Her mother used to be a star trampoliner.
She loves the trampoline, too.
She's also talented, and people
used to have high expectations of her.
But after her mother died,
she quit the trampoline.
Marion!
You're amazing. I saw your
trampoline for the first time.
Like mother, like daughter.
I was just playing.
Please don't tell my dad.
After school, let's do it again, Jonathan.
Marion was on the trampoline?
Yes.
Her performance was so free and beautiful.
If she practices it,
I bet she'll be even better.
Marion's mom was a top
star of the trampoline.
While she was imitating her mom's techniques,
she learned the trampoline naturally.
"In the future, they'll be mother
and daughter Kaleido Stars."
People used to say stuff
like that all the time.
Wow...
I wonder why she quit.
Maybe because it reminds her of
her mom and makes her sad, I'd guess.
She may have become afraid of jumping.
Maybe...
Marion looked so lively at that time.
Well...
She was saying not to tell her dad.
Does that mean she's practicing
but keeping it a secret from Jean?
Marion!
Why did you tell my dad?
I asked you not to tell him!
Marion, did you jump on the trampoline today?
Well, Marion, I...
I didn't jump.
I didn't jump!
Jean was...
Did he hear our conversation?
Sorry...
I don't want to see Dad
look like that anymore.
I don't want to see Dad look so sad.
I'm sure he'll be very sad
if I get hurt on a trampoline.
That's why I don't do the trampoline anymore.
That's what I decided.
That was why...
Sorry, Marion. I didn't know how you felt.
But...
I'm gonna do it. I want to do it.
But... Are you really sure?
But you want to be like
your mom too, don't you...
How could you say something like that?!
Marion!
What's wrong?
It's almost time for standby.
Marion really loves the trampoline.
But I'm not sure I know
what I can do for her.
The Sagittarius is sinking further and
further into the darkness of uncertainty.
The key to getting out of
the darkness is Aquarius' girl.
Say, Marion.
About this afternoon...
If you're talking about
the trampoline, don't worry.
I'm not interested in trampolines at all.
Marion, do you remember Mom's shows?
She was so pretty.
She looked like a bird
which flies the sky freely.
I loved to watch your mom
when she was on the trampoline.
Dad...
I have something I want to show you, Marion.
Look at this.
What?
Dad... This is...
It's your mom's stage notebook.
I'm sorry for hiding it from you.
I thought it would make you sad.
Mom's...
This is the notebook your mom used to
jot down her ideas when they came to mind.
Then she used to practice over
and over until she could do them.
"Marion's Debut Show"...
That's right.
Your mom would come
up with performance ideas,
and I'd come up with staging ideas.
I remember we'd talk about it every day,
and even quarrel every once in a while.
To appear on stage with you
and do a trampoline act was your mom's dream.
Mama...
I want to...
I want to jump on the trampoline
on stage with you too...
Marion...
When I heard that you were jumping
on the trampoline, I was happy.
I'm sure your mom feels the same way.
Mom too?
Yeah.
You like the trampoline, don't you, Marion?
Yes.
Then, for your mom's sake,
I want you to grow to like it even more.
Yes.
Wow, amazing. This is good.
Yeah, it looks fun.
It's perfect for the image
of the Kids' Stage too!
I want to do that one.
Yeah, I think it's a really good idea too.
Isn't this great, Marion?
Yeah.
Hey, what we're going
to do about Cynthia's role?
Oh... Well...
Sora, will you do it for me?
What?! Me?
You don't want to?
No, it's not like that.
You don't mind me doing it?
Yep. I want you to do it.
Then I'll take up your kind offer and do it!
Yeah!
Wow, things are getting exciting!
Does this mean I'm going
to pair with Jonathan?
Oh, it could be a good idea.
Jonathan, let's do our best.
Peep!
Here!
They laughed...
Okay, Jonathan, say hello to everyone!
Ready? Go!
Good boy.
That looks good on you, Marion.
This is the place where my mom was.
Ready? Jump!
Jump!
I wonder why it is...
When someone performs with Sora,
they always start smiling.
Marion...
This is what they went against me to create?
How frivolous.
Leon, wait.
Everyone is smiling.
This is the real Kaleido Stage.
Maybe this is the Kaleido Stage
I'm aiming for. Maybe! Maybe!
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
I can see why he's called a God of Death.
And so, this is the circus festival
that's held once every three years!
The previous winner was Miss Layla
who did the Golden Phoenix.
My partner is the God of Death, Leon.
Then tragedy strikes May.
Just watch, I will definitely
be a contestant! I will! I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Training With Leon."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...