Ryuu-chan...
Ryuu-chan!
Y-Yo.
W-Why?
Ryuu-chan, you're all right?
A-Aren't you...
I-I-I-In... Help...
Yasuko...
You've raised Ryuuji-kun well.
Yeah, I-I have...
The reason why my life was in "danger"...
L-Listen, Ya-chan!
Ryuuji is...
After falling for the fake voicemail that Taiga left,
Yasuko cried a lot and Grandpa scolded her.
Somehow...
Somehow, it's like Ya-chan is a child right now.
Families are amazing.
Even though they haven't seen each other in about ten years,
they're still...
Mom, thanks!
It's all because of you spoiling Yasuko-
Come on, there's nothing wrong with it.
No, but you...
Yasuko must be tired.
We're a family, aren't we?
Family...
Ryuuji-kun, hurry up and take your bath before the water gets cold.
Okay.
So you weren't married...
You found out?
Yeah.
Your dad ran away with another woman while I was pregnant.
Even though everyone told me to get an abortion,
I really wanted to protect you.
In the end, I couldn't protect you and things broke.
Nothing broke.
Didn't Grandma say you raised me well?
See, I'm a lot taller than you.
Be proud.
Yeah, you've grown.
Your back was really big when you were running...
So big that I didn't recognize you.
I was really scared,
but I was also a little happy.
But I was so afraid that you'd leave and never come back...
So you left by yourself?
Idiot.
I'm the last person who should say this,
but running away won't get you anywhere.
Ryuu-chan...
I will become an adult.
I'll do it right in front of you, not in some place far away.
That's why you have to look at me... always.
Come on, stop crying!
But...
W-What is this?
Grandma said there's nothing wrong with sleeping in the same room since we're going to get married.
Now I understand how Yasuko became the way she is now...
Ya-chan is laughing!
Yeah, she is.
Hey, turn off the lights.
Huh? Why?
Just do it.
What are you doing?
There are a lot of stars.
To be honest, I'm kind of worried.
I don't think running away and getting married will work out,
but I still want to have this dream.
I feel like if I don't do something here, things will break again.
Seriously, you and Yasuko...
Nothing broke, right?
Also, it's okay for us to start here.
We don't need to run away to get married. Let's do it with everyone's approval.
Wouldn't it be best to receive everyone's blessing?
Who do you mean by "everyone"?
Grandpa, Grandma and your parents.
That will take a long time...
It doesn't matter.
Since we'll be happy anyway,
why not share our happiness with everyone else?
Okay,
but before that, let's have a little rehearsal.
Look,
a veil.
Taiga...
Um... I, Takasu Ryuuji, will...
Uh... What should I say?
It doesn't matter, just say something.
H-How can it not matter?
Uh... will marry Aisaka Taiga-
As I thought, I don't want a vow yet.
What?! Wasn't this your idea in the first-
Do you remember what you said before?
Huh?
"Since ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast to equal the tiger."
That's why, even without a vow, we'll always be together, right?
Yeah.
Tai-
Your eyes are red.
Your breathing is all weird.
Shut up!
Your lips are cracked.
It'll hurt if we kiss.
It's not like...
If we kiss, it'll definitely hurt... a lot.
How was it?
Just as I expected...
It was like a rough, dry wilderness.
Also, it was really, really warm...
Hey, it's cold, so let's do it one more-
One more...
Sign: Takasu
Somehow, it feels weird.
Just us two left,
but now three people and a pet are coming back.
Ryuuji, you believed it, right?
Huh?
That Ya-chan would come if you lied,
then get back on good terms with Grandma and Grandpa.
I didn't think she would,
but I didn't think she wouldn't either...
I wonder why.
Perhaps it's like that.
Perhaps families are like that...
Oh, I'm so hungry!
Taiga-chan, you're coming over for dinner, right?
I...
It's all right.
We're a family of three, right?
Oh, I forgot about you, Inko-chan...
Taiga?
You guys go ahead, I'm going to go change my clothes.
But won't your parents be-
I'm coming with you.
Fine.
Be quick, since I'm making your favorite tonight; pork cutlets.
Huh?
Mom?
Taiga, what are you think-
You seriously don't think about the consequen-
Cut it ou-
Taiga...
Taiga... do you really hate me that mu-
Fine!
I don't give a damn anymore!
I'm leaving, so do whatever you want! Bye!
She's just like a kid...
Ryuuji, you know,
I always thought that I would never be loved...
It smells great!
I'm not just making pork cutlets.
Grandma taught me how to make some delicious taro rice.
Yay!
Thank you, Ryuu-chan.
...but perhaps that was just an excuse for running away.
I can't see the stars...
It's so small...
It's hidden and lonely, just like me.
I blamed my lack of confidence on my parents and my surroundings,
but Ryuuji still loves me.
That's why...
I won't run away anymore.
I have to change.
I have to accept everything.
I will be proud of myself and love Ryuuji.
That day, Taiga didn't come over for dinner.
Takasu, we can't understand if you don't tell us anything.
What actually happened?
Why did Taiga-
Come on, everyone, back to your seats.
I have some bad news for everyone.
Due to family reasons, Aisaka-san is withdrawing from this school.
I've just received that message from her mother.
Aisaka-san will be going back to her mother's-
Wai- This is a lie, right? It's a joke, right? She was forced, right?!
She didn't tell us or...
In your lives, you will all come to different crossroads.
Regardless of if you decide to stay where you are or turn back,
you still have to make a decision.
Aisaka-san's decision may mean leaving you all,
but it's a decision she tried her best to make.
Let's support her, okay?
Kids these days are so scary!
Are you all calling Aisaka-san? Texting her?
Unbelievable!
You should all take a good, hard look at your lives!
Takasu?
It won't go through if we all call at the same time!
Everyone, back to your seats!
Takasu-kun!
Kushie-
Can you clench your teeth for a second?
Why did you come back by yourself?!
Why is Taiga transferring?!
I don't get it!
Hey, Takas-
Wait, Kushieda!
Kitamura-kun.
I... I didn't want her to go.
I'd bring her back right now if I could.
I'd ask her why she decided everything by herself,
but...
she believes in me.
That's why the only thing I can do right now is accept it.
Takasu...
Wow, she learns how to be tidy at the last minute.
What's this?
Oh! A single sock!
Unforgivable!
Where's your buddy? I'll definitely find him for you!
That clumsy girl...
How could she forget these?
You're really stupid, aren't you?
One new message from Taiga
You never told me that you love me
I didn't?
I remember when I fell into the river-
Oh, yeah! Crap!
I was interrupted...
Gosh, I even said it a few times to Kawashima...
Stupid.
Yeah, I can be really stupid sometimes too...
Tomiya-kun, are you free today?
Yeah.
There's somewhere I want to go, can you come with me?
Hey, this is...
Ami-chan!
Taiga...
"I'm sorry for yesterday."
That won't happen.
Then why are you telling me?
I think I kind of understand what you said now...
Hey, hey! Taiga's text message!
I got it!
I got it too!
This is it, right?
Yeah, that!
It seems like Taiga replied to everyone who texted her.
Why is it just a picture?
I really don't get it.
Yeah, what does it mean?
Seaweed?
It's the night sky.
Kushieda?
Oh, she's right.
Is that small dot a star?
Really? You're imagining things, aren't you?
No, it's definitely a star.
But why did she take a picture of it?
"I will protect you all from the faraway sky."
Shut up! She's not dead yet!
I think she means, "I'll try my best."
Huh?
"Even if the sky is pitch black, with nothing to see,
there will be stars shining somewhere out there.
If I keep shining brighter and brighter,
I'll definitely look better to people."
I think Taiga is kind of selfish.
But even if that's the case, the sky will connect us.
As long as we all shine,
no matter how far apart we are,
we will definitely be able to see each other doing our best.
You overdid that...
It sent chills down my spine...
W-What?!
I think she's right.
Yeah.
This is the feeling of being young, right?
Me too! I'll be happy if she's right!
Yeah.
Speaking of stars, someone caused a lot of trouble back then.
Oh, that!
After taking the time to send us this, I think she'd be happy if we replied.
Be careful!
I can't find it...
Where is it?
I remember putting it away with Ami-chan's tree...
Thanks.
You think of these things to make others happy...
How should I put it... You're amazing at it.
I guess.
My existence itself should be surprising.
You know, before she became who she is,
people loved her even though she caused trouble for everyone.
I was jealous of her.
But that's not true at all.
Even though she seems amazing,
her body and heart are both so small and timid.
All she does is take whatever people throw at her.
She won't let anyone see her true self.
She's the same as someone.
Yeah, she was seen through from the very beginning.
Didn't you say I was a kid?
You know, I hate myself when I pretend to be an adult.
That's why I'm desperate to have others accept me for who I am.
But I finally understood after meeting Taiga...
As long as there's at least one person who understands me, I'll be okay.
Even if it isn't love...
Kawashima-
I found the treasure!
Uh...
So I just have to press here?
Miss, please hurry up before my godlike power runs out!
Come on, Takasu-kun. Smile.
Smile already.
I am!
Amin.
Okay.
Here I go!
I'm a dragon.
You're a tiger.
Since ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast to equal the tiger.
Even if you're not by my side right now,
I will leap through space and time and always be by your side.
These feelings will never change.
nitete mo chigau yo
Even if they’re similar, they’re different
mandarin orenji
Mandarins and oranges
tomodachi koibito
Friends and lovers
futari no kokoro mo
And our hearts too
kizutsukitakunai
I didn’t want to get hurt
watashi wa nigeteta
So I ran away
soshitara hikari mo
When I did that
sashite wa kurenai
Not even light would shine upon me
Hey, Inko-chan...
Isn't this makeup a bit much?
I'm a mother, after all.
I should just use some softer colors...
But I don't have things like that...
Inko-chan!
I-Inko-chan finally said his own name!
Oohashi High School 78th Graduation Ceremony
It'll be lonely once the seniors leave.
They're all so cool and interesting...
Did you know that our student council president, Kitamura-senpai,
will be studying abroad in America after graduation?
The president and the seniors made the Cultural Festival and the Sports Festival amazing!
Yeah!
But I heard that the previous cultural festival was even more amazing.
Oh, I heard about that!
It was the legendary one where 2-C won everything, right?
Yeah! It was all because of the Palmtop something...
Palmtop something?
You mean the Palmtop Tiger?
The one who brings you good luck?
That person really exists?
Yeah, the Palmtop Tiger!
She went to this school last year.
Moreover, she's Takasu-senpai's girlfriend!
There's something in this world that no one has seen before.
It is gentle and sweet.
Maybe if it could be seen,
everyone would fight over it.
That's why no one has ever seen it.
The world hid it so that no one could get their hands on it easily.
However, someday, someone will find it.
The person who deserves it the most will definitely find it.
What?
I was planning to surprise you...
It seems like you grew.
Not even a millimeter.
I'm sorry.
Listen...
I love you.
Tai-
W-Why would you say something embarrassing like that?!
You should've waited for a better mood or something...
This is how it's created.