So Aki-kun, how many people are coming with you on vacation?
Yoshii Akihisa is faced with a predicament...
There are nine people altogether, including you. Is that too many?
If I borrow a minivan we should have enough room.
But who are the other seven people that you invited?
L-Like...
People you know... Yuuji... and Hideyoshi... and Muttsurini...
And the others are...?
The others are...
This is bad.
My sister has forbidden me to get close to girls.
Kirishima-san is Yuuji's fiancee, so that's a good excuse.
But if she were to find out that I also invited Hijemi-san, Minami, and Kudou-san...
There's no telling what she'd do!
So... the others are?
Eh?! Hmm... Hi-Hi-
You've already mentioned Hideyoshi-kun.
Hi-Hi-
Hi-mi-tsu~
Aki-kun, brace yourself, please.
I'm sorry! It was a joke!
If you tell me the truth, then I'll reward you with a kiss.
The rest are aliens.
Aki-kun, close your eyes.
Wait a minute! That was obviously a lie, right?
Well, depending upon your point of view, humans can be seen as aliens...
Stop it! I apologized, so stop! Stop!
No way... I can't believe that you'd reject me...
I'm sorry, but a relative should no-
Pretty hot, right?
Pervert! You're a huge pervert!
Don't take me so seriously.
Serious
Joke
I was mostly joking.
This is bad... she's partially serious.
Aki-kun, you're a very bad boy for trying to deceive me.
Why are you trying to hide things from me, anyway?
Can you say that you won't be mad if I tell you?
Yes.  As long as you're not going to tell me
that there'll be girls there...
...I won't be upset or force you to cross-dress.
Where are you going, Aki-kun?
I don't want to be scolded, punched,
crushed, or forced to cross-dress!
Now I see... you're inviting a girl, aren't you?
No! That's...
They always help me study, and we're on the same team, so I feel bad if I don't return the favor by inviting them.
But I didn't know that we'd be staying overnight.
Geez, you're that kind of person...?
It's okay.
Eh?
So...
Just this once.
But if you try to do something shameless with the girls...
I'll kill your whole family.
That means you'll die too.
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 1
『 Me and Everyone and the Beach! 』
And finally, the day has arrived.
The weather's nice, isn't it Yuuji?
Yeah, and everyone was able to come, too.
I was looking forward to this so much that I could barely sleep.
Mizuki, you're not an elementary school student anymore.
I bought a new swimsuit just for today.
Didn't you just buy a new swimsuit recently?
That's... umm... the size was...
Could it be... you gained weight?
Weight Gain
Only a little bit!
Really, just a little bit!
Only a litte bit...
What do you mean?
I made a mistake.
It's just because my hair got longer.
Geez, it's just that you're not being careful enough.
I'm slimming down during the holiday
because of the summer's heat.
Eh? That's unfair, Minami-chan! You're betraying me!
Yeah, I'm much slimmer now... mostly in my chest.
Himeji, Shimada, I think you're worrying too much. You don't seem much different than before.
Well, excuse me... I know that my chest has developed slower than yours.
My chest doesn't develop, you know.
Don't worry about it. We know that you'll grow into a nice body.
Yeah, someone like Kinoshita-kun couldn't understand our plight.
I'm a guy! I don't have to worry about your problems!
What's wrong with the two of you today?
It's because...
I'm jealous of that chest.
I'm jealous of that slender waist.
Indeed, Akira-san is a threat.  I must keep a close eye on Yuuji.
She's good-looking from absolutely every angle.
I bet she'd look perfect in one of those erotic swimsuits from a porn magazine.
Is something wrong Kouta-kun?
I'm just a little car sick.
Getting a nosebleed from car sickness is pretty rare.
Aki-kun, can you get some car sickness medicine from the bag in the back?
Okay.
Uh? It's stuck.
One - Two!
Okay, it's open.
A school swimsuit, and a tight-fitting one at that... wow.
Sis, out!!!
What's wrong, Akihisa?
What should I do, Yuuji?
I've just discovered that there's a hopeless pervert in my family!
You're the one who looks like a pervert with that swimsuit in your hand.
No. This is my sister's swimsuit.
I see. So you're interested in your sister's swimsuit, huh?
You're right, you are  hopeless.
It's a misunderstanding! I won't accept this!
School Swimsuit
Sexy + Cute
Moe Points + ∞
Aki-kun, you asked me to
wear a swimsuit,
that doesn't show much skin so that
you wouldn't be embarrassed.
I'm sorry!
Compared to seeing someone your age wearing a school swimsuit, I'd rather  have you show some skin!
Change it! Change the swimsuit!
As your brother, I just can't agree with it.
So the problem with the swimsuit is that it doesn't expose enough of my body?
Expose
Yeah, whatever...
Akihisa, don't be a pervert.
The King of All Perverts, Muttsurini, just called me a pervert!
Don't cry, Akihisa. It's the same as when you call other people idiots.
So you're saying that I'm the Idiot King?!
I guess I don't have a choice. I'll have to wear something else.
A swimsuit that's so tight my chest is spilling out of it.
Muttsurini!
Muttsurini-kun!
Hang on, Muttsurini!
Oh, check out that view!
The wind feels so nice.
The perfect location.
Come on, let's hurry up and change so that we can go swimming.
Okay.
Today, at last, I'll show them all that I'm a man!
This time I'm not mistaken. I definitely bought a pair of men's trunks.
No one can complain about it.
Yahoo!
Kudou Aiko... changed in the car.
The swim club's suit shows different tan lines than this one.
This one is sexy... right, Muttsurini-kun?
Just this one time, you can take as many shots as you want.
I don't mind at all.
Don't be so full of yourself, Kudou Aiko.
Huh?
Your swimsuit doesn't satisfy me-
I blame the heat.
Well done there, Muttsurini. That was a whole 28 seconds.
That's awesome, Muttsurini. You just set a new record for your pre-nosebleed endurance.
Are you okay, Muttsurini-kun?
You'd better not come too close, Kudou-san.
The heat is so strong...
Muttsurini-kun!
I wish to be reborn as a bird.
No way! Don't say things like that!
That way, I'll be able to peep into girls' locker rooms from the sky, as much as I like.
He's failed to learn from the thing that just killed him.
Swoosh. Swoosh.
So, lemon juice really does go well with sugar, huh?
Excuse me!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Thank you for waiting.
Is Tsuchiya-kun all right?
He's calmed down at this point.
Aiko...
Don't bully Tsuchiya so much.
No, I didn't even do anything...
Tsuchiya-kun got turned-on because her swimsuit's so cute.
The truth of that statement hasn't been verified yet.
Turned-on?
Yes. Tsuchiya-kun is  a boy after all.
I see.
Scissors.
Oh My God!
Just what are you trying to do?!
You should get turned-on by my  swimsuit.
There's no need for that, considering that both of you already look pretty.
No way! You called me pretty.
Now I'm so embarrassed.
Yoshii, thank you.
I'm sorry for not being pretty enough for you.
That's not true!
After all, you're quite slender, Minami, but parts of you stick out just right.
I know, I know! My chest is small and my belly is too slim!
I didn't mean that!
Hey everyone, sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey, what are you doing?!
What do you mean?
Why aren't you wearing a top?!
Well, that isn't normal for man's swimsuit.
A girl shouldn't be wearing a man's swimsuit.
But, I'm a guy, you know.
Anyway, come with me!
Wait! Let me go!
Oh, Minami-san.
Did my brother do something wrong again?
What's wrong, Minami-san?
Nevermind... I know I'll never win!
Akira-san, please excuse me.
Amazing!
Sorry! Excuse me as well!
The beach is so cruel!
The one who's cruel is God!
Sorry, everyone.  I'm late.
What's wrong, Hideyoshi-kun? You look depressed.
Just leave me alone.
The beach, in summer, is cruel in many ways.
Question 1
Fill in the blank in the following sentence with
the correct term.
In chemical substances in solid or liquid state,
molecules are held together by the (      ) force.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
( Van der Waals ) force
Teacher Comments
Correct. It is sometimes referred to as intermolecular forces.
Van der Waals force occurs between ionic bonds.
Be careful not to confuse it with Coulomb force.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
( Wandervogel ) force
Teacher Comments
I can tell you sort of remember how it sounds like.
Unfortunately, this is a force
involved in interactions between mountain hikers,
not molecules.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
( Ef ) fort
Teacher Comment
Idiots and Tests!
I do not mind this answer, actually.
Right
Akihisa-kun, a little more to the right!
Left
No, that's wrong, to the left!
Yoshii-kun, just go forward!
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Right
Left
Forward
Who should I listen to?
Aki-kun, turn 32 degrees to the left,
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
then walk forward 4.7 meters.
Opposite
Actually, it's the opposite.
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
Front left 32 degrees
Distance 4.7m
Opposite
They're all giving me different directions.
What should I do?
What about Yuuji?
Yuuji, how's this swimsuit?
It's fine, I guess. I've seen it, remember?
You certainly haven't taken another good look at it since then...
you should take a closer look now.
Wait, hey, don't just grab me!
It's touching me!
Right there!
Just Die!
That's dangerous, you know!
Damn! I missed.
Sorry, Yuuji! I thought you were the watermelon.
But it sure looked like you were aiming right at him.
Come on, Hideyoshi. It was a misunderstanding.
Yeah, Hideyoshi.
Akihisa was only aiming for the watermelon.
Now, it's my turn.
What's wrong? Let go of the bat, Akihisa.
Yuuji, you just took your turn, and failed.
That was the first round. Now we're on to the second round, and I'm going first.
But it's supposed to begin with the last person in the first round going first in the second round.
Um, it'd be such a waste to crush the watermelon into pieces... so let's stop trying to split-
It's okay!
I swear that I won't crush the watermelon!
Then what are you guys trying to crush?
I'm tired.
I didn't even swim, so why do I feel so tired?
That's because of your own behavior.
Thanks for waiting!
We bought lunch.
Sorry we're late.
Was the store crowded?
No, it was...
Well, some guys tried to hit on us.
I really hate things like that!
So do I.
Oh, that sounds like a problem.
Why don't you just ignore them?
Yeah, you're right!
Hey, that's not how you're supposed to react!
Geez, you really don't understand girls at all.
That's right. Yuuji, you should be more worried.
Huh? What are you-
My eyes!
I wish that Akihisa would show a little concern about us.
I know! Why don't we make him worry?
I know, right?
The guys just keep hitting on us!
I know! It's always so tiring having to deal with it!
Huh? A bunch of guys hit on the both of you?
Yes! All the time!
Really, anywhere we go!
But you don't seem like you're used to it.
Th-That's not true! I'm just tired of it since it happens all the time!
Yeah! A slow guy like you wouldn't understand!
That's so rude! I hit on girls all the-
All the what?
For starters, how can you pull off hitting on girls?!
Exactly! I can't believe that it goes very well at all!
Don't try to show off!
Yuuji, as well. You aren't popular because you don't understand girls either.
How dare you say-
Everyone has things that suit them and things that don't.
A romantic relationship just doesn't suit you well, Aki-kun.
Damn it! They're ridiculous!
It feels like they were just picking on us for fun.
What the hell's with them saying that we aren't popular?
I agree! If I get serious about it, hitting on a girl is...
Huh?
What is it, Akihisa?
What an unbelievable scene...
What?
Muttsurini is getting hit on.
What are you talking about? I told you not to mumble unless you're sleep-
You're a photographic genius!
This is a "normal feature."
Come on, please don't be shy.
You're so cute!
Impossible! How can Muttsurini...?
Yuuji...
What?
Is it possible that you and I are the only ones who aren't popular?
Don't say something so ridiculous! There's no way that's true!
Yeah! Of course not!
It's just because Muttsurini looks so quiet and harmless.
He's just a different type!
That's why we shouldn't jump to any conclusions!
Exactly! How dare they say that we can't hit on girls?!
We'll show them what we can do if we're serious!
That's the spirit, Akihisa! Let's show them how good we really are!
Yeah!
Now that
I'm looking
back on it,
Now that I'm looking back on it,
I can only think that there was
I can only think
that there was
something wrong
with us back then.
something wrong with us back then.
But do you know how to hit on a girl?
Learning by copying others is the
fastest way. Let's watch Muttsurini.
So we can go after girls by taking photos, right?
Yes, one of us will say, "If you'd like, I can take your picture."
That'll be a good opening line.
I see.
Next, the other person can try to strike up a conversation,
and it should be a piece of cake after that.
How will they decide what topics to bring up?
They'll just think of something.
So, it's the last person's fault if it doesn't go according to plan?
Damn you, Akihisa! What's up with you running like that?!
What about you, huh?!
You can just follow me!
Yuuji, I'll start the conversation up for you!
Like I trust you! Leave it to me!
I won't let you!
Thanks for waiting!
I'll take the picture now!
Milady...
You look pretty.
If you like,
we'll take some swimsuit photos.
I didn't expect her to call the police.
Maybe taking photos isn't the best way to start up a conversation.
Yeah.
We don't have camera skills like Muttsurini.
All right! Let's change our approach.
What are we gonna do?
First, we'll compliment their looks, and then we'll start up a conversation. How about that?
Everyone loves to be given a compliment!
But how do we compliment them?
We'll make comparisons...
Tell them that they look like TV stars or athletes.
After we compare them with someone, and the conversation starts going...
it will be easy!
Thank you.
Um, you look really pretty.
Eh? Do I?
Yes, you have a perfect body!
I think so, too! You look really great!
Oh my, you're flattering me!
No, no, it's not like that!
Yeah! You're really pretty!
Yeah, yeah! You look great, just like...
Right, just like...
Like a porn star!
She has a world-class right hook.
I'm sure that she'll become a champion one day.
I just know it.
Oh? Where have the two of you been?
Swollen faces.
What happened?
N-Nothing at all! Right, Yuuji?
Yeah!
We just tripped, right, Akihisa?
Yuuji, let's get back to our swimming race!
Yeah! This time I won't lose!
We were finally about to succeed, but you had to go and ruin it!!
No way, it was your  stupid comment that ruined us!
You're playing innocent? What the hell?!
You want to go?!
Enough of this, we won't able to settle things anyway.
You're right.
I was thinking... maybe it's not working because we aren't serious enough.
Eh?
I think that we might be holding back since they're not really our type.
I see. We can't fake our true feelings.
Just kidding!
That's just a lame excuse.
What's wrong, Yuuji?
All right! Let's give it one last try, and hit on the two of them!
Yeah, I agree.
U-Um...
I-I think we're lost.
We're looking for the b-beach, do you know where-
Idiot! We're at the beach!
Sorry. It just slipped out...
Her hair color changed?!
This is my real hair.
Sh-Shouko!
This is bad!
Eh?
Sorry, Akihisa.
Muttsurini!
Why?!
They'd have killed me if I refused.
D-Did they notice what we were doing here?
Right arm, they said.
Right arm, eh? Sounds painful.
I don't want to go back.
They said that they'd break everything except  the right arm!
Akihisa-kun, please stay where you are!
We have a full course meal ready for you, so prepare yourself, Aki!
I'm so sad that I'm losing my brother!
Run, Akihisa! These three are seriously-
Akihisa, thanks for all the memories.
No!!!
Yuuji.
Yes.
Kneel down.
What? But we're in...
But we're in the sea.
Do I need to repeat myself?
Kneel down.
Question #2...
What is the main component of seawater, other than water?
Tears of regret and repentance...
Did something happen?
Next episode!
"Me and Yukata and Fun Festival!"
This will be on your test.