The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
So where is Masaomi?
He left a bit ago.
He had something to do.
Leave it alone, and the tinder will keep piling and piling on...
We're over. Finished!
You did what you thought was right, didn't you?
Is this the leader of the Dollars?
And if the Dollars are behind them, we beat them up, too.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Don't let her get away!
Find her!
That way!
You guys, go that way!
Block the exits!
Why?
Why is Kida...
The girl runs.
To escape from the pursuing shadows...
She had only wanted to know the truth.
Geez! What a pain...
Where did they go?
They won't get away.
Why is Kida...
She couldn't feel a thing.
Why?
The shock at what she'd seen mentally overwhelmed her.
Anarchy
I'm glad you're able to leave the hospital early.
Thank you.
You've all been wonderful.
Here you are.
Thanks!
The Slasher incidents had stopped that night,
and the city was calming down.
A normal life awaited Sonohara Anri, or it should have.
Sonohara!
I'm so glad I made it in time...
I was busy with the student council...
Ryuugamine...
I heard you'll be back in school starting tomorrow.
Are you okay now?
Yes! I'm fine.
I'll carry your things.
N-No, I'm fine.
Let him carry them!
He ran the whole way here 'cause he wanted to.
Anri, how many times today do you think he's said this:
Sonohara's getting out of the hospital today!
I wonder if she'll be okay coming to school.
She's so erotic, so cute—
I didn't say that last one!
Thanks, both of you, for coming to see me so often, while I was in the hospital.
Not at all...
By the way, Masaomi, you just came out of the hospital, right?
Y-Yeah.
I just missed you.
Oh, right!
Sonohara, you can use my notes for the time you were absent.
They might be a little hard to read, but if you want them, they're yours.
Just a second. I'm sure I have them here somewhere...
Something's different about Kida.
The girl felt there was something different, something wrong, about the boy.
Ever since he'd first come to see her...
You're okay now.
Kida?
Anri... What happened?
It's nothing, really.
The Slasher kinda...
But it's nothing, really.
Sorry, gotta run.
I'll let Prince Mikado walk the princess home.
Don't blow your chance.
See ya!
See you tomorrow!
An indescribable uneasiness overwhelmed her.
Don't let them do anything till I get there.
Okay?
<Tanaka Tarou> There are a lot more Yellow Scarves around lately.
<Kanra> You're right.
<Kanra> You can see clearly them, so they stand out more than the Dollars.
<Setton> They've been around for a long time, but lately, they seem different.
<Tanaka Tarou> Different?
<Setton> I don't really know.
<Setton> I guess they're not like they used to be.
<Setton> They're kinda more violent now, I think.
Saika has joined the channel
<Tanaka Tarou> Oh, hey, Saika.
<Tanaka Tarou> Evening.
<Kanra> Evening!
Saika has joined the channel
<Setton> Welcome!
<Saika> Good evening...
<Saika> Um, I'm sorry.
<Tanaka Tarou> Why apologize?
<Kanra> You weren't used to the net at first,
<Kanra> so you got a virus, and that's why you acted that way, right?
<Kanra> You couldn't help it.
<Saika> I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
<Tanaka Tarou> You apologize too much.
<Kanra> By the way, Saika,
<Kanra> ever heard of a color gang called the Yellow Scarves?
<Saika> The people with the yellow bandanas in town?
<Kanra> Yeah, those guys.
<Kanra> Another group, called the Dollars, is a lot like them.
<Kanra> Because of the Slasher case, the two of them are in a kind of dangerous situation.
<Saika> Um... What do you mean?
<Setton> Let's talk about something else, Kanra.
<Setton> You shouldn't just start talking about that stuff to someone who doesn't know many details.
<Kanra> No, no.
<Kanra> If you live in Ikebukuro, you should know this!
<Kanra> They never caught the Slasher, right?
<Kanra> And there are victims among both the Dollars and Yellow Scarves, right?
<Kanra> Both think the other's responsible.
The Dollars don't think it's that big a deal.
But I think neither side knows much about the other, and that's creating confusion.
Either way, if the two of them don't find and lynch the person behind it,
a rain of blood's gonna fall on Ikebukuro...
It's pretty scary.
A real gang war!
You have a private message from Setton
Don't worry about it, Anri.
The two of them are just out of control.
You weren't behind it, so turning yourself in won't do any good.
Don't do something you'll regret.
The cops are really scary these days.
Really scary!
Really scary, Okay?
Especially the traffic cops!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Next time, I'll teach you how to use private message mode.
I'm sorry. I'll be going.
Oh, okay.
Good night, Saika.
Night!
See ya!
Saika has left the channel
I'll be going, too.
Good night.
Good night!
Setton has left the channel
Kanra, about the Slasher...
I'll tell you anything I find.
And with a good discount.
Somewhere in this city is the real criminal.
Catching them will soothe the misunderstandings between
the Yellow Scarves and the Dollars.
I don't know if it'll be that easy.
Neither the Yellow Scarves nor the Dollars is really a single organization.
Some of them will probably take advantage of the gang war to mug people.
If that keeps up, it'll be a real gang war.
I won't let that happen.
I dunno.
It may be too late to stop it.
There's no way for you to stop the Yellow Scarves.
Even so, I'll keep it from happening.
I'll look forward to that.
I must do something,
thought the girl with the cursed blade inside her.
thought the girl who'd watched the world through a frame.
But...
The young boy who'd come, through the frame and into her world, was already enslaved.
By the heavy chains of his past.
It was too late for him to escape.
Yeah?
okay.
Got it.
Be right there.
Sorry! A friend has something he needs right away!
Yeah?
If you want to hate someone, hate my friend all you like.
Hating someone's free, and it doesn't hurt me at all.
Two birds with one stone!
Two chicks with one guy!
Two chicks and one guy?
See you tomorrow!
Was it really that important?
Kida's been acting weird lately, don't you think?
Really?
Sure you're not overthinking things?
I'm sorry.
I have to do something.
Bye.
I heard some members of the Dollars got mugged by the Yellow Scarves last night.
I heard that someone almost got killed.
The Yellow Scarves say that the Dollars are behind the Slasher attacks.
Something had to be done.
The boy who led the Dollars knew this.
But he still didn't know that he was one of the pieces on the board.
Come eat sushi!
Sushi is the soul of Japan!
It's traditional!
I wonder if it's true, that he does a cossack dance, when he delivers something.
Those kids last night were lucky Simon was out on delivery.
Swing that pipe down, and you'll be the main ingredient in sushi.
Human sushi...
It hurts, and it doesn't taste good.
Luck doesn't continue.
Geez... I don't like the look of things.
Does anyone know about the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves?
Anyone?
Our boss is Kida Masaomi.
I've seen him with you, Mother.
He said he was going to take revenge for you.
No...
Of course, she couldn't believe it.
But the children could not lie to the girl, their Mother.
Where is Kida?
He'll be coming to the meeting today.
Take me there.
And then...
She knew everything.
Kida is...
Think she's back here?
She had to run.
It's simple.
Why is Kida...
I'll love them all.
Kida Masaomi...
The yellow children, too...
All of them.
Cut them up
What would happen if she were caught?
and love them.
You can't love others.
I'll love them for you.
So much! So much! So much!
I don't want to hurt anyone!
The girl was terrified that the boy would learn she was a monster.
It's too cramped.
I'll go.
Kida!
Save me, someone!
Someone!
Hey, that's...
Standing in the pouring rain...
was the female Dullahan.
I'm here. Where are you?
The only thing she'd been able to do was seek help from one just like her,
another one who shouldn't exist in this world.
She jumped over the wall on her bike...
She could do it.
She's going to move.
Seriously?
Celty!
You can tell me what's going on later.
We're getting out of here.
Get on back.
Right!
Thank you.
Hang on tight.
I've seen you around for a while.
I always thought that riding suit was too curvy to be a guy.
I don't care about guys,
but if you're a girl, I could love that suit alone.
If I fell in love with a nun, I'd love even the gown she wore.
He's the one who's always with Mikado and Anri...
I see.
She doesn't want him to see her face.
I don't know why, but I get it.
What?
Damn it...
Monster!
Don't!
She looked just like the headless knight of legend.
The fragments of information came together in an instant.
An intruder with a blade like the Slasher's,
the black bike coming to their rescue,
and the rumors that the black bike belonged to the Dollars.
They all reached a single conclusion.
The Slasher was part of the Dollars.
The young boy didn't know if his conclusion was right.
All he knew was that, regardless of what he thought,
he could no longer contain his companions.
Hey, you ever heard of a Dullahan?
No, I haven't.
They say it's a headless knight, with a headless horse,
who visits the homes of those about to die.
Like the grim reaper.
A sudden thought came to him.
One of them could die.
Why...
Why, at times like this, do I want to see them first.
The sky has fallen.
A phrase meaning that everything changes for the worse.
It was the phrase on the banners of the Yellow Scarves in the Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
The sky ain't blue, yeah.
Ain't yellow either.
Tanaka Tarou has joined the channel
Kanra has joined the channel
Evening!
Oh, is it just you?
Evening.
Seems like it.
Private message right away, huh?
There's something I want to ask you.
Um,
have the Yellow Scarves been in Ikebukuro for a long time?
About three years...
They were a quiet little group at first.
The young boy who led the Dollars
learned of the terrible fight between the Yellow Scarves and Blue Square,
not knowing that the girl
sacrificed to it was his friend's former lover.
And not knowing that the man telling him all this
controlled her heart and had inflicted terrible, lasting wounds on his friend.
So in the end, the Yellow Scarves were the only ones left...
But Blue Square didn't die.
What do you mean?
The leader of the Yellow Scarves got sick of fighting
and left.
After that, they joined the Yellow Scarves.
So they merged?
Basically, yeah.
Outside of the leaders, no one would bother checking who was part of which organization.
They just had to take off their blue clothes, say they wanted to join,
and that was it.
But then the leader who quit...
He doesn't know, I imagine, that the ones who sent his
girlfriend to the hospital are with his old gang now.
You take care, too.
Some people are part of both the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves, it seems.
That's why, if I send word around the Dollars
that we had nothing to do with it, they might tell the Yellow Scarves.
If it really isn't the Dollars behind it.
The Dollars don't have any rules,
and you don't watch them all.
A part of the Dollars may be the Slasher,
and you simply don't know it.
That's how the Dollars work.
If you're going to be a part of this world,
you should know that.
I'll keep that in mind.
Morning!
Good morning.
What's wrong?
You seem down.
Are you still not feeling well?
No, that's not it.
Morning!
Morning.
Oh, I saw Kida at the station.
He said he was staying home today.
Why?
Dunno.
He didn't say.
I see.
See ya.
Thanks.
You can't run from your past.
The reason you're worrying is because of your past, right?
If you can't run,
then fight and win.
If I could only fight and be rid of my past with you,
I'd love to.
Why can't you?
I couldn't fight with you.
He wanted a place to be. That was all.
Each time he'd told his friend about the new city he lived in,
he'd realized that he wasn't really a part of the things he talked about.
Now he knew
that his sole reason of taking part in the Yellow Scarves was Mikajima Saki.
And now he was working for his dear friend, who was his new life.
Geez. It's raining again.
Kadota.
You came back?
Yes.
Let's talk somewhere else.
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Next Time
Dullalala!!
A New King Will Arise
A great man once said that the world is a void.
A great man once said that the world is symbolic.
A horrible past is the product of a delusion.
It never existed.
Isn't that enough?
Next time:
A New King Will Arise.