Thank you very much!
Aisaka-senpai, because of you, we've found happiness!
We did!
Do you know them?
I have absolutely no association with jerks performing lewd acts in public this early in the morning...
Taiga!
What the hell is with them?
Ah, Aisaka-san...
What's with you guys?
Why did you move away, Taiga?
I won't ask you to do a lariat on me...
But could you at least kick us with your foot or trample us with your heel...
That's so disgusting!
Don't get near me!
Don't look!
What's going on?
Ami-chan doesn't really think much of these so-called jinxes.
See, like this, and like this...
What are you doing, Stupid Chihuahua!?
Hey, hey...
Ami-chan's beautiful face...
Completely uncensored...
See? That rumor is a total fake!
Ami-chan is already unhappy!
Hey!
Don't wipe that on my skirt!
The stuff from inside got on me.
How are you going to pay me back, you contaminated garbage?
You put it in yourself!
A rumor?
Oh, yeah.
Apparently, of the people who came to see our pro-wrestling show at the cultural festival...
Some either got swung around by Taiga or got hit on the head during the outer ring riot...
Anyway, anyone who got touched by Taiga...
Found happiness one after another.
Happiness?
That's right!
Like suddenly getting confessed to.
Or a strange old man suddenly giving you his entire inheritance.
Anyway, it's like a huge avalanche of happiness.
They say any wish of yours can come true!
Well, we don't know where it started, but that's the Legend of the Happiness of Tenori Taiga.
I see.
That's why.
What the hell?
Getting all happy without my consent...
It's okay, Taiga...
Just a little bit...
Don't get so friendly!
I don't care who it is! I won't let you touch me!
Good Morning!
What are you all doing there?
Minorin!
The only one who can touch me is Minorin!
Now, now...
Good girl, good girl...
If you touch Taiga, you can find happiness...
On the day of the cultural festival, Taiga was probably far, far away from happiness.
If there was anyone who became happy from Taiga that day...
That would be...
What? Hurry up with my lunch.
Y-Yeah.
Really ironic.
It's ironic about Takasu-kun.
Even though he is the closest person to Aisaka-san...
Aisaka-san was dancing so happily with Maruo.
If you're touched by her, you'll find happiness...
He stood by her side the whole time, but Maruo stole her so easily at the cultural festival.
What's that...?
A weird rumor is...
Poor you.
It's true, Kitamura-kun stole me away from you.
Hey, you think it's okay to let this rumor continue?
It's true that it's complicated to be the ex-girlfriend of a dog, since I'm a human after all...
But it seems I've thrown you out.
Now Kitamura-kun and I are...
I wasted my time worrying.
Oh, thanks.
I've got to get to my seat.
That single teacher will put on her "single" face, and come do her "single" homeroom.
"Single" face?
Takasu's lunch today looks great as always!
Is that a spring roll?
Uh, yeah...
I took some leftover tuna salad and tried wrapping it in rice paper.
Impressive!
Takasu-kun's great, but rice is great too!
You're being targeted, Taiga.
Dammit. I can't eat in peace.
Who would believe that?
Mind if I sit here?
Aisaka, don't worry about that rumor concerning the cultural festival.
Which rumor?
Oh, no, nothing. Nothing at all.
The cultural festival was really fun!
It really was!
The class exhibit, the Miss Contest, and the Lucky Guy, we got them all!
It's great!
Yeah, really...
It's all thanks to Aisaka.
That's not it at all...
Taiga?
Hey!
Hey, drink this.
Not milk!
What?
But!
I want soda!
Orange!
Even at a time like this, you...
She's always, always...
She's gone back to her usual self...
That's a good thing, right?
Yes, I know.
There's some tests coming up too.
Yeah...
Anyway, a little more.
I got it.
I'll call you back later.
Bye.
Hey.
What was that phone call?
What, do you want to know my secrets?
It doesn't really matter to me.
Orange, orange...
Soda at lunch time?
What a kid.
Not for me.
It's for Taiga.
She said she didn't want coffee flavored milk.
Hey!
Bye!
What am I going to do...
With this?
Cyclone Kick!
You're late!
I had to drink tap water!
What are you going to do about it?
How the hell would I know?
You suddenly...
Hey, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It wasn't on purpose.
I wanted to ask Aisaka-senpai a favor and I thought I'd pick up your juice and approach you...
You again...
You've been hanging around me for a while now.
For a while?
You mean because of that rumor that if someone is touched by you, they'll find happiness?
T-That's it!
I have someone I like right now and I want it to go well, so...
Sure, go...
To heaven that is!
The pursuit of happiness is really a survival game.
Come on, we're going.
Lunch period is going to end soon!
Where?
They're going to post pictures from the cultural festival.
What about lunch?
I already ate!
But I haven't!
Hurry up!
That reminds me. I've been touching you...
Pretty often, actually.
Don't talk dirty like that!
That's right.
If I touch Taiga this much...
I should be the one most likely to find happiness.
Making such a happy face...
It's number 113.
Don't mess it up.
Be quiet...
It's a really great picture.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Minorin!
Lesson well, Taiga.
Number 200, Ami's picture is worth checking out.
The password is: breasts.
I'm sick of this perverted dog.
What was I doing?
I've gone so far beyond being sick of your lust, there are times I've thought of killing you.
That's a pretty amazing stretch.
If you're that interested in Stupid Chihuahua's breasts, let me inform you...
She has six breasts!
I saw it!
She doesn't!
If I hang out with you, the perverseness will stain me.
Minorin, I'm going to look over there.
Damn Taiga.
Takasu-kun, it's time!
Our destined duel-down!
I sacrificed 90 yen to summon nine pictures.
Activate face-down card!
Execute instant magic, "I just found it"...
Number 93, a picture with my softball teammates I just now found.
I summon by paying the cost of 10 yen.
Ummm...
Yes, Takasu-kun, it's your turn!
Turn?
Silly, I'm talking about showing each other which pictures we got.
Is that it?
Of course you're going to summon the picture of the whole class with an attack status, right?
I didn't understand her at all.
Show me, show me.
Number 85.
85, 85...
That is...
Maybe I'll...
Get this picture too...
As a souvenir.
Yeah, let's...
Look at this guy.
You only bought pictures of Class B's Sugo!
Shut up. Don't look!
Buying pictures of the girl you like...
You're so sappy.
What?
Hey, next time let's go to that place...
Getting all excited over some pictures...
Everyone's really childish.
Ami...
As for me, getting my picture taken is my job.
Those pictures are sold all over Japan.
It doesn't matter who has my picture...
Or whatever feelings people may have with that picture.
That's what makes it just a picture.
Yeah... Just a picture.
You're right.
It's just a picture.
As expected from Ami-sensei!
You really have a grown-up perspective.
What do you want to do on the way home?
Hey...
Do you mind if we go by the station today?
Okay. Is there something there?
The other day...
A single person's face. A single person's love.
A single person's palm reading.
The fortune lines are fading.
Sensei!
Do you need something from this single person, Kawashima-san?
I've been wondering about it since this morning...
Sensei, your cardigan is from this year's winter collection, isn't it?
You noticed?
Of course I can tell.
Sensei, you wear top brand clothes with ease.
It shows that you're an adult.
It's great.
People in the know can see it, Yuri-chan-sensei's adult charm!
Kawashima-san, you're really, really an angel!
Really.
I'm such an adult.
No, it's nothing.
Let's see...
Let's stop by the supermarket on the way home.
Yeah. Today, I'm feeling like...
Meat! Something with fat!
You always say meat.
So what? I'm paying for it, right?
Think about the balance, the balance!
You...
Just because you got a picture of yourself and Minorin holding hands, hasn't your ego gotten bigger?
You were watching?
I just thought you would definitely buy it. I was right.
You bought one too!
That's true.
It's not like I needed one, though.
After all, I'm his girlfriend now.
From earlier...
I'm very sorry, I...
You again?
And this time you're looking up my s-sk-skirt!
No, that's not it!
Hey!
Wait!
She's totally gone back to how she was before the festival.
Even though something like that happened.
No...
Because it happened?
President...
We've finished calculating the final expense report for the cultural festival.
Oh, let me see.
Tomiie-kun is being attacked!
What was that?
It's probably "The Legend of the Happiness of Tenori Taiga."
They say if you touch Aisaka Taiga, anything you wish for will come true.
It's just a rumor though.
So that's where Tomiie comes in.
"Even if it's a rumor, even if it's a lie,
I want to try to take a leap of faith."
It's not something I can't understand.
I'm surprised that you would say something like that.
Really?
President...
Kitamura.
I've got something to tell you.
In the end, I never got to touch Taiga.
I'm jealous of those who did get touched.
Taiga herself is all happy with Maruo.
All they did was dance together!
There's no way Taiga likes Maruo!
What are you getting so mad about?
Like I said...
Seriously believing in that jinx is stupid.
But Ami-chan, you're okay without something like that.
If it's about love, whatever you wish for would probably come true.
That's true.
You're really grown up, and you have a great figure.
There isn't a guy out there who wouldn't fall for you if you went after him.
That again...
Ami-chan?
One cut goes for 1800 yen.
You buy some pretty nice stuff.
Kawashima!
It's good to take it seriously...
But Takasu-kun, you've been totally marked as a shoplifter.
Can't you look a little bit happier when you're shopping?
But, listen.
If I go with pork, for the same price, I can get 4 packs.
If you're worried about the price, why don't you quickly go touch Aisaka-san for a bit?
If I remember it correctly, it's "a strange old man suddenly giving you his entire inheritance."
Hey, if you touch Taiga, you'll find happiness, right?
The chance it'll work is probably zero, though.
But if it were true...
What would Taiga do for herself to find happiness?
She's already plenty happy.
In this case, it's quantity over quality, right?
As long as she has enough to eat, she won't complain, not her.
You're right.
Alright! I'll go with pork.
I don't need any plastic bags.
Takasu-kun, you've really saved up a lot of points.
You're such a housewife.
Be quiet.
Oh, yeah!
Here, take them.
I'll give them to you.
We're just three people, and for one person, two packs is plenty.
You're giving these to me?
But Ami-chan doesn't even cook.
Nevermind that, eat some pork!
You don't look too good today, you probably don't have enough vitamin B2, right?
You seemed kind of listless all day.
Like when you were by the vending machines.
What's with that?
You're just like a nagging old woman.
Call me what you want.
You're probably just eating snacks all the time anyway.
You're really such a kid.
Ginger stir-fry is a must!
Ginger warms your body up.
Bye!
A kid?
That damn mongrel.
Who does he think he is, leaving his owner behind and going home by himself?
Ki- Kita- Kitamu-
Aisaka.
What are you... doing?
Nothing at all, is what I'm doing.
The Happiness of Tenori Taiga...
Sorry.
What am I doing?
Did something happen?
Did you lose your wallet?
Did that damn student council president push you around?
No.
That's not it.
It's nothing.
Um...
You can touch me.
I don't really get it...
But look, touch me as much as you want, a lot, go right ahead!
No way!
What am I saying?
Aisaka.
Sorry, I'm okay.
Thanks.
Tomiie-kun, are you really okay?
Yeah...
I'm okay.
Really?
Really, really?
Yeah, Sakura-chan.
I'm really okay.
Welcome home!
Why did you leave without me?
Hey, Ryuji, what's with all the food?
Is today something special?
Umm...
Yeah, since I missed lunch, I was really hungry, so...
It smells good!
This was in your repertoire too?
Yeah.
It's a western style pork stew.
The key ingredient is the Shinshu miso in the sauce.
I won't lose to those restaurants that your old man took you to.
All that's left is the gratin...
What an idiot.
Really.
Even though it doesn't really matter.
Nothing.
Get moving!
Okay.
The Legend of the Happiness of Tenori Taiga?
It was really stupid.
Rub, rub, rub, rub...
Y-Yacchan...
I'm already happy!
That's way too fast.
You know...
Being able to rub Taiga's head...
Eating a delicious dinner with my whole family...
That is the happiest thing for Yacchan.
Family?
That's right!
We're a three person family!
Leggo! I can't breathe!
If you touch her, any dream will come true.
Tenori Taiga.
If that were really true...
Yeah.
That's why, Mama...
I'm going to stay here for a while longer.
Yeah.
I have more friends now.
And...
I'm okay.
I'm considered really responsible.
Yeah.
Everyone says I'm like an adult.
What...
Would I wish for?
Right now...
I don't really know what it is that I really wish for...
I...
Don't even want to know.
Ryu-chan too!
Rub, rub.
I'll rub you too! Here!
Gross! Don't touch me with your feet!
I'm going to quit, quit, quit, quit, quit, quit, quit, quit, quit, quit!
Wow!
As expected of Kitamura-kun!
You said it ten times without messing up!
Quit what?
Everything!
I'm going to quit everything!