Okarin?
How?
I can feel her. She's really here.
You're not a ghost?
Do you want me to call the cops?
I just want to know the truth!
You were stabbed here...
What do you mean by "the truth"?
Are you stupid? Do you want to die?
That's Louise's famous line!
I saw it!
You were stabbed!
Three hours ago,
during Doctor Nakabachi's press conference at the radio building!
Okarin, try to control your delusions.
Doctor Nakabachi's press conference was called off!
But...
Ms. Makise! It's almost time!
All right!
Wait! Are you running away?
You're...
I have a name.
It's Hououin...
Kyouma!
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
is basic research with little glamor for you
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
are a vain theory we allowed
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
towards a cruel agreement and choice
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
and protect your smile
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
is sucked a solitary observer
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
Time Travel
Paranoia
Are Time Machines Possible?
Thank you all for coming here today.
I don't have much experience with lectures like these,
so I hope you'll bear with me.
Makise Kurisu's giving the lecture...
So, she isn't a ghost?
Still bringing that up?
I've been asked to speak to you about time machines.
It's a different theme from what I presented in my Science Magazine essay,
but I'd like to give it a try.
Time machines?
I believe that time machines are foolish.
I'd like to spend the lecture discussing how I arrived at that conclusio—
Objection!
Time machines are impossible?
It's far too early to decide that!
Okarin, you're embarrassing yourself.
You're...
I believe that "early" isn't the issue.
It's theoretically impossible.
What?
Well then, let's change the format of this lecture to a discussion.
That will make it easier for certain stubborn people to understand.
Right? Mr. Hououin Kyouma?
Makise Kurisu...
And from this,
we can conclude that, in a universe based on string theory,
time travel is unrealistic.
Do you want to try it?
Mr. Hououin?
I imagine so...
Then why not find some exotic matter for us,
Mr. Hououin?
That's all I have to say. But if you have any further objections, I'm listening.
Mr. Hououin!
Don't be so damned arrogant, just because you've some little bit of genius!
Wait... She must be an agent of the Organization!
It's hot... It's so hot...
The lecture was, in itself,
an act of carefully planned psychological warfare, aimed at me!
Well, I'm not falling for it.
Yanagibayashi
Shrine
Eight...
Nine...
Just one more swing.
You can do it!
Ten!
Way to go, Ruka!
Okarin!
Mr. O-Okabe... No, Mr. Kyouma.
You forgot the secret words, Rukako.
E-El Psy... Congre...
Congroo!
E-Excuse me.
So, what did you want me to carry?
This right here.
Thanks.
Mayushii can't carry all this.
My dad brought them, and we can't eat them all.
I see.
Thank you for donating these provisions to the lab.
This will raise morale amongst the lab members.
I'm so glad you like them...
Um... Well...
Ruka practices swinging a sword daily!
Yes. I promised Oka... I mean, Mr. Kyouma.
When the Magical Blade Samidare acknowledges you as a suitable wielder,
it will show its true power.
Do not forget that.
Yes!
You got such a deal on it at the weapons store. Only 980 yen!
Then, show me the results of your training.
Can you attempt an exorcism?
I-I suppose... But...
If you need a real exorcism, you should talk to my father...
An evil spirit has possessed my right hand!
Hurry and perform the exorcism, before the power overtakes my entire body!
R-Right!
That's a different hand than from last time.
The evil spirit possessed this one today, okay?
Urushibara Ruka.
The mannerisms and voice of a woman...
No... More feminine than any woman.
But he's a guy.
Taller than Mayuri, but so very thin...
Looks great in a shrine maiden outfit...
But he's a guy.
It's already twilight.
And yet, it's so hot.
The cicadas are crying.
But...
He's a guy.
Bye-bye!
Ruka's so great, able to do those exorcisms!
He's the scion of a shrine clan.
Sorry.
Restricted
Area
Akihabara
Police
It's off-limits?
Yeah, this leads behind the radio building.
The radio building...
Give me those.
You've got work soon, don't you?
Thank you.
I'm working late tonight, so I'm going straight home afterwards.
Mayuri...
You really didn't hear a scream, did you?
A scream? When?
Today, at the radio building.
I don't think I did.
I see...
All right.
Then that's fine.
Oh, Okarin...
So, no one remembers...
Not Mayuri. Not Daru. Not Makise Kurisu.
Open
Closed
You're closing up early today, Mr. Braun!
I told you not to call me that.
I'm interviewing a part-timer today.
A part-timer?
At a dreary shop with no customers,
run by an over-muscled old man?
You know...
'Sup!
I heard that's the popular way to say "hi" now.
This can't possibly be your part-timer...
Is it a problem?
Your name?
Amane Suzuha.
Age?
Eighteen.
Reason for working here?
I love CRT TVs!
You're hired!
Is this a comedy routine?
Some kind of joke?
Who are you?
His name's Okabe.
He's an idiot who rents a room upstairs.
It's not Okabe! It's Hououin—
Shut up! I'll double your rent.
I'm Okabe Rintarou.
Hi!
Say, what's in those bags?
Special Intelligence Corn that was donated to the lab.
If you want some, you must adequately compensate—
Corn?
With the little bumps?
So this is how it looks when fresh.
You didn't know?
Can I see—?
The Organization has targeted many people
because they've come into contact with me.
Sara, Claudia, Simona...
I see.
If you want, we could talk about it.
Don't worry about him. He's just making that up.
Think what you'd like.
Someday, the entire world will bow at my feet.
So, that's what's popular these days...
Unknown satellite crashes near Akihabara Station, around 12:00...
Crashed, around 12:00...
So, Mayuri and Daru were right.
Doctor Nakabachi Press Conference
The conference was canceled?
Makise Kurisu stabbed...
Was that some kind of hallucination?
@channel
John Titor?
A time traveler's here! lololol
SERN maintains an exclusive monopoly on time machines.
Neither civilians nor corporations may acquire one.
They've used the time machine for their sole benefit,
to bring about dystopia.
I've come here to change the future.
To destroy SERN's dystopia, and to set the world free again.
Then you claim that SERN are dictators?
You mean the so-called Grandfather Paradox, right?
257 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
All I can think of is the European Laboratory for Particle Physics.
There's no such thing.
451 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
If you time travel, can you meet yourself in the past?
It's possible to meet yourself in the past.
If you do, you simply move world lines.
What's a world line?
Inb4 parallel worlds.
Let me begin by saying
that time isn't a single line, moving from past to future.
It's comprised of an infinite number of parallel lines, like rivers, called "world lines."
For example, let's say a serial killer was to murder you today.
If I came from the future and prevented it,
the world would diverge into two streams:
a world in which you survived, and a world in which you died.
So, this Titor is Japanese, huh?
A self-proclaimed time traveler,
who appeared on the American internet, in the year 2000.
He claimed he'd come from the year 2036, to save the future.
He then became famous on the internet, leading to several books being published about him.
I didn't think I'd see some idiot pretending to be Titor now.
618 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
Pretending to be? Huh?
Then click this link and go read up on Titor!
Daru must've deleted the link on Titor...
John Titor            About 12 Results
Twelve?
Impossible.
Sure, it was ten years ago, but it was huge!
It can't be!
John Titor      About 56 results
They're not here!
They're not here! What is this?
I had a book collection on him, right here.
Damn it!
Hello?
Daru?
What is it?
I'm at Feyri...
What happened to the books?
The books?
The books on John Titor.
I had a bunch of them on the bookshelf, didn't I?
Where'd they all go?
Wait, Okarin?
What?
Who's... John Titor?
I stayed up most of the night looking into John Titor.
I found every bit of information I could on the internet.
But...
I want an answer from Titor.
About ten years ago... In other words, the year 2000.
It's interesting that you should ask that.
But unfortunately, I've never been to the year 2000.
Nor do I intend to go.
Hey! Wait!
You there! You! You!
You took my picture, didn't you?
You should delete it! For your own sake!
I apologize
if I've made you unhappy.
What were you taking pictures of?
Proof.
Of where I walked today... Of what I saw.
I want to ask you about something.
This.
That's a really old PC.
Do you recognize it?
No.
Do you know anyone who might?
Daru, maybe...
Who is that?
Nothing to do with you.
Delete that photo.
Tell me...
The e-mail...
For that person.
No!
Are you threatening me?
If you tell me,
I'll delete it.
Very well.
But I won't sell out my friends!
I'll give you my own address.
What's your name?
It says "Hououin Kyouma" right there!
Oubouin Kyouma
Give me that.
Send me a blank mail.
I'll just send something back.
Welcome back, Master!
It's Okarin!
Welcome, Okarin!
Yo, Mayuri.
When I'm working, it's Mayushii Nyan Nyan!
Come to think of it, "Okarin" kind of sounds like "welcome."
Where's Daru?
He's in the back.
Kyouma!
I've missed you.
What happened to your promise to visit every three days?
I'm sorry.
The Organization's sabotage has been just awful...
The Organization's gone that far?
Then you'll hold another secret meeting today on defeating them?
That's right.
Give me the usual Stealth Field.
On it!
I wish you'd let me join!
No!
The Organization is far too vast for you to handle!
But I've got my forbidden special move...
What?
You finally mastered it?
That's right.
After months of harsh training in the Guiana Highlands,
and having overcome my master's death, at last I...
I've mastered it!
I'll never forgive you. Ever.
So, about what I said in my mail...
I believe talking to a winner makes me a loser.
Don't worry.
I've no interest in that girl and her lies.
Is this today's "you're the last one I want to hear that from" thread?
Shut up, cheater!
Your 2D wives are crying.
Feyris is special!
She may be 3D, but she has a 2D soul!
Anyways, look at this.
This picture.
That's an IBN 5100, right?
IBN?
A legendary retro-PC.
It was about a month ago...
I'd heard a rumor one was somewhere in Akihabara.
She must've heard about it.
What happened?
No one ever found it.
Even the famous "Lightning Speed Night Heart" tried to find it and failed.
Meaning it probably never existed in the first place, is my final answer.
Is it that valuable?
It was sold over thirty years ago.
At the time, no one bought PCs. They were too expensive.
That's how stuff ends up incredibly rare.
That girl...
I sent that mail...
I'm Kiryuu Moeka...
Sender: The Lightning Shiatsu-ist
Subject: I'm waiting
Hououin, I sent that mail! I'm Kiryuu Moeka! Age 20! No real job!
I can mail you, right? I'm sending it, whether you like it or not! Moeka
Age 20... No real job...
I'm sending it, whether you like it or not...
Is this the same girl I just talked to?
What's wrong?
Be glad I didn't sell you out.
It's a rare and valuable PC,
but there's a good chance it's not in Akihabara.
El Psy Congroo.
Master!
Here you go, Nyan Nyan!
The
World's
In Danger ! !
It's my "The World's in Danger" omelet!
Yummy...
Calm down.
The World's in Danger!!
Analysis by the university laboratory
reveals that the gel-banas
have been torn apart at a molecular level.
So they turned into something that wasn't a banana.
Isn't that bad?
What's going on?
Right now, the one thing that comes to mind
is the EM wave effect from the Phone Microwave. (name subject to change)
Why think that?
It's my intuition as a mad scientist.
So, no reason.
Okay, it's all set.
Then let's use this.
Property of Mayushii
Aren't these Mayushii's?
Don't worry.
I bought them with research funds Mayuri donated to the lab.
Doesn't that make them hers—?
Now, let's toss the whole thing in and see what happens.
Wouldn't one work? Hurr.
Can we really discover the Phone Microwave's (name subject to change) true power
that way?
That (name subject to change) is annoying. We should take it off.
We can't change the world's ruling structure
if we're stingy with experimental funding!
You're the only one who wants to, you know?
Really?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, done.
What's wrong?
It's gone...
The banana's gone!
Impossible!
It's me.
Emergency Order 666.
Initiate the cool-off!
Government approval?
No time for that!
Talking to yourself... Fail!
Shut up!
Where'd you hide it?
What? You're the one who hid it, Okarin.
I see... I get it!
This must be some kind of teleporter microwave!
Wh-What?
That's crazy.
Then how do you explain this?
We took the banana from the bunch, put it into the microwave, and...
Gel-bana...
But it's completely connected to the rest of the bunch...
A second ago, we definitely removed one, didn't we?
I think so...
It's really a teleporter?
Is that what it is?
You're conducting an interesting experiment, Okabe Rintarou.
No, Mr. Hououin Kyouma, wasn't it?
Makise Kurisu?
kisei sareta chikai mujihi nari juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten