Caution... Fragile
Hey, Chitanda, is there
a superstition that says
that whatever you do on New Year's Day
will be repeated all year long?
Well, I don't think there's
a superstition about that.
Otherwise, it would mean that
when you took New Year's off,
you would wind up taking
the whole year off, as well,
which would be awfully absurd.
It's just that, Oreki-san,
if I had to say, I'm more concerned
about our present state
than I am about the other 364 days.
How did we end up like this?
That's a good question. Probably because
you picked an unlucky fortune, isn't it?
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Mishap-py New Year
Yes?
Hello, this is Chitanda.
Am I speaking to Oreki-san?
Yeah.
Um, do you have any plans
for New Year's Day?
Nope, not really.
Is that right? Well then, would
you like to go visit the shrine?
Visit the shrine?
Yes. Mayaka-san said
that she was working at
Arekusu Shrine as an attendant.
Not really up her alley.
That's not very nice, Oreki-san.
Fukube-san said that he was going, too,
so I wondered if you would
like to come, as well. Also...
You mean there's something else?
Not so much a "something," but...
I kind of want to dress up in my kimono.
Arekusu Shrine
It's cold.
It's New Year's, all right.
Thank you very much.
Some people have gotten all dressed up.
Right.
Ah! Oreki-san!
A happy new year to you.
A-A happy new year to you!
I look forward to your continuing
friendship in the coming year.
Oh, no, it is I that ask for your favor.
I came to show this outfit off.
Well, shall we get going?
Huh? Yeah.
Want me to carry that?
Huh?
Thank you very much. If you would.
What is it?
A bottle of saké. We have some
dealings with the priest here,
so I have come to offer
a New Year's greeting.
Already running errands for
the new year? What a hassle.
The real hassle came during the daytime.
I spent the whole time paying respects
to relatives, and being a good girl.
Oreki-san, what were you up to?
I...
was doing my imitation of a hermit crab.
Dark Clouds
Odani Castle
Oda Nobunaga
Imagawa Yoshimoto
Mori Shinsuke
Hermit crab?
It's nothing, never mind. Where's Satoshi?
Mayaka-san is the one who got
in touch with Fukube-san.
Oh, you know what, Oreki-san?
Let's start by offering our prayers.
Okay, let's see here...
May my year be spent in only
moderate energy consumption.
Excuse us!
What is it?
A happy new year to you.
On behalf of Chitanda Tetsugo,
my name is Eru, and I have come
to pay my respects for the new year.
And I'm Oreki, along for the ride.
Oh, you're Chitanda-san's girl?
Well, please, come on in.
I'll go get him.
Right. Pardon the intrusion.
So this is a genuine shrine
priestess. Very distinguished.
A happy new year to you.
I look forward to good relations
with you in the coming year, as well.
A happy new year to you.
I brought a bottle of saké from
my father. Please accept it.
Huh? Oh...
This is how distinguished families
associate with each other, huh?
Thank you very much. I accept.
Oh, it's nothing fancy.
Oreki-san, that's for me to say.
Oh...
We don't want it if it's not fancy.
Huh?!
Oh, don't say that. Please, accept
our gift. It is nothing fancy.
They're putting me on? And I panicked.
You're in Class B, right?
That's right.
I thought Fukube-kun was coming with you.
How does she know that? Divine powers?
This is Jumonji Kaho, from Class 1-B.
We're classmates?!
Um, we would like to see Ibara Mayaka-san.
Ibara? Oh, her.
This leads to the rear of
the kiosks, so go on ahead.
Mayaka-san...
Ah, Chi-chan!
That hairstyle is very becoming.
They put it on for me.
Don't stare.
A happy new year to you.
Happy new year. That kimono
looks great. It's very pretty!
Thank you very much.
Is it long-sleeved?
No, it's a normal pattern.
I will get to wear a long-sleeved
one once I go to college.
I'll be done here in another hour.
Chi-chan, what are you going to do?
I think I will remain in attendance
here in the main hall.
Where's Fukube-san?
He was here during the day. He went
home to watch... was it called...?
Dark Clouds: Odani Castle, some drama.
I think he'll be back
before too long, though.
Ibara, what are you selling there?
Fortunes. Also, I have lost-child,
lost-and-found, and change duty.
The parishioners are all worked up
making the rounds here,
so if anything of even a little bit of
value gets dropped, it comes right here.
It was busier during the day.
Lots of lost children.
Not that anyone asked.
A fortune would be nice. I'll take one.
Okay, pick from here.
Right.
Oh, that purse is terrific!
It looks so fancy!
Thank you very much.
You sure seem pleased.
Yes.
Here you go.
Fortunes
Number 10.
Oreki-san, would you like to try?
Hm...
Here.
Thanks.
Wow! "Great Luck"!
Fortune ♪10
Great Luck
Good for you, Chi-chan!
Yes!
Number 16.
What's the matter, Oreki-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
It looks like it's going
to be a great year.
You drew "Good Luck
Forthcoming," didn't you?
Fortune ♪16
Bad Luck
I've never
seen a "Bad Luck" fortune before today!
Are you that delighted by my "Bad Luck"?
I'm sorry. You're right. Oreki-san,
this must be bothering you.
Whatever, just give it back.
Kaho-san!
Oh, sorry, Eru. I didn't
even offer you any tea.
No, never mind that,
has something happened?
One of the part-timers
overturned some pots.
Now we have to make the dumpling soup
and sweet saké we were
serving all over again.
Oh, my. Was she burned?
No, it sounds like she's okay.
I'll help you.
No, that's okay. You can't cook
when you're dressed up like that.
Then, is there anything
else that I can do?
Hm...
Okay, could you bring in some
saké lees from the storehouse?
They're on the left right after you
go in, so you'll recognize them.
Sorry about this.
Not at all.
I'll come with you.
Storehouse, huh?
That was next to the
Inari statue, as I recall.
Whoo, it's cold.
Let's hurry and get this taken care of.
That's not very secure.
I hope there's a light in here.
Yes...
There's a wall along the left.
Could it be further inside?
That could be.
I thought this would be a simple errand,
but this is becoming a pain.
Oreki-san, this is a shed, right?
Yeah, well, call it a shed or call it
a shack, this is the place, right?
No, it's the storehouse.
Huh?
Kaho-san said it was in the storehouse.
Oh! My family doesn't have a storehouse,
so I got mixed up! Tee-hee!
Nah, I can't say that.
If you knew that, then speak up.
I'm sorry. I wasn't exactly sure.
I know that the mikoshi storage room
is next to the shrine office.
Then let's head back.
Oh, this is unlocked.
Huh?
There we go.
Don't tell me!
What's the matter?
We're locked inside.
Touji ('Depth of Winter')
When the sun reacheth its southmost
extreme, and the days are shortest
Hyouka
Caution... Fragile
Sorry.
This is all because I
made a stupid mistake.
No, no matter what
kind of mistake it was,
we never thought that we
would get locked in here.
All right, I'll call for someone.
I'm going to shout as loud as I can,
so you should cover your ears.
Ah, just a minute. Um...
♪ Ah... Ah... ♪
Just a moment, please!
I-I'm sorry! But please, wait.
Okay.
Um, if you shout out now and call
people over, what will happen?
Hm? Well, someone will probably come.
They'll unbar the door, and open it for us.
And then, how will the two of us look?
How will we look?
Those parishioners know me.
If those parishioners help me out,
they're sure to misunderstand
what happened.
I am here today representing my father.
If it were another time and place,
that would be one thing,
but now, here, if they were to
find me alone with you, Oreki-san...
I just don't understand her world.
All right. But then, what do we do?
If someone comes here needing to
get something, and opens the door,
they're definitely going
to get the wrong idea.
The only ones who would
understand our situation
are Kaho-san and Mayaka-san.
Yeah.
I just had a good idea!
Oh?
It's simple. We can use a cell phone.
Well sure, that would
work fine. So, go ahead.
I don't have my cell phone.
Neither do I.
That's right! What are we going to do?
We can't remove the door itself.
Um, Oreki-san, I forgot that
you don't own a cell phone.
That's why I asked you not to
shout out to call anyone over.
Mm-hm.
But at this point, it's another story.
Let's call someone over.
If we don't do something soon,
you're going to catch a cold.
But you're worried, aren't you?
That people will misunderstand?
If we run out of other options,
we'll call for someone.
Until then, though, let's think
of anything else we can try.
Oreki-san...
We can't move the bar,
and we can't remove the hinges.
But there are still four avenues of
escape that we haven't explored.
Huh? That many?
Yeah.
One, we could break the door down.
Two, we could break the wall down.
Three, we could dig a hole
to crawl out through.
Four, we can open up a hole in the ceiling.
No, we can't do those!
Even though they are old, they're
still Arekusu Shrine's buildings.
Yeah, I guess those are out.
Someone is heading this way!
Hm?
That's a parishioner, making his rounds.
It looks like he picked up
a cell phone strap.
You can see that?
I have good night vision.
What is she, a wild animal?
Oh, he's heading back.
He's going to drop it off
at the shrine office.
The shrine office... Hm...
Listen, Chitanda, would it be okay
to break open the wall a little bit?
Hm?
Ibara mentioned earlier that when
someone dropped anything of value,
the parishioners bring it
right to her, remember?
And right now, Ibara is
in charge of lost items.
Yes...
So we drop something that
clearly belongs to us from here,
and have a parishioner
deliver it to Ibara for us.
If we can convey our plight to her,
she may come to rescue us.
I see what you mean!
How big a question it raises that
it was picked up near the shed
all depends on Ibara, though.
What about my handkerchief?
I think Mayaka-san has seen it many times.
All right, let's use that.
Chitanda, drop your
handkerchief through there.
R-Right.
Please let this work.
Chi-chan and Oreki are already here.
Come to the office and wait.
Ah... Jumonji-san! Happy new year!
Happy new year to you.
Fukube-kun, have you seen Eru?
Chitanda-san? I just got here,
so I'm not really sure.
Oh. Sorry I can't show you around,
but go on in on your own.
The stove is on in the great hall.
I just don't know how to
act around Jumonji-san.
Mayaka!
Wah! Oh, Fuku-chan...
Is she still embarrassed
about her attendant getup?
It must be hard work in all
this cold. You're a real trouper.
Mm-mm. But never mind me,
how was your drama?
It was a masterpiece! I got to start
the year with a huge smile!
Really? Oh, right...
Look, Fuku-chan. Do you recognize this?
No.
It seems to me that
Chi-chan had one like this.
It's nice that you might know
who the owner is, isn't it?
Once Chitanda-san gets
back here, you can ask her.
Mm-hm, you're right.
Help... isn't coming, is it?
I thought we were headed
in the right direction, too.
I guess a handkerchief
by itself isn't enough.
It isn't something that leaves
much of an impression.
All right, in that case,
we move to the next step.
Let's try my wallet.
Here you go.
Right.
Change made
Hm? Look at this, Fuku-chan!
That's Hotaro's wallet, huh?
Mm-hm. Looks like the idiot
dropped it. It's been emptied out.
What's that?
That's the fortune that he drew.
Whoa!
Hotaro went and drew "Bad Luck," huh?
But this is strange.
It's emptier than empty.
Mayaka...
Let me draw a fortune, too.
The ones here seem to really work.
Help isn't coming, is it?
No...
Are you okay?
Yes. I wish I'd worn my haori, though.
Haori?
It's a coat that you wear over a kimono.
I'm regretting not wearing
a trench coat, myself.
It really is getting
a bit chilly, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Chitanda. We might not
be able to hold out any longer.
I'm sure it's reached Ibara by now,
but it wasn't enough to make her
skip out of work and come look.
That's okay. Thanks for going along
with my selfish request for so long.
You aren't being selfish;
it's your responsibility.
That doesn't excuse dragging
you along with me, though.
Let's call for help. There's no getting
around some degree of gossip.
Fukube-san should be
here by now, as well.
That's it! Satoshi!
Bowls
Oreki-san?
Chitanda, do you have any kind of string?
S-String, you say?
About this much. 50 cm long
should be plenty.
Once we have that, I can definitely
let Satoshi know of our situation.
The strap from my sandals?
Too short.
Ah, I have the drawstring from my purse!
That won't work. We're going
to use your purse.
Then, Oreki-san, what about your shoelace?
I'm wearing boots today, with no laces.
If there's no other choice, then...
we might be able
to use my sash's obijime.
Is that a string?
Yes.
Will taking it off be hard?
Yes, well, I suppose.
It will take a little effort.
Listen, Chitanda, I don't know
much about kimonos,
but if you remove the obijime,
will the kimono still be okay?
The sash will pretty much fall down.
Well, that's not an option, is it?!
No, I suppose not.
Is there some other string
around anywhere?
Um, how will you be able to get help
from Fukube-san with a string?
I remember there being
a flag outside the shed...
Please forgive me.
Oreki-san...?
I've found a string!
Chitanda, let me have your purse.
What are you doing?
Why is this...?
This is definitely Chi-chan's
purse! I saw it earlier!
A handkerchief, a wallet,
and now a purse.
I wonder if this is Hotaro's
"Bad Luck" at work.
They said they found this
next to the shed, too.
I wonder what the two
of them could be doing.
There's a dirty old string
attached to it, too.
String?
Mm-hm, see?
Is this...?!
W-What's the matter, Fuku-chan?
Mayaka, where's the shed?!
Over that way. Next to the Inari statue.
I'll be right back!
Hotaro, Chitanda-san,
I'm coming to save you now!
Your purse is a bag.
When you tie up the
opening and the bottom,
it closes up whatever is inside it.
Just like in the expression
"trapped like a rat in a bag."
A rat in a bag?
I'm not the one who thought it up.
It comes from a historic episode.
You've heard of the
Battle of Anegawa, right?
Yes.
There's a famous story that came
before it; do you know it?
The withdrawal from Kanegazaki?
When Nobunaga was laying
siege to the Asakura Clan,
Nobunaga's brother-in-law,
Azai, betrayed him.
Nobunaga's sister, Lady Oichi,
sent a bean bag tied up at both
ends to Nobunaga in the field,
to convey to him that she
was a "rat in a bag."
Well, I don't know how much
of it is actually true, though.
There's such a tale, is there?
Just today, both Satoshi and I saw
that episode play out in a drama.
Knowing him, he'll
understand what it means.
Hotaro! Are you in there?!
Yeah!
You saved us. We were
about to freeze to death.
They're serving hot
sweet saké at the office.
I'll open the door now.
Hey.
Mis-happy new year!
Yo...
Mis-happy new year.
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "The Case of
the Homemade Chocolates."
The Case of the Homemade Chocolates