Go!
In the year 850, humankind reclaimed
lands from the Titans for the first time
since their appearance some hundred-odd years before.
The cost, however, was great.
You who stayed, you are now one of us.
Allow me to welcome you to the Scout Regiment.
This is a genuine salute, soldiers!
Together, we give our hearts!
Sir!
Those of you standing here have worked through your fear.
You've proven yourselves courageous.
Each one of you has my respect.
One short month later, led by Erwin Smith,
the Scout Regiment set out.
Leaving the relative comfort
and safety of Calaneth District,
they sought to carve a route to Shiganshina,
the place believed to hold the Titans' secrets.
It's officially begun. The 57th Recon Mission!
Scouts, move out!
We've got a ten-meter closing in from the left! Gah!
I want to know what's rolling
around in that glorious belly!
Never mind. Let the support squad do their job.
Damn! Too shallow!
Just focus on defending the ranks!
Eyes front! Their job's to
handle it. Yours is to keep moving!
Forward! Ride for all you're worth!
They'll only have our backs
'til we're clear of the city ruins.
Everything beyond that will be
uninterrupted Titan territory.
We'll be more or less on our own.
The only thing to fall back on out there is
Commander Erwin's long-range scouting formation.
The special ops squad'll be positioned here.
Loaded question. Be straight with me.
You think my friends have a shot at taking down a Titan?
Really? I should certainly hope so, otherwise
what the hell have they been training for?
Now listen, and listen well. Prepared or not,
you're all Scouts, which means the time
is nigh to choke back those fears and...!
Long-range formation. Let's go!
See you 'round. Good luck.
Do us a favor if you run into
one of 'em and don't piss yourself.
Yeah. Same goes for you.
The long-range scouting formation
is a forward-facing semicircle.
We'll be positioned relative to one another at
equal intervals within view of signal fire on all sides.
The idea is to extend our spotting
and signal range as far as possible.
Stay calm. You're alright.
You can bet the lucky bastards riding in the
front-row spotting squads will see a lot of Titans.
The second one comes into view, lock and load.
Alert your nearest comrades with a red smoke signal.
They in turn will alert their nearest
comrades by doing the same, and so on.
Once the commander feels he has a
decent read on the Titan's position,
he'll be firing off a green smoke signal.
At the sight of one, the
platoon is to reroute accordingly.
The fewer Titans confronted head-on
en route to our goal, the better;
we'll need all the able bodies we can
spare. The name of the game then is evasion.
Now keep in mind, this isn't a foolproof strategy.
The terrain is wild; plenty of
places for the enemy to lie in ambush.
Red smoke. Have to fire...
Braus! Over here!
Damn! The Spotters missed a live one!
I say we lure it in our direction!
Braus! Cross back over to us!
Break away! I'll take care of it!
Sir!
Sorry!
It's alright, he's out. Return to your position.
Something feels off.
It's been too long since the last red signal,
and the formation's still all over the map.
Wait.
Keep in mind too, this whole approach
assumes we'll be dealing largely with Normals;
Titans whose behavior is predictable.
Black smoke? There's a Titan ignoring the
outliers and making a b-line for the center!
That can only mean...
...an Abnormal!
If one or more of those show up, I'm
afraid we'll have no choice but to engage.
Son of a... Well there's no help for it I guess. Heads up!
The nape's all yours, okay? I'll go for the legs!
You got it!
ODM gear's worth squat on level ground.
I'm not exactly thrilled about our odds here.
But hell, we can't let it break up the formation!
Arlelt's up ahead at my ten o'clock, isn't he?
I'm not letting a rookie face this bastard alone!
It's now or never!
All yours, Cis!
Way to go! Nicely done, Ness!
Not so bad.
Hey, hey! Nothing scares you, huh?
That's my li'l darlin' Charrette!
Not again. What in the hell are the
right wing spotters doing back there?
Looks like we've got another Abnormal on our hands.
It's not their fault.
Ahhhh. I hate these things.
Fine. One more for the road, then.
Right!
Damn it. Someone mind tellin' me what we did to
deserve two in a row? Bad enough it's an Abnormal,
but it's gotta be 14 meters.
This is gonna be a pain in the ass.
It's moving so fast. Too fast!
We have to keep it clear of Arlelt! Cis!
On it!
Did that really just happen?
We're not dealing with an Abnormal.
This thing's showing intelligence!
Like the Colossal. Like Eren!
It's a human being wrapped in a Titan body!
But who? Why?
What am I gonna do? I'm dead! I'm so dead!
Go! Make a break for it!
Why is it...
No. Why are they...
...doing this?
Somebody tell the others.
The right-wing spotters are all but wiped out.
Tell Commander Erwin...
that the Female Titan brought a hoard with her.
Is anyone left? There has to be someone.
Huh?
This doesn't make any sense. Why
didn't it... Why didn't it kill me?
It pulled back my hood. Looked at my...
Why would it need to check my face?
Armin!
Reiner!
Hey. Can you ride? What the hell are you doing?
This is full-blown Titan country,
you can't be without a horse! Climb on!
I came as fast as I could when I saw the black smoke.
Nice ass for an Abnormal, you gotta admit.
It's not an Abnormal.
It's a person controlling a Titan body.
Wait. What?
I'll explain in a second. We need to
fire off a signal to warn the others!
Come on! Work you piece of garbage!
It's an emergency!
Hey. It's alright. Looks like Jean's got you covered.
Oh man, that's not good. The right-wing spotters
have suffered too many causalities to carry on!
Yeah, apparently most of them
were wiped out by a Titan ambush.
I don't know how it happened, but it
was bad. Sons-a-bitches were lighting-fast.
The spotters didn't have time to react.
Whoever's left is trying to hold them off, but
that means now there's no one on lookout duty.
Talk about a setback, right?
If we don't watch ourselves,
we're all gonna get wiped out.
Wait. She came from that direction.
Does that mean...
Could she have led the Titans here like a commander?
Who, her?
Why the hell's she running from us, by the way?
Is she an Abnormal?
No, she's isn't. I still don't know how it's possible,
but she's another human who's taken Titan form.
Someone who has the same power as Eren.
Please say you're not serious.
Really? Why do you think that?
Titans eat people, but they're not murderers.
Sure, they kill us in the
process, but that's not their intent;
they just feed on instinct like any creature.
This one was different. When the others went for her nape,
she struck them down in cold blood.
Swatted them like flies.
She didn't eat them; she killed them and moved on.
That's out of character, even for an Abnormal.
The Titans that took out the right-wing?
I think she brought them here.
Just like the Colossal and the Armored when they struck.
I just know it.
She's not simply satisfying bloodlust.
She has it in for us.
Or perhaps more specifically,
I think she's actually after someone in particular.
At which point the question becomes who and why?
Hey, wait a second, could it be Eren?
Eren? He's with Levi Squad.
They're spearheading the right-wing. Or, they were.
Wait. Levi's team?
I'm pretty sure you're wrong there, big guy.
My copy of the plan had them in the left wing.
That's odd, because my copy of the plan
had them at the front of the right-wing, too,
which now that I think about it doesn't make sense.
Putting them at the vanguard like
that wouldn't be smart strategically.
Then where exactly are they supposed to be?
Come on, where else? The safest position in the formation.
Which, I assume, at least,
would be rear of the center rank.
Armin! Now's not the time to be
chasin' our own tails about this!
We've got to get word out how dangerous
this one is; smoke signals aren't gonna cut it!
At this rate, she'll cut down the command squad!
We let that happen, the formation
goes to hell and we all die!
You have a plan?
More of a wing and a prayer. Look, we've got to try
and distract her so the platoon has a chance to retreat.
If we're careful, from this distance
we should be able to manage it.
And make it out alive.
Well, maybe anyway.
She's smarter than the ones we usually deal with.
You can take my word for it. From her
perspective we're little more than insects.
One swipe of that arm and we're all flattened.
Is that a fact?
What a terrifying thought.
Seriously. What have you done with the real Jean?
No offense, man, but the one I knew could
only be counted on to look out for himself.
Your people skills need work.
Believe me, friends. I'm still all about number one.
I just don't wanna end up a pile
of bones no one knows were mine.
Thing is, I get it now.
I get what needs to be done if
we're going to survive this fight!
And last I checked, nobody
forced us to take on this position.
Now are you with me or not?
Pull your hood all the way over so it covers you.
She won't try to kill you if she can't see your face!
If she's looking for someone specific, she won't
mow us down unless she knows for sure we're not them.
Good idea. As far as she knows, any one
of us could be Eren underneath this getup.
That's actually kind of an encouraging thought.
Hey, you never know, maybe we'll get
lucky and she'll be near-sighted to boot.
Not gonna lie. The way you clung to Eren like a
security blanket all the time used to really creep me out.
But I always knew you were brilliant.
Uh. Okay, thank you.
Not exactly sure how I ought to take that, but thanks.
She's slowed a bit since she first came at us.
Tired maybe? Let's hope.
If she speeds up, we lose her.
We have to do this now, before she gets her wind back!
Okay, guys. Like we discussed.
Lure her away from the others so
they have a chance to get out of here.
Keep her on our trail for as long as possible.
Give the rest of the platoon plenty of time.
Slicing her Achilles' tendon should do the trick, I think.
Nothing crazy. If she's what
Armin says, we need her alive.
She's aware of her soft spot, so she'll defend it.
No run of-the-mill nightmare, this one.
Killing her is out of the question.
Well, it would be for normal people anyway,
So let's just focus on keeping her distracted.
When the time comes, maybe they could take her down.
Armin!
The moves on this one, she's like a damn athlete!
We are so screwed! Didn't think this through!
What? She's protecting her weak spot?
Jean!
Damn it! There's nothing I can do.
I'm a dead man! She's gonna yank my wire and...!
Jean! Don't let that suicidal maniac die in vain!
What the...?
Why did she stop?
She did it! She's the one who killed him!
I told him the right wing was
suicide but he went along anyway!
And how he's dead, thanks to her!
What the hell's going on?
Of all the times for Armin to get the sense
knocked out of him! What's he talkin' about?
Reiner.
She crushed my best friend, I saw it with my own eyes!
His entrails were stuck to the bottom of her foot!
He's going straight for the nape? Of course!
Now's his chance, while she's focused on Armin!
Oh no. No.
No! Reiner. Oh, god.
That beautiful bastard!
Mikasa's been hogging so much of the limelight these
days, I'd let myself forget how much of a badass he is.
Odds are that bought the platoon more than enough time.
I say we follow suit and get outta here!
If she doesn't have an appetite for people like
you say, I'm guessin' she's not gonna follow us.
Alright! Looks like she's in retreat!
Poor thing's running home with her tail between her legs!
What? Wait. No.
She's headed for the center rank.
She's... She's going for Eren!
The monster advances.
Even the Scout Regiment, for all its training and skill,
cannot bring its newest foe to heel.
Until at last, in a forest of giant
trees, she catches sight of her goal.