We're not getting anywhere without the first issue.
You're right.
I wish we could get Satoshi and Ibara to help.
No, I...
At any rate, even if we can't solve the mystery,
sooner or later, it'll become a thing of the past.
A thing of the past?
I understand. Let's ask Fukube and Mayaka to help.
I'm curious about what happened to my uncle 45 years ago.
Please help me find out.
Your uncle, huh?
I never knew.
The secret of that heroic tale will be solved 45 years later by their juniors, huh?
I've actually been doing some research on that time period.
I'm pretty curious about this picture too.
I'd like to know the story about it.
Isn't this exciting?
Who knows? Maybe we could even use it for our anthology.
You should use this as an opportunity to do all the research you want.
And so, researching the club's history was of utmost importance.
退屈な窓辺に吹き込む風に
The wind blew into the boring classroom
顔を顰めたのは照れくささの裏返し
That grimace on my face hides my tiny bit of joy
Hyouka
曖昧に頷く　手のひらの現在
I just nod my way through the life designed for me
描いてる自分は少し大げさで
Maybe I'm a little too pretentious
何か変わりそうな気がしているよ
It feels like something is about to change
心に呼びかける君のせいだね
You're probably to blame, for calling out to my heart
曇り空覗いた予感
It's as if I saw a glimpse of color through the clouds
手を伸ばそういつよりも力強い勇気で
Let's reach out with more courage than usual
光も影もまだ遠くて
Light and shadow are still so far beyond our reach
それでも僕らは優しさの理由が知りたい
But we still want to know the source of your kindness
今は誰の名前でもない
Your name doesn't define you
輝きの彼方へ 全部過去になる前に
Let's go find what lies beyond the light
見つけに行こう
Before everything turns into the past
Glorious Olden Days of the Classic Literature Club
I'm so sorry! Did I keep you?
What's with you, Houtarou?
Shut up!
Have you no shame?
Anyway, did you do your research?
What about you?
Find anything interesting?
Sort of.
I look forward to hearing your hypothesis.
Crap. I forgot to write one.
All right, let's go.
The Chitanda farmer family has one of the best mansions in Kamiyama!
You seem to be having fun.
Duh! Cycling is fun!
I'm using my legs to divide the wind! This feeling-
No, I mean with your high school life in general.
Oh, right. The whole "rosy" thing.
I try to keep a rosy lifestyle wherever I go.
You mean shocking pink?
That's a good one.
By that logic, you're gray.
We've been through this already.
We have?
I wasn't trying to mock you.
After all, I have a shocking pink lifestyle.
No one can change that about me.
I won't let 'em.
Aren't you painted all over?
Nope.
What's the matter, Houtarou?
Don't tell me you're upset with how busy I am with the committee and Sewing Club.
But I'm right, aren't I?
No.
No matter what, I am who I am.
Not something people want me to be.
I'd say you're colorless if I'm actually mocking you.
I don't want to be liked by you.
You got a point there!
By the way, Houtarou.
How did you do on your midterms?
I got an average grade in every subject.
I didn't expect any less from you, Mr. Gray.
See that?
That's the Chitanda estate.
What do you think?
Isn't it impressive?
Let's go.
They're waiting for us.
Yeah.
Houtarou.
Doesn't it feel like a servant will come greet us?
Hello.
We've been waiting.
Coming right in.
Please follow me.
Have a seat wherever you'd like.
Took you long enough.
We're not late.
I've never seen someone look so out of place at the end of a table.
Let's get this meeting underway.
Yeah!
Okay.
Aight.
Today, I thought we could look over the events within the Classic Literature Club 45 years ago.
If we come to a conclusion, I'd like to use it as part of this year's anthology.
First, we'll distribute the documents and our reports.
We'll then have a question and answer session,
followed by each of our hypotheses.
And to wrap it all up, we will analyze our hypotheses.
Oh? She actually seems like a great host.
So, would the first presenter...
Huh?
Who should present first?!
Never mind.
It doesn't matter who.
You should start things off.
Ah, you're right.
Let's go clockwise starting from me.
I researched about Hyouka itself.
Only the preface mentions what happened 45 years ago.
I summarized the facts, which you can see in the second page.
1.
The "upperclassman" left (from where?)
2.
The "upperclassman" became a hero 45 years ago, and became a legend 44 years ago
3.
The "upperclassman" was a "quiet fighter" and a "gentle hero."
4.
The "upperclassman" gave birth to the name "Hyouka."
5.
Conflict and sacrifice (sacrifice = the "upperclassman"?)
First, the "upperclassman" is my uncle, Sekitani Jun.
He dropped out of Kamiyama High,
and received no further education.
2.
The "upperclassman" became a hero 45 years
ago, and became a legend 44 years ago
Second, I believe this means that the story would have gone through many changes.
1.
The "upperclassman" left (from where?)
2.
The "upperclassman" became a hero 45 years ago, and became a legend 44 years ago
3.
The "upperclassman" was a "quiet fighter" and a "gentle hero."
4.
The "upperclassman" gave birth to the name "Hyouka."
5.
Conflict and sacrifice (sacrifice = the "upperclassman"?)
Three and five go hand in hand.
The quiet and gentle upperclassman became a fighter, then a hero.
And in the end, he was sacrificed.
4.
The "upperclassman" gave birth to the name "Hyouka."
Four is quite intriguing, but let's not discuss it at this time.
That's all for my report.
Any questions?
Heroic Tale
Why did you skip over the "It was not a heroic tale in any way" part?
That part represents the writer's state of mind.
Maybe it means that it wasn't as glorified as it sounds, but that it was actually a struggle.
I see.
Allow me to present my hypothesis.
My uncle might have had a conflict with someone, so he decided to drop out.
I've also looked into another element that hasn't been mentioned.
This part. "It's been a year since."
My uncle dropped out in the season of Kanya Fest.
We're getting a bit off topic, but a friend from another high school told me there was trouble in their cultural festival.
Oh, cultural festival saboteurs, right?
The students were extorted and in the end, lose all their earnings!
I believe that delinquents have always been around.
Unfortunately, Kanya Fest was their target that year.
So maybe my uncle resisted with violence and became a hero.
The juniors who mourned his loss must have left this behind.
Hypothesis rejected.
Yeah, rejected.
It's no good?
Please tell me why!
Chitanda, do you remember what I suggested when we were talking about anthologies?
Um...
Food stalls?
Right.
But you said that they've always been prohibited.
If there's no chance of making money, cultural festival saboteurs wouldn't show up.
I don't think all saboteurs are after money.
You're pathetic, Houtarou.
Oh? Then let's hear your idea, Mr. Big Shot.
Believe it or not, cultural festival
saboteurs didn't exist 45 years ago.
Why not?
Does anything about the '60s ring a bell?
Tokyo, the Diet Building, placards, demonstrations.
What are you talking about, Satoshi?
Student protests.
The sort of school violence that Chitanda is describing was rarely seen in the '60s.
This was an era where people picked fights against the government instead of teachers and schools.
Don't act as if you've seen it first hand.
Like I said, I'm researching that time period.
He's right. I didn't take history into account.
I'm sorry, Chii!
Why are you apologizing?
Your hypothesis doesn't work according to my research.
Since I was next, I didn't know if I should've interrupted you.
Dammit, Ibara.
You made me listen to all that for nothing.
We'll put my speculation aside for now. Please let us hear yours.
Is that all right with everyone else?
Yeah.
My legs are numb.
Seriously though, this is a huge mansion.
Do you have a pond in your garden?
Yes, we do.
Really? I would love to see it.
Me too!
Let's continue this in another place then.
Our porch is very cozy!
A pond, huh?
Boushu
The time to seed for crops
Hyouka
It's a scan of this book I found in the library, Unity & Triumph Vol. 1.
I couldn't find any other volumes.
It was published 44 years ago, just like Chii's document.
"Our relentless activism," huh?
Sounds just like what I'd expect from this era.
Well, here I go.
We
Assume that "we" means "students,"
while "reflexive forces" and
"authoritarians" means teachers.
Reactionary Forces
Authoritarians
June
During the previous June, there was a huge clash between the students,
and the Classic Literature Club's president, Sekitani Jun, led the movement.
They then executed this "activism," causing trouble with the teachers.
Activism
Oh. So it's clash, not conflict?
This Unity & Triumph book looks pretty fishy.
Fishy? How?
I'm not doubting its authenticity.
It just sounds like someone who admired student protests wrote it.
So what about it?
Nothing, I was just talking to myself.
Sorry about that.
Any other questions?
I'll move on to my hypothesis, then.
But before that, I'll disprove Chii's hypothesis.
According to Unity & Triumph, the incident occurred in June.
He did something that led to expulsion.
I can only think of violence.
This means those who followed Sekitani Jun...
Bam! They attacked the teachers.
I don't know if they actually hit them,
but something happened 45 years ago that endangered a students' individuality,
and they retaliated.
My uncle was their leader?
I see where you're getting at, but...
What is it?
You're saying that a student used violence against the teachers' suppression.
I guess so.
Your speculation is too abstract.
Well, it's not like you can go more in-depth anyway.
It's true I didn't get into the specifics,
but were there any contradictions?
There were.
Hyouka
Unity
and
Rejoice
Assuming both Hyouka and Unity & Triumph are true,
then the incident occurred in June, and he was expelled on the month of the cultural festival, October.
Incident
June
Expelled
October
If it's a punitive action for violence, then he should've been expelled right after the incident.
You sure?
This four-month gap bothers me as well.
They saying "it's been a year" by the time of the cultural festival,
so the expulsion was probably in October.
You're all so picky.
I think you're on the right direction.
I agree.
So is that the end of my turn?
Yes. Thank you.
Next up...
My bad. I'm pretty hungry.
Good grief. Haven't you eaten enough snacks already?
Well...
I can make some rice balls if you'd like.
Why don't we all take a break?
Is there anything I can do to help, Chii?
No, I'm fine here.
Really?
Yes.
It's hand-made!
You ecstatic little bastard.
Fuku, what's this?
Sorry, Mayaka!
My research disproves part of your hypothesis.
I forgot to mention it.
Oh.
Is this Kami High's Monthly Report?
Oh, yeah. Toukaidou mentioned that they were nearing 500 issues.
Correct!
My research was on archives of the Wall Newspaper Club's Monthly Report.
This was all I could find from 45 years ago.
The summary is on the next page.
The first and the last entries are what we already have.
Violence wasn't used in the incident,
so Mayaka's hypothesis needs some reworking.
Also, if "the entire school" here is what they mean by "we,"
then all the students must have been involved in the incident.
Otherwise, someone was there to organize the entire school.
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks, Chii.
Don't mention it.
There are plum, kelp, and leaf mustard fillings.
Please try them.
Thanks!
What's up?
Nothing!
It's good!
It's delicious!
Is the rice made in your farm?
Yes.
You can ask your questions now.
Are you sure this legendary protest was the cause of Sekitani Jun's expulsion?
I don't think this scan is conclusive.
Who knows?
I can't prove it.
"Who knows?"
We can't use this for research, then.
Oh, really?
But we have indirect evidence.
Sekitani Jun's incident,
and the legendary protest are different.
That means there should be a line that says "this is the legendary one" instead.
Yeah! That's what I wanted to say!
You really get me, Mayaka.
Let's hear your hypothesis, then.
Hypothesis, huh?
What's the matter?
Chitanda, I'm sorry, but I can't make a hypothesis.
I can barely correct Ibara's speculation with what I have.
Not to mention,
a database can't come to a conclusion.
I knew he'd say that.
Let's see...
What will I do with this?
Okay then, Oreki. If you'd please.
Houtarou, is this...
Kamiyama High's 50 Years of Journey?
I was wondering if we could find something in the official records.
But now that I look at it again, there's nothing of significance here.
I don't have a hypothesis either.
What will I do now?
What's the matter, Houtarou?
Hey, have you already forgotten the process?
First, you present your information.
Is this really even necessary?
Houtarou?
Oreki?
Whatever.
I need a way out of this.
What is it?
I forgot I was drying some Shiitake mushrooms.
I need to take them inside.
Do you need any help?
I can handle it.
Chitanda.
Yes?
Sorry, but can I use your bathroom?
Exit this room, then go straight.
What are you, nervous?
Go straight... Go straight.
I'm lost.
She did this much research?
I guess I should use my head.
45 years ago, something happened to Sekitani Jun.
There are four documents.
What do they have in common?
Think.
Student protest.
Violence.
A gap in expulsion.
45 years ago, Sekitani Jun was...
Took you long enough.
Well, sorry.
It's my turn to present, right?
Sorry, but I didn't have a hypothesis.
So let's end my turn,
and come to the conclusion.
You came up with a solution, didn't you?
Sort of. I think it'll explain most of the mysteries.
You figured something out, Oreki?
Come on, Chitanda. Relax!
Let's hear what he's got.
Don't disappoint us.
Fine. Let's take it from the top.
First, when.
It was 45 years ago.
The problem is what time of the year.
If we trust both Hyouka and Unity & Triumph,
then the incident happened in June, and he left in October.
Next, where.
It was in Kamiyama High School.
Then, who.
From Unity & Triumph, Sekitani Jun is the center of everything.
According to Kami High Monthly Report,
the entire school was involved with the incident as well.
Now, why.
Students would only protest against a certain type of person.
Right, the teachers.
Using Ibara's words,
the reason they stood up was because their independence was lost.
And the cause of the incident is...
the cultural festival.
Was it written somewhere that the cultural festival was responsible for the incident?
No, but judging from what happened,
I think there was a debate between the teachers and students on June,
and the cultural festival was held on October.
By debate, you mean this "Cultural Festival Discussion Meeting?"
Yes.
Take a closer look.
There are circle and square marks on top of each line.
I know!
Squares are yearly events,
and circles are events unique to that year!
I checked other years too. That's seems to be the case.
Why was the only Cultural Festival
Discussion Meeting held 45 years ago?
There must have been strong demands from students.
The hint can be found in Hyouka.
Right here.
"In a single year, he turned from a hero into a legend.
"the cultural festival will be held once again for five days of glory."
The key here isn't "held once again,"
but "five days" part.
What do you mean?
"Five days" is the achievement of the hero, Sekitani Jun.
This is just my guess, but the principal's "Declaration of Focus on Education" is related.
The principal might have tried to shorten the five days of cultural festival.
That's why the entire school was engulfed in rage.
This is the cause of the incident, why.
As well as the actual action, how.
Under Classic Literature Club president, Sekitani Jun's
heroic guidance,
relentless activism was held.
Which leads to the final item, what.
The student's didn't use violence.
They must have boycotted at most.
The staff had no choice but to negotiate with the students,
and refrained from shortening the cultural festival.
However, the hero, Sekitani Jun was expelled in exchange.
As for why there's a gap in the incident and expulsion...
the conflict would only get more out of hand if Sekitani Jun was expelled back then.
That's why it happened after the craze, after the cultural festival.
That's all for my conclusion.
Something like that happened to my uncle...
I'm impressed, Oreki.
That was pretty impressive, Houtarou.
It all checks out.
Oreki did it again! I can't believe it!
I was just lucky.
Are there any questions?
Nope.
I hate to admit it, but I think he's right.
Let's base our anthology this year on Oreki's conclusion.
I'll inform you of the details in a few days.
This meeting is adjourned.
Good work, everyone.
Thank you so much.
I didn't do it on my own.
No, it's all thanks to you.
Thanks for lending me an umbrella.
See you.
If he's right, why did I...
cry back then?
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね　見つけてね
Please come and find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
芽生えてた温もり　暖かくて戸惑う
I'm at a loss to this warmth growing inside me
こんな気持ちをまだ　あなたは分からないの
You're still oblivious to my feelings
その視線には意味なんて別にないはず
I'm sure your gaze doesn't mean anything
だって友達にしてるのと同じ
Because you look the same way at your friends
明け方に消えてく　小さな願い星
The tiny wishing stars disappear into the dawn
夜の間だけの魔法
Our magic only lasts until daybreak
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
Next week: Truths of the Historic Classic Literature Club.
Truths of the Historic Classic Literature Club