Summer vacation will be over soon, huh?
Yeah.
Then school will start, huh? I can't wait!
You can't wait?
Because then we can see everyone from class.
Everyone from class...
Torun!
Darn it, Yutaka!
Jeez, I lost again.
Say, Run-chan...
You always have guys around you. Why is that?
Really? I don't think that's true, but...
I wonder why.
No one's c-confessed to you?
Confessed? Come to think of it, not long ago...
Huh? It happened?!
Mr. Sato did.
Huh?
He said, "That's what I like" and gave me this.
Strange for someone to like candles, isn't it?
I don't think that means he likes candles.
Huh?
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
SUMMER FESTIVAL
Hey, look at this!
SUMMER
FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
Wanna all go together?
What is it?
Oh. They do this every year, don't they?
The fireworks festival.
They do?
There are lots of food stalls, so it's very busy.
Huh, it's this weekend.
It's the end of summer vacation, too.
I'd like to go to a festival with you all!
Right?
We can all wear summer kimonos.
Let's do it!
Yeah.
Well, why not?
Okay, it's settled!
So, what are we gonna do next?
I hadn't thought about it.
It's hot, so I don't want to move.
Oh! Wanna all go do karaoke?
Karaoke, huh?
Karaoke? Nice. I love it!
Yuko, you like karaoke?
Yeah. I can sing most of what
I've had as ringtones.
Which ones do you like, Run?
Well... That place's jambalaya is undefeated!
Their ramen is an ambush-in-waiting, too!
Oh, and their parfaits and
ice creams are big sizes!
Huh? Aren't we going to karaoke?
Yup! Karaoke.
KARAOKE
A little cramped, isn't it?
Well, I'm gonna order the food and drinks.
What are you all getting?
I'll have a melon soda.
Grapefruit juice.
Toru, what do you want to drink?
Um, an iced tea.
With pleasure!
Ah, hello? I'd like to place an order.
They already have this month's new songs.
Two iced teas, a melon soda
I'll put the top one in.
and grapefruit juice.
Also, a jambalaya and some fries, please.
Okay. Yes. Yes, please.
All right, here goes!
Take me summer, please
Saratte, take me summer, please
Carry me off, take me summer, please
Watashi no koi wa
My love
Kaze kanjiteru
Feels the breeze
Touch me summer, please
Yasashiku, touch me summer, please
Gently, touch me summer, please
Hitonatsu no yume
The dream of one summer
Anata to takeoff
Takeoff with you
Yuko's great!
Anata to takeoff
Takeoff with you
She really is good, huh?
Anata to takeoff
Takeoff with you
Take me summer, please
Thank you.
Gotta put in the next one.
Toru looks pretty serious.
Does she want something in particular?
Um, take your time to choose, Toru.
Why you glarin' at me like that?
Ochamelodical Beauty Bang Bang
(Prelude)
Okay, I'm up next!
Kenage na mezamashi, nidome no gravity
A brave awakening, a second gravity
Naku naku mofu mofu nukedasu hibi
Cry cry, fluffy-wuffy, days that get away
Shushu no kodawari, ronsou suru best friend
Particular about scrunchies
A best friend who argues over them
Saigo no hitokuchi, suki ari desu
The last bite, there's your chance
Minna ni hiromeyou, bakuzen to shita mahou
Let's spread this to everyone, this obscure magic
Hayarisou na kotoba ni hasande
Gripped by words that look like they'll be popular
Ochamelodical beauty banban, sou, egao de
Ochamelodical beauty bang bang, yes, with a smile
Okuru mail ga rin ni natte, birthday no surprise
E-mails sent will form a circle, a birthday surprise
Toru, you done staring angrily at the songbook?
Okuru mail ga rin ni natte, birthday no surprise
E-mails sent will form a circle, a birthday surprise
Spider Nest Paradise
Cloud Letter
With the Flow of the Clouds
Beyond the Clouds
Where the Clouds Are - CLOUDS
Okuru mail ga rin ni natte, birthday no surprise
E-mails sent will form a circle, a birthday surprise
Spider Nest Paradise
Cloud Letter
With the Flow of the Clouds
Beyond the Clouds
Where the Clouds Are - CLOUDS
Okuru mail ga rin ni natte, birthday no surprise
Spider Nest Paradise
Cloud Letter
With the Flow of the Clouds
Beyond the Clouds
Where the Clouds Are - CLOUDS
Automelodic ni chakka bonbon, kagayakasete
Spider Nest Paradise
Cloud Letter
With the Flow of the Clouds
Beyond the Clouds
Where the Clouds Are - CLOUDS
Automelodic ni chakka bonbon, kagayakasete
Ignite it automelodically, poof poof, make it sparkle
I'm putting it in.
Automelodic ni chakka bonbon, kagayakasete
Ignite it automelodically, poof poof, make it sparkle
Okay, it's sent.
Automelodic ni chakka bonbon, kagayakasete
Ignite it automelodically, poof poof, make it sparkle
Appli-chic na uranai de wake it wake it, mirai
With an app-like fortune-telling, wake it wake it, the future
Good job!
It's started.
Do your best, Toru!
Um, well...
The mic, the mic!
What's the matter, Toru?
Beyond the Clouds
(Prelude)
Sorry for the wait!
The jambalaya's here!
This is hot, so please be careful.
I've got the grapefruit juice.
Nagi, here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And I've got the melon soda.
Here!
Thanks.
Song
Canceled
Thanks.
Song
Canceled
Huh?
Song
Canceled
She didn't wanna sing it.
Sorry for putting it in there like that...
Yoiyami ni kasureteku
In the twilight, cracks open
Inaka musume no junjou sa
In the purity of that girl from the country
Kanawanai
It won't come true
Koi de ii
Love alone is enough
Semete mou ichido
At least, once more
Aitai yo
I want to see you
You're takin' it seriously, huh?
Two more songs.
TOTAL CALORIES YOU CONSUMED:
If I sing two more songs,
I can eat eight French fries!
It's for your diet, huh?
Just eat and don't worry about it.
Hey, Toru. You like that song, don't you?
Friend... And Life
Friend
More Than Friends, Less Than Lovers
Friend... And Life
Friend
More Than Friends, Less Than Lovers
Look, this one.
Right?
But I've never sung it. I probably can't.
It's all right!
Toru, the switch isn't on.
I'll go first, okay?
Run-chan...
Te to te tsunaide ne
Hold hands, okay?
Ooki na oka no mukou
Beyond that great hill
Hitotsu, futatsu, mittsu
One, two, three
Tanoshii koto aru yo, motto
There are other, more fun things
Masshiro blanket
A solid white blanket
Ooki na me no puppet
A puppet with big eyes
Mizutama no skirt
A polka-dotted skirt
Hanbunko dekinai keredo
We can't split it in half, but...
Korondemo nakisoudemo
Even if I fall, even if I seem about to cry
Minna to issho
I'm with everyone else
Dokidoki ga fukurandara
if this beating in my heart swells greater
Kitto shiawase
It's sure to be happiness
Te to te tsunaide ne, massugu aruitekou
Hold hands, okay? Let's walk straight ahead
Hitotsu, futatsu, mittsu
One, two, three
Tanoshii koto aru yo, motto
There are other, more fun things
Three left.
Oh, that wasn't very nice.
So, no one's put a song in?
Oh, I'll put one in.
Do it AFTER you're done eating.
Okay, what to do for the next song?
Tada shinjitai
I just want to believe
Next door, huh?
But it was empty.
Maybe they just came.
Ima, kimi no te...
Right now, your hand...
Wow. Whoever's next door is good, huh?
Still, this song is kinda stifling, huh?
Oh, it's started.
Run-chan! You mustn't sing.
Huh? Why?
Just because.
Huh?
Toru!
Shh!
Mitsukedashita kotae mou sugu
Soon enough, you should realize
Could it be?
Mitsukedashita kotae mou sugu
Soon enough, you should realize
That voice...
Mitsukedashita kotae mou sugu
Soon enough, you should realize
Wakaru hazu sa
The answer I discovered
What?
What, what?
Sure would love to do karaoke with Run-chan...
Okay, come on!
One more time!
Yurete, yurete, yurete
Waver, waver, waver
Mujaki na sono hitomi
Those eyes, so innocent...
Karaoke was fun, huh?
Let's go again, okay?
I want to get good at singing.
Oh, that's right! They showed how go be
a good singer on TV the other day.
It's been a while since I've worn
a summer kimono to a festival.
It's gonna be fun, huh?
I have a few different kimonos.
Which one do you want?
This is nice, this chic-looking color.
It looks grown-up.
Which one?
Did I even have one this color?
This has gotten moldy and the color's changed.
These just won't do, huh?
Maybe my old ones will be your size.
I'll go get them.
Grown up-looking mule sandals...
Maybe they're Run's mother's.
With those, I might get up to a
hundred and centimeters.
At this rate, I'll never be a grownup!
Mom!
Oh, my!
Look. We got dressed up! What do you think?
Today's the festival, isn't it?
You're so cute and vibrant!
They look wonderful, on both of you.
Yaay!
Thank you very much.
But the festival's not till tonight, right?
It's still 10:00 am.
We got too carried away!
There they are!
Oh.
Sorry for the wait.
Okay, we're all here.
Yuko-chan, you really are cute
no matter what you wear, huh?
No...
And Nagi, you're... Oh, you curled your hair!
You're right.
Oh, she did.
It's cute!
Um, well... Sometimes, you know...
Uh, there's still time before the fireworks,
so let's kill time by checking out the stalls.
Can we go to the mask stall first?
Oh, yeah.
Huh. You like kids' anime, do you?
No.
I get handed lots of samples at the stalls
in the shopping arcade. Not good.
Oh...
A candy apple!
Candy apple...
Yuko-chan, can I have a bite?
Sure. Here!
It's delicious!
Huh? Toru, you want some?
Not really.
Oh?
Run, lemme have some of your cotton candy.
Sure!
Delicious!
Huh?
HUH?!
Yuko-chan and Nagi are doing the ring toss.
Ah! I got third place!
7th
Place
3rd
5th
Place
Ah! I got third place!
7th
Place
3rd
5th
Place
Congratulations.
Here. It's a fireworks set.
We came to see fireworks,
but your prize is fireworks...
All right! I'M up next!
I'm aiming for first place. Hyaa!
Huh?
I've already spent this much money?
These stalls are expensive, huh?
You gotta be careful with your money.
Worst case, you get to where
you can't buy anything else.
But when you see something, you want it, huh?
In that case, just have a plan, and buy things
you can enjoy for a long time.
Cookie cutting?
Nagi! Why don't we do somethin'
we can all enjoy together?
You've never done cookie cutting,
have you? It's fun...
Wanna give it a shot?
It will be my first time.
Then let's try an easy-looking one.
Skrch Skrch Skrch Skrch
Ah!
It broke!
Sir, one more.
Sure thing.
Skrch Skrch Skrch Skrch
This is pretty hard, isn't it?
Come on, hurry.
I harn't ertn yakisba y't!
Ladies and gentlemen, the fireworks
demonstration will soon begin.
The fireworks already started?!
Everyone, let's hurry!
So many people...
I know a good place.
Let's run to higher ground.
There's a spot up there!
Nagi! Never mind the cookie cutting!
My gourd!
It's right up these stairs!
Suddenly, I don't really care about fireworks.
Nagi, let's go.
I'm done for!
Keep pushing, Nagi-chan!
Let's make it!
We're here!
A bunch at once!
I-incredible...
Ladies and gentlemen, this concludes
the fireworks demonstration.
When leaving, please take all trash with you,
or dispose of it in the designated trash areas.
What?
When leaving, please take all trash with you,
or dispose of it in the designated trash areas.
It's... over.
No...
Just getting that at the end wasn't quite enough.
It's kinda sad, huh?
Oh.
That's right! We got fireworks
from that stall earlier!
Yes! Great job, Yuko!
But we have no lighter.
No problem!
Matches?
A candle?
You brought those?
How come this only has sparklers in it?!
Pretty plain, huh?
But, you know, I like sparklers.
I guess.
Yeah. They're pretty.
Delicious, isn't it?
You're eating too much.
M-Mr. Sato! Why?
Well, why not?
Please don't come near me!
That's MY line.
By the way, you came to the festival alone?
I'm not alone!
Another beer, please.
But you ARE alone.
I'm telling you, I'm not!
Again with this...
Summer vacation was fun, huh?
I guess so.
And we went to the beach.
Let's watch the fireworks next year, too.
Yeah.
Next time, I WILL win at cookie-cutting!
That again?
What's with you? It was fun, right?
Yeah! It was better than I thought. Right, Toru?
Yeah.
It was fun.
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!!
When you think of the
end of August, you think of...
Cicadas!
Typhoons!
Summer homework.
My dad making craftworks for me!
Taking photos at the houses
of kids who've finished!
Taking an obviously fake photo...
Writing your journal in a hurry,
not remembering what the weather was like.
Seeing old newspapers being
collected right in front of you.
I'd like to see an episode
like that on this show, Mr. bb!
Note: Reference to the show's original creator: "bb".
I'd like to see an episode
like that on this show, Mr. bb!
Note: Reference to the show's original creator: "bb".
Next
Episode!
Next time, on A-Channel: "The New Semester"
Next
Episode!
Next time, on A-Channel: "The New Semester"
Next
Episode!
Wait, it's not like we're
elementary-school students.