What?
99th Seisho Festival
Day of the Performance
Let us go,
to pluck that Star together!
No matter how many arrows I let fly, none of them can reach that Star.
You two who blithely make that same Star your aim—
how could you comprehend my rage?!
I had it within me to take that Star in my grasp.
So I believed.
But that conviction was naught but arrogance!
In the face of an unsurmountable obstacle, 'tis better to run!
Yes! Evasion was the only path left to me!
But I remain frozen in place,
bound by regret and lamentation!
This jealousy, my own hideous jealousy.
O, tell me!
What must I sacrifice for my beloved to be mine?
Alas, the wheel turns once again.
The cycle of despair shall repeat
beneath that Star's light...
Their dream could never come true.
Dazzling!
99th Seisho Festival
2 Days Later
First Year
Joint Cast Party
We're here to celebrate the 99th Seisho Festival and the 99th cohort's first performance of Starlight!
A toast to our production's great success! Cheers!
Cheers!
You were great out there, Junna-chan.
Nana...
This was just our first performance. We've got next year's to prepare for now!
I think you might be getting ahead of yourself.
We really did it, right Karen-chan?
You were great yourself, Nana!
Mahiru-chan, were you nervous?
Nope! I was just fine once Karen-chan helped me calm down!
It's our two leading ladies!
You really brought the house down!
Thank you very much.
I haven't lost, you know.
In that case, we'll have to give next year's auditions our all.
Together.
Daiba Nana-san.
You as well.
Maya-chan?
Man, I seriously thought I wasn't cut out for that Goddess role,
but I pulled it off somehow!
"Pulled it off somehow"?
You sell yourself short, dear Futaba-han!
Nana!
Futaba-chan?
You were such a huge help! Thanks!
I really must thank you as well for all your assistance, Nana-han.
You give the most divine backrubs!
You practiced with me, too!
And you helped with the costumes!
And painting the set!
Plus, you brought us homemade snacks whenever we were hungry.
Nana, it's thanks to your banana muffins that we got through the final crunch!
Hey, that's it!
Banana!
Nana is like a banana to all of us!
Sweet, mellow, and chock full of nutrition!
And effective on stiff shoulders to boot!
Nana is... Banana?
Oh, how cute!
I say, that's quite right! She's very tall,
and rather bananesque!
And she smells great!
Banana, huh?
Nana?!
Was it what I said?
Nana-han?
That's not it. I'm really happy!
I'm so glad I'm here.
I didn't know that creating the stage with everyone
would be so much fun, or make me so happy, or create such radiance.
I'll never forget this performance. The 99th Seisho Festival's Starlight!
The eternal friends I made here and the fated stage we shared.
This was the day of my birth.
As Daiba Nana, Girl of the Stage.
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Who shall be the one to grasp hold of that Star?
To stand at the peak of that tower?
A quietly kindled flame now blazes and consumes my heart
Whatever fate might bring
We dance on this stage of our own will
to
bi
ta
te
And we take flight!
I AM REBORN
I'm certain of what I saw on that day
The sparkle of those scattering stars
Shine on me until my fingers touch yours
From across a promise faded by time
The true story begins before the curtain rises
And it unfolds before our very eyes
It's here, in the place where I was reborn
That I found you once more
hiding the french shit
Seisho Music Academy
First Day of Spring Vacation
Yes. I'll be landing tomorrow at 3.
Oui. J'atterris a 15 heures demain.
Bye-bye, Banana!
Look forward to your souvenirs!
Let us make haste, Futaba-han!
Carry your own bag, then!
Okay then!
We're off!
It's so quiet here with everyone gone.
The only ones left are me and Junna-chan!
Oh come on, do you really need another picture of me?
The next Seisho Festival is the 100th.
It's an important milestone!
I'm not letting any of it slip by undocumented!
Are you really okay with not going home?
Hm?
I decided that I wasn't going back until I graduated.
If you're only staying for my benefit—
Junna-chan, would you like some udon?
Hm?
I wanted to stay here.
I'd love some.
Seisho Music Academy
New Semester
It's the first day of our second year!
Okay, Junna-chan, say something encouraging!
Hold on!
I must present myself properly, as befitting of a senior student and class representative!
Those look brand-new,
even though they're exactly the same!
Oh, new first-years.
Look at them, all tense from nerves.
They're also brand-new.
Actor Training Department
Here we are in our second-year classroom!
We look forward to spending the next year here!
Spring vacation is over and everyone's back together again.
Hm?
Naruse-san and Osaka-san aren't here yet.
They dropped out.
Naruse  Ayahi
To think that this would be my first task as second-year class rep.
Okay.
If we're going to create an even greater stage, we've got to move on.
Yeah...
100th Seisho Festival
Start of Auditions
Actor Instruction Classroom
The 100th Seisho Festival,
and our second performance of Starlight!
Today is the day of the long-awaited auditions for the principal cast!
This time around it will be a decisive victory for me.
Tendo Maya, you're going down!
The role of Flora will be mine!
Then I'll be Claire!
It's only natural that the next starring role should go to me!
Geez, you're heavy...
Daiba-san.
After this, might I speak to you for a moment?
Sure.
It's time for auditions already, huh?
It hardly feels real.
I can still see it so clearly whenever I close my eyes.
Our Starlight!
The ultimate stage, for us alone, that we all created together!
Can't we do it all over again?
That same stage?
Even if the players and casting were to remain the same,
the same stage could not be recreated.
That's true, but...
Those girls made up their minds.
Surely they experienced anguish, despair, and rage fiercer than we can comprehend.
I recall saying this—
that with the lead roles on the line,
we must give next year's auditions our all.
Opponents that, despite everything,
could not be overcome.
Dreams that could not be realized even with the last of their strength—
They left all of that, and the stage, behind them.
An ideal physique.
A resplendent voice.
A broad outlook that considers the entire stage.
With all of that, why are you—
Make up your mind already!
Do wait just a bit longer.
If you're witholding your true potential just to remain everyone's beloved Banana-san,
I will...
Daiba Nana, I will never forgive you.
Maya-chan...
Nana?
Junna-chan.
Ooh! Are those pictures of the cast party?
Yeah. Wanna see?
Why, it's Miss Class President!
Nice shot!
Hey! Did you really have to take that one?
Oh!
That was only two months ago,
but somehow I already feel nostalgic for it.
The Seisho Festival, and our Starlight—
I love them.
So do I.
Yeah, me too!
With Group B backing us up,
Group A got to sing and perform.
The 99th cohort created a stage
that was all our own.
I wonder if we can ever recreate that same stage again.
I don't think I could stand on that stage again.
Eh?
The stage is a living entity.
Even if we perform Starlight again,
the stage will never be exactly the same.
Some of us aren't here any more, either.
Right!
So that's why we've got to practice more and more,
and create an even greater stage!
Karen-chan?
Hey! Don't stand on the benches, Aijo-san!
This is a stage! My stage!
See? I took my shoes off!
That's not the issue here!
You sure like high places, Aijo-san.
Yep! I do!
Like Tokyo Tower!
An even greater stage.
Even greater possibilities.
But to me, that Starlight was
my greatest and my most beloved...
Oh.
A giraffe...
It's so cute.
Good evening, Daiba Nana-san.
Do you find it dazzling?
Huh?
I understand.
A real giraffe?
A Revue.
Song and dance interwoven on the mesmerizing stage.
As a Girl of the Stage shines with greater and greater radiance,
the light, the sound, and all the machinery of the stage will begin to move in turn.
The stage responds to her acting, singing, and dancing,
and moves in accordance with her radiance.
Radiance?
The one who presents us
with the most radiant Revue
shall find open to her the path to the Top Star.
Top Star...
The one who stands upon the fated stage,
who lets forth unending radiance,
who brings all her abilities to full bloom,
who shines across time itself—an eternal leading lady!
I'm not interested.
I understand.
Yet,
with the wish you hold, it will not matter which stage you stand upon.
It won't matter...?
It exists for you as well, does it not?
A dazzling stage.
However deep your yearning, you can never again reach it.
It overflows with radiance, that dazzling stage.
Does it dazzle you?
I understand.
Is it true?
Can it be any stage?
Any stage? From any time?
Will you participate in the auditions?
I understand.
So this is your true potential?
What was it that changed you?
Is it dazzling?
Huh?
It's dazzling to me.
What was it—
I can't reach it.
that made you go this far—
Position Zero.
Unreachable,
and dazzling.
Congratulations.
Do you find it dazzling?
It's dazzling.
The one to successfully pass the auditions is you, Daiba Nana-san.
Now that you have become the Top Star,
upon what fated stage do you wish to stand?
The 99th Seisho Festival.
A repeat performance of Starlight.
Radiance like a gemstone's fire.
A multitude of happy days like a sparkling rainbow.
That dazzling thing, once more...
Even now, that stage.
Very well.
The work we've chosen for the 99th cohort's performance
is Starlight.
I love Starlight!
Me too!
Ah, Lumière d'étoile, is it? Sounds good.
Starlight?
Why is everyone acting like this is the first time they've heard we're doing Starlight?
Junna-chan?
What?!
Y-You caught me off guard using my first name like that,
Daiba-san.
Actor Training Department
Huh?
Seisho Music Academy
Leadup: First Year
Daiba Nana
The Fated Stage
And so, the repeat performance began.
The 99th Seisho Festival.
Our precious friends,
our precious stage,
the precious days we spent together, repeated.
In my repeat performance, there is nothing to fear.
We never have to grow up, never become adults.
Never feel the anguish of pushing ourselves, the hardship of challenging new things,
nor the sadness and pain of giving up...
I'll protect everyone from all of it.
Hey, that's it!
Banana!
Nana is like a banana to all of us!
Sweet, mellow, chock full of nutrition, and effective on stiff shoulders to boot?
Y-Yeah...
Yeah, yeah!
What can I do to recreate that exact same stage?
While I thought of that...
I should have already made it there,
but it's still too dazzling...
Congratulations.
The one to successfully pass the auditions is you, Daiba Nana-san.
Now then, Nana-san. You have become the Top Star.
What sort of stage do you wish for?
It's still dazzling.
I do not know how many times around this makes,
but very well.
Why?
Why do you do this for me?
The moment a Girl of the Stage becomes the Top Star,
that miracle and that radiance produce a chemical reaction.
An eternal sparkling, a momentary combustion,
and at last, a fated stage that defies all estimation.
I wish to see it.
A fated stage that defies all estimation...
The work we've chosen for the 99th cohort's performance
is Starlight.
Who was she?
Huh?
You okay, Karen-chan?
I just can't stop thinking about sandwiches.
K-Karen-chan!
Are you okay, Karen-chan?
She's fine. The girl's a rock!
You're so heartless, Banana-chan!
Hey, you all right, Karen?
So we have a transfer student who'll be joining us here in the Actor Training Department.
I know it's unexpected, but please give her a warm welcome, everyone.
Huh?
This has never happened before.
Who is she?
Kagura
Hikari
I made an exemplary effort in dancing today!
Let me onto the motorcycle!
No can do. Walking home is good training for our legs!
Slack off and the taxi fare'll be 5 million yen!
I folded my T-shirts and towels.
But—
What's going on here?
I wonder if it's getting boring
repeating the same stage again and again.
A fated stage that defies all estimation.
But no matter who shows up,
my repeat performance will never change.
Kagura Hikari-chan.
Why, I think I want her for my stage too!
Where Her Light Shines
Shoujo Kageki
Revue Starlight!
I understand.