Why are my memories...
I really didn't want to die!
Why is it?
Why am I feeling these things?
What exactly did I do
when I was alive?!
Takuto?
What's the matter, Takuto?
Shut up!
Please leave me alone!
Takuto!
Izumi, will you hear me out?
I never thought it
would be so painful
to keep that girl alive for
the duration of her life span.
But Takuto doesn't understand
how I feel at all.
Well, it's our job to
adhere to the schedule,
but do you want me to
fix that problem for you?
What do you mean?
I would reap that girl's life
in your place.
What?
You're awake, Mikki?
Long time no see.
What's the matter?
Did you forget my name?
Poor Mikki.
No one can save you now.
I'll take you to the world where
your parents and Eichi are.
Eichi...
That's right.
Don't you want to see him?
Come, follow me.
What has happened to me?
That's my memory from
when I was alive.
Why, all of a sudden?
I just wanted her to sing one more time.
That's all I wanted.
Takuto?
I like your singing, Takuto.
Hey Takuto,
what kind of songs did you sing?
It's happening again!
Why does this happen
when I think about singing?
Why... Why is this happening?
My...throat?
We'll have to resort to surgery.
No, he won't be able to sing again.
I remember... I used to sing.
But a tumor formed in my lungs.
And I sped off on my motorcycle
out of despair. And I died.
Damn it!
I can't believe I died.
I... I...
That was great, wasn't it?
Yeah.
They sure know how to perform.
We've gotta work hard to catch up!
I used to sing.
By myself?
Or in a group?
Takuto!
Takuto.
Wakaoji...
No way!
The world where Eichi
and my parents are.
Where is that?
Tonight is the new moon,
but the moon is there even though
you might not be able to see it.
Didn't Eichi teach you that?
And that Eichi, your mom,
and your dad...
All the people that you want
to see are in the moon.
In the moon?
Not only them.
There are also animals
in the moon too.
Like the mochi-making
rabbit and cats too.
There's an African mythology
that goes like this.
Long ago, God tried to bestow
eternal life to humans
and sent a rabbit
as a messenger.
But the rabbit opposed the idea, saying,
"Humans are supposed to die."
So God got mad and locked
the rabbit in the moon.
Rabbits have always been a little dumb.
I guess that's what makes them cute.
Don't you agree?
Now...
That's a good girl.
I depended on Izumi
without thinking.
But right now, Izumi might be
doing what he said he'd do.
Maybe I shouldn't have run away
just because it was so tough.
The one who's suffering
the most is her.
Eichi died two years ago.
Huh?
My son and daughter-in-law
adopted Eichi,
but all three of them died
in an automobile accident.
He...died?
But I just couldn't watch her
like that anymore.
But it would be cruel to force her
to continue living in this state.
This is the first time I've had to deal with...
such an exhausting case.
That's not true!
Even if her life is short,
making her feel that it was worth living
is part of our job too, right?!
What was I supposed to do?
I'm so lonely without you, Meroko.
Without you, Meroko, it's like
there's something missing...
like something's different.
We have to be together.
If the three of us aren't together
like we used to be, it'll be sad.
So let's go home together!
Here you go.
It's cute!
You and Takuto are
my precious friends.
I love you so much, Meroko!
Mitsuki...
Mitsuki!
Maybe I'll tell you another story
about the moon.
Do you know why the moon
waxes and wanes?
The other gods were jealous
of the moon goddess's beauty.
Fearing that people's hearts would never
turn to them if the moon were always full,
they made an agreement.
They promised her eternal beauty
if she would go away every so often.
So the moon also
symbolizes eternity.
Everybody's existence
is eternal in the moon.
Welcome to the world
of the eternal moon.
Takuto.
Wakaoji... No, Keichi,
I finally remember you.
You, me,
and Mitsuki's father Aoi.
I remember the days when
we used to play together.
Route L... The place
where I started singing...
And the place that took me in
when I had no relatives.
That feeling that I felt back then...
It was because I was able to see
what was important to me again.
I'm regretting the fact
that I died!
I should have lived,
more strongly!
Mitsuki...
I don't care if I become a ghost!
I won't allow her to have the same
kind of regrets that I have!
Now, come.
Mikki!
Look down below.
Eichi?
And your dad and mom.
My dad and mom...
I told you, the moon is there
even if you don't see it in the sky.
And that's the entrance
to the world of the moon.
Mitsuki, I missed you!
Mitsuki, I have so much to tell you.
Hurry over here.
Mitsuki, you've grown so much.
Come and show me your face!
Dad, mom, Eichi...
I missed you.
I wanted to see you so badly.
Dad?
Mom?
Mitsuki, goodbye.
No.
No, Eichi.
Don't leave.
Now, Mikki, let's go together to
the world of the eternal moon.
Mitsuki!
Who?
Getting in the way...
Get off of there now!
It's dangerous! Now!
Don't think of killing yourself!
Kill myself?
But I'm just going to go see
Eichi and my dad and mom.
Where?
Please, Mitsuki!
Please just come over here!
If I let you die, Hazuki and your father
will never forgive me!
No!
I-I don't want you to die!
I don't want anybody
to die anymore.
Please, just come back!
Mitsuki!
Grandma?
In that case,
I guess I'll have to be a little rough.
That's right. It's Grandma.
So please get over here right away.
Grandma?
Grandma...
Mitsuki, come on!
Grandma!
No!
It's useless. It's too late.
Grandma! Grandma!
Grandma!
What's too late?
Takuto!
Grandma!
Don't worry.
She just fainted.
Izumi, you little...
I'm not going to forgive you this time!
Don't get so mad.
It's not entirely my fault this time.
What?!
He's right. It's my fault.
This all started because
I depended on Izumi.
I told you.
But...
I was wrong! Even if we are Death Spirits,
we can't do things like this!
Mitsuki, you had to go through such
a scary experience because of me.
I'm sorry!
Mitsuki...
Oh boy, now I'm the bad guy.
I was just trying to take
her soul for you Meroko.
This is why I shouldn't butt
into people's business.
Izumi...
More importantly, you remember
all of it now, right, Takuto?
Or should I call you
Takuto Kira of Route L?
Y-You! How did you know that?!
I'd love to hear you sing
one of these days
before you become a ghost.
Takuto, do you remember
your past now?
Route L?
Dad and Dr. Wakaoji's band?
I remember. When I was a human,
I was in Route L.
Takuto, your memories
have returned?
No! You have to forget them right away!
Or else something bad will happen!
It's fine.
If the return of my memories
causes her to want sing again,
I want to remember everything.
Takuto, no! Takuto!
Next time on Full Moon:
"New Moon Night."
- Look forward to it!