Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
Yay! I won, I won!
24-HOUR COIN LAUNDROMAT
The amount of money I spend
at the cleaners is murder on my budget.
It would be nice to have
enough time to do my own laundry.
At least we get to go home
every once in a while.
TRAIN ARRIVING
THE NIHON KEIZAI SHIMBUN
Oh, hello, Deputy Commander.
Good morning.
Good morning, sir!
Coming in early today, sir?
I was topside on Ikari's behalf.
Oh, today was the regular session
of the council, wasn't it?
Pointless busy work...
Ikari has always dumped
the meaningless drivel in my lap.
If it weren't for the Magi,
I don't know what we would do.
That reminds me, the city council
election is coming up, isn't it?
The city council is a charade.
All city administration is effectively
in the hands of the Magi.
The Magi?
The three supercomputers do that, sir?
Majority rule via three
interlinked computer systems.
It's a system that's in precise
accordance with democratic principles.
So the city assembly
just rubber stamps their decisions?
It's the most efficient,
least wasteful form of governance.
A true city of science.
We're in an age when science
can solve all our problems!
Wow, what a cliché...
Right, you have Unit 00's
trials today, don't you?
Yes, sir. Starting at 1030 hours,
we'll be conducting stage two
active time extension tests.
Here's hoping for good news.
Abort test. Cut all circuits.
-Switch over all circuits!
-Power coming back online.
-That's definitely where the problem is.
-Yes, ma'am.
The conversion efficiency is 0.008
below theoretical values somehow.
It's barely enough to register on
our instruments. What do we do?
Lower the interconversion value by 0.01
and try it again with the same settings.
Roger.
All right, let's start
the reactivation test.
Hey! Hold that elevator!
Damn.
Wow, I really had to book it!
Someone woke up on the wrong side
of the bed today.
Because I saw your ugly mug
first thing in the morning.
One moment, please.
What is it?
-Uh... Father...
-What? Out with it.
Uh... The thing is...
They told us at school today
to tell our parents...
that our future plans meetings
are coming up.
I put Katsuragi in charge of all that.
Don't waste my time with this nonsense.
Don't put through calls from--
-Huh?
-A power outage?
No, that's impossible.
That's strange.
Was there some kind of accident?
Maybe Akagi botched another experiment.
Main power feed has stopped!
Voltage is zero!
I-It wasn't me.
What do you think happened?
Whatever happened,
the backups will kick in soon.
No go! Backup circuits not coming online!
Impossible! How many circuits
are still working?
Just 1.2% in all, sir! Only the old
circuits past no. 2567 are operating!
Route all available power towards
maintaining the Magi and Central Dogma!
That will disrupt life support
throughout the complex, sir.
Do it! Give it top priority!
PUSH-BUTTON TRAFFIC LIGHT
Man, I can't believe how big
a slacker Ms. Katsuragi is.
She should at least go pick up
her own laundry.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR VOTE!
Huh?
Maybe Commander Ikari
was just really busy.
I don't know. It seemed more like
a malfunction than him hanging up.
Sheesh, grow a pair.
Stop worrying about every little thing.
Huh?
What are you doing? Come on, let me do it!
Damn it, this stupid thing must be broken!
Let's hurry to the command center.
The power's been out for seven minutes!
-Something major is going on.
-What's your power setup here?
Triple-redundant:
Main, auxiliary, and backup.
It's inconceivable for all three
to fail at the same time.
Which means...
We should assume that the breaker
didn't trip, but was rather thrown.
Whatever the cause, if an Angel
attacks now, we're in trouble.
Tracking radar has picked up
an unidentified object!
Estimated point of landfall
is the former Atami region!
It must be the eighth one.
-Yes, it's probably an Angel.
-What should we do?
Raise the alert status of all forces.
That's the protocol.
That thing is probably
going after Tokyo-3 again.
You're probably right. Well,
there's nothing that we can do about it.
-Angel has made landfall!
-Continuing inland!
Anything from Tokyo-3?
Still nothing, sir.
What the hell is Nerv up to?
I thought this gangway ladder
was just a retro decoration.
I never imagined
we'd actually have to use it.
As they say, "To prepare is to prevent."
This one isn't working, either.
None of the equipment is. This is strange.
Does that mean something
happened down below?
That would be the natural assumption.
Let's try to call Nerv HQ, then.
It's no use.
Even the emergency line is dead.
No go, sir. Even line 77
isn't getting through.
No luck. I can't get through.
Me, neither. Even the emergency
hardwired line is down.
What should we do?
What are you doing?
Are you an idiot? I'm looking
for my emergency manual!
Let's try to get to HQ.
Agreed. So let's settle on
a group leader before we set out.
I'm the natural choice for leader.
There are no objections?
Right, let's go!
We can go down through
Route No. 7 over here.
But if the doors aren't working, how...
A manual release...
Okay, Shinji! Time to do your thing.
You only turn to me for help
at times like this!
The Joint Chief Council only turns
to field commanders at times like this!
What's the government saying?
The civilians in Tokyo-2?
Packing their bags, from what I hear.
PREVENT MOUNTAIN FIRES
Angel is still active and advancing!
In any case, we need to
get in touch with Nerv.
But how?
We go in person.
This is the Third District
Air Defense Force.
An unknown object is currently
approaching this location.
All residents, proceed to
your designated shelters.
Oh, crap!
I have to let HQ know about this!
But how?!
Vote Takahashi, the candidate who
keeps his cool even in emergencies!
Vote Nozoku Takahashi for city assembly!
What a lucky break!
Boy, it's getting hot in here.
Yeah, the ventilation is shut down.
Katsuragi, if the heat's getting to you,
just take off your shirt.
It's nothing I haven't seen before.
I don't care what kind of mess we're in,
don't get any funny ideas.
Fine...
This is bad. The air is getting stale.
This is a facility that's pushed the
boundaries of modern science, but now--
Look at the Commander
and Deputy Commander, though.
This heat isn't getting to them at all.
-This water is lukewarm.
-Yes.
Due to the special state of emergency
declared in this district,
please make way for
this emergency vehicle!
-Um, this is a dead end!
-Just blow through it!
-Like you said, this is an emergency!
-Roger that!
Enough! Please stop!
This Geo-front was designed to be
a colony capable of sustaining itself
even if completely cut off
from the outside.
It's theoretically impossible for all
of its power systems to go down.
Which means this blackout is deliberate.
Their objective is probably
to study this place.
Infer HQ's structure by observing
how we restore our power?
What annoying troublemakers.
I'll have the Magi run decoy programs.
That should help obscure
the overall picture.
To think that HQ would be compromised
for the first time by humans, not Angels.
It's difficult to swallow.
In the end, man's greatest enemy
is his fellow man.
It usually only takes two minutes.
Is this the right corridor?
Once we reach that light up there,
I'm sure we'll be at the Geo-front.
That's the fourth time you've said that.
You're such a nitpicker, you know that?!
You get hung up on every little detail!
-Be quiet.
-Was that an order, Miss Perfect?!
I hear a voice.
It's Mr. Hyuga!
Hey!
An Angel is coming!
I repeat, an Angel is coming!
An Angel is coming?!
There's no time to waste.
Let's take a shortcut.
Hey, I'm the leader here!
Don't boss me around!
So, where's this shortcut?
I don't care if this is a shortcut,
this is so degrading...
Say, what do you think the Angels are?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Angels. Messengers of God.
Our enemies, bearing divine names.
Why are we fighting each other?
Don't be an idiot!
Those freaky things are attacking us!
When you're attacked,
it's only natural to defend yourself!
The right.
I think it's the one to the left.
Who cares what you think?
How about you, Shinji?
Uh..
I don't know.
Sheesh! I'm the leader here,
so keep your mouth shut and follow me!
I knew this wasn't right.
We're going up, not down.
You knew that, did you?
You nag and nag about everything.
See? This has to be
the right one this time.
We have visual confirmation of the Angel.
Now we know that we have to hurry.
An Angel is currently closing in!
Recommend immediate Eva launch!
This is bad!
Take care of things here, Fuyutsuki.
Ikari?
I'll go to the cage to get the Eva
launch preparations underway.
Hold on... Surely not manually.
There are emergency diesel generators.
Yes, but...
What we don't have right now
are the pilots.
This again...
This way.
So, I hear that you're
Commander Ikari's favorite.
Being his favorite makes you special,
right, Miss Perfect?
Come on, this isn't the time.
That's why you stay calm
and composed all the time.
Hey! Don't look down on me
just because you get special treatment!
I don't look down on you.
Plus, I don't get special treatment.
I would know.
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Roger. Shutdown signal plug
extraction complete.
Very well. Prepare all three
entry plugs for insertion.
But we still don't have any pilots--
Don't worry. Those kids will be here.
This one can't be opened by hand.
We have no choice. Let's break open
a duct and keep going through there.
The First sure is scary.
She's the sort who thinks
the ends justify the means.
A real holier-than-thou type.
-Plug ready and locked in position.
-Now we just need the children.
Keep your eyes down! Straight down!
If you look up, you're a dead man!
Idiot! Jerk! Jerk!
I told you not to look!
Like I have a choice!
How can I move if I don't look?!
There you are!
All units, prepare for entry!
Roger. Open the hatches manually.
How are the Evas?
Ready and standing by.
But nothing is working.
We did it by hand.
It was the Commander's idea.
Father's?
He got them ready because he
had faith that you would come.
Plugs inserted.
All units activated using auxiliary power.
Remove lockdown bolt no. 01.
Releasing hydraulic locks two through 32!
Pressure, zero! They're standing free!
All units, force your way free
of your restraining frames.
Launch immediately!
Target has come to a stop
directly overhead!
Hook them up right away!
Emergency batteries have been attached!
Right, we're good to go! Launch!
Come on, this is so degrading!
We're coming up to the shaft.
This is even more degrading!
This is bad. Take cover.
Ew!
The target's goal must be get into HQ
by using a powerful corrosive agent.
-So what should we do?
-What else? We take it out!
I know, but how?
We dropped our rifles,
and our battery backpacks are drained.
We'll be immobile in three more minutes.
Listen up, I have a plan.
One of us stays here as Defense.
It neutralizes the target's A.T. Field
and protects Offense from its acid.
Support heads down.
It retrieves a rifle,
then passes it up to Offense.
Offense then fires a volley
and destroys the target.
Everybody got that?
Okay. I'll be Defense.
Sorry, but no.
-I'll be Defense.
-You can't! It's too dangerous!
That's exactly why.
It wouldn't feel right if I didn't
repay you for saving my life earlier.
Shinji is Offense.
Miss Perfect, you're Support.
Got it?
Understood.
Okay, let's do this!
Los geht's!
Ayanami!
Asuka! Get clear!
Okay, this makes us even.
Damn! Why won't this stupid thing open?!
This is an emergency!
My bladder's about to explode!
Hey! I told you not to look up!
Yeah, yeah...
Hey! Watch it!
How indecent.
I had no idea the stars
were this pretty without electricity.
Without artificial light.
It's ironic.
Yeah, well, without those lights,
the place look deserted.
See? You feel safer this way.
Man fears the darkness, and so he
scrapes away at the edges of it with fire.
Ooh, how profound!
I wonder if that's what makes
humanity special.
Maybe that's why
the Angels are attacking us.
Don't be an idiot!
How can we know something like that?
TO BE CONTINUED
Misato has made it her mission
to destroy the Angels.
She discusses her past.
But when the largest Angel to date
attacks from the stratosphere,
it makes everyone abandon hope.
Next episode! "A Miracle's Worth".
Watch it with your friends, okay?
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming