The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
My name is Mikado Ryugamine.
Wow, it's really you, Kida?!
A lot of them got arrested after they fought a gang in Saitama.
My name is Anri Sonohara.
Nice to meet you all.
Harima!
Wrong person!
If you swore to yourself to become an upstanding Ikebukuronese,
you must undergo the ordeal!
I found you...
...my love.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
I-I'm sorry!
I apologize!
I'll give it back! I will!
Please, forgive me.
Cry Wine
And Sell
Vinegar
I'm stumped.
Really stumped.
Blame me, Selty.
It's my fault for accepting such a lame offer!
The task itself was supposed to go smoothly.
But then, that thing just happened to pop up.
You're not human.
You're a monster.
Monster.
You heard voices coming from your wound?
They said I was a monster!
That's just rude.
They could have at least called you an enchantress.
What was it?
What if it was an alien?!
Selty...
Is this where I'm supposed to laugh?
A-A monster!!
Let's scram!
I heard this city is made up of jokes, whims, and coincidences.
Saika has entered the chat.
Humans
The strong
Desire
Love
Humans who desire love
Desire Because the strong humans love
Desire because Because because
I
This is why I desire
strong humans
I desire
I, love
That is why
This situation may also be God's whim or His joke.
I fell in love at first sight with thirty-seven girls during the opening ceremony.
I'm leaving school in a soap opera-like twist with one of
those girls in the top five, who happens to wear glasses...
But some dork is getting in my way.
This sucks.
Pretty scary event the other day, don't you think?
Yeah.
This isn't going very well.
I was so surprised back then, man!
Wasn't expecting Mikado to steal a march on me.
It wasn't anything like that!
You're kidding!
Mikado!!
But you saved me in a way.
If I were in your shoes, I wouldn't miss out on a chance like that.
We'd be comfortably talking about love over at West Gate Park by now.
So, please! Go out with me!
Huh?!
Hey-
Kida!
Umm... I-
Whoa! I don't need a reply right away!
I'm currently waiting for a reply from seven girls, and I'm trying to decide which one of them I should go out with.
You don't need to take him seriously, Sonohara.
You'll just get worn out.
And he talks like he's a playboy, but he's not even that impressive.
He tried to pick up some girls the other day, but-
Hey! Come on, Mikado!
This guy, Mikado Ryugamine, is my best friend.
It's only been a few days since he arrived in Ikebukuro.
He's simple, honest, and naive, but he can also be pretty stubborn.
You just can't leave him alone.
And I'm currently in a love triangle with this pure boy.
Is this what they call 'youth'?
Oww...!
Hey! Kida!
Looks like you two are really close.
Yeah, we are!
Although it's more of a fatal tie.
Mercy! Mercy! Mercy!
If I were to explain how this current situation came about,
I'd have to start from the opening ceremony.
I'm Seiji Yagiri. Nice to meet you.
Okay, Yagiri, please have a seat.
No thanks.
I don't think I'll be able to attend school for a while.
Actually, I don't think I'll ever be coming back.
I've got something to take care of that means more than my entire life.
I don't have time for you all.
Well then.
Hey, Yagiri. Wait.
Wait a second...
After hearing that story from Mikado, it made me
realize just how many weirdos there are out there.
Yagiri!
Come back here!
Please, wait!
Yagiri, are you sure something's not bothering you?
And that's when I fell in love!
Her cute smile made my heart do a flip!
I don't know what you're talking about.
B-But skipping school on the first day?
Well okay, she didn't really have a smile on.
I told you, I don't know what you mean!
Wait!
Umm...
Is something wrong?
Anyway, with the girl who immediately made it to the top of my list of girlfriend candidates...
Hey, Sonohara.
You on your way home now?
Yes.
Hey, is something bothering you?
You're not being bullied or being dragged into trouble, are you?
No...
If something happens to you, be sure to tell me right away.
I'm fine.
Yeah?
On a different note, Harima still isn't attending school, huh?
And you two were placed in the same class too.
You know, it took a lot of effort to arrange that.
Mr. Saito from your middle school told me to take good care of you.
So you don't need to be so reserved, okay?
Oh yeah, I'll walk you home today.
You heard about it, right?
There's been another slashing incident in Ikebukuro.
Mr. Nasujima, is this sexual harassment I'm seeing right now?!
You just made the innocent bespectacled class rep moan!
Is this some genuine sexual harassment?!
Or as Simon would put it, "sexy harasho"?
Quit joking around, Kida!
Don't get the wrong idea and start
spreading weird rumors, Sonohara.
Does she really look like someone who'd do something so frivolous?
Yeah, you're right.
You need to stop scaring me.
Besides, I'm the one who's going to spread the rumor. Don't worry!
I was totally someone from the
Justice League for a second there!
Wasn't that really cool of me?
Anyone would fall for me right there.
Kida?
Oh and Sonohara too.
Nice timing, jerk.
Sorry for the wait.
Here.
Thank you.
But yeah, you should seriously watch out.
Most of the rumors you hear about Nasujima are fake,
but it's true that he hooked up with a student.
She's a junior, Haruna Niekawa.
She actually moved to another school
during the second semester of last year.
I heard people almost found out her and Nasujima were dating.
Seriously?!
No one knows whether it was her own decision to switch schools,
if Nasujima threatened her, or if the school made her do it.
Well, if something happens, Mikado and I will do something about it.
Right, Mikado?
Yeah.
I don't really get what's going on,
but as long as it's something I can do, I'll be glad to help.
Idiot.
This is where you say, "Even if it's impossible for me, I'll make it happen with the power of love."
Else you're not a man.
What?
That contradicts itself.
The words come out of the atmosphere.
Anyway, about the other day.
The girls who were bullying you
went to your middle school, right?
H-How did you know that?
Well, it was the only possible solution I could derive from the conversation.
Someone with a lot of influence had your back during middle school,
but now that she's gone, those bullies started coming back.
What was the situation again?
You still can't find your lost friend?
Mika Harima, the girl in our class, right?
Mika hasn't been attending school,
but she also hasn't been home since before the entrance ceremony.
Isn't that something the cops should take care of?
Friends Forever
She contacted me through my cell, and she also let her family know.
The message read, "I'm on a trip to
ease my grief. Don't worry about me."
A trip to ease her grief?
Did something happen?
Well... umm...
Don't be too startled when I tell you, okay?
The events that took place over the past few days have made me immune to astonishment, really.
Harima...
...is a stalker.
Friends Forever
I see.
So it's that guy you were bugging the other day, huh?
So Mika, who was stalking him-
I mean Mika, who wanted his love,
got rejected. And so she went on a trip.
You probably have to leave it to her family then.
If things get really bad, they'll probably tell the police.
Were you good friends with her?
What's with that doubting attitude?
Well, I guess it's true that we were always together.
He's real quick on the uptake when it comes to certain things.
I'm really clumsy, and I'm terrible at interacting with people.
But Mika was always there pulling my hand...
She went out of her way to pick the high school I was planning on going to,
and I just felt so bad about that.
That's probably because...
"That's probably because she didn't want to let go of someone who made a perfect foil to her..."
Mikado, even if that's what you're thinking right now, you just can't say that.
I know.
Know what?
I know that Mika was using me as her foil.
But I was using her as well.
Because it's so much easier to live while depending on someone.
And I thought that was the only way for me to live.
But now, I don't feel like it's really necessary to do that anymore.
I started to get used to her not being here.
The reason I decided to run for classroom representative is because I remember her saying she wanted to do it as well.
I felt the need to do it in her stead.
I felt like I'd be able to surpass her if I became the class rep.
Isn't that foul of me?
I think it's even more foul that you're telling people this.
It's almost like you're asking for forgiveness by doing that.
You made the right choice by deciding to surpass Harima.
So in that case, you should keep your head high about it.
Uhh...
You're absolutely right.
Thank you for your comment.
This is what I like about him.
Kida!
You're so lame!
What's that supposed to mean?!
What? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yep, the strongest.
Writer
Shuji Niekawa
You a magazine writer or something?
What do you mean by "strongest"? That's hilarious.
Well, that would have to be the dude on the black motorcycle, right?
I've heard of that.
No head, right?
No way!
Oh, and there's that slasher guy too.
Oh yeah, that thing.
But the strongest in this city right now would have to be the Dollars, don't you think?
"Dollars"?
Yeah, the Dollars!
Well, my home is this way.
Thanks a lot for today.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Bye, Anri!
This thought crossed my mind...
I can't help but think that Yagiri and Mika are together.
The stalker and the victim?
Well, it could be that Yagiri has been kidnapped by the girl.
I see what you're saying.
Searching for someone, huh...
What should we do?
Just leave it be.
Anri said it was fine too.
I guess we'll need the help of an organization or something?
Like the Dollars.
Hey... don't tell me you're thinking about joining the Dollars?
Huh?
Dude, no way!
Seriously, don't do it.
People join a color gang out of the rashness of their youth,
and most of them regret it afterwards.
Yeah.
But we are still young, you know.
It's a pain...
It's so boring...
What's boring?
Before Mikado came to Ikebukuro, I was seriously depressed.
The reason why I'm so cheerful now...
...is, well, thanks to a lot of people, including Mikado.
He just came to Ikebukuro, so the heated
atmosphere of the city is really getting to him.
He looks so cautious, I can't just leave him be.
I guess I could just splash cold water on him,
but seeing the gleam in his eyes pulls me away from doing so.
Toshima Ward
Ikebukuro West Gate Park
So I at least try to watch over him by always being by his side...
If I could help it, I'd rather not have him go near the darkness of this city.
I also...
Bang!
...swore to myself I wouldn't go over to that side again.
Saika has joined the chat.
I desire
a love that is far more powerful.
By "desire", I mean I "want".
I want a love that is far more powerful.
I want to love someone strong.
Desire, I, mother, mother
Mother, mother, mother mother mother
Mother mother mother mother mother
mother mother mother mother mother
Mother mother mother mother mother mother mother mother mother mother mother
Saika has left the room.
Are we being vandalized?
Kanra has entered the chat.
Setton has entered the chat.
Tarou Tanaka has entered the chat.
Saika has left the room.
Kanra has entered the chat.
Setton has entered the chat.
Tarou Tanaka has entered the chat.
They sound like an alien.
Kanra has entered the chat.
Setton has entered the chat.
Tarou Tanaka has entered the chat.
Note: The kanji Saika used for mother can be pronounced haha.
They may have been laughing...
That's scary...
See the "haha" there?
No, I'm not saying that aliens are scary,
or anything like that.
Setton has left the room.
Is it read as "tsumiuta"?
Or perhaps, "zaika"?
Meaning "wealth"?
I'll look it up later.
Moving right along, you've got a job to do.
It's from Mr. Shiki again, from the Awakusu Group.
Not the greatest job in the world, but will you take it?
Delivery again?
Yup, delivery.
Awakusu Group
For Mr. Shiki
Collect B4 size suitcase
Suspect on the run
But you're supposed to start with getting the object back.
I haven't asked what's contained in the object.
But it's probably better for the both of us if I don't ask.
I know.
So, about that object...
The guy who stole it is on the run.
We have a good idea of where he's hiding at, so it shouldn't take you too long to get him.
Roger.
I heard there's been quite a few victims of the Slasher lately, so be careful.
The Slasher?
Yeah, the Slasher.
I heard he was seen again.
He just wounds people without killing them, and leaves, YO.
How can you call him the strongest then?
The strongest in this city would have to be...
...Simon from "Russia Sushi".
What about that informant who moved over to Shinjuku?
Izaya Orihara.
Wait... it would have to be that guy, don't you think?
Shizuo Heiwajima!
The strongest color gang?
That's gotta be the Dollars, yo.
The Dollars don't have a color.
Although those yellow guys had quite an influence up until last year...
Yellow...?
Yeah, they're called the Yellow Scarves, yo.
But I heard they had a fight with another color gang, the Blue Squares, last year.
The two groups supposedly took each other out.
Well no, I heard they were revived pretty recently.
Keep the orders coming!
Flounder fins and scallops are very cheap right now!
Very cheap!
Now that I think about it, haven't you been seeing those guys a lot lately?
Who?
Oh, the yellow guys?
So you noticed?
By "yellow", you don't mean...
The Yellow Carves!
You mean Yellow Scarves.
Yeah, them!
Hermes, right?
No, the Yellow Scarves were wiped out
during the battle with the Blue Squares.
Oh, you're right.
And their boss supposedly left the scene too.
Welcome!
Could you tell me about the Dollars?
One of my bros is trying to poke his head in it, and I want to stop him.
But why ask us?
Well, I don't have anyone else I can ask.
You can't just go and ask Izaya Orihara either.
Well, we don't know much about the Dollars ourselves.
But we'll tell you everything we know.
There are times when I feel like the city is about to suck me in.
But Mikado, I won't let you go over to that side.
Mikado?
My bad.
Whoa, is that all you're gonna say?
Can't you tell we're part of the Yellow Scarves?
Yagiri!
Huh?
That's not Mika Harima...
I don't know who you are, but I'd appreciate it if you
could refrain from getting in the way of our elopement.
"Elopement"...?
Let's go.
But who was that exactly?
Kida.
Are you guys really Yellow Scarves?
Do you even have to ask?
I'm asking because I don't know.
You son of a...!
K-Kida!
Come on, Mikado. You too?
A-A monster!!
Let's scram!
Quit worrying me, man!
You worried me!
It may actually be me that's relying on him.
Ever since Mikado moved here, I feel like my show of courage is slowly starting to become real.
This time, I may be able to see her without running away.
Come in.
I'm actually starting to feel that way...
I didn't think you'd be visiting me again,
Mr. Izaya.
Hey.
How's he been lately?
Well... he visits me from time to time.
Before that...
I'm home!
Haruna, did you eat already?
Haruna!
No, that's not always true.
Mass slashers, headless riders... this place is just too strange.
Dangerous world we live in, huh?
Oh yeah, what happened to that guy who barged in here?
Oh, I've banned them.
Looks like things will be more peaceful around here.
Let's hope so...
I heard members of the Yellow Scarves were attacked by the Slasher yesterday.
Who are the Yellow Scarves?
I wonder if the Slasher was sent by the Dollars.
What?! No way!
This may turn into a war.
The things happening in this city
may look like they're unrelated, but
they're probably connected somewhere.
They probably carry a distorted truth unfathomable in our minds.
But...
Morning!
M-Morning, Sonohara.
Good morning.
I only realized this just now,
but I seem to like our current relationship.
Even if the points begin to connect someday,
and that reveals something we can't see right now,
I firmly believe that our relationship won't change.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Always On The Move
The Dollars?
I can't really tell you much about them.
Anyway, let me give you the details about the Kaztano incident,
which is basically seen as a legend now.
Next time: Always On The Move.
But you better not call me 'Dotachin'.