Wrong! That ain't even close!
What are you talking about?! I played it exactly right!
There wasn't any swing!
If you aren't feelin' it, it just ain't jazz to me!
Ritsu, do you know the name of the tune he was playing on the piano?
"Moanin'," by Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
My aunt's gone off shopping for dinner.
I've got one hour to make or break it.
Dissonant chords, syncopation, and a unique accent...
I thought I understood the distinctive features of jazz in my head,
but reproducing them is proving to be extremely difficult.
This guy don't get jazz and he's got no sense for it.
Dammit! No matter what it takes, I'm gonna show him up!
I wanna master this as soon as possible
and then perform it in front of him and Ritsuko!
Y-You win...
Kaoru, how wonderful...
As if...
Well, well, Nishimi...
You sure look like you're in a good mood.
Where ya headed?
Don't make a fuss.
That's not true!
Ritsu?
What's wrong?
Cut it out! Let me go!
What'd I ever do to you?!
It's my neck, is all.
These days, I got a crick in my neck that just won't quit,
an' it's puttin' me in the worst mood.
So I figured havin' a little fun like this would make it all better.
Other than that,
you've kinda been gettin' on my nerves lately.
W-What do you mean?
He's on the kendo team, so you shouldn't resist.
Sentaro!
There's trouble! Come quick!
Let's see...
How can we entertain ourselves?
How about splitting a watermelon?
D-Don't...
We can do better than that.
What do you say we pants 'im?!
Now that's a thought.
D-Don't—
Don't move.
Keep nice an' quiet.
Students from the girls' school come home this way too,
so let's give them a good show.
Too much momentum...
Hey! You still alive?
Hey, when this jerk wakes up,
tell 'im that no real man gangs up on a weakling...
Wha—? It's you, Richie?!
W-Well, yeah, sorry!
A-Are you okay, Yamaoka?
Y-Your front tooth is...
Why are you just standing there?
I don't care how you do it, make 'im eat dirt!
Oh, what's this?
We gonna play a game, like "monkey in the middle" maybe?
Oh, no... At this rate...
R-Ritsu!
What are you...?
Sentaro will take care of 'em,
so run away!
Huh?
Clearly, you boys ain't used to scrappin'!
I must look pathetic.
She literally caught me with my pants down.
And on top of that, she rescued me...
Ritsu, would you hold onto my glasses for me?
Take this!
I think I'll pay you back for knockin' out my front tooth!
What the hell?
He dead?
Little twerp!
Get 'im!
All right!
Now it's startin' to get interesting!
Ow!
Well? You up for s'more?
I-I'm gonna see to it that everyone in class gives you the cold shoulder!
You an' me are in the same class?
I don't remember seein' you...
B-Be prepared!
Huh?
My neck feels better...
Kaoru, your forehead's bleeding...
Are you okay?
Don't worry 'bout his forehead.
How are your fingers?
Huh? Is he actually keeping an eye out for me?
I'm home.
Oh, you took another beating, eh?
Somebody's waiting for you.
Go on downstairs.
Could it be Brother Jun?!
Come on!
Why is the squirt beat up, too?
He was in a fight.
Brother Jun!
Hey!
Sen-boy, you been gettin' rowdy again?
Yeah, well, today wasn't much of a fight.
Well, it's good to see that spunk.
So who's this cat?
He's my buddy.
Huh. Cool.
An odd couple, yeah?
Yeah!
Actually, we're not friends...
Oh well...
Say, is he your brother, Ritsu?
Nah. Brother Jun is from next door.
Now he's a college student in Tokyo...
Ritsuko...
Watch the store for just one tune.
Dad, you always say "just one" and then you don't come up for two hours!
It's not every day that Junichi is back in town, right?
C'mon Ritsu, do it for me.
Next time, I'll treat you to a cream soda back at our place.
How about throwing in a cream puff?
Of course, of course.
All right! We got us a deal!
Let's start!
S-Start what?
A live session...
Richie, get over there!
Me?
I can't!
Just make some noise, that's all!
What are you so jittery for?!
Don't sweat the details, just jump in!
Huh? You've only been playing jazz for two weeks?
Amazing. It was all over the place,
but you picked up on the mood.
You've played piano for a while?
Y-Yeah, kinda...
How about comin' over here from now on to practice?
He'll come every day even without being told, right?
Well, I have to get to work.
Thank you, Ritsu.
Oh, that's right, Brother Jun.
What's the name of that record you mentioned?
Oh, the Elvin Jones one?
Yeah, that's it. "Tommy" something...
"Flanagan."
Maybe it's upstairs...
The two of us are alone.
Um, say...
Ritsu, what do you usually do on your days off?
Oh, you mean with summer vacation coming up?
Yeah, right.
I was thinking maybe we could do our homework together?
Sure! I bet I could make real progress workin' on it with you, Kaoru.
How's next Sunday?
Does 11 work for you?
Sure, of course!
I know! Let's meet up there, behind the church.
Hold on, I'll draw you a map.
That's right, summer vacation...
Up until now, all my summer vacations have been spent alone in my room,
with far too much time on my hands...
What should I do? I have so many things to look forward to
that I can't wrap my head around all of it...
Looks like I'm a little early...
Oh, church on Sunday morning...
Ritsu
is a Christian?
No way...
Him too?
Kaoru!
Sorry to make you wait!
That's okay. Well, should we—
Let's go!
Huh?
Wait a second!
This is how we're going to the library?
Better yet, why is he here?
Kanoko-mae Wharf
Bus
Stop
Um... What about the library?
It's so hot today.
Doesn't it feel much better near the ocean?
Sentaro agreed this was the way to go, too!
Ritsu...
I meant for this to be a date...
Hey!
I rented a boat!
Hop in!
How did it come to this?
Why'd it end up being the three of us?
Richie, give me a bite of that, wouldya?
What's with the face?
Doesn't the rower get any kinda reward for his services?
Sentaro, you can finish mine.
N-No, he can't!
Why not?
Well, uh...
Fine!
Here, take it!
One bite, right?
Ritsu, do you always have a cross on, too?
Nope. I have a rosary,
but it's not something you're supposed to wear around your neck.
Our priest says Sentaro is special, tho—
Ri'ko...
You don't have to tell him all that.
For just a second there, the tension was abnormally high.
Or was it just in my head?
Wahoo!
Kaoru, aren't you gonna swim?
We came all this way, so let's take a dip!
Thing is, I didn't bring along a bathing suit.
Neither did Sentaro. He's just wearing his undies.
Let's swim, Kaoru!
Yeah. Okay!
Hey! Ri'ko, hurry up and dive in!
R-Right...
What are you bein' bashful about?
You're flat as a board!
Last time we went swimmin', you had nothin' but your slip on!
Oh, for goodness sake!
That's when we were in elementary school!
Don't say weird things like that in front of Kaoru!
Enough, Sentaro!
Ritsu...
Do you...?
Ri'ko, pinch your nose!
Hey!
Alley-oop!
Ritsu!
You too, Richie!
Oh, c'mon!
You're an ogre, Sentaro!
It feels good, don't it?!
He really is a jerk, isn't he?
Say, Kaoru...
Why do you keep swimming in circles?
This is the only way I know how to swim with my head above water.
Kaoru, you're a funny guy!
She laughed...
Why do I feel so happy when this girl smiles?
Oh... I feel like I could do anything for that smile...
Hey, you two look like you're havin' fun.
Let me join in!
Forget it!
Ritsu, let's get away!
Kaoru, wait for me!
Hey, what gives?!
Why are you swimmin' away?!
Oh, I only wish that we could keep going...
That I could take you away from here...
Let's trade places.
I'll take over rowing.
It's pretty hard, y'know. And on top of that...
Just let me do it!
Dammit...
Wanna switch, Richie?
No, it's not about strength, it's how you do it!
And I think I'm gettin' the hang of it!
Not that I'm complainin',
but you've been takin' us in circles.
Cool.
You took us to a completely different beach.
It's fine.
The sun is already setting anyway,
so if we tell the boat rental guy what happened, he'll come by and pick it up.
Come on, girl, have a little fun with us.
Don't be such a prude.
No! Leave me alone!
We ain't gonna hurt ya!
Let go of me!
We got a car, so let us take you for a ride!
Come on!
Hey. The lady ain't willin'.
How about gettin' your mitts off 'er?
What's that?!
Who the hell are you?
Actin' so tough... What, you tryin' to be a hero?!
Hey, this dude is Kawabuchi from East High!
East High... You're...
Kawabuchi?!
Th-This time, I'll let you off the hook.
You saved me.
Thank you.
It happened in an instant.
I didn't realize what had just taken place,
but when it comes to falling in love,
you don't need rhyme or reason.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change