July 22nd
(Fifth loop)
Ushio?
Hizuru!
Thank goodness!
Ya came back to life!
Hold up, Nezu! Please listen!
Ain't that the Kofune girl who died yesterday?!
I knew yer sidin' with the Shadows.
Stop, Nezu. Don't be rash.
Did I die?
Yes.
I see.
The world you observe becomes reality.
That's what the four-armed one said?
Yes.
But why do I have this power?
If your right eye originally belonged to Haine, then...
...that eye is made of Shadows.
Can you remember when it was printed?
I just woke up with it.
I'm pretty sure it was after I came back to the island, though.
I've just connected all the dots.
The one who granted Ajiro Shinpei that eye was Ushio.
You.
M-Me?
How does that work?
What do you think was the cause for your failure this time?
One thing is that after taking down Mio's Shadow,
we acted separately from each other.
I'd like for all of us to work together this time.
I agree.
Hey, Hizuru!
Wh-What the?
Nezu, Ushio is our ally.
She was our ally until the very end.
Miss Nagumo, can ya hear me?
That message and Ajiro Shinpei's right eye are thanks to her.
I believe you.
Miss Nagumo.
Believing in fictional constructs from the bottom of one's heart is to be human.
Whether it be currency, religion, or stories.
That is why I became a novelist.
But I'm not fiction.
I know that.
I've never seen her laugh before.
So yer riskin' yer lives too, eh?
So the four-armed one's goal is to resurrect that girl, Haine?
The four-armed one plans to feed a ton of people to Haine at the summer festival.
I don't know what happens after the ritual completes, though.
But he did call it "the end."
That giant flat body is its real form, Hiruko.
If the Shadow at Shiori's feet is only a small part of Hiruko,
that explains why it wouldn't die no matter how many times we killed it.
But Shiori's not that strong.
All it can do is walk around in her form.
Hiruko's main body is too weak to move from that cave.
Basically, it's like this.
Haine is immobile (weak legs)
True form (Hiruko) is weak and immobile
Can walk around as Shiori
Shadow at her feet is a part of the true form
Shiori is at the funeral right now
What's your plan?
I'd love to go straight underground and destroy the main body.
But without a surefire way to take down its guardian,
the four-armed Shadow, we'd just fail again.
Most of all, I'm concerned for Mio, Sou, and the others.
Where do we even start?
I'd say
y'all should capture Shiori at Koba Mart just like last time.
But we can't kill it.
What happens after we capture it?
I think
I can erase it.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Friend
Yeah, I'm doing better than yesterday...
now that Shin's back.
I see.
What's the matter, Sou?
I gotta talk to Dad.
It's about Ushio.
Get out. I don't have time to waste.
Sei!
This is none of your concern.
If ya don't have time, then make time. Got it?
I'll leave her in your care, Negoro.
Dad!
Come to my room at 10 o'clock tonight.
I'll give you five minutes.
Thanks, Mom.
It's fine. What is this all about?
Well, it's uh...
Yes, that's right.
Ajiro Shinpei is looking into the shadow sickness.
What's going on?
First it was Ushio Kofune, then it was Minakata Hizuru.
Why are all these people showing up and stirring the pot?
I find it hard to believe it's a coincidence Minakata Hizuru has returned.
And it seems Ushio contacted Shinpei.
I hear you were unable to completely erase Ushio's Shadow and it's gone missing.
Is this true?
Don't worry. It will be found and erased.
I'll start by investigating the family.
You intend to turn all the Kofunes into Shadows?
Yes, and that includes Ajiro Shinpei.
Hm? What is it?
I'll be right there.
Hello? I'm sorry.
My mother is calling. Please excuse me.
Yes, run to Mommy.
Today, we're coming to you live from Kinokawa,
where we'll be showcasing seasonal delicacies from Wakayama—
It's your turn, Ryuunosuke.
Ya can erase Shiori?!
Haine almost took over my mind in that battle.
She entered inside me, so if I trace those circuits in reverse...
Then you could do the same?
Can't say I really get it,
but it seems like it's worth a shot, no?
Indeed.
Truth be told, I'd rather bury them myself.
Nezu told me all about it in a previous loop.
How Ryuunosuke was killed by a Shadow 14 years ago.
And that there were strangle marks on his neck.
Was Ryuunosuke's killer Haine?
That's right.
And that woman is my friend.
What?
Yer friend?
Kofune Mio
Oh, it's Mio.
Answer it.
We can go over the details later.
I wanna hear Mio's voice!
Can I answer it?
Are ya stupid?
I was only pullin' yer leg.
She's alive.
Kofune Mio
My phone's vibration is letting me know that Mio's alive.
I won't let her die again.
Hello? S-Sorry!
Copying my movements from the last loop should yield the same results this time.
In other words, we can capture Haine with plan B.
Haine stole you, Asako—everything from me.
If it weren't for her, Kofune Ushio and others wouldn't have died.
Let's end it, Ryuunosuke.
Roger that, Sis.
Are ya ready?
I was ready before y'were even born, kid.
I'm ready whenever too!
We're going to erase Haine.
The four-armed Shadow's beloved Haine is going to bite the dust, here and now.
Doing so will save everyone from the end of the summer festival.
Oh, Hizuru!
Sorry to intrude during dinner—
I mean, pardon me.
But since I'm here...
Aw, ya didn't have to do that!
Come on in.
Pardon me, then.
No one's around.
Ya can come out now, Ushio.
Ya transform, ya fight.
What are ya, a Pretty Cure?
Y'think so?
Gosh, my dream since kindergarten's come true!
Y'know what PreCure is?
My grandkid used to love watchin' it.
Oh my gosh, Shinpei.
I just realized something amazing!
That's the nail gun the four-armed Shadow destroyed!
Y-Yeah.
Then, Ushio, does this mean ya can take the data ya scanned in previous loops with ya into future ones?
Cool, right?
Yeah, it is.
Yer amazing, Ushio!
And ya scanned those clothes last time, yeah?
What a shame, though.
If only I hadn't let this get destroyed.
Ya ain't gotta worry about a thing.
I've got the original, after all.
Nezu brought two nail guns,
so we named his "nail gun A" and mine "nail gun B."
Ushio scanned nail gun B again,
Nail gun A
Nail gun B (shadow)
overwriting the data of the old one,
then she erased the original.
That way I could use B again.
I wanted her to copy nail gun A as well,
but her storage was full, so we held off on that.
Five minutes have passed since Ryuunosuke went inside.
We should be getting a message telling us to change to plan B, right?
Yeah.
And about two minutes after that,
Shiori will jump off the veranda.
Ya miss the third shot,
and Shiori runs off toward that Green Soft Serve flag where I capture her.
And I finally erase her!
Yup.
First, we wait for Ryuunosuke to contact us.
Wha—
R-Run away...
Miss Nagumo!
Wait!
This is no longer like the 22nd you know—
Why hello, everyone.
So nice of you to come see me.
Summer Time Rendering
H-Hizuru!
I-Impossible!
How?
Why are ya here?!
Cheating is naughty, Shinpei.
What?
Remember what I said that time?
"Found ya."
I branded ya.
From now on, no matter what world ya go to,
I'll be able to find ya lickity-split.
Get it?
I've been chasing ya all this time.
Ever since our eyes met at the end of the summer festival.
I can loop too.
I figured out y'all came here on this day in a previous loop after digging through Ryuunosuke's memories.
No... That can't be!
Two observers is one too many.
Mother
or you?
The world the survivor sees
shall become the truth!
Bring it!
I'll kill ya dead!
Three hits!
It shouldn't be able to move after three shots.
Why didn't it work?!
Not good!
If I scan the whole thing, I'll lose my sense of self!
But if it's just one arm—
Oh well.
That was just a greeting, Ajiro Shinpei.
Repeat as much as you like.
In the end, I will catch up to you
and finally seal away that power.
Haine!
I was naive!
I should've realized that the enemy would have the same power as me!
She came from that summer festival too, after all.
My naivety got them both killed!
Ushio? Where are ya?!
Over here!
Sorry, did it hurt when I sliced yer head off?
I tried to make it as clean as possible.
Th-Thank goodness yer here, Ushio.
I'm fine.
Nice thinking back there.
What about ya?
Ya all right? Still got yer sense of self?
I thought I could figure out whose Shadow the four-armed one is, but...
It was empty.
Its body has no data.
I don't even know how it's moving.
I see...
Still, strangely enough, it had the same smell as Haine.
Ya think ya can beat an enemy that can time loop?
I think Haine's using ya and following along to loop.
So she should end up at the same starting point we do.
We're on even terms!
We can win if we're together!
Thank ya.
Huh?
Is this our home?
Bistro Kofune
I was expecting the loop's starting point to shift, but were we ever here?
No, this is weird.
I don't remember it raining.
Whenever I returned to the 22nd, it was always sunny.
Hey, wait up!
I said wait for me, Sis.
That was...
It can't be...
Miss Nagumo?
Ain't no time to be thinkin'.
Shinpei, go after 'em!
Right.
The scene changed?
Wow, it sure is packed today.
Oh, welcome!
Hizuru and Ryuunosuke.
I knew it.
These two are Hizuru and her twin brother, Ryuunosuke.
Wh-What's goin' on?
The first time I died, something similar happened.
Hiya! Just ya two?
Why are ya wearin' an apron, Akemi?
Today's the tenth anniversary of Kofune's opening,
so the whole island's comin' out to eat here.
Really? Congratulations!
Thanks. That's why I'm helping out too.
M-Mom?
It's really Akemi! Wow!
So this really is the past.
Fourteen years ago.
The first time I died, Mio was nearby and something similar happened!
I was transported to when ya died at the private beach and witnessed a scene from the past.
And that was a memory of Mio's?
Then this must be from Miss Nagumo's memory.
Dessert is free today!
Yay!
The crowd is unpleasant. I'm leaving.
Stop right there!
Asako. Didn't see you there.
Today's a big day for Kofune.
Let's celebrate it together!
I don't see the need for all of us to make a fuss just to celebrate.
But yer here, so there ain't no need to leave, either.
Ain't ya got a human heart, Hizuru?
I am human, therefore I have a human heart.
Miss Nagumo hasn't changed since she was a kid, I see.
Congrats on the ten years, Kofune!
You. Leave.
Oh, dear!
Hizuru, are ya that happy to see me?
Yer makin' me blush.
Toru! Masahito! Thank ya!
Ten years sure goes by in the blink of an eye, huh?
Alan, um...
Your cooking's always good.
Please keep that flavor in the years to come.
Have ya looked in a mirror today?
Ya gotta shave and fix yer bedhead!
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
Even yer dad's here!
I didn't know this day happened.
Yeah, it's amazing.
They're moving.
Their voices, their mannerisms. I remember now.
What did yer parents do again, Shinpei?
They were marine archaeologists.
They spent a lot of time diving.
Masahito, I hear yer finally head priest now.
Yes. I'm still very new at everything, but I'm managing so far.
What have ya been up to lately, Toru?
I was thinking of diving in that spot I mentioned the other day.
Hitogashima is so full of history. It's very interesting.
I'm glad I moved here.
And the food's great too!
Hey, Ryuu!
Ain't Hizuru in a bad mood?
Yeah, that's actually my fault.
I shoulda never told the likes of ya.
Huh? What, what?
Well,
she said she made a friend.
Can ya believe it?
I can't, so I said it was probably a dream.
Or maybe someone only she can see, then she got mad.
Now, now, Ryuu, that's
certainly unbelievable.
Hey.
I'm kiddin'!
Sorry, Hizuru. I believe ya.
Liar.
The faith of a liar means nothing.
That's not what Asa meant.
It's fine, Ryuu.
So what's this person like?
There ain't even 20 people in our whole middle school.
Where'd ya meet a new face?
Mt. Takanosu.
The scene changed again!
Hishigata Clinic
Shinpei, this is...
Yeah.
The old Hishigata Clinic.
Did ya really meet her here?
Where is she from? She local?
Probably.
Probably?
And I suspect she's not from our time period, either.
You'll understand when ya meet her.
She always appears at this time.
Up there.
A light comes on in the second floor window.
That totally sounds like a ghost.
Th-That's so creepy!
I heard this place is haunted too!
Nothing's happening.
M-Maybe today's just not her day!
Hizuru, we should be headin' back.
Our parents will be worried.
It'll be dangerous getting back down in the dark.
I promised I'd meet her today.
And I keep my promises.
Hizuru!
I'll walk ya home, Asa.
When she gets like this, she won't even budge an inch.
Ya gotta be kidding me.
Good evening,
Haine.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time