I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
Space travel log 0968.
Empty time. It sounds good to call
bounty hunting freelance work,
but all that really means
is that we're self-employed.
So when there's no one to hunt,
we have nothing.
Nothing to do, nothing to live on.
Well, that's all part
of the life we've chosen.
Our destiny, if you like.
But when you're out of money,
you start thinking about quick cash.
You're fine with both
of these now, right?
Even.
You're going with even?
No, make it odd!
Odd. You're sure?
Yes. Odd.
Snake eyes. Even.
Oh no!
I can't eat any more...
I'd actually prefer payment in cash.
I'm not a pawn shop, you know.
Well, Jet?
A man keeps his word.
And that's why I told you
not to play against her.
Humans were meant to work
and sweat to earn a living.
Those that try to get rich quick,
or live at the expense of others,
all get divine retribution
somewhere along the line.
That's the lesson.
Unfortunately, we quickly forget
the lessons we've learned.
And then we have to
learn them all over again.
Ah, dammit.
Hm... I don't remember that.
A refrigerator way back here?
"Survival of the fittest"
is the law of nature.
We deceive, or we are deceived.
Thus we flourish or perish.
Nothing good ever happened
to me when I trusted others.
That is the lesson.
How much did you swindle?
A word like that could
damage my reputation.
He just had a run of bad luck.
He just didn't know about this.
That's part of the skill of the game.
You could at least
give him his clothes back.
- I'll rent them to him.
- Greedy, aren't we.
Well, I prefer to think
of it as "enterprising."
Hey, what happened?
Something bit me.
What do you mean by "something?"
It wasn't a rat, okay?
Look at this, there's a weird
mark on the back of my neck.
Well, that was a waste of time. Sheesh...
Spike, it happened near
that old refrigerator.
Refrigerator?
Yeah, you got any ideas?
Hmm...
Maybe... There was a...
Nope, can't remember.
You sure this is gonna work?
It works on everything but
nearsightedness and cavities.
- Then it works on athlete's foot?
- Yeah, sure.
Don't you have any real medicine
that's just for sores and wounds?
That would be this.
- Ew... That heals wounds?
- Yup.
You squish it up and boil it
in three cups of water,
and when it turns green
and goopy, you drink it.
Spike, isn't there something
more, you know, different?
Oh, yeah! I got it.
Yeah, gimme that... ooh.
I'll take the other thing.
Great... I'm feeling a lot
sicker than I did before.
Do I look pale or what?
You're always pale.
What is that awful smell?
- Herbal medicine.
- Herbal medicine? That swill?
Smells like day-old roadkill soaked
in sour milk and maggot juice.
More like rotten soybeans and turpentine.
Oh, yeah...
That's enough.
I gotta drink this stuff.
Oh, brother.
Come on, will you quit joking around?
It was a rat, right?
I mean, this is no big deal...
- Am I wrong?
- I have no clue.
He's got some kind of poison
that's not in the database.
I'm checking the file
for some similar toxins.
Cryptosporidium...
No, that's not it.
Cholera...
Nope, it's not that.
Ebola virus...
Nope.
Bifidobacterium...
Not even close.
So what is it?
Ein, give it a rest, would you?
Well, this is not an ordinary rat.
Ein, keep it quiet!
- So what could it be then?
- Well, it's, uh--
A mystery space creature!
Spooky! The attack of the horrible alien!
Well, yeah. That is possible, I suppose.
Oh, yeah, right.
Then what is it?
It's not in the database, right?
- Well--
- Look! These pairs are abnormal.
Uh, you think so?
Ed has never seen this before.
So what else could it be
but a horrible alien, huh? What?
Maybe it's...
Something like a rat went through
a mutation, and it evolved...
and turned into some kind
of unusual creature...
and secreted this new form
of mysterious poison.
Oh, that's brilliant!
Right up there with Ed's theory
that it's a horrible alien!
Really pitiful.
Aiya, what are we gonna do, Ein?
You believe it's a
horrible alien, don't you?
Spooky!
All right, this locates
and monitors heat sources.
We usually use it when we're tracking down
bounty heads that have gone into hiding.
- Can you see me?
- Whoa, yeah!
Oh! Woof woof woof!
That's fine... I'm gonna test it now.
Don't move till I tell you.
Ein! Where are you going?
Hey, wait! Hey!
Huh?
This is weird. Did it break?
What's wrong? Did you find something?
Do you remember that theory you had
about a mutant creature, Spike?
Uh, yeah?
What do you suppose happens
if you're bitten by it?
I can't really say for sure until I catch
one and examine it, but I can guess.
Death...
No, please... why did it
have to be this way?
I still have a lot to live for...
I haven't committed any crimes...
well, at least no really bad ones.
- I'm still young and full of life!
- Full of what?
Life is so unfair! Poor me!
Hey, come on.
What's gotten into you?
August 6th. Sky day.
Today, Ed goes looking for the
spooky, mysterious, horrible alien.
Lesson, lesson.
If you see a stranger, follow him.
Where are you?
Are you here,
Mr. Spooky Space Creature?
Ed! Ein!
Hey! This isn't hide-and-seek, dammit!
Exploration, experimentation,
exploration, exclamation!
I will come back alive.
I trust you, Ed.
Ein?
Ein? Ein!
Are you here? Hello?
Answer me!
Oh man...
Ein! Ed, where are you?
Ein!
Hey, hang in there. Where's Ed?
I can't believe they got you.
Where are your animal instincts?
No choice. Gotta go in.
Currently in cruise mode on Route 66.
Approximate cruise time
remaining: 82 hours.
Preparing to enter full autopilot.
After passing the gate, this ship is
preprogrammed to land on Mars.
The route cannot be changed
once it is confirmed.
Ed, are you in here? Hey!
It must have gotten her too.
Don't do that!
That's it!
Come on!
Let's go, slimeball!
This thing smells kinda familiar.
I guess I should've eaten that stuff.
Well, I'm sure it's still in the fridge.
That was when I remembered everything.
It was, oh, one year ago.
I had gotten ahold of a
real Ganymede rock lobster.
I hid it in the fridge in the stockroom
so no one else would eat it.
But I had forgotten about it
and left it there for a whole year.
I wonder what it
looks like in there now...
Ah, shit!
Ah, that's great!
So that's the story.
And what was the real lesson?
Don't leave things in the fridge.
Mmm... more pudding...
No... I can't eat any more...
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
And so, they all passed away, every one.
It was a short series,
but thanks for your support.
That was the last episode.
May they all rest in peace. Amen.
And for the next series,
we bring you "Cowgirl Ed!"
Ed is the the main character!
- Hey, wait a minute!
- What kinda selfish thing is that?!
Next episode:
"Jupiter Jazz, Part 1."
There really is a next episode!