Shinpei!
Shin...
A sniper shot from outside the window...
A rifle...
They got to Nezu!
I didn't sense any shadows.
A shadow bullet didn't kill ya.
It was a real rifle bullet.
It was a mistake to let Nezu be alone!
He went beyond yer detection range.
This is all on me!
They found out that Nezu was our sniper.
Dammit!
I assumed they'd come directly fer me!
Wait. I thought they wanted to capture ya alive?
You'll just loop, so why'd they kill ya?
They probably figured it out because Haine is looping alongside me.
I told ya that the starting point gets later each time.
I can see it.
My limit is getting close.
The ledge of time is slowly but surely crumbling.
If I get killed at the same time, most likely...
I can only loop one more time.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
July 22nd
(Seventh loop)
Yer only able to loop one more time?
Lights, Camera, Action
If this is the limit, I return to this point each time I die.
Limit
Time
I can't go back past the limit, so this is the starting point.
Death
Last time, I died at 7:55 p.m.,
and my starting point was 6:40 p.m.
Limit
It's like I'm steadily walking forward from that point.
Present
It's currently 7:20 p.m.
Limit
The limit moves forward as well.
The limit can't catch up to me now
since it still moves slower than I do,
but it gets faster each time I die.
If ya die now, when's the next starting point?
Well, based on the past...
maybe a little past seven o'clock.
That was a few minutes ago!
If I die any earlier than the last time, I probably won't get a ninth loop.
Limit
Present
While I'm treading in time,
Death
the limit will pass me by.
There wouldn't be anything to return to.
I would fall into the darkness below.
Hey, are ya serious?! It's not just yer imagination?
He saw it as an observer.
It must be true.
That cliff is an event horizon.
If he falls, his death is fixed.
The world Haine sees after that will become reality.
Haine realized that and came to kill you.
That's horrible!
How'd they find me?
Haine may've discovered our strategy in the fourth loop.
I must've been scanned when I
was fatally wounded at the end.
They must've read my memory leading up to it.
How do shadows exchange information?
Do they show their memories the same way yer doing it?
Yes, they can also talk or write.
Haine also uses telepathy.
Shadows experience pseudo loops like we do if they come in contact with Haine.
Hold it.
Data is passed through loops, ain't it?
Could they have copied my rifle?
If so, this place ain't safe.
We're fine.
A copied item will disappear if it's too far from the shadow who printed it.
Copied items can't exist beyond a
50-meter radius from the shadow.
So a bullet from the copied sniper rifle will only have a 50-meter range.
Even an unlimited supply of bullets would be meaningless.
The enemy won last time, but we also learned a lot.
This mark means Haine knows where I am.
Haine will definitely come here to watch me die.
Let's finish this here tonight.
Shinpei!
They're coming at ya head-on.
Ya have quite a large entourage, Shide.
You've gathered many to your side too, Shinpei.
I don't see 'em here, so they must be hiding.
Is it a trap?
I'm not like y'all!
I don't use any underhanded tricks.
Let's stop playing games and fight face-to-face.
Oh?
You sound so confident.
It would be our pleasure.
Right, Mio?
Yes.
Shin doesn't disappoint.
He's so cool!
Sis?
If they're after my life, then I'll be the bait!
He ran away.
What happened to a face-to-face fight?!
Where are ya taking Shin?!
Ajiro Shinpei,
yer quite the rat.
That shadow called Shide has no weakness.
Is it invincible?
Hurry!
Wait, Mio.
Excuse me.
What?
Mommy and Daddy, come with me.
We'll go after Shinpei and Ushio.
Finish the hunter, Mio.
Yes.
I understand, Mother.
Ryuunosuke!
Leave this to me.
Thanks!
You probably won't be able to hear me now,
but I forgot to tell you something important, Ryuunosuke.
Thank you.
Shit!
It's coming!
Yer turn!
That's my shadow!
I got it!
What the... Crap!
You're so dumb, Brother.
You get so fired up easily.
S-Sorry, Tokiko.
Rosencrantz.
Gildenstern.
Go crazy.
Be as quiet as an explosion.
Hizuru...
Asa!
Go left.
That bullet should've hit.
I told ya he'd take a hit fer 'em.
I see...
Ryuu...
It can see how I move two seconds into the future!
Now shoot!
Nezu!
That old man doesn't even need the scope. He's quite the shot.
Are ya okay, Shide?
Go and hide where he can't see you.
It's dangerous here.
Oh my.
What's taking Mio so long?
Tokiko?
Crush it, Gil.
Stop!
Yer boss is no longer Tokiko.
Kill Tokiko.
Kill Tokiko!
What's wrong, Haine?
That stray shadow's link with me is cut off.
The only one who can do that is...
Ushio!
If that pissed ya off, I dare ya to come and get me!
Is this yer doing?!
Well, they're certainly making this fun.
What a graceful body.
Ya always were athletic, Mio.
Oh, how I'd love to keep watching ya move, but unfortunately...
Now, Sou!
You said you wanted a face-to-face fight. Such lies.
This is sad. I believed you too.
I'm actually quite the trusting type.
I knew ya'd chase me, even if ya knew it was a trap.
Yer just that cocky!
So ya think yer above all of us?
Shinpei is even higher!
Summer Time Rendering
It's a sea of gasoline flames.
They have nowhere to run!
It's working.
Shadows really are weak to fire!
I'm sorry, Mommy and Daddy. I know it's hot.
But don't worry.
It'll all go back to normal after I kill him!
Take this, ya goddamn shadow freak!
If yer gonna try to get a bird's-eye view,
don't take yer eyes off the prize, Haine!
This is fer Ushio!
Gotcha.
I'll erase ya!
Quit messing around with Shiori's body,
ya fake!
Stop!
S-Stop.
Please don't erase me.
I chose this body.
I want to go home as her and be with her family forever.
Haine! C-Crying won't work on me!
Please...
Don't erase me.
N-No way!
It's still alive!
Ushio!
Shinpei!
Y-You can't kill me with f-fire!
B-But y-you will die!
I w-was th-thinking.
Y-You and Haine carry d-data into the n-next loop, d-don't you?
Th-That means y-you carry injuries and d-death too!
I-It'll take a f-few minutes for Shinpei to d-die.
I made sure not to hit his vitals.
Wh-What happens if y-you die b-before him?
I-I'm so c-curious to d-discover the answer!
No...
No!
Sorry, but I ain't interested in yer "experiment."
I don't plan on dying!
How smooth.
I d-didn't notice you changing p-places.
I g-grabbed a dummy p-printed on a lock of hair.
Yer not invincible.
I'll erase ya!
A human hand!
Someone's inside it!
The flames disappeared.
I can't breathe...
Haine...
What did...
ya do...
What the hell happened?!
They ran away.
I was so close to erasing it.
Ushio!
Shide, are ya okay?
Yes, I can mold myself back together.
Where's Mommy and Daddy?
Shinpei is fatally wounded.
He'll die soon and the final loop will begin.
I'm hungry.
I know.
Ushio!
I'm okay, Shinpei.
I'm just tired after copying so much.
But yer bleeding.
Don't act so tough.
Shinpei.
This blood is just from some glass touching my true form.
Never mind me, yer wounds are serious!
A bulletproof vest.
I found how to make it online.
Ow! That hurts! Stop!
My shoulder and side still got shot!
Thank goodness.
A flame caused by copied gasoline and matches is just data.
Ushio chose what burns by it.
It didn't harm the building nor us.
Fire was effective on shadows.
Shadows made by Shide died instantly.
It also slowed down Shide's movement.
Furthermore, Ushio's hacking helped us
learn that someone is inside Shide's body.
However, Haine scanned the air in the gymnasium and erased it.
Outside air gushed into the building, allowing them to escape.
Ushio was unable to scan Shide's true identity.
The air, though? How in the world...
We can copy liquids and gases too.
It just needs to be in some container.
You were able to copy the gasoline in the gas can.
If you consider the gymnasium a container, it is possible.
I hate to say it, but it's impressive.
I can't scan something so large.
I was so close.
We did learn a lot from tonight, though.
Yes.
Everyone survived.
That's the most important thing.
Right.
Ushio.
Come with me.
Like we planned?
Yes.
Lemme ask this again, Ushio.
If ya cut that link to Haine, will it really be safe?
It worked with Rose and Gil.
Yes. I tweak their minds a bit.
They basically just gotta be like me.
We could easily kill it right now.
Are ya sure, Mio?
Yeah.
Do it, Sis.
Make my shadow our ally.
Next time
Original