I kill people with this hand... and I eat with this hand.
There isn't any difference.
I do these things... to live.
That's... how life is, right?
Conflagration
Hey.
That was unfortunate, hardhead.
Gant, you son of a bitch! Why do you have to show up on such a day?!
You've got quite a look in your eyes, Tony.
What're you talking about, old man Gant?
Don't play innocent.
I've known you guys since you were snotty brats.
So I can tell...
that look in your eyes says that you're about to start a bloodbath.
Don't do anything stupid, okay? I'm always watching you.
Are we gonna do it, Tony?
Yeah. We'll crush Inferno.
It's not for revenge. We'll do it in order to protect our town.
But Gant is keeping a close eye on us. We have to be careful.
I've got an idea.
There's a way to send them to their maker without dirtying our hands.
In sum, Inferno is a bunch of betrayers
who go against their bosses and join hands with their families' rivals.
Among the organizations on the West Coast,
these fifteen guys would benefit from joining Inferno.
Richard Harrington. Carlo Mendoza.
Are yo saying that such big shots are joining hands behind the scenes?
If we obtain evidence of that and reveal it, they're done for.
Any organization would take care of misconduct by their own people.
Those who spit on the code of conduct...
will go to hell because of their own foolish deeds.
Amazing... That's the smartest way.
Anton, I'll leave the arrangements to you.
Stay close to them and reveal their true colors.
But... be cautious.
Good morning, Ms. McCunnen.
I see you're your usual beautiful self today.
Why are you here?
I asked him here.
He offers his opinions based on his unique insights.
We can gain quite a bit from them.
I plan to have him participate in future executive meetings as a regular.
Do you have any objections?
No, sir.
I called for an urgent meeting today
to inform you of Tony Stone's latest actions.
Tony? Is that hardhead still trying to do something?
I've obtained information that he's using spies.
I thought that an annoying fly has been buzzing around me lately...
So he was sent by Tony of all people.
It looks like the message we sent him the other day had the opposite effect.
If they had come at us in a frenzy, that would've been convenient for us.
But I didn't expect that he'd try to strike our weak point.
I guess we should immediately get rid of him after all.
However, our goal at the beginning was...
to gain the Stone Family's turf without turning it into a battlefield.
You have some sort of plan?
I can't help but thinking...
that Tony Stone's careless action is a one-in-a-million chance.
Oh? Interesting. Let us hear it.
Ein's been gone for a while now.
That's reckless. Such a daring plan is...
It's possible if we use Phantom.
I think she's proven her ability many times by now.
True. Although the scale is bigger,
it's not that much more reckless than her previous missions.
We may just have a shot at making this work.
I'd like to hear your decision, Mr. McGwire.
You sure know the right timing to promote your talent.
Thank you very much.
Fine.
Why don't we take a change on that confidence of yours, Scythe Master.
Good, Ein. Wonderful.
You're really the best subject.
This meaningless world filled with confusion will be changed by my will.
A new order... A new balance... I will build it all.
In this program, even God is just watching from the upper gallery!
You are the lead... Ein.
My precious prima donna.
Did the meeting drag on?
These are the instructions for our new operation. Look through them later.
This one is a series of missions. Our targets are...
twelve people.
Twelve? In one night? Seriously?
Our individual missions aren't hard.
We have to time things carefully and aim to be in perfect sync.
These are all senior members of Inferno's rivals.
If this succeeds, the power balance on the West Coast will change considerably.
Is this okay? Isn't it too hasty?
That's not your concern.
It's natural to think about the meaning of the mission, right?
Did someone tell you that?
You shouldn't bother. It doesn't suit our way of existing.
What is our way of existing?
Be an instrument. Be a tool.
All we need to do is just function.
Don't think about unnecessary things.
How can you say that so firmly?
Does thinking harm us?
We'll be destroyed...
Both you...
and I...
Looks like everything is ready, huh?
Don't give me that silly smile, you rotten snake.
Your plan is far from an operation. It's acrobatics.
It's the same as walking a tightrope or jumping through a flaming hoop.
I planned it all because I have confidence in you guys' abilities.
To start with, why are you running this all by yourself as if you own the place?
Where's Clo?
She said she couldn't come because she had to attend to another matter.
What are we going to do with her?
If Clo orders it, I'll go out on a limb no matter how dangerous it is.
But there's no reason for me to risk my life on your orders.
We'll have more and more of this kind of operation.
You may end up being forced to rethink your future plans, you know...
...Ms. Garland.
Lizzie. It's time.
Get a move on! We're leaving!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Well then. I'll see you later.
Hm?
Phase one complete.
Roger. Starting phase two.
Back! He escaped to the back!
Search over there!
I got him! This way!
Who's this guy?
I've seen him before.
If I remember correctly, wasn't he working as a bouncer in Tony's turf?
Stone Family?! Why did they come after the old man? Those bastards!
Carlo isn't doing anything special tonight.
He's having dinner at one of his usual restaurants right now.
What a stuck up bastard.
Yes... Okay.
Well then, I'll talk to you on the next scheduled call.
What's going on?!
With regards to Ahlen Construction's bidding,
there was a rumor that local mafia was involved.
So it's very possible that this is a fight between gangs.
I see.
Ah, yes.
According to the information we've just received,
there was a gunfight and car accident on the Pacific Coast Highway.
We have a relay from the scene.
They're overreacting.
The night has just started.
You mean there are going to be more big scenes like that?
Tonight's bloodshed is just the beginning.
From here on, it will truly be an era dominated by survival of the fittest.
It's a world where any dream is possible as long as you have power.
Mr. Godo... would that way of life... appeal to you?
Anton, what the hell is going on?!
Abel, Bark... No-one's reporting... when things have gotten this serious!
They're all dead by now.
Like a bullet, they left their mark. I'm sure they're satisfied.
Wh-What do you mean?
Are you saying that Bark and the others killed... Don Ronny and Hugo?!
That's what everyone will believe...
since no-one will go interview them in their tombs.
Anton... Why...?
Don't you get it? I guess you don't...
since you're hardheaded.
Well done, kid.
Yeah. Now I can say goodbye to this filthy town.
It took me twenty-five years to get out of this cesspool.
I'm sick and tired of it.
You're retiring at such a young age?
I received enough compensation from Inferno.
I'll buy a cottage or something on a Caribbean beach.
What's your cut?
My first promotion in fifteen years.
I did end a mafia war, after all.
Looks like we both will live a long life.
An era came to an end yesterday.
The six old men who had long controlled the criminal underworld on the West Coast
died tragically.
And Tony Stone was considered the mastermind of it all
and the law brought him to justice.
Having lost their leaders,
each organization will be led to the new era by our brethren...
under the banner of Inferno.
Splendid. Another miracle caused by your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
Lieutenant Cyrus Gant received an award from the mayor
for his contribution in resolving the mafia war that shook the entire city.
Tony Stone, who was known as a gang leader and the boss of Melanie Square,
I wonder if everyone takes this news at face value.
simultaneously attacked six West Coast -based criminal organizations and succeeded in all.
No-one cares about the truth... nor are they interested.
However, his ambition was suddenly crushed by Lieutenant Gant's heroic actions.
I wonder who'll pray for the people who died that day.
I wonder who'll atone for that sin.
There's neither prayer nor atonement.
Death is the end of everything.
No matter what you do after that...
there's no point.
The Past
Next episode
There is nothing.
Dreams are just illusions.
All they do is get in your way.