You're in an awfully good mood today.
You're quite the vulgar boy, aren't you?
You should know better, Haruka!
It's nothing.
Anyways, what's in the bag?
Some sweets I bought at the hotel for Moritani yesterday.
I wonder if she'll like them.
And now a shocking new development in this string of random assaults!
Did something happen?
What? What's wrong?
It's Moritani.
She's been arrested?
One morning I suddenly realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
✩Ah✩
Nothing good can come from cuddling you all the time
Cuddle,
cuddle,
cuddle
The scent of my feelings might stick
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Tell me, is this "love"?
That's a secret beyond all secrets, you know?
Yeah!
That's a secret beyond all secrets, isn't it? ♡
Interrogation Room #2
Are you sure you can't tell me what happened?
But You're Not Here
It's just if you don't,
that scary-looking old guy—
his name's Yama—
will get really mad.
Um.
Hey, you hungry?
I'll just bet you're hungry.
Okay, let's order something up.
Moritani!
What's that?
Are you sure Moritani's here?
Yeah. They're weak, but...
I can definitely hear her thoughts down this way.
That right? Well then—
Can you hear me, Moritani?!
It's me, Manabe!
Kotoura's here too!
If you're there, answer me!
Manabe.
Kotoura.
Manabe! Kotoura!
I... I...
I didn't do anything wrong!
Honest! I... I didn't...
What are you two screaming about?
You're not allowed back here, kids!
I'm sorry! We only need a second!
I heard her. She was clear this time.
Moritani! I know the truth!
I know you were just a bystander!
Moritani!
Can you hear me, Moritani?!
Your friends? They're pretty incredible!
You two truly redefine "temerarious."
They're gonna take you in too.
Well, when I heard Moritani had been arrested,
my brain kind of shut down, so...
So of course I had to follow her, for her own good.
I do appreciate your concern,
but please don't end up like them.
Mori! Mori!
Set Hiyori free!
Unlawful arrest is disgraceful!
Mori! Mori!
Miss Hiyori! We'll save you!
Want to join them?
So just to make sure I'm clear on this,
Moritani was arrested on suspicion of
committing the random assaults, right?
That's right.
The reporters and police at school this morning were all thinking about it.
But they're wrong!
I've seen the real criminal.
I know.
We could try making a desperate attempt to tell the police,
but now that you've gone and done that...
Sorry.
What's up, Muroto?
I see... something?
The detective from school?
Moritani!
Oo guyz god arres'ed oo?
But man, when I actually thought about it,
I suddenly realized I hadn't eaten since last night.
Sheesh. But I'm glad to see you're okay.
No need to worry about me!
She can say that now, but when she heard you calling for her
she started blubbering like a baby.
B-Be quiet!
Forgive the tangent, but was it really okay to let us in here?
Uh. As long as no one finds out?
And anyway, having her friends here'll make it easier for her to talk.
Um. She seems to be in earnest.
So Moritani, how did you wind up getting yourself arrested?
Well...
Remember that rumor that Kotoura knew who the criminal was?
It was a friend of mine who started it.
I tried to stop her from spreading it any further,
but she just got mad at me.
I decided to check all the places she'd be likely to go.
So you found your injured friend after she'd been attacked,
and they arrested you.
Right.
But is it really standard procedure to arrest someone
just for being at the scene of a crime?
No, but we had a tip-off in this case.
A witness said the suspect was being very belligerent, and had made threats on the victim's life.
And that liar called herself my friend.
So just for trying to stop the rumors about me, Moritani was falsely accused.
Kotoura.
Moritani is not the criminal!
I know who the real culprit is!
Eh? What?
Looks like you bums are having a pretty interesting conversation.
If you do know somethin' about the perp,
why don't you fill me in?
O-Okay.
You sure about this, Kotoura?
Yeah. It's okay.
The thing is, I...
Tsukino, send 'em home.
I'm not lying!
I really can hear people's thoughts!
Sorry, but I don't have the time for kids' games.
Hold up, old-timer!
Do you really think Kotoura wants to tell you all this?!
Manabe.
Let's see.
All right, how about we test her psychic powers on you.
You're gonna read my mind?
Ooh, I'm shittin' bricks.
Go on. No holding back.
Okay.
Um. You'd been having a hard time getting by because your wife wouldn't give you any money.
Your hemorrhoids were worsening and using the toilet was agony.
Your wife refused to wash your poop-stained underwear.
H-Hold it—
And late one night, you came home to find no dinner.
In its place were the divorce papers, already signed.
Stop! Please stop!
I give up. For the love of mercy, spare me.
You'll let Moritani go now, right?
Sorry kiddo, no can do.
Why not?
Psychic abilities aren't actually supposed to exist,
so they're not admissible evidence. Is that it?
Damn straight. And we police got our honor.
We can't let this magic mind-reading mumbo-jumbo do our job for us.
The honor of the police?
Where was that "honor" when you took credit for my mother's talents—and then let her die?!
President Mifune.
What are you blabberin' ab—
I had a feeling I'd seen you somewhere before.
Could you be...
The daughter of Mifune Chizuru.
I see. The clairvoyant's daughter.
Let's go, guys.
What? But, wait—
Kotoura.
Yes. Let's be on our way.
Mifune Chizuru the clairvoyant was pretty well-known among the police force.
She even assisted in police investigations.
Unofficially, of course.
That bein' why we had no choice but to cut her loose
when she was declared a fraud.
'Course, I didn't believe in this psychic bullshit anyway.
I wonder how those kids can stand to be around that girl.
Anyway, time for a chat.
What?! But I got the testimony!
Cut me some slack!
I couldn't do anything.
Even though it was my fault Moritani was arrested.
Don't be an idiot. You didn't do anything wrong.
Well, it's fairly obvious she's innocent.
They'll clear her of suspicion soon.
Why don't we search for the criminal after all?
It doesn't look like we can rely on the police.
Leaving Moritani in their custody would just break my heart.
Yuriko, you...
This could be a chance to help Moritani with your power.
My power... can help?
I'll do it.
I'm a little scared,
but if my power can help someone...
Don't worry, Kotoura.
The ESP Society will do everything it can to help you.
P-President Mifune.
Count me out.
Manabe?
I'll never condone the use of psychic powers
to track down a criminal.
Where's Manabe?
He hasn't spoken to you at all since then?
No. Not a word.
He's stubborn, like all fools.
Not even Kotoura can sway him now.
Kotoura, finding the criminal is not your responsibility.
But it's my fault Moritani—
Don't make me repeat myself!
It wasn't your fault. Moritani knows that too.
Besides, what can you hope to do if you faint
every time you're even close to the criminal?
That's not...
I thought my heart was going to stop.
I couldn't bear to see you like that again.
Manabe.
But I still believe this is something I must do.
There it is again!
Don't you just love taking everything on yourself!?
You haven't made any progress since you ran off!
So doing whatever I can to help people is wrong?
Don't forget that the person I'm trying to help is a friend!
Taking this kind of risk isn't noble, it's just stupid!
It's not stupid!
Forget it.
I'll never get through that thick head of yours.
I hate you!
What?!
Is that so?! Fine, do whatever you damn well want!
I will do what I want.
And Manabe can do what he wants.
Well, you were pretty harsh back there.
Y-You really think so?
Nothing we can do about someone who's not here.
We'll find this psycho assaulting people in our town.
Um, what are these red dots?
The crime scenes, and the point where you walked past the criminal.
Looking at this, it's pretty clear the criminal is based inside city limits.
This spot here where Kotoura ran into him
is the busiest place in town.
I'd assume the criminal was there picking out his victims.
If he stays downtown, there'll be no shortage of the high school girls he targets.
He'll have his pick.
He probably follows them until they reach a less crowded area, and then attacks.
Hey, Kotoura.
Y-Yes! Of course I'm not thinking about Manabe!
You can head home for today.
No, that's okay.
To be honest, you don't have anything to do yet.
You should rest up while you can.
R-Right.
See you later, then.
Sort of feels like old times again.
Yeah.
It was just you and me at first.
Then we got an actual esper when Kotoura showed up.
Then Manabe and Moritani came along, too.
It was fun.
It was fun while it lasted, but it could never have lasted.
No matter what I do, I...
What do you think of me now?
Didn't I tell you before?
I'll neither help you nor condemn you.
I'm here because I choose to be.
You don't have to worry.
He probably follows them until they reach a less crowded area, and then attacks.
I've gotta get home, fast!
Whoa, calm down! It's me, Tsukino!
Um, I'm sorry about the screaming.
Nah, it was my fault for startling you.
I just happened to see you while I was out investigating.
So, how is Moritani doing?
She's doing real good. Actually...
For
Tomorrow
(Part 1)
"Mori!"
Maybe too good.
Please tell her that we're going to find the real criminal and prove her innocent.
What are you talking about?
You saw my power, right?
I can hear the criminal's thoughts.
Woah, woah. You high school kids definitely shouldn't be messing with this case.
But I've made my decision.
Why? You want to show off your abilities?
My powers have always isolated me.
But...
the people I've met here gave me a chance to change.
Thanks to them, I'm not alone anymore.
That's why
this time, I want to be the one helping them.
Sorry, I don't really follow you.
What?!
Well, it's just that I've never had any friends myself.
How can she be so nonchalant?
But it sounds like they must be good friends, right?
Yes. They're more than I deserve.
I guess, since they seem to have no problem hanging around you.
Friendship sure is incredible.
She's not a bad person. She's just a little blunt.
Isn't she lonely, having no friends?
Anyway, just let the police handle this, okay?
Moritani!
Mori!
I was worried sick!
I'm so grateful you're unharmed, Miss Hiyori!
Are you alive, Kotoura?
Um. I'm sorry for worrying you all.
So you were released because the real culprit struck again?
That's what I heard.
I guess I can't be too happy, since someone else got attacked.
No, it's only natural to feel relieved.
We didn't even get a chance to do anything.
What do you mean?
We were trying to clear your name by finding the criminal ourselves.
Th-That's pretty reckless.
Actually, could we keep up the search?
Are you sure?
Thank you.
So I've been wondering,
where's Manabe?
Well, uh, Manabe is...
Um.
Whoops! Gotta go!
It's my fault Kotoura and Manabe split up.
You know those two will be fine.
So don't get any ideas about taking Manabe for yourself, Moritani!
What?! Of course not!
So Kotoura hasn't picked anything up this whole time?
And the attacks have stopped abruptly.
It's possible the criminal left town.
It's Tsukino.
Hello, this is Kotoura.
Hey there. How's it been going?
Well, we haven't found a thing.
Huh? No, I meant with Moritani.
You're really looking for the criminal?
What did I tell you about that?
It's much too dangerous for you.
Is there even any reason to keep looking for the criminal now that Moritani's been released?
There is.
Please give it up.
And don't let any of your friends go near that 2nd Street alleyway.
We've gotten word that the suspect may still be hiding out there.
Promise me, okay?
Wait, Tsukino!
What did she want?
She knows we're looking for the criminal,
so she warned us to stay away from the alleyway off 2nd Street. It's not safe.
This is our chance!
President Mifune?
No! It's too dangerous!
You can't use yourself as bait!
This is my only chance to get back at everyone
who sneered at the occult and at my mother!
You'll all help me, won't you?
I'm surprised it's so crowded at this hour.
Well, it is the heart of town.
Kotoura?
Kotoura!
I think this was the one named Mifune.
So she really did come.
How?
How does the criminal know President Mifune's name?
"She really did come"? What is this?
Calm down, Kotoura.
Are you sure you heard right?
Muroto! President Mifune is...
Why? How?
Kotoura!
Muroto.
You know where the criminal is?
Yes.
I'm so close, Mom.
Kotoura is a real psychic, just like you.
She's helping me.
We can finally show the world that you were wronged!
So just you watch, Mom.
Mom!
Yuriko!
How do you stand again when something trips you up?
Can truth be found by thinking about the days to come?
We all come into this world alone when we are born,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
Kotoura. I'm done for.
It's only been a few days! What happened to you?!
There...
There...?
There wasn't anything sexy in this episode...
It seems Manabe is suffering from lust withdrawal.
Sadly, there'll be nothing dirty in the next episode either.
Episode 11
Stand  By  Me