Good luck, Tanaka Taro!
As a member of The Dollars, I'll hold onto this.
You're acting pretty tough despite Harima Mika being gone.
How does this thing die?
Did you hear? There's been another
incident involving The Slasher in Ikebukuro.
Then I'll have to make a war break out that only I can cause.
Right?
I've had it!
Welcome, Welcome!
It's Russia Sushi!
It's good!
It's cheap!
Eat sushi!
The Slasher...
...struck again!
How many people does that make?
This is the scene where yesterday,
protests against The Slasher took place.
Six months ago, a large-scale gathering
occurred suddenly in downtown Ikebukuro.
And The Slasher incidents began at about the same time, didn't they?
Also, amongst teenagers, something called the "headless rider" has—
America has already made contact with the headless rider and wants—
The Slasher?!
The headless rider...
I'm so scared!
Something is born and something disappears every day in this town.
No way!
But...
It's good to eat.
Even so, nothing happens. Nothing changes.
Really?
The Dollars?
That's...
Her everyday life.
Everything about our love is fake.
Yet it's stronger than the real thing.
I love the wound on your neck.
How is that wound connected to true love?
I love you, Seiji.
I love everything about you with all my heart!
I get jealous every time I see them.
Then just don't watch them.
If you see a beautiful girl, you look at her—and talk to her.
That's what's been embedded in our DNA as part of Team Boys, right?
Don't lump me in with you...
However, don't worry.
My body may belong to everyone, but my heart is yours alone, Anri.
Eh?!
I've always thought, "Just how can Anri be so erotically cute?"
E-Eh?!
She's not erotic.
She's not erotic, Masaomi!
I sheee.
Eroticism aside, you do admit that she's cute.
Eh?
Uh, well...
Oh? Then you're saying she's not cute...?
Sh-Sh-She's cute!
She's cute, but...!
I see. So, you acknowledge that she's cute.
Yet I also acknowledge that she's erotic.
In other words, acknowledging Anri's eroticism
means I better understand and love her more deeply.
This battle finally...ends with my victory!
Why do you get to decide everything all by yourself?!
You lose, Mikado!
Six months ago, a small disturbance occurred.
Everyone was talking about it all over town, and even in school.
However, it didn't have anything to do with her.
She's not even interested in it.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Thank you.
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's...her everyday life.
Huh?
Man, I'm glad I had some points saved up.
Hurry it up.
What're you going to do about the poster?
She's in a hurry.
What's with her? She's riding around even more than before.
Yeah, she is.
I'd want her to be a little sneakier about it, wouldn't you?
It'd be perfect if we were the only ones
to know, like finding out a rich girl's secret.
Like "Nogizaka Haruka's Secret."
You two...
Don't be like that.
They've got their own problems.
And her, too.
Hey, look!
It's the headless rider!
This is Celty Sturluson's everyday life.
It was...something she was used to.
People who're drawn into the abnormal tend to panic.
In that instant, she easily escapes.
That was how Celty Sturluson did things.
But...
I've always thought...
"In the manga or movies in which someone like
you would appear, we're always made to play the fool."
Whenever the superpower-wielding protagonist enters, we're always
face down in pools of blood, dramatizing how strong his opponent will be.
That's fine...
Since it means we're considered that strong.
It's something you can't help during production.
But there's one thing I'd like to say.
If a real monster, evil psychic, cyborg, or ninja were to appear...
I'd have one thing...
...one thing to say:
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you monster.
I'll say it again.
Don't underestimate traffic cops, you monster look-alike.
Celty!
Welcome—
What? What's wrong?
Being embraced by you is an honor deeper
than the deepest oceans and wider than the sky.
Uh, I guess that doesn't quite work.
Hey, you're shaking...
Really, what's wrong?
Celty...
I-I-It was so scary!
It was so scary, Shinra!
Th-Th-The police nowadays are monsters!
The police?
A pack of ten or eleven white and
silver vehicles chased me down and...
So, you're saying a huge group of people on white bikes came after you to challenge your authority?
I have heard there's a problem officer named Kuzuhara Kinnosuke, who often causes accidents by over-pursuing offenders.
I was so scared.
I really was.
I was too conceited.
From now on I'll live modestly, so please forgive me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Who're you apologizing to?
Showing vulnerability isn't like you, Celty.
Although, if you were to show it to me in bed—
Don't say such embarrassing things at a time like this.
Okay. That's fine.
Anyway, I'm sorry about that, but...
Could you go meet someone for me?
No, it's not a job.
My...father's come back.
Jeez...
He could just catch a taxi...
He was pretty meddlesome back then, but...
Hey, hey, hey!
What's that?
Say something!
He's pretty white.
Too white...
Oh, man...
What's with you, geezer?
He's wearing a pretty cool outfit.
Right, Horada?
You three.
Don't you think the air in Tokyo is dirty?
Huh?!
It seems like that dirty face of yours would normally
serve as excellent protection, but in this filthy air...
Hey, it looks like this geezer's full of himself!
Meh, it doesn't matter.
It looks like the time has come to teach you about the power of adults.
Under the Juvenile Act, you can kill people and still be protected.
Or I assume that's what you think.
Remember this!
When you try to kill someone, you'd better
be prepared to possibly get killed by—
I guess you are full of yourself, geezer.
I'm over twenty years old!
Wait a minute.
This really hurts, and I can't run away because you're stepping on my feet..
I'm being finger-stabbed!
What're you doing, Celty?!
Huh?!
Help me now!
Huh...?
I really don't want to help him...
Don't you realize that the reason I acted so bold with
these people is because I felt safe when I saw you?
Horada, this's the black biker.
What?! Are you serious, Higa?!
Yeah, I saw her on TV.
Weren't you at that Dollars thing six months ago?
Man, everybody's tryin' to act tough here on our island.
What's up?! Say something!
Huh?!
Huuuuuuuuh?!
Huh?
What is this?!
Yep, that was the right response.
Great, it's not broken.
It's so important to me because I got it from Shinra.
Did you see that?
This is the power of adults!
Nope, I'll never like him.
Is there any meaning to using these?
Just what kind of rules do you use?
Russia Sushi, Russia Sushi!
Boss...
Oh, Izaya!
Yo. You're working as hard as ever, I see.
You've been coming to Ikebukuro a lot lately.
If you're here, you should stop by the restaurant.
I just opened up the canned goods this morning.
The ingredients are so fresh!
Sorry, but I'm busy with some stuff.
Maybe some other time.
"You can't hide an awl in a bag."
"Don't talk about ropes in a house where someone hanged himself," was it?
Alright, let's say what we like about
Anri to show who understands her better.
I'll go first. Her eroticism!
You're going to start with that?!
Stop talking about erotic stuff.
Those who laugh at eroticism will be reduced to tears by it.
That doesn't make any sense.
This was her first experience being friends with boys.
Anyway, Mikado, what do you like about Anri?
Well, I...uhh...
Well, to be exact, she'd probably never been friends with anyone before.
"There's nothing good about Anri...poo poo." Is that it?
I didn't say that!
Then tell me. Right now! Quickly!
In the past, she was only around to make Harima Mika look good.
Three, two, one!
But that was fine.
That was her place.
However...
Now that she's lost that place, she's been unable to find a new one.
Okay, in order to prove how erotically
cute you are, Anri, let's all go pick up girls!
What kind of logic is that?!
By "pick up," you mean...
It'll be fine.
Anri's the trap to make them think, "Oh, there's a girl here, so it'll be okay to go off with them," so she doesn't have to do anything.
W-W-Wait a minute, Masaomi!
Alright, let's go! Everyone, follow me!
Get set, and...bang!
Let's do this!
K-Kida...
Masaomi!
Do you really think it's okay?
It's fine. He'd just be hitting on girls by himself anyway.
Honestly...
What a pain.
I have to make a big scene about it since you're so shy.
I'm such an incendiary man.
Umm...
She did notice that the two boys loved her.
However...
Uh, the sunset's really pretty, isn't it?
Eh?
Uh, but there are some weird clouds over there...
It might rain later, so be careful.
You're right.
Umm...
Eh?!
What?
This is it for me.
Eh?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Uh, yeah, see you tomorrow...
The sunset was a bad idea.
She probably couldn't answer, no matter who confessed to her...
Because she still liked Harima Mika.
The two of them are so similar...
That the girl still doesn't understand the difference between friendship and love.
What do Harima Mika, Ryugamine Mikado, and Kida Masaomi mean to her?
Can we get you to change your answer?
We really do need you...
I've told you, I have nothing to do with this anymore.
This isn't where I belong.
I don't plan on coming back...to your side.
Really?! That's so funny!
There've been a lot more people wearing yellow around town recently.
Yellow?
That's so true. They stand out more than
The Dollars because you can tell who they are.
Oh, are you talking about The Yellow Scarves?
You know them, Setton?
Yes, well...
They've been around for a while.
And The Yellow Scarves are...
They're an old gang in Ikebukuro.
They disappeared after getting into a fight with another gang.
Ahh, I've heard that story before.
Does this mean they're back together?
Ikebukuro's all up in arms again.
Seriously. And the police are scary, too.
I'm serious.
Don't underestimate the police.
The police?
Aw, she fell down.
How lame.
All you did was kick her a bit.
You're such an idiot.
That's cuz she's a parasite.
What's with the face?!
It doesn't look like The Slasher Case will be solved anytime soon.
Speaking of that, have you heard?
There's a rumor that The Slasher is in The Dollars.
There are rumors that the headless rider is, too.
Eh?! Who's spreading that?!
I doubt it's true.
All joking aside...
You really should be careful of The Yellow Scarves.
Some of them don't take too kindly to the fact we expanded our influence while they weren't around.
Is that so...
Alright, I'll be careful.
Honestly...
You sell yourself to Ryugamine and Kida after Harima, and then Nasujima on top of that?!
How many people are you going to sell your body to until you're satisfied?
You whore!
All you can do is live off of someone else, you parasite.
Parasite!
She wondered, "Maybe what those girls are saying really is true."
She used to be dependent upon Harima Mika.
And she might still be...
What're you bein' all quiet for?!
Say something!
What? Parasites don't have mouths?!
Now she might be dependent upon those two boys...
...trying to find her place amongst them.
You reek, parasite!
Don't ever come to school!
It's your fault I've lost two boyfriends!
What're you spacing out for?!
She'd gone about protecting her heart and body in this way.
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's her everyday life.
Your house is nearby, isn't it? You should let us in. We'll search it for you!
Hurry up and take us there!
You better do it if you wanna make up for what you've done!
Saika has entered the chat room.
It's here!!
Ah...
Huh?
I cut.
I want to cut.
I'm the one who wants to cut you!
I cut.
I want to cut.
Wrong.
Is this the person who was spamming any
message board related to Ikebukuro six months ago?
Wrong.
Weak, wrong,
Can't, control
You haven't banned this person yet?
Weak, wrong,
Can't, control
Desire, is, want
I did!
It doesn't work, no matter how many times I do it!
Desire, is, want
Love, not enough, love
Oh, I see.
Want, love, people
I banned the IP address, but they just use a different host and come back.
More, strong, love, want
Ah, you mean a proxy?
Desire, I, mother, mother
Hmm, it doesn't look like it's a proxy...
More, strong, love, want
Desire, I, mother, mother
Wow, that's scary.
[Mother]
Nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's her...
The Slasher is somewhere in this city.
Every time an incident occurs, fear awakes and
spreads rumors along a heavy and stagnant night breeze.
However...
Next Time: Uproar.