Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
along with my food!
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
but sorry for finding out!
gomennasai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
Getting lost in silly conversations
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Chatting about love and relationships
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Say, why can't you make friends?
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
You came right out and asked?!
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You two never quit!
iitai houdai ne
The three leaves are on a rampage,
mitsuba ga daibousou
and there's nobody who can stop them!
dare ni mo tomerarenai
I thought it was called
"miso" or "malt" or something like that.
To keep the nasty pests
from staring at Miss Youko,
we'll strike
quickly and stealthily.
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
issei no mae mitekou
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
mae mae miteru
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
Three heads are better than one!
sannin yoreba monju no chie
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
Everything's going my way,
hora going my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
susumesou my way
Let's go full steam ahead
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
I'm living the best days of my life,
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
I'm sure that this is a
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
Wow!
It's the ocean!
The beach is
a summer necessity!
It was worth
waking up early for this.
This is my first time having
a view of the ocean from a train.
Ah, because you're a rich girl, huh?
She was one.
At the beach, we've gotta...!
Relax by the water?
Make sandcastles?
And split a watermelon!
But...
Yeah...
We came here to work, huh?
Veggies,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, and Fish
Summer.
Summer means the ocean!
And the ocean means a beach hut.
This August, I present:
Himitsu no Hanazono, beach hut version!
Working at the original
is hard enough...
And now there's
a beach hut version.
Don't worry.
Mitsugu came across
this fine location for me.
Yamaji...
Always there to serve.
Of course, the shop
is closed for today.
That's not what we're worried about.
Wait, I've been wondering this for a while,
but what's "Himitsu no Hanazono"?
It's the name of my shop.
What?!
Oh!
Secret Garden... is English
for "Himitsu no Hanazono"!
Did you know, Miss Youko?
She ought to know the name
of the place where she works.
Um...
Well, I thought it was called
"miso" or "malt" or something like that.
Those are totally wrong.
It's a Western cake shop!
Well, if it were based on Sonobe,
it should be called "Den of Thieves"...
...or "Shop of Chaos."
As I said, it's "Himitsu no Hanazono"!
Same difference.
Quite right.
It's completely different!
It's perfect for someone
stuck in the '80s.
Oh, Yamaji.
So you knew, Yamaji?
Yes.
Every time I get a receipt,
I cringe with embarrassment.
Anyway, from today we'll be
Himitsu no Hanazono, beach hut version!
Oh, I have a question.
What is a beach hut?
M-Miss Youko...
Are you serious?
Th-That's right!
Of course Miss Youko wouldn't know.
You're a rich girl
who knows nothing of the world.
I-I've at least heard of them before!
I just don't know
exactly what they are.
Sonobe!
Explain to me, in plain terms,
what a beach hut is.
Huh?
With interpretive dance!
Waves.
Wind.
I don't understand. Not at all.
In that case,
I don't think I can work.
Sand! I am sand.
Uh, what is this?
Some kind of ritual?
W-Well, we've come
all the way out here.
And she said she'd pay us.
I suppose there's no other choice.
Then let's get changed!
Yes, let's.
Yeah, let's go!
Truthfully, I didn't approve
of this beach hut idea.
I'm getting excited!
There's nothing good about
getting sunburns and heat stroke.
To keep the nasty pests
from staring at Miss Youko,
we'll strike
quickly and stealthily.
I see. Good luck.
And I was playing—
Yum! What is this? It's so good!
Wow, it's delicious!
I'll have the melon
and orange ones too!
Oh, but I want to try all of them!
What's that? It sounds good.
I want to try it too!
It's so obvious she's a fake customer!
And I'm stuck
helping out again as usual.
Thank you very much.
Please work hard so that
nasty pests don't notice Miss Youko.
I think she'll be fine.
What is it?
You seem dissatisfied.
Well, you look different
from what I had imagined.
I do?
Yes.
I had imagined...
Summer!
Under the bright sun!
A summer time for girls
bursting with youth!
The seductive lure
of a flushed body.
A paradise of sweets
by the shore!
Himitsu no Hanazono.
Now open, this summer
at the beach hut.
Mwah!
Something like that.
Absolutely not.
Old-fashioned, as usual.
And you could get sued
for that disguise at the end.
If you could at least wear something
like Hayama or Futaba...
I don't want
to get an unsightly tan.
How about working
in a bikini to avoid that?
I'll make your uniform a bikini.
Sonobe, you can wear a bikini.
This place is more like
a fancy café than a beach hut, huh?
That's true.
We'll have a summer menu
with gelato, frappés, and gelatin desserts.
What about ramen?
Curry? Fried noodles?!
We're a dessert shop.
Aren't fried noodles a dessert?
What? It's not a side dish?!
Himitsu no Hanazono!
Open today. Himitsu no Hanazono!
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Man, what an
embarrassing name for a shop.
Should we try somewhere else?
What's that?
Youko! Youko!
Youko!
Yuu?
I heard that you were
working at a beach hut.
I'll help with sales.
Just give me
some of everything!
Oh? But the whole menu
is ice cream and drinks.
Oh, really?
What should I do?
Need some help there?
Maybe it's not a good idea.
I'm cold after eating so much.
You don't have to push yourself.
But you made this. I'll finish it all.
Here's the peach lassi.
What?
Thank you for waiting!
Youko wasn't
the one making them?
Hmm?
So immature.
He's really immature.
Just because you're an adult,
doesn't necessarily mean you're mature.
I thought you were aware.
Yup.
It's true.
Closed
for the day.
Today was our pre-opening,
so I closed up early.
Thank you for your work.
We were only open for half the day,
but sales were excellent.
It was harder than I expected.
And very hot.
We're not used to it.
I've prepared a barbecue to restore our energy,
since tomorrow will be a full day.
Meat?!
Meat!
I-I want some too...
Are you all right, Yuu?
I'm fine. That much food
is nothing for a man like me.
Especially if you'll
cook the meat for me...
Everyone, the food's ready!
What?!
You really never learn.
So immature.
Wow, so enthusiastic.
Apologies.
Is my cooking not to your liking?
No, I just don't feel like eating it.
Well, I didn't
feel like eating anyway...
We'll have some, then.
Let's eat!
Food is so revitalizing
after hard work.
Yamaji! Grill with the ratio of veggies,
meat, meat, meat, meat, meat, meat, and fish!
Right...
There go today's profits...
Teru!
Wow, it looks so yummy!
Big Sis!
You were up early
for work today, huh?
I came to help...
What? We're done already.
Your sister is very kind.
Would you like some too?
I'm jealous since I'm an only child.
Yeah, thanks!
You've told me that before!
Oh, it's the little boy!
H-Hello!
You're not going to eat any meat?
That's not good.
You won't grow bigger.
I know! I'll make some for you.
Oh... Thank you very much.
Yuu...
This might be the last straw.
Oh no, barbecue should be fine.
Did you know that raw meat
has more vitamins?
I'll call an ambulance, just in case.
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Here's your mango frappé.
This is our last day working here.
We made it through somehow.
But we didn't get to play at all,
even though we're at the beach!
We haven't done anything but work.
Thank you both
for accompanying me this whole time.
Still...
You got tan, Futaba.
More like burnt.
Well, it's summer!
Even so!
Summer means curry!
Aren't I kinda like curry?
You're okay with that?
Anyway, I have a farmer's tan now,
so I wanna even it out.
We'll be done working,
so let's go all out and play tomorrow!
We haven't been in the ocean,
so we need to seize the opportunity!
You're right.
I'm pretty much done with homework,
so let's have fun for the rest of summer.
H-Homewor—?
I'm not sure I know that word.
We've got a reflection essay
for Modern Japanese. Can you handle that?
Well then, I'll prepare lunch
for you as thanks.
Really?
Do you have any requests?
Barbecue!
We had that the first day.
But what's the beach
without barbecue?!
There's more to the beach than that!
How about curry?
I've got enough curry
just looking at you.
You can leave it up to me, then.
Aw!
Regardless, let's enjoy
the beach tomorrow!
Yeah! There's lots of food in the ocean!
You're going to catch stuff?!
All right!
Let's make the most
out of tomorrow!
SHARK SIGHTED
NO SWIMMING
It depends on the species,
freshness, and how you cook it.
What are you talking about?!
Aw, man!
What the heck? I can't go swimming!
How disappointing.
If only it were a dolphin
instead of a shark.
Yeah, really...
Youko!
Yuu!
You're not working today, are you?
You can play, right?
That's what we thought...
There's a shark—
Not to worry!
Southern Sea Resort Hotel
I've got tickets
for the hotel pool.
Southern Sea Resort Hotel
So let's go there!
Oh, can we?
Yeah!
Can we barbecue there?
I said it's a hotel.
Wow!
A pool!
It's so pretty!
This is all thanks to you, Yuu.
Don't mention it.
It's really been a while since
I've gone to a pool with Teru.
Y-Yeah...
Now, make sure to stretch.
Here's a floatie.
It's like you came with your mom.
Oh yeah,
where's Sonobe?
The food is taking
longer than expected.
She said she'd
meet us for lunch.
All right, Youko, let's pla—
Futaba!
Sakura.
Usuda, what're you doing here?
Oh yeah.
He's not good at dealing with Sakura.
I just happened to come here
with my family. Hm?
Yuu!
I found you!
The damage was probably
more emotional than physical.
I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Wait, Sakura went with him!
Oh...
Miss Youko, be nice to him next time.
I suppose I should.
Now, let's enjoy the pool!
Yes!
We'll enjoy it enough
for Yuu too.
Wow, this is amazing!
Hotel pools are great!
Stop already. It's embarrassing.
But it's so cool, Nishiyama!
Your swimsuit
is pretty amazing too.
Th-This is normal!
By the way, it's amazing
you got free tickets for this pool.
Someone gave them to me.
Really?
They're from Hayama's sister.
What?!
H-How did that happen?
You see...
It's so heavy!
Excuse me.
Do you need a hand?
Really?
So that was Hayama's...
Then she gave me
the tickets she won!
I can't really enjoy myself
with that in mind.
Well, it's not like
she's here or anything.
Oh, it's Hayama and the others!
What?!
They're having a good time...
Just... ignore them.
They're having a good time.
Ignore them.
Got some turban shells!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Oh, Nishiyama.
I'm practicing catching sea urchins
and abalones and stuff.
Don't do that here!
Yeah. It's against the law
unless you're a fisherman.
That's not the problem here!
Ah, you two—
Oh, Nishiyama?
Why are you always following me?
No way, do you like me?
Don't make up gross things like that!
Oh, it's the nice girl from before.
Oh, Hayama's sister.
Even her sister's here.
Is she your friend too?
Nishiyama is just my classmate.
Oh, right! Since we're all here,
let's play together!
Wai—
I-I have some friends here...
Huh? You do?
Come on, let's go!
Nishiyama!
Now, I'll go finish my sandcastle—
Teru!
You should swim too!
Y-You know I don't know how...
Ah, you can't swim, huh?
Is that true?
It'd be pretty scary
if something happened, huh.
Like if your boat sank
in the middle of the ocean.
That's true!
Let's practice swimming!
It might come in handy someday.
When would it come in handy...?
There!
Right now?!
You can do it, Teru!
Th-The sisters definitely
share a certain resemblance.
Come on, Teru.
You need to try harder.
No way! I can't!
Hayama, you don't like the water?
No, I just can't swim.
I've lasted this long
without knowing how to swim.
I'm fine just the way I am.
Hayama...
Teru...
Then let's go practice
in the kiddie pool!
No!
You can do it!
Please try your best.
Girls!
I brought lunch.
Oh, Sonobe.
I'm saved.
You sure took a while.
Sorry; it took me a while
since it was such a new experience for me.
Lunch is served.
I've been waiting for this!
Yeah, it really took a while
since it was a first for me too.
By the way,
why are you both beat up?
It was just harder than expected.
And it was wild.
But we managed to get
a hold of a rare ingredient.
Rare ingredient?
Oh, I don't think that shark
will be bothering us anymore.
Though I still don't recommend swimming,
since there are a lot of jellyfish.
Oh my, is that so?
Don't tell me...
Delish!
You ate it?!
It's ground meat.
They seem like good friends.
Swimming does make you sleepy.
You can use me as a pillow too.
N-No thanks.
Go ahead, you can lean on me.
Th-That would be improper.
I can't eat another bite...
Sounds right.
Was she sleep talking?
She's probably having a feast
in her dream right now.
So, I can have a feast if I sleep?
No, that's not...
Go to sleep. Go to sleep!
Sleep. Sleep.
I don't think you can sleep
if you're that focused.
Go to sleep. Sleep.
Sleep. Sleep. Go to sleep.
Miss Youko...
Sleep. Go to sleep.
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if it's turned black inside
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if I can't be extravagant
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
ryou ga ookutemo
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
sannin dakara tabechaou
I'm not wasting electricity at night
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Things that make me smile?
egao ni nareru mono
Food! Money! And things I can't say
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
Let's have fun and make silly memories
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
Will continue forever in just the same way
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
If you want to know the answer to one times three
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
Then come on over here
nee koko ni oide
Mumble
I can't eat another bite...
Well, I probably can.
Seriously?
I cannot. I cannot eat any more.
I'll take the rest to go.
I can't?!
Wah~
Next
Time:
Ten Yen Short
Next
Time:
Ten Yen Short
A nightmare.