Sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
Well, Nagase, you're pretty popular, so I thought you already had a boyfriend,
but I heard you didn't give anyone chocolate on Valentine's Day.
So...
A-Actually, I've...
liked you for while now.
Just stop.
You don't need to keep going.
Why?
Do you hate me that much?
No, I don't hate you.
Then why are you acting
so differently from usual?
You're usually smiling and beaming
.like the sun, and everyone likes you.
I get it now.
So you like that Nagase and
not the one you see now?
Um...
You don't know anything about me.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Something just isn't right.
This isn't it.
I can't do it anymore.
It's too hard.
Impossible.
I can't.
Liar.
No.
I'm definitely not a liar.
Definitely.
Definitely not.
But...
my ideals and reality only grow further apart.
I can't keep this up.
I really can't keep this up.
I can't even keep up appearances anymore.
I hear your voice on the wind
like the rhythm of our daily life
You smile impulsively like the sun itself
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Since when can we remember these exciting days?
How to get
points from
the judges
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Inabaaaan!
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Universal Studios
sounds good too
A map that shows
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get
points from
the judges
recommended places
around school
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Inabaaaan!
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Universal Studios
sounds good too
What awaits us past tomorrow?
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
I'm hungry
Inaban's white rabbit
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Let's beat the jazz band!
Frankensteiner!
How about curry doria?
Cheep
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Today connects to brighter days yet
which catch up with us
in a flood of colors
We walk our path through life with strength
and after today know that the light itself is with us
In your smile I can see warmth
Forever and ever
we live through ups and downs here
Let us believe in that and the future it brings about
I heard you gave Shiroyama
a really harsh rejection.
So I did.
How can you be so calm about this?
Are you that full of yourself?
You're always pretending
.to be such a good student.
You're the one who's full of herself.
Whoever confesses to me and whoever I reject are none of your business.
You're really screwed up.
If you ask me, you're the
one who's screwed up.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you...
Even I...
Really...
You what?
You bitch!
You Don't See Anything,
You Don't Understand Anything
Hey, did you hear?
Nagase rejected him.
I still can't believe Iori would say something like that.
It's true!
It's all an act.
She's completely fake.
Hey, Iori.
There's a strange rumor
.about you floating around.
But I don't believe any of that.
I don't think you're that kind of person. They must be making it up.
Then why don't you just let
them say whatever they want?
Just ignore it.
Well, I thought you'd be mad about it.
I ain't even mad.
It's fine. I don't care anymore.
Come on, Iori. You're starting to scare me.
That's just how I am.
Oh.
Well, see you later, then.
Sorry.
Nagase used to be so cheerful and bright.
I guess you think I'm a liar.
We're starting the research today.
We don't have much time,
but let's do our best.
Okay.
Nagase, you've been acting strange lately.
I wouldn't say different, though.
Um, if you're acting like this because you
rejected me, I don't want you to worry about it.
Sorry.
You're stressing over something, aren't you?
I'm no Superman, but I'd do anything for you.
Thank you so much.
I don't need your help!
Don't come any closer to me.
That's how it is.
Let's split up the work.
Should we just dissolve the SCS?
Thanks for calling.
This place is too fancy
.for me to come in alone.
It does look like a good
.place for couples, though.
But seriously, isn't it annoying to have your thoughts randomly heard by other people?
Sorry.
I'm not blaming you or anything.
That's just how it is.
Inaba.
What did you mean by that?
About dissolving the club?
It's something I've been
.thinking about for a while.
Heartseed looks at us five as toys for him to control and amuse himself with.
Perhaps if we no longer gather together, these episodes will finally stop.
So we'd disband to put an end to all this?
We can't be sure, though.
Iori's been acting a bit strange
lately, don't you think?
It's starting to negatively impact the class.
Iori's reputation is only going to
.tank as these episodes continue.
Then...
If we split up, everything'll go
back to normal, including Iori?
Is that what you really want, though?
Okay, fine. You got me.
I still want everyone to stay together.
As if I'd want to dissolve the club.
I thought so.
Since when were you so perceptive?
I feel the same way you do.
I want everyone to be together forever.
No matter what happens.
It's only because of the
.SCS that I met all of you.
There's still so much more I want
.to do together with everyone.
Together with you.
Could you say that again?
That last part.
Together with you?
With the same passion you had before!
Together with you!
Never mind that whole disbanding thing, Iori's still getting worse.
I want to believe she'll return
..to normal with time, but...
I feel like I haven't been able
.to be there for her at all.
Me too.
I thought I understood her
.better than anyone else.
If I hadn't come in between you guys,
then maybe things would've worked out between
.you two, and Iori wouldn't've turned out like that.
I don't think so.
It's all because I couldn't
.understand Iori's feelings.
In either case, I'd have ended up rejected.
It's not your fault, Inaba.
It's my fault for getting rejected!
What's wrong?
I got rejected!
What? What's wrong?
Rejected! Rejected! Rejected!
Okay!
What are you doing?
I wanted to clear my head of some stuff, so I tried shouting it out.
I can't carry all that baggage forever.
I have to face it, accept it,
.think on it, and move forward.
Wow, you're actually kinda cool...
even though you got rejected.
Even though you got rejected.
You didn't have to repeat it.
What did you want to talk about?
Please take a seat.
Why so serious?
That's so not you.
Why are you sitting so close to me?!
Why don't you take a seat over there?
What's wrong?
I'm busy too, so make it quick.
You gave me chocolate on Valentine's Day, right?
Yeah, so?
At the time, you said,
"This is my true love chocolate!"
Oh yeah, I remember that!
So?
So? Well, uh...
I love you, but only as my sister!
We're siblings, so that sort of stuff...
You're so funny!
It isn't like that at all.
.You're just my brother.
Oh, I see.
Okay, that's what I thought too,
.but I was just making sure.
Geez. Just how much do you love me?
Well, you are my sister.
Can you lend me your ear?
By the way, that was my first kiss.
I got kissed on the cheek by my little sister!
Gross.
Yamaboshi Academy
Ugh, we have soccer today.
It's torture in such cold weather.
I bet you don't have a problem, Yui, since you're good at all sports.
Even I don't like the cold.
Iori.
Don't talk to me.
What's wrong, Yui?
Iori's always been there for me.
When I didn't go to school because I was depressed, Iori came to visit me again and again.
Iori is kind, cheerful, and dependable.
She's a really wonderful girl.
Right now, it's obvious from her
thoughts that Iori is suffering.
But I don't know the exact reason.
Even though I'm feeling her emotions directly, I can't understand her.
Even though we're sharing the
.same pain, we can't help her.
Student Cultural Society
Did Iori and everyone else feel like this when I shut myself in and them out?
There's no point in just thinking about it.
For now, I have to work hard
for the club presentation.
And for when Iori comes back.
There's a little-known café recommended for dates, a cheap but filling Chinese restaurant,
a shop that sells cute accessories, and...
Isn't it amazing that we got all this information?
Aren't we being too generous by putting everything on a pamphlet and just handing them out?
It's taking too much time.
That's what it's gonna take to beat the jazz band.
Is it okay to keep the lettering of the title like this?
Yeah.
We'll regret it if we compromise on it and lose.
And I don't want to lose.
Yui.
You're the best with your hands, so we won't get anywhere if you don't work hard.
Oh, sorry.
I thought Iori came by.
Nagase isn't coming today either.
Well, there's a lot going on now.
We don't know when and to who our thoughts will be transmitted.
It's only natural.
Even so, we'll...
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm really scared!
Is something wrong?
Did you hear someone's thoughts?
Uh, yeah.
Yui, there's no need to explain.
Yeah, okay.
In any case!
Iori should know that she can come to us for help when she needs it.
So let's just wait for when that time comes.
Yeah.
That's one thing I like about you.
Finally Yui admits her love!
No!
I meant that was the one thing I like about you!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Wh-What's happening?
I can guess what happened.
Aoki's right, though.
We have to work hard in Nagase's place.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go see Iori.
What, now?
I can't stop thinking about it.
I'll work hard tomorrow to make up for today.
Let me go.
What's wrong?
Do you need my help?
I'll be fine by myself.
Inaba's working hard.
I need to get a hold of myself too!
I'm not sure now's the best time, though.
Yeah.
Didn't we just decide to wait for Nagase?
We shouldn't rush things.
It'll be fine.
And you're not one to talk, Taichi.
I feel like this isn't going to end well.
Not for Iori, but for you.
I'll totally be fine.
I've become strong, after all!
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
Something like this happened before too.
It seems the tables have turned, though.
Yeah.
Back then, you saved me.
Now it's my turn to save you.
What do you think about the thought transmissions?
What do you mean?
Like, is it really tough or stressful?
I think it's tough.
Could you be a little more specific?
I want to help you any way I can.
You can't help me.
Hey, what's wrong, Iori?
You used to always smile and cheer everyone on.
Now you're always gloomy.
You helped me out so much, Iori.
If there's anything I can do to get
you back to your usual self, I...
There's nothing to get back to.
Yui, you don't see anything.
You don't understand anything.
But it's not just you.
No one notices the real me.
What do you mean?
I'm tired.
It's hopeless.
I can't do it.
It's not hopeless!
You can do it!
I can't be friends with Yui anymore.
I love you, Iori, and that won't change.
No matter how much I change?
Of course.
Even if everything changes?
What part of me do you want to stay friends with?
If everything about me changes,
there'll be nothing left.
I'll be a different person at that point.
There's all that stuff we've
been through up till now.
Say you were friends with someone in the past.
Can you still stay friends,
even if they fall to the dark side?
Suppose they turn into a vicious criminal.
Shouldn't the other person's
new personality matter?
This isn't the Iori I know!
That's why I can't be friends with you.
So your friend turned to the dark side?
I wouldn't go that far.
She's just a little cynical.
Are you calling me because you got anxious?
Yeah.
I figured someone uninvolved
would be able to advise me on this.
But if you don't tell me the
details, I won't be able to help.
Are you still depending on other people?
She totally called me out.
Good day to you, Ms. Kiriyama.
Oh, it's nighttime, so good evening?
Maybe I shouldn't've tried
.to use unfamiliar greetings.
What's wrong, Ms. Kiriyama?
You don't look well.
What?
Please don't try anything.
I'm stronger than you are.
But I'm sure you've figured that out by now.
What do you want from me?
Ms. Kiriyama,
what do you think of this episode?
Are you afraid?
Afraid that everything in
your heart could be revealed?
Help me!
Yui, where are you?!
Where are you?!
They heard me!
Thank goodness! They'll come save me!
Aoki and Taichi will definitely save me!
Are you still depending on other people?
What are you doing?
Having others hear my thoughts is scary, and I really don't like it.
But I've decided I won't run away anymore.
I've embarrassed myself so many times already.
It doesn't matter what everyone finds out about me.
But I can't just depend on them.
Everyone's doing their best!
So I have to, too!
You shouldn't always ask your friends to save you,
but you can't do everything alone either.
You say, "Let's do our best together!"
It seems like this wasn't the best way to do this.
I'm bored. Maybe I'll stop.
Seems like nothing I say will have an effect.
What are you saying?
I must say, Ms. Kiriyama, you've become strong.
Perhaps you're more boring than Mr. Aoki now.
And that's why you're interesting.
No.
It's enough.
Goodbye.
"Goodbye"?
Kiriyama!
So Taichi's first.
Are you okay, Kiriyama?
Yeah.
Sorry for making you come all this way.
I'm fine now.
He left already.
I see.
Thank goodness.
Taichi, I failed.
At what?
I couldn't reach Iori.
I ended up only making things worse.
Same here.
I was completely rejected by Nagase.
That's not true.
Iori is definitely waiting for you to rescue her.
Taichi, haven't you been a little useless lately?
What happened to the busybody
white knight from before?
And how can you ignore what's
happening to Iori in class?!
I want to do something for her.
But I don't know what she wants.
I failed horribly once already.
What should I...
Stop being so wishy-washy and man up!
Even I don't know what I should do!
I tried my best, but it blew up in my face.
If you fail, then you should think about what do next time so you don't fail.
Calm down a bit, Kiriyama.
I actually have no right to
be lecturing you about this,
but I have to because of the
way you've been acting!
Don't make me do this again, idiot!
S-Sorry.
Did you think I'd accept your apology?
Do you think that's enough?!
Well, I'll forgive you eventually.
Thanks, I guess?
Hey, Kiriyama.
What?
Let's do our best together.
Yeah, let's.
Yui! I'm almost there!
He's always too late!
Or is Taichi's timing just too good?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Today's only gotten worse since I woke up.
I broke one of my favorite hair clips,
I got into a fight with my mom,
I didn't get enough sleep, and I don't feel well.
Yamaboshi Academy
But it's on days like these that
.fate decides to mess with you.
Yamaboshi Academy
Just spit it out already.
We're way past ignoring the problem.
What should you do?
Tell me what you're thinking!
You can hear what I'm thinking, can't you?
I can only hear some of your
thoughts, not all of them!
I want you to tell me with your own mouth!
Everything.
Why should I tell you everything?
Iori, you helped me.
That's why I want to help you.
I don't want to overstep my boundaries,
but we're friends, aren't we?
Friends help each other out, right?
So ask for help already.
Don't push your values onto me.
What... happened to you?
You weren't the sort of
.person to say that before.
You're acting really strange.
You've been like this ever
.since you rejected Taichi.
I understand this has been a
tough episode to get through,
but why?!
Why did you have to reject Taichi?!
I don't get it!
You liked Taichi—
That's what you're pushing onto me!
You want me to speak my mind?
Fine.
I will.
Inaba, you're too selfish.
You're the one I don't get.
You tried to get me and Taichi together and forced me to notice him.
You were almost annoying in your persistence.
When I actually develop some feelings for him, you come in and say that you like him too.
Despite all that, you reject my rejection.
What is it with you?
What do you want?
You're too selfish!
You push us together and then mess everything up when something might happen.
Why are you so cruel?
Have you ever considered my feelings?
What are your thoughts?
Next Time
Determination and Thawing
Shall I make you cry?
Shall I make you scream?
I loved you, Nagase.
Others surprisingly do notice
.when you're trying your best.
...whether we can do the
.presentation with five people.
Why are you trying to do
everything yourself?
I don't deserve to feel
.what everyone feels.
I am lost and confused
and yet I know that someone is holding out their hand for me
Inside the little box I locked
was the taste of a path I thought I knew
One by one I soothe my wounds
and again jealousy, ardor, coldness, light,
rejection and hope,
all become one and I stand screaming helplessly
My feelings are like melting chocolate, black and sweet
My dreams have long since turned to ash
I am weak, and ringing fills my ears and I hear nothing else
Please find me
mi     chi     ra      n      do      m
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
Frankensteiner!
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
Tune in next time!
Yaegashi Taichi
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get points from the judges
A bonus extra for the SCS paper
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
How about
curry doria?
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Inabaaaan!
Cheep
A map that shows
recommended places
around school
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Inaban's white rabbit
Universal Studios
sounds good too