The star fell, Bull.
That is no ordinary star.
That is the tear of a warrior.
What is a warrior?
One who has finished his battle
somewhere on this planet...
A pitiful soul that could not
believe in the Great Spirit...
The report from Callisto
went directly to Sir Vicious.
He is requesting a deal for Red-Eye.
30,000 woolongs per gram.
A total of 7,500 grams.
Why did he specify you as the dealer?
He is a Titan veteran.
We were in the same unit.
Why does he rely on you now?
Callisto is undergoing
a depression right now.
If he can't see the future,
he is sure to worry.
All the more reason to keep
our hands out of that moon.
Vicious, are you not
the one that is worrying?
You have no permission to
make your own decisions.
Regardless of who it is, those who go
against the Van's will are punished.
You believe that I would
betray my own mentor?
Mao's case was merely bad luck.
Lin... You shall go with Vicious.
Yes.
Wang Long!
Callisto is a frigid planet.
Take plenty of winter clothes.
To me, no cold climate is
worth taking precautions for.
It is true that the planet
is warmer than your heart.
Your heart is colder than a snake's skin.
Vicious.
A snake cannot eat a dragon.
I will be fine by myself.
I'll go with you.
Remember this.
If you want to survive,
you must betray me at times.
No, never.
That would go against the Van's will.
Such old-fashioned thinking
makes me nauseous.
Those damn corpses!
I will protect you, for the
honor of the Red Dragon.
Honor, huh...?
Then, it's up to me to slaughter them all!
It's hot...
Where are the others?
What a depressing bunch...
What's with this humidity?
It's so muggy that I can't sleep!
Oh, it's just a breakdown.
"It'd be hard for me to do
if I saw your faces,
so I'm leaving without seeing you
one last time. Please don't look for me."
That wench...
She sucked out all the
antifreeze from the radiator.
It'll be out for at least half a day.
Even if she didn't pull this stunt
we wouldn't look for her. Right?
She emptied out the safe as well.
7, 8, 9... Hello!
Are you really looking for Faye?
1, 0, 1, 1, goodbye!
Are you just wasting time?
Is there anything else to do right now?
--Ooh! Boom!
--You found her?!
I wonder who this is...
Lessee... code name...
Julia!
Where is that coming from?!
Lessee...
Pretty close...
Looks like Blue Crow on Callisto...
Where's it going to?
It got disconnected...
Hey!
But...
Actually, there are no girls in Blue Crow.
Honestly...
Hey, Spike...
Is that it?
Hey!
Hey, wait, Spike!
That's a common woman's name!
What about Faye?
Leave her.
This is a lawless area.
A woman surely can't survive
wandering about all alone!
Feeling sympathetic?
Plenty of sympathy...
for the money she ran away with!
Spike!
--I'm gonna go look.
--What?
I'm gonna look for my woman.
You can look for that other woman.
You're gonna have nothing to do with this?
That's right. We only go so far.
Even if you come back,
there won't be a place for you here.
Can't do anything about it.
I'm sure you're not as lonely now that
you have more strange roommates.
Me?
You stayed here just for that reason?
You're being stupid!
It's been three years since
I teamed up with you.
But I never knew you
looked at me that way!
I was under the impression
that you were the lonely one!
Well we got rid of that misunderstanding.
Good riddance! Now we'll
have more money for food!
I never did understand you,
even to the very end!
I don't understand, either.
So long!
I don't know any woman.
Like I would know!
Not even a rumor?
I have no luck with 'em!
I'd rather be with an armadillo!
Have you heard of the name Julia?
You shoulda said so earlier!
There's one in front of
Tony's place every night!
Excuse me! I'm not Julia.
Ju-li-us! I'm Julius!
Oh, I see...
Hey, you're my type.
Wanna hang out with me tonight?
I'm sorry, I already have plans.
Oh, yeah. Gren might know something...
I've seen him with a woman before.
Gren?
It's cold.
Looks like this is it for tonight.
Oh, a customer?
Not even. Can't you tell he's straight?
Come on, let's switch locations.
Hey, who and where is Gren?
So you wanna hang out with me tonight?
He's a sax player in Blue Crow.
Take care.
That was close.
When someone sneezes and
doesn't get told to take care,
that person becomes a fairy...
That's what they say around here.
Then it's okay.
I'm already a fairy.
I'm not as easy as I appear to be.
Unfortunately, I am not
interested in women...
Oh, that's a shame...
But the others seem to be highly interested.
You didn't know that there
were no women in this town?
So I'll be very popular...
You should watch out...
Thanks for the warning.
I'm searching for something...
There's nothing here.
The only things are stale bread,
a broken-down car, and rancid booze.
--I'm looking for a guy named Gren.
--No idea.
I see.
Hey, you need something?
You're Vicious, right?
Me?!
Where's the money?
If ya don't put out,
it won't do ya any good!
This is annoying...
So annoying it's repulsive!
What the hell do you mean?!
Why the hell am I Vicious?
There was info that there was
gonna be some deal for Red-Eye.
From Gren to Vicious.
I thought of taking that cash...
You think I look like I got money?
Foreigners are all rich.
And the code name was Julia?
Heh... Sure sounds like
some easy wench's name!
Yeah... really.
Gimme a Cowboy.
There are no bounties around here.
Bourbon with milk.
Oh, that Cowboy. I knew that.
You can't possibly be a bounty hunter.
So, who's our customer today?
Grencia Mars Elijah Guo Eckener.
That's a long name!
Yeah. He escaped from
military prison three years ago
and the statute of limitations
is about to expire.
And that means?
The bounty is double!
This is a chance you can't miss!
But I kinda feel like we can let him go...
Judy, what are you saying?
He's an escaped convict!
But Punch...
He's very handsome!
Just look at his picture!
Lessee... Oh, come on...
I'm much more handsome than he is...
Punch, I just can't laugh at that joke...
Hey, can you turn that thing off?!
Well, calm down.
I'm sorry, man.
Don't worry. That guy
passed out over there is a cop.
What do ya wanna say?
Actually, there's a bounty on my head, too.
This place is a hideout for people like that.
I see...
So you can rest assured.
Me?
What's with this?
I wanted to get rid of all this
frustration, and nobody's coming?
Oh... you're all here.
Miss, your appearance is
rather harmful to the eyes.
Or are you enticing us?
Yeah, I am...
Hold on a minute.
If I don't do this, I'll chip a nail...
Okay, any time now!
You wench...!
Hurry!
Why did you bring me here?
Because you said you're a fairy.
Why did you come with me?
'Cuz I got no place to stay.
You can trust me that easily?
You said you weren't interested in women.
I might take your money and kill you...
That's fine.
I've lived longer than I seem.
It's broken.
You came to such a slummy
neighborhood all by yourself?
I'm alone.
I don't want comrades...
and it's not worth having any.
I end up worrying about
things I don't have to...
You know, 'cuz I'm such a good woman...
All the guys end up fighting for me.
They often say that
humans can't live alone...
But you can live pretty long by yourself.
Instead of feeling alone in a group,
it's better to be alone in your solitude.
When I'm dealing with them,
it's nothing but trouble...
And I don't get squat out of it...
So it doesn't matter if I'm there or not...
You just got scared of losing them.
So you distanced yourself from them.
You're weird.
Think so?
I don't know why I'm
talking to you about this...
I feel like I'm in a confessional...
Have you ever had
experience as a minister?
No...
Take care.
You want to take a shower?
No thanks.
I don't know where
peeping toms might be...
You shouldn't peek, either.
Hm, I can't guarantee that.
Gren... You're not there?
Vicious?!
I'm out with "honroutou."
Along with the "mangan" and the
"ura-dora," it's 32,000. I'll be waiting.
Are you dating Julia behind my back?
Sir Spike!
Hey, Lin. You've gotten pretty big.
He used to work under you,
but things are different now.
I feel sorry for her. Having her name
used for some crooked deal like this.
You were always the one
leaving others out of the loop.
We still haven't settled
the score from earlier.
Any time.
Lin!
Get out of the way, Lin!
Julia was here, in this town.
Hey, out of the way, Lin!
Lin...
A woman?
Wh-Which are you?
I am both, but I am neither.
Too much time has passed by...
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Sitting in muddy water...
...isn't such a bad life...
...if it ends after the first time...
Hey... How are men and women different?
Hmm... I think women are hiding
more vital things than men are.
Yeah... but there are women
that aren't feminine.
And there are men that aren't masculine.
What about those that
aren't normally feminine,
but show that side on
some chance circumstance?
I like that.
Oh?
I'm not talking about you.
Then who?
Maybe it's Ed!
Next episode: "Jupiter Jazz (Part 2)."
"Jupiter Jazz (Part 2)"
Maybe it's me.