And so, on a sunny and calm Sunday morning…
Go on, go home.
We have brought you home.
I guess it’s more natural for you to be in the forest.
Anya, sorry about this, after all the trouble you went through to catch it.
It’s okay. I wanted you to meet one anyway, so it’s fine.
Alright, go.
Uh, um… hold on!
Negi-sensei!
Aah! Stop! Stop!
He can’t follow you.
It wants to be with Negi-kun!
I think it likes Negi!
Eeh?
Wha…?
Negi has become a Chupacabra once, so won’t he have the scent of a friend?
Anyway, you can’t bring Negi with you.
Go home yourself.
We will come over and visit again!
Bye bye!
Laters!
Take care.
Negi…
That is…
What’s that, Negi?
He’s close.
Father is nearby!
Don’t say you are alone!
We will definitely meet each other again!
By Negi.
No. This is my problem.
EEERRRRK! NO WAY!
Everyone…
After you hear that, shouldn’t you be saying “You’re right!?”
She’s right, Negi-sensei!
We’re your partners after all!
Let’s find your father together!
And I was wondering why we should be gathering in class.
Negi, understand?
It’s important to trust your partners too!
Onee-chan.
You might not like what would happen if you refuse.
Anya.
Aniki, you should gratefully accept their powers.
Chamo-kun.
Alright. Understood.
Contract, activate!
Whoa! I really transformed!
It feels kinda embarrassing, doesn’t it?
Woah, I’m surprised, we became Chinese fairies!
That’s true! It’s awesome!
And now, for the Sukas.
Asuna-neesan.
Konoka-jouchan.
Nodoka-jouchan
And also…
The cheerleaders.
Chizuru-chan.
Natsumi-chan.
The rest are all cosplay…
There are only 3 sukas, aren’t these good results?
It’s by chance though.
Even so, it’s pretty good.
Well, even when making contracts, 31 people sure is a lot.
Why am I even…
Isn’t it good, master?
"The journey requires companions and the world requires compassion."
Don’t force metaphors that don’t work!
Alright, everyone. Sorry for the trouble, but thanks for your help!
Yes!
Alright. Where should we look first, Ojou-sama?
Nipaa~
This is so enjoyable!
Oh man, if this goes on, I want to take her home!
Oh no!
What am I thinking!?
To bring Ojou-sama home!?
Please forgive me, Ojou-sama.
Please forget what I just said!
C’mon, hug me!
Sure!
Eh, I mean, NO! I cannot do that!
My mind is always filled with wicked thoughts!
Huggle!
Please forgive me!
Huggle huggle!
Please spare me!
What are they doing anyway?
Always the comedians.
It’s comedy?
Alright, from here on let’s split into two teams.
Kuu Fei-san and I will examine downstairs.
Makie-san and the rest will do upstairs from here.
Understood!
Come, Kuu Fei-san.
What have you been drinking anyway?
Black vinegar, aru.
It’s good for health, aru.
You look drunk.
I’m not, aru.
Well that’s fine.
Let’s go.
Yeah, aru!
Right, let’s go too!
Father!
By Eva.
Is it alright not to help in the investigation?
Why me?
It’s the Thousand Master.
When we met,
I never thought I’d wield magic.
When I got back I only felt unhappiness.
That which you don’t have in your heart…
What are you trying to say?
That’s…
Cute.
I’m going to get rid of it!
By Asuna.
Look, Negi!
Black Rose?
Black Rose Ba…
You don’t have to do it.
Black mule!
You don’t look like it at all…
This feeling is…
Thousand Master?
That’s shocking!
But, why is it here?
It might be a hint.
A hint?
You mean a "Try and look for me!" thing?
Alright.
What are you going to do?
Ras
Tel
Ma
Scir
Magister!
The light that guides us…
Those who exchange vows…
Spirits of all things of the night…
Show us the path…
To the bonds that we so desire!
Negi… can use this kind of magic?
Yeah. Takamichi taught it to me.
That’s awesome.
Anya…
It looks like a magnifying glass that can see the future, de gozaru.
Fumika is awesome!
This means that…
If we can see the future…
We will be able to see our adult selves!
Oho, that is interesting.
I would like to look at my future, de gozaru.
No problem, desu!
Let me be a wonderful lady in the future, de gozaru!
Eh? What’s going on, de gozaru?
Did something terrible happen in my future!?
Noooo!
Just what do you mean "no!?"
We can’t say!
You can’t say!?
Hello?
Fuuka-san, Fumika-san! Can you hear me?
Oh! Negi-sensei!
Lend me your powers!
Powers?
This is a first.
It sure is!
You girls use your magical powers of deduction and do something about it!
Magical Roger!
So what part of this is magical?
Over here or…
over here and stuff.
Don’t tell me it was a life mistake?
Yeah…
If that were the case, what happened?
Ah, well something was up.
It’s an adult thing…
My future is…
Hey, is it really okay to just disappear?
It’s an emergency.
You want Nodoka to try it?
Consumables should be checked first.
Or you’ll feel insecure.
Here you go.
You’re evil.
It’s just juice.
It’s not dangerous.
Then why don’t you drink it yourself?
I feel sorry for Negi-sensei but…
Before the investigation, I believe we still need to make records of this costume.
Magical girl Chiu is MOE.
There’s no disputing who the number one net idol is now!
Magical Girl begins!
Alright! We will now do a Magical Girl transformation!
Is this really a Magical Girl?
I give up.
Desu~
We’re sorry!
It’s okay.
I was the one who forced you to do it. Please don’t worry about it.
Negi-sensei is kind!
Alright. Let’s try again.
Ras
Tel
Ma
Scir
Magister!
That is…
Konoka!
Secchan, faster!
Yes, Ojou-sama!
Faster!
What was that…
That looks fun…
They completely forgot what they were supposed to do though.
My future is…
Stop right there.
We have risked our lives for cheerleading.
The three of us are the fingers of our teacher!
We are here to cleanse thy dirty soul!
The Misa of Lilian.
Madoka of Yoyo.
Sakurako of the beads.
We, the cheerleaders have arrived!
Alright, hand over that circus girl!
You wish.
Wow. She’s good.
Thank you.
Ryukyu.
Sakamoto Kyu.
STOP FOOLING AROUND AND START YOUR INVESTIGATION!
Yes, Maurice…
OWW!
It got clipped in the crack…
Geez. You’re so clumsy, Yuuna.
Thank you, Ako!
What? Looks like he’s not here either.
Yeah. I wonder where Negi’s dad is anyway.
What are you doing, Hakase?
Well, since you asked…
Whoa, huge.
It’s a plastic model!
This bag seems to contain things that I wished I had, yet they somehow come in an incomplete state.
Wow. It would be nice if we could finish making them.
That’s what I was thinking.
I was thinking that it would be nice if we could build a satellite…
that would be able to search for Negi-sensei’s dad.
Ah, I see. So that’s what this is.
Alright! Let’s start defiling it!
Using the dry brush, let’s make it real.
Just like the German Army!
But it’s a satellite…
Over there. There. Here.
Ah, this is so convenient.
Natsumi…
Ah, we’re still in the middle of an investigation.
Return!
I’m sorry Chizu-nee. Let’s go.
How do you use this anyway?
It’s a serving tray, right?
A magical one.
I know! If we use this to make tea, you’ll be blessed with descendants!
What are you talking about…
Oh, and if you hold it under your armpit your breasts will grow bigger!
I don’t get it.
Grow up! Grow up!
It’s not going to happen!
This is Chilli Sauce?
As expected of Mexican Meat Buns.
It tastes great as a snack.
Why, thank you.
Um, so Takahata-sensei…
I wonder about the Russian one.
Ooh. Piroshki flavored!
This one is great.
What else is there?
Takahata-sensei…
I think it’s time we head back to our investigation…
I see it now…
Eh?
I just thought up a new type of Ramen!
I thought up a name too: Meat Bun Noodles!
So is it a meat bun? Or noodles?
Ah, but it’s great right?
Sensei, well we should be on our way…
Alright.
It’s time to get working!
Satsuki-kun, Lingshen-kun, help me out.
Fight-O!
I see, there are no clues there either, huh?
Come to think of it Misora, that cosplay is… quite awesome.
Oh. I guess so…
Anyway, let’s check out the dorms and search there.
Sure.
I want to use transformation powers but…
We don’t really understand it, so…
Oh well, we’ll forget it for now.
I, too, as an expert, shall assist you.
Thank you, Daddy!
Oh yeah, Maki-chan…
Why do you call Motsu your daddy?
Ah, I’m also wondering why…
If you don’t mind…
Oh. That’s right. I haven’t told you guys about it yet…
Here! This is my Daddy!
It was taken last month. The Latest Version!
Oh? He’s still alive?
He’s alive! Don’t say such ominous things.
What the hell? I was just a bit disappointed.
Don’t say you’re disappointed!
Maki-chan’s daddy is really handsome!
Eh? Really?
But… He doesn’t look anything like him, does he?
Yeah. That’s true.
Completely different.
Really? I thought I looked a lot like Enomoto.
He’s got a really pleasant feeling face, in a good way.
Pleasant looking?
Oh, there!
It really looks like him!
Maki-chan, this dog…
Yes! That’s Daddy!
Don’t tell me, your dog’s name is…
Daddy?
Yes.
Why?
You see, when that dog came to our house…
Daddy!
Such a cute kid.
You have grown.
Daddy!
By your side, as always.
Whenever I call out for daddy, he’s always the one to turn around.
Man, he’s a really troublesome stupid dog.
So, since I had no choice, I gave him the name "Daddy."
Oh. What is it, Daddy?
See you look like him right?
See?
Stupid dog.
Stupid dog!
STUPID DOG!
STUPID DOOOOOG!
Hey, Daddy!
He can even fly…
May he rest in peace in heaven…
To hell with the humans!
Keep it together, Kuu Fei-san!
I know, aru!
This cosplay is drunk, aru!
The more drunk I get the stronger I become!
Getting drunk from black vinegar… Ugh!
Iinchou-san! Do you hear me?
Wah? Negi-sensei?
It’s finished!
Whoa!
For us, it’s the beginning of a great era.
Alright! Let’s try firing it!
Sure!
Hey, so how are we going to launch it?
My ability to seek out a smell?
Yes.
Using your powers,
you can use that black rose…
to find out where my father is.
I understand.
Leave it to me.
I see it!
On the lake shore!
Negi!
In the end, you were bothered by it, weren’t you?
I’m only going for a walk.
Boy…
Father!
Motsu-san.
Shichimi-san.
Master has just left, mya.
Looks like he intended to leave without meeting with you…
So, you guys are…
Thousand Master’s servants, mya.
Well, that was until not too long ago anyway.
From now on, we were ordered to be your servants, mya.
Mine…?
Also, he left a message for you.
"Grow up happily."
Negi-chan.
We’re back.
Wow, we were transformed for a long time this time.
It’s because of Negi-kun’s powers.
He’s still growing, that boy.
Thanks to everyone.
Negi…
Father, I will work hard.
I will work as hard as I can,
and become a magician like you.
So, watch me.
Father.
We’re back.
Yeah. We’re back.
Come on, let’s go.
Everyone’s waiting.
Negi-sensei!
Come, let’s race.
I’m not gonna lose!
Me neither.
I’m not going to lose either.
Go!
The story of the magician has just begun.
With the 31 girls as his beautiful partners, together, they will strive!
For Negi to become a Magister Magi, and aim for his father!
Tel
Ma
Amorista!