Such pretty eyes.
You have pretty eyes
and a smile to match.
Looking to score riches?
I welcome all.
You know the first rule in combat?
To get the first attack.
What an extended greeting this is.
I didn't know that the
sure-shot and master of poker,
the legendary female gambler
Poker Alice was still alive.
If she was still alive,
she'd be 219 years old now.
Of course.
You sure don't look over 200.
Besides, Alice never
lost during her lifetime.
She kept winning, without cheating.
You have a way to prove that?
I hear you are carrying a large debt.
Which do you prefer,
the police, or my establishment?
A prophecy?
Charlie said,
"Only hands can wash hands.
If you want to receive,
you must first give."
Hey, doesn't that mean that Charlie
is telling us to just do it?
Right?
Do you think Charlie Parker
would quote Goethe?
Oh, come on, it's all part
of the dream I had.
The way things go,
I say even the hard-earned
5000 woolongs
will disappear with your dream.
Let me tell you something, Spike.
This is a no smoking area.
You shouldn't play.
Your eyes are too good for this.
They'll kick us out
if you win too much.
Then don't bring me here.
Pray, man.
I'll take one.
Small jack.
I'll play a few.
Must be him.
Nice, Jackie.
The target will sit at a blackjack
table, and lose at a certain point.
Of course, you will help him with that.
And he will hand you the last
chip he has as a dealer's chip.
And what about it?
It's something that'll make your debt as
small as one tiny second in this universe.
Last game.
I'm not lucky, nor am I nimble.
Then what are you?
Generous.
Blackjack.
You got me. I give up.
I'll take this as a memento.
Wait a minute!
Hold up!
Hey, you!
What part of you is generous?
This wasn't the plan I heard!
I thought you were supposed
to give me the last chip!
Why should I?
I played along with you
and your cheats!
Did you hear that?
Cheating!
Is that for real?
The dealer has been cheating!
Can you come with me to the office?
Why?
What do you want?
You piece of...!
Come on.
Does this casino
also run a fitness club?
It's showtime.
Pardon me here.
Spike.
All right.
- Jet.
- That's why I told you not to.
That's not it!
But we gotta split!
I haven't cashed these in yet!
Hey!
He doesn't have it. The chip is a fake.
Neither you nor your boss realize
why we cooked up this whole thing.
If that chip falls into police hands
it's all over!
Boss, we still can't find that broad.
Find her!
Put a reward on her if you have to!
Why is my reward for bringing you back
being trapped in here?
I see. She smells like
money to you, too, huh?
You have got to be kidding.
Jet, how much did you have?
Oh, 200K. Easy.
And who put it all to naught?
What, only 200K?
That's nothing compared to my debt.
Don't you think this is
a bit much for a false accusation?
Well, that mono-carrier
should sell for about 400K.
If you had just given me that chip,
we wouldn't have had a problem.
- Chip?
- Yeah.
Disgusting.
If you give that to Gordon,
he'll give you as much as you want.
Yeah, let's do that.
I don't know any guy named Gordon
nor do I want to
believe your stories.
Wait a minute!
Let's go, Ein.
Are you listening to me? Come on!
- It's a chip.
- Of course it's a chip.
I don't mean that kind of chip.
There's a microchip in this thing.
Amigo! Leave it to us
for bounty information!
Thanks for waiting!
It's time for Big Shot!
- This is--
- So, first up this week is...?
Shame we have to hand her to police.
Doesn't look it, but
- Hey, Spike!
- she's a real mean one. Faye Valentine.
The bounty is a whopping
6 million! A real deal!
- Hey, Jet!
- First come, first served.
Good luck, cowboys!
I've been waiting for you.
First off, let me tell you
that I didn't intend to run.
I trust you. Where are you?
An old fishing ship in the gate.
They have the chip.
So, hurry up and...
What?
Well, we thought we
were being immature.
To leave a young woman
in a place like this.
You aren't thinking
weird thoughts, are you?
No, we thought we'd escort you to a
place more considerate of your situation.
Oh, and where would that be?
The police.
We're sorry that we were so cheap
earlier with the 200K bit,
Faye Valentine.
What, there's a bounty on me?
A whopping 6 million.
What, only 6 million?
How much are you in debt?
Come on, please!
Anywhere but the police!
Only the police would give us money.
My mother's last will was for me
to not be in any place for too long!
Yeah, yeah.
My family have always been Romanis,
wandering about in search of love.
You don't know anything, do you?
That's another term for Gypsies.
Everyone else, like you guys, with no
pride in their lives are called Gadjo.
I'm fine with being a Gadjo.
It's calling me.
The great outdoors is calling out to me.
- You can do all of this with the cops.
- Let's go, Jet.
Oh, fine. I won't run.
At least untie one hand!
I can't even go to the bathroom!
Man, we got one yappy woman here.
Like taking candy from a baby.
More like a small sacrifice
for a large reward.
As Charlie said, "If you want
to receive, you must first give."
I guess what I see in dreams is
worth something once in a while.
What do you think you're doing?
I don't know who you are
but I would like the chip back.
I don't know who you are,
but I refuse.
It's just a chip
that means nothing to you.
Although we can sell what's
in the chip for a pretty penny.
There was a decryption program
called Crypt-Breaker
that was developed by
SIT three years ago.
Rumors say that after its completion,
the programmer was killed,
and the program
went into the black market.
It's a magic key
that can decode and unlock
almost every protection code.
But that program itself was encoded.
So, there was a need to find
the key to open the program.
I heard rumors that both the cops and the
ISSP were parting hairs to find the key.
I never thought I would see it
in a place like this.
You're pretty good.
I used to work in a shady place
called the ISSP.
I'm sure the casino
was to take attention away
from the large sum of money,
and to fool the cops.
You just chose the wrong day.
Of course, this thing is
useless for us as well.
It would only be proper
to give it to the cops.
I'll pay.
300 million.
No, too much. How about 30 million?
Not bad for the price
of a magic key, eh?
All right.
Okay, 6 million turns into 30 million.
The money just keeps growing.
Don't get caught off-guard.
Okey-dokey.
Someone who specifies cash
up front is rare nowadays.
I'm an old-fashioned guy.
All right.
We'll both count to three.
At which point, we release
the magnetic field of the suitcase
and send it that way.
- You toss the chip our way.
- Okay.
I'm trusting you.
When you confirm that we got
the chip, sink that ship.
Roger.
Let's go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Shutters are meant to be opened!
What?
Hi, Gadjo.
Hey, Romani.
- Bye.
- Don't let her get away! Fire!
Shit!
Jet, let's get out of here!
All right!
Get them! Get them!
What the hell are you doing?!
She dropped chaff!
What?
Missiles are approaching!
That wench.
It's only proper to use it.
Guess we have to build up again
from square one.
That's cheating!
It sucks this world is
such an unruly place.
Economic recession everywhere,
making kids lose their minds.
Come on, this isn't the time
to be reading the paper.
Things aboard the Bebop
are becoming even more unruly.
This is nothing.
Look at this, terrorists.
Apparently they want
to blow Ganymede up.
Environmental Protection Society?
Perfect. We can have them
take care of this fleabag.
Next episode: "Gateway Shuffle."
Man, I'm about to lose it.