No!
Takasu-kun, what would you do if I showed you my real self?
Would you... Like me?
Would you?
W-Wait a minute.
I...
Taiga!
Were they there?
Does this not look good? Is Ami-chan's timing bad?
T-This isn't what it looks like!
TA-I-GA!
Minorin!
No one's here!
I wonder where they went.
Why are you hiding it?
Is it... Because you don't want to admit it?
That he let a woman other than Aisaka-san into his room?
H-Hey, don't say it in a weird way!
But...
No buts! Hurry up and tell the truth!
The truth?
You're so bold, Takasu-kun!
H-Hey!
T-Taiga!
Taiga!
Morning!
Taiga-chan, did something happen?
Nothing at all, not to me.
What's for dinner today?
Takikomi rice. One of your favorites, right?
You should've made red bean rice.
Right, ugly bird?
H-Hey, Taiga, what happened earlier...
That was just Kawashima teasing you.
It seems to have made you mad, so...
I'm sorry.
I wonder why you're apologizing!
You're a weird guy, Ryuji.
Inko-chan!
Hold it together, Inko-chan! Stay awake!
Taiga! Wake up!
It's so late...
Ow. Huh?
S-Sorry.
What?
We overslept!
Hurry up and get ready!
What's for breakfast? Why did you wake me up like this today?
No breakfast or lunch!
If we don't leave in five minutes, we'll be late!
If we don't stop at a convenience store, we won't have lunch!
Hey, are you listening, Tai-
I'm listening, you perverted dog. A convenience store, right?!
What's with you? Over something like food, don't get so-
Ouch!
We made it!
You finally came!
Thank you for doing that for me yesterday.
Y-Yeah...
What's that?
Did you fall for my summer look?
Just kidding.
You're in the way, you Stupid Chihuahua.
Oh, I didn't see you, Aisaka-san. Good morning.
Good morning, Kawashima-san.
Already in heat this morning? You're working hard.
Hey, you guys...
Ah, I get it.
Don't get so jealous over something like that.
That was just a misunderstanding on your part.
You're the one who doesn't get it.
Yesterday...
Good morning, everyone!
This could be great for making my arms thin!
Minorin, don't use me for exercise!
Tomorrow is what you've all been waiting for, the opening of the pool!
I'm going to explain the rules now.
Summer is the time of adventurous love!
This is the last battle for me while I'm still in my twenties!
My stomach's getting too fat.
So are my thighs!
My arms are even worse.
You guys...
What the hell are you saying?
It's enough that you're young, dammit!
In this school, swimming is with the guys?
It's so embarrassing!
Why? You're so cute.
You're a model!
What the hell do you have to be embarrassed about?
What? Huh? What? What! What?!
Sensei! Shall we close homeroom now?
Please do that!
Stand!
Taiga, hurry up!
No way, I don't want to buy a swimsuit!
Yours from last year rotted, so you have to!
With swimsuits, you have to wash and hang it out to dry as soon as possible.
I said no!
And why is that here?
But this is the only place that sells swimsuits.
I-It's not like I invited her!
Hey, hey!
This looks like it would suit Aisaka-san!
Maybe it suits her too well!
Calm down, Taiga! People are watching!
Takasu-kun, what do you think of this?
I-It looks really go-
Hey!
What about this?
Is it weird?
It doesn't make me stand out or anything, right?
What's with those long legs! You're practically falling out of them!
Really? I tried to pick a plain swimsuit.
K-Kawashima-san, who made that swimsuit? Where was it?
Over there.
Should we go in matching suits?
Not that!
Anything but that!
Kushieda?
Hey, hey.
Ami-chan is way, way, way too cute!
Ain't it scary?
Even in this really plain swimsuit!
This cuteness, this beauty, this figure!
Hiding it is almost a crime!
Hey, Takasu-kun, you think so too, right?
Hey!
Are you okay, Tai-
What are you do-
I don't know what to do!
What? What's wrong?
I just can't decide.
What's wrong with them?
You can only get dark blue or black.
That's not it! They don't fit!
What about child sizes?
Over my dead body!
Don't say the same thing as that Stupid Chihuahua.
This is pretty small.
The price is reasonable, and the fabric is thick. It's well-made so you can put it in a dryer.
Did you try it on?
That...
I... Tried it, but... Well...
That was kind of okay...
But... It was...
Then this is fine! Right?
Yeah... I guess.
Taiga!
What do you want for dinner?
I'll make whatever you want.
Oh, yeah!
Did you pack for the pool?
Don't forget a towel! A bath towel.
Shut up.
Hey, you.
What are you so unhappy about?
The swimsuit?
Or are you still mad about last night?
No!
Then what?!
I... Can't swim!
That's why!
Something that you can say so easily can't be the real reason!
I'm going to be late!
Hey, wait.
At least drink this.
Thanks, Ryu-chan.
What's that?
It's Ryu-chan's Special Soy Milk!
Isonobonbon in soybeans makes your breasts bigger!
That's isoflavone.
It wouldn't be good if they started sagging.
Yacchan's smart!
Taiga-chan's a pervert, sketchy, touchy!
Don't sexually harass other people's parents!
I'm going!
She's noisy.
What's with you?
You're acting weird.
A bean.
Hey!
Horrible! Give me another one!
What are you doing?
I want to have Isonobonbon too!
Why do you need...?
The size of the swimsuit and isoflavone...
Taiga...
Is it possible...
Don't say it! Don't say anything more than that!
You're... Flat chested?!
Is it really worth worrying that much?
Just because her breasts are small...
I'm done.
How is it?
It's flat, right? I'm flat chested, right?
Umm... W-Well...
Cups?
They're in.
But... T-They sink in...
That's why I hate pools.
Anyway, put something on.
You'll catch a cold.
What's this?
If you see that, even you will understand my sorrows.
This is... Horrible.
They said, "pitiful breasts." Pitiful...
They said I was so flat it was pitiful.
This is really just the impression of the guy who wrote that...
Of course, I made it rain blood in the photography club.
That's right, the photography club was suddenly shut down.
I don't want to show this pitiful figure in front of Kitamura-kun...
I don't wanna! I don't wanna!
Hey, Taiga.
I got it.
I'll do something about it.
I'll make it so you can go out with pride in front of Kitamura.
It's okay. Go home and sleep.
No, I'll wait here until it's done.
I'll stay awake until you finish.
Hey.
Getting stubborn and all weird on you... That is...
Sorry.
How is it?
I'm definitely taking this with me when I get married!
Maruo!
Maruo, you look better without glasses!
Switch to contacts.
Really?
Absolutely!
I'm not wearing any glasses either...
Bye, Aisaka-san.
I'm heading out.
Taiga?
Hurry up. I'll do your hair.
Yeah...
Maya-chan, I'm sorry!
I had a tough time doing my hair.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ami-chan!
Wow! Just like a model!
You have a great figure!
I'm just... I'm moved!
She's a goddess!
You're different from us average girls.
Not at all.
Of course! Today's Ami-chan is cute!
I give permission for you commoners to worship me!
Lick my shadows! It's the best feast for you guys, isn't it?!
Don't tease me, Maya-chan!
Takasu-kun!
Minorin, don't run! My hair will fall down again!
Let's keep going, it'll be a warm up!
I'm going running... Or not!
Minorin!
Kushieda!
I've figured it out!
If I stay in the pool, no one will see my stomach.
So I'm going to go do a lap!
Bye!
Minorin...
Oh, Aisaka-san, you finally came?
I was wondering if you weren't coming out because you were so embarrassed that your swimsuit was loose?
What are you saying? Are you talking in your sleep? Are you still asleep?
I'd hate to get a sunburn.
It's perfect.
In just one year, it's amazing she's gotten that far...
I'm really a Tiger fan!
What, it's just normal and boring...
We did it!
Yeah!
Fake Breasts Special Command Force.
She figured it out.
That's just like Minorin.
Aisaka?
Huh? It's Aisaka... Right?
I don't have my glasses so I can't really see, but that size is Aisaka.
Why are you hiding?
That hairstyle is nice, like a mouse.
Go away!
What?
Did I say something bad?
W-Who knows...
Show me your muscles.
Like this?
Wow!
That guy...
Flirting with the girls!
We question this classed society!
This is the summer-drop!
Maruo? Are you okay?
Hey!
Let's do it!
It's always been a "do what you want class," but...
Isn't this dangerous?
Right, Tai-
Kitamura-kun said my hairstyle was cute...
He did say it was nice, but...
Spotted our prey!
Let's go, my softball mate!
Alright!
Alright, next one!
Yes, Boss!
You got pushed in.
It really does look fun, Aisaka-san.
Y-You!
Let's play, let's play.
Don't get mad!
Hey, you should've held back a little!
I was just playing!
Hey, Taiga, are you okay?
Taiga?
She...
I... Can't swim!
Really can't swim?!
No way!
Hey, hey.
Hold on!
Taiga!
Sensei!
No!
Calm down!
Wha... What should I do?
One side of the cup came off!
Hey, it's looking pretty bad.
Aisaka!
Taiga!
Aisaka I'm coming!
Don't come!
Taiga!
Shit.
In that case!
Taiga!
Humiliation.
Like I've said already, I'm sorry!
I didn't know you couldn't swim.
Hey, everyone's gone home already. So stop being so mad and...
It's not something that can be solved with "I'm sorry."
Because you did something stupid, my b-breast...
Anyway, apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize! Apologize!
But if Aisaka-san can't swim, then we can't go to the beach or the pool together.
Hey, Takasu-kun, we have a mansion by the beach.
Would you like to spend the summer vacation there with me?
Hold on, weren't you just apologizing to Taiga?
Then, if Yuusaku came along too, it'd be fine, right?
Oh? Is something wrong, Aisaka-san?
If you do something like that again, I'll spread around the pictures from when you did 100 imitations.
Wait, 150.
If you did that, I'd sue you for using my pictures without permission.
Even Tenori Taiga can't win against the judgment of the court!
Hey, you guys.
Stop it!
You'll get a wound on your fist.
But, but, Minori-chan, Aisaka-san was going to...
It's this Stupid Chihuahua's fault!
What are you saying?!
Originally...
Be quiet!
If you want to develop your friendship with your fists, don't do it through fights...
Do it through sports!
Sp-
Sports?
A competition for Takasu.
Ami-tan versus Tiger?!
Why does Takasu get all the good parts?
Steal me too! Mess me up too!