All right then, introduce yourself next.
U...Um.
I'm... Akemi Homura.
Also... Um...
Please take care of me.
Because of heart problems, Akemi-san has been staying at the hospital.
Akemi Homura
It's been a while since she last came to school,
so she may need your help with a few things.
Everybody lend a helping hand, okay?
Akemi-san, where was your last school?
Are you in any after-school clubs?
Sports? Literature?
Wow, your hair is so long.
Isn't it hard to do every morning?
Umm, I... That is...
Akemi-san.
You need to go to the nurse's office, right?
Do you know where it is?
No.
I'll take you there, then.
I'm the health representative.
Sorry everyone.
Akemi-san has to go to the nurse's office during breaks to take some medicine.
Oh, is that so?
Sorry.
Sorry for holding you up.
Akemi-san, see you later.
Sorry.
They don't mean any harm.
It's just that transfer students are rare.
They're a little excited.
No. Umm...
Thank you very much.
You don't have to sound so formal.
We're classmates.
I'm Kaname Madoka.
Madoka is fine.
How can I...
It's fine.
Can I call you Homura-chan?
I...
Not many people call me by just my name.
My name is pretty weird too.
Of course not!
I think it feels really passionate and cool!
Then I don't match with my name.
That's such a waste!
Since you have such a cool name,
you should try to be as cool as your name!
Well then, try doing this problem.
You recently took a break from school, right?
Borrow some notes from a friend.
Isn't it tragic to faint after just a few warm-ups?
It can't be helped if she's been in bed for half a year.
You should try to be as cool as your name!
It's impossible.
I can't do anything...
I can only bring trouble to others,
push others away...
Why?
From now on, will I...
stay like this forever?
Then isn't it better to just die?
Is dying really better?
Yes. You should just die.
Die...
What is this place?
What?
What's happening?!
No... No!
That was close.
It's all right now.
Homura-chan!
Y-You are...
Those girls are Magical Girls.
They hunt down Witches.
The secret's out now, huh?
Make sure the other classmates don't find out!
Tomoe Mami
Kaname-san.
Are you always fighting that kind of thing?
Well... not always...
Mami-san is the real veteran here.
I just made a contract with Kyubei last week, so I'm still a rookie.
But today's battle showed that you've gotten a lot better, Kaname-san.
Is it really okay?
Aren't you... scared?
It's never really "okay..."
Of course, we get scared too.
But as long as Witches are defeated, lots of people can be saved.
It's a pretty meaningful job.
Kaname-san, before Walpurgis Night comes,
you should work hard to become an outstanding Magical Girl.
Well, I'm going to go now.
How can you...
Tomoe-san is already dead.
That's why I have to go.
I'm the only one who can stop Walpurgis Night.
You can't do it!
How can you defeat that thing alone?
Even you will die!
But I am a Magical Girl.
I have to protect everyone.
Please... please run away!
What else can you do?
No one will hate you for it!
Homura-chan.
I'm really happy I became friends with you.
Saving you before you were assaulted by Witches
has been my pride until now.
That's why being a Magical Girl is truly great.
I really think so.
Kaname-san.
Farewell, Homura-chan.
Take care.
No! Don't go!
Kaname-san!
Why?
You knew you were going to die.
Rather than saving someone like me, I wish...
...you could keep living!
Is that true?
Akemi Homura.
Can you bet your soul on your wish?
If you have a wish that must be fulfilled, even if you have to battle destiny...
I will help you.
As long as I make a contract with you,
can any wish come true?
I believe so.
You look like you qualify.
Tell me.
With what wish would you like to light your Soul Gem?
I...
I want to meet Kaname-san over again.
I don't want to be the girl that is always protected.
I want to be someone who can protect her!
Contract established.
Your wish has surpassed entropy.
Come, let it out.
Take this new strength.
This is...
I...
...haven't left the hospital yet.
It wasn't a dream.
All right then, introduce yourself next.
My name is Akemi Homura.
Please take care of me.
Because of heart problems, Akemi-san has been-
Kaname-san.
I've also become a Magical Girl.
Let's do our best from now on.
Now then, let's go!
What do you think, Mami-san?
It's Time Stop.
Although it is powerful,
you're not doing it right.
Yes.
Bomb                             making
Mami-san, now!
OK!
Akemi-san, please!
Y-Yes!
We did it?
We did it!
Good job.
Incredible, Homura-chan!
What's wrong?
Kaname-san, please hang on!
Why?
What?
How? Why?
I have to tell them.
Everyone was deceived by Kyubei!
Hey now.
What good can come to Kyubei if he lied like that?
That...
Telling us such a strange story,
are you trying to split us apart?
Could it be that you're really working with the one called Kyoko?
N-No!
Sayaka-chan, that's what really splits people apart.
Whatever.
I'm against being in a team with her.
Madoka and Mami-san are both long-range fighters, so it doesn't matter,
but if something suddenly explodes right in front of me,
I don't want to be there.
I've almost been caught in the explosion several times.
Akemi-san, don't you have any weapon other than bombs?
I'll think about it.
Bastard! What the hell are you?
What did you do to Sayaka?
Sayaka-chan, stop it!
Please, I beg you!
Sayaka-chan should hate doing things like this.
Sorry, Miki-san.
Sayaka!
Damn it... this is...
It's so cruel...
This is too much.
Tomoe-san?
If Soul Gems breed Witches,
doesn't everyone have to die?
You're just like me!
Stop!
No!
I've had enough!
It's all right.
Let's work hard together!
Let's stop Walpurgis Night together!
We're also...
...finished, aren't we?
The Grief Seed is also...
Yeah.
The two of us will become monsters just like that,
and ruin the entire world.
Taking bad things,
sad things,
and wiping all of it clean.
Destroy. Destroy.
Destroying without end.
Don't you think that's good too?
I was lying before.
I saved another one.
How can this...
Why, for a person like me...
There is something I can't do,
but Homura-chan can achieve it.
Homura-chan, you can go to the past, right?
To prevent such an ending,
you can change history, right?
Can you save me before I get deceived by Kyubei?
I promise!
I will definitely save you!
No matter how many times I go back!
I will always protect you!
That's great.
Can I ask for just one more thing?
I don't want to become a Witch.
Although I've seen terrible and sad things,
there are still many things I want to protect in this world.
Madoka!
Homura-chan, you finally called me by my name.
I'm so... happy.
No one will believe the future.
No one can accept the future.
Even so, I...
Who?
Madoka.
If someone came to tempt you with miracles,
never be manipulated by them!
Homura...
There's no one to rely on anymore.
There is no need to let anyone understand.
I will never let Madoka fight again.
All the Witches will be destroyed by me.
And so, this time...
I'll take care of Walpurgis Night...
Myself!
How cruel.
There's no other choice.
The burden is too great for her to bear alone.
She can't! Not alone at least!
How could she?!
Madoka!
Don't listen to him!
The moment you give up, it's all over.
However, you can change your fate.
It's up to you...
...to change the course of this destruction and grief.
All the power you were blessed with was meant for this moment.
Really?
Don't be deceived!
That will satisfy him!
Can someone like me really do that much?
Can I really change this outcome?
Of course.
That's why you should make a contract with me, and become a Magical Girl.
Stop!
That's really impressive.
Madoka transformed.
Although it was predicted that she would become the strongest Magical Girl...
she stopped the Walpurgis Night with only one hit.
No matter what the ending is...
have you predicted them all?
Whether sooner or later, the ending will be the same.
As the strongest Magical Girl, she defeated the greatest enemy.
Of course, after that she can only become the most evil Witch.
The Madoka now,
would probably destroy this planet in about 10 days.
Anyway, that's humanity's problem now.
Our energy recycling quota is approximately fulfilled.
Are you not going to fight?
No... My battlefield is not here.
Akemi Homura.
You...!
Return.
No matter how many times, I will always choose to return.
Repeating the same period of time over and over again,
searching for the only exit.
For you...
a path out of the destiny of despair.
Madoka.
My only friend.
Homura-chan.
You... Just for you...
Even if I am trapped in the infinite maze of eternity,
I'm fine with that.
Episode 10  I won't depend on anyone anymore
Mura Kuroe
Looking over them for so long,
don't you feel anything at all?
Have you never tried to understand how much pain everyone has to go through?
Episode 11 The last checkpoint
The last checkpoint...