On that day, mankind remembered with fear...
that we were subject to their dominance,
and recalled with shame that
the walls around us were a cage.
Prepare to engage, men!
There's only a single target!
We will eliminate it and make this
mankind's first base outside of the walls!
Target approaching!
Take a five-pronged formation!
Remember your training!
My team will distract the target!
All attack teams, switch
to your Maneuver Gears!
Attack it simultaneously from all directions!
Feel the steel claw of mankind's wrath!
Huh, Mikasa?
Let's go home.
What are you doing here?
Was your sleep so deep that
you still haven't awoken from it yet?
No, but I think I had a really, really long dream.
What was I dreaming about?
I can't remember.
Eren, why are you crying?
Huh?
Hear me! The walls were constructed as a manifestation of the Lord's wisdom!
The walls are the work of the Lord!
None shall desecrate these walls!
Don't tell anyone I was crying.
I won't.
But if you don't know why you were crying,
maybe you should get your dad to check you over.
Are you insane?
I can't tell my dad about it!
What are you crying about, Eren?
Hannes.
Did Mikasa scold you?
What?
Why would I cry?
You reek of alcohol!
Hey, what's wrong with that?
You're boozing again?
Want to join us?
Um... What about your duties?
Well, we're watching the gates today.
We're stationed here all day, so we're obviously going to get hungry and thirsty at some point.
And the fact that our drinks are
alcoholic is neither here nor there.
How are you going to fight when the time comes if you're drunk?
When what time comes?
You have to ask?!
When they breach the wall and burst in!
That stings.
Eren, don't raise your voice
out of nowhere like that.
You're so energetic, Master Doctor's Son.
If they do end up breaching the
walls, we'll be here to do our duty.
But guess what?
That hasn't happened for over a hundred years.
Even so!
My dad says it's at times like these that we're in the gravest of danger!
Dr. Jaeger says that?
Well, there's some truth in that.
He has saved our town from plague in the past.
We can't thank him enough.
But these Titans are a different matter entirely.
As a soldier, I see Titans milling
around while I'm mending the walls,
but I don't think they're a match
for this fifty-meter-high wall.
Th-Then, you guys don't have
any intention to fight them?
'Course not.
What the hell?
You should stop calling yourselves the City Guard and call yourselves stonemasons instead!
Has a nice ring to it.
But you know, Eren, if a soldier is called into
action, that means the peace has been shattered.
Everyone's much better off and much happier when
they get the opportunity to call us useless freeloaders.
Even if we never leave the safety of these walls,
we'll survive as long as we eat right and sleep well.
But doesn't that make us...
the same as livestock?
What empty words this kid spouts!
It's not like he can do anything about
it anyway. Ain't that right, Hannes?
Um, guess not...
Hey, Eren!
You're not right in the head, kid!
Surely he doesn't want to join the Recons...
Eren, I don't think you should join the Recons...
What? You also think that what they do is idiotic?
I'm not saying that their objective is idiotic...
The Reconnaissance Battalion has made it back!
The front gate's opening!
Let's go, Mikasa!
The heroes have returned!
Dammit, I can't see a thing.
This is what's left of the battalion?
The rest of them were eaten.
That's what happens when you
step foot outside the walls.
Moses! Moses!
My son, Moses! I don't see him here.
Where is my son?
This is Moses' mother.
Bring it to her.
This is all that remains of him.
But my son... was useful, right?
Perhaps he didn't contribute directly,
but his death has helped fuel
mankind's resistance, hasn't it?!
Without question!
No...
On this reconnaissance mission, we...
No, on all our missions...
We haven't made any progress whatsoever!
Because of my incompetence,
I have led countless soldiers to their deaths in vain,
without even figuring out their true nature!
What a pitiful display.
You said it.
It's like we're just offering ourselves up on a plate and making them stronger.
Hey, what the hell are you doing, kid?
Hey! What are you doing, Mikasa?!
Hey, get back here!
Mikasa! Okay, okay, I get it!
What did you do that for?!
Look at what you've done to my firewood!
Eren, have you changed your
mind about joining the Recons?
Help me pick them all up.
It's not like you had that much, anyway.
We're back.
Welcome home.
Wow, Eren.
You brought back a surprising amount today.
I-I guess...
What was that for?
Your ear was red.
You were lying.
Mikasa helped you, didn't she?
Huh? Dad, are you going out?
Work?
Yeah, I have to go see a
patient behind the inner wall.
I'll be back in two to three days.
Oh.
Eren wants to join the Reconnaissance Battalion.
Mikasa, don't tell them that!
Eren! What's going on in that head of yours?
Do you realize how many people die on the other side of those walls?
Of course I do!
No, you don't!
Eren.
Why do you want to go outside of the walls?
I want to see...
the world outside of our cage!
I don't want to die inside these walls, never knowing what's out there!
And if no one carries on their work, then all those who have died up to this point will have died for nothing!
I see.
My ship's leaving shortly.
I must get going.
Wait, dear!
Convince Eren to forget this foolishness!
Carla, you can't suppress a
person's overpowering curiosity.
Eren, when I return, I shall take you
down to the basement I've kept off-limits.
Really?
Have a safe trip!
I won't allow it.
You're not doing anything as stupid as joining the Reconnaissance Battalion.
You call it stupid?
People who accept living like livestock are way more stupid, if you ask me!
Eren!
Mikasa, he has a terrifying reckless streak.
When you're in trouble, make sure you watch out for each other.
I will.
What's wrong, heretic?
Why don't you throw a punch if you want to prove me wrong?
Why would I do something like that?
I'm not going to stoop to your level!
Say that again!
All you can do is whale on me,
because you have no arguments you can use to prove me wrong!
Doesn't that mean you've admitted defeat?
I've had enough of your lousy arguments!
Stop that!
It's Eren!
What a dope. He's back again.
Does he want us to tear him a new one?
Let's teach him a lesson!
M-Mikasa's with him!
Shit! Run!
Hey, did ya see that? They
ran away at the sight of me!
No, they ran away at the sight of Mikasa.
Ow.
Hey, are you okay, Armin?
I can stand without your help.
Oh, sorry.
So I told them that mankind needs to eventually leave these walls behind.
Then they beat me, calling me a heretic.
Dammit.
All we want to do is go outside.
Why does everyone hate us for it?
Well, it's because mankind has been living
peacefully inside these walls for a hundred years.
If anyone attempts to go outside the walls, they might accidentally let in a Titan,
so the King's Council issued an edict that effectively
banned all non-military interest in the outside world.
We're risking our own lives.
Who has the right to stop us?
No, you can't!
You can't.
That reminds me, Mikasa! How
could you tell my parents?!
I never swore not to.
So how did it go?
Well, they weren't happy.
Figures.
I also believe that people who consider mankind
perpetually safe within these walls are out of their minds.
Mommy!
Even if the wall hasn't been
breached in a hundred years,
who's to say that it won't be breached today?
Wh-What was that?
An explosion?
Over there!
Something fell out of the sky?
I'm not sure.
Hey, Armin!
What happened?
What are you all looking at?
It can't be! That wall's fifty meters high!
It's one of them...
It's a Titan!
H-He... punched a hole through the wall...
One's got inside!
The Titans are attacking!
We have to get—
Eren!
My house is over there...
Mom...
Mikasa!
It's all over...
The Titans... are going to overrun the city!
My house can't have been hit.
When I turn this corner, my house
will be there like it always has been!
Mom!
Eren.
Mikasa, grab that end!
We have to move this pillar!
Hurry, Mikasa!
I know!
The Titans are flooding in, aren't they?
Eren, take Mikasa and run!
This instant!
Believe me, I want to run!
Hurry up and get out from under there!
My legs have been crushed by the debris.
I wouldn't be able to run even if I did get out.
You understand?
I'll carry you and run!
Why can't you listen to your
mother for once in your life?!
Please listen to me just this once!
Mikasa!
No... No!
If you carry on, all three of us will die.
Hannes!
Take the kids and run!
Don't underestimate me, Carla.
I'll kill the Titan and save all three of you.
Wait!
You can't fight!
She's right. I can save those two, no problem.
But the time has finally come! I'll save
them and repay them for all they've done!
Hey, Hannes!
What are you doing?!
Thank you.
You're leaving Mom behind! She's...
Eren! Mikasa!
Live on!
Don't go...
Stop!
On that day, mankind remembered with fear...
that we were subject to their dominance,
and recalled with shame that
the walls around us were a cage.
Shiganshina has fallen. Mankind has
no choice but to pray, scream, and die.
However, in his tiny heart, Eren swore vengeance.