Mornin'...
Hurry up, Momoka!
Just gimme a sec.
I'm using my own clothes for today's shoot, so I need to get changed.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
I'll bring you some of our new stuff!
Morning, Dad...
Good morning.
Erika, make sure you eat your breakfast!
Yeah, yeah...
You only need to say it once!
Yeah!
They're always running around like this in the morning...
I think this'll do nicely.
Boy, it sure is nice being a model.
You get to skip school, everyone pampers you,
and you get to wear pretty clothes at your shoots.
If it bothers you so much, why
don't you become a model too?
You two are always like this!
Will you give it a rest already?
Still, our daughters are cute even when they're angry!
That's good!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Ta-da!
Why do you have that?
Well, I'm always asking you to teach me about fashion, Erika,
so I thought I'd buy this and study some for myself!
This model Momoka is really pretty, isn't she?
She's the most popular and charismatic model at the moment, it seems.
You must know her, right, Erika?
That model Momoka... is my older sister.
Really?
Wait, what?!
What is the Cause
of the Charismatic Model's Sighing?
My mom was a really charismatic model back in the day.
So it was only natural for her to expect both me and Momo to become models.
But in the end, only Momo became a model.
She got scouted back when she was in
elementary school, and ever since then...
So that's what happened.
Now that she mentions it, back when her
Flower of the Heart became a Desertrian...
Doll!
We're finished!
I hate you, Momo!
Just cause you're kinda pretty and stylish
doesn't mean you can act so damn proud!
No!
I mean, I'm trying my best too!
But I'll never be as pretty as Momo!
I can't help being envious!
What are you doing?!
We're sisters, so why do we have to be so different?
Erika, please stop that!
E-Erika!
Hmm?
U-Um...
Oh, a new crepe place just opened near the station!
Why don't we go there after school and do some planning for the Fashion Club?
Oh, that's a great idea!
Coffret!
If that's the plan, let's finish eating and then go invite everyone!
Okay!
Today went well, Momoka!
We'll be counting on you to work just as hard tomorrow!
Right!
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, that's quite all right!
She spoke to me!
You're so lucky! I'm jealous!
Momoka!
It worked!
She's so pretty!
Momoka?
Yuri!
I've brought you the notes from this morning's lessons.
Thanks for always doing this for me.
Hey, Yuri...
It might be a bit selfish of me to think this, but...
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
I see.
Ta-da! Here are my design sketches!
Wow, they're really pretty!
You really are the daughter of the Fairy Drop owners!
In any case, I'd like you all to make some designs like this!
Sounds like fun!
And after we make the designs, we'll actually make them for real?!
You've got it, Rumicchi! You catch on quick!
Whoa! It's Kurumi Momoka!
Please give me your autograph!
May I take a photo?!
Isn't that Momoka?
For real?!
Momo...
No way!
Momoka?!
She's so prettyyyyyy!
She's so beautiful...
It's kinda shocking that Momoka is Erika's sister...
Yeah, it is.
E-ri-ka!
Wh-Wh-What do you want?!
You want to come watch my photo shoot?
Well, it's my friends...
They insisted on coming to see you while you're modeling.
I told them no, but they said that it was a good chance to study fashion, so I couldn't exactly refuse...
Study fashion?
Oh, you run the Fashion Club, right?
What of it?
What exactly is it you do?
If you show me that, I'll let you come to the shoot tomorrow.
O God, O Buddha, O Erika! I'm begging you!
Just this once!
This'll be the last time!
Please!
Fine, whatever!
Here! These are designs for some clothes I'm going to make!
That's enough, right?!
We'll be coming to see you tomorrow, all right?!
Why do I have to put myself through this humiliation?!
Erika, what's the matter?!
The Fashion Club, huh?
Wow, this is a really crude design.
Though I guess you amateurs are trying as hard as you can.
This is all your fault, Tsubomi!
I think this new summer swimsuit will really suit me!
If you can't even make yourself beautiful without dressing up...
We really are worlds apart. Tu es trés pitoyable.
Wh-What did you say?!
You truly are pathetic!
Weak! All of you, weak!
A real man meets conflict bare and unshielded!
Do not entrust this to the likes of them.
This time, I shall defeat the Precure.
Very well.
Um, sorry to bother you... I'm Kurumi Momoka's sister.
Yeah, yeah. We get girls like you occasionally,
thinking they can get in by saying stuff like that.
Hey, what's with you?!
Erika really is...
Right, right. You're disturbing the shoot, so if you'd just...
Sorry about this! She really is my little sister.
She and her friends came to observe the shoot.
Seriously?! I'm really sorry about this...
Thanks for always looking out for Erika.
Just relax and observe, okay?
O-O-O-Okay!
It's certainly frantic down there.
Well, that's fine. Now, where's someone with a usable Flower of the Heart...
All right then, one last pose if you would.
Right!
Models sure are amazing...
They sure are. She's really cool!
I wish I had an older sister like her...
If I could give her to you, I would!
Insensitive little...
What?
Erika!
You're blushing...
You're so cute!
Stop it!
Hrm?
I'm gonna keep tickling you!
H-Hey, you guys!
If you're going to observe, please do it quietly!
We're sorry...
Okay, Momoka, let's restart.
Momoka?
Who are you?!
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles... Kumojacky!
The Flower of your Heart is
about to wilt, so I shall take it!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
Momo!
Momo! Momo!
I suppose that will suffice.
You're up, Desertrian!
Looks like it's a weak one...
Well, it'll do. Desertrian, run wild!
Beaaaaauuutyyyy!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
Erika, let's transform and save Momoka!
Yeah!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
So you show yourselves, Precure.
Go get them, Desertrian!
No one... No one understands how I feel!
Marine!
Blossom...
Shower!
Certainly, I have attained my dream of becoming a model.
I get to wear pretty clothes, appear in
magazines, and all of my fans cheer me on.
But because of that, I've lost so many things.
A normal life, with normal friends.
Erika's my sister, but I can't help being envious of her!
Momoka...
Let loose your wails, Desertrian!
Run wild until the Flower of your Heart wilts!
I don't want to be treated differently.
I just want to be able to have fun with my friends!
Is that too much to ask?!
Puff puff puff puff puff!
This Desertrian's surprisingly
capable considering how it looks.
Now, run wild until the Flower of your Heart has wilted!
Beauuuuuuuuutyyyyyyyyyy!
Stop it...
Don't.... play with her heart any more!
It is not I who is playing here.
It's the fault of those she holds dear
being unable to empathize with her!
That's... not true!
Maybe we haven't noticed the loneliness within her heart...
But the one who dragged out her heart and toyed with it like this...
was you, Kumojacky!
And I've had it up to here with this!
Blossom...
I can't forgive myself for not
noticing Momo's feelings before.
But...
that's why I'll definitely save Momo!
Right!
My heart may be more vast than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Say your prayers, Kumojacky!
If you think you can defeat me, then go ahead and try!
Desertrian!
Puff puff puff puff puff puff puff!
You're not going to catch me with that!
I won't fall for the same trick twice!
Blossom Flower Storm!
Wh-What?!
Marine! Now's your chance!
Right!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Tch... I guess makeup is as weak as it seems.
Momo!
In the language of flowers, a dahlia means "elegance."
It suits Momoka perfectly!
Yeah!
Just what happened back there?
I thought it was a dream, but the staff said they saw a strange monster as well...
Maybe it was some kind of prank.
Who knows?
By the way, Momo...
What is it?
Working as a model isn't all it's cracked up to be, is it?
Like, how do I put this...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, it sure is a lot of trouble.
Especially for a popular model like me!
But you know...
I put everything I could into becoming a model, so when it finally paid off, I was so happy.
The clothes I model become fashionable, and my fans imitate my hairstyles.
That's why I don't want to give this up.
Momo...
I'll be fine!
My dream of becoming a model came true, so my new dream is to make some friends!
I'm going to follow your example and make a lot of friends!
Okay!
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born...
Who'd've thought you of all people would worry about me, though?
What?! That's not very nice!
Oh, let me clarify. I meant, "Who'd've thought a little brat like you..."
I'm not a brat! I'm already in middle school!
Oh really now...
Now that you mention it, that
design of yours was pretty good.
You might've grown up. Just a little, mind you.
Don't change the subject like that!
I wasn't trying to do anything!
Jeez!
I was paying you a compliment, so
you really should be more grateful.
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
When I was young, I was with my Grandma,
always waiting for my beloved father and mother.
I knew they were busy with work, but I
could never stop the tears from welling.
But now that I'm in middle school, I'm an adult!
And no matter how busy my father gets, I'll wait here, patiently, for as long as it takes.
HeartCatch Precure:
My Father's Been Scouted!
He'll Quit Being a Florist?!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!