Hey, did you watch that show on TV yesterday?
What show?
The only one worth watching!
"Reporter on the scene! Hamana Lake's
Giant Eel — Hassie's Shocking Identity."
I watched that too!
There's no way it's real.
Ghosts are nothing but figments of our imagination. Right, Houtarou?
You're such a boring guy. Isn't there a romantic in you?
What do you think, Chii?
I'm curious as to whether or not it actually exists. The truth.
Well, I don't care if they really exist, but I hope we see one today.
Wouldn't that be fun?
Ghosts are nothing but figments of our imagination.
That's exactly what I expected to hear from you.
退屈な窓辺に吹き込む風に
The wind blew into the boring classroom
顔を顰めたのは照れくささの裏返し
That grimace on my face hides my tiny bit of joy
lce Cream
曖昧に頷く　手のひらの現在
I just nod my way through the life designed for me
描いてる自分は少し大げさで
Maybe I'm a little too pretentious
何か変わりそうな気がしているよ
It feels like something is about to change
心に呼びかける君のせいだね
You're probably to blame, for calling out to my heart
曇り空覗いた予感
It's as if I saw a glimpse of color through the clouds
手を伸ばそういつよりも力強い勇気で
Let's reach out with more courage than usual
光も影もまだ遠くて
Light and shadow are still so far beyond our reach
それでも僕らは優しさの理由が知りたい
But we still want to know the source of your kindness
今は誰の名前でもない
Your name doesn't define you
輝きの彼方へ 全部過去になる前に
Let's go find what lies beyond the light
見つけに行こう
Before everything turns into the past
Identity Revealed
Kamiyama High's Classic Literature Club has four members in total.
Why are we all riding in a transit bus, you ask?
The answer is obviously our destination.
Our final stop is Zaizen Village.
It's well known for hiking and hot springs.
We're coming for the hot springs and not for hiking.
I wouldn't be doing anything during my
summer break if I was living by my motto, but...
Thank you so much for solving the mystery of my uncle!
Why don't we all visit a hot spring?
Let's go to a hot spring!
O—Okay.
The shuttle bus should be here to pick us up soon.
What a nice view!
Oreki, are you okay?
I'm car sick.
That's our Houtarou.
Our ride was only an hour and a half long.
You're so pathetic.
I'm surprised you were able to find us a place, Mayaka.
My relative who runs an inn is letting us stay for free. They're renovating right now and have spare rooms.
We're here, Oreki.
Yes! We're finally here!
Hurry up, or we'll leave you behind.
Here we come! Our inn!
Welcome to the Blue Mountain Resort!
Blue Mountain Resort
She's the big sister, Zenna Rie,
and she's the little sister, Zenna Kayo.
Hello.
They're in sixth and fourth grade. You've grown agai—
Your rooms are at the end of the second floor!
Wow! Check this out, Houtarou!
This room's got a pretty nice view, huh?
I guess an occasional trip isn't all that bad.
I would've preferred to come here alone though.
You, going a a trip by yourself?
You must be joking!
Just remember that we're here because of
Chitanda's planning and Mayaka's connections.
Time for dinner.
Come eat!
Hear that?
Let's go.
Cheese?
Could it be stew? Gratin? Fondue?
Chilled shabu-shabu?
Ready? Let's eat!
We have dessert too.
Cheesecake?
How did you know?!
I smelled it.
That's amazing!
Is it?
He's exactly like Maya said!
What did you tell them, Ibara?!
Let's light some fireworks tomorrow.
Good idea!
Right? My dad bought some yesterda—
What are doing?
Sorry, Sis.
Here.
Thank you.
I hope you didn't burn yourself.
I'm fine.
Sheesh, be careful!
I'm so full.
Satoshi already went for a dip?
We're at a hot spring resort, after all.
Where are you going, Oreki?
Same place as you.
What about Ibara?
She's occupied with the kids.
Sorry for the sudden question, but what's your sister like?
Wow, that really is sudden.
Oh, you're an only child, right?
My sister, huh?
She's strange and incredible in many ways.
I couldn't ever beat her in anything.
Oh?
Not that I ever wanted to.
Why did you ask about my sister anyway?
Was it because you saw the Zenna Sisters?
Actually, I've always wished for siblings.
A big sister or a little brother.
Don't you think it's wonderful to always have someone close to you?
Not at all.
It seems the princess is a bit too naive.
She's living in a fantasy world.
In reality, siblings aren't wonderful at all.
There's no mixed bathing here.
Of course not!
Satoshi's here?
Hurry, Dad and Grandpa!
Geez!
Oh! This place is bigger than I thought!
Hey, Houtarou.
You're finally here.
The water here is really nice!
It really improves your blood circulation!
It would be dangerous if the water  mixed with my blood!
Don't be silly.
It's good to see you're relaxing though.
Is that Chitanda?
Oreki? What happened?!
Are you all right?
The heat got to him.
What?
It's just pathetic.
I was there for twice as long as he was, but he passed out when I glanced over.
Y—You're just so...
Thanks, guys.
You're welcome.
You're destined to miss fun events.
I agree.
Car sickness may have played a part in it too.
I feel sick.
Is it Chitanda?
Oreki? Are you all right?
Not really.
You're still feverish.
Should I get you a cold towel?
No... I don't need it!
I'm going to sleep.
Sorry for ruining our trip.
You aren't ruining it.
We're about to share ghost stories.
Please come over if you start feeling better.
Take care then.
Okay.
It's not even 8 PM yet.
Drumbeats?
We actually didn't need an annex.
The other room's window is open too?
There's a secret.
A secret?
A creepy guest came to stay here a few years ago,
and he stayed in room seven of the main building.
Seven
He didn't want food or anyone to change his bed sheets.
He didn't want anyone to come inside.
But it ended up working out. He had already paid for his room and it was a busy season.
Seven
However, there was a horrible scream that night.
A scream?
Someone saw the shadow of a
swinging corpse dangling by the neck!
That guest escaped to our resort after embezzling money from his company!
Here we go!
Stop that!
Ever since then, the guests who stayed in room seven
claimed there was something in the room, and they still see shadows at night!
And then there's the ninth guest.
What happened?
He died from a sudden illness!
No way!
That's what I was waiting for!
Cut it out!
My grandma had the room exorcised and built the annex
so that rumors wouldn't spread.
Where's room seven?
It's that room directly across from our window.
We live on the first floor, and try to avoid the second floor.
You're kidding, right?
This is our secret, okay? Promise?
That's so clichéd.
Seriously.
Risshuu
The term of autumn's approach
lce Cream
It's morning already.
Good morning.
Where are the others?
It appeared.
What did?
Last night I woke up to a warm breeze.
I just happened to turn in my sleep. That's when I saw the shadow of a hanging man.
It was swaying and had a hazy glow!
It's not every day that you see Ibara so frightened.
I wish Satoshi was here to see this.
Thanks for the food.
How was the bath?
It was great!
I'm glad you liked it.
Rie
The futon was soft too, right?
Yes. I slept really well!
I don't see one for Kayo.
Rie
I never knew those sort of stories scared you.
I'm not afraid of ghosts!
But what I saw was just too creepy!
Did you really see it?
I did. I'm certain of it!
Did you tell them? Dad said not to tell anyone!
What? Who cares? It's Maya!
What is it?
Um, what do you think of Maya's story?
The hanging shadow?
Well, clichéd stories like that are passed down because people love them.
So do you think what Mayaka said was the truth?
I don't.
Was I mistaken as well?
What do you mean by that?
I also saw that hanging shadow.
Mayaka woke up, and that woke me up too.
Then I saw it in the darkness.
Oh?
I thought I might have imagined it, but Mayaka saw the same thing.
You must have mistaken it for something else.
Like I said yesterday, ghosts are nothing but...
...figments of our imagination?
If that's true, what was it that we saw?
Yeah.
Why don't you tell us what we mistook it for?
Why me?
Let's find out,  Oreki!
I'm curious!
I'm sorry, Chii!
I promised to help out with their summer homework.
Leave it to us.
We'll definitely discover the truth.
Right, Oreki?
How should I know?
In any case, "always rush through the things that you have to do".
So you saw this shadow directly across from your room?
Yes. I did.
How big was the apparition?
It was about the size of a normal person.
The shape?
I don't clearly remember it.
What about the color?
I don't know. I only saw its shadow.
Shadow, huh?
You were looking against the light, so you only saw someone's shadow, right?
I think so.
Against the light.
The main source of light at night has to be the moon.
I think so too.
The moon was pretty bright last night.
What about it...?
Chitanda, how long after the ghost stories did you go to sleep?
It was 10 PM.
And the shutters at the time?
I believe they were closed.
The shadow couldn't have appeared if the shutters were closed.
That's troubling.
We'll have to take a look at room seven in the main building.
This is great! Mysteries!
I'm glad we had this trip!
I'm not.
Hey.
Yes, what is it?
Can you handle this? I'm bad with kids.
Sure.
Kayo! Can I talk to you for a minute?
We're going to the main building.
The main building? Why?
We're investigating the hanging shadow.
Can we see room seven?
I'm sorry.
You can't go in there right now.
My sister will get mad.
Then just tell me one thing.
Is it still a guest room now?
No.
Only the baths and the cafeteria in the main building are used by guests.
It's a vacant room, then?
As of right now, the second floor is used for storage.
Is that all?
Yeah, thanks. You have been very helpfu—
She hates me.
Don't worry about it. I'm sure she's just scared by tall guys.
She's so cute!
No Trespassing
Wouldn't it be a problem if we can't go into room seven?
It's more troublesome than problematic.
Since we can't see where it actually happened.
Oh, I remember these!
A
Blue Mountain
Resort - Annex
Rie
Morning stretches...
I used to do these up until two years ago.
A
Blue Mountain
Resort - Annex
Until she was in eighth grade?
Is she for real?
Let's check out the back too.
Did it rain last night?
Yes, for a while.
You would have to open both windows to see the shadow.
Um...
It's time for lunch.
I'm all done.
Having a sister has to be great!
Oh, you wish that you had a sister?
Yes, a little bit.
So? Did you discover anything?
Nope.
We're still doing a preliminary investigation.
I do have a theory though.
Oh? Let's hear it.
Hey, what are you guys talking about?
You guys left me out of the loop.
What? Where do you always sneak off to, anyway?
I never see you around.
You don't get it, do you?
You've got to take multiple dips on a hot spring trip.
Is that how it is?
What do you think of my yukata?
It's beautiful.
You look nice!
I finally got my parents to buy one for me at the beginning of summer break.
I remember you've always wanted one.
She has good taste.
What's wrong with it?
The sash.
Isn't it an imitation?
How is that an abrupt change in a genomic sequence?
Imitation... not mutation.
She used a sash that's not meant to be used for a yukata.
I don't approve of that.
That's absurd.
What's the matter?
Did I get cursed by the hanging shadow too?
Let's go to the hot spring we went to yesterday.
Let's!
The hanging shadow.
It's an optical illusion seen by Ibara and Chitanda...
Figments of our imagination.
But it needs a clincher.
Let's wait for each other when we're done, okay?
Satoshi, huh?
Weren't you eating with us just now?
When did you get here?
Well, I took a shortcut right behind the entrance. You can slide down this resorts little cliff at the back.
This guy slid down a cliff just to take a shortcut?
Why am I not surprised?
I can't come up with an explanation good enough to satisfy Chitanda.
The shadow's identity isn't hard to figure out.
The question is why it happened.
Are you about to pass out from the heat again, Houtarou?
Were there any special events last night?
You passing out from the heat.
Not that!
Yeah, we shared ghost stories.
I felt like a pimp, having more girls
than I could wrap my arms around.
No, I'm talking about official events.
Oh, there was a summer festival.
Didn't you hear the drums?
Drums...
I see! A summer festival!
It all clicks.
And? What about it?
The hanging shadow...
must have been a yukata on a hanger.
Huh?
Why would anyone hang a yukata there?
And it doesn't make sense for anyone to open the windows just to show it to us.
It wasn't done to show you.
Then...
Someone was drying a wet yukata.
The windows were opened for
ventilation and to dry it more quickly.
Why?
Because it rained.
No, why was it in room seven?
So that it wouldn't be seen.
But we saw it.
No, it was meant to be hidden from the family.
Why?
It was Kayo who put up that yukata to dry.
She was envious of Rie's yukata, and wanted to wear it.
I doubt Rie would let her borrow it, though.
Why not? They're sisters.
Didn't you notice?
Rie
Her cup, stretching card, and bowling ball...
She's a girl who makes her own things identifiable.
Kayo couldn't ask a girl like that to borrow a yukata.
No way.
But Kayo wanted to wear it no matter what.
So she took it out, and wore it for the summer festival last night.
She left at 8 PM.
Kayo went to the summer festival?
I saw a glimpse of someone
leaving the place at 8 PM yesterday.
Kayo wasn't there for ghost stories, right?
You're right, she wasn't.
However, a misfortune befell her.
It rained.
The rain didn't last long, but the yukata got all wet.
She remembered the fireworks we were planning for the next day.
Rie would almost certainly want to wear the yukata for fireworks.
She had to dry it somehow before the next day or Rie would have found out.
It would be found in the main building's first floor.
The annex is out of the question.
She couldn't use the dryer at night either.
So she waited until everyone fell  asleep to hang the yukata to dry.
Her misfortune continued.
Moonlight shone through the open
windows, revealing the hanging shadow.
The final misfortune is the fact that we're investigating the hanging shadow.
NO TRESPASSING
Kayo must have felt like a cornered rat.
The presence I felt back then must have been Kayo.
Kayo...
She returned the yukata early in the morning.
Unlike Rie, she does stretches
early in the morning every day.
It must have been easy for her to return it.
I see.
I'll keep this from Ibara.
It'll probably create complications.
If that's true...
They must not get along very well.
I can't imagine having a sister who you can't even borrow a yukata from.
Isn't that how siblings usually act?
I wanted a sibling.
A big sister I could respect, or a cute little brother.
The sibling in Chitanda's ideals...
It may be nothing more than a figment of her imagination.
It's so hot...
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Well, maybe it's not entirely a figment of her imagination.
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね　見つけてね
Please come and find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
芽生えてた温もり　暖かくて戸惑う
I'm at a loss to this warmth growing inside me
こんな気持ちをまだ　あなたは分からないの
You're still oblivious to my feelings
その視線には意味なんて別にないはず
I'm sure your gaze doesn't mean anything
だって友達にしてるのと同じ
Because you look the same way at your friends
明け方に消えてく　小さな願い星
The tiny wishing stars disappear into the dawn
夜の間だけの魔法
This magic only works at night
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
Next week: Let's Go See an Advanced Screening!
Let's Go See an Advanced Screening!