They see through the darkness with their shining eyes
hikaru me de yami wo yomu
Such dreadful children
osorubeki kodomo tachi
Ever since the moment they were born
umarete kita toki kara zutto
love has been a lethal weapon
ai towa kyouki de
Grasping my blood-soaked chest
makka ni nureta mune wo tsukande
I buried it in my wounds
kizuguchi ni uzumeta
In the world that arises from decay
fuhai no naka kara naseru sekai niwa
there is a cheerful despair
hanayagu zetsubou
Whether we spare their lives or kill them, it's our karma
ikasu mo korosu mo watashi tachi no gou
They laugh like a dog, they squeal like a pig
inu no you ni warai buta no you ni naite
Now what are we going to do after their continued screams?
wameki tsuzuketa ato niwa saa dousuru
They're protected, fondled, and broken
mamorare ayasare kowarete
I'm a mere shell of myself though still alive
ikizuku kono mi wa nukegara
My heart is cracked and sparkling
hibiware kirameku kokoro no
I put my finger on its trigger
hikigane ni yubi wo kake
They're protected, fondled, and they break things
mamorare ayasare kowashite
I pretend that I understand it all
subete wakatta furi wo shite
And everything I shoot is an unworthy illusion
utsuno wa kai naki yume bakari