I'm sleepy.
Gosh.
You left tissues in the pocket of your skirt and just threw it into the laundry basket, didn't you.
That caused a lot of problems.
Make sure you separate colors into a different pile.
Dark colors should be put into an orange basket...
Shut up, shut up!
You talk too much!
Men shouldn't be so picky!
Make a big hit!  Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Make a big hit!  Yeah!
Don't mind.
All right!  It's my turn.
Captain!  Fight oh!
Thank you for your cheers, everyone!
Kushieda...
Throw it with all you've got!
...your invigorating smile...
...Kusheida...
...your sparkling sweat...
Going around first base, second base, third base, a home run.
...your off-key singing...
Home in!
...ah, Kushieda, this morning you're as usual.
Your look was perverted, you disgusting dog.
Kushieda, it's about this weekend's joint practice.
Hi, Kitamura-kun, I was also going to-
Do you really understand, you stupid dog?!
H-Hey, stop it!
The "Going Home Club" refers to grade school students who are not involved in any school clubs' activities.
Though they are in the Going Home Club, they're getting plenty of exercise this morning.
Good health is always the number one priority.
Cell phone decoration?
Minori, you have skillful fingers.
Oh yeah, I don't look like it, but actually I am quite talented.
Kushieda...
...what is she doing?
I made it.  The first one is done.
Next is...
What kind of strangled voice is that?
N-Nothing.
Oh yeah, shall I make one for you, Takasu-kun?
I'm a cell phone decorator for a part-time job.
Decorator?
I put your name "Ryuji" with Swalo's purple rhinestones.
Kushieda can make one for me...?
No, No, I don't...
Kushieda.
Can you do ours too?
Orders?  Okay.
Fill out your name, favorite colors and image here.
I want pink, with a big heart...
She decorates cell phones part-time huh...?
Shiny Kushieda, shiny cell phone, what a amazing coupling!
Is Ya-chan coming home from accompanying her client tonight?  I want her meal...
She even remembered my given name Ryuji.
That's because I always call you that.
How about Ya-chan's meal...?
I talked with her a lot.
Taiga, I was able to talk to her without being ner...vous...
Listen to me, I'm telling you!
And just to let you know...you looked extremely nervous!
When is dinner ready?
Ow, that hurt!
It will be ready soon.
It's a bowl meal today.  I can serve it when the rice is done.
Hey!
What's the matter?
The rice cooker is broken.
Welcome, good evening.
What shall I order?
Why a family restaurant?  We didn't have rice...but we had bread.
You can only groan for now.
You'll end up appreciating what I've done.
Here are the two catering orders.
We haven't ordered yet...
Huh?!
It's a secret.  I dished up double ice cream for your Taiga Special.
Hide them from the other customers and eat.
Thank you as always, Minori.
Always?
You don't like sweets?  How about fried potatoes?
I'll serve plenty, like a lot.
No, I...
Minori, you are working for a convenience store and Karaoke Box, right?
Yeah!  I added a shabu shabu restaurant last week, too.
Shabu shabu is a Japanese variant of hot pot.
That much?!
I try not to work too much.
As the captain of the girls' softball team, I can't be absent from the club.
Why do you work so hard?  You want to buy anything?
I have time to work.  I must labor.
Labor...
That's right, the Mysterious Files of Labor.
Huh?
The resurrection of the Mysterious Files.
Anyway, you two look really close.
Waitress, another glass of water, please.
Well, enjoy your meals.
Ah, ouch!
My vision has gotten significantly worse in just one day.
You stupid mongrel, drooling at the sight of Minori in her uniform.
I just...
I only thought her smiling face was sparkling and radiant.
Don't hit my eyes.
If I do more, my fingers will be stained.
Crap!
But why is she juggling so many part-time jobs?
Didn't she say that she just wanted to work?
There might be reasons for her needing money.
Maybe money for her house or helping her sick mom...
She was saying that she just wanted to work.
But you know...
You should give up ideas like,
"Only I can truly understand her."
My sick feeling got worse.
Ah, I can't stand this.
Can you walk a distance behind me?  You make me sick.
Hey, Taiga, why are you talking like that?
You're cold.
Don't come so close.  When am I not mean?
Come to think of it, you're right.
Hi Inko-chan, thank you for waiting.
Here is your dinner.
I'll serve you a big amount, a super big amount.
Poo.
Are you ready, Inko-chan?
Poo, poo.
Poop!
Yeah, holiday mornings are so refreshing.  Do you agree, Taiga?
I shouldn't have told him.
What did you say?
Abandoning the duties of making breakfast and going to the family restaurant to see Minori.
No way, the rice cooker is still broken.
Then shouldn't you need to go to the appliance store first?
You said that you didn't like bread.
But it's okay for breakfast.
You're so overeager.
You don't look good in that outfit.
I left something at home!
Such a complicated man!
Let me go, please.
It doesn't matter what you wear.
Hey, boy!
Aren't you Mirano's son?
Ah, Uncle Inage.
Mirano?
Yeah, it is Yasuko's business name at the bar.
Hi.  Go two hundred meters straight from North Exit, I am Mirano-chan of Bishamon Tengoku.
How old do I look?  Twenty-three?
You're right.
I have good luck this morning.
I get to touch Mirano's DNA.
Good, good, it's got a nice firmness!
So great to be young.
Shall we go?
This man makes me mad.
Hey you guys,
if you haven't had breakfast yet, I recommend Fish Meat, full of calcium and DHA.
You?
Kushieda?
Minori?
Here, carry these boxes.
W-Why?
Here, one more.
I had better carry...
Don't worry.
You can sip a cup of tea, Mirano's son.
Why...do I...have to do this kind of job?!
I hire Kushieda only for the holidays.
Kushieda, work hard!
All right, count on me!
Good.
My business has been very busy lately.
I need more manpower.
Manpower?
Because you're Kushieda's friend, would you try working here part-time?
I'll pay good wages.
Yes,
I'll do it.
With her.
How can I continue doing this?!
Don't cause any trouble for Kushieda.
Then you can help by yourself.
Hey, small one, can you deliver three cases of beer?
Yes, gladly!
Alright, that's all.
Be careful.
What's the matter,Taiga?
Don't tell me...you can't ride a bike?
Shut up!
It's not a problem just because I can't ride a bike!
The point is that it is delivered, right?!
Wrong direction.  Wrong direction!
You're so exciting, Taiga!
This worries me.
Pushing the bike is safe...I guess?
I have to restock the Shochu.
Shochu is a Japanese distilled liquor.
I'll...I'll help you.
B-Because I'd feel bad, if I didn't help.
Sure, I'll accept your offer!
O-Okay!
Well, where is the potato vodka...?
It's kind of dark and you can't really see anything...
Yeah.
No one really uses this place.
We only open it like once a week.
I see.
It would be awful if you got locked in,
then you would just have to enjoy being forgotten.
That kid, leaving the darn door open.
Hey, there are still people in here!
S.O.S., S.O.S.!
You have to relax, Takasu-kun!
Kushieda...?
There is a result to this occurrence.
Huh?
A result?
Yeah.
I feel like an idiot...
There's no need for me to be working this hard.
Seriously, I can't keep this up.
Can't keep what up?
Oh!
Ki-Kitamura-kun.
W-Why are you h-he-h-h-here?
Just some personal training...
By the way, is that Aisaka's?
Oh, um...yeah,
well, something like that.
Ah, you learned how to ride a bike?
What remarkable progress.
Oh...well...it's not exactly riding...
How do you know that I can't ride a bike?
Well, last year I kept a close observation of you.
Bikes are so nice, aren't they?
They really open the world up.
Well, see you tomorrow, Aisaka.
Last year, he was...
...me...
Ow...dammit!
A world that Kitamura-kun won't watch me in...
...is pointless even if it opens up!
Dammit!
You're back late...you look-
Never mind...but where are the other two?
Speaking of that, I wonder where Kushieda has wandered off to.
But Ryuuji-kun wandering off is fine.
That mongrel, just lazing around while I work my heart and soul out!
What are you talking about?
Anyway, the next delivery is to the Third Street-
Ryuji!  What the hell are you doing?!
"Oh, oh, the bridge that connects to the future,"
"That bridge, bridge...!"
Ah, my voice is all hoarse now.
No one notices even when we are making this much noise.
Around this time the shopkeeper is too absorbed with his horse racing.
Is that so...
It's getting a bit colder, isn't it?
If you want, you can wear my jac-
Alright, let's warm up!
Huh?
The pitcher is freaking out, hey, hey, hey...
Freaking out?  But the pitcher is Kushieda...
Freaking out, hey!
...the pitcher is freaking out, hey, hey, hey!
The pitcher is freaking out, hey, hey, hey...
Wait, is she actually freaking out in reality?
...freaking out!
Your hand is shaking.
Eh, oh no, that's just shaking with excitement.
Okay, I'm gonna go!
Hey!
Strike!
Okay, change.
Let's switch places.
Oh...sure...
Because it's pointless to freak out...
So that's why you bat away all your weaknesses.
Kushieda...
By some chance...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Can't we get out from there?
Where are they, where are they?
Where are they, where are they?!
Where are they?!  Where are they?!
Where are they?!
Look, Takasu-kun.
Over there, huh.
Maybe the reason why Kushieda looks like she's sparkling all the time,
isn't because she's bright and happy.
Whoa!
Ah, watch out!
Kushieda, my bad!
Are you okay?
Wah, n-nose bleed.
Oh, it's all good!
It's all good?!
Nose bleeds are perspiration from the heart.
Plus, we only have a bit more to go.
Pile 'em up, Takasu!
Yes!
Oh I see, batting away all the weaknesses.
Alright!  We will make this succeed!
Yeah, sure!
Fight oh!
Eh?
If I say, "Fight oh," you reply?
O-One shot?
That's right!  Oh, it's coming!
Fight oh!
O-One shot!
That's right,
Kushieda sparkled from the very beginning.
When I met her,
Fight oh!
and even now.
One shot!
She glitters!
Eh?!
I
finally
found
you!
Taiga?!  How did you get in here?
What do you mean, how?  I used a ladder.
Yes!  Takasu-kun, we can get out now!
Uh...but...
Thank you, Taiga!
This is definitely the bridge that connects us to the future!
But...Minori...
Takasu-kun, hurry and get up!
I was trying to tell you!
I accidentally...
...dropped the ladder.
Tucked away deep in my heart,
the memory of the two of us that I cannot tell anyone.
Oh, I've talked to Takasu about it.
Kitamu-!