♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLING]
HUH?
- THINK YOU FORGOT THIS.
- OH!
BUT WHAT WOULD
AN OLD FART LIKE ME
BE DOING WITH
A STUFFED TOY?
AND I DON'T HAVE
ANY RUGRATS EITHER.
BUT I DIDN'T SAY
IT WAS YOURS,
NOW, DID I?
AH, IT'S A CUSTOMER'S.
A KID PROBABLY LOST IT.
UHH...
HEY, LISTEN.
THE EVENING'S YOUNG.
I KNOW A ROCKING JOINT.
CARE TO JOIN ME
AND CHECK IT OUT?
NO, I HIT THE SACK EARLY.
I'M NOT A NIGHT PERSON.
IT'S A FIRSTRATE HOTEL
THAT OFFERS FREE
BODYGUARD SERVICE AND MEALS.
THE PLACE HAS EVERY AMENITY.
ONE COULD... LIVE THERE.
I'M SURE THEY REQUIRE RESERVATIONS.
HMM. NOPE,
YOU DON'T NEED ONE
FOR HOTEL PRISON, TEDDY BOMBER.
NICE OFFER, BUT I'LL PASS,
SPIKE SPIEGEL.
OH, YOU KNOW ME?
ANYONE WHO HAS A PRICE
ON HIS HEAD KNOWS WHO YOU ARE.
WE DREAD GETTING CAUGHT
BY EITHER YOU OR ANDY.
ANDY?
I'M FINISHING
WHAT I SET OUT TO DO.
UH!
HA HA!
SORRY, PAL,
NO FIREWORKS TODAY,
BECAUSE I PULLED
THE IGNITION PIN OUT.
UH!
AH! UH!
AAH!
[GRUNTS]
3 MILLION, PAL.
THOSE WOOLONGS ARE MINE.
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE BEAR.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU'LL BE KILLED, TOO.
WELL, NOBODY LIVES FOREVER.
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO BLOW EVERYTHING UP?
BECAUSE, SPIEGEL,
THAT'S HOW I DELIVER A WARNING.
I'M SOUNDING THE ALARM,
ALERTING THE MASSES.
YOU'D BETTER LISTEN UP
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
[HOOFBEATS]
[CRASH]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
ANDY!
ANDY?
[WHISTLES]
TCH, TCH, TCH.
YOU CAN CALL ME WYATT EARP.
HUH?
REACH FOR THE SKY,
TEDDY BOMBER!
WHO, ME?!
I FIGURED THAT YOU'D PLANT
AN EXPLOSIVE HERE TODAY.
IT WASN'T DIFFICULT
AFTER I STUDIED
YOUR CRIME PATTERNS
AND PROFILED
YOUR CRIMINAL MIND.
THAT'S YOUR
SERIAL BOMBER THERE!
YEAH, RIGHT,
THAT OLD SECURITY GUARD.
BUT LOOK AT HIS FACE, ANDY!
FACES ARE TOO UNRELIABLE
TO COUNT ON NOWADAYS.
THEN WHAT DO YOU RELY ON?
WELL, MY... GUT INSTINCT.
AND INSPIRATION.
[GROANS]
HEY, COME BACK HERE!
YAHOO!
UGH! AAK!
WE'RE ALL DOOMED!
[LAUGHS]
AW, NUTS.
I TOLD YOU THAT WAS
TEDDY BOMBER, YOU IDIOT!
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
- LET'S RIDE, YEEHAW!
WAAH!
PHEW! THAT ONE
WAS MIGHTY CLOSE.
HYAH! GET AFTER HIM!
[GROANS]
HORSE, YOU SAY?
HORSE, CORRECT.
A HORSE, HUH?
I THOUGHT IT SOUNDED
KIND OF FISHY
WHEN YOU SAID YOU'D NAB HIM
WHILE YOU WERE OUT FORAGING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN YOU SPENT
ALL OUR FOOD MONEY, DIDN'T YOU?
- I WHAT?
- WHAT DID YOU BLOW IT ON?
IF I'M LYING,
THEN HOW THE HELL
TO DO YOU EXPLAIN THIS
ON MY BACK?!
OK, OK. CHILL.
I TOTALLY BUY THE HORSE.
YOU DO?
BUT YOU'RE LACKING CREATIVITY
IN THE COWBOY CHARACTER.
HE'S LAME.
YEAH, MAYBE THAT'S
THE PROBLEM.
PERHAPS IF HE WAS
A SAMURAI INSTEAD.
NOW THAT I WOULDN'T QUESTION.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
HERE HE IS, LITTLE ANDY!
HE WAS REGISTERED
AS A MEMBER OF THE YMCA.
- HOW ABOUT THAT?
- HE'S A CHRISTIAN?
NO, NOT THAT Y,
THE YOUNG MEN'S
COWBOY ASSOCIATION.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF THAT ONE BEFORE.
OH, AND HE GOT KICKED OUT
SHORTLY AFTER HE JOINED.
THE REASON?
FOR BEING A NUISANCE
TO OTHERS.
THAT FIGURES.
ANDY VON DE ONIYATE.
HE'S THE HEIR
TO THE ONIYATE RANCH.
AND HE'S PRETTY HANDSOME.
DAMAGE TO PRIVATE PROPERTY,
123 COUNTS.
DAMAGE TO PUBLIC PROPERTY,
89 COUNTS.
NUMEROUS INJURY VICTIMS.
HE SURE REMINDS ME OF SOMEONE.
SEE, HE EXISTS!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
ANYTHING?
NO, NOT YET.
HOWEVER, WE CAN'T
CHANCE AN EXPLOSION
WITH ALL THESE PEOPLE AROUND.
HE'S ONLY TARGETING
THE BUILDING.
MURDER ISN'T PART OF HIS M.O.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
HIS TYPE IS MORE CONCERNED
WITH AESTHETICS.
WELL, HE COULDN'T PICK
A BETTER PLACE TO HIDE
THAN A MASQUERADE PARTY.
THERE'S A SERIAL BOMBER
COMING TONIGHT, YOU KNOW.
OH, REALLY?
I WASN'T AWARE OF THAT.
OH, HE'LL BE HERE.
MY MAN.
HUH?
IT'S ALL ABOUT MAKING
LOVE AND PEACE IN THE WORLD,
SUGAR BEAR.
YO.
HOW DID YOU KNOW IT WAS ME?
THIS BABY SHOWED US
THE WAY TO PAPA.
YEAH, AND THE TEDDY BEAR SUIT
WASN'T A TIPOFF AT ALL.
GEEZ, YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO QUIT, DO YOU?
LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
WHAT'S WITH
YOUR BOMB OBSESSION, BABY?
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
I'M HERE TO BRING
A WARNING TO THE WORLD.
LISTEN, HEED THESE WORDS:
THE ROOT OF ALL EVIL IS... AAH!
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[DING]
[CROWD MURMURS]
[COUGHS]
A HORSE.
A COWBOY.
I KNOW THAT'S YOU,
TEDDY BOMBER.
HUH? WHO, ME?
I TOLD YOU.
OR IS IT YOU?
AH! ARE YOU
BRAINDEAD OR WHAT?
WE MET EACH OTHER YESTERDAY!
HMM. I DON'T RECOLLECT.
- WHY, YOU!
- EXCUSE ME, SIR,
HORSES AREN'T ALLOWED IN HERE,
AND IT'S QUITE DISTURBING
FOR OUR CUSTOMERS.
AHA, BUT MY ONYX
IS NO ORDINARY STEED.
SHE'S A GOOD COMPADRE
WHO EASES MY MIND
AND PLAYS A DECENT
GAME OF CHESS.
HORSES CAN'T PLAY CHESS!
WHO CARES?
IF IT'S ONE THING I HATE,
IT'S BEING IGNORED!
HUH?
[SCREAMING]
WHAT HAPPENED TO AESTHETICS?
CALM DOWN! CALM DOWN, FOLKS!
REMEMBER PEACE AND LOVE.
- MY, WHAT A LOVELY ANIMAL.
- DO YOU LIKE HORSES, MA'AM?
HOW ABOUT A RIDE?
SURE. MY PLEASURE.
AAH!
HA HA HA!
YOU!
AAH!
OH!
UGH.
I'VE NEVER BEFORE
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE
SEEN SUCH A TOTAL
LACK OF TASTE.
[ONYX NEIGHS]
PREPARE FOR A TREAT.
THIS IS MY OWN SPECIAL RECIPE,
CALLED SON-OF-A-GUN STEW.
IT'LL SURE BLAZE A TRAIL.
HA HA HA!
[CHEWING]
UGH!
SO WHY WOULD A MAN LIKE YOU
BECOME A BOUNTY HUNTER?
SINCE YOU'RE SO RICH--
I MEAN, YOU HAVE SUCH
THAT'S TRUE. BUT WHY?
I'D HAVE TO SAY
BECAUSE IT SUITS ME.
HUH?
AND BOY, WHAT A RUSH!
LIKE A COWBOY CORNERING A BULL!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
BUT SERIOUSLY,
SUCH A DANGEROUS LINE OF WORK
SEEMS UNNECESSARY.
NOW I UNDERSTAND WHY
NO ONE GOES AFTER TEDDY BOMBER.
MMM?
NOBODY WANTS TO GET
HIS BUTT BLOWN OFF
IN SOME DAMN EXPLOSION.
WELL, WE CAN'T
WORRY ABOUT THAT.
MA'AM, I CAN'T
WHEN MY MIND IS SET,
WELL, I'M WEARING BLINDERS.
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS.
OH, THAT PERSONALITY
IS WAY TOO FAMILIAR.
- MMM?
- NO, NOTHING. HA HA HA!
- NOW...
- HUH?
WHY DON'T WE DRINK TO ME
AND MY REFLECTION
IN YOUR LOVELY EYES?
- CHEERS.
- YEAH, CHEERS.
[DOOR OPENS]
BROUGHT YOU A SOUVENIR.
YEEHAH! SOUVENIR, SOUVENIR!
I'M NOT GOING TO EAT
THIS CAN OF CRAP.
BUT IT'S ALL WE'VE GOT.
I'D RATHER STARVE.
[DOG BARKS]
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
ANDY REALLY
PUSHES YOUR BUTTONS.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT HIM
THAT GETS YOU SO BENT?
I KNOW WHY HE HATES THE GUY.
THEY'RE TOO MUCH ALIKE.
WHAT PART OF ME COULD BE
ANYTHING LIKE THAT STUPID ASS?
THE PART THAT MAKES YOU
SO DAMN TROUBLESOME.
MMHMM.
HEY, WE'RE MISSING
"BIG SHOTS"! IT'S ALREADY ON!
OUR FINAL NEWS ITEM
IS ON TED BOWER,
THE TEDDY BOMBER,
A.K.A. T.B.
T.B. SENT A LETTER
TO OUR STATION
TO READ ON OUR SHOW.
WHAT? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
UM, HERE WE GO.
"A WARNING: ALL OF YOU WHO
PUT ME DOWN AND LAUGHED AT ME,
"THE JOB I DO NEXT
IS YOUR LAST CHANCE.
THIS TIME I WILL BLOW YOU UP
AS WELL LIKE FIREWORKS."
SHUCKS, HOWDY!
THAT'S A RATHER HARSH TONE!
"UNLESS YOU CAN FIGURE OUT
WHAT MY NEXT TARGET WILL BE.
"HA HA HA. LASTLY, I SHALL TELL
YOU MY PURPOSE FOR DOING THIS."
OOPS! WELL, JUDY,
IT SEEMS WE'VE RUN OUT OF TIME.
THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T
READ ALL OF IT, T.B.
TILL NEXT TIME, FOLKS.
GOOD LUCK!
[GUNSHOT]
[THEME MUSIC]
HE'S GOING TO BLOW UP
CITY HALL.
YOU KNOW ALREADY?
TARGETS HAVE BEEN BY HEIGHT,
STARTING WITH
THE TALLEST BUILDING.
REALLY. IT WAS SOMETHING
AS SIMPLE AS THAT?
I'M OUT.
I DON'T WANT THIS ONE.
- YEAH, I'M GOING TO PASS, TOO.
- SPIKE, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
LIKE YOU HAVE TO ASK!
[RUNNING WATER]
OHH. THEY'RE LATE!
DAMN THEM.
THOSE FOOLS ARE SADLY MISTAKEN
IF THEY THINK
THEY'LL GET AWAY WITH THIS.
OH!
YOU ALONE?
HOW DARE YOU INSULT ME
BY SHOWING UP LATE!
WAIT!
[WHISTLING]
OH, DAMN, IT'S THE WRONG GUY.
YOU KNOW, IT HAS NEVER BEEN
MY INTENTION TO MURDER ANYONE.
BUT IN YOUR CASE,
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION!
BASTARDS LIKE YOU
DESERVE TO BE
- SHH!
- HUH?
[WHISTLING]
AH, HE'S HERE.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
SO, YOU AGAIN.
FINALLY REMEMBERED ME, HUH?
YOU'RE ALWAYS--
YOU'RE ALWAYS,
ALWAYS BUTTING IN!
STAY OUT OF MY WAY!
WHAT?!
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S ALWAYS IN THE WAY!
NOW THAT I HAVE BOTH
OF YOU GENTLEMEN HERE TOGETHER,
I WILL EXPLAIN MY REASON
FOR BLOWING UP THINGS.
THE REASON IS...
LET'S SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
DAMN IT, YOU STOLE MY LINE!
WHY WON'T YOU LISTEN TO ME!!
Both: SHUT UP!
WHAT DO YOU WANT? WHO ARE YOU?
HUH?!
OH, WHY CAN'T YOU
TAKE ME SERIOUSLY?!
DAMN, WE'VE GOT
TO CATCH HIM FIRST!
HEY, WAIT!
COME ON!
HUH?
HA!
YOU FELLOWS HAVE
GROSSLY UNDERESTIMATED ME.
THAT ELEVATOR DOOR
IS NEVER GOING TO OPEN AGAIN!
SOON THE CAR WILL START MOVING,
AND THAT WILL BE THE END!
IT WON'T STOP UNTIL IT ARRIVES
AT THE TOP FLOOR.
THERE MY ADORABLE
LITTLE TEDDY BEARS
ARE WAITING TO GREET YOU.
AND AT THE VERY MOMENT
THE ELEVATOR REACHES THEM,
BOOM!!
HA HA HA!
LET ME LEAVE YOU
WITH A WORD OF ADVICE:
ENJOY THE REST OF YOUR LIVES
WITHOUT REGRET.
[CHUCKLES]
GOOD LUCK.
NOW DON'T PANIC.
I'M ONE STEP AHEAD
OF OLD TEDDY BOMBER.
REST ASSURED, I KNOW
EXACTLY HOW HIS MIND WORKS.
HMM?
I KNEW THAT HE WOULD ALTER
THE SECRET EMERGENCY
ACCESS CODE,
SO I REVERTED IT
THIS AFTERNOON. YEAH.
BUT I REVERTED IT
THIS AFTERNOON!
IF I DID, AND YOU DID,
THAT MEANS IT'S BACK
TO WHAT IT WAS!
STOP IT, YOU MORON!
WHA... WHAT DO WE DO?!
OH, NO!!
UH! GET DOWN, IT'S TOO TIGHT!
LET ME BACK!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
FOND FAREWELL.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THEY WERE A PAIR
OF TRULY BRAVE YOUNG MEN.
HMM?
YEOW!
THEY'RE CLIMBING UP,
LIKE A COUPLE OF MONKEYS.
I GUESS THEY LIKE
TO BE UP HIGH.
SCARY HOW SIMILAR THEY ARE.
CAN WE LEAVE NOW?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
I JUST HAVE TO DROP
THIS GUY OFF FIRST.
YOU DON'T EVEN DESERVE
TO STAND IN THE SHADOW
OF A COWBOY!
YOU'RE ONE PERSON
WHO I COULD NEVER FORGIVE.
[CLICKING]
AAH!
WELL?
[GROWLING]
UH!
[RUMBLING]
HUH? OOPS.
[CREAKING]
AAH! AH!
AAH!!
[GRUNTING]
YOU WIN.
THAT WAS SOME PUNCH.
HMM?
I SEE NOW THAT
YOU'RE THE REAL COWBOY.
[DING]
AS OF TODAY,
I RETIRE FROM THE JOB.
MY HAT'S OFF TO YOU, PARTNER.
[CHUCKLING]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
I HAVE NO DOUBT
I'LL FIND SOME NEW CAREER.
SEE YOU, SPACE COWBOY.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
IT WAS ONLY
A RICH BOY'S HOBBY.
HE WAS ON A DIFFERENT LEVEL,
OR SHOULD I SAY,
OUT OF HIS LEAGUE WITH ME.
HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING?
YEAH, YEAH.
ANDY WASN'T MY ADVERSARY
AFTER ALL.
OF COURSE I NEVER REALLY
HAD ANYTHING PERSONAL
AGAINST THE GUY.
YOWWEE! YOW! YAHHOW! YAHOO!
HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING?!
YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, ANYWAY.
WHAT WERE YOU TRYING TO ACHIEVE
BY BLOWING EVERYTHING UP?
I ONLY WANTED
TO SEND OUT A WARNING
AGAINST THE NEEDLESS WASTE
CREATED BY CAPITALISM
WITHOUT PHILOSOPHY,
THE NEEDLESS COLONIZATION
OF PLANETS,
THE NEEDLESS CIRCULATION
OF SLANTED MEDIA,
AND NEEDLESSLY TALL BUILDINGS
THAT SYMBOLIZE ALL OF THIS!
YOU SEE,
BY DESTROYING THESE MONOLITHS,
I INTENDED TO REMIND THE WORLD
WHAT THE PIONEERING SPIRIT
IS TRULY ABOUT.
WAIT, WAIT! WAIT!!
HUH?
ANDY.
CALL ME MUSASHI! HA HA!
GO, JINOMARU!
[HORSE NEIGHS]
BUT THEN, IT WAS ONLY THIS,
TOO, WASN'T IT?
"COWBOY BEBOP."
SO, DID EVERYONE CATCH ME
IN ACTION THIS PAST EPISODE?
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
NOW ABOUT THE NEXT EPISODE...
WHY ARE YOU DOING THE PREVIEW?
ONCE AGAIN, I, ANDY,
WILL BE THE MAN IN ACTION.
YOU HAD YOUR TURN ALREADY.
NOW THAT I HAVE
BECOME A SPACE SAMURAI,
I WILL SLICE UP THE COWBOYS
ONE BY ONE!
I SAID, YOU'RE
NOT COMING BACK.
NEXT TIME, ON COWBOY BEBOP,
ANDY'S COUNTERATTACK.
THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT TITLE!
COWBOY BEBOP.