kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
...is how the arrangements came out.
Roger.
The strategy meeting—
Are you going out, Kana-chan?
Good morning!
So you're going to use up your first paycheck right away?
Not all of it!
I have good intentions.
After all this time, I wanted to get some presents or something, and then...
...buy something for yourself as well, right?
Yes!
Since the first month was only training, you didn't get much, huh?
You're happy, right?
Yeah.
But I was surprised.
I heard that there were usually issues with the wages, and that we're paid in military scrip.
Here. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much!
I never thought I'd receive real money.
Well, of course! That's because our platoon was set up to—!
Kanata!
Um, that is, you see...
There's a fair today!
It's your first one, right?
Your first paycheck and your first day off, is it?
You're having all kinds of firsts this week, aren't you, Kanata-chan?
Forget about your occupation and enjoy yourself!
Yes, ma'am!
Kanata's Day Off
Hairdressing
I'm heading off!
I told you not to let Kanata suspect anything!
Come on!
If you really think about it,
even if we weren't in the middle of nowhere and our supplies weren't always delayed,
they would still never give us actual money.
Even so, Kanata simply believed you.
It's best if she stays innocent.
Yeah.
It's not like she'll figure out where the money comes from anytime soon, unlike you two.
Right!
Now then.
With that, how about we forget our normal occupations as well?
It came out well.
Right?
But there is one problem.
At this point, there's nothing left but to say you lost.
I-I'm sorry! I wasn't paying attention.
It looks like the preparations are complete.
Yeah.
There were no problems at all.
There was a problem on my side.
Concerning that one proposition, will you help?
Please tell us the details.
This is cute as well!
So it's you?
These are the sellers?
Has something caught your attention?
It's not bad.
However...
...there's a bit of a problem.
My, what could it be?
Just this case.
Although it sells, it will take a lot of time and effort.
When you think about it like that, we're a little short on manpower.
Therefore—
We don't give discounts on principle.
The cost is a part of its flavor.
It's not like we're saying that we've lost or anything...
We'll just take all of it!
Stop right there!
Just try shooting.
Then again, maybe I'll be able to pull the trigger before you can,
and this time I might just blow a hole in your head just like that hat.
In that case!
How foolish.
This is your punishment for taking us lightly.
Good night, boys.
Like I said...
Hey.
Are you two with them?
Mishio-chan!
Th-The car!
Boss!
Give it up!
But the Don's souvenirs...
...are worthless if we're dead!
Boss!
Forget it! I'm never coming back to this town with those dangerous people!
You heard them.
Indeed.
Well, that's enough everyone!
Well now, that was exciting.
It seems we deceived them somehow.
We are grateful for your cooperation.
Not at all. If we had gotten involved with the mafia, our business would be doomed.
It's a dog-eat-dog world, right?
Nevertheless, for our part in this act, of course you'll be giving us our due, right?
Oh, please! You're full of jokes, Mikhail-san.
No, no, no. It's not a joke.
From here on, it's back to business.
About that... why don't you leave those with me?
Weren't you the ones who crushed their car?
It wasn't you?
What is it?
No?
It seems like someone crushed their car.
There was a pile of goods from the fair inside.
How about I say I bought them, and then we split the profits?
It appears we've reached an agreement.
Yes.
This farce is finally over.
But I was a bit surprised.
About what?
Because you were in high spirits.
If it got out that we're moonshining, we'd have to apologize in a court martial.
Monopoly law violation and tax law violation as well.
Worst case, charged with treason.
You're right.
It may be a side job handed down to us from our senpai,
but Rio never once objected.
Even I'm a bit surprised.
I was surprised at first.
The drink that my mother loved, this calvados...
When I found out it was made at the fort...
Then perhaps it was your mother that guided your assignment to our platoon.
Well, I'm heading off!
Yumina-oneechan!
I'm done! Look!
It's very nice, Seiya-san.
Mishio-san.
Today is your first visit to the church.
The pastor is also coming.
So, just for today...
No!
Don't trouble Onee-chan, Mishio!
What's wrong with her doing your hair properly?!
She can't! I won't let her!
Why not?!
You're always bugging me to do mine! You're so annoying!
Shut up, Seiya!
You shouldn't do that, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10.25 yen.
Watch out, little girl.
I-I'm sorry! I wasn't paying attention.
Seriously, people like you...
Those two are the problem.
It seems they somehow caught wind of the transaction.
Are you all right?
Yes.
But, Naomi-san! What should I do?
This is the first time I've ever had money in my wallet.
If I say I want it now, I could finally buy it, right?
Hey, if someone came and snatched up that dolphin, what would you do?
What?!
Is there someone who said they wanted it?
No, it's just a "what if" situation.
Let's see... If it was me...
I know! I'd tell them to give up because dolphins are super scary animals that eat humans.
You're a genius!
I can hold onto that dolphin until you need it, so don't worry about it.
Well, I'd better find presents for everyone first.
Um... there's Dad, Mom, Auntie and Uncle, Grandma and Grandpa Warren, Great-Grandmother...
Oh, and Auntie Nanae from next door!
Wow! They're selling so many different things!
Like this!
Sorry...
Huh? Mishio-chan?
Are you buying something?
It seems like she's searching for a box.
A box?
Like this. Have you seen it anywhere?
Sorry.
If you're looking for it, can I help?
Kanata, what are you doing?
I'm buying presents.
I was wondering if there were any wonderful things I could send to my family in the country.
But I'm not busy, so...
I don't need your help!
What's wrong with Mishio-chan?
Th-This is kind of...
What a wonderful shirt.
This is cute as well.
Yumina-san?
Um, Kanata-san, have you seen Mishio-san?
A box?
Yes. I think it was something important to her.
Is that so?
When her mother passed away, all of their belongings were taken.
When that happened, it seems that box—a memento from her mother—was also taken.
Every time there is a fair in town, she hopes...
I said something bad.
I got my first wages yesterday, so I thought I would send something to my family.
That is fine.
Right now, I... we are trying to be Mishio-san's family.
Even so, if you say Mishio-san is jealous...
Then it is all because I am not doing an adequate job.
Hey, Mama, which is more important, your treasure box, or me?
You!
Mama...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
So! How about Treize's famous firecrackers!
Such a loud sound! How about it?
Onee-chan...
Yumina-oneechan...
Onee-chan!
Mishio-chan!
Th-The car!
I'm sorry I'm not Yumina-san.
Onee-chan!
Yumina-oneechan!
Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Now then...
Um...
H-Hey, what is it?
Could it be... that car...
...was Naomi-san's?
Don't tell me that was you two?!
I'm sorry!
Um... I have 150 yen here! The car...
You sure helped us out, you two.
Take care of that.
The payment has already been taken care of.
N-Naomi-san! That's...
These ideograms mean "Beautiful Ear of Rice".
If you carve these onto her seal stamp, she should live a life of happiness like that of a bountiful rice field.
My...
Miho, you've received a good name. Isn't that great?
Did you find Mishio-san?
Even though I try to be her family,
and intended for her to accept me in her heart...
I am still inexperienced.
No, you're doing your best.
Mishio-san!
I'm glad you found it!
You have to take care of it.
It's the only thing left with your mother's memories...
You're wrong!
I... want Yumina... to have this...
Mishio-san is one of the children taken in by the Church when their families died.
First, her father was sent to the front lines and never returned.
And her mother?
Her family lived on the eastern border of Vingt.
You don't mean...
Yes, the town that was touched by the "Invisible Reaper."
And when the two of them came to Seize, her mother was showing signs of the illness, and before long...
Mama told me...
"I'm sorry I can't do you hair anymore."
And then... And then she told me to give them to the person who was the most important to me.
And that's Yumina.
Humans go on living.
For example, when we're separated from those precious to us,
and it feels as if we could die, we will still continue to live.
We can still go on living.
That strength is very sorrowful, but also a display of great willpower.
I'm sorry, and thank you... Onee-chan...
Everyone is already in the bath.
Okay! I'll go soon.
You worked hard, didn't you?
I wanted to avoid washing my hair, but a lot happened.
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Well then, senpai. Let me dry your hair for you.
I wanted to feel it once.
In the end, you didn't buy the dolphin?
I thought that would be your treat for yourself.
Rio-senpai, do you believe in fate?
What's that, all of a sudden?
It's just that... I thought that today.
That was enough of a reward to fill me up!
I don't believe in it.
I hate the idea that everything was decided and set from the beginning.
But, you're right.
A coincidence brought forth by someone could go around and around and make a stranger's life grander.
If that could be called fate...
Then maybe...
D-flat.
It looks like Senpai also had a wonderful day.
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
The Chirping Crickets
Offerings for the Deceased
Next time: The Chirping Crickets · Offerings for the Deceased