Mister!
That armor!
It's the mark of a Trump Kingdom warrior!
What were you to the princess?
My name is Jonathan Klondike.
Princess Ann's fiancé.
The princess's fiancé?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Solitaire
Help yourselves.
Now, ask away.
There's so much to ask, I don't know where to begin!
So you know about Ai and the Royal Crystals?
Is it true that you're the princess's fiancé?
I'll answer one at a time.
First off...
I'm a survivor from Trump Kingdom, just like you.
"Joe Okada" was simply a persona I assumed to blend into this world.
Next,
I've seen these Royal Crystals before.
I knew they were real right away.
So they were real.
Thank goodness.
So, what about Ai?
Beats me!
I can say that I picked up her egg by the river.
She's a strange baby.
You're not playing dumb again, are you?
No trust, huh?
It's 'cause you always act suspicious!
And lastly, my relationship with Ann.
We most certainly did vow to spend the rest of our lives together.
I never heard a word of this from the princess!
I suppose not.
This was before you served under Ann.
Don't refer to the princess with pet names!
Hey now, let's calm down...
Going back, there's one thing I must mention.
There are five Royal Crystals in total.
When all five are gathered,
a miraculous trump card will appear.
A miraculous trump card?
What's that?
I don't know the details, either.
All I can say for certain is that we should gather the crystals and save Trump Kingdom.
You're right.
If we put off the one that Regina took,
there's only one crystal remaining.
But we've got no idea where it is.
And for that, I have...
this.
Traveling with Joe Okada
The First Trip of Summer
What's this?
A travel guide.
This is no time for a vacation!
A steam train and a rape blossom field?
They're photos of a train on a scenic railroad.
This scenery looks much like a place that holds many memories for Ann and I.
A place that... holds memories?
He's the one that found it.
A trip, huh?
I understand!
Now, I'll go pack some lunches!
My, how exciting!
Oh, you two.
I guess we're going.
The final clue to the princess...
It's Appeared!
The Final Royal Crystal!
So this was a treasure handed down in the Trump Kingdom...
I'll be the judge of that.
Oh, what fine craftsmanship.
What would you know?
Just let me decide.
Hey, I'm not lettin' you swoop in and nab it!
I'm doing no such thing, so let go!
I can't let you mishandle that.
It's mine, after all.
So pretty...
This radiance belongs to me.
Yes, all of it.
What's eating her?
What a beautiful train!
It feels so dignified!
It's slower paced than a normal train.
That's what makes it charming!
Time for lunch!
Finally!
Ta-dah! Peach buns!
I made them with Dad!
We made plenty, so have as much as you like!
Don't mind if we do!
Here you go.
No thanks.
Let's drink
together!
I brought my own.
I see.
Is Makopi upset?
A maiden's heart is complex indeed.
Thanks for the food!
That was yummy.
Amazing!
Wait!
This wasn't a trip for pleasure!
You're right!
We've gotta look for that crystal!
Kyupirappa!
What's that?
What the...
Don't tell me...
Ai?!
That's weird...
We'll do a quick inspection just to be safe.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Why are you apologizing, ma'am?
Can't have a trip without a bit of trouble.
Mister, where are you...
Just a stroll.
We came all this way, so you should come too.
But we should wait here!
Impatience won't get you the crystal any faster!
Knowing his past doesn't make him any less unpredictable.
Ai!
Let's go, girls.
It's amazing!
This is the scenery he was talking about?
Ai may have lead us here.
It's just like Trump Kingdom when it was peaceful!
Is that so?
Yeah.
Can I have a minute?
Certainly.
You know,
back when we first met in the Clover Tower,
I thought you were a pretty strange person.
You never answered our questions clearly,
but for some reason, I never disliked you.
I'm sure that's because you were always showing us the way.
You're overestimating me.
The only ones who can defeat King Selfish and save Trump Kingdom
are the legendary Precure warriors.
The strength you've gained until your search for the crystals
was earned by your own efforts, and nobody else's.
Just a bit longer...
What was the princess like?
Makopi never told you?
I want to hear it from her lover!
You've got me there.
It's a bit of a long story, okay?
Hmm, the Ann that I knew...
Princess!
Where's the princess?
Here!
Though a swift stream
Princ—
What in the world are you doing?
Yet divided, it speeds on
and at last, unites again
Karuta.
It's a game from the human world.
She was a bit tomboyish, but still a lovely woman.
Ann was as curious as they come,
and was interested in cultures from around the world.
It's missing something...
Would this do?
I was a warrior in her service.
It's quite wonderful.
It didn't take long for us to fall for one another.
Soon after,
I was ordered to defend a faraway region.
I had no choice but to part from the castle.
But then...
that nightmare began.
Selfish!
Ann...
Ann!
Selfish!
Ann, where are you?
Is this...
Ann is in the world beyond...
Trump Kingdom... Ann...
Cure Sword wasn't the only one who couldn't save anyone.
I failed too.
Sorry.
It wasn't a very happy story.
I'm glad I heard it.
We should get back to the station.
Was that enough for you?
I swear we'll meet Ann again.
Yes.
Hey, kid!
What are you doing?
Lemme drive!
No, you can't!
I wanna drive!
I know how you feel!
You wanna do what you wanna do!
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Locomotive Selfish!
Chugga Coupling!
Is that...
Selfiiiiiiish!
It's a Selfish!
It's a train now?!
Selfish!
The flower field!
We have to stop it!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor train who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Hi, Mana!
Regina!
I came to take all the crystals from you.
Well, we won't let you!
Resistance is futile, you know.
'Cause I'll just take them by force.
Mister!
Leave her to me!
You girls stop that Selfish!
Good luck!
Stay out of my way, mister!
Return that crystal, if you'd please.
No way.
It belongs to me.
Then you leave me no choice.
Please stop!
How is it running without a railroad?
You're supposed to be a train!
Point! However...
I'm too off the rails to be railroaded!
That's absurd!
No matter who tries,
they ain't stopping the Selfish train!
SELFIIIIIIIIIISH!
If this keeps up...
Cure Heart!
What are you planning?
SELFIIIIISH!
Full speed ahead!
You can't go any further!
I won't let you harm...
his memories!
I swear that we'll meet the princess!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Self?
Seeelf!
Selfish!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooooove!
Huh? I lost already?
What now?
Want to continue?
I'm kinda bored...
so nah!
See ya!
Thank goodness, the train's safe.
This is...
The final crystal!
We've done it!
All that's left is the stolen red crystal!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
The winner gets the crystals!
It's a bet, Regina!
Dokidoki Precure:
Betting the Crystals!
A Selfish Game!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!