Wake up! Armin! Hey!
Can you hear me? C'mon!
Snap out of it! I need you to talk to me! Say something!
There you are. You with me now?
What's going on? Where's your squad?
Squad?
Alright, let's get you on your feet.
You shouldn't be out here alone.
And what the hell you got all
over you that's so damn slimy?
What happened?
You're worthless! Why can't you just die?
Hey, you need to pull yourself together!
Damn you!
Where is everyone?
Let it go, Conny.
He's it. There rest of 'em are dead.
Damn it, don't talk like that!
We can't assume he's the only one!
Take a look around you; isn't it obvious?
We can't waste any more time here with him.
We've gotta move on.
You're not making any sense.
Why would the Titans ignore him?
I dunno. Maybe they thought he
was already dead or something.
When you get right down to it,
that's the real tragedy here.
Eren and the others bust their
asses, and the one left standing is him.
Alright. That does it, bitch.
I'm gonna shut your mouth up permanently!
Both of you stop it right now!
Look, we're all at the end of our tether, okay?
We're seeing our friends being killed like animals.
It's normal to be upset.
Look at my Christa keepin' the peace!
You're so gonna have to marry
me when all this crap is over!
Yeah, well...
She'd best get a hold of that mouth.
Alright. Come on. We gotta get out of here.
Are you able to stand?
Sorry to be a nuisance. Don't worry about me.
I'll rendezvous with the rear guard.
But... Armin!
Conny, hop to!
We've been given orders to advance!
I was wrong. This world hasn't become hell.
It's been hell. I just couldn't see it before now.
We're condemned. All of us. Have been from the beginning.
Strength preys on weakness.
It's a very straightforward arrangement, actually.
And my friends... They...
They tried. They knew how the world worked.
They wanted to be strong. For me.
Someone who only brought them down.
In their eyes, I was a victim.
I needed protection.
But all I wanted was to stand
shoulder- to-shoulder with them;
to be strong, like they were.
To be worth something.
And this is how it all ends up.
Eren tried to protect me and...
Hanna. What are you trying to do?
Oh god, Armin! Help me, please!
Franz quit breathing and I can't wake him up!
He won't respond to CPR! Come on, baby!
You got this! Stay with me!
Somebody help us!
Hanna, please. It's not safe on the ground,
we need to get you on a rooftop...
No! I'm not leaving him like this!
You really don't understand, do you?
Hanna, I'm sorry. Franz is...
Please stop. Please stop doing that.
I can't.
I... I can't take it.
This is hell.
What in the hell is wrong with you people?
I don't think you fully
appreciate how bad the situation is!
Oh, I appreciate it just fine, believe me!
You wanna make it out of here
alive, stop whining and help!
You're a soldier! Do something!
Make him move that damn wagon!
I'm not exactly sure...
Take your best shot, little man.
I'm the president of this town's merchant guild.
Uh... Well, I...
Who do you think pays all the bills for
the food you and your buddies crap out?
Or maybe you've got some finances tucked
away to fund the racket you call a job?
Now shut up and push! This cargo's worth
more than you people make in your whole lives!
Nobody's getting out of here
unless the wagon's in front of 'em!
There's a reward in it if you help!
Don't worry, sweetheart.
Daddy's going to use those big, loud
cannons he showed us to scare the Titans off.
Mommie, look. There.
Push it through, dammit!
If you don't, that thing's gonna kill us all!
Stop! You'll trample the children!
Someone wanna tell me why the
son of a bitch is ignoring us?
It's an Abnormal; stop trying to figure him out!
He's too fast! There's no way we'll
overtake him before he reaches the gate!
Just stay on him!
Excuse me. What is all this?
Couldn't have asked for better timing!
Force these useless morons to push my wagon!
I'll pay you handsomely!
Seriously? Soldiers are dying back there.
Laying down their lives for you.
All because this is taking too long.
Yeah, that's their job. You expect me to shed a tear
'cause they gotta fulfill the duties they signed on for?
They're supposed to be willing to lay down their lives!
Don't get all high-handed on me just 'cause you
finally gotta earn your damn keep after all these years!
Yeah. No arguing with that. You're absolutely right, sir.
Guess it's what you call the greater good. Still.
Sometimes it's not the life or the death of
a soldier that makes the biggest difference.
Don't you even dare! Your commander and I are old friends!
One word from me and you'll be court marshaled!
Believe it!
That word gonna come from beyond the grave?
No! Wait!
Sir, maybe we should uh...
Pull the damn wagon out.
You're amazing!
You've saved our lives, miss. All of us are in your debt.
Good work, Ackerman. I'm impressed.
I did what I could here, sir. But, thank you.
I need to be a bit more careful in the future.
I inadvertently dulled both of the blades.
I'll do better next time.
What on earth have you had to
live through to be so non-chalant.
I'm sorry. That was uncalled for.
Why do I have to suddenly think of you now?
I'm finished, Momma!
What do you think? Did I do good?
Oh, darling. It's absolutely fantastic! Excellent work!
Aww, thank you!
We've kept this style of embroidery a special
family secret for heaven knows how many generations.
One day, when you have children of your own,
you'll be able to pass the secret on to them.
Huh? I don't understand; how can I have children?
Uh. Honey, why don't you explain?
Yeah! Please, Daddy?
Well I'm not sure I'm really an expert on the subject.
But you know what? That nice Dr. Jaeger's scheduled
to pay us a visit today. Maybe you could talk to him.
Ah! Speak of the devil!
Just a moment.
Her name's Mikasa?
Yes, and she's just about your
age, so try to get along, okay?
There aren't really that many children around
here and I'd rather you not grow up to be an outcast.
If she's nice to me, then we won't have a problem.
Eren. Look for the bad in people
expecting to find it and you will.
That's odd. Are they home?
Mr. Ackermann! It's Dr. Jaeger!
Is anyone there?
Well are they or aren't they?
Dad? What's wrong?
Damn it.
Look around. Can you see the daughter anywhere?
Perhaps she's outside.
I don't think so.
This is bad. I need to alert the Military
Police of this while the trail's warm.
Wait for me at the foot of the mountain.
Understood? Say that back to me. Word for word.
Eren!
Uh-huh. All I'm sayin' is she
better go for a decent price.
I didn't get blood on my hands for nothing.
Look at her face and tell me what's she's worth.
Sure, she's cute and all. Just young.
Wouldn't go for her myself.
Then I guess we're lucky you're
not the one we're sellin' to.
Plenty of folks'd pay a premium.
She's exotic; what they used to call an "Oriental."
You know about all that, right? Back when
there used to be different breeds of people.
A bunch of 'em from the Far East
came scramblin' here for safety.
The old perverts in the capital
really go for that sort of thing.
This li'l beauty's gonna fetch a mint at auction.
It's great business; she's the last of her kind.
All the rest of her people died out.
Tell me another one.
It's not like she's a pureblood or anything.
Her old man wasn't "Oriental."
Good point there.
The mother would've been a nice addition, right?
Too bad she's in pieces!
Gimme a break! What was I supposed to do?
She was puttin' up a fight!
So you couldn't have just knocked her unconscious?
We were just talking about you, Doctor...
Sorry. Hope we're not interrupting.
Let's take this nice and easy. I don't imagine anybody
wants their skulls split open by this little guy...
This bitch is out of her mind!
Run, Mikasa! Run as fast as you can!
Stop it; you're scaring me.
I want you to be scared! Move it! Get away from here!
Dad?
Screw it. You ain't worth this crap!
You stupid bastard! The plan was to only kill the father!
She was nuts! I'm supposed to let
her gouge my eyes out with those shears?
I don't want to hear it! Just bag the kid!
Fine!
Hey. Let's not give me any attitude, alright?
If you're feelin' feisty, this is what you get.
So cold.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't move from that spot, you little vermin.
How did you even you find this place?
Uh. Well, I was in the woods and got lost.
I saw your cabin and...
Lost in the woods, huh?
A kid your age shouldn't be out
there on his own to begin with.
Big bad wolves are liable to
pounce on you from outta nowhere.
It's alright now, though; you'll be safe here.
My buddy and I'll be happy to take y...
I appreciate that, sir. But I'm not stupid.
And I'm the last thing you'll ever see.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Hey, you little bastard! Get back here!
You're an animal! You hear me? No! You're a disease!
This is what you get, you son of a bitch!
This is what you get for being what you are!
Die! Die!
The hard part's over. You're safe now.
Anyway, Mikasa, right?
My name's Eren. I'm Dr. Jaeger's son.
I met your folks once or twice while I was with him.
We were stopping by your house today for a checkup.
We saw...
What happened to the third one?
This is all your doing, isn't it?
Answer me, you little bastard! You did this!
I'm gonna kill you! You're gonna die!
Take... Take him out.
Fight!
Kill or be killed. Fight for your life!
It's... It's the only way.
Who the hell do you think you are, you little brat?
The only way to live is to fight!
I can't. I don't think I can do this.
And all of a sudden, I remembered.
I'd seen it all before.
Many, many times. Since the day I was born.
It'd been all around me. Forever.
But...
I always looked the other way.
Yeah. The world is a cruel place.
And it's home.
All of a sudden, my body wasn't shaking.
I was in total control. Focused. Ready.
All of a sudden, I could do anything.
"Fight."
"Fight!"
Fight!
Stabbed through the heart from behind.
Surely a couple of kids couldn't've done this.
Damn it, son. I made it clear I wanted
you to wait at the foot of the mountain.
Do you even understand the magnitude
of what you've done here today?
Sorry, Dad. I'm not gonna feel bad for what happened.
They were animals disguised as
humans who needed to be put down.
Listen to yourself!
By the time the Military Police got here,
they'd have been long gone and you know it!
We couldn't afford to wait!
That's not what I'm arguing about!
You threw caution to the wind and survived by pure luck!
You're strong, yes,
but you are too damn young to be so
casual about gambling with your life!
But, I... I didn't know how
else I was supposed to save her.
Mikasa. Remember me? We met a few times before
when you were just a tiny little thing.
Yes, Dr. Jaeger. So, um...
Sorry, can you just tell me how to get home?
It's cold. I'm tired.
There's really nowhere else for me to go.
Don't worry. You can keep it.
That ought to keep you warm, right?
I think so.
Mikasa, how would you feel about coming to live with us?
What?
I can't even imagine what you've been through.
But I do know you need your share of rest.
What's the problem?
Don't think about it. Just come on.
We gotta get home.
Yeah. Okay.
The world's a cruel place.
If you want to live, you have to fight.
That's it. We're done.
Now scale the wall.
I should help the vanguard withdraw, sir.
Ackerman! Wait!
It's a cruel world, but I have a place in it.
Eren. As long as you're part of my life,
I can fight to the bitter end.
"It's a cruel world, but I have a place in it."
Mikasa races through hell to be beside the
one person who makes the struggle worthwhile
only to learn just how deep hell goes.