Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Yuu-chan, I got your thread knot done.
Thanks a bunch, Haruka!
I'll start sewing from here.
Yeowch!
Yuu-chan, are you okay?!
Why do we have to make costumes if all we're doing is reading a script?
Yuu-chan's so cute when she's sulky.
"Culture Fest: Sleepover Time!"
We're barely making any progress.
Right? It sure looks like we're not gonna finish.
Would you two settle down and get back to work?
We won't make it in time for tomorrow if you keep messing around.
Shall we stay the night?
That's what you wanted from the start.
Sensei!
We're gonna spend the night here!
Then fill out the request form.
You're all going to stay here overnight?
Yuu-chan, you don't want to be here tonight?
Are you staying?
Yeah, we really need the extra time.
Then I'll do it.
So you're all staying.
Aren't you, Shizuku-chan?
Yeah, I am...
shake
Just how tense can you get?!
Shizuku-chan, is this your first time staying overnight for a cultural festival?
M-My middle school had a strict 6pm curfew.
Ours didn't really care either way.
Right?
What about your middle school, Haruka-chan?
We were allowed to stay.
I'm the only one who's never done it...
Yuu-chan always went home though, so I never actually slept over.
That's because I always finished my work early!
It's not like I was scared of the
school at night or anything!
Okay, I get it already!
Oh yeah.
Shizuku-chan went to a different middle school from all of us.
But Kotone, you were already friends with her when we started high school, right?
You're even living together.
Kotone and I are actually related.
We've been really close our entire lives.
I don't know if I'd consider that "close"...
It was just you playing an unending series of tricks on me.
Gosh, you're embarrassing me, Shizuku-chan!
See what I mean?
How wonderful it would be to live with your love...
Haruka, morning...
Good morning!
Yuu-chan, there's some on your mouth.
Haruka, take care!
Be a good girl, okay?
Haruka, welcome home! Make food!
I can't get over how great the school is before a culture festival.
Me neither!
The decorations really give the place some new spice—
seeing it all makes me happy!
I'm all worked up too!
You're always like that, but I totally get you.
You think?
Haruka-chan, we need to finish setting up the haunted house stuff in the classroom.
We lost our sleeping area.
Wanna try the hallway?
I think they're still finishing up out there...
Now what?
sweat
H-How about the unused classroom?
We can probably sew there too.
Huh, what's wrong?
I nabbed us the key.
Thanks, Kaede!
It's packed full of desks.
I guess they're using it as storage.
It looks like our usual desks got stuffed in
alongside the ones that were here originally.
How can you tell?
No reason...
Wanna go see if we can find somewhere else?
Wait!
If we pack them tighter,
there should be enough space.
Shizuku-chan's such a hard worker.
Stop staring and help me out here!
Okay!
Look at all this space we made!
Are we supposed to sleep directly on the floor?
Like, all nestled together?
I brought us blankets.
Really? You're a lifesaver!
She really is a hard worker.
What now?!
Check it out, Shizuku-chan!
They must've put up all the signboards while we were working.
It's really happening.
I can't wait to eat it all!
That's what you meant?!
Slurp, slurp, slurp...
Let's take a quick break.
I'm gonna check out our class.
I'll go with you.
Shizuku-chan.
Let's get some fresh air on the roof.
Sure.
It's up to us to finish this off, Yuu-chan!
Right...
Ouch!
Looks like we've still got a ways to go.
All better!
Thanks!
Say, Haruka, what should we eat tomorrow?
I'm thinking crepes, buttered potatoes, and...
Oh yeah! Let's buy different things and then share with each other!
Sound good. Once we're finished, let's go check out all the food stands.
I guess you're too scared.
I'll show you what I'm made of!
She fell asleep while we were still talking!
Don't you think you're pushing yourself too hard?
Like with the whole witch thing, too.
It's not like you to be so pushy.
What are you trying to say?
The Shizuku-chan I know...
...is more like this!
Cultural festivals are a pain.
Do I really seem that detached?!
I guess I do.
To tell you the truth, my middle school let us stay overnight too.
But I was too shy to join the other girls,
so I left early without finishing my work.
Then why did you decide to sleep over this year?
Because I'm here with you.
I couldn't understand where you saw the fun in doing all this,
so I decided to try and find out for myself.
Why do you try so hard to enjoy everything?
You weren't always like this, either.
"These three years will go by before you know it,
so enjoy every second you've got."
That's what my older sister said to me.
I can't imagine that much time going by so quickly.
But you know what?
When I'm with the girl I love, everything I do takes on a shade of fun.
And I'm having fun right now.
It's not just you!
I'm... having fun too. I'm not
pushing myself too hard.
I bet I know exactly what kind of face you're making.
Are you saying you have eyes in the back of your head?
Let's check.
It's dark, so we have to get closer.
Show me what kind of face you're making.
Stupid.
Yuu-chan, no sleeping!
We're nowhere near finished!
Do you need a wake-up kiss?
Come on, Yuu-chan! Get up!
If you don't wake up soon I really will kiss you!
It didn't work.
Maybe because I'm already awake.
I guess I'll just sleep too.
I've done enough, haven't I?
Good night.
I'm still not awake yet.
Wake up!
I'm awake now.
"Culture Fest: Sleepover Time!"
The end
West Misato Fest
Come one, come all!
How would you like a frankfurter?
We're hosting a stuffed animal cafe!
The a cappella starts at 11 o'clock!
"Culture Fest: Today's the Day!"
Magic mirror on the wall, who is the fairest one of all?
Oh no, what shall I do?
Good Melody Girls: Play Reading
Snow White
Run away, hide!
Hurry, fair princess!
Thank you, hunter.
And thus, Snow White made her escape. However...
The old peddler woman held out a bright red apple.
A gift for the beautiful young lady.
What an absolutely scrumptious-looking apple!
What do we do, what do we do?
Snow White has passed away!
The bright red apple was a poisoned apple.
My, never have I laid eyes on such beauty! It is as if she soundly sleeps.
The prince was entranced and kissed Snow White as she lay in the glass coffin.
Whatever have I been doing?
Where have I been taken?
Beautiful princess, I am at your side.
Remain by me forever.
And they lived happily ever after.
That was a reading of Snow White by the Good Melody Girls!
President Mitsuki!
West Misato Fest
I never thought I'd be so nervous just for a play reading!
You did well, comrade.
And thus, the two witches concluded their battle.
I'm still not sure how we managed to have two people play a single part.
Onee-chan, thanks so much for helping us out!
Was I able to meet your expectations?
Yeah!
You were really the perfect choice for Snow White, President Mitsuki.
You exuded an aura of magnificence—
you really felt like the main character!
Your hair is nice and fluffy too,
so you make a perfect princess.
A princess?!
It stood up!
All Done
Big Sister
That reminds me, Yuu. We're going to go look at the stalls together, right?
Um, but Yuu-chan and I have plans...
Yeah, let's go!
Where should we start?
Let's see...
Wh-Why don't you stick with us?
Yuu-chan forgot about our promise...
This is the last culture fest they'll ever have together, so let them be for a while.
I know, but still...
You're such a pain.
It wouldn't kill you to give me some attention too!
W-Wait, there isn't enough room in my heart for another person...
That wasn't a confession!
Class rep, got a second?
Coming!
I'll be back in a bit.
We'll chill here.
We don't get to do stuff with Kaede-chan that often because of all the class rep work she has.
Well, it's her own choice.
Yuzu-chan bravely holds back tears of loneliness.
Don't just assume what I'm feeling!
Why did Kaede-chan decide to be our class rep?
She's done it every year since elementary school.
I don't know exactly why either.
You're telling me you still don't
know after all these years?
Why should I?
You should learn a thing or two from the girl
who knows Yuu-chan inside and out despite not meeting her until middle school!
Just so you know, that's nothing to be proud of.
Then prove it by telling me something about Yuu I don't know.
No problem.
Yuu-chan always sleeps on her right side.
Also, she has a beauty mark next to her bellybutton.
I knew that one.
It seems she's self-conscious about it.
Hey, sorry to have left you hanging.
Kaede
Kaede-chan, Yuzu-chan is bullying me!
I thought I raised you better than this.
Exactly what part of that was bullying?
Yuzu, you know a lot more
about Yuu than I expected.
It's more like Yuu just tells me these things.
Yuu-chan!
And yet, you have no idea
why I'm always the class rep.
I-I don't not know. I just forgot.
Then allow me to enlighten you.
No need!
I'll think about it as we walk.
Good old Yuzu-chan, showing us what true friends are like.
Good old Yuzu-chan, showing us what true friends are like
I wonder if Yuu-chan will even
bother trying to remember.
Our promise...
Haruka, let's go already.
The festival's in full swing!
Let's eat!
Yeah!
Eww, this sata andagi is drenched in oil.
Want some takoyaki?
Gimme!
They've got yakisoba!
Yakisoba
Here, one plate of yakisoba!
Yuzu-chan,
do you remember yet?
Ah, uh... not yet...
I forgot to remember.
Three Stuffings Later
I had five!
Seven, eight, nine... nine plates!
None can outdo my gluttony.
Go fetch me some juice.
Haruka, what you lack is willpower.
This sucks!
What's the point in competing
over something like this?
Who wants to be class rep?
Second Elementary School
April 15 (Fri)
Me!
I do!
You too, Kaede-chan?
Then decide with rock-paper-scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay, I won!
Looks like Yuzu-chan's the class rep.
I'll be coming for that class rep throne of yours next year,
and don't you forget it...
Was it because you lost to me back then?
No.
Then why?
There was this one time when you were carrying a huge stack of textbooks.
You fell down the stairs because you couldn't see and hurt yourself.
Did that really happen?
So to prevent you from ever being hurt doing something like that again,
I decided to shoulder those responsibilities by myself.
Oh, I see...
Yuu-chan!
Haruka, where've you been?
Same to you! Way to go off with President Mitsuki and completely break our promise!
The plan was to check out the stalls with you after!
Onee-chan has student council work now.
I didn't hear a thing about that!
Because I didn't tell you!
I never told you!
Yuu-chan...
Haru
I'm sorry, Haruka. Wanna go now?
No, I already ate my fill.
That was mine...
Then, how about going to
see the stage performances?
I'm too busy eating for something like that.
Then, um...
I bequeath you this hair accessory, a Sonoda family heirloom!
How about now?
I-I am not worthy of such a great honor!
She believed me!
Sorry, sold out!
Tehehe
You've gotta be a moron not to buy this!
Bring out your wallets!
Geez, Sensei, why can't I do that?
Listen here, Josephine.
West Misato
Head over Heels
Who you callin' Josephine?
Catherine.
I ain't her either.
Simone.
Yes?
I wub you.
What the heck?
Knock it off already.
Thank you for listening.
I think a band's on next.
Did you like that last joke?
I was just thinking of how we match.
The afternoon sunlight
I'm really sorry, Haruka.
feels warm
even as the day grows old
Hey, I already forgave you.
But you were feeling down the whole time I was having fun, right?
When I'm with you, my heart
I'll let you do anything you want right now.
never seems to calm down
Huh, is she joking around?
You've drawn so close, only a few millimeters separate us
She looks serious.
Then I'll have my way.
I trace the floating clouds with my fingers
and move them around
Yuu-chan and I kissed until the lights in the gym came back on.
And as you look straight at me
wearing a smile on your face
I just can't seem to say "I love you"
No way!
Before we knew it, the band's
performance was over,
and all sound vanished from the room.
All I could hear was Yuu-chan's
heartbeat, her breathing,
and the faint moans escaping from our mouths.
"Culture Fest: Today's the Day!"
The end
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
Hey Yuu, do you eat the same kind of food as President Mitsuki?
That's right.
Then it must be something else?
What must be?
President Mitsuki, do you do anything special at home?
Special?
Well, she studies and sleeps a lot...
That's it!
Seriously, what is it?!
Next time, Trick 7:
"Swimsuit Fanservice: Accidents Included",
"Swimsuit Fanservice: Accidents Included"
"Shopping with Yuu-chan"
and "Shopping with Yuu-chan".
Look forward to it.
I sleep a lot too.
So it wasn't that...