This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's twelve and dreams of becoming a singer.
But, unfortunately...
...she only has one year left to live.
We, the Shinigami were asked to keep an
eye on her until the inevitable fate, but...
Today, she became an adult...
...and she performed incredibly at the audition.
Aren't we...
...changing her destiny?!
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand.
Yes.
Um...
...I'm home.
What gives!
She really has no manners!
I'll make a bunch of rice cakes for you then.
Which do you like better, red beans or soy beans?
But we're out of tea...
I'm home.
O-Oh... Mitsuki-chan's back home.
Yes.
I'll put her on.
Hello?
She finally put you on.
I thought that I would have to talk to Tanaka-san forever.
Wakaouji-sensei!
Why are you calling me?
Ah... well...
Actually...
The person who's going to be
your manager has come to see you.
Eh!
Manager?!
Keep your voice down!
Someone's listening...
Why'd the manager go to your place?
That's because...
...I've become your guardian.
And I just talked with her a moment ago.
So then...
The manager said that she was going
to come to visit you and me, but...
Mitsuki-chan, could you come
to the hospital right now?
Of course!
I'll be right there!
Along Came the Manager
If it's to see Dr. Wakaouji...
...he's coming on a house call tomorrow, right?
Yes, but...
...I want to go right now.
Um...
I have to go shopping, so...
...shall I take Mitsuki-san to the hospital?
That is acceptable.
Please take care of it.
My eyes, Meroko!
No way!
Mitsuki-chan's still changing!
It's okay now.
Besides, what's the point of changing?
She can't meet the manager in that body.
Ah...
That's right!
Then, after we get to the hospital...
...transform me into a sixteen year old, okay Takuto?
Wait a minute.
That'll be fine for the manager...
...but she's going to be with her guardian, Dr. Wakaouji, right?
Won't she?
What will the Doctor think if he sees Mitsuki as a sixteen year old?
What do we do...?!
What do we do?
Well...
At times like this...
The Shinigami Handbook...
Let's see... let's see...
Just as I thought...
...we'll have to tell them everything!
These are the two are the Shinigami...
...Takuto and Meroko!
Manager
Takuto turned my twelve year old body...
...to one of a sixteen year old!
Manager
And when I'm like that, I don't have any cancer in my throat!
I can sing with all of my heart!
Manager
Really? That's how it is?
I don't have a problem with it!
Manager
Okay.
It's not okay!
Doing something as strange as that...
...is totally out of the question!
Geez!
Let's see...
Meroko...
Is that handbook even useful at all?
I get it!
I'll give you a rare chance to see my power!
Oh? You're gonna show me?
So then, what's your plan?
W-Well, that's...
Tell the manager...
Um...
It's her little sister, Mikazuki!
(Mikazuki means "New Moon")
Or something like that...
The details aren't important!
Won't that Wakaouji guy think it's weird?
Like I said...
Mikazuki is... her modeling stage name...
That's it!
Let's go then!
Oh well, I guess we'll just have to try as hard as we can.
Yeah.
You have to try as hard as you can, too!
Yes!
Reception Room
Here we are.
Yeah.
I wonder if I should go in with you.
Wait!
If she does something like that, it'll be a proble-...!
Um... what'll be a problem?
Eh?
That's...
...I think that would be too much of a problem for you.
Please take care of your shopping.
Then...
...I'll come to pick you up later.
Please wait in the lobby, okay?
Okay!
Meroko!
No more...
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Just remember that when I'm in that form...
...I can't take that much.
Anyways...
...let's go inside.
Okay.
Really?
Oh?
She's here.
Excuse me.
Hey.
We've been waiting for you.
This is your manager, Ooshige-san...
...introduce yourself.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Ooshige from Rage Pro.
It's a woman, huh?
And this is...
Ah!
P-Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki.
Stupid!
What are you saying...?!
Did you forget everything we said back in the house?!
Ah?
That's not what I meant!
I'm her little sister, Mikazuki!
Huh, little sister...?
Um... that's...
That's it.
Mitsuki-chan, tell Dr. Wakaouji to step outside.
Tell him that you're going to explain everything.
Okay.
Sensei, can you come out for a bit?
I see.
Mikazuki is your stage name, huh?
That's right. That's right.
Then, what about the little sister part?
That's...
Um...
That's it!
You...
...refer to yourself as little sister because it's a catchphrase within the company.
You're just starting out, right?
Eh... is that true?
It's not, but...
Just tell him that!
Ah, I see!
It's a catchphrase to say I'm the little sister of someone in the company....
...since I'm just starting out.
So that's it!
But...
There's still  something else?
Hmm...
Hmm?
Oh well.
Hang in there, Mitsuki-chan.
Eh?
The first experience is always the most important.
Now you need to properly greet the manager you'll be depending on from here on out.
Shall we head back?
Man... sorry about that.
She hadn't told me the whole story yet.
It's nothing.
Please don't worry about it.
Let's start over.
She's Mikazuki-chan, a little sister.
I'm looking forward to working together.
Me too.
So then...
Um... where's the person herself?
What person...?
Um... l-let's see...
School!
Say she's at school!
Are you sure that's going to work?
It's fine!
Um...
She's at school!
Ah. So she's at school, huh?
Yeah...
She goes to school like she should.
See.
That took care of the two of them just fine.
Well... it sure seems like it.
What should we do now?
Shall we wait for her?
Wait... for who?
Say she'll be here very soon!
Um, um...
She'll be here very soon, so...
Really?
Then I'll have the guardian, Dr. Wakaouji...
...take a look at the arrangements for next time.
Oh, sure.
That was too close.
Is it okay to just listen and watch like this?
Ooshige-san, there's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
She's... going to be very busy from now on, isn't she?
Well...
You want me to contact the school?
Yeah...
That too...
There's that problem with your throat too, right?
That won't be an issue.
Mitsuki-chan will be with people her age...
...they'll only be working after
school and on weekends.
It's a relief to hear that.
The most important event
remaining is her debut, then.
Since she's a fresh new artist coming off auditions...
...it would be wise to act now.
Of course.
For that reason...
...there are voice training and dance lessons...
...for her to receive instruction in as well as participate in.
Hold on a minute.
You said something about voice training...
Then...
...it's almost as if Mitsuki-chan is becoming a singer.
Oh man...
He found a flaw in your story, didn't he?
Sensei! Actually, that's...
Eh?
What are you going to do?
Um...
Um... well...
Not this!
Hello?
Wait, what am I supposed to do with a phone?!
Phone?
Ah.
Are you going to call her?
Ah... yes!
You're going to do that!
An hour long conversation...!
W-Wait!
Just now, that was...
Free roll?
Ah...
For some reason, I have no idea what's going on...
Don't sound like it doesn't concern you.
This isn't a simple matter.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
The manager, Ooshige-san...
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
...thinks that she's Mitsuki-chan's little sister, Mikazuki.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mitsuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Dr. Wakaouji thinks that Mitsuki-chan is
just using Mikazuki as a stage name.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
That much I can explain.
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
Ooshige
Little
Sister
Mikazuki
Stage
Name
Wakaouji
But if Wakaouji-sensei...
...finds out that I've become a singer...
You can't settle everything just like that.
If only there was some way we could do all of this over...
As I thought, it'd be best to tell Wakaouji-sensei the truth.
No way.
Telling him something like this so suddenly...
There's no way he'll believe it.
Yeah!
You're the only human that can see Meroko and me.
That's right.
He'd never believe you about us Shinigami.
But...
If I can't get him to believe it...
You're such a helpless kid.
Mero-Mero Change!
How's this?
There's two of me...
"How's this...?"
Meroko, you...
If I'm like this...
...I'll be able to do something.
The ones who silence the tears of children...
Shinigami Duo!
Spring Onion Ramen's leader is going to
show you just what she can do!
Sensei!
Mitsuki-chan!
I was worried.
Where did you run off too?
Sorry!
I...
...was feeling a little sick.
Do you want to lie down somewhere then?
Nope!
I'm totally fine now!
Really? I guess it's okay then.
Her voice is kinda off...
Geez...
Her personality's wrong too...
No way, no way!
It's just your imagination! Your imagination!
By the way, Mitsuki-chan...
Yes?
About what that Ooshige-san said...
...for some reason, I don't understand it.
What are you talking about?
After I heard what she had to say...
...it sounded like you were going to become a singer.
That's because...
That's right!
A commercial!
She was talking about a commercial!
Really?!
Yep.
In it...
...a girl debuts as a singer!
Come! Come!
Hurry!
Let's go back to where Ooshige-san is.
We still have things to discuss, don't we?
Ah... yeah... I guess so.
She's really something else,
babbling on and on like that...
It feels like something is going to go wrong.
I convinced him, didn't I?
What part of his face shows that he's convinced?
If that's the case, I still have a trick up my sleeve!
Ah!
Wakaouji-sensei, over there!
Eh? What?
Whoa!
It looks like an emergency!
Let's hurry!
E-Emergency? Wait!
Eh?
W-Wait!
Now that the Doctor isn't around...
Mero-Mero Change!
How's this?
Meroko... again?
For now...
...I'll go take care of the manager.
(-gozaru: Implies a tone of respect [Archaic])
I mean... I'll go take care of her.
Nobody talks like that nowadays.
Well, you're pretty good at manipulating others.
I wonder... if this is really okay...
Huh?
I... no, I mean...
(Watashi is the feminine form of "I")
(Boku is the masculine form "I")
Is there something wrong with me?
No... where is that girl?
Ah...
She's feeling a bit under the weather...
Huh?
She'll feel much better after resting, though.
Ah... is that so..?
Your talking still sound weird.
I know that.
Anyways, Ooshige-san...
Yes?
I've decided!
I'm going to put my faith in you...
...and leave everything to do with Mitsuki to you.
I'm honored...
So...
...how are you going to explain this?
That's...
Yes. This is Wakaouji.
Yes.
Ah. I understand.
Ooshige-san.
There seem to be visitors for you in the parking lot.
For me?
I wonder who it could be...
Again?
If we make it through this...
...that should take care of everything.
This is exhausting, though.
Ah...
I guess that...
...I can't just leave it up to them...
I have to go tell the truth!
Man... Mitsuki-chan.
Ah!
There wasn't an emergency at all.
Wa-Wakaouji-sensei!
What is it this time?
Did something happen...
...or are you just crying wolf ?
That's not it!
It wasn't a wolf!
Um...
They call themselves Spring Onion Ramen!
You really should just stop joking around.
Like I said...
...they're Shinigami who call themselves Spring Onion Ramen...
What are the two of you doing out here?
Come in, come in.
You should leave this up to Meroko.
Dr. Wakaouji.
Yes?
Mitsuki-chan is amazing!
Ah... not that  much...
Well, anyways...
...I think she's a great girl who's full of talent.
R-Really?
Please!
Put your faith in me!
Leave Mitsuki-chan to me!
O-Okay.
Ah... what a bother.
There weren't any visitors here to see me.
What do you mean by visitors?
Because... you just said that...
I did?
A-Anyways...
From now on... Kouyama Mitsuki is depending on you!
It's my pleasure.
Okay!
I really want... Mitsuki-chan to do her best.
Eh?
Actually...
I can't give you the proper treatment,
but as your doctor...
...I plan on taking the place of your parents.
Sensei...
Work hard, okay?
Wakaouji-sensei...
Mitsuki, come out for a sec.
Are you okay, Meroko?
Going through this many transformations in one day...
It's a first for her.
'Sup...
She's already reached her limit.
I'm just fine.
Who should I transform into this time?
Ah! Takuto is good.
Um... Dr. Wakaouji.
Yes?
Forgive me if I'm wrong, but...
...did you play keyboard for
Route L a long time ago?
Eh... yeah.
Just as I thought... you're the  prince!
I'm a huge fan of yours!
Is that so?
I'm really an incredible fan of yours!
Back then...
...at a studio somewhere...
...I also tried to be an idol.
But unfortunately... I failed miserably.
Oh. That's right.
Now that I finally have this chance...
...could you sign this?
Ah?
Does Mitsuki-chan have a cellphone?
Ah. Mikazuki-chan!
Ah. Yes?
Mitsuki-chan is still in high school, right?
Eh... yes.
Actually...
...I came today to give her a cellphone.
Without this, she can't get in touch, right?
Yeah...
That's right.
Then...
...I'll be heading to the high school.
Great timing.
Thanks, then.
What are you going to do now?
If she goes to the high school...
...Mitsuki won't be there.
Takuto! Please!
Turn me into a sixteen year old!
I want to talk to her myself!
It can't be helped.
If I'm sixteen year old Kouyama Mitsuki...
...I'll be able to go introduce myself!
Ooshige-san!
Mitsuki-chan?
Yes.
I'm sorry for being late.
I heard from my little sister
that you were coming here.
Really?
I'm glad we met.
Yes!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki!
I'm Ooshige Masami from Rage Pro.
You'll be very busy from now on, so...
...prepare yourself!
Eh?
Even if I said that...
...you're still a new artist, aren't you?
I'll have to take care of you in the beginning.
Please take care of me!
Okay.
For now, let's work hard!
Okay!
Eichi-kun...
My manager has arrived.
It's all falling into place...
...for me to become a singer!
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiipai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Preview
That girl's debut has finally arrived.
The producer is...
...super-famous... Takasu Kohei!
Hmm... that's impressive.
But you know...
That girl doesn't like Takasu's songs...
...and she's writing her own songs.
Can an amateur like her really
do something like songwriting?
It's all right. Everything will
work out as long as I'm there.
That's wrong!
Songwriting is...
...something you have to pour your soul into!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The Feelings In Your Song.
The Feelings In Your Song
Look forward to it!