Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
Lakes Ashi 2 and 3…
I hope we don't get any more of them.
Chairman Keel lodged a complaint
yesterday regarding delays in the plans.
It was addressed to me personally.
The man was rather annoyed.
Towards the end, he even implied
that you would be relieved of your post.
Adam is progressing smoothly.
And Project Eva has begun work
on the Dummy Plugs.
What do those old Seele fools
have to complain about?
The key Human Instrumentality Project
is behind schedule.
All the projects are interlinked.
There are no problems.
Does that also go for Rei?
Suit yourself.
By the way, what will you do
about that man?
Let him do what he wants.
Same with the Marduk Institute.
True. They might prove useful for a while.
KYOTO
What was set in motion here 16 years ago?
It's me.
Oh, there you are.
Shannon Biotech. A chemical firm
funded with foreign capital.
It's been here for nine years, but it's
been sitting empty the whole time.
Of the 108 companies with ties to
the Marduk Institute, 106 were dummies.
And this is number 107, huh?
This is the company's registry.
You want me to look at
the board of directors, right?
-You already knew?
-I recognize most of the names.
The Marduk Institute:
An advisory body directly under
the Human Instrumentality Council
that was established to find
potential Evangelion pilots.
Its true nature is still
shrouded in mystery.
Your job is to investigate Nerv.
Sniffing around Marduk is unhealthy.
Well, I just happen to be
the type who can't let something go
until I've seen it with my own two eyes.
Hello. You've reached Kaji.
I'm out at the moment.
Please leave your name and a message.
Help me, Mr. Kaji!
Get away from me, you pervert!
That will get his attention.
What was that about?
We don't have school tomorrow
since it's Sunday.
I called Mr. Kaji to see if I could
get him to take me someplace.
But he's never home.
He's always out when I call these days.
So that means you're free tomorrow?
I hate to say it, but, yeah, I'm free.
In that case, do you think
you could do me a favor?
Here's the thing…
A date?!
He's my sister Kodama's friend.
He's been begging me to introduce you two.
Please!
Head strike!
-Stay focused!
-Sorry.
Stay focused on the cleaning!
Necrosis operation complete.
Reversible graph measurements complete.
Decided what to wear tomorrow?
Oh, to the wedding, you mean?
Well, I wore my pink suit
to Kiyomi's wedding…
And I just wore that
navy blue one to Kotoko's.
Or that orange one?
You haven't worn that lately.
Oh, that one…
There's a slight problem with it.
-Too tight, huh?
-Yes.
Guess I'll buy something on my way home.
The bills just don't stop…
With all these nonstop weddings,
the gift money is really adding up.
Everyone's anxious to get hitched
before the big three-oh hits.
Yes, nobody wants to be
the last one who's still single.
Come on out, you three.
Good work today.
All we do is tests! This is so boring!
Come to think of it, Shinji seems
even more mopey than usual today.
Because of tomorrow.
Oh, right. Tomorrow…
I have to see my father tomorrow.
What do you think I should
talk to him about?
Why are you asking me?
I saw you having a nice conversation
with him one time.
So, my father… what's he like?
I don't know.
Oh.
You've been staring at me all day
because you wanted to ask me that?
When we were cleaning the classroom today,
you wrung out that rag, remember?
You seemed like a mother
when you did that.
-A mother?
-Yeah.
It seemed like the way a mother
would wring one out.
Who knows, maybe you would
make a good housewife, Ayanami!
What are you talking about?
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
You should get to bed.
Don't you have a date tomorrow?
Yeah, with a hot guy.
That reminds me!
Lend me that lavender perfume of yours!
Forget it.
Geez, don't be so stingy!
Kids don't need perfume.
Is Shinji in his room?
He's been holed up in there all evening.
I don't think he wants to see his dad.
If he doesn't want to go, he should just
say so! I swear, you Japanese people…
He's loathing and eager at the same time.
That's what makes this difficult for him.
Get out!
Good work, Shinji.
Shinji? I'm coming in.
Are you afraid to be alone
with your father?
All this running away
from him isn't healthy.
Unless you take that first step,
nothing's ever going to change.
I know that!
You'll understand someday.
It's not just that first step.
What's important is to keep on walking.
Anyway, keep your chin up tomorrow.
You'll be seeing your mother, too.
Good night.
You bought a new outfit
for tomorrow? Let me see!
You want to see it? It's really expensive!
Style trumps price.
No worries on that score!
So… do you buy your outfits
based on what Mr. Kaji likes?
Absolutely not. Not anymore.
THE NEXT DAY
-Well…
-I'll see…
…you later.
Always remember, "Happy wife, happy life"!
The red, the blue, the yellow…
And now, let's all mingle for a while.
MR. RYOJI KAJI
Ryoji sure is late.
That moron's never been on time
to anything in his life!
Only for your dates.
He's always been on time for work.
Hi, ladies! You two look
even lovelier than usual!
Sorry, I couldn't get away from work.
Says the guy who stands around
like he's got nothing to do!
And not like I care, but can't you
do something about that stubble?
Geez, even your tie is crooked!
Thank you kindly.
You two are like an old married couple.
I like the sound of that, Ritchan!
Marry a jerk like him?!
It's been three years since
we last came here together.
I ran away from home after that.
I haven't been back since.
It hardly seems like
mother is resting here.
I can't even remember her face.
Forgetting is what
lets people go on living.
But there are some things
that we must never forget.
That's an important lesson
that Yui taught me.
I come here to remind myself
of that lesson.
Don't you have any pictures?
None. This grave itself is a facade.
There's no body.
They said you threw everything away.
You really did.
You keep what's important inside you.
That's enough for now.
It's time. I need to go.
Father!
Um, I'm glad I had the chance
to talk to you today.
I see.
You're pretty good!
I didn't even know you had one of those.
I started when I was five,
and that's the best I can do.
I don't have any talent for it.
Perseverance pays off, huh?
That's mildly impressive.
I started because my teacher suggested it.
I could have stopped at any time.
Then why didn't you?
Because no one told me to.
Sounds about right.
You're sure back early. I thought
you'd at least stay out for dinner.
That guy was so boring!
I ditched him when we were
in line for the rollercoaster.
Wow, that's mean.
The only decent guy
around here is Mr. Kaji!
Oh, come on, you're bringing that up now?
-I'll be in the ladies' room.
-You'd better not try to ditch us!
She's in heels…
How many years has it been since
the three of us went out drinking?
I think Misato has had enough.
She's particularly bubbly tonight.
She drinks more when she's
trying to rein herself in.
Maybe it's the opposite tonight.
As someone who lived with her,
you would certainly know her best.
We lived together, but that was before
she started wearing heels.
Yes, I never would have pictured her
like this back in college.
I was just a kid, too.
It was less "living together" than it was
two kids sharing living arrangements.
We were playing house.
Life is never that simple.
Oh, right.
Here's a cat trinket I picked up.
Why, thank you. You're so thoughtful.
Only with the ladies.
With work, I'm lazy as hell.
I doubt that. Get anything for Misato?
I already lost that war. I'm not the type
who fights battles he can't win.
I think you have a chance.
How about you?
I make a point to not talk about myself.
I'm really not that interesting.
Katsuragi sure is taking her time.
Is she fixing her makeup or something?
So, what were you doing in Kyoto?
Huh? I picked that up in Matsushiro!
Don't play dumb.
If you dig too deep, you'll get burned.
Advice from a concerned friend.
I'll take it to heart.
If I'll get burned anyway,
I want it be from us--
-Can I buy some matches for you?
-Hey, you're back.
You'll never change. Always the flirt.
Sure, I've changed.
As they say, to live is to change.
Homeostasis and transistasis.
What are those?
The ability to maintain the status quo
and the ability to change.
All living things possess
both of those contradictory traits.
Sounds like men and women.
Well, I have to run.
I still have work to do.
-Really?
-That's too bad.
See you.
Sure.
Is that you, Shinji? It's me!
I'm out drinking with Kaji.
Yeah, an after-after-party.
Okay. Sure. Bye.
Was that Misato?
Yeah. She said she'll be home late,
so we shouldn't wait up.
Huh? She isn't going to
stay out all night, is she?
Why would she?
I mean, Mr. Kaji is with her.
Are you stupid? That's exactly why!
You're too old to throw up.
Well, pardon me for being old…
-I guess we're in the same boat.
-Yeah.
It's because you're wearing those heels.
I really feel the years.
Shave this stupid stubble…
Yes, ma'am.
I'll walk from here. Thanks.
Kaji? Do you think I've changed?
You're more beautiful.
I'm sorry I broke up with you
out of the blue back then.
That stuff about
finding someone else… I lied.
-Did you know?
-No.
It suddenly hit me.
I noticed how much you're like my father.
I was looking for my father in other men.
When I realized that, I freaked out.
I was scared to death.
I was scared of being with you.
Of being a woman.
I was terrified of everything.
I hated my father, but then I fall
for a man who was just like him.
I joined Nerv to try to
put all of that behind me.
But my father had also belonged
to that organization.
I was deluding myself by thinking I was
in this to get revenge against the Angels.
It's what you chose, Katsuragi.
You don't have to apologize to me.
No, I didn't! I didn't choose anything!
I was just running away!
Trying to break free of the hold
my father has over me!
I'm no different from Shinji!
I'm such a coward.
I'm sorry, really.
It's the alcohol talking.
You don't need to hear this.
Drop it.
I'm such a child! I don't have any right
to look down my nose at Shinji.
Drop it!
And to make it worse,
I'm a conniving bitch who only asks men
for help when it's convenient for her!
Even back then,
maybe I was just using you!
-I hate myself!
-Drop it! That's enough!
I can't live with myself anymore!
Hey, Shinji. Want to kiss?
What?
I said, let's kiss.
You haven't kissed a girl before, right?
-Let's kiss, then.
-Why?
Because I'm bored.
You want to kiss because you're bored?
That's your reason?
You don't want to kiss me because it's
the anniversary of your mom's death?
You're afraid that mommy might
be watching you from Heaven?
-Not really.
-Or are you afraid?
I'm not afraid! It's just a kiss!
You've brushed your teeth, right?
-Yeah.
-Then here goes.
The breath from your nose
is tickling me. Hold your breath.
Blech! That's definitely not something
you should do to kill time!
Okay, you're home. Pull yourself together.
Mr. Kaji!
Well, I should get going.
Why don't you stay here tonight?
I'll be the office laughing stock
if I show up for work in this.
Don't worry about that!
Come on, Mr. Kaji!
See you later.
He smells like lavender.
Sorry, you two.
Take care of Katsuragi, okay?
Yes, sir.
-Good night, then.
-Good night.
What's wrong? You look bummed out.
Because I kissed an idiot like you!
THE NEXT DAY
All right, let's have one of
the girl students continue. Ayanami.
Is Ayanami gone again today?
NERV HEADQUARTERS
DEEP UNDERGROUND FACILITY
CENTRAL SECTION
CENTRAL DOGMA
2008 METERS BELOW SAME
TERMINAL DOGMA
Hey. How's the hangover this morning?
-Finally better, thanks to you.
-That's good to hear.
Is this your real job?
Or is it a side gig?
Good question.
You're Ryoji Kaji, Department of Special
Inspections, Special Agency Nerv.
But you're also Ryoji Kaji, belonging
to the Japanese Home Ministry's
Department of Investigations.
-I guess you know everything.
-Don't underestimate Nerv.
Did Commander Ikari send you?
No, I'm here on my own.
If you don't give up
your side gig, you're dead.
I'm useful to Commander Ikari.
I'm still safe.
But I do apologize
for keeping secrets from you.
I owe you for yesterday,
so we'll call it even.
You're too kind.
But the Commander and Ritchan
are keeping secrets from you, too.
And that… is this.
Is that…
an Eva?
No… It can't be!
It is. The key to all that's happened
since the Second Impact.
As well as its beginning.
This is Adam.
Adam? The 1st Angel is here?!
I guess there really is
more to Nerv than I thought.
TO BE CONTINUED
Shinji grows cocky,
and he becomes trapped in a Dirac sea.
As his clock ticks down,
it teaches him the meaning of despair.
Next episode!
"The Sickness Unto Death, and Then…"
Tune in next time
for lots more fan service!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming