Go for it, Subaru!
Kirihara
Middle School
Shizuno
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Invoke the big halation
ano hi no chikai wo hatasu tame
あの日の誓いを果たすため
To fulfill that promise you swore on that day
hirake! new formation
開け! new formation
Open out, the new formation!
shisen no aizu yobiau
視線の合図呼び合う
Call out to each other with eye contact
kibou o nosete hanate arch
希望を乗せては放て arch
Bear and release the arch of hope
itsumo no toori ni ne
いつもの通りにね
Just like always
shinjiteru (makasete)
信じてる (まかせて)
I'll believe in you (Leave it to us)
mune ni te wo atete
胸に手を当てて
Bring your hand to your chest
hikiyoseta heijoushin
引き寄せた平常心
and tug at your usual attitude
kanaete dekita koto
叶えて来たこと
The things I fulfilled,
sorezorega oboeteru
それぞれが覚えてる
I can remember them all.
ano hi hisoka ni naita koto mo
あの日密かに泣いたことも
Including that day when you cried in secret.
onaji yumemiteru no wa
同じ夢見てるのは
Surely, we can't be the only ones
watashi tachi dakeja nain dayo ne
私たちだけじゃないんだよね
having the same dream.
me no mae ni arawareta
目の前に現れた
Appearing in front of our eyes,
yuru ganai hitomi hibana chirashite
揺るがない瞳火花散らして
is an unfaltering spark that's dispersing.
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Drop the big halation!
hiraku space e hashiriko me
開くスペースへ走り込め
Run into the open space!
wazukana sensation
僅かな sensation
The slight sensation
senobi shite ita kinou e
背伸びしていた昨日へ
when you were overstretched yesterday
wakare wo tsugetara
別れを告げたら
Announce your goodbyes,
egao wo tsunagete
笑顔を繋げて
Connect your smiles,
yume mita basho e hanate arch
夢見た場所へ放て arch
Release the arch to where you see your dreams
A Foolish Man
It's great you could join our interest group, Kashima.
You were just as highly acclaimed as Suga during your middle school years at Shizuno.
Yeah, but I lost to Suga in the first match.
Me too, at the final match...
However, if you're in our team, I'll feel more assured, Kashima.
You know, I think you might be getting my name wrong.
My surname isn't Kashima, it's Kashii.
Sorry!
I always thought...
Eh?!
Kashii?!
Yeah.
Kashii Banri.
Oh~! Rub, rub. It feels great!
Hey, are we meeting in front of the station on Sunday?
Yeah, and then we'll move to the court which Hasegawa-san and his friends often use.
Maho, you're still wet.
What kind of place could it be?
Oh~, it's making me really look forward to it!
Airi, that's not the towel you usually use right?
No, it isn't.
It belongs to my brother.
So you've made up with your brother?
Nope, my mother probably got them mixed up.
I see.
Erm...
You know, I haven't spoke to my brother all this time.
Eh?
I'm sure you'll be able to make up in no time if you get the chance.
I want to start talking to him, but I'm still a bit afraid.
Besides, my brother seems to be avoiding me.
I think it's better not to rush things.
As long as you don't give up, I'm sure it'll happen one day.
Yeah!
To think that you're Airi-chan's older brother...
I was quite surprised as well that you knew Airi.
Which means...
You know Airi's pervert of a coach, right?
Eh?
Pervert coach?
The Keishin girls basketball coach is an unknown high-schooler from somewhere or other, right?
What's more, that coach slept with my sister during camp.
Erm, that is...
I heard that he even made them play basketball in swimsuits!
That's totally messed up!
I get so worried knowing that there's guy like that near my sister.
What's wrong, Hasegawa?
I'm sorry, Banri.
It's me.
What is?
I'm that coach.
I punched him on reflex.
Damn it!
Have you heard from Airi-chan about her brother?
No.
I do know for a fact they aren't on good terms.
I see...
All right, let's begin our practice!
Nice shot, Nana.
Of course!
You girls are in the way!
From now on, only we adults can use this place.
Adults?
So middle-schoolers are adults, Nana?
Huh?
What are you talking about, Mayumi?
We paid the adult rate to get in here, didn't we?
I see.
First year middle-schoolers are adults.
Hey!
If you are adults, stick to the queue!
The girls were here first.
You can either wait your turn or play together with us.
Huh?
Why do we have to play with elementary school-
But if it's you, we'll play.
Someone else will be joining us soon, so let's bet the court on a match.
All right!
That's exactly what we want!
Then, it's decided.
Oh, he's here.
Ryuu!
We decided to have a match against these guys!
Huh?
Not interested.
Why do I have to do what you say?
Suga Ryuuji?
You're Hasegawa Subaru.
Long time no see.
I heard that your basketball club got suspended.
Serves you right!
I'll be a part of the bench soon.
I'll become the ace of the strongest team in the area, Itoda Commerce High School.
I congratulate you.
That's all?
Nana, be happy.
I changed my mind.
What?
I'll get to see them again after so long...
...your basketball skills.
Ryuu Team
Subaru Team
Sorry for dragging you both into this.
No, as long as we're of some help.
Am I up to it?
There's a reason why I chose you, Airi.
That girl, Mayumi-san, probably plays as centre.
I need your help.
Y-Yes!
I'll do my best!
Erm, Subaru-san...
Is that person someone you must beat, Subaru-san?
I don't want to lose to him in basketball.
I understand.
I will do my best!
Subaru-san!
I'm sorry!
No, my pass was bad.
Sorry.
I will reach it next time!
Oh? Tomoka is acting weird.
That's true.
Her movements are different from usual.
It isn't just Tomoka-chan who is off-form today.
What should I do? I can't stop her!
Airin!
That Mayumi-san is quite aggressive.
She's the worst opponent for Airi-chan given her condition now.
Everyone, do your best!
Do your best!
Airi, behind you!
Thank you!
Don't worry, Airi.
Let's get it back next time.
Y-Yes.
Tomoka, relax.
Yes!
I'll try my best!
Ryuu Team
Subaru Team
I'm sorry, I-
It's not your fault, Tomoka.
Don't worry about it.
Well, you guys weren't much at all.
Hasegawa, warm-up's over.
Let's start the main event.
1-vs-1.
One on one.
That was...
That's a jab step.
Jab step?
Put simply, it's a feint in your footwork.
He uses his speed and the big degree of the turn to pull away.
During the prefecture tournament, there wasn't anyone who could counter Suga's feint.
Of course, that includes Subaru.
Subaru-san...
What's wrong?
You won't come?
Then I'll go at you.
I won't lose in spirit!
I'll attack head on.
Well, that's about it.
[Name] Nagatsuka Saki
[Date of Birth] September 1
[Blood Type] O
[Class] Grade 6 Class C
[Height] 148cm
[Chest Size] She has a bit for her age but it is below average. (Secretly, she is conscious about it.)
[A word from Subaru] Sorry for the trouble Maho always causes...
Looks like I've overestimated you.
During that prefectural match, I still had some expectations of you.
I thought you could play the perfect supporting role for me.
You knew you couldn't be anything but my support, right?
That's why you went to that puny school.
This is the result of that.
If you don't win in basketball, what's the point?
As expected from Ryuu!
Now for the remainder of the autumn holidays, we can use the court!
Let's go home for today.
But, because of me, because of me-
Why would it be your fault, Tomoka-chan?
Of course, it isn't Airi-chan's fault either.
He had the match, and he lost.
Right, Subaru?
Yeah.
But-
Subaru blames himself, and only himself right now.
So let him be alone for a while.
Yes.
I won't tell you not to be sad.
But now, you're their coach,
so you have until tomorrow pick yourself up.
You're too slow on your passes!
The supporting players should do their bit and be of some use to me!
I won't let it end here.
I failed a lot today...
Me too...
Hey, hey!
If both of you feel bad, won't Hasegawa-san be more hurt?
But Tomoka, you were playing quite badly.
That's true.
Normally, Tomoka would have caught those passes.
As I thought...
Why didn't I...
Hm?
I know.
Also, I do too.
Eh?
Tell me!
Please!
If so, tomorrow morning...
...be sure to crash Hasegawa-san's house...
...and practice as per normal.
Yup, got it!
Hmm, I don't think that's enough.
Say it all!
I'll do my best!
Then...
Yeah!
Let's stop here today.
Y-Yes!
Jab step.
To conquer that...
Uh...
Eh?
Tomoka?!
The bath is a place you can connect deeply with someone.
Erm...
Please!
Please let me wash your back!
Eh?
Eh?!
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Don't worry!
I'm not hurt or anything.
I'm really sorry.
I'm always making mistakes, and of no help at all.
That's not true!
You're always helping me, Tomoka!
But...
I see.
She's still worried about yesterday.
Then, could I leave it to you?
Yes!
Subaru-san, you're really big.
It's really big.
Subaru-san's back.
For someone this big,
I'm too small to be of any help.
Tomoka, my passes yesterday didn't make it through at all.
I'm sorry.
I was no good.
Were you frustrated that you couldn't catch the passes?
Yes, I was frustrated!
I see.
Then, if there's another match,
will you want to catch it?
Yes!
I want you to let me catch it!
For that, I will go through any kind of harsh training!
Let me stay by your side, Subaru-san!
Thanks.
Everyone, I'm really sorry!
I'm sure you're all disappointed to see your coach get beaten like that.
I'm so frustrated that I can't help it.
I feel pathetic that I couldn't hold my own against Suga.
So I want to go for revenge.
Could you fight by my side?
Not as my support, but to win by playing as team!
I will work hard!
I don't want it to end like this!
Nana-san and her friends will only be here for the autumn holidays.
We don't have much time!
That's the way, Subarun!
Oh~!
Let's work hard, Onii-chan!
Hey, do you need someone to help out?
Aoi!
You'll help us?
Don't ask obvious questions like that.
Actually, I was told by the fifth-graders to come.
Mimi-chan and the rest?
That's right.
Having you guys lose before they could beat you irritates them.
Wow, sounds like something TsubaHii would say.
Aoi, thanks to you, I calmed down.
Thanks.
That much is-
Ah, sorry.
Kashii Banri
Answer
I'm sorry for punching you!
No, that couldn't be helped!
Anyone would get angry if they had to entrust their younger sister to someone they didn't know!
So you're getting along well?
That was the wrong choice of words!
That's not how it is!
It's just that my explanation wasn't clear enough!
Then that's fine.
Actually, I have something important to talk about.
Become Airi's coach?
There's no one better than you for the role, Banri.
Lend me your strength.
I'm sorry, but that's not possible.
I'm hated by Airi.
As you can see I'm brash, and I say hurtful stuff without meaning to, which scares her.
As well as being afraid to speak to me, she now won't even dare look at my face.
Given these circumstances, it wouldn't be possible for her to accept me as her coach in such a short time.
I'm sorry.
I see.
But you see, Banri...
Airi, Airi!
Onii-chan...
I'm sorry!
I was just resting for a bit!
What if you caught a cold?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I said too much.
Airi is changing bit by bit.
You've been training till very late recently.
Really?
Yeah, that might be true.
Why are you working so hard?
I want to change.
I have important people beside me, and an important place to be.
But given its importance, I disliked
that I couldn't accomplish anything.
If I could change even a bit of that,
I'm willing to work hard.
I see.
Airi, you're really admirable.
Starting today, Kashii Banri-kun, Airi's older brother, will be joining us for training.
Nice to meet you!
Banrin, you're really nervous!
Maho, don't say that.
Airi, your brother came!
Yup.
The three of us are going to work hard, okay?
Yes!
I'll do my best!
Tomoka!
Yeah, you've improved quite a lot.
But it's still not like how it used to be.
This isn't that different from morning practice, though.
I'm really sorry.
Since it's down to this, we'll have to try that strategy, Mokkan.
Eh?!
Oh~!
Hina wants to do it too!
No, you shouldn't.
If it isn't Tomo, there won't be any meaning to it.
What strategy?
Tomo's slump treatment!
You can do that?
Of course!
As long as Subarun cooperates with us for a bit!
Coming!
G-Good evening!
Good evening.
What's the matter?
Yes, actually...
Tonight, I'd like to...
P-Please let me stay for the night!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつずけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show your guts cool say what it's the best! Yay!
karada mo kokoro mo SS dakedo
カラダもココロもSSだけど
Although our bodies and hearts might be small in size,
yume wa LL datte ii jan! ii jan!
夢はLLだっていいじゃん! いいじゃん!
isn't it good enough that our dreams are large!
seishun miman no onayami ippai
青春未満のお悩みいっぱい
We are full of worries about growing up
hitori janai kara norikoerareruyo
ひとりじゃないからのりこえられるよ
We're not alone, so we can get through this!
motto umaku naritaina
もっと うまく なりたいな!
I want to become better!
(motto)
(もっと)
(Much)
(umaku)
(うまく)
(better)
anatano (oh...) odoroku (sugoi) kao ga mitai no
あなたの(おぉ...)おどろく(スゴイ) 顔が見たいの
I want to see (boo~) your surprised (Impressive!) face!
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
chikyuu wa okki na Basket Ball
地球はおっきな Basket Ball
The Earth is just a big basketball.
ashita wo shinjite ikuyo! (hai i-ku-yo)
あしたを信じていくよ! (ハイ い・く・よ)
Believe in tomorrow and move forward! (Yes, let-us-go!)
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
uchuu wa okkina Basket Court
宇宙はおっきなBasket Court
The universe is a big basketball court.
anata ni todoketai na... (se-no!)
あなたに届けたいな... (せーのっ)
I want it to reach you... (One, two!)
pasu! pasu! pasu!
パス! パス! パス!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
uketometekudasai!
受け止めてください!
Please receive it!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつづけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show you guts cool say what is the best! Yay!
What's wrong with those middle-schoolers?!
I'm so frustrated!
Acting so high and mighty!
But, but, Mokkan and Airin and Subarun will totally and utterly frypan them!
Next Time:
Overnight sensation!
Just you wait!