Finally!
I have started working on my dojinshi!
Well, participation is at one's will.
If this sells, it's the
celebrity road all the way!
Even Otome Road is unreliable.
Look at my way of living.
Please, look after her
in a lukewarm way.
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
If I keep the story short...
...how do I draw a book
that's going to sell?
It's confidence.
'Cause, there's no point working
on it slowly and dragging.
So I thought it'd be fastest...
...if I learned from you,
someone who's already selling a lot.
Your techniques...
Techniques...
What the hell are you thinking?
Yeah...
So, what kind of book really sells?
That's of course one
with good drawings and is...
...erotic.
An interesting story.
There's no way I can draw that!
Are you making fun of me?
Other important components
I should bring up would be...
...love.
Love to your characters.
Love to your creation.
Love is what hits
the heart of the reader.
Well, I think I understand it, but...
So it's love.
I have the confidence to not lose
to anyone with that one.
That's because I've been given
lots of love from my father and mother.
3rd Edition
Am I... about to sell?
Lenma University (alias)
Najimi's not here?
She hasn't been here
for the past two or three days.
More like, it amazed me more
that you were in the same school.
But I am not a teacher.
I'm a student.
That amazed me even more.
It's Najimi.
I've got it.
I finally got it.
Najimi, you really got it?
Yeah...
Then...
...you're going to give birth to it?
I think it's going to be a struggle,
but do your best.
Oh come on, I did my best already.
And I experienced the struggles
of giving birth enough.
What, you gave birth already?
That's why I'm this tired!
I didn't realize at all.
I didn't come for a while.
You didn't come for a while...
...and you became uneasy...
...so that's when you confirmed it?
What are you talking
about "confirmed"?
You were worried all alone.
I discussed this with Justice.
Right, Justice?
What?
Calm down, Justice.
Yeah...
Did you choose the name already?
Yeah, "Love Typhoon."
How original.
It's amazing that the
public office accepted that.
Love Typhoon Osana...
What are you mumbling about?
So, who's the other party?
Other party?
What is the other party
thinking about this?
Oh, you mean the customers?
Customers?
Najimi!
Ouch, what was that for!
I've lost respect for you!
Stop this dating with
compensation right away!
What?
Love Typhoon...
Hey, I was talking about the manga!
I know.
Huh?
Well, that was funny.
No, it wasn't funny!
Justice clearly got the wrong idea.
Whose fault is that!
So, can I see that "Love Typhoon"?
Love Typhoon, The feeling to convey
Beauty Love
How is it?
Tell me your candid opinion.
Okay, well...
It's nice paper. It's really
good paper, seriously, yeah.
Najimi, you're lucky to be able to get this
kind of nice paper on your first publishing.
The texture on your fingers is great
and the gloss is a wonderful finish.
Tsuyuri, what is it?
Well, um...
There isn't much technique,
but the feelings you stuffed into this...
...will reach the readers.
Really? That makes me blush.
I'm becoming impatient.
No, nothing.
Najimi, what is this?
Oh, my pen name.
Beauty Love.
Well, um...
It's perfect for you, Najimi.
Seriously, yeah.
Especially the ending
to "love" isn't "bu" and...
...instead is "u" with dots
makes you feel the pickiness of it.
More like, sorry. I can't do it anymore.
What?
It's here! This day is here!
Aim for the 10,000 yen!
You obviously can't make 10,000
if you only have 30 copies.
Hey, don't pull me back to reality!
So Najimi, you're at 30 copies, huh?
Yes, that's right.
It's a thousandth of your amount!
Stop it!
No, it's okay, Sora.
To Najimi, this is a special piece.
These 30 copies are the
crystallization of love and tears that...
...totally overthrows my 30,000 copies.
He's taking this
misunderstanding all the way.
Najimi...
I'll help you.
It's not just your body anymore.
Just as I told you...
...you sent it out to the printer, huh?
How is it?
First of all, it's really good paper.
It's good paper, yeah, really.
It's your first publishing,
and you got good paper like this...
Wait, what?
You put your child's name as the title?
Ah, it's a proud child, Najimi.
You can't look at that because it's 18+.
Um, I'm sorry.
What the hell is up with her?
Let's go, Sora.
Yeah.
Is this that bad beyond belief?
What do you mean
by that way of laughing!
You're from that time!
Well, well.
What is it, huh?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
We're so busy we don't even
have time to take a break.
Yeah, but it's fun.
The two that keep on moving even
if they don't have time to take a break.
The many customers
that watch over them.
Don't you feel it?
It's like a masquerade
for just the two of them.
Justice!
Sora!
Really...
Justice apparently sold out.
What?
He's asking, "How are you doing?"
This is bad.
If it keeps up like this, on top of
not selling at all, I'll be totally in debt!
Hey!
You're from the other day.
What?
You remembered me?
Well, I didn't want to remember, but...
This is something you drew?
This is the feeling of someone
reading the erotic comic you drew?
Yes, it's definitely embarrassing.
Like if you were exposing
your naked body in a public place.
It's covered, but that is
an unpleasant metaphor.
That will eventually turn into pleasure.
That's not likely.
It's pretty perverted.
Oh, you mean the comic.
I'm not like that.
More like, I'm imagining things that
the readers would like...
...and that's what I'm drawing,
so it's not what I'm into or anything.
What am I explaining myself for?
Instead, I'm a weird girl now.
I'm not having a
narrow view or anything.
That's right.
Also, just because
I wrote an erotic book...
...doesn't mean I'm
sexually frustrated or anything!
I know, and...
...I like women that draw
these kinds of manga too.
What is this sexual harassment!
Sexual harassment?
Is it a sexual harassment theme?
Hey, could we look at that?
Please get in line.
They're reading it.
So many men are looking at my erotic
drawings and reading my erotic lines!
Your hard work is coming across.
Can I get a copy?
Can I get a copy of this?
Are you serious?
Seriously.
I-It will be 500 yen.
Here.
I love you!
Wait, what is this all of a sudden?
How much is this?
Can I get one too?
We are not doing a service
where you get a hug if you buy it.
What a bummer...
I'm so sorry!
Thank you very much.
Well, if you would like, want to
go somewhere just the two of us...
Hey, what is it!
He's going to get me...
Are you the one?
You're going to take care of her, right?
What!
I don't know!
I finally sold one.
Please look this way!
Things that you can and
can't sell. Let's be careful.
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
In the next episode,
I will service you in 3 different ways.
3-way service...
4th Edition
Please stop, Master.