Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Good morning, Kagami.
Yo.
You're in a good mood.
What happened?
I got a new cell phone.
Finally, huh?
Seriously?
Then you can use songs for
ringtones and set screensavers.
You're actually like a kid.
Wait a sec.
Do you watch anime and stuff then?
I already switched to one of my favourites.
Mi-Mi-Miracle! Mikurun-run! Mi-Mi-Miracle! Mikurun-run!
That's some song.
But you know...
You have to pick up before it gets to the chorus...
...which makes you stress out and regret it, right?
And if you don't pick up, they'll hang up anyway.
I don't really care about that stuff...
Is that how it is?
Ring
If I had to choose, I'd say Kagami's...
...an orc!
Why?!
I'm the only one who's a monster?!
Yes, hello?
This is Hiiragi.
Yeah...
Too used to answering the phone at home.
She was all mad at me a second ago...
I got a sandwich with balsamic vinegar sauce today...
How come women can switch moods so quickly?
But the other day, my mother...
I'm home!
Yes?
Hello?
Miyuki?
Geez!
Miyuki!
Here, phone!
From Konata-chan!
Um...
Did I do something wrong?
No.
My mother is incapable of guile...
...so you can tell when she's mad.
I believe she hit her leg against the table.
But that wasn't exactly an issue of guile...
She's exactly the way she seems.
It's a good thing Miyuki knows so much.
I can ask you about anything I don't know.
I enjoyed being praised by Mother...
...so I became accustomed to looking things up.
Miyuki knows more than Mama does.
Now, I enjoy learning as well.
So in other words...
...I did a wonderful job of raising you, right?
That's how the conversation went.
That's some silly conversation.
In any case, I now know that you're
undeniably your mother's daughter.
Are we similar?
Down to the very last gene.
But...
Miyuki isn't just good at studying...
She knows a lot about all kinds of stuff.
There are many sources of information these days...
...and it's fun to learn a lot.
I couldn't do it.
No motivation!
Wanna play!
Rely on others in a pinch!
They say that only children and oldest children tend to be selfish...
That's right.
Aren't you an only child?
I guess it depends on the person.
Not at all.
You could say that I had a model...
...or someone who was like an oldest child...
...in my life.
I don't feel like cleaning!
Laundry is tiring!
Can we order out?
In our family...
...we have two older sisters...
...and meals turn into battles...
...which helps build character.
Yay!
Sukiyaki!
Eat up.
Let's eat!
And then, Kona-chan...
Oof.
...said that cell phones go out of service because
of a thick concentration of these something particles.
Mine.
Really...
And when her battery runs out...
...she says her phone's out of commission.
This one.
Modern girls use some strange words.
Hey.
Leave enough for Tsukasa.
Tsukasa.
You can have mine.
Thanks.
You sound nice...
...but weren't you stuffing yourself?
So having a lot of siblings can be good and bad.
You can say that about being an only child as well.
That's right.
Miyuki-chan spaces out sometimes.
Space out, is it?
You know...
Like the other day...
I can never get sick of the name elegant sea urchin.
What happened?
I was walking and thinking...
...and I ended up running into the door.
You have incredible concentration, Miyuki-san.
That happens a lot, huh?
Not often, though it's embarrassing.
Huh?
Doesn't it mean you have no concentration
if you start thinking about something...
...while you're doing something else?
Huh?
Which way is it?
That sounds like something Miyuki would do.
Indeed.
The other day, I was warming a drink...
I forgot.
I'll have to reheat it.
Many minutes later
One more time...
And again...
Geez, Miyuki...
You forgot again, didn't you?
Sorry, it just happens.
You're so hopeless.
I'll bring it to you.
Thank you so much.
Click.
Many minutes later
I forgot.
Like mother, like daughter.
Though it's embarrassing.
When did you start wearing glasses, Miyuki-san?
Midway through grade school, I believe.
So you weren't born nearsighted.
When I was little...
...I loved how my mother would read to me before I went to sleep....
...but my mother would fall asleep first...
...and I would want to know what happened...
...so I would read by myself in the dark room...
...and eventually, my eyes...
But it's best when you're close with your parents like that.
The reason kids these days tend to be cold and apathetic...
...may be a lack of...
...parental love or intimacy.
That's right...
I wonder when the last time Mom gave me a big hug was.
You're clingy...
...so you were really close to Mom until middle school.
Really?
That might be why you're such a good girl.
My dad is still clingy about me.
That might be why you haven't grown up in a manner of speaking.
Speaking of kids...
...there sure have been a lot cases of kidnapping and confinement.
You seem to be sensitive to that stuff.
Well, first, I'm worried about my dad.
Don't just blurt out scary things.
Well, it more or less has to do with the games I play.
I wish they'd stop since it creates problems for other users.
At the very least...
...this stuff doesn't happen in the games I play.
Oh, yeah.
It's almost been a year.
Since what?
Since I started working.
My coworkers...
...said they're going to do something to celebrate.
That's right.
We've never gone before.
Maybe we'll check out the place you work some time.
As payback for New Year's.
Sure.
It's okay?!
Don't people usually hate that?
Well, half my job is to let other people look at me.
It's called a costume café, right?
Let me know before you come.
It can be pretty crowded at times.
We'll do that.
Hey, y'all.
Class started.
Hello?
We just left the station.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll buy it for you.
Okay. Okay!
Did Kona-chan say it was okay?
It's okay...
...but she wants us to go over there and buy this month's Comp...
...and the Lelou** comic for her.
I wonder if we can find it quickly.
She said to remember to ask the clerk to stamp the receipt...
Sounds complicated.
Excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
Can I take a picture?
I'm not Kamigishi.
I'm Hiiragi.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Could I also get a picture?
Sheesh!
Stop that!
Excuse me then.
Could you say Hiroyuki-chan?
Hi-Hiroyuki...
...-chan?
We're leaving.
This is the first time I've been in one of these places.
It's so big that I'm quite nervous.
She said on the phone that we'd see it once we got there.
Kona-chan would know.
I'd get lost if I were alone.
Is this it?
Now we just need the Lelou** comic.
Not here.
I can't find it.
Excuse me.
Where would I find the Lelou** comic?
That would be this.
Code Ge**s.
You could at least have told us the title...
Can I put this on a point card next time?
Then you'll have to bring this receipt with you.
Okay.
Thank you very much!
Now we just have to go find Konata.
I'm hungry, Sis!
I'm almost done working.
Hold on a bit.
How are we supposed to find our way?
Here
Gamers
I looked it up just in case.
I believe it's this way.
That's our Yuki-chan!
Guess we can only count on Miyuki.
This is the place, right?
Yes.
On the third floor.
Welcome back, Master!
You can have a seat here.
The first hour is 800 yen.
All the soda you can drink.
All the games you can play for free.
All the sweets you can eat.
Can I get this broiled eel?
Currently not available.
Then the shrimp pilaf...
Currently impossible.
Then spaghetti with meat sauce.
It will take fifteen minutes.
Permission?
Okay.
Do it.
They can do business like that?
You people.
What do you want to drink?
H-Hold on a sec!
Hurry it up.
There's a penalty if you take too long! A penalty!
Is this how you should treat a customer?
It's how we do things here.
You're done deciding, right?
I'll have a melon soda.
I have no interest in an ordinary menu.
I'll have milk tea.
What do you want?
I'm looking!
A brigade member shouldn't be this slow!
When did I become a brigade member?
That's the setting in this place.
You're a hundred years too early to be defying the chief.
What a pain...
Then give me an ice coffee.
Order from the chief!
Wait here!
Oh, boy...
Hasn't stunk in a while...
We're going on stage now so watch.
If we can solve all the mysteries on this planet...
...we can all go anywhere we want!
Even to the end of time!
Boooon!
Encore! Encore!
Amazing!
They're all very talented.
Ponytail version next!
Ponytail version please!
She's an exchange student.
A first-year at our school.
My name is Patricia Martin.
Nice to meet you.
We've even put out a CD.
Here.
Should you really release something like that?
Excuse me.
Could I get some tea?
Do you want warm tea?
Yes.
Hot tea please.
I'd like a melon soda please.
Got it.
Uh...
What's this Up-To-Us Mixed Juicy Juice like?
Classified information.
House rules!
This café really exhausts me.
Nurse's Office
AAA
M-My height...
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll grow in time.
Th-That's right.
Big Sister!
Yu-chan.
And here's a person to crush my hopes...
H-How much taller have you grown since you entered high school?
Man...
I haven't grown in either direction.
You'd better prepare yourself.
Touch
No need to fret.
You're still in demand.
Hey, you two.
Have you ever been to a class reunion?
Not yet.
Me neither.
But where did that come from?
Isn't the phrase "You haven't
changed" usually supposed to be a compliment?
But the only people who want to hear
that have probably changed considerably...
...in various places...
So it does concern you.
Okay!
Golden Week's starting...
...but listen up.
You've also got tests right after break...
...but don't forget that you're preparing for exams...
...and use your vacation wisely.
Also...
...you still have a few days left of school before break.
I won't let you take any sick days.
Kamchatka!
The aura emitting from her whole body...
No question about it.
She's Legendary Girl A.
Is today's target that new book?
Or is she after some goods?
Use your head!
Don't forget that we're having a spring audio/visual special!
Not yet!
Give her enough room.
Recommend an item once she's let her guard down.
That's right!
Slowly wait to approach her.
That's it!
Now!
Approach her!
Heading out!
Welcome!
We have these new releases!
Mi-Mi-Miracle!
Kagami?
You made it?
Be right there.
Just killing time while waiting for someone?!
When you're boiling something...
...you use rough cutting...
...and cut them into random shapes.
My...
Really...
That increases the total surface area...
...and lets the taste soak in.
Once you've scooped out the Iye...
...you let it cook on medium for around ten minutes.
It'll become soggy if it sits too long...
...so take it out once you can poke through.
I see.
Somehow, when it's home ec...
...Miyuki starts looking below average.
Now I know how you see us.
Hiiragi-chan.
Want to study for the test in the library together?
Sounds good.
Club activities are on hiatus right before a test...
...so there's nothing to do.
That's why you study.
That's the point.
Well...
I know that...
But when my club time is suddenly free...
...it's like a whole new world is open to me.
When you look at it that way, I can't waste the time on studying.
It gets me all excited.
Anyway, you should realize you're
half the reason for this study session.
Pooped!
That was fast!
Let's take a break!
Maybe you can't concentrate because you have no goal?
Don't you have any dreams for the future?
Dreams?
Not really for the future...
But this time of year, don't you wish you could win the lottery...
...and live the simple life?
Everything's a drag.
Minegishi.
Do something about her.
When I use my head...
...I need sweet stuff!
Once we're done, I'll give you some cookies I baked last time.
Hang in there.
So you bake sweets and stuff.
Can't compare with that Ajiyoshi boy.
Nah, you've got that Ajiyoshi boy licked.
Studying's a pain!
Sis.
I tried making a madeleine.
What's wrong?
Oh, yeah...
I wouldn't lump you with them...
...but I was just thinking that you tend to make similar friends.
Haven't you been overly lax...
...because you thought it was only stomatitis?
They sure are a lot more medical programs like these.
That's true.
It's scary since it could really happen.
Especially for me.
Actually, after watching this...
...I start feeling like my time's almost come.
Too many possible causes.
Please stop the depressing talk.
I beg you!
Live!
Sis!
Teach me this part.
Um...
Curses, like chickens, come home to roost?
This means...
...that Kazu likes chicken.
When you go home, you'll find roast chicken...
...I think?
Sis.
Translate the next part.
Let's see.
When you make the contract...
Did we ever learn this?
That's right.
This one time when I was working as a shrine maiden...
...a foreigner told me about why the gate is called a torii.
What'd he say?
In the past, people believed that birds would carry the dead...
...so they named it tori (bird) i (here)
because it was a place for birds to rest.
They know way more about Japan than we do.
It might have been faster to ask Kagami...
The freezing Sea of Japan...
Where have my loved ones gone?
Lucky Channel
Production
AKIRA
KOGAMI
BIG
SHOW!!
Now she swims solo through the
raging waters of the entertainment industry.
Here's a song.
Akira Kogami with "Cape of Thirty Years."
Hey!
How is this a concert?
This is the best we could do on our budget!
Don't think you'll get away with this!
It's starting!
Who do you think I...
Would you mind if I talked to myself?
I softly whispered to the seagulls.
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
Frozen by the northern sea winds...
Gone astray...
Love falls apart...
Drinks are taking a while.
Resentment crumbles...
Yes.
I've brought your drinks.
Unable to reach you so far away...
Thanks.
I stand still...
Soaked in...
W-W-Wait!
The brown one's mine!
Cape of Thirty Years!
Lucky Channel
Production
AKIRA
KOGAMI
BIG
SHOW!!
Good stuff!
We break down in tears in our own little lodge...
Let's see...
"Exhausting Life Returns" is...
Regretting that night of love...
Man, making selfish promises...
Never keeping a single one...
Thrown right into...
Yes?
That's right.
Extension...
...the spray of the waves...
It's okay.
Yes. Thanks.
Five minutes left.
Unable to meet you so far away...
Time to clean up, clean up.
Bye-bee!
I wish to offer you my yearning...
Man...
I want to release a song by myself, too.
Soul of Thirty Years!
For-For-For-Forgot my something...
Would you mind if I talked to myself?
I softly whispered to the seagulls.
Woman, led by a sincere heart...
Frozen by the northern sea winds.
Gone astray...
Love falls apart...
Resentment crumbles...
Unable to reach you so far away...
I stand still...
Soaked in tears...
Cape of Thirty Years!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Gloomy!
Nagato.
Nobody's gonna watch if you're like that.
Sound more like somebody...
...happily moving from the TV to the
tearoom at 6:30 on a Sunday night.
One more time.
Go!
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Nothing changed!
Forget it.
「Under the Sun」
Next time:
Under the Sun.
Look forward to next time.
Er, no.
Rock, paper, scissors!