I apologize for the delay.
It's been a rather hectic night.
I understand.
It is quite a situation.
I imagine covering it up
will prove challenging.
Yes, well...
It is certainly too much for the Church alone.
We intend to accept any offers of help.
Moving on, Father...
Have you reached a decision
regarding my request?
As relates to the bounty
offered for Caster's defeat?
Thank god...
Once I receive the extra Command Spell,
Diarmuid and I will be truly linked.
My right hand is gone...
My right hand! Without my right hand...
Without it...
Oh no, I can't call Diarmuid!
He won't care for me!
My right hand... Right hand, right hand, right hand!
My right hand!
My hand...
I have captured Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri
in the new city.
I cut off her arm, to prevent her
from using Command Spells.
Good.
Now get out of there quickly.
Lancer will be back soon.
Roger.
I have saved Matou Kariya's life...
Knowing full well that he will seek
vengeance upon my master.
This is an inexcusable act of betrayal.
But what am I feeling?
It isn't regret...
I feel exhilarated?
Observers have indeed confirmed
that during this evening's battle,
the Servant Lancer
was instrumental in defeating Caster.
Then I have the right to one of
the Command Spells?
Well...
Lord Kayneth Archibald,
I am debating whether or not you should
be considered a Master at this point.
My pact with Lancer is shared
by my fiancée, Sola-Ui, and myself.
And currently,
does Sola-Ui not act as both
Lancer's mana source
and the Command Spells' custodian?
That's correct.
I have temporarily entrusted Sola-Ui
with the Command Spells.
However, I still maintain all rights
granted by the pact.
After all,
my name alone is registered
with the Church as a Master.
Very well.
I acknowledge your right.
Lord Kayneth, hold out your hand.
Take this cup, and drink from it.
This is my blood, given to you,
for the salvation of all.
The blood of a contract!
I hope that, as a Master,
you will continue to fight honorably.
Oh, of course.
It's one mere Spell!
I'm hardly any better off.
I couldn't give the other Masters a chance
to lay claim to an extra Spell!
Lady Sola-Ui!
You useless screw-up!
Incompetent, worthless dolt!
I can't even trust you to protect one woman!
So much for your chivalry.
I have disgraced myself.
Even if she was a temporary proxy,
you have utterly failed to protect your Master!
What kind of pathetic Servant are you?!
I can't believe you'd have the nerve
to stroll back here alone,
as if nothing had happened.
Unfortunately, my Master,
because Lady Sola-Ui and I were never
linked by a pact,
we could not sense each other's presence.
Which is exactly why you should
have taken extra precautions!
My Master,
Lady Sola-Ui still lives.
My mana supply has remained steady.
So what?!
Without a pact binding you,
you cannot trace her whereabouts,
so it's irrelevant!
Oh, Sola-Ui, I should never have
given you those Command Spells...
I could not convince her otherwise.
I share in her responsibility.
Your arrogance is unbelievable.
Don't play me for a fool, Lancer.
You were encouraging Sola-Ui.
No, I would never!
Just like the legends...
You can only see a monarch's fiancée,
as an object of lust.
My Master...
I ask that you retract your words.
Oh, did I hit a nerve?
You blather on about your
oath of unconditional fealty,
But you are just an animal
consumed by your base desires.
Lord Kayneth...
Why...
Why will you not understand?
I...
I only wished to preserve my honor.
To fight and win glory by your side!
Don't take that tone with me, Servant!
You forget your place.
You're nothing but a ghost,
given form by magic!
But you presume to lecture your Master?
Ridiculous!
If you are so unhappy,
then use your precious pride
to disobey my Command Spell.
You can't do it!
This is the string that moves the
puppets we call Servants.
Lord Kayneth...
Master.
What?
You still have more to say?
No, sir.
But something approaches.
It's just as Kiritsugu said.
There are remnants of
a magic barrier.
But it's odd...
Perhaps it hasn't been properly maintained.
It's failing...
everywhere...
I never expected you to come here, Saber.
My...
My ally found this place and informed me
that it was your current location.
My Master's fiancée has gone missing, Saber.
You wouldn't happen to know
where she might be?
I fear not.
Did something happen?
No, never mind.
Anyway, are you sure about this, Saber?
I imagine you haven't come
to make small talk.
But fighting Caster for so long,
and using that attack,
must have taken its toll.
The same can be said for all the Servants.
None will seek further conflict tonight.
They will shore up their defenses.
And thus, we shan't need to worry
about outside interference.
It's nearly dawn...
But I believe tonight
may be our best chance to finish our duel.
What say you, Lancer?
Saber...
Your pure, unclouded fighting spirit
is the only thing that still calms my heart.
Her strikes are weak.
Saber...
You intend to fight without
using your left hand?
Don't misunderstand, Lancer.
Should I use my left hand,
the shame of it would surely dull my sword.
Against your spear,
that would prove fatal.
Saber...
Therefore, Diarmuid,
this represents my best chance
at defeating you at full strength.
Pride resides in the sword of chivalry.
I...
I am glad to have met you.
I am first spear of the knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne!
En garde!
Well met.
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
shall face you.
Have at you!
Why can't he win?
If he cannot guarantee his victory,
he should return to his Master and escape.
Rescuing Sola-Ui should be our top priority...
Why does that useless Servant not
even understand that much?
Of all people...
Him?
This is...
a Self-Geis Scroll.
A mage contract,
enchanted to be completely unbreakable,
regardless of circumstance.
Restraining Spell.
Affected Party: Emiya Kiritsugu.
Dictated by crest of the house of Emiya.
Upon fulfillment of the conditions below,
the contract's Terms will become binding,
restricting the Affected Party
without exception.
Terms:
The fifth heir to the house of Emiya,
Kiritsugu, son of Norikata,
will be forever forbidden from
inflicting death or injury upon,
or acting with the intent to
inflict death or injury upon,
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and
Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri.
Conditions...
The Geis's curse
is fundamentally irrevocable,
once the contract is signed.
Even should the Affected Party die,
so long as the crest exists,
it will bind the soul, even after death.
It's true that if I meet its demands,
he can never kill me.
But...
Given these Conditions, my battle...
is over...
The Holy Grail...
The pride of the Archibalds...
He requires me to discard it all?
Sola-Ui...
Use all of your remaining Command Spells
to compel your Servant to commit suicide.
The conditions have been met.
Do you...
Do you really desire victory so much?
Do you desire the Grail so much?
You have trampled...
You have trampled upon my one last wish...
And you...
Do you feel no shame?!
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive you for this!
Monsters, blinded by your own ambition,
defiling the pride of knights,
may my blood stain your dreams!
May the Grail be cursed.
May the wish it grants bring only disaster!
And when you roast in the pits of hell,
remember the rage of Diarmuid!
Has the Geis taken effect?
Yes, the contract is complete.
I can no longer kill you.
At least, not personally.
Kill me...
Please kill me...
Sorry.
I'm contractually bound from that.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
I finally see you for the vile man you are.
I was a fool.
I believed that though our methods differed,
we shared a common goal.
Until now,
I have trusted in Irisviel's words,
and did not question your character.
But now,
I cannot believe that your
ambition for the Grail
will ever save anyone.
Explain yourself, Kiritsugu!
What do you truly desire
from the Holy Grail?!
Even if my sword ultimately claims the Grail,
if that means I must relinquish it to you...
Answer her, Kiritsugu.
This time, you have a responsibility
to explain yourself to her.
Now that I think about it,
this is the first time you've seen
the way I kill, Iri.
If you neutralize only the Master,
the Servant may form a pact
with another Master.
Thus, I needed to eliminate
them both simultaneously.
Hey, Kiritsugu...
Speak to Saber, not me.
She needs to hear your explanation.
No.
There's no point in trying to explain anything
to a murderer who can take pride
in things such as honor and glory.
You would even insult chivalry
to my face, fiend?!
A knight will never save the world.
They pretend there are
right and wrong ways to fight,
as though there is honor on
the battlefield itself.
These illusions named honor and glory,
created by the words of heroes,
have entranced countless
young men throughout history,
leading them to their deaths.
They are not illusions!
Even in the taking of another's life,
as a human act,
law and principle must still hold.
Otherwise, every single war would
unleash hell on this world!
And there it is.
You heard her, Iri.
Our Heroic Spirit says that
war is preferable to hell.
What idiocy.
War is hell itself.
Hope does not exist on a battlefield.
There is nothing but indescribable suffering.
Just the victory birthed
by the pain and anguish of the defeated.
But humanity has never learned.
Because in every era, larger-than-life heroes
have blinded the masses with
fantastic tales of their deeds,
until no one can see bloodshed's inherent evil.
Human nature has not
evolved since the Stone Age!
So, Kiritsugu...
When you insult Saber,
is this because of your
hatred for Heroic Spirits?
Of course not.
I don't let personal feelings get in the way.
I will obtain the Holy Grail and save this world.
And I am using
the most effective weapon at my disposal to do it.
Justice will not save this world.
I have no interest in pursuing it.
Kiritsugu.
Do you truly understand?
If you commit evil, in the
name of hatred for evil,
your anger and hatred can
only bring further conflict.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I know not who or what betrayed you,
or what has caused you such despair.
But your anger and sorrow...
These belong to one who once sought justice.
Kiritsugu,
as a young man,
you, too, hoped to become
a just hero, correct?
More than anyone,
you believed in, and longed to be,
a hero who would save the world.
Or am I wrong?
I will break this endless cycle.
And the Holy Grail alone can
make that possible.
The blood I spill in Fuyuki City
will be the last blood humanity will ever shed.
If I must take on every sin in the world,
to save that world from evil,
I dirty my hands gladly.
Kiritsugu's gone, right?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!
Episode 16:
The End of Honor
This cannot be permitted!
An alliance? At this stage?
Allow me to tell you the truth
of this Holy Grail War.
Very well, I accept.
Die, for the sake of his dream.
What a tedious end.
Next Time:
The Eighth Contract
Goodbye, Father!