Over a century ago, mankind had to face a new enemy.
The difference of power between mankind and their newfound enemy was overwhelming.
Soon, mankind was driven to the brink of extinction.
The surviving humans built three walls: the Maria, the Rose, and the Sina.
They then lived the next century in peace, under their protection.
However, in year 845,
the Colossal Titan and the Armored Titan appeared out of nowhere.
Instantly, the walls were shattered,
along with the peace of everyday life.
Mankind abandoned Wall Maria.
They lost a fifth of their population, and a third of their territory,
as human activity was pushed back to Wall Rose.
In year 850,
the Colossal Titan once again appeared out of nowhere and broke the wall,
allowing for the further advance of the Titans.
In two hours, the evacuation of civilians was completed.
No one fell victim to the Titans,
with the exception of the soldiers who sacrificed themselves in the defense.
Eren! As long as you're there for me, I can do anything.
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
A Small Blade
Defense of Trost (pt 3)
Please stop, Commander!
If the Titans attacked, us supports won't be able to hold this place by ourselves!
Please stay with us!
Get out of my way.
I must leave to oversee the organization of the reinforcements.
Behind the safer inner gate?
What the hell are you trying to say?
My actions adhere to the regulations.
I am just following the rules!
It is what soldiers are supposed to do!
But if this place falls—
Silence!
If you say one more word, I will consider it as treason and punish you accordingly!
They should've heard the bells that signaled for retreat.
Why aren't they climbing the wall yet?
This is the end...
We're done for.
Great.
What's the point of that?
Hey, Jean! What do we do now?
What can we do?
We finally received the order to retreat, but we
can't get over the wall because we're out of gas.
We're all going to die.
Thanks to those fucking cowards...
You mean the support squads?
What happened to them?
Are they all dead?
They probably lost their will to fight.
I understand how they feel.
But I doubt they've abandoned their mission and barricaded themselves away in the HQ.
I'm guessing the Titans have them surrounded, which is why they can't supply us with gas.
That's exactly why we have no choice but to go all in on those Titans!
Sitting here and waiting to die isn't going to make a difference!
The Titans are going to surround us too!
If we keep running away from them, we'd just end up wasting the little gas we have left.
Once we lose our agility, it'd really be over!
I never thought I'd hear you make an intelligent comment, Connie.
But how do you propose we do that with the forces we have left?
The vanguard has nearly been wiped out.
Moreover, which one of us cadets could
possibly take command of such an operation?
Not that we could do anything about the Titans even if someone took command.
The gas storage is probably crawling with 3-4 meter class Titans by now.
And of course, we can't fight them inside the storage.
So it's hopeless?
I had such a boring life.
If someone told me beforehand...
Let's do it!
Stand up! If we all work together, we can do it!
I'll be in front!
Armin! Let's go together and—
What now, Reiner?
It's not time yet. We must group up first.
It's over...
No matter what we do, we'll be
dead before we make it out of here.
I mean, I'm prepared to die...
But what exactly am I going to die for?
Mikasa!
Weren't you with the rearguard?
Annie!
I think I understand the situation.
And I apologize for bothering you,
but have you seen Eren's unit?
No, and I haven't seen anyone climbed the wall either.
Armin's over there, though.
Armin!
Mikasa?!
Crap! How can I look her in the face?
I don't even deserve to be alive.
If I knew it'd come to this...
I should've just died with him!
Armin, are you hurt?
Feeling okay?
Where's Eren?
Armin?
Our unit... The 34th cadet unit...
Thomas Wagner.
Nic Tius.
Mylius Zeramuski.
Mina Carolina.
Eren Jaeger.
All five of them have fulfilled their duty
and died heroic deaths in battle!
No way...
So the 34th unit was nearly wiped out...
If we fight the Titans, we'll end up like them.
I'm sorry, Mikasa.
Eren died in my stead...
I couldn't do anything!
I'm so sorry!
Armin.
Take a deep breath.
This isn't the time to be emotional.
Stand up.
Marco.
If we take out the Titans around the HQ,
we can replenish our gas supplies and climb the wall.
Does that sound correct?
Yeah...
But even if you're with us, there's just too many...
We can do it.
I'm strong.
Stronger than all of you.
Extremely strong.
I can kill all those Titans there.
Even if I'm alone.
You're either incompetent or you're spineless cowards.
How pathetic.
You can sit here and suck on your fingers. Yeah, do that.
Hey, Mikasa! What are you saying?
You want to fight all those Titans by yourself?
There's no way you can do that!
If I can't, then I'll just die.
But if I win, I live.
Unless I fight, I cannot win.
Hey!
Your oratory skills are what's pathetic.
Was the point of that to shock us into action?
It's all your fault, Eren!
Hey! Were we trained to let our comrades fight alone?!
At this rate, we're going to turn out to be spineless cowards!
I'm surprised I'd hear him say that.
Hey!
Cowards! Weaklings! Retards!
They're nuts...
Dammit!
Let's do it!
Hurry! Follow Mikasa!
Let's keep this fight short!
We need to kill them all before we run out of gas!
Mikasa's just amazing.
How can she move that fast?
She's using too much gas.
She'll run out right away.
I don't care how skilled she is...
Without our agility, we can't do anything!
She's not in her usual cool-headed state...
She wants to drown out her pain through action.
If she keeps this up...
Mikasa!
Dammit!
Jean! You lead the others!
I'll go with Armin!
I'm coming with you!
What are you talking about?!
There are more Titans left!
We need your skills!
Again...
It happened again.
I lost my family once again...
This pain is familiar.
Will I have to start fresh once again?
Currently Disclosable Information
Design of the 3D Maneuver Gear (pt 1)
(The spatial maneuver unit)
It reels steel cables in from the drum
There are two independent axes
Currently Disclosable Information
Design of the 3D Maneuver Gear (pt 2)
(The control unit)
The control unit is a black box
(The engineering department designs and improves it in secret)
(The gas cylinder)
The cylinder is filled with compressed gas
It's no good.
We won't get close to HQ...
Unless we're prepared to make sacrifices.
Damn!
He's outta gas!
Stay away!
Tom! I'm going to save you!
Stop! You can't!
Stop!
Why couldn't I stop them?
Why didn't I stop them?
If I had stopped them, even if by force...
This wouldn't happen.
Am I really cut out for this?
Am I really cut out for a position with so much responsibility?
Stop! I don't want to die!
This world is merciless...
And it's also very beautiful.
I lived a good life.
Huh?
Why?
I thought I'd given up.
Why am I standing?
Why am I struggling?
Why?
My life has no meaning anymore.
What's keeping me going?
Fight!
Eren...
You must fight!
Fight! Fight!
I'm sorry, Eren.
I won't give up.
I'll never give up again.
If I died, I won't be able to remember you.
So I'll win, no matter what!
I'll survive, no matter what!
What's going on?
A Titan...
is killing...
another Titan...
Please be all right, Mikasa!
Mikasa!
Mikasa, are you hurt?
Are you guys okay?!
Yeah!
We must get going!
Shit! This is bad!
There are two 15 meter classes!
No... That Titan's...
It finished the other Titan off?
It knew of a Titan's weak point?
We must get going before it comes this way!
No. It doesn't care about us.
It could've attacked us long ago.
It seemed like it had an idea of how to perform hand-to-hand combat.
What was that?!
Just consider it an abnormal!
There's just too much we don't know.
Anyway, we must hurry to the HQ!
Wait!
Mikasa's out of gas!
Huh?! Are you fucking kidding me?!
What are we gonna do without you?!
It's obvious what we need to do.
I don't have much gas left...
You can take mine.
Armin?!
There's no other choice!
The gas is useless on me.
But please use it carefully this time.
You must save everyone.
I moved in without the determination to shoulder their lives.
I even gave up on my life without
realizing the responsibility I held.
And it was all due to my own issues.
I...
All right!
Your maneuver gear's good to go.
I gave you all of my blades as well.
Just leave one with me.
Now that I think about it, I don't want to be eaten alive.
B-But...
Armin.
I won't leave you behind.
At that moment...
I was utterly confused.
I've never heard about Titans killing their own kind.
Then I was slightly exalted.
Because what I was looking at
felt like the reification of mankind's anger.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
A Titan that kills Titans.
The cadets of the 104th class stood astounded and petrified after seeing it for themselves.
Soon, however, they witnessed something even more shocking.
I Can Hear a Heart Beating
Defense of Trost (pt 4)