Thank you.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Her name is Fukahori Yurika.
Second year, class six, seat number twenty-two.
So she's a year ahead of us.
She moved here from Tokyo during her first year of middle school.
Her hobbies are oil painting and fencing.
Her birthday is February 10th.
That's all.
Just for your information...
W-What are you talkin' about?!
Don't play dumb.
This has gotten as hard as a rock.
When you think about her, you get a lump in your throat,
so you can't get the food down, right?
Poor thing...
You're completely lovesick.
L-Love?!
This is what love is?
Don't tell me you've never fallen in love before?!
Nope.
You're kiddin' me.
Wait.
If he actually falls for that girl,
he won't get between Ritsu and me.
All right, we'll skip jazz after school today and meet up to formulate a plan, instead.
Mikanomachi
End of
Summer Sale
Huh? At my house?
We ain't gonna go to Ri'ko's basement?
You'll be able to relax more at home, right?
I don't mind, but...
If we went to Ritsu's place, it's possible she would overhear us talking...
Here it is.
But this is Ritsu's shop...
It's a row house, so Ri'ko's place is connected.
Hey, Ma!
Bro!
Welcome home, Bro! You're back early today, huh?
Play with us!
Hold on, hold on. Where's Ma?
Ma, Bro's home!
Richie!
What're you doin'? Come on in!
Ma, this is Richie.
Oh, hello there.
I appreciate you always looking out for Sentaro.
Oh, you're too kind...
Don't be shy. Dig in, Richie.
I thought you didn't have an appetite today.
I can always eat watermelon.
Sentaro loves his watermelon...
He told me he wasn't hungry, which is pretty strange,
but I just knew watermelon would do the trick, so I iced one up.
Hmph...
Bro! Bro!
What is it, Taichi?
We found a weird bug!
A bug?
Is it a big one?
It's over here!
Bro, if you plant a watermelon seed, will it grow?
Let's plant one an' see.
Look, there!
Oh, there it is!
It flew!
Yeesh, don't cry about it!
A group date?
Yeah. The four of us will go, including Ritsu and me.
If you two started things off alone, she'd be on her guard.
Huh. I get it...
Of course, you'll be the one to invite Miss Yurika.
What's the point if you're not the one who does it?
I can't!
I just don't got it in me!
Look...
What's that sound?
Sarah.
Sarah?
My girlfriend.
Huh?
What's wrong, Sarah?
You're in a bad mood...
Cute, ain't she?
Her full name is Sarah Vaughan.
A pigeon, huh?
What's up, Sarah?
You're really agitated today.
She's probably jealous.
Since you keep talkin' about another girl...
Huh? What's wrong with me?
I'm suddenly enjoying myself?
That was so funny!
I know!
Oh...
U-Um...
I-Idiot!
Who goes up to the girl and then runs away?!
I can't do it, man!
The note! The note!
Y-Yeah...
He's coming back...
I'm sorry
for suddenly interrupting you.
Are you free this weekend?
I would like to take this opportunity to cult...
Cult...
"Cultivate."
Cultivate our friendship!
That idiot...
Richie!
She agreed! She says she'll go!
We're going to Rendezvous Rock, right?
Should I pack us a lunch?
Um, that'd be great.
Just something light like rice balls would be good.
Okay, leave it to me.
By the way, just so I know...
Which of you two is inviting me?
Oh, that would be...
This guy!
He insisted on inviting you!
Huh?
Oh.
I see.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
You said okay to a date?!
Really?!
You really are a fool!
It was going so smoothly and then you blew it!
Yeah, I dunno why I said that...
Turn back time for me, Richie!
As if I could?!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
There you are, Kaoru!
Hey, what happened to your face?
Oh, just another one of Sentaro's fights...
Let's go, Kaoru.
Wait a minute, Ritsu.
We actually have one more person joining us today...
I'm sorry!
I'm late!
Making lunch took longer than I thought it would...
You're the girl who was getting harassed back at the beach...
Th-That's right!
You remember her, huh?
Actually, today—
Hey! Get a hold of yourself!
The one with the glasses invited me...
Are you all right?! Hey!
Kaoru did?
Yes.
What the heck are you doing?! Hey!
Is it okay for a newcomer like me to intrude?
Get up already!
O-Oh, of course...
The more the merrier!
What's wrong with you today?!
Really? Good.
Oh, so it was Kaoru who asked her...
She's beautiful...
Kaoru must have a weakness for pretty faces...
What is it?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that your hat is really stylish.
Oh, this?
Even if I wore it, I would still look like a hick.
Oh, that's not true.
Pardon me...
Ritsu, when did you change your hairstyle?
Yurika did it for me.
You like?
It looks super. Really cute!
Oh, that's right.
I'm told your family owns a record shop, Ritsuko.
Yes...
Do you like jazz, Yurika?
These two practice playing jazz music together just about every day.
They play jazz?
Uh-huh. Kaoru plays piano and Sentaro is on drums.
That's really something!
I know some people who listen to jazz,
but this is my first time meeting anyone who actually plays it!
My two big brothers like jazz, so I listen too, once in a while.
My brothers frown and furrow their brows a bit while they listen,
but I prefer music that really hits you with a bang, y'know?
Y-Yeah! That's it!
I'd like to hear you play the drums.
Y-Y-You can't!
I still, uh... stink at it!
Oh, but you know you can't get better at music unless you have an audience.
Come on, let me hear you play.
This is an unexpected development.
Ow!
Oh, no! I think I got scratched by a branch.
Well, what do you know?
Looks like he's got it after all...
Say, I heard a rumor that couples who climb together
to the top of that rock will get married some day.
No girl's gonna get up that!
Richie, you up for it?
Why me?!
Oh, I'm not letting you get away with that.
I can climb that far!
Would anyone like to go with me?
Go on, already!
N-No!
I mean, the sign says it's off limits.
It's dangerous.
Oh, that's too bad.
I really wanted to see the view from up there.
You shouldn't have wolfed it down!
Those two seem to be hitting it off pretty well.
Kaoru... You can have this.
Where are you going?
I'm just going to pick some flowers!
Probably the bathroom.
Boy, this rice ball is huge...
It's my fault.
I hurt Ritsu...
In the cruelest of ways.
I made the girl who's most important to me cry.
Those shoulders look so sad, but I have no right
to try to comfort her.
Good morning, Kaoru.
Good morning.
Richie!
C-Come with me a sec!
This! This handkerchief!
Yurika gave it to me as an apology for my towel yesterday!
It smells kind of nice...
Or is it my imagination?
What the hell was that for?!
Kaoru?!
You can't pick up this handkerchief!
I just can't bear it!
If you're here for this, you can have it back.
I was in the wrong.
It's all my fault.
What are you talkin' about?! Spill it!
Shut up!
You're satisfied as long as you have this handkerchief, right?!
Go home and sniff it all you want!
That's enough.
You lookin' to start a fight?
Stop it!
Sentaro, let go of Kaoru!
This is stupid...
Don't get rough with him!
You owe Kaoru an apology!
Hmph.
I don't owe that guy nothin'.
Wait, Sentaro!
You can't forget this.
This handkerchief is important to you, isn't it?
Kaoru...
I bet Sentaro is drumming away like a madman right about now.
"Richie, you stupid idiot!"
Like that.
It's easier to make up if you do it early on.
Come with me to practice.
No...
Kaoru, before you moved here, Sentaro always practiced alone.
Shutting himself up in the basement, not letting anyone near him...
Even I didn't feel welcome down there.
But ever since you came, Kaoru, that feeling's disappeared.
I'm positive he was happy to find a friend he could play jazz with.
Kaoru, should I guess what you two were fighting about today?
You like Yurika, don't you?
So you got mad at Sentaro for showing off that handkerchief...
She is really pretty.
I wish I'd been born looking like that...
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Ritsu, you're plenty
a-attractive.
Thanks for trying to cheer me up, Kaoru.
I'm not...
I wasn't...
I wasn't trying to cheer you up.
I...
Here we are!
Well, good luck!
Hey! Ritsu! Open up!
Let me out, Ritsu!
What's the ruckus, Ritsuko?
Drastic measures.
I-I didn't come here to see you.
What?
N-Nothing...
He has the same feelings for the girl he likes.
Hey, don't just join in!
Huh?
I wasn't joinin' in anything.
He's following along again...
What the heck is this?!
Festival jazz!
Cut it out! I can't play if I'm laughing!
Next time, maybe I'll play something just for Ritsu...
And then,
maybe I'll try letting her know how I feel.
Sentaro...
I'm coming in.
Oh, don't be so stiff.
What the
hell is he doing?!
I'm sure Ritsu is thinking about him...
Meanwhile, he's...
Um, Ritsu...
There's a song that I'd like to play for you.
Actually, I wanted to practice the song a little more first...
But I feel like I have to play it for her right now...
This piece I've secretly been practicing my heart out...
Play through me, Bill Evans.
"Someday My Prince Will Come."
That's the title of the song.
So are you the prince, Kaoru?
I'm right, aren't I?
You've been practicing for Yurika, right?
And this is your dress rehearsal!
No.
This is the real performance.
You're the one that I like...
You don't have to give me an answer right away.
I just wanted to let you know that there's somebody here
who's in love with you.
Ritsu has eyes for him.
He's always on her mind.
Still, that doesn't bother me at all right now...
You taught me that it was possible to fall in love like this.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change