This is terrible!
We can't do anything about it.
It's too much for her,
but I'm sure she's prepared.
She can't handle this. I can't just stand here and watch!
It's over once you give up.
But you can change your destiny.
The destruction and grief are inevitable.
You just need to change it all.
You possess the power to do it.
Really?
Can someone like me really make a difference?
Can I avoid this outcome?
Of course.
If you want to, please make a contract
with me and become a Puella Magi!
I was dreaming...
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
The endlessly ticking time marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
I'll open this locked door bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 1     As if I met her in my dream...
Good morning, Dad!
Good morning, Madoka.
Where's Mom?
Satsuya's already in her room. Go ahead and help him.
Okay~!
Mama! Mama!
Morning! Morning!
Wakey! Mama! Mama!
Rise and shine!
Huh?
Mama wakey!
How've things been lately?
Hitomi got another love letter.
That's the second time this month.
You don't want some guy who isn't even
brave enough to confess to you in person.
How's Kazuko doing?
She's still a teacher. She talks about love in homeroom.
This week marks her third month as a teacher. That's a new record.
Well, we'll see. Now is a really crucial time for her.
Really?
If she's not serious about it, she'll
start having problems around now.
But if she doesn't have problems,
then she can probably keep at it for a year.
Finished!
Which ribbon should I wear?
Really? Isn't that too colorful?
It's perfect. Appearance is really important for girls.
Isn't that nice?
Now all of your secret fanboys will be head over heels for you.
I don't have any of those.
You need to tell yourself that you do.
That's the key to being beautiful.
Gotcha!
Here you go. Eat it up.
Yay!
Do you want another cup of coffee?
Oh, it's okay.
All right! I'll see you guys later.
Good bye!
Madoka, you need to hurry.
Huh? O-Oh yeah!
See you later!
Good bye!
Bai bai!
Good morning!
Madoka! You're slow.
Your ribbons look so cute.
Really? They aren't too colorful?
I think they look great!
And then she said that you have to confess to
someone in person. You can't use love letters.
Your mom's always been cool, Madoka.
She's such a gorgeous career woman.
I wish I could be as honest as she is.
You're worried and jealous, huh?
Wouldn't it be nice to get a love letter at least once?
What? I didn't know that Madoka wanted to
become a popular young hottie like Hitomi!
So that's why you used those ribbons
today. You want to change your image!
No way! Mom did this...
You must've learned the secret to
becoming popular from your mom!
How could you do that?! Come here, you shameless little girl!
Stop!
You're such a cutie.
But don't even try to make
yourself popular among the guys.
I'll make you my bride!
I have something important to say to every one. Please pay attention.
Do you like your fried eggs fully cooked or half-cooked?
Answer me, Nakazao!
W-Well, I-I guess either way is fine...
Exactly! Either way is fine!
We're just talking about how you want your eggs cooked.
It's totally wrong to assume this has anything
to do with whether a girl's hot or not!
Girls, please be careful not to date those
guys who insist on eating them half-cooked!
She probably got rejected.
She must've gotten rejected.
And boys! Don't become someone who tries to
find something wrong with his fried eggs!
Okay. Now I have a transfer student to introduce to everybody.
So you decided to talk about eggs first...
Please come in, Akemi.
She's cute!
Woah, she's hot!
No way! It can't be her!
Here you go. Please introduce yourself.
I am Homura Akemi. Nice to meet you all.
Well... Akemi?
Which school did you go to, Akemi?
I went to a Christian school in Tokyo.
What club were you in?
A sports club? Or the literature club?
I wasn't in any.
Your hair look so gorgeous! What shampoo do you use?
Akemi seems so mysterious.
Hey Madoka, do you know her?
It seems like she's been staring at you for a while.
Well, uh...
Sorry. I'm so nervous. I don't feel very well.
I'm going to go to the nurse's office for a bit.
Oh, let me take you there.
I'll come with you too!
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I'll try asking the person who's in charge.
Madoka Kaname.
You're the class nurse, right?
W-Well...
Can you take me to the nurse's office?
U-Uhm, excuse me.
How did you know that I'm the class nurse?
Ms. Saotome told me.
Oh, really? Well, the nurse's office is...
This way, right?
Yeah, you're right...
Hm, I wonder. Did you know where it was to begin with?
Akemi?
Just call me Homura.
Homura...
What's the matter?
Well... that's a pretty fancy name.
O-Oh, I don't mean that in a weird way...
I think it's cool.
Madoka Kaname. Do you believe that your life is precious?
Do you think that your family and friends are important to you?
W-Well... I-I... do.
I love my family and friends very
much. They're really important to me.
Are they really?
Yes! Why would I be lying?
I see.
If they are, then don't even think
about becoming someone that you're not.
If you do, you'll lose everything.
All you need to do is to be Madoka Kaname.
Please keep being the person who you've always been.
D-Did she break the prefectural record?
What? What does that mean?
So you don't understand what's going on.
She's a hottie who's good at both academics
and athletics. How can she be such a nutjob!
How badly does that damn transfer student want to be remembered!
Moe? Is this MOE?
Madoka, is this really the first time you've met Akemi?
Well, assuming I haven't lost my mind...
What do you mean? There's another you who's insane?
Uh, I kinda saw her in my dream last night.
Wow, Madoka! You also want to be remembered, don't you?
Don't say that! I'm really, really concerned about this.
Ah, I don't see any other possibilities. This is fate!
You met her after traveling beyond time and space! What destiny!
What happened in this dream of yours?
Well, I don't remember it very well. Anyway, it was a strange dream.
Maybe you really have met Akemi before.
Even though you may not remember it any more,
you still have an impression of her deep in your heart.
Maybe that's why she appeared in your dream.
Don't you feel that's too good to be true? Total coincidence.
Maybe you're right.
Oh, look at the time.
Excuse me, I have to leave now.
Do you have piano lessons today? Or Japanese dance class?
I need to study tea.
We'll be tested soon. I don't know
how long I'll be able to study there.
It must be nice to be born into a middle-class family.
We should leave, too.
Madoka, can we go to the CD store on our way home?
Okay. You wanna get Kamijo again, huh?
Well, probably.
See you!
Bye!
Help.
Help, Madoka!
Help me!
Who? Who is that?
Renovation in Process
Due to renovation, this floor is closed.
Help!
Where are you?
Who are you?
Help!
Was it you?
Help...
Homura?
Leave him alone.
B-But, he's injured.
N-No way! Don't be mean to him!
This is none of your business.
But he asked me for help!
I heard him! He wants me to help!
Really?
Madoka, this way!
Sayaka!
What timing...
What on earth is she doing!
Is she dressed up in a costume trying to kill someone?
By the way, what's in your arms?
That's not a doll, right? Is it an animal?
I don't know... I don't know, but I have to help him!
What? Where's the emergency exit? Where are we?
What's going on in here? The halls are changing dramatically!
I've had enough! What's going on?!
Oh, there's something there!
This isn't real, is it?
Madoka, I'm having a nightmare, right?!
What?!
This is...?
That was really dangerous, but you're safe now.
Wow, you saved Kyube?
Thank you. He's an important friend of mine.
I heard him. He spoke right into my mind.
I see.
Based on your uniforms, I assume you two are from Mitakihara.
Are you 2nd years?
Who are you...?
Right. I need to introduce myself first.
But, before that...
Let me take care of something.
C-Cool!
I-It's back to normal!
The witch has already fled. If you want to kill
her, please go after her as soon as possible.
I won't get in your way this time.
I need to deal with someone else.
You don't seem to understand, huh? What I
really mean is I won't kill you this time.
You don't want to get into trouble if you don't need to, right?
Thank you, Mami. You saved me!
You should thank these two girls here. I was just passing by.
Thank you very much! My name is Kyube!
So you were asking me for help?
You're right, Madoka Kadome. And Sayaka Miki too.
Why do you know our names?
There's something I want you to do for me.
S-Something?
I want you to make contracts with me and become Puella Magi!
Artist hanokage
I can make anything you wish come true.
Huh? Really?
My wish...
It can be anything.
I can make any miracle come true!
Episode 2     That's really nice of you
That's really nice of you.