Tina!
What's over there?
Is that ship...
my father's?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Hey!
Oh, Kirara!
Decorating the Christmas trees?
Yeah, take a look!
Whoah, that's big!
Well, so is our tree!
Decorating this fir tree is an annual tradition.
Where might you be off to?
The library.
I wanted to study some English and French for next year.
Blooming with motivation, huh?
Dreamy Shore Library
Easy English
Got it!
Hm?
Boo!
Kirara!
Sorry, my B.
You looked super into it, so...
Anyway, whatcha reading?
I was just looking for books
that might pique my interest.
So... anyway, I have to go. Bye!
By Kitakaze Asuka
Doctor of the Sea
Doctor of the Sea?
By Kitakaze Asuka
Doctor of the Sea
Isn't she the woman from before?
Minamin...
Welling Emotions!
Minami's True Feelings!
Oh, Minam—
Minami?
Haruka! How is the tree decoration coming along?
Huh? Oh, fine.
If you need anything, feel free to ask.
I'll come help once my student council business is finished.
Um, Minami!
Yes?
Are you doing all right?
Why wouldn't I?
Just... a feeling.
Oh, it's nothing.
Bye.
Miss Kaidou.
What is it, Mrs. Zama?
You haven't turned in your career guidance survey.
My apologies. It slipped my mind.
Hmm, a rare occurrence for you.
Be sure to turn it in soon.
I will.
Um...
Yes?
Why did you choose to become a teacher?
Huh?
Was it always your dream to teach?
No, my dream in elementary school...
was to be an idol!
Wha?
In middle school, a police officer!
And in high school, a cartoonist!
How... unexpected.
I could never decide on which calling to pursue until I settled on my dream of educating.
Indecision isn't a bad thing.
Just be sure to think it all through.
All right...
It's about time for the Academy's annual Christmas event.
Plan for Construction of Ichijou Ranko Graduation Statue
Rejected
Finished
Plan for Construction of Ichijou Ranko Graduation Statue
Rejected
Christmas Party Plans
The boy's dorm is a bit behind schedule.
It's the end of the semester, so everyone's busy.
Sure it's not because your dorm's tree is huge?
Minamin!
It's an emergency!
Kirara, what happened?
It's serious! You gotta come!
W-Wait!
How far are we going?
Whew, it's cold!
The beach is freezing in winter, huh?
Kirara, over here!
What?
Thanks for watching the stuff!
Gee, thanks for calling us out on zero notice to make me freeze my feathers off!
C'mon, Bro, a little play will warm you right back up!
So, what's this emergency?
No need to rush.
Since it's cold out...
Ta-dah! I made some piping hot tea!
C'mon, have a seat!
So this emergency of yours was made up?
What are you thinking?
I didn't make anything up.
You being worried is totally an emergency!
Here.
Doctor of the Sea
By Kitakaze Asuka
I checked it out.
I can check out my own books.
You know you want it.
Quit sneaking around and just read it!
This is none of your concern!
What're you being stubborn for?
I could ask the same of you!
Geez, I didn't mean to start a fight...
Huh?
Having you girls support me helped me a ton,
so I wanted to return the favor
if any of you were having trouble.
But I'm not used to this sort of thing,
so I didn't really know what to do.
Sorry, Minamin.
Kirara...
But hey, we're already here,
so how about a cup?
Slow doooooown!
Lately... I've been having a dream.
What kind?
A dream... of the sea.
I'm called into the ocean and welcomed by its inhabitants.
It's so joyful and uplifting that I want to learn what lies next in this deep blue sea...
But I can never go any further.
Why?
Because...
Do you want to go?
Good question.
I'm... not certain myself.
A second despicable rainbow!
Dyspear's heart much be in oh so much torment!
And if I don't hatch a plan soon, so will I!
I'm naught but to take a stand!
Haruka, what's wrong?
Well, I think Minami might be feeling kind of blue.
I've noticed it a few times before, but it's more common now...
Maybe she's worried about something?
That's why I tried asking her, but she said it was nothing...
It was nothing?
Towa?
Minami told me once before...
I've used those words quite often, myself.
I just didn't want to worry others, after all.
I knew it!
If I want to see tomorrow,
there's naught but to defeat them today!
You there!
What are you doing here?
Silence! If you value your life, then stand aside!
Goodness, what a potty mouth!
It's simply repulsive!
You have some explaining to do.
Come to the guidance office.
Silence!
The only guidance I need is naught but my own!
Now, show me your dream!
I want to nurture the dreams of my students!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Sorry about this.
Guess I wasn't much help.
No, I'm glad you asked.
I hope you find your answer.
That's the issue here, right?
It is...
Dyspairvil!
Over there!
There you are.
Isn't that...
Mrs. Zama?!
Princess Precures,
you'll be guided naught but to your doom!
We can guide ourselves, creep!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Mermaid?
Dyspairvil.
Dyspair!
Dyspairvil!
Flora! Scarlet!
Sorry for the wait!
Now let us fight together!
Dyspair... vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
My power!
Viiiil!
Mermaid!
Why? Where has my power gone?
What's wrong?
She's not her usual self!
What's going on?!
I knew it...
Oh, seems you've lost your touch.
Dyspairvil, aim for Cure Mermaid!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Vil! Vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspairviiiiil!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Are you okay?
Yes...
I'm sorry.
I know...
it must be because I'm wavering in my dream.
It's weakened my power of dreams as a Precure!
So she was worried...
We all have days when we're not sure where to go.
You're not alone, Mermaid.
Twinkle...
Dyspairvil!
Lily!
Dance, O lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Viiil!
Flora...
Mermaid!
Y-Yes?
Why wouldn't you talk to us if you're going through a crisis?
Aren't we supposed to be friends?!
I'm sorry.
It's not easy to say this...
but I've... found a new dream.
My concern has been over which one I should pursue.
You can't turn your back on this new dream, can you?
Well, what's the problem with that?
What?
There's nothing wrong with changing your dream.
Dyspairvil!
Mermaid,
I'd like to hear your new dream as well.
Scarlet...
The way I see it,
it doesn't matter what you should pursue.
It's what you want to pursue that counts!
Dyspairvil!
What I... want to pursue?
Hmph! You're naught but to aim for Cure Mermaid!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Viiiil!
What?!
Mermaid!
The truth is, I knew all along...
that this desire was welling up within my heart of hearts.
Yet I tried to turn away from it.
Because my childhood dream...
was just that important.
But now...
Dyspaiiiirviiiil!
Dyspairviiiiil!
I'll hesitate no more!
I'll walk the path I believe in!
Coral!
Rage, O coral!
Precure!
Coral Maelstrom!
Dyspair... viiiil!
Guess you're doing fine.
I am, thank you!
Let's finish this!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Why? Why can't I win?!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Thank you so much, Mrs. Zama.
Is that...
the Castle of the Sea?
A vet?
Yes.
Meeting Asuka made me think about it.
I want to understand the sea.
I want to connect with the sea and its denizens directly.
So I want to be a doctor for sea animals!
It's perfect for you, Minami!
Perhaps you could contact Asuka for some advice?
Where is she right now?
In America! At an aquarium in Florida.
Actually...
I happened upon Asuka's blog
and I've been reading it every day.
Minamin, you sure get started quick!
Minami, I wish you luck!
We'll be rooting for your dream to come true!
Thank you!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
My parents would be disheartened to hear about my dream.
Minami?
I can't live up to their hopes...
Hey now!
We're having a Christmas party, so lighten up!
Now, Minami, take the mic!
Everyone, listen to our song!
What?
And a one!
Merry Christmas!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Surging Confession!
Minami's Deep Blue Dream!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Aichi Prefecture - Mizuki (Age 4)
Hyougo Prefecture - Hitomi (Age 5)