Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you "ex-Phantom"?
That's all in the past, though.
Right now...
...I'm Phantom.
That Scythe dude calls me Drei.
Ein, Zwei, Drei. That's enough explanation, right?
To greet me with a phrase such as "Nice to meet you."...
...Phantom must have become pretty charming.
I can kill whenever I want to.
But...
...that wouldn't be interesting, right?
I tracked you down, cornered you, and will now finally kill you.
This is all I've been living for over the past two years.
Those Inferno fuckwits have been feeding me well.
So come on, provide me with some entertainment.
You two were frightened...
...and turned tail.
Will that give you satisfaction?
Better believe it.
It was too cool to see how startled Reiji was when he saw me.
He was pale, as if he'd seen a ghost.
Next up is... oh, yeah...
I could kill you directly in front of Reiji, how's that?
What face would he make then?
No chance.
Huh?
You met me first...
...so you will be killed here...
...by me.
Oh, you came prepared.
You put your life on the line to protect Reiji?
How lovable...
The one who's lovable...
...is you.
What?
You couldn't forget how Reiji left you, right?
You want him mourning and distressed.
But you see, he is no longer...
...who he used to be.
He has thrown away his past and lives only for the moment.
Your point?
You're no more than a ghost from the past.
If you stand in our way,
Reiji...
...will kill you.
You talk like you know him.
You just have no idea...
...of his strength.
The lead actor is here.
Elen. Cal.
There's no reason for you two to fight each other.
So he says.
Ein, it seems you're a bad judge of character.
Not yet.
Not all the actors and actresses have assembled yet.
Get us away.
Yes, sir.
Shoot me.
Reiji.
Stop it, Cal.
You left me for dead once already.
Who cares if you do it a second time?
Cal.
Shoot me!
But... I'll shoot this woman.
I'll take her along to hell.
Stop it you idiot.
Dammit, like I feared.
What are you doing acting ahead?
Mind your own business.
This is Japan you retard.
You can't just take out a gun in broad daylight.
Who cares...
Oh, really? Then pull the trigger, Phantom.
But once you do, I'll kill you and the other two.
Your call, Phantom.
Put your gun away and pull back.
I'll cover you.
Bang!
Dang, what a boring ending.
Cal?
That's your successor, Zwei.
I happen to be her supporter.
Thanks to that each day is hell.
I owe you.
Damn right you do.
Anyway, playing student is over.
The cover of your hideout is blown, you better move someplace else.
Sorry, but from now on...
...I won't have the confidence to stop that crazy bitch again.
Ok, we'll get moving right away.
Lizzie!
I owe you...
Just stay alive, Zwei.
For Clau's sake, too.
Were you planning on shooting her?
What about you?
I...
Between me and her,
which one would you choose if it meant your life?
That choice...
There's no time.
I'll set up the escape route.
All the while, there's Drei...
Let's make sure she's held up by Inferno.
It's time to deal the cards.
Hurry up!
Or we'll leave you behind.
Ah, sorry.
Come in.
Excuse me.
You have a call, brother.
Who is it?
Well...
He said he's "Claudia's trusted friend".
Shiga speaking.
It's been two years, Shiga Toru.
Who is this?
Like I said...
Claudia McCunnen's trusted friend? The kid that was always beside her?
The assassin...
...Phantom?
That's right.
It seems you're being chased by Inferno.
What are you up to now?
Does Shinokura High School ring a bell?
Shinokura?
That's right, the daughter of Godou Kaiten, the Godou clan's boss,
Fujieda Mio, goes to school there.
Hey, do you understand what you're saying?
There are some things you just shouldn't touch, you bastard.
Don't worry.
Why not go see a movie with me
on Saturday, the day after tomorrow?
\ Sanae
If you stay out of our way, we will leave her alone.
If you stay out of our way, that is...
What do you mean?
Right now an assassin of Inferno is tailing us.
It's your job to stop her, Shiga Toru.
Put a leash on Inferno in Japan with your authority.
\ Sanae
I'm inviting Reiji-kun along!
Don't fuck with me!
It's your call whether to do it or not.
Okay
I'm coming.
She has nothing to do with this.
Give it your best shot.
You've become an actor, haven't you?
I'm not as good as you, though.
If this runs smoothly, it should buy us some time.
Shiga is smart.
Don't worry, he will follow the plan.
And if he doesn't?
When that happens we have to think of something else.
I don't plan to put Mio in danger.
About Drei...
Are you happy she's alive?
Yeah.
I thought she died that day.
It was my fault I got the innocent Cal involved.
I let her die.
But...
She survived.
I'm heading north at dawn tomorrow.
I'll negotiate with a smuggler who has his freighter docked there.
Alone?
Yeah.
You stay with Mio.
Let's go home.
Gosh, it's gotten late, I'll prepare dinner right away.
Hey, Phantom!
There's a call from the big shots.
Don't fuck with me!
Judging from her reaction she knows already.
Godou Clan's Godfather...
Godou Kaiten's illegitimate child.
It seems they weren't playing students on a whim.
I don't care about the Japanese yakuza.
Cool your head, Phantom.
The Godou clan is a branch of Inferno.
Exactly.
All movement is restricted until Godou's princess is secured.
Zwei is making a fool of us.
We will stop here.
Wait for the next opportunity.
Asshole.
Guard a high-school girl?
Yes.
Who is it?
You don't need to know.
However, to me and to this clan, she's someone precious.
Is there a need to deploy us?
Yeah.
Protect her with your life!
Got that?
Yes, sir!
Do you hate him that much?
You bet.
Why do think I worked as Inferno's dog until now?
It was to hunt him down and kill him.
That's the only reason.
To be honest, I'm relieved.
Huh?
I can't stand to see you and Zwei fighting each other.
Cal.
You're looking down on me, do you think I'd lose?
That's not it.
It's true he deceived us all two years ago and fled.
Me as well.
He's a con man.
But you know, you alone Zwei always protected.
He tricked me the whole time.
Without knowing anything he piled lie on lie.
He was afraid,
afraid of the moment I wouldn't believe his lies any longer.
He only lied to protect you.
Protect?
The only one he wanted to protect was himself.
In the end he left me,
and ran away with a woman.
Even so, there was no need for you to be an assassin.
You didn't become one because you wanted to, right?
I wanted to be one.
Right now I'm the dreaded and venerable Phantom.
Crooks and gangsters in town tremble with fear when they hear my name.
Isn't this awesome?
I can kick, punch or kill those punks.
Is there any way of life better than this?
He was afraid of me.
He realized...
...that I would get too strong for him.
The debt for lying to me and using me...
I will collect it.
Cal...
You...
...are like fireworks burning out.
Elen is absent today, eh?
Yeah, she got a fever last night.
I'm sure it's just a cold.
You should have told me sooner.
I'll go warm her up.
Hey.
As usual you two dimwits are having a stupid conversation.
Shuddup.
By the way, we'll go see a movie today. You guys should tag along.
Are you inviting us?
Mio is coming too.
Sorry, I'll pass. I have important business today.
Is it a date?
Oh, good call.
Ok, we've been ditched.
Seems like it.
That Sanae, what was that with "everyone going to see a movie"?
She's so roundabout.
Yeah.
I hope Elen recovers from her cold soon.
How about we go see a movie?
Even if I go home, I'd just disturb Elen's sleep.
Okay.
What a convenient situation.
If I stay with her...
...I can prompt Shiga to move.
I ran around like a child.
Embarrassing.
The movie was good, wasn't it?
We should thank Sanae.
Reiji-san,
you're a mysterious person.
Eh?
How can I put it... the way you see things...
...is different from normal people.
What do you mean?
For us it's just something normal and a part of our daily lives.
But you treasure it deeply.
So if I watch you, I can love the present.
I never feel bored or sick of it.
Everything has meaning.
Everyone seems to have forgotten that.
Was I disturbing?
Reiji-san?
I see, so she's Fujieda Mio?
Ein, me and Godou's princess.
You sure use a lot of women.
You don't have any intention of harming her, am I right?
Cal.
Alright, the game starts.
Let's find out who's the true Phantom.
You're Phantom, Cal.
I'm simply a student right now.
Don't make me laugh, Zwei.
You didn't lose your balls, did you?
If you want my head, you can have it.
Why were you running away until now?
Because you don't want to die?
Or simply to live on?
Wasn't it just that?
If my life ends by your hands, that would be my punishment.
I don't mind being killed, I never did.
There is one condition, though.
In exchange for my life,
I want you to spare Elen-... Ein's life.
You want to trade your life for hers?
She doesn't oppose Scythe or Inferno any more.
That's why...
You want to protect her with your life.
You, a coward who ran away and left me behind, has someone so dear to you...
That's not true, Cal, back then I...
I'll kill you, just as you wish.
However, you'll feel much more pain...
...and suffering...
...before I do that.
Reiji-san...
If you can't shoot,
you're a real coward.
It's only natural for you to die here.
Right?