What's the rank of Rider's Noble Phantasm?
It's the same as Gilgamesh's Gate of Babylon.
In other words, too powerful to be given a rank.
Things ended exactly as we'd planned.
If we'd gone against Rider without knowing about his Noble Phantasm, we wouldn't have been able to defend against it.
This begins the second stage.
We will use the information Assassin gathered and mobilize Archer to defeat our enemies.
A means to defeat Rider should reveal itself in the process.
Yes.
As a Master, your work is done.
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
I believe last night's attack involved all the Assassins.
Understood.
By the way, Maiya.
Where are we with our new atelier?
Tomorrow morning, I will take Saber and Madam there.
I see. Thank you.
No problem.
Goodbye, then.
No activity at the Tohsaka residence.
Tokiomi has been cooping himself up
since Assassin's attack on the first day.
The silence is almost unsettling.
Miyama
The Matou Master appears undefended, an easy target.
But...
Berserker should probably be left alive due to his strange special ability, if only to distract Archer and Tohsaka.
Miyama
New Town, East
Lord El-Melloi should be out of the running...
But Lancer still remains.
I'll need to discover his new Master's identity as soon as possible.
Fuyuki City Serial Kidnappings and Murders:
No Progress in Investigations
Caster's location remains unknown.
But last night, several children vanished from the city again.
They'll likely continue their atrocities without reserve.
Rider always travels with his Master in his flying Noble Phantasm.
Tracking him is difficult.
However largehearted he may seem, he is an extremely dangerous foe.
I'm also concerned with the "Ionian Hetairoi" Noble Phantasm that Maiya reported.
But, more importantly...
Can we assume that Assassin has been completely eliminated this time?
In that case, their Master...
If his plan was to work with Tohsaka
and use Assassin to spy on the others,
then he wouldn't have taken a single step out of Fuyuki Church.
But that isn't what happened.
His ambush at the Fuyuki Hyatt...
His attack in the Einzbern forest...
Both of those are inexplicable.
However, it all makes sense if he was after me from the start.
But why?
Why pursue me?
Two days ago, he should've had no way of knowing that I'm Saber's Master.
Kotomine Kirei, who are you?
You seem in an excellent mood today, Archer.
I still see no worth in the Grail.
But even if it's trash, that's fine.
I've found another form of entertainment.
In this age and world you've mocked
for being ugly and full of fakes?
That hasn't changed.
However, I am now curious to see this Holy Grail War to the end.
I am fond of prideful individuals.
Individuals who harbor grand ambitions, not knowing they aren't fit for the task.
Simply observing such people gives me great enjoyment.
There are two kinds of pride.
One where you aren't fit for the task,
and one where your desires are too grand.
The former is commonplace stupidity...
...but the latter is rare and difficult to come by.
But they're identical in that they're both stupid, no?
Isn't rare stupidity far more precious than commonplace wisdom?
Those who have renounced their humanity for the
superhuman wishes they harbor despite being born human...
I never grow weary of watching their grief and despair.
Kirei, you seem to be in a good mood yourself, for once.
I am simply relieved.
I've finally been freed from an unpleasant burden.
What happens to the Command Spells once they disappear?
In theory, they return to the Grail.
The Holy Grail retakes the Command Spells from a Master who has lost his Servant and is thus out of the war.
And if a Servant loses its Master, the Grail will take those
unused Spells and redistribute them to a newly chosen Master.
The Command Spells remain in this world until they are used.
Any that remain at the end are given to the judge.
So, depending on what happens from
now on, a new Master may yet appear?
Yes.
However, those that the Grail would
deem eligible are few in number.
Thus, when a new Master is sought, the Grail tends to select those it has previously found suitable.
What's wrong?
Continue, Kirei.
That's the reason the Holy Church protects those who've dropped out of battle.
Should an empty place open among the remaining Masters,
there is a high probability that an ex-Master will receive the unused Command Spells.
This is why Grail War participants try to kill
enemy Masters rather than simply disable them.
From that theory, Kirei, is there not a good chance that you will receive Command Spells yet again?
Impossible.
If the Holy Grail chose me to support the Tohsaka camp like Tokiomi suggested, then I have fulfilled my duty.
Tokiomi has already prepared a winning strategy for the remaining Masters and their Servants.
There's nothing more for me to do.
If you ask me, Tokiomi's hypotheses have been dubious from the start.
He never struck me as worthy enough to
receive that much backing from the Grail.
I'm surprised you have such harsh words to say about your own Master.
Kirei, you seem to be sorely mistaken as to who serves whom in my relationship with Tokiomi.
He pays me every due respect as my subject and supplies me with mana as an offering.
I answered his summons precisely because those were the terms of our pact.
What do you make of the Command Spells, then?
I don't like them.
However, if a subject wishes to perform his duties better,
he must be willing to listen to criticism from time to time.
More importantly, Kirei.
You mentioned that the Assassins have fulfilled all their duties.
But what of the matter we discussed?
Your interest in learning the motives of each Master in seeking the Grail?
Yes, that investigation is more or less completed.
I should've had Assassin report his findings in person last night.
That would've saved me the trouble of-
No, this is just fine.
I'm not interested in what that shadow has to say.
Kirei, this report is meaningless unless it comes from your lips.
How does it feel to drive a car, Saber?
It is indeed a splendid thing to steer.
I can't help but think what would've
happened if these had existed in my time.
Irisviel, are you sure it's all right that I drive this vehicle?
You seemed to enjoy the act of driving.
It's fine.
I'm happy if you are too.
I have to say, the skills of a Servant are amazing.
This is your first time touching this machine, yet here you are, driving it perfectly.
I find the sensation a little strange myself,
but it's like I'm employing skills that I was taught long ago.
Rather than understanding it intellectually,
my body instinctively knows what to do next.
Still, is this a wise idea?
The estate to be our new base of operations lies right in the center of the battlefield.
No need to worry about that.
Fighting in secret is the great rule of the Grail War.
The Tohsakas and the Matous boldly fortify their bases within the city.
It's the Einzberns who are unusual for
building that castle in such a distant area.
Since its location isn't known to the others,
the base that Kiritsugu prepared for us might be
more advantageous than the castle we've been using.
This is yet another strange building.
From now on, this will be your base of operations.
Ah, if you could hand those to Saber.
Understood, Irisviel.
Maiya, what is this key?
It looks quite different from the others.
It's the key to the storehouse in the yard.
It's old, but I've personally confirmed that it's solidly built.
No preparations were made, so it might be somewhat lacking as a residence.
That's fine.
I have no complaints as long as it shelters us from the rain and wind.
Well then, Saber.
Let's explore our new home!
Okay.
I think this is supposed to be like one of Japan's haunted houses.
I'm sure all the hallways have wooden floors, while the rooms
are floored with woven grass and have partitions made of paper!
I did say once that I wanted to see a Japanese mansion.
Maybe Kiritsugu remembered!
Was it not what you expected?
No, I enjoyed touring it.
But this isn't really an ideal base for a Mage.
The magical fields are well-laid, but to establish an atelier here...
The design is too open to the outside, so mana will be readily lost.
I would've preferred a room walled off with stone or clay.
This is ideal!
It's a little small, but I can craft my spells here just as well as back at the castle.
Simply inscribing a magic circle here
should be enough to make this place mine.
Let's get started.
Will you please help me, Saber?
We'll draw a magic circle there, six feet in diameter.
Okay.
I'll need your help once we start placing the mercury.
I'll tell you how to distribute it, so don't worry.
Saber, can you bring me the ingredients we left in the trunk?
Irisviel, I'd like to ask you something.
It seems that you've been careful not to touch anything today.
Am I imagining things?
Driving the car, holding the keys...
I wouldn't have worried about small matters like that.
But you aren't even performing your own magic.
It's important that you tell me in advance if you aren't feeling well.
It's my duty to protect you when necessary.
That's why I need to know.
I'm sorry.
You're right. This isn't something I should hide from you.
Hold out your hand.
Saber, I'm going to squeeze your hand with all my strength.
Ready?
Yes, go ahead...
Irisviel?
I'm not playing around.
This is all the strength I can muster.
Tugging your fingers is the most I can do.
Holding them or gripping them is beyond me.
Getting dressed this morning was really tough, too!
Wh-What could be wrong?
Are you hurt?
I'm not feeling very well, so I've severed my sense of touch.
Shutting down just one of the five senses
lets me suppress the spirituality quite a bit,
so that it won't interfere with anything else that I do.
I guess the ability to do such things is an advantage of being a homunculus.
It can't be that simple!
What exactly is wrong with your body, anyway?
Do you require treatment?
You may have forgotten, but I'm not a normal human.
When I'm ill, a doctor cannot treat me.
Well, I guess you can say the problem
stems from defects in my construction.
Don't worry about it.
Though, it does mean I'll need you
to help me with all kinds of things.
I'll need you to drive my car like you did today and help me with my magical rituals.
I'm sorry.
But I'll be relying on you, my knight.
Absolutely.
And I apologize for prying. Please forgive me.
It's fine, don't worry.
Well, let's quickly get that circle crafted.
My condition should improve a little if I rest in a
magic circle properly connected to local ley lines.
Understood.
I'll bring the ingredients in.
Neither Lancer's Master nor Rider's Master
have wishes they'd like the Holy Grail to grant.
They simply seek victory to bring them glory as Magi.
As for Caster's Master, he doesn't
even understand what the Grail is.
He's taking part in the Grail War just so he can continue killing people for fun.
As for Berserker's Master, he seeks the rather naive act of atonement.
Because he had once severed all ties with the Matou family,
the younger Tohsaka daughter was taken in
to be groomed as the next Matou family head.
Yet, he is now demanding that the girl be set free.
He has been given the task of winning the Holy Grail to secure his end of the bargain.
In addition, he appears to have some sort of past relationship with Tokiomi's wife.
In a sense, his motives are probably the most
vulgar and banal among the five competing Masters.
What is it?
Continue, Kirei.
Saber's Master...
It appears he was merely hired to achieve the Einzberns'
long-held, delusional dream of manifesting the Holy Grail.
How very disappointing.
He's just another mongrel.
They're all a bunch of mediocrities with utterly uninteresting reasons for seeking my treasure.
That's all you have to say after
making me go through all that trouble?
Think of all the effort I wasted.
Effort you wasted?
What are you talking about, Kirei?
The hard work of you and the Assassins has paid off splendidly.
Are you mocking me, King of Heroes?
You don't understand?
I can't blame you.
You're a man who doesn't even know what he finds pleasurable.
A soul naturally seeks pleasure, consciously or not.
That inner desire is expressed through one's interests and concerns.
In other words, Kirei, having you talk about what you make of
the things you've seen and heard already has plenty of meaning.
What you speak of at greatest length is what interests you the most.
First, let us rule out the man you deliberately avoided talking about.
An interest you're aware of is nothing but obsession.
So, which of the remaining four did you speak of most passionately?
Berserker's Master.
Kariya, wasn't it?
Kirei, you spoke of him in great detail.
The circumstances surrounding him are complicated.
He simply required additional explanation.
Wrong.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin to investigate to such a
degree that you could understand those "complicated circumstances".
And this was all due to your unconscious interest.
I admit I made a judgmental error.
It's true that Matou Kariya poses no threat in the long term, and so was not worth the attention.
My overestimation of his abilities has invited your pointless prying into me.
That's your response?
Then imagine for me a scenario in which Berserker and his Master survive until the very end by chance and fortune.
Can you picture what would happen then?
Hey, Kirei.
Isn't it about time you realized the
true meaning of what I've been asking?
Tell me, Archer.
What is the point of picturing Matou Kariya's victory?
No point.
None at all.
Come on now, don't be so mad.
Think about it.
The fact that Kotomine Kirei never recognized the pointlessness in such speculation.
Don't you think there's clear, unshakable meaning to it?
Explain it to me, Archer.
If you'd been given the same question regarding another Master,
you would've immediately realized its
pointlessness and rejected it as a waste of time.
But that was not how it went with Kariya.
You abandoned your usual sharp wits and wasted your time in pointless thought.
You forgot it was pointless.
You didn't mind the effort was wasted.
In other words, you clearly enjoyed it.
Celebrate, Kirei.
You've understood what entertainment is at last.
Entertainment?
Pleasure, in other words?
Exactly.
There is nothing in Matou Kariya's fate that could bring a man pleasure.
His life is nothing but suffering and tragedy.
For him, a quick death would be a blessing.
Kirei, why must you see pleasure in such a narrow sense?
Where is the contradiction in treating
suffering and tragedy as forms of pleasure?
Pleasure doesn't just come in one form.
You're confused because you don't understand that.
This isn't something that can be forgiven!
King of Heroes, an inhuman demon such as yourself
might find the suffering of others sweet to the taste.
But that is the soul of a sinner!
An evil that must be punished!
This is all the more true in the path of faith that I follow!
So that's why you define pleasure itself to be a sin.
It's incredible how far you've managed to warp it.
You're an unbelievably interesting man.
This pain...
Ooh.
Just as I'd thought.
But faster than I'd expected.
Impossible...
No Servant has yet been released from their contract.
Why has a new Master been chosen?
It looks like the Holy Grail expects
great things from Kotomine Kirei.
Kirei, you should attend once again to the Grail's summons.
Without a doubt, you have a reason to seek this wish-granting device.
I have a reason to seek the Grail?
If it really is an omnipotent wish-granting device,
then it can give shape to the wish even you
don't understand in the depths of your heart.
So you're saying I should use the wish-granting device as a means to infer my wish, since I don't know what it is.
But that can only happen after I've destroyed six other wishes.
If I seek the Grail for my own desire...
...it'll mean becoming my teacher's enemy.
Then you'd better find yourself a strong Servant if you're going to fight me.
But that's only if you manage to steal a Servant currently bound by contract to another Master in the first place.
In that case...
No, I won't say it.
Everything from here onwards is up to you.
Do as you desire.
That is the true meaning of entertainment.
Entertainment leads to pleasure...
And pleasure will lead you to happiness.
Your path is now clear, Kirei.
So clear that there's no need to hesitate.
Episode 12
The Grail's Invitation
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
I shall be the first to strike!
This would be the perfect opportunity to defeat him.
Let's finish this.
I'm sure the world is filled with God's love.
Now let us once again raise the flag of salvation!
Next Episode
The Forbidden Banquet