To all of our freshmen, congratulations on your admittance.
Here at Ounan Middle School we value our students' stances,
and their individuality even more so.
At the same time, to live in society,
you will learn to be cooperative and disciplined.
I would encourage you to fulfil your responsibilities...
Um... are you feeling all right?
Eh?
Ah, thanks. I'm fine.
Next, we will hear from the Freshman representative:
Hayama Nayu-san.
Adult...?
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
The Girl with the Adult Panties!
Congratulations on Admittance
I'm starting to get nervous.
Even Haruka's getting nervous?
What about you, Yako-chan? Aren't you nervous?
Not particularly.
Well, I don't quite know how I'm feeling yet.
It's the girl with the adult panties!
Eh? What's that?
You didn't hear, Yako?
That girl...
...Hayama Nayu.
As usual, she was wearing some amazing  panties, wasn't she.
She wears them for work, right?
It seems like she was getting paid to go on dates.
Which would mean that since she was an elementary school student,
she's been doing vile things?!
I can't see a girl like that doing such things, though.
Actually, she's got enough money,
but she was forced to do dirty things!
But if she gave the greeting to the freshmen,
it means she got good grades from somewhere, right?
It's definitely not a lie!
That girl's been in schoolgirl prostitution.
What!?
So...
The crotch area needs to be a little bigger or...
...it'll wedge into my delicate parts...
Eh? Where does it wedge into?
Where?
Come on, quickly now.
C...
Cr-
The crotch!
No need for such a loud voice, I can hear you fine.
Ah! Keigo-san!
Hey.
Your freshman greeting was great.
You didn't go home?
Here you go.
It's definitely not a lie!
That girl's been in schoolgirl prostitution.
I can't hear 'em.
Basically,
"Here's the underwear from when you stayed over."
"Before you return them, wash them."
Punishment, perhaps.
Keigo-san, see you later!
A friendly young man,
who she was discussing her crotch with,
and a bra and panties that she can't stop wearing.
This is...
A pro without limits!
I'm not sure.
We have no choice but to make sure!
Mizuno-sensei, see you.
Sensei, see you at our next club meeting!
Okay then, goodbye!
Don't be late!
You too, Sensei.
I won't!
With the arrival of the new freshmen,
it's got quite lively, hasn't it.
Takato-sensei.
Yes, I've got to do my best and keep this up!
Mizuno-sensei's share of liveliness
comes from the size of that suit, eh?
Is it really too tight?
I wonder if I ate too much over spring break...
You didn't ride your bike in these clothes, did you?
You think I shouldn't?
She doesn't leave a lot to the imagination.
Goodbye!
Now then, I've got to get back to my lively spirit!
Be careful, okay?
...in more ways than one.
Mizuno-sensei's bu-
The target hasn't noticed that she's being tailed.
I'm sure they'll rendezvous around here.
You think so?
She's moving faster...
Didn't she just come to buy underwear?
She sure is looking at a lot of clothing.
Surely it's to show to the guy.
Why does she look so happy browsing underwear?
Whenever I put on underwear,
it feels like I get a lot of lewd stares.
Why does she enjoy underwear so much?
When we were kids,
boys and girls wore the same kind of underwear.
When we entered middle school,
it's not like we suddenly became adults.
Our body's changing every day but our hearts can't keep up.
I can't even talk to my mother about wearing this new underwear.
Is there a kind-hearted person who could teach me about it?
Even so,
that's a nice smile.
Aren't you in my class?
A coincidence, coincidence!
It's not like we'll be wearing that!
They've already become friends!
Or maybe they came from the same elementary school.
It'd be nice if I could make a lot of friends, too.
Is there anyone who could take care of this?
I don't want to look incompetent here...
Perhaps it would be best to say something...!
Then, your recommendations.
Yes! I believe that among the girls,
Hayama Nayu-san will be fine!
Right? She's smart.
I agree!
Hayama-san had the best entrance exam score,
she would fit the job, I think.
I guess so.
Well then, those in favour, raise your hand please.
What, wait! Hayama as...!
Something didn't feel right about that, Yako-chan.
About what?
Our homeroom just now.
About the class rep?
It was essentially forced upon her!
Oh. But, look at it another way.
She's been in schoolgirl prostitution.
If that rumour's true,
then they're not going to stop with just condemning her.
With your enormous breasts, you'd definitely be scouted by them.
No way! You're thinking too much-
Hayama-san!
Um... Aren't you two...
Shiraishi-san and Jingouji-san?
Y-Yeah.
What a nice smell!
Today's sweet-and-sour pork?
It's about time for school lunch...
What's that you're carrying?
Oh this?
These are the materials for next lesson...
Must be a burden, huh?
To be forced into the position of class rep.
Ah, no, I'm doing fine.
Doing fine...
Now, Haruka! Run for it!
Shiraishi-san's chest was...
...as I thought...
What was that just now?
You haven't realised?!
That girl was estimating your value!
What?
She was evaluating your chest!
Huh...
Which means, she's scouting you for her schoolgirl prostitution!
You'll earn your income with those giant breasts!
W-Why?!
That's a rumour, a rumour!
That's true, but...
For now, let's keep our distance from that girl.
Shiraishi-san?
Shiraishi-san!
Um...
Uh-
Class rep.
The teacher wants you to take this to the staff room.
He asked you to.
Uh... sure...
Eh?
I thought the officer of the day was supposed to take them?
We've been able to keep running away...
...but we had to leave early to do so.
Even so...
...it felt like we could have become friends.
Did you hear?
The freshman Hayama-san...
Hayama-san who?
You know, the one who gave the greeting.
Ah, that girl who showed off her black panties?
That was a surprise!
A freshman with black ones!
But it kind of made me want to try some.
No way!
But I heard...
What, what?
It seems she's been into schoolgirl prostitution or something...
And she has all kinds of crazy underwear.
Such as?
G-String?
See through?
And some days, I bet she wears nothing.
I can't believe we're in her class for middle school, too.
W-What's that?!
String panties?
How dirty.
A-Are you all right, Hayama?
Did you hurt yourself?
Ah... pardon me...
Try to be more careful.
Sure.
So the lingerie was for this.
Eh? What do you mean?
That girl's trying to tempt guys with her panties.
What would she tempt them for?
She could be doing dirty things with them, and getting money for it.
P-Prostitution?!
Hayama! Could you lend us your homework?
Pwease?
Ah, sure.
Here you are.
Wait, Haruka!
But she's...!
Did you forget? That girl's...
I can't see a bad thing about that girl!
She's always smiling; to call her that's just-
I understand.
If you're going to say that,
today I'll find you evidence that she's guilty!
An ideal location!
Wait, Yako-chan!
Secretly taking photos is a crime!
Conscience
W-What? But she's a criminal,
you can't compare her evil deeds to this...
More importantly, I want to see the adult
panties I missed at the entrance ceremony!
Yako-chan!
All right; the best position!
Yako-chan, your panties! Panties!
Deep in conversation, this person is totally distracted!
Ah, Hayama-san, right?
You must be amazing to be chosen as our rep.
You must be smart!
Ah, I'm not...
Okay...
Almost...!
Yako-chan!
I can't...
I'm slipping!
I can't balance!
Hayama-san?
What was that?
Ow.
Huh?
Um...
Those briefs are Claire's teen's line,
from the "Clover" series, aren't they!
A low-rise that appeared in this year's Fall-Winter collection!
Low-rise?
They're panties with a lower waistline.
When you're wearing jeans or the like, these panties won't stick out.
Enough with the panties!
Cute, aren't they?
These are just the ones my mum bought for me, I'm not that-
Hmm, you've got...
Sorry, one moment.
It might be about time for you to wear adult briefs.
Underwear for children
are made to fit the body-line of a child, after all.
Their hips are small, but with an adult,
the waist tightens while the hips widen, right?
So they're produced differently.
Someone with as womanly a body as yours
would be better off with the adult kind!
You know a lot, huh.
When it comes to underwear,
I enter a sort of daze or, um...
Is that why you wear those outrageous panties?
Let me see them.
These were also designed by an acquaintance of mine so,
I'm testing them out a bit.
Not long ago...
Good work testing them out.
Here's your change of clothes.
I had some confidence in them, but...
It seems like they are hard to wear.
Put these back...
Working you hard would be bad,
but getting negative results is perfectly fine I think.
If you fix it, and get better,
Surely I'll be happy as well.
Nayu, you're really an underwear nut, aren't you.
So that's what it was.
I'm sorry.
Eh? About what?
Eh?! You thought I was getting paid to go on dates?
I haven't done anything like that!
Then why was there that rumour?
Ah...
I don't know if this is relevant, but...
In sixth grade, everyone suddenly started avoiding me.
I was wearing a new black laced garter that day,
and since the morning I had been in a great mood.
That was probably the source.
Oh yeah, Hayama-san,
wasn't there something you wanted to talk to me about?
Eh? Oh yeah!
Ah, sorry about this-
As I thought.
This bra is bunching up your breasts!
If you leave it alone, it'll become flab on your back or somewhere.
Eh?!
It might seem easy to force them into a small bra, but...
Oh yeah, recently it's been a little tight.
You've been growing that much?!
But how did you know?
It was easy to tell from over your clothes.
Your breasts were saying "It's painful!" "It's tight!"
"It's painful!" "It's tight!"
Maturing breasts like our own are especially delicate.
You need to wear a bra that offers them space.
I see.
Well then, shall we size them up?
Eh?! No way!
Don't be shy. Come on now, Yako-chan too!
Hmm? Somebody's still here.
Isn't it that girl's voice?
Sounds as though she's in trouble.
Hayama, Nayu!
You are being outrageous!
Calm down and consider what you're doing!
Hayama, N-Nayu!
S-Stop it!
Oh, no.
After prostitution, it'll be suspicions of lesbianism.
And it'll be with me.
I'm s-sorry!
I'm sorry!
We can't do much about it.
In exchange...
For one week,
treat us to ice cream!
Don't think about going home alone!
Okay!
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
They suspected you of selling yourself,
and you ended up comparing panties?
I wish I could have been there for you.
You didn't need to be there.
But you know,
it sounds like you're making friends.
That's great!
It seems like it.
It'd be nice if I did.
Preview
Hey, do you know how to choose the right bra cup size?
Dunno.
I don't know.
It's determined by the difference between your top-bust and under-bust size.
Incidentally, an A-cup is 10cm,
B-cup is 12.5cm,
C-cup is-
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra!
This Swelling Chest