SHIN-KAWASAKI (TENTATIVE)
Get your T-shirts!
We're also selling towels!
Please!
Please...
I told you there was no point
in trying to sell merch.
Why even make merch if we
haven't even settled on a name yet?
Well, it's just... I thought maybe
we could get a leg up on it...
What, like a football team
selling ahead of season?
Well, if we become famous enough, maybe we really can go premier.
Aren't you optimistic...
Hey!
What are you spacing out for?
Thank you for showing up!!
I'll be supporting you!
Good luck!
Hope to see you next time!
It's my pleasure!
Wow... Rupa-san sure is popular...
More importantly, we gotta get the
band's name sorted out already.
- Right...
- You have a moment?
Yes?
6: PUT A NAME ON IT
- A concert...?
- Yeah.
Someone that I owe a lot to...
offered me a great opportunity.
Where's the venue?
Suwa, in Nagano prefecture.
The plan is to head there the night before the show,
And to come back right after.
It's a hectic schedule,
so I can manage on my own.
Especially since you're busy studying, Nina.
We're going.
Right?
Are you serious?
Our coordination is still a mess.
Isn't it fine? The more experience we get...
If you say so, Rupa...
- In conclusion: let's go!
- Fine.
Hmm...
What?
What are we gonna do
about our band name?
SOMEDAY LATER
Let's be clear, if we stay as
"Shin-Kawasaki", I'm seriously quitting.
I get it already!
We're just as serious about
being professional after all.
And what does Momoka-san think?
Nothing.
When I told her we were
serious about going pro...
She said nothing.
- Like a Cold War stalemate, huh?
- How can you say that with a straight face...
Momoka-san has been giving Nina
the cold shoulder, alright.
Huh? Where did the lizard go?
GECKO!
She tends to hide away
whenever she's not feeling well.
Why's she like this?!
If she's got a problem,
why doesn't she just tell us?!
Stop shouting!!
Well, I can't blame her for being mad.
Given how Nina just does whatever she wants.
I thought this whole thing was your plan.
Teehee!
Just as a warning, but if you three can't
work as a band, we're pulling out.
We ain't got the time to spare.
I get it, jeez...
On that note, what name
do you think would best fit
A ragtag team of misfits like ours?
- Don't you have any ideas?
- Huh? Why you asking me?
Shouldn't you go first?
Exactly! If you ask something,
you should answer first!
Huh? My name's a little
embarrassing though...
How about you all say it at the same time?
If you say so...
Alright, on the count of three then.
Okay.
One, two...
- Undine!     - Dream Girl!     - Chokolate!
Not "Chocolate", with a "K", Chokolate!!
I should've seen it coming....
A real Kumamoto bumpkin...
That's so cheesy it's giving me diabetes.
Rude!
What even was yours? Undine?
That's...
That's way more cringe than mine.
Huh?! Are you kidding me?!
They're both cringe.
Then what did you come up with?
Yeah! Say it again?
...Dream Girl.
...Are you all okay?
I never imagined it'd be this
hard to agree on a name...
I swear nothing's good
enough for you, Subaru....
- THE NINAZ!!  - Village People Kawasaki
- Heavenly Cow Voice  - Summers Ladies
- Nina's Nakama  - Bukubuku
- Fluffy TotoroTororo  - TanTanTanmen
- What's on tomorrow's test?  - Mermaids
-Hamburg Set Meal   - You Reap What You Study!!
-Gamadas  - Sekarashicar
- Roku-on! (sounds cool!!) - Katsudon! Gyudon! DON!!
- ADAMAS - Birthday - BEEG KAWASAKI
- rAMEN tsukeMEN - Short (BIG) Cake - OrangeLemon&Mikan
- Adolescent Salad Dressing (I'm hungry now)
Heh, that's my line~!
"You picked the name yet?"
Fuck off.
Ugh, and we wasted a whole day on this...
Late as always...
O... onee-chan?!
You could've let me
know you were coming!
I wanted to surprise you!
But I wasn't expecting
you to get home this late...
I usually don't...
Today I was... busy.
Ooh? With a boyfriend?
Don't tell me you're
doing a sketchy job?!
What is it then?
A band.
A band?!
Yeah.
You?! Wait. You're serious?
Pics or it didn't happen!
Look for yourself.
Wow... no way. You're the vocalist?
What's with the shirt?
That's...
What we call Rock.
Rock 'n' Roll!
What's with that?
Ugh, forget it.
That explains your plummeting grades.
You knew?
Well, you'd expect a school to call the family
if their kid starts skipping classes all of a sudden.
Those rats...
Be grateful that I convinced
your dad to come in his place.
So?
I left that home. That's all.
That's good and all,
But once you tell him that,
you won't be able to return again.
You know, I also think your father was wrong.
HOW TO RAISE A CHILD 101
For a professor renown for
his publications on education...
...He couldn't stand the thought
of his daughter not going to school.
Even if he ended up
hurting you in the process.
But I also understand
where he was coming from.
If you hadn't escalated the
situation with the bullying,
The school would've owed you one.
And with your grades,
you could've gotten into a good university.
But that's... not fair!
So that's why ran away
to enter university all on your own?
Yet look where that's got you,
and you still say you won't come back?
As I feared, not even I can defend that.
SOME DAYS LATER
Come on, we've got practice
tomorrow morning, so let's get a move on.
Ok...
Sorry I'm late!
What's with the baggage?
What about it?
Let me have a look.
This, this, and that...
And some clothes.
Okay, leave the rest behind.
You need to learn to travel lighter.
Alright...
We're taking the Chuo Expressway,
right? For the tolls--
Silence.
Manual? That's rare these days.
I had to borrow it from an acquaintance,
so I guess beggars can't be choosers...
How you do this again...
Oh, like this?
Everyone in favor of switching drivers.
You're very good at driving, Rupa-san!
I had to drive a lot for my last job.
You sure you wanna do it in one go?
We can take breaks, if you want.
Was my driving really that terrible?
If I get tired I'll just pull over to a gas
station, so feel free to rest if you need it.
Eeh? But we finally got time
with the five of us together...
Then, wanna play a game?
You ask a question, and if everyone
can relate, you win.
For example... I prefer cats over dogs!
Ooh? I would've never guesssed
you were a dog person, Tomo-chan.
The say people who act like
a sourpuss tend to like dogs more.
Your turn, Nina.
Okay, uhm...
I have almost no friends!
Gottem!
Game will be over in a second like that...
Okay then, Momoka-san!
Huh? Pain in the ass...
Then... who here hates my driving?
DANGOZAKA SERVICE AREA
Let's take a little break.
I'll be right back,
so hang in there.
- Woah, it's packed!
- Cut it off!
- Rock, Paper, Scissors!
- How long?
Excuse me.
Took you long enough.
How much was this?
Did I pick the wrong one?
...Nah, it's alright.
I'm glad.
Tomo-chan... why did you drop out of school?
Why are you asking?
Because I can't ask anyone else.
I didn't have the luxury
to waste my time there.
My parents were never there for me, so...
I knew I'd have to survive
on my own after I graduated.
Mom?
When she brought other men home,
she felt like a whole other creature.
Seeing her like that,
it flipped a switch in me.
It's not rare for indie artists
to start before they even graduate.
So the sooner I run away, the better.
So I fled to Tokyo, formed a band,
School was taking up too much of my time, so...
That's all.
You're incredible...
I never thought that far ahead.
When you don't have anyone you can rely on
anymore, you have no other choice.
Rupa lost her mother in an accident, so...
...She said she felt the same.
I never gave it any thought.
I've always wanted to do this!
Give me a big smile!
Momoka-san, Tomo-chan, smile a bit more!
Okay! Say "cheese please"!
We look like idols.
Shut the fuck up.
WELCOME, TO THE LAND OF SUWA.
I know we can't afford a hotel, but...
I'm boiling...
And you're heavy...
Hello~!
Hello...
Girls Band Cry.
TOMORROW: SUWA FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
Alright, we're getting somewhere!
Where? We're all over the place!
Huh? Aren't you two the newbies here?
You know that's not true!
We all suck equally.
That aside, Subaru-chan,
your neck is... uh...
I know! Sleeping in a car ain't easy!
So this is your new band, Momo?
"Momo"?
Indeed!
"Indeed"?
Ah, I fixed it.
I wouldn't say you're great,
but you're not half bad either.
I've heard worse.
My apologies. We will try our best
to not spoil the show.
Oh? That guitar...
Yep. The one and the same.
Even your sticker's still there.
DIAMOND DUST
Is it just me or is she...
like a whole other person?
Or maybe this is how she always used to be.
If it's okay, could we do this final song together?
- Is that okay?
- I'd be honored!
You want to play with us?
It's why I invited you to begin with.
Are you all up to it?
Ah... ehm, yes.
While we're at it, why don't we have a quick session.
- Session?
- Practicing together, she means.
You're the vocalist, right?
Yes.
Waving goodbye to melodies of past
Until the day we may meet again
Even if that may mean
That I'll forget
I'm an adult once again
- So?
- Huh?
- Can you sing it?
- Ah, yeah!
Probably...
I'll try my best!
It's decided then. I'll go fetch the manager.
- She's a great singer, isn't she?
- Yeah!
When I first landed in Tokyo,
I got to see her playing live.
She was just an extra for the opening act.
And yet she sang her heart out
like her life depended on it.
I thought: "Ah... this is Rock!!"
So I'm glad that I can perform
with her for my final concert.
I'm quitting the band.
After tomorrow, it's over for me.
I'm quitting.
What are you even saying...?
I'm sorry. I don't have the heart to
support this band... to go pro again.
Why?
My music isn't the type of stuff
that makes it in the world of pros.
Nina... when you said you
liked my music, it made me happy.
And I'm grateful that you stood up
for me. Thank you for everything.
Are you really okay with that?
Yeah.
I am.
YAKITORI
Never would've thought you'd become
this much of a drinker!
Rupa-san, you can hold your alcohol too!
Dragging others into her alcoholism...
Don't tell me we're gonna have to drag
her fat ass again... Ugh, I can already envision it...
Be sure to keep it together tomorrow.
We owe our customers that much.
- I get it...
- What's with the long face?
What, are we arguing?
Ah! That aside, what type of
music do you like, Mine-san?
Mine-san, have you ever thought of quitting music?
Wow, why are you asking?
Cut it out!
I don't think anyone enjoys
having to make that choice.
The more you do something,
the more you realize your skill with it, right?
If you fail once, it's easy to chalk it as bad luck.
But fail twice, and we already resign
ourselves that we've got no talent.
So you stop believing... that you're any good anymore?
I'd like to keep believing.
But the taller we set our hopes,
the more painful the scars from the fall.
It's scary.
Because we love music so much.
I'll be counting on you tomorrow!
Mine-san!
Do you... not get scared?
Me?
Yes.
Of course I do.
Even now, I sometimes
can't sleep or eat over it.
Even now?
Of course!
But that's the life of turning your
true passion into your job.
When I was studying music,
I thought about becoming a teacher
and just sing for fun.
I kept telling myself
that was the smart choice.
What made you change your mind?
I wonder...
I've probably forgotten already!
You... forgot?
It's just that the stage is the only place
where I can truly express myself.
It's my safe place.
So I won't stress over if it's too scary or difficult.
Well, that's probably why, at least.
What are you--
Ah, you STINK!
What are you sayjing... I havennn drunk a drop...
I'm shocked you can lie this shamelessly!
Oh jus ssshut up already...
You're always, always, always, always,
- See ya.
- alWAAAAAAAYSSS...
Hey, are you lisssening??
Take care of Momoka-san for me!
Hey, don't dump us with this!
Nor fair, Nina!
Sorry, which way is the lake?
Thank you so much!
I've decided.
I've got it!
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it! I finally got it!
I know what I want to do!
KAMISUWA KAICHO VENUE
Thank you all!
Coming up is a band that's dear to me, so stay tuned!
Shall we?
Yes ma'am!
Oh by the way, what are we even naming ourselves?
Have you picked one?
We tried to settle it over dinner, but...
Still, Shin-Kawasaki is... ugh, fine, I guess.
Huh?
Good evening!
- We are...
- That sly...
Uhm...
TOGEARI TOGENASHI
(THORNLESS THORNS)
TOGENASHI TOGEARI!
Oh wow, same as my t-shirt!
What a coincidence!
Hello!
This Spring, we started this
band kinda out of nowhere
I'm not really sure why I did it,
Or why I'm even singing.
But... it's fun.
For the first time in my life,
I've become passionate about something.
Come on, let's go.
My life... all changed
thanks to this one song.
It became my strength to keep moving forward.
So I want to prove that song was not wrong!
That this song can move hearts,
I want to tell people how incredible it is!
Subaru-chan, Rupa-san,
Tomo-chan, and Momoka-san...
I'm sure that we can rely on each other.
So I'll try my best.
I'm scared...
but I want to believe.
So I'm gonna...
I'm gonna..
Cut it out~
Enough monologues!
Right.
Jeez.
What a mess of an opening.
Nothing quite like it!
Scarred, forever, my mind and body are fragmented
Passion and cruelty go round and round in my head
I plunge into the city, full of lies, it just makes me sick
Within the stench and the noise,
I cry out alone.
Nothing is happening. How are you doing today?
Can you stop saying such dumb things?
That creepy voice echoes in my mind. While my tears keep flowing.
"You don't have to be afraid, so stop hiding.
Come and dance with me," you said
I want to run away from this putrid world
I want to disperse
Disperse, disperse, quietly
Quietly, don't let me be alone
Like sorrow laid out in the bars of a song
Forever and ever and ever.
Until love can be proven
I don't want to believe that love is an emotion
I could go insane
Rupa-san.
Tomo-chan.
Subaru-chan.
Momoka-san.
I'm...
Dropping out of school.
Ah, fuck.
NEXT: IF YOU WERE TO CRY