When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
It was a Christmas present!
Thanks to a very common high school boy's, Ayasaki Hayate's, generous parents,
he was kindly given to very nice people.
However, destiny was waiting for him at the park.
I'm not really sure, but you saved me.
Villains! Hand her back to me now!
So I'll make him my, Sanzenin Nagi's, new butler!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
So I'll make him my, Sanzenin Nagi's, new butler!
Why are you stating it twice?
Hey, where am I?
Are you set?
Are you done with your life?
Oh please, Mr. Santa Claus.
You sound as though I'm dead.
You are dead.
You were so red that we couldn't even put you on the airwaves.
I see.
But if so, oh well.
I don't have any family to grieve over me, or a house to return to.
Really?
A kidnapper trying to act as a tragic hero?
Besides in the last episode, although it was in your mind, you did punch me.
Don't forget. Although it didn't actually happen,
what you tried to do is a crime.
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'll never do it again.
I'm really sorry.
I'm... sorry...
Hey, where am I?
This splendor... it can't be of this world.
Which means, this is Heaven.
If not, it has to be an illusion created by my mind due to a long, poor life.
Thank you, Mr. Santa Claus. I'll enjoy it to my fullest.
What a stupid hero we have.
He did hit his head hard, but there's nothing to worry about.
He must have been training regularly.
If anything comes up, call me.
Maria. I want to make him Himegami's replacement.
Um, I'm having a hard time following you.
It's true that it's the person who saved my life's wish, but...
How do I say...
He confessed love to me at the park.
Very passionately.
"I want to take you away" or something like that.
I see...
Anyway, when Hayate wakes up, let me know right away.
I'm leaving it to you.
What is going on? I have to check on a few things.
Oh, but before that.
Wow, my dream's awesome.
It's more flamboyant than anything I'd ever seen when I was alive.
Man, but if this is Heaven, it's not such a bad idea to die.
The alone part is a little lonely, though.
I-It does feel good, doesn't it?
I-It really calms me down.
Don't be!
Is this really a dream? Wh-Why is that scarf person here?
Um...
Y-Yes?
Your body is really quite tough.
Although your life isn't in any danger, to take a bath...
The wounds would open for any normal person.
And the bath is now stained.
It's stained by the red bath agent that oozed out of Hayate!
Get a hold of yourself! Are you all right?
Hey! A shooting star!
No wait, we're not even at the halfway point of the episode!
Here's a fan service shot to make up for it!
Are you awake, Ayasaki Hayate-kun?
You were in the bath-
You've been out all this time, ever since you were carried into the mansion, but are you all right?
I've been out all this time?
Of course!
You've been out the entire time.
I see. So that was a dream.
Oh, but how do you know my name?
And, where am I?
Let's see...
This is Lady Sanzenin Nagi-sama's mansion, whom you saved.
I saved...
That girl's?!
And I am her maid, Maria.
And, though I know it's impolite of me, I took a look at this.
It seems you are in a difficult position.
N-No, nothing much.
By the way, I have something I want to ask you.
Regarding what happened with our Lady in the park.
E-Everything's exposed?
I'm told that you were going to "take her away"?
Ummm...
I-I'm sorry! I'll never even think about kidnapping!
I see. I understand your situation.
I really don't know how to apologize regarding this matter.
Well, there are lies that people say out of necessity.
Oh, so you were awake already.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine now.
Thank you so much for being so kind to me.
But I'm sorry for the terrible request I made to you at the park.
For ¥156,804,000, too.
Well, it surprised me, but I wasn't against it.
It was your first moment being confessed to, after all.
Although you mistook it.
But we don't know each other well,
so I'm not too sure about rushing the steps.
I-I've given it some thought after that, too!
You were looking for live-in work, weren't you?
Then be my butler here at the mansion.
Oh, yay.
Butler?
U-Um, Milady, how about asking his situation first?
But we do need a replacement for Himegami.
Besides, your toughness is greater than anyone's.
He was moving even after getting hit by a car.
She's about to forgive me for trying to kidnap her and is now offering me live-in work?
What a... What a kind little girl!
Thank you, Mr. Santa Claus.
This must be my first present from you.
No, not necessarily.
B-But Hayate-kun doesn't know what a butler does, does he?
I'll do it!
Leave it to me, Milady.
No matter what happens, I, Ayasaki Hayate,
will protect Milady, even at the cost of my own life!
Y-You idiot!
Don't say such an embarrassing thing in front of Maria.
W-What should we do about these two naturally empty minds?
What is this?
A new butler?
Yes, we were looking for a replacement
to fill in for head butler with Himegami gone,
but what exactly is this Ayasaki Hayate boy like?
Let's see...
Someone who can catch up to a car speeding at 120km/h
on a bicycle and can withstand being run over by said car.
Maria, which ***dam is that?
That's as sturdy as a giant robot.
No, Klaus-san, he is a human.
And, that ***dam is not a giant robot, but-
I-I see, so that ***dam isn't a giant robot?
I'm studying anime to have
a common interest with Milady, but...
"Foolishness caused by youth."
You seem to be understanding it.
So regarding Hayate-kun's case?
Anyways, the likes of him won't suffice as our butler.
Have him leave.
But...
Okay?
Wow.
How's the fit?
Yes, it's perfect.
That's great. It was worth fixing it last night.
Maria-san, you did this?
Shall we get to work now?
Yes.
So, what exactly is my job?
Let's see...
Since it's the end of the year, I guess cleaning every spot you see.
Klaus-san said to send him out, but I cannot really do that, can I?
Cleaning... Then I can do that, too.
If I get fired from here, I can't pay the ¥156,804,000 back.
I won't have a place to live, either.
Yes, today, my new life will start here!
Yes, as a butler to the Sanzenin family.
Don't take my line.
Time for commercials.
Love.
Hate.
Yes, today, my new life will start here!
As a butler to the Sanzenin family!
I got to say it all this time!
Ah, Nagi. Good morning.
Ah, good morning, both of you.
Look at this, Milady.
Maria-san redid these clothes for me.
Well, I hope you work well.
I-I feel she's become cold all of a sudden.
If you ask me, I think she's getting heated up.
Anyway, I'll gain her trust back through work!
U-Um-
His motivation... How can I send him away?
And how can I untangle the misunderstanding?
That wasn't the right attitude to take.
That was way too mean.
If I could sew like Maria...
What do you think, Hayate?
It's amazing, Milady.
Hayate.
Milady.
Milady!
Oh, Maria. Where's Hayate?
He's helping me with cleaning.
He's filled with motivation.
I see.
Apparently, he is going to work hard to gain your trust.
If you have anything in mind,
I think it is the best if you talk to him in person.
Y-You're right! We have to get to know each other well, first.
Yes.
I'll get to where Hayate is!
Make sure you kindly untangle the misunderstanding.
Maria-san, could you check the cleaning for me?
Huh? Is something wrong?
No, just thinking how unsynchronized you two are.
It looks really clean here.
Does it? Thank you very much.
Very thorough in the smallest places.
That's...
Ah, that door handle was made of silver, so I used Silver Duster to polish it.
This statue here, after taking the stain off with a brush made of brass, I cleaned with a neutral detergent.
Then I wiped the water off and finished it with a wax coating.
The carpet was Kilim style made with wool,
so I used cosmetic detergent with cold water.
Um, did I do something wrong?
No, I'm honestly surprised.
Rather, I'm at a loss for words.
Well, I was working at a sanitation company when I was eight, while hiding my age, to get money for my parents to drink off.
So cleaning turns out to be one of my specialties.
I'm sorry, Klaus-san, I can't find a reason to send Hayate-kun off.
It looks like Nagi's eye for selecting people seems to be true.
But this mansion is really huge.
How many rooms are there to clean?
Study?
I don't sense anyone in here.
What is this?
Milady's notebook?
Th-This is!
A picture diary?
It's a manga.
N-No, I mustn't look at a private thing like this.
Hey!
What are you looking at in someone else's room?
M-Milady! Um, this is...
Th-That's my-
No, I didn't read your picture diary at all!
P-P-Picture diary, you say?
You idiot!!!
Milady?
Shut up! I don't care about you anymore!
What do you understand about me?!
Idiot! Hayate, you idiot!
Milady...
Get out of here!
Farewell, my peace.
It was short, but thank you.
We meet again, kiddo.
Hello...
Are you sure?
Sure about what?
Hayate-kun really left.
On a black pumpkin carriage, too.
Wh-What?
H-Hey! The second half of this episode isn't over yet!
Indeed.
Are you sure you want to leave him?
I only told him to get out of the room.
I didn't think he'd leave the mansion.
It is because you are not in the habit of putting away your important things.
Not much we can do now.
Let us forget about Hayate-kun.
If you say you are through with him, then there is no reason to stop him.
But that's...
If you hate Hayate-kun, then it is better to leave things as is.
No, I don't hate him or anything.
You don't?
In any case, Hayate is the person who saved my life.
As a part of Sanzenin, I can't abandon my savior.
Um, Mister Nice People, where is this?
The Immigration Office.
Oh, I'm so happy. Volunteer work is waiting for me ahead.
I'm never going to return to Japan.
I probably won't be able to come back.
Wh-What should I do? At this rate, my life will...
First, it'll be a cruise with everyone on a gorgeous boat.
But on the way, pirates will attack us,
and for some reason I'll get recruited into their crew.
After becoming a wanted man,
I get cornered by an ocean monkey,
and my dream to become the Pirate King sinks into a cross-shaped ocean.
Um, I have a little emergency to attend to.
Let me go!
Don't worry. Your luxury boat is ready, too.
S-Someone help!
Bro!
It hurts!
Bro, stop moving.
Want me to help?
Please stay still!
That voice. Could you be...
Milad-
NO!!!
My name is Na-
No, um...
Mask...
Right, Mask the Money!
I came here at the request of Nagi.
And, here's a message from her.
"I-I'm sorry for yelling at you earlier."
That's what she wanted me to tell you!
A-And, what you saw in the notebook is her latest work,
a manga titled Millennium Legend: Magical Destroy,
and it absolutely wasn't a picture diary!
Okay, I got it!
Ah, Mask the Money-san!
Good. Then continue being a butler at her house.
She'd be happy that way.
I think...
Yes!
Of course, you're not going to be able to do that.
He's got a ¥156,804,000 debt made by his parents to pay back.
He's got to return it in full.
Are you talking about this?
So what about this piece of paper?
I told you to shut up, or did you not hear me, baldy?!
This brat...
D-Don't touch this person!
Don't be so arrogant.
If you don't want us to touch her,
then pay the ¥156,804,000 back right now.
I will.
The entire debt.
You're kidding...
That's all real money?
Of course, you idiots!
You don't have any more problems now, do you?
Bro.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Now you need to get the money back from him.
Mask the Money-san.
When you see Milady, please relay a message for me.
I will pay the money back with work.
And thank you for my position as butler.
But she meant the money as a gift to you.
N-No! I have to pay it off! Otherwise I can't be even with her.
After all, she came to save me with such a funny looking mask.
I don't even have to note that she thought it was cool.
So that money-
Pay it off!!!
On second thought, money-related matters must be kept black and white for the sake of justice.
So you must work like a horse to pay everything back to Sanzenin Nagi!
Y-Yes, of course.
I'm definitely, DEFINITELY, not going to give you any discounts, you hear?!
Hmph!
Mask the Money-san, your mask fell off.
PLACEHOLDER
W-W-W-W-What?!
Looks like they're fighting.
D-D-Don't look!
I think it's fine.
Not yet!
Yes, I understand!
They are like brother and sister.
You understand?!
Are you sure you didn't see?
I'm sorry.
Got that?!
It's snowing.
And this is how the two's Christmas came to an end.
However, spring is still far away.
One trouble after another.
Next week, we'll pit the mascot character of this anime and 21st-century household machines in a fight.
I'm absolutely against hiring a boy who's so pathetic and looks like he'll never have any luck with money for the rest of his life!
What?
If you see a problem with Hayate-kun's strength or potential, how about testing him?
A test?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
The Beast, Robot, and Butler That Kinda Shout Love at the Center of the World.
Don't worry, Hayate; I know you can do it.
The red lion goes roar!