The Dollars?
They're angels that fly around going,
“Pi piru piru” and show their panties.
Make sure to put enough in. If she doesn't wake up, she's going to be worth a lot less.
It's not like we know much about The Dollars.
But I'll tell you everything we do know.
Apparently they're a color gang, but no one knows their color.
Dengeki released some new pocket editions, so...
We bought ten for various reasons.
Various, indeed.
Don't think you can get away! Yeah!
I'm turning right!
Abs make the man.
This is first time we've done anything like
this since entering The Dollars, right, Kadota?
Sit down and shut up!
The Dollars aren't angels that fly around going,
"Pi piru piru," and show their panties, are they, Dotachin?
I told you not to call me that!
Alright, we ditched them.
That's insane!
Damn!
Well, why don't you tell me if you're in league
with the group that's experimenting on humans...?
I'm Kadota Kyohei.
I don't actually like being called "Dotachin."
Anyway, this all started eight hours ago.
I'm about to tell you the story of the well-known Kaztano Incident.
The one who went missing is my classmate.
To be exact, she's a friend of a friend...
I've never even met her once.
So, your friend's gone missing, Tanaka Taro?
Speaking of that, lots of people have been disappearing recently...
Or at least there are lots of rumors about missing persons.
Kanra, you're a gossip maniac.
Ahahahaha.
The missing people I've heard about are mostly kids that ran away from home or illegal aliens.
By that I mean people who leave no trace once they disappear.
Tons of people like that are disappearing between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
And once they disappear they're never seen again.
Is that true?!
There are some even scarier rumors, you know.
They suggest that the reason those people can't be found is
because The Dollars dispose of the bodies somewhere and eat them!
Huh?
Hm?
Nice rusty sign.
So this is where that information dealer said the supplier would be?
It definitely seems like this place would be crawling with illegal aliens.
Let's grab our meal ticket and deliver it.
Kaztano!
Hey, now!
This is fun!
Whoa, teenage girls!
That's twenty percent more money!
Naw, let's get what we can today.
If we go after those kinds of people, that thing might appear again.
Ugh. The headless thing?
Let's hedge our bets with this guy today.
What's up?
It sounds like there's something wrong with him.
Well, he's still a person.
Alright, a middle-aged dude's considered damaged
goods, so I assume we're prepared to get less for him?
Hey.
Yo, meal ticket.
I'm Japanese!
I'm the same as you!
But many people say I look like a foreigner.
It makes me unpoko sad.
T/L Note: He messes up his Japanese.
There is sometimes bullying.
We won't even get enough to cover the cost of food.
What the hell does "unpoko sad" mean?
That's why if she doesn't have a "younger
brother savior" character like Yuuta around,
she's just a crazy, masochistic wolf with a hair fetish.
You say "younger brother," but he's actually a guy dressed like a girl.
I want a "younger sister savior" character.
Oh, but an older sister character would be okay, too.
It's unforgivable that you're talking that way at dinner time.
Dotachin, let's go get some food.
Food, food!
Okay.
Wow, wow, wow, you did a great job as always.
This bathroom's bigger than my bedroom.
They tell me the concept for this place is "a cabaret that's a step above other places and provides a calm space in which to relax."
Hmph.
Ah, we should hurry. This day only comes once a month.
Yeah.
Who's that?
It's from Kaztano.
"The plate...broke."
Can't he just buy a new one?
At the 100 yen shop!
I'm Japanese!
Could he have messed up the kanji for "I got abducted by someone?"
You're over thinking it.
This guy's too loud. Put him to sleep now!
Gotchya.
Oh...
Come on, it's cheap!
Our ingredients are fresh!
So you heard about the rumor, Sonohara?
Yes.
She's fine. That rumor's a total lie.
That's right. Harima just went missing,
it's not like she could only have been abducted.
There's no way that she could have been abducted and disposed of...
Why're you talking about this?
I just dug my own grave.
Alright, nigiri for three.
It's okay, we use fish in our sushi.
Even on half-price day, we don't use people.
But, the sushi bar on the corner...
He's going to keep this horrible topic going?!
Simon, the banner out front snapped in half!
The banner?!
Yeah, the banner.
Let's go fix it!
Yeah!
Let's fix it!
It's true!
The sushi bar on the corner doesn't use fish on half-price day, they use people! People!
Togusa,
let's decorate the car with anime characters and stuff.
It'll look great.
I'd kill you.
Italian cars are expensive, right? Since they're foreign and all.
Some salmon from the Inland Sea, please!
Some yellowtail and striped sea bass!
That's dangerous!
Yes, it is.
Ugh. No one empties a whole bottle of that, especially all over themselves.
It's no good. I'm...too sleepy.
You can't sleep until we deliver the goods.
Oh, crap.
M-My eyelids!
Look straight ahead!
Um, excuse me...
What?!
This guy's the source of sleepy.
If you dump him there, we'll all be better.
Huh?
Kaztano?
We brought you some sushi.
Hey, we got an old plate from Russia Sushi for you.
Whoa, what happened?!
His email wasn't about a plate breaking...
Yeah...
It was a bowl!
Dotachin.
"Simple Kanji Conversion..."
Kaztano...
Kaztano was abducted by human traffickers.
We'll never find him again.
How will I ever manage without Kaztano?!
What will I stand for?!
We all knew just how important Kaztano was to Togusa.
No one could take Kaztano's place.
Not Karisawa, not Yumasaki, and not me.
We were all kind of sad.
If he was abducted at the time he sent that email, not much time has passed.
We'll find him and bring him back before he gets handed off.
But how?!
I know!
I saw their car!
Hasim!
He's here!
The best kind of "younger brother savior" character!
An alien autopsy took place in the town of Avers, Texas!
Okay, I understand. When she finds the car, all she has to do is free the foreigner, right?
We succeeded in interviewing someone who was present at the autopsy.
Yeah, but we don't know when or where the hand off will take place.
We just want to help him as soon as possible.
Okay, so it's a black van.
Do you know the plate number?
Yeah, I'll give it to you.
Just a second.
Okay.
Thanks, Hasim.
Can you eat sushi?
Yeah!
See you.
Does this have wasabi?
Yeah, it does.
You'll be fine. Russian wasabi isn't very strong.
You shouldn't lie to him.
Let's go.
Alright!
It's a black van, alright?
This is the plate number.
Be careful!
The perpetrators must be contracted by some corrupt organization.
They're probably just the underlings.
Apparently they abduct people who
no one will look for once they disappear.
Those people are probably used for a bunch of different things.
It's just like cannibalism.
We haven't got many shipments this month.
Correct. Lately, our materials have started to get more cautio—
Enough with the excuses.
Just cut ties with any contractors that can't raise their numbers.
But—
Or would you like to become a subject?
You can leave now.
Seiji...
Shinra, you idiot!
It flaps and flutters in the gentle breeze.
The roaring sound—
We desperately searched for the black van that abducted Kaztano...
...with the notion we'd save him planted firmly in our hearts.
We tried everything we could think of...
Good boy. Nice...
But we didn't have the slightest idea where he could be.
Go!
Fear began to creep into my mind.
Fear that I may never again hear
that nostalgic phrase Kaztano used to say.
That nostalgic phrase I heard so often as a kid.
That phrase I never thought I'd hear again once I grew up...
Do you have tickets? Tickets here!
Yes, Kaztano's occupation was on the brink of extinction.
Do you have tickets?
And Kaztano was the one who presented Togusa with the greatest joy of his life.
Mister, two tickets, please.
Great.
Hijiribe Ruri will forever be Togusa's goddess...
A goddess on whom Togusa one-sidedly showers his affections.
Togusa views Kaztano as a magician, since he was able to get him the seat closest to his goddess during a packed concert.
For Togusa's sake, we have to save Kaztano, no matter the cost.
Dotachin?
What're you talking about?
And to whom?
Well...
I was just thinking, why don't we try calling Kaztano's phone?
Maybe we can negotiate with his abductors.
Sushi love. I like the fatty tuna.
Who are you?
Is that your voice, Dotachin?
Yeah, I was walking by and found this guy sleeping,
so I picked up the phone for him when I heard it ring.
Huh? Here?
I'm diagonal from the Southern Ikebukuro Taishouken...
I mean, c'mon, it's discount day at Russia Sushi—
Izaya, don't ever come to Ikebukuro!
Aw, Shizu-chan found me. Later.
IIIzaaayaaa!
Wake up!
Hey, wake up!
Wake the hell up!
Don't use those; he'll stay asleep forever if you do.
But if we don't hurry, Kaztano will...
She's right! Once he's handed off, he'll be disposed of!
What're you gonna do?
I'm going to impersonate you and get them to
tell me where they're going to hand off Kaztano.
It's almost time to hand this guy over.
A higher-up is coming, so be on the lookout.
Okay.
I'm a Japanese, right?
You're going to realize you've made a mistake, right?
You're still saying that?
Then it says you're Japanese in your family registry, right?
That's the thing; my family registry was destroyed in the fire bombings!
Just how old are you?!
Yes?
Hey, it's me.
Oh, Kanazawa? You woke up?
Sorry, I'll head over there right now.
By the way, where's the hand-off spot again?
Man, you're hopeless.
We're amazing...
We did it!
Yay!
It paid off!
We did it...
Who the hell are you?
We're...
The Dollars!
The Dollar...?
"S"!
Remember that!
I'm sleepy...
So sleepy...
Let's go.
The series of events that led us to join The Dollars was simple.
Before I knew it, Togusa, Yumasaki,
and Karisawa were already hanging around me.
I don't know what's so great about someone like me...
Well, they are great people.
One day, I received an email on my cell phone.
It said, "Do you want to join The Dollars? There are no restrictions or rules.
All you have to do is say you're part of The Dollars."
It was a strange invitation...
From those eccentric Dollars I'd started hearing rumors about.
At first, I thought it was just a prank...
But I accepted for the hell of it, and the
next day I was sent a URL and a password.
When I logged in, my handle was displayed right there on the website.
None of the members, including me, have
ever met someone you could call a leader.
There are multiple smaller organizations within the main one...
...and although they form a hierarchy, no one can find the absolute top.
Since there's no top, I don't feel like I've been placed under anyone.
However, I'd be lying if I said I don't
want to know who created this organization.
Don't tell anyone, but some people think he was the one.
That rude guy who started calling me Dotachin.
Mm, fatty tuna's the best.
What you're looking for isn't that way...
Nooo!
I'm sorry, Celty.
How much do you think we can sell him for?
Enough to pay off our expenses.
Is that all? Typical.
Huh?
Is that a higher-up?
Probably...
Eh?
What the hell?!
Kaztano!
We're here to save you, Kaztano!
It won't be so easy.
You're so impudent!
Ooh, what a retro phrase.
What's "impudent?"
Th-The headless thing!
But we made sure to get a worthless old guy!
We don't do it anymore! We won't do it anymore!
What?
Kaztano!
Dotacchino!
They're getting away!
Don't think you can get away! Yeah!
I'm turning right!
Can I go home?
You should just tell us now where you were going to hand him over.
No way, this'll be boring without some torture, right?
Please choose a book.
We'll base our torture method on the content of the book you choose.
Now I don't dare what you guys do, as long as you don't use gasoline inside the car again.
Gasoline?!
Togussano, it's morning ritual time!
Okay, I'll tell you, I'll tell you!
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, huh?
What a fancy place.
Is this really it?
They're experimenting on humans here.
We were half in doubt about it.
At least, as far as we could tell from the outside...
However, there is usually an outer and an inner lining to everything.
There are mountains of things with evil linings in Ikebukuro.
Alright, shall we go get some food?
Sounds good!
I want the morning set at Russia Sushi!
Good enough for me. Let's go!
Alright, it's decided!
You can use as much money as you want, however you want.
Thanks, sis.
See you, Seiji.
Let's go.
That's the story of the Kaztano Incident.
Anyway, we're happy that we were able to get our friend back safely.
How annoying!
What a pain!
How disgusting!
My body moves on its own if I can't keep it in check.
It doesn't care what will happen to me.
Next Time: Best In The Land.
That's why I hate violence!