Under these vast skies,
there are thousands - tens
of thousands of people.
All sorts of people live their lives,
harboring desires and
emotions of all sorts.
Those emotions sometimes touch one
another, and clash with one another.
But still, a few of them are sure
to bond to each other,
and can communicate
with one another.
Such a story is about to begin, one
of new introductions and contacts.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the
smile that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
Ancient resonance, turn into light!
Put those that are unforgiven
inside the ring of sealing!
Jewel Seed, Seal!
I let it get away...
I have to go after it...
Someone...
Listen to my voice...
Lend me your powers!
Magical... powers...
Episode 1: Is This What You Call
A Mysterious Encounter?
That was a pretty strange
dream I just had.
I'm Nanoha Takamachi.
I'm a third grader at Seisho
Elementary, a private school.
And in the Takamachi family,
I'm the youngest of three children.
Good morning!
Oh, Nanoha! Good morning!
Good morning, Nanoha.
Here, take these, please.
Okay.
These two are my father and mother.
You woke up all on your own!
Such a good girl.
This is Shiro Takamachi, my father.
He's the owner of Midoriya,
a café located across the street
from the train station,
and the main pillar of our household.
Breakfast is almost ready.
And my mother, Momoko Takamachi.
S I e Midoriya cafe 1ot
So beautiful and kind...
I love my mother!
By the way, Midoriya is located in
the middle of the shopping strip,
across the street from
the train station.
It prides itself on cakes, cream
puffs, and house-roasted coffee.
It's a favorite after-school
hangout for schoolgirls,
as well as for all the ladies
of the neighborhood.
Where's big brother and big sister?
They might be over at the dojo.
Big brother, big sister, good morning!
It's time for breakfast!
Morning.
Oh, Nanoha. Good morning.
Here.
Thanks.
These two are my older siblings.
Then that's it for this morning, Miyuki.
My big brother, Kyouya Takamachi,
is a freshman in college.
He's a swordsman following
in my dad's footsteps,
and acts as coach to my sister.
Okay. Then we'll continue once
I'm done with school for the day.
And my sister, Miyuki Takamachi,
is in 11th grade.
It's tasty as ever this morning!
Especially these scrambled eggs!
Really? I topped it with
tomatoes and cheese,
and a hint of basil to add to the flavor!
You're all really fortunate to have
such a great chef for a mother!
Do you guys understand that?
We get it. Right, Nanoha?
Yeah.
Oh, stop it, honey!
The parents of the Takamachi family
still act like newlyweds.
Miyuki, your ribbon is all twisted up.
Really?
Here, let me fix it.
And my big brother and big sister
get along really well...
But in such a loving family,
I think I'm a bit of
a third wheel at times.
Good morning!
Nanoha!
Nanoha! Over here!
Suzuka! Arisa!
Morning.
Good morning, Nanoha.
Good morning.
Arisa Bannings and Suzuka Tsukimura
have been in my class
since first grade.
And this year, the three of us go
to the same cram school too.
Just as I had you research, there
are many stores in this city.
Actually seeing and hearing
the behavior and cleverness
of all the people who
work in such stores
must have been a very
educational experience for you.
Just like this, there are various jobs
in all sorts of places,
so what kind of jobs would you
like to hold when you grow up?
It might be a good idea to
start thinking about that now.
Rise!
My future, huh...
Arisa, Suzuka,
you two have a good idea
of what you'll be, right?
Both Mom and Dad run a company,
so I have to study a lot so
I can properly take over.
I like machines,
so I'm considering an
engineering specialty.
I see. Both of you are amazing.
Saherit Caré Mideriya?
That's one of the visions
of my future, but...
I have a feeling that there's
something else that I want to do,
but it's not really clear
what exactly that thing is.
I don't have any special
traits or talents.
You idiot!
Don't say that about yourself!
That's right.
I'm sure there is something
that only you can do, Nanoha.
In the first place,
your math and science grades
are better than mine!
So which mouth is blabbering that
she has no talents at all, huh?!
But I'm not good at Japanese,
and I'm terrible in physical education!
Both of you, stop it... Come on...
Come on, already!
Something I can do...
Something only I can do?
You were amazing in
dodge-ball today, Suzuka.
Yeah, she was really awesome!
Oh, not at all...
Be quiet!
Over here!
Cutting through here is a shortcut!
Really?
The path is a bit rough, though.
This is the place I saw
in my dream last night.
Something wrong?
Nanoha?
No, it's nothing.
Sorry, sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Then let's go.
That's impossible.
Nanoha!
Yeah!
Help me!
Nanoha?
Did you hear something just now?
Something?
Like a voice.
Not really.
I don't think I heard anything.
Help me!
Nanoha!
Nanoha?!
I think it was from over here.
What's wrong, Nanoha?!
Running off so suddenly!
Look, an animal.
It looks like it's hurt.
Yeah... What should we do?
What should we do?
Maybe a hospital for starters?
You mean a veterinarian's office!
Was there a vet's office around here?
Let's see... Around here...
Wait, I'll try calling home.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha!
Nanoha!
Hey, Nanoha!
Okay, I'm coming right over!
The wounds weren't that bad,
but it seems to be
very weak right now.
Maybe it's been on its own for a while.
Thank you so much, Doctor!
Thank you very much!
Oh, you're welcome!
Doctor, this is a ferret, right?
I wonder if it was someone's pet?
Is it a ferret?
It's a strange breed if it is.
And on the collar...
Is this a gem?
It woke up!
It's looking...
Nanoha, it's looking at you.
Yeah...
Um... um...
It's best to let it rest for a while,
so I'll take care of it
here until tomorrow.
Yes, please do!
So come by again tomorrow
to see how it's doing, okay?
Yes, we will!
Oh no, it's time for cram school!
You're right!
Then, Doctor, excuse us...
We'll be back tomorrow!
Well, let's start with an application
of what we learned last time.
Starting from the top of
page 47 of the textbook.
Let's look at the sample problem.
What should we do with this guy? -N
The sample problem says 3945.
We have dogs running around
in our backyard... -A
The sample problem says 3945.
We have dogs running around
in our backyard... -A
Both the numerator and denominator
can be divided by three.
So it can be reduced to 1315.
We have cats in our house too. -S
We handle food as our business,
so raising pets is basically
out of the question.
Then let's have the answer to
this question answered by...
Okay, %29, Miss Takamachi.
Okay!
Problem 3, on page 47!
Let's see... Let's see...
5742!
Yes, that's correct.
Some people stop here, thinking
they've solved the problem,
Good going!
Some people stop here, thinking
they've solved the problem,
Nice!
Some people stop here, thinking
they've solved the problem,
Nice!
but in this case...
I'll talk to my family to see
if we can do something.
And so, that's the reason
why I was wondering
if we can take care of
that ferret for a while.
A ferret, huh?
By the way, what's a ferret?
It's an animal related
to a weasel, Dad.
It's an animal that's been popular
as a pet for quite a while now.
Ferrets are small critters, right?
You know about them?
It was about this big.
If it's for a short while...
If you keep it in a cage,
and take proper care of it,
I don't mind.
Kyouya, Miyuki, what do you think?
I don't have any problems with it.
Neither do I.
And that's that.
Isn't that nice?
Yeah! Thank you!
Now, eat up before it gets cold.
Okay!
Momoko, can you pass me the salad?
Sure, here you go.
Me too.
Coming!
Arisa, Suzuka,
I have permission to raise
the little guy in our house.
Let's go pick it up together after
school tomorrow. --Nanoha
And... sent!
Can you hear me?
Can you hear my voice?
The same voice as last night's
dream, and this afternoon...
Please listen to me.
You can hear my voice.
Please, lend me just
a small bit of your powers!
Is the little guy talking to me?
Please, come to me!
Time is... Danger is now...
Please reach her!
Makihara Veterinary
That sound again?!
That was...
What?! What in the
world is going on?!
You came for me?
It talked!
Well... I really don't know
what's going on here.
What in the world was that?
What's going on?!
You have talent.
Please, lend me just
a small bit of your powers.
Talent?
I came here from a different world,
in order to search for
a certain something.
But I might not be able to fulfill
that wish with my powers alone.
So, I know this will
be a burden for you,
but I want people with
talent to help me out.
I will reward you. I will make sure to!
I want you to use
the powers that I have!
My powers.... The powers of magic!
Magic?
I will make sure to reward you!
This is no time to be talking
about rewards and stuff!
What should I do?!
Take this!
It's warm.
Hold it, close your eyes,
and open your heart.
Repeat after me.
Okay? Here goes!
Yeah.
I am the one who has
been given a mission.
Under the contract,
release those powers.
Um... Under the contract,
Winds to the sky,
stars to the heavens.
And the unyielding soul...
To this heart!
Magic to these hands!
Raging Heart, set up!
Stand by ready. Set up.
What magical power!
Calm down and imagine,
a magical wand that will
control your powers,
and a sturdy armor
that will protect you!
You say that, but everything
being so sudden...
Let's see... let's see...
I think this will do for now!
Success!
What? What? You're kidding!
What is all this?!
What?!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of
cellophane and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying
inside a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining on
the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something I
can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
I'm Nanoha Takamachi.
I thought I was an
ordinary third grader,
but by some stroke of luck
or strange destiny,
I've been assigned as a magical girl!
What kind of fate awaits me now?
And this ferret, whose name
I haven't even asked,
is it all right for me to
raise it at my house?!
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 2: My Magical
Incantation is Lyrical?
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 2: My Magical
Incantation is Lyrical?
Lyrical, magical, I'll do my best!
Episode 2: My Magical
Incantation is Lyrical?