Thank you for coming, Subaru-kun.
Nice to meet you. I am Maho-Maho's father, Misawa Fuuga.
Oh...
Uh, what is the meaning of this?
I would like to thank you all for the guidance you provided to Maho-Maho.
Today is a special day!
What?!
Congratulations, Maho-Maho, Subaru-kun!
M-Marriage?
Maho! What's going on here?!
Subaru and I are going to get married? Nobody told me about this!
M-Marriage is something with oden noodles and miso on top, right?
Oh~, that's konjac.
My, have I made a mistake?
Father, you got it all wrong!
Subaru belongs to everyone!
So, he's going to marry everyone!
That's wrong, too!
I see.
Maho-Maho always seems so happy when talking about you,
that I was led to think you were that close already.
Close?
I'm sorry, Subaru-kun.
Marriage aside, I always wished to meet you.
W-What is it?
Maho-Maho is right. You really are a fabulous man.
I feel safe leaving Maho-Maho in your care.
Thank you very much.
I told you, Subaru is the best coach there is!
Right, everyone?
Yep!
Yes, of course.
Oh~, Onii-chan is the best!
Yes, he's the best.
I see, I see.
You seem more responsible than I expected.
I wouldn't exactly say so...
I apologize for calling you all here today.
I hope I haven't caused you any inconvenience but...
Is there anything I can do to make up for this?
Don't worry about it.
Just ask away!
A personal basketball court,
tickets to watch NBA live,
I can invite the entire Dream Team here!
What?
You're awesome, Father!
Hasegawa-san, what shall we do?
I'm grateful for his offers, but they're all a bit too much...
Excuse me, Fuuga-san...
I do have one favor to ask.
Isn't ForM the brand of Maho's dad?
How annoying.
More importantly, there are special rules for entering.
Teams are limited to five-player teams of grade-school girls.
No substitutions are allowed.
With those rules, our team and Tomoka's team can enter.
Here comes our chance for revenge.
You just wait, stupid Maho.
We definitely won't lose!
It'll be hard to beat Tomoka's team, though.
We may have become stronger, but so have they.
We'll win anyway! Definitely!
I don't really care, let's just start practicing.
We don't have much time.
You don't need to tell us!
We know already!
Tsuba, let's practice here!
Alright, gather around. I've got a special menu to prepare for the tournament.
A special menu?
This sounds like a pretty interesting tourney...
Aya!
Aya, we may be able to meet her soon.
That girl you've always respected.
Really?
Finally, we can meet each other!
Unyaa~, I'm tired...
This training menu is rough...
It's a special training menu that Hasegawa-san thought of for the tournament.
It's tough, but let's give it our all.
Hina-chan, are you okay?
Oh~, if I take a nap here,
I'll lose to Kage.
I'm sure the fifth-graders are working are training a lot, too.
I won't lose to those idiots!
Time for one hundred sit-ups!
Calm down.
Subaru-san told us.
Just believe in ourselves and we'll be fine.
Oh~, if that's Onii-chan said so, I'll believe him.
Me too...
We got this far thanks to Hasegawa-san.
We couldn't enter official tournaments.
And now he prepared such a fantastic stage!
We must give it our best shot and win!
Yeah!
I can't... go on...
No more! I can't move!
Good work!
We'll stop here.
All we've done so far is running.
Is this your special menu?
Does this really help us beat Saki and the others?
I'm sure our coach is just doing this because she's angry.
Masami's been practicing shooting on her own!
Yes, exactly!
What are you talking about? You two started doing passing exercises!
Mimi and Kagetsu have been practicing alone, too!
What are you saying?
Say that to my face!
Calm down, everyone!
Relax, relax...
Maybe we shouldn't enter the tournament after all.
Huh?
W-Why?!
Only teams of five players may enter, remember?
You're arguing about everything.
Do you call this a team?
If you enter now, you'll just lose to the sixth graders.
Can we really beat Saki and the others just with running exercises?
Well, that I don't know.
But if we don't do anything, we'll lose for sure.
We aren't a team, huh...
She was so blunt.
I hate to admit it...
But she's right.
Aoi has a point.
In order to beat Nee-sama and the others,
We not only have to improve our stamina and technique,
but also our teamwork.
So you're saying we've got problems everywhere.
Grade schoolers are the best!
It can't be helped.
I, too, don't want to lose anymore.
This time we'll win for sure!
Thank you for waiting.
Please teach us, coach!
Please!
My girls...
If we do as we're told, we can defeat the sixth graders, right?
I can't guarantee that we win,
but I do know how to figh them evenly.
I'll show you the way!
Let's fight together!
Yes!
You seem all fired up.
Obviously.
There is undoubtedly a difference in skill.
But...
But..?
That's what makes it fun, right?
Well then, allow me to challenge you.
We won't lose.
We won't lose, either.
Let me show you how a wild boar fights.
...Wild boar?
And now...
Let us commence the mini-basketball tournament!
Here's the bracket! Come on!
Oh~, Yamahara is a bunny!
W-wait...
Is that what Fuuga-san's into?
Should I look? Should I not look?
Oh, the bracket seems pretty interesting.
Looks like we'll meet in the semifinals.
Saki! I only have one thing to say to you:
Exactly! If we beat you, we'll become the real basketball team!
No complaints, are there?
Sure.
However, if we win...
Then you'll be our practice assistants for a while.
Eh?
You'll order us around like slaves, am I right?
Well, whatever.
We just have to win.
Exactly as Masami said!
The winners are us anyway!
I'll make you swallow your words!
Oh, I see.
I get it.
If the sixth graders win, you'll have an official club with ten people.
Then you can enter real tournaments.
Tomoka and everyone else came up with it.
I don't know how this will turn out,
but having a partner for practice helps both teams.
But will they really keep their word?
Long time no see, Subaru-kun.
Manaka-senpai!
I've brought the team from Suzuridani.
Good luck today!
Is your leg alright?
Yeah, the surgery went perfectly!
I remember having texted Aoi-chan, but...
I wanted to surprise you, so I kept quiet.
Hey!
Anyway, I'm really happy for you.
I'm not fully recovered yet, but I'm getting there.
Ah, nothing beats a game of basketball!
So, Suzuridani's in, then.
What about Miu-chan and the others?
I'm sorry, but they're not in our starting lineup.
I don't want to brag, but our bench is great.
She's our renowed rookie.
M-My name is Miyakoouji Aya.
Pleased to meet you.
Aya used to be on the gymnastics team,
but as you can see, she's grown a lot taller.
So then I scouted her for the basketball club.
I'm sorry... Even though you scouted me, my basketball skills are terrible.
U-Uhm, are you Airi-san?
Y-Yes, I am.
I knew it! My teammates told me about you.
There's someone taller than me in Keishin.
I'm sure you were surprised when you suddenly grew so much.
It's like the world is running away from you. It's scary.
Hm?
Airi?
I feel the same way.
I love gymnastics, but when I grew taller, I couldn't do them as well.
I started falling behind, so I wanted to try basketball.
But I'm falling behind in basketball as well.
I'm losing my confidence...
We're the same.
When I started playing basketball,
I was terrible and felt like dead weight.
I'm still far from good.
Airi-san, you too?
Yeah, but my height helped me so many times on the court.
I found something only I could do.
So, Aya-chan, you'll be fine, too.
Airi-san...
I'm really glad I could talk to you...
So, so glad.
Me too.
If I can, I'd like to talk with you even more.
Oh~, Airi's so cool!
Subaru! Airi said something that cool!
We shall now commence the match between Keishin Academy's sixth grade team and Wada Basketball Team.
Please meet at court A.
Well then, Subaru-kun...
I'll be waiting for you in the finals.
Don't lose before you get to us, alright?
That's my line.
See you later.
Alright, everyone, let's go!
Okay!
Just play as usual and give it everything you've got!
You'll be fine!
Okay!
Just maintain your rhythm to win!
Do your best, everyone!
We'll win for sure!
Yeah!
Tomo!
Mokkan! Saki!
Alright!
They're fast!
They're not playing mind games but bet on their stamina?
Do they want to make this a contest of speed?
Mokkan!
I won't let you!
Yay, thanks, Maho!
Calm down! We still have plenty of time!
Hina!
Nee-sama, I challenge you!
Oh~, I won't lose!
Looks like a good game.
It's essentially tied.
Wait, the sixth graders are losing?
That's strange.
I thought we were up.
We can win this!
Are they worried about their score?
They keep missing their shots.
A wild boar?
Hey, Subaru!
You're paying too much attention to details, we're falling behind!
Aoi, you're to blame, you keep charging in like a wild boar!
It's working!
They can't keep up with our speed at all!
I can see them clearly!
My legs can still run!
Our practice has paid off!
We were pushed into a corner last time, but today we're in the lead!
Everything's going according to Aoi's plan!
Good work.
Alright, everything's coming along nicely.
Coach, how was my shot?
Was I fast enough?
You're all fantastic! The practice helped a lot!
Can we win like this?
Let's see...
If they keep playing as before, yes.
But that won't matter at all.
We just play our basketball, right?
Exactly. That's the easiest and the hardest part.
However, you can do it now!
Believe in yourselves and believe in everyone else!
Okay!
Alright! Time for the second half, we'll win for sure!
The fifth grade team is getting stronger and stronger.
I'll have to work on my skills as point guard!
That's right, I'll work on my stamina using this conveyor belt sushi!
I feel dizzy...