Hey, everyone, we're
going to start Kaleido Star!
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
What are your fun memories
from when you were small, everyone?
Going places with your mom and
dad, and doing things with them...
You were happy just to be together with them,
and those memories stay with you
no matter how much time goes by.
They're wonderful treasures, aren't they?
Me, I'm here because that day happened.
I won't forget.
So I don't want you all to forget
things, either! I don't! I don't!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Leon.
Leon, are you listening?
Come on, Leon!
I'm listening.
Say, make my training harsher.
I want to perfect the Angel's
Maneuver before the Festival.
This isn't the only year
they'll hold the Festival.
There's no need to rush.
But it's already been more than
five years since we left Alain's...
That's okay, isn't it?
The time hasn't been wasted.
After all, now all kinds of circus troupes
are inviting us to be guest performers,
and we've even been nominated for the
Circus Festival, even if we are in the lowest seat.
That's all because of you.
I'm just an extra bonus.
To make up for my deficiencies, you're
always training yourself without a break.
I want to work harder too!
This is just the habit I've
had since I was a kid, that's all.
Never mind. I'll make
my training harsher myself.
Hey!
I'll perform the Angel's
Maneuver at the Circus Festival.
Perfectly!
Sophie!
Okay, I get it.
We'll toughen up the
practice menu for the Festival.
Only a demon can raise an angel...
"Flight of the Amazing Angel."
The perfect Angel's Maneuver you're
shooting for is just like I told you yesterday.
Have you burned the image into your mind?
Yes.
Then do right-leg-only squats on that log.
But do it without making the water ripple.
If you can't do this,
there's no point in going on.
I understand.
When you can do it on either leg, come get me.
Right!
Come on, let's all do what we need to do.
Okay.
I'll stay with Sora a little longer.
All right, take care of her.
This is going to take a long time, isn't it?
Again...
Do you believe that Sora
will become a true Kaleido Star?
To be honest, I can't tell yet.
I can't tell, but I'm thinking
I'll try betting this on Sora.
You believe in this that much,
but you didn't take any steps
when she went back to Japan?
If she hadn't come back,
it would have meant that was the
highest level player she could be.
Other than invite Leon here,
I haven't done anything.
If I had to say, I suppose all
I did was terminate her contract...
If Sora can really become a true Kaleido Star,
no matter how many detours she takes,
I'm sure she'll find her own path.
And in fact, she did come back.
Or rather, it's almost as if the stage is in
love with her and doesn't want to let her go.
In love?
In that case, perhaps what
I'm feeling right now is jealousy.
Kalos, I have one proposal.
I want some move...
I want a new move to
compete with the Angel's Maneuver.
Softly...
Aw, it's rippling!
No good...
I wonder if I can really do this...
Sora!
Huh?
You've stopped already, Sora?
Sora?
I-I-I g-g-got a l-l-little c-c-cold...
Thanks for the food!
It's warming me up!
You can't push yourself too hard!
I know...
It's a good thing Marion was with you.
Sora!
Hey, will you take a look at this?
Mia! Did you get an idea?
Yep! I've talked about it with
Miss Cathy too, and I think it might be good,
but I wonder what you'll think, Sora.
The rest of you shout out
your opinions too, okay?
How cute!
Aren't they just?
Now, there are a lot of different
interpretations of Swan Lake,
but the most orthodox one is that
even though they defeat the demon,
Odette and Prince Siegfried both die
and they're joined together in Heaven.
What about Odile, the demon princess?
That's right! That's the mystery!
After she's tricked the prince,
she disappears from the story!
Odile loved the prince too, right?
Can't there be a story where
Odile gets to be happy too?
I thought you'd say that.
And so I tried thinking of Odile
as another personality that lives inside Odette.
Odette is the loving heart
that cares for the prince,
and Odile is the hate that heart, which
wanted a monopoly on love, gave birth to.
Even though they're in conflict,
what they seek is the same.
Odette realizes that hate too is a form of love,
and her love grows to be so
great that it encompasses everything.
Hate is love too...
Odette accepts Odile's hate,
and she turns into love itself.
I want to try expressing that
Odette with the Angel's Maneuver!
A happy ending!
Not bad!
Truly an angel.
Really?
Sora?
Sora, is something wrong with it?
Oh, no, I think it's good! It's really great!
I was wondering if I could
really play such a great angel.
There's nothing to fear on that score!
Because I've written it all tailored
to your normal personality, Sora!
Okay.
Yay!
All right, I'm starting to get fired up!
The angel Mia envisions...
So she accepts her hatred, and becomes a
great love that encompasses everything, huh?
That might be something
a true star needs to do too.
But I crumbled under the atmosphere
of the Circus Festival and ran away.
Can I become that kind of angel?
An angel, huh?
We've decided that Kaleido Stage's first
show after its reopening will be Swan Lake.
The lead, Sora Naegino, will present
to you the maneuver of a true Kaleido Star.
I hear the Angel's Maneuver will be used?
Sora Naegino failed in the
Circus Festival, didn't she?
I have enough confidence
in her to open the show.
She hasn't mastered it yet, has she?
Mr. Leon, are you satisfied
with Sora Naegino as a partner?
Of course I am.
It's rippling...
It's no good.
The rippling of the water
is a wavering of the heart.
She cannot become a true star
while she still harbors uncertainty.
The angel Mia envisioned for me...
An angel who accepts even hatred.
She accepts battles,
hatred, and everything else.
If I can't do that,
maybe I can't become a true Kaleido Star
even if I do perfect the Angel's Maneuver.
The reality is, you won
against me and got the lead role.
After all, when all's said and
done, I'm competing with May.
What do you mean, you don't want to battle?!
You're just running away
from the competition, that's all!
You should think carefully about how
much your attitude just now hurt May.
It's impossible to become a star without
being hated or begrudged by anybody.
If I admit that a stage without hatred or
fighting is a dream that will never be realized,
I won't have to agonize like this.
So you're thinking that the
best thing is for you to have it easy?
But you shouldn't forget the feelings of
the people who are watching, now should you?
I know that, but...
Then...
instead of a sports bra, one with more frills or
something would be more pleasing to look at...
What are you doing?!
What do you mean, "what"?
I was just trying to unpack your boxes for you!
Out of goodwill!
Thanks, but no thanks.
I see...
I thought you were giving me advice for once.
Yes, advice about your underwear--
Thanks, but no thanks!
If you've become uncertain,
it's also important to try taking a
break from practice to change your mood.
But...
Are you confident you can do it just
by throwing yourself into it headlong?
Well...
Then your chances are the same either way.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe I'll try going to Cape Mary Park;
I haven't been there in ages.
While you're at it, it would be great
if you'd buy some panties with ruffles.
I won't!
No uncertainty there, huh...
I guess even people who look happy sometimes
fight and hate while I'm not there to see them.
I should have kept practicing after all.
This isn't making me feel even a bit better...
Angels...
It's no good, I don't get it.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Um, I didn't notice you there...
Is he okay?
Yes, he's not hurt.
Good boy. You handled that so well, Love.
Good dog.
Thank goodness. I'm sorry!
It looks like that wasn't intentional, then.
Of course not!
Some people do intentionally step on his feet or
his tail when they realize he's a seeing-eye dog.
Intentionally?
Yes.
Seeing-eye dogs are trained not to bark
while they're working, no matter what happens.
So they step on him to check and see if he will.
I'm Donna Walker, his trainer.
This boy's name is Love.
He's training to be a seeing-eye dog.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I'm sorry, Love. It must've hurt, huh?
Miss Sora Naegino?
Not the one that's slated
for the lead role in Swan Lake?
Um, yes!
Skipping practice?
Kalos contacted me,
saying he by all means wanted me
to come and watch a true star be born.
But skipping is bad, isn't that right, Love?
For the boss to contact
her directly... Who is she?
But I feel like I've seen
her somewhere before...
Well, we're still in the middle of training.
Go straight, Love!
You're the Donna Walker who played Alice?!
Yes.
I'm a huge fan of yours!
Oh, that's right, could
you please sign my shirt?!
Yay! Thank you so much!
I'm sorry I ended up following you
all the way to your training ground.
That's okay, it's kind of a nice
feeling thinking that you're my fan.
I'm not the only one! Miss Layla is too!
But you'd already quit when
Miss Layla joined the troupe, huh?
Yes. I couldn't bear to
stand on the stage anymore.
The pain of having to climb to the top
even if it meant stepping on someone
and the pressure of thinking
someone might overtake me someday.
It seemed to me like everyone
around me had demons' hearts.
So one day, I ran away.
I couldn't work up the
desire to be on stage again.
But... But your shows
were fun, and they sparkled.
They were really great!
I believe that Alice if nothing else
was bathed in smiles onstage and off!
That you couldn't have had hatred or fighting...
Normally I'd tell you you were right,
but you're a stage performer.
So I'll tell you the truth.
Then you mean...
Yes. The reason I couldn't
endure any longer was because
I felt like I was deceiving
audience members like you, Sora.
Love, up!
But I was mistaken in my thinking.
These dogs taught me that.
They're angels.
Angels?
Yep, slightly mischievous angels.
Excuse me, what does it
mean that the dogs are angels?
Please tell me!
It might be scary at first.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Love, up!
Go straight!
Don't brace against him.
Right!
So fast...
Wait, that's too fast!
Love, stop!
Were you scared?
Yeah.
But that was slower than a normal walking pace.
Really?!
Love felt your unease through the
harness and walked slowly for you.
Now, trust Love and try it again.
Okay.
Love, go!
Huh? This might be
going well. It might! It might!
Huh? Wait, where are you going, Love?
That's not the right way...
Ow!
He tried to avoid an obstacle.
Follow where Love leads you.
Right.
Huh?
Go!
What's wrong? Love, go!
Sora, take off your mask.
If this were a real street,
you could have been hit by a car.
Good dog, Love. Good boy.
You praise him too, Sora.
Good boy, Love! Thanks!
Good dog! Very good!
Was that hard?
Yes.
They do all kinds of training like this.
But only about one in
three become seeing-eye dogs.
The others become normal pet dogs.
Poor things...
Do you think the dogs are
being forced to train, Sora?
They're not?
Look closely. Do they
look like they're suffering?
No, they look very happy.
They know that if they follow
instructions, we'll be pleased.
The thing that makes them the happiest
is to please the people they're with.
Come! Love, come!
These creatures wish only to
make those around them happy.
That's why I think they're angels.
Back then, I could only
see everyone's bad sides,
but after I met these guys,
I realized "Oh, it wasn't like that."
Everyone who stands on the stage
must have an angel's heart inside
that wants to give the audience a
good time and make everyone happy.
It's just that the feeling of
"I can do this better than her"
changes that angel heart to hatred.
I'm sure you must have seen everyone's
angel hearts as you watched us on stage.
Everyone's angel hearts...
Yes.
Although I couldn't see them back then.
I see... During the Festival,
I couldn't see them either.
When Mute and the others were
talking about their dreams with their friends,
their eyes weren't lying.
Everyone else had dreams too...
They all had angel hearts that wanted
to give the audience a good time...
And battles and hatred were
the other side, the result of that.
"Hate is love too"... so that's what it meant?
In that case...
You have a really serious look
on your face, so Love is worried.
Love, thanks!
Thanks to you, I think I can move forward again!
Sora.
Yes?
I've got high hopes for
the birth of the true star.
Yes! Thank you!
Maybe the Angel's Maneuver
isn't a maneuver to become an angel,
maybe it's a maneuver to wake up
the angel hearts inside everyone.
No, I'm sure that's what it is!
I'll believe in the angel inside me.
I'll believe in the angels inside everyone!
I'll believe in the Angel's Maneuver!
Go for it, Sora!
Something's different than
it was up until yesterday, huh?
Maybe she's freed herself from her doubts.
Won't doing it that slowly
actually cause more wavering?
No, the log isn't wavering.
The water's not rippling!
She did it!
Right leg: success!
Amazing!
Impressive as always, Sora!
You did it!
She can really do it!
What kind of woman is she?!
It appears she's cleared the
first stage. Let's return home.
Yes, ma'am.
Like, yes.
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation, I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
I can't show the audience something fake!
And so, Sora's intense training began.
Why are you going that far? Stop this!
I won't stop!
I've come to get back my
dream that I entrusted to you,
or rather, the thing
I left forgotten on the stage.
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Injured Swan."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...