Good morning, Nayu.
You're up early on a Sunday.
Yeah.
I'll wash your pajamas, so go and get dressed.
Okay.
Not again, Nayu.
If you're going to change, do it in your room.
Ah, right.
She seems pretty down.
It's pretty unexpected, considering it's Nayu.
Striped bra
Polka-dot panties
Her bra and panties didn't match.
I wonder if she caught a cold or something.
Between Adults and Children
What?
You have to go to the office again today?
When I turned in the sample for my latest design, they told me that it wasn't really what they were looking for.
It's an emergency meeting.
I see. You're busy, Keigo-san.
Is there something you wanted to talk about?
No, it's nothing.
Nayu...
Is there something you want to talk to me about?
What? Oh, um...
I want you to do my hair.
Do you have the time to do this? Is it alright?
It's fine. It's fine.
When Nayu couldn't do her own hair,
I used to tie it up for her in place of her late mother.
When Nayu has her hair down, it's Nayu's way of telling me she wants to be by me.
Seriously, she's still such a kid.
What is it?
You know, for some reason,
Keigo-san's hand calms me down.
Well? What happened?
Why don't you tell me about it?
W-Well...
I see.
During your Underwear Club fitting, some boys peeped and turned it into a disaster.
Yes.
I caused trouble for all the people who showed up and for my friends who helped me.
And on top of that, I was scolded by a teacher and won't let me make an Underwear Club anymore.
Well, I can't blame them for wanting to peep.
To boys, underwear fuels a lot of their fantasies.
Boys around your age starts expressing interest in girls,
and girls start taking interest in boys.
Just as your body grows and develops,
your heart and mind mature as well.
Yoko-san also used to say, that love and underwear are inseparable.
Love?
Well, regarding the Underwear Club, you just have to gradually get everyone to understand it.
I wonder if it's a package?
I'll go get it.
Who is it?
It's Komachi.
Komachi-kun...
Um, I'm surprised you found your way here.
I asked your cram school teacher.
Oh, I see.
*Stare*
No, it's not like that.
I'm starting to feel a little lonely.
I told you, it's not like that!
Well, I've got to get ready for work.
Um, why are you here?
I'm sorry.
W-What? What's wrong?
It's my fault that the Underwear Club member recruitment got messed up.
I know my apology can't make up for it.
You didn't do anything wrong, Komachi-kun.
You even beat up the ones who were peeping.
And because of that, it became a huge commotion.
Not at all...
I see.
So if there's anything I can do, let me know.
I don't want to owe any favors to girls.
B-But you don't need to do anything.
It's fine, so just tell me!
You really don't need to do anything.
Tsukamoto-Sensei already said she wouldn't allow an Underwear Club.
And you're just accepting that?
Is it fine for you to go along with what she said?
Are you feelings toward underwear that weak?
Would you really give up if someone tells you you can't do it?
Damn that Tsukamoto, acting all high and mighty.
You shouldn't give up so easily!
If you can't make a club, there's always the option of making an appreciation society!
If you're a man, see it through!
B-But I'd never be able to do it alone.
And I'm not a man, either.
There's nothing else I can do.
Then, I'll make one with you.
Um, really?
Oh dear...
I'm going now.
Are you sure? It's underwear.
A man never goes back on his word, probably.
That's right. It's okay for boys to join as well, right?
It seems that you're always taking care of me, Komachi-kun.
I don't really get it, but if you're gonna thank me, then do it!
Thank you, Komachi-kun.
Y-You're always getting way too close to me.
Get up already.
Huh? Why am I getting so embarrassed today?
Those who have finished, hurry up and go outside.
Ah, Sensei.
Hayama-san. I'm sorry about the Underwear Club.
But don't give up, okay?
No, I've given up on it.
Instead, I'm going with making an Underwear Appreciation Society.
I see...
I see. Even if the school doesn't approve it, you can still carry out the activities.
Yes. I won't get a club room or funding, though.
If it's an Appreciation Society, I'd be able to participate in both Kendo Club and Society.
Isn't that right, Mizuno-Sensei?
It should be okay... I guess.
Yako-chan!
Maybe I should join it as well.
Thank you, Haruka-chan!
With you two included, we'll have four members!
Don't you mean three?
Komachi-kun said he'd join, too.
Komachi-kun said himself that he'd become a member.
He was also the one who told me to make an Appreciation Society.
He encouraged me not to give up.
I don't know much about him...
But he's a boy and wouldn't it be tough to run an Underwear-based Appreciation Society with boys involved?
Looks tight.
Haruka-chan, just a moment.
W-What?
I thought your bra looked a little tight.
Haruka-chan, haven't your breasts gotten bigger since the fitting?
But I got some larger-sized bras not long ago.
It's almost my time of the month, so that might be it.
Your time of the month?
Oh, right. Sometimes your breasts will swell during your period.
I see. It's exactly as the book said.
Sorry. I'm so childish.
Don't worry about. That's one of Nayu's good points.
She's got a great figure. She looks like a model.
Truly, you really are like a bunch of virgins.
Listen up, Class E students.
Everyone hurry up, next is your eye exam in the nurse's office.
Okay.
Oh yeah. I was thinking of meeting up and talking about the Underwear Appreciation Society today.
Sure, sounds good.
It's fine by me.
Sensei, would you like to participate as well?
M-Me too?
You're our advisor.
I really am their advisor.
Welcome, Sensei. Come on in.
Thank you.
Where are your parents? I want to greet them.
Nayu.
Your friends are staying over, right? What should I make for dinner?
Sensei, this is my older brother.
It can't be...
It can't be... Senpai?
Senpai?
It's me, Mizuno from First High!
Mizuno-san?
Yes!
Mizuno-Sensei?
He was my Senpai during high school.
I wouldn't have guessed that he's Hayama-san's older brother.
I'm really surprised.
Does Sensei wear her loved one's panties as well?
I'm surprised to learn your brother was Mizuno-Sensei's senpai.
I know, right?
What is it, Yako-chan?
I was just wondering if string panties really do come undone if you pull on them.
There are some that come undone,
but there are some sewn together.
Which type are these?
Hayama-san?
Was the bath too hot?
Please sit down and relax, Sensei.
I can't do that, Senpai.
I'm sorry for coming and eating dinner like this.
And instead of calling me "Sensei," please call me by my family name the way you did in high school.
I'm surprised you remember me even though I joined the Paranormal Club the summer of my Second Year.
Well, you know...
But you suddenly stopped showing up in the middle of the season.
I guess. Things were pretty hectic at home back then.
Is that so?
Senpai?
Oh, but I do somehow remember you, Mizuno-san.
You already had huge breasts back then.
The only thing anyone remembers about me are my breasts.
Sorry, sorry.
My eyes did that instinctively because of my grandmother's influence.
Your grandmother was an underwear designer, too?
Yeah. She was really busy and rarely at home,
She was really cool and a grandma I can be proud of.
Your brother is amazing too. Not many men can cook like that.
It was definitely good, but...
Thanks for having us over.
G-Good evening.
Welcome. Let's see, Yako-chan and...
Ah of course, the busty Haruka-chan.
I'm just not very good with guys.
What is it, Nayu-chan?
Oh, sorry.
What?
Haruka-chan, do you have someone you like?
Haruka, since when?
There isn't anyone like that!
What kind of stuff are you saying out of the blue, Nayu-chan?
S-Sorry.
This morning, Keigo-san said my grandma used to say that love and underwear have an inseparable relationship.
Love and underwear?
I didn't really understand what he meant.
He also said our hearts and minds develop into adults just like our bodies.
But my body's still really child-like.
I wonder if I'll understand if I find someone I like.
I see. Nayu-chan doesn't have someone she likes yet.
Why do I feel so relieved?
I think I'll get out now.
Me too. I stayed in too long.
I wonder if it's okay for a child like me to make an appreciation society?
That reminds me, it sounded like that girl knew what she was talking about.
Isn't that the underwear used during sex?
She said some pretty outrageous things.
Maybe she's already an adult.
They still haven't come out yet.
Well, I should get going.
Eh? You aren't staying overnight?
Eh?! It's too soon- that's not it!
I'd be causing trouble.
No, not really.
If you need a change of clothes, I've got a mountain of trial products.
Is that so?
You have a pretty bust line.
I got scolded by Hayama-san the other day and bought some new bras.
It seems I wasn't wearing the right size bra.
She said that underwear is supposed to protect the body, but mine had the opposite effect.
Will protect you, huh?
To Nayu, underwear really is something that protects her.
Eh? What do you mean?
When my father and stepmother died, she started wetting the bed.
They had an accident while traveling.
It hasn't even been six months.
And they have such a young child.
In the end, Nayu's grandmother took us in.
So that's why you couldn't show up for club activities.
I had no idea.
I think Nayu was pushing herself back then as well.
Thank you, Nayu-chan.
I'll help you out!
However...
Nayu-chan?
What are you doing up so early?
You know that I can take care of the laundry.
It's fine.
But...
You don't need to wash this one!
That happened another two or three times.
I'm sorry.
Nayu-chan, I'm not angry.
Come on, give me your panties so I can wash them.
It's fine. I can wash them by myself.
It's fine.
My, My. Siblings fighting this early in the morning?
Yoko-san...
What's wrong? Aren't those the panties that I made?
I'm sorry, grandma. I ruined the panties.
I'm happy that you're wearing the the panties I designed, Nayu.
Listen carefully, Nayu. Underwear exists to protect girls.
Protect?
That's right.
Underwear will gently envelop and protect your body, Nayu.
I can't always be with you because I'm busy with work,
but I'll always protect you with the underwear I make.
so don't worry. It's okay to get them dirty.
Sensei.
Y-Yes?
Please look after Nayu.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Sensei, are you going home?
I wanted to hear stories from your high school days.
I'll see you all at school.
Thank you for the dinner.
Sensei, take care.
My heart is pounding.
Made to protect us, huh?
Is it okay if I go over there?
This reminds me of an elementary school camping trip.
Let's work hard at the Underwear Appreciate Society.
Yeah. We forgot to discuss about it.
Tickle Attack.
Wai-Stop, Yako-chan.
Nayu.
Nayu, I'm coming in.
They're still just a bunch of kids.
Nayu, girls. It's time to wake up.
Class 1-A
Well? What does an Underwear Society do?
I wonder what we should start with.
Listen, you...
Let's do what we can with the four of us.
You're always getting way too close to me!
Sorry...
Nayu-chan must not pay any attention to boys.
Is this the Underwear Appreciation Society?
Amahara...
You know her, Komachi-kun?
Yeah, I know her.
I'm Kiyono. Amahara Kiyono.
Amahara Kiyono-san...
Mind if I join you?
Do you all know your three sizes?
94, 61, 86.
That's an hourglass figure.
What about you, Haruka-chan?
Let's measure them now, then.
Take off your clothes.
That's intense.
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
Wild Adolescence