That's not right!
You idiot!
Ow...
I don't care if it hurts.
It might be a replica,
but you're still in the same armor
the Blue Knight wore in the old stories.
Yeah, but...
Plus, you don't listen to me when
I try to teach you how knights act.
You can't even draw your blade properly.
Huh?
I can't get it out.
Are you daft?!
The sword is a knight's soul!
You need to be more careful with it!
You're going to get it
if you break that sword!
I-I understand.
Your Highness, Satomi-sama,
tea is served.
Ruth-san...
Oh, well.
Guess we'll take a break.
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
My Knight
I was surprised.
I can't believe Satomi-sama's measurements match
the Blue Knight in the legends perfectly.
I thought there might be a
malfunction since the armor
didn't automatically adjust itself,
but I guess there are some
amazing coincidences.
By the way, Ruth, what about the ship we saw?
We haven't detected anything since.
What ship are you talking about?
A Fortorthen ship appeared near
this planet the other day.
We detected a space-time
quake when it arrived,
but we haven't been able to
determine anything further since then.
It's Clan. The second crown princess
to the Fortorthe Galactic Empire,
Clariossa Daora Fortorthe.
It has to be her.
She's your rival, then, Tulip?
But, you don't have any evidence, right?
Why do you think it's this Clan girl?
Having no evidence is evidence itself.
Clan's ship, the Rougetsu, has a stealth
system she developed herself.
It reduces her combat capabilities, however.
Anyway, let's get back to training.
What? Already?
Come on. Let's go.
Can't we take a longer break?
No. We might as well...
You don't have to push.
Hercules-chan, here's some food.
Hey Yurika, how long do we have to keep him?
I don't know... The club's vice
president still hasn't finished moving.
Those are some big pincers.
We, uh, well..
What type of bug is that?
You don't know, Ruth?
No. It's my first time seeing one.
His name is Hercules-chan.
I see. He's pretty cute.
Are you okay, Satomi-kun?
I heard you were going through
a lot of training, but...
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll do what I must to help the play!
The Neanderthal messed up again.
How many times do I have to tell him?
Hasn't he gotten pretty good at
standing and walking now, though?
You must have worked pretty hard, Theia-dono.
So, Kiriha, why are you wearing that?
Weren't you supposed to be a stage-hand?
The person who was supposed to
play the priest caught a cold.
She matches pretty well, so
I asked her to take over.
I haven't had much time, so I haven't
read through the whole thing.
Don't start crying after you read it.
Hey, everyone!
We're going to start
rehearsing the first scene.
Okay, let's do this.
Sure.
Koutarou, if you forget a
line, I'll help you out.
Right. Thanks.
Hm?
Koutarou?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I've just never seen that girl before.
But, if you take our side now
that we've been dethroned,
you'll be turning against all of Fortorthe.
You may be correct, Princess Alaia.
Then, you shouldn't...
But my pride and my
loyalty won't allow it,
and most importantly,
I don't think we should turn
against the hearts of the Fortorthen people.
It feels like what really happened...
But, why am I here?
Why isn't the Blue Knight
trying to protect me, instead?
Then, tell me just one thing...
Anything you wish.
You have a crest on your chest marking
you a knight of the royal house.
Your appearance, your mannerisms,
and your prideful heart...
There's no question you're
a knight of Fortorthe,
but... but I do not recognize
that house crest on your sword.
From whence have you come?
I have come from beyond untold
time and untold distance.
Where are you from?
I have come from beyond untold
time and untold distance.
That was the same thing I was told...
But, why?
Did the Blue Knight...
Watch out, Theia-dono!
The light!
Are you injured, Your Highness?
The Blue Knight...
I'm glad you okay.
Can you stand, Tulip?
Blue Knight, you're hurt!
Oh, I am.
Don't worry. No big deal.
But, the Blue Knight got
hurt because of me—
It's fine, I said.
I'm not really the Blue Knight, anyway.
S-Sorry...
I was kind of jumbled
up there for a second...
R-Right.
So, this wasn't an accident...
You think this Clan person
was trying to get Theia?
Yeah. She's stealthy...
She's good at hide-and-seek.
Always hiding in the shadows.
A royal shouldn't be doing that.
Do they not get along?
Yes...
They're rivals in both house and name,
and since their personalities
are polar opposites,
they often clash with each other.
Oh yeah, she was talking about
that at the hot springs.
She can't lose in all of
this because of her mother.
You can't show your
rival any weakness, huh?
Theia-dono, you'll have to think about
a way to deal with her, I assume.
Yes, but you could say that
things are actually safe for now.
If Clan was really trying to get rid of
me, she wouldn't leave behind evidence.
If Fortorthe found out about what happened,
Clan would be excised from
her right to the throne.
So, she's not so short-sighted.
I'm sure if she wanted to take you out,
she would have attacked you
with her ship, or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's still
something to worry about.
You should make sure you
protect me, then, Neanderthal.
Isn't that your job, Blue Knight?
You know, you only call me the Blue
Knight when it's convenient to you.
Okay. We should be finished
with our final rehearsal.
I want everyone to have fun
at the party tonight, and rest
up before the play tomorrow!
Dismissed!
Right!
No!
I want to go to the party, too!
I want to have fun!
No.
You're practicing more so
you become a proper knight.
Come on, Theia. I wanted to
go have fun with Koutarou.
Don't worry so much, Sanae.
If Koutarou really wanted to leave,
I'm sure he'd find a way to escape.
So, you mean Koutarou
really wants to practice?
You know, he's really kind
at the weirdest times.
Why can't he only be nice to me?
Hey Neanderthal, your
stance got worse again!
You know, Tulip,
it's a pretty hard to draw a sword
without changing your stance.
I don't need any excuses!
If you have time to complain,
you have time to practice!
Now get to it, before I beat it into you!
I'm going to get you back for
this, Princess Theiamillis!
No, you won't.
Like this.
Like this, right?
No!
Hey, this is right, isn't it?
No, like this!
Satomi-kun never acts that way around me.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
How was the party?
It was fun,
but I need to give Hercules-chan some food.
Weather Forecast
The skies will be clear until about noon,
and overcast in the afternoon.
It's a new show! We're back with
more fighting after you demanded it!
Rhinoceros Man, Second Impact!
Rhinoceros Man
2nd Impact
The legendary Yamato Beetle is back!
Along with three others...
Atlas,
Caucasus,
and Hercules...
You need to see these
rhinoceros beetles fight!
Rhinoceros Man, Second Impact!
I see...
So, Hercules-chan is a rhinoceros beetle.
Shoo! Shoo!
Stay away!
Shoo!
Well, I guess that works.
R-Really? That was good?
There's some problems,
but I'll let you off with that.
Yay! I'm done!
I told you to act like a knight
when you're dressed like that.
S-Sorry.
Hm? What's that?
The dance music for the party.
A dance, huh?
I haven't danced in a while.
Teach me how to dance.
Hm?
You taught me how to be a knight,
but you haven't taught me anything else.
You need to know that kind
of thing to be fancy, right?
Ow!
Don't step on my feet!
Sorry. It's difficult to follow the steps—
You're going to give me
compound fractures in my foot!
What's going on?
I thought he'd be bored
with all the practice.
Thanks for watching the place.
Was there anyone who entered
the gym while I was gone?
Nope!
Harumi-chan came for a second,
but left without coming inside.
I see.
That's fine.
Keep guard.
Right!
So, Theia-chan's involved
in a family quarrel?
Guess she really is a princess.
She acts like she's not
in danger at all, though.
Save me, everyone!
Yurika? What's wrong?!
Ruth-san found out that
Hercules-chan is a rhinoceros beetle,
and she looks really angry,
and she's chasing after me!
What are you doing?!
Anyway, we'll need to hide you.
How about you hide in the shed over there?
Once Ruth comes, we'll make something up.
Sis, Ruth-chan is coming!
Come on, Yurika!
Hurry!
Y-Yes!
R-Ruth!
You're here?
Did something happen?
You're over there?
This is bad.
She's so angry, she's not listening to us.
What should we do?
You're really bad at this.
It's my first time. You can't blame me.
You messed up again.
You're supposed to go right.
It might be right for you,
but it's left for me.
Silly.
Your Highness... and Satomi-sama...
Where am I?
What was I doing?
Sis, emergency alert!
We've detected a spacial
distortion within the gym!
What?
Theia-dono, Koutarou, we've got an intruder!
Clan, huh?
That's correct, Theiamillis-san.
Clan!
That's Clan?
She was...
I didn't think you'd try to attack me directly.
Did you build that weapon on this planet?!
The level of science here is so
poor, it took quite a bit of time.
If she created the weapon from materials
she gathered here on this planet,
Fortorthe won't be able
to determine anything!
I went through all this effort, and it's
all going to end with this one shot.
Kind of anti-climatic.
Damn.
Something's strange...
Why was Clan here before?
She was hiding this entire time...
So why would she risk herself
to mess with that light?
Maybe there's a reason why she needed
to come here to get rid of Theia?
That's enough!
I just have to hit you with something harder.
Blue Knight, pulse laser!
As you wish, My Princess.
Cancel it, Tulip!
Neanderthal, don't get in my way!
She wants you to use your weapon!
What are you saying?!
Believe me, Theia!
Your Highness! Satomi-sama!
Are you okay, Theia?!
I-I'm fine. You saved me...
What just happened?
It seems that Clan had rigged it so that if a
weapon appeared, it would explode instead.
She knew that if she provoked the princess,
she'd use a weapon...
She didn't come here just to
mess with the light before.
She also came to make sure
that explosion would happen.
Why'd you have to go and do that?
I won't let some savage from out
here in the boonies ruin my plan!
Koutarou!
We're here to help you!
No problem!
You guys, protect the princess.
Thanks!
Wait, Koutarou!
You can't fight by yourself!
Let me help!
Your Highness,
the battlefield is for your knight.
An imperial princess musn't dare to enter it.
B-But...
If you won't believe in me,
then how can I come out victorious?
I am your knight.
Koutarou...
My knight...
Here I come, Clan!
Don't make me laugh, you
knockoff Blue Knight replica!
And you're only trying to keep people down!
What are you going to do
with that blunt sword?
What's going on?!
This can't be!
A replica can't have the same
power as the real Signaltin!
That light from the sword...
That light... It's the same as...
That sword should have that power...
Could it be that you're the real...
I just need to take you out first!
Koutarou!
I'll handle it!
Sanae-chan Tulip Part II!
A cat, huh?
That's what you're worried
about, Shizuka-sama?!
Hey! What are you?!
People call me the Schweiger Moon, and
I was defeated by some Neanderthal?
Give up.
You've lost.
This is all your fault.
No one back home should have any problems
if I attack you with my ship, Rougetsu.
What?
This is bad.
Run, Koutarou!
Run... where?!
It's too late now.
Rougetsu, atomize this Blue Knight!
As you wish, My Princess.
Burn in hell.
I'm not so sure about that.
Here you go!
That's...
Hoisted by your own petard.
Bye!
Clan got away.
You don't need to chase after her?
It doesn't matter.
Trying to find her would be a waste of time.
You did a good job today.
Yeah.
I'm pretty exhausted though.
There is something I have to tell you.
Sorry, it broke.
I see.
I guess it did.
Huh? You're not going to get mad?
You kept saying that the sword
is the soul of a knight.
You don't understand anything, do you?
Huh?
A sword represents the promise
that a knight has made.
It is that promise that shouldn't yield,
not so much the sword of itself.
Why don't you understand something so simple?
All right!
I'm going to have you start knight training!
W-Why?!
We're all done with that, right?!
No, we're not!
If I let a half-assed knight like you go,
I'll be an embarrassment
to the Mastil family.
We're starting training tomorrow!
No!
Let me off!
This is not happening.
I can't believe I lost.
Oh, well.
I didn't want to use this while
I was developing it, but...
Goodbye, Theiamillis.
Farewell—
Oh no...
I'm going to fall!
Ow...
Hm?
Who are you?!
I'm going to make this all not have happened.
For Hercules-chan.
Hey, what about Yurika?
Yurika-sama was here?
No, nothing you have to worry about, Ruth.
Right...
Shouharu Festival
So, the festival ended without incident.
Princess Clan returned home.
You performed your duties well.
I would normally reward someone
with whatever they requested,
however, I am unfortunately
unable to do that for you.
I have decided to bestow
upon you the title of knight
as a way to show my appreciation.
However, I imagine you would not like
being treated like my subordinate.
That is why I have come at this hour.
Ruth is my only witness, as well.
Forgive me, Koutarou.
I know of no other way to show my thanks.
You may laugh at the fact that I have
been sheltered my entire life.
Until I came to this land,
I wasn't aware there was another
way for me to live my life.
Satomi Koutarou, I, Theiamillis
Gre Mastil-Sagrada Von Fortorthe,
give you the position of knight,
and the title of "Theiamillis' Blue Knight".
Rest well, my knight.
What's this game?
Pop-up Something
I'm not good at this.
I always strike out...
on the first turn.
Next Episode: An Evil Magical Girl Appears?!
That's...
Pretty impressive.