Damn.
A third one?
Looks like the bastard's only going after kids.
But Yama, the victims aren't children. They're high school girls.
They're in school, making 'em kids.
Hell, you too.
Some detective you are, getting sick at the sight of blood.
Too bad you decided to grow boobs instead of brains, kid.
Yama, I'm pretty sure that's sexual harra—
Ah, can it. Let's get going!
Hey, wait up.
So you think you know where the suspect went?
I'll be damned if I don't find this rat.
I don't care if he doesn't actually kill 'em.
Putting kids in the hospital is goddamn disgusting.
Now get your ass moving before I move it for you, Tsukino.
Yama, I'm positive that's sexual harrassment!
Just shut your pie hole and get!
Ouch.
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
Stop!
Why?
Please, let me go!
Help!
Help me!
Then I passed out.
Everyone is Around Me
And I woke up in a hospital bed.
So that's what happened.
And what did the doctors say?
Well, it seems I'm perfectly healthy.
They told me it was probably anemia, said I should watch my diet,
and bundled me out of the hospital as quickly as they could.
Well, I'm glad it was nothing serious.
At least you got your power back, right?
Yeah.
Actually, I'm most curious about what you saw with that power.
Tell you what: I bet it's nothing serious.
You probably just walked past someone coming home from a horror movie.
We can't say that for sure.
A THIRD VICTIM Random Attacks!?
Wh-What is this?
You hadn't heard?
There's been a string of seemingly random assaults.
R-Random assaults?
Yes. The victims are all high school girls.
The most recent one was from our school.
What?!
From our school?
How do you know? It doesn't say that here.
Word does get around though.
The rumor is all over school.
So that explains it.
I thought the mood around school seemed a little weird.
They really weren't just talking dirty behind my back?!
S-So, there's a chance the mind I read was the criminal's?
Did you see the person's face?
There were a lot of people around. I couldn't tell who it was.
Do you think the criminal saw you?
We only passed each other by, so I doubt it.
The police! We've gotta call the police!
And tell them we read the criminal's mind?
They'd never listen.
Honestly, I think you're in the clear even if the criminal did see you.
No one would ever suspect that you can actually read minds.
Y-You're right.
That settles it. I'm sure the police will catch this crook soon enough.
I'm sure.
For the time being, don't let yourself get all hot and bothered about this.
R-Right.
So this is the kinda thing that turns Kotoura on?
Pay attention. This is not the time for dirty jokes.
Right.
Don't take it so seriously.
It's not like there's anything we can do.
I've read a lot of minds since I was little.
A lot of those minds weren't very nice.
Many of them were bad.
But still.
This is the first time I've seen something so awful.
I'm scared, Manabe. I'm really scared.
Kotoura, this little hand is so tiny and smooth and soft!
It'll be okay. I'm here for you.
Stupid.
I'll come pick you up again tomorrow.
Okay. Thanks for walking me home.
See you.
Manabe!
I-I just can't do it!
Please don't leave me alone!
S-Say whaaa—?!
Clear your mind, Yoshihisa.
Be ice in the calm moonlight.
Do not unveil your lust to Kotoura while she's upset!
H-Here.
Uh, oh.
It's getting dark.
I really should be heading home.
But how could I?
I can't spend the night here, though.
That would...
I-I trust you, Manabe.
What?! Can it be?!
I don't wanna go home tonight...
Is that what's happening here?!
So wrong it hurts!
Wait, what do you mean "go home"!?
I live here!
Grrrlm
Sit tight. I'll make some dinner.
Sure.
Man, that was great.
Your cooking is seriously delicious, Kotoura.
I'm glad you liked it.
OK, now that dinner's out of the way...
I'm gonna run over to my house for a minute.
I still have to change and get my school stuff for tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll be back soon, but don't forget to lock up.
I won't.
Later, then.
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
O my father! Mother mine! Hell, even brother dearest:
Behold! This is the day Yoshihisa becomes a man!
Aw yeah!
Fear Meter
With Manabe
Alone
Now what do I do?
Of course I like Manabe,
but we're still in high school!
We haven't even properly confessed yet.
So fast!
What-what-what do I do?!
What to do? What do to?
Oh, just screw it!
Welcome back! That was faghhh—
Booyah! Gearing up took longer than I thought!
I hope Kotoura isn't too worried.
Were you scared, Kotoura? Don't worry, I'm ri—
Who is it?!
Hi!
M-Monster!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Oh God, please. I'm so sorry. Please stop hurting me.
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
Lecher!
Do not allow
into your home!
You seemed so terrified I thought I should come over and keep you company, but what do I find?!
Do you seriously not get what that degenerate will do if you let him stay in your apartment?!
Wh-What do you mean? I'm sure he'd be a gentleman!
Really?
I apologize.
I hope you've learned your lesson.
Still, I'm afraid that there will be consequences, young lady.
I'll have to inform the club president and your grandfather of your behavior.
This hurts me more than it hurts you, but you leave me no choice.
Please, anything but that!
I heard the big news!
So you finally went all the way last night?
We didn't do anything!
Moritani told you the whole story, so you should know that.
Hel—
Manabe! Now!
For you, Manabe.
Hello, this is Manabe—
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Just plotting to spend the night with Haruka!
I'm almost there! Just a little closer—
Fool! As a man, you should be ashamed!
How can you let so many chances pass you by?!
I was so close! I was almost there!
Next time, I swear!
You have sworn, and you shall keep your oath.
I don't think I can handle these lechers much longer.
Whoa there.
Sorry about that. You okay?
Y-Yes.
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, no worries.
I'm always spacing out, too. It really annoys my boss.
She's so big.
But her eyes are so gentle. She reminds me of an elephant.
Holy crap, she's like gerbil-sized!
Oh yeah, mind if I ask you a question?
Where's the cafeteria here?
It's on the first floor of the annex,
but it's not open yet.
What? But I didn't get any breakfast today!
The school store's open though.
Really?!
Thanks a bunch, girls!
Some damn sleuth you are, Dumbo!
Ouch.
Yeah, she should have started like this.
Y-You're police officers?
Wow, I've never seen a real badge before!
As I'm sure you've heard,
there have been several random assaults in this area.
And all the victims have been local students.
If you've noticed anything at all,
I'd sure appreciate hearing about it.
Have we noticed anything?
No, nothing in particular.
Right?
Huh? Oh. Right.
Right, Kotoura?
R-Right.
Aww, you shouldn't frighten innocent little girls, Yama.
Shut your damn trap!
Well, if you do think of something, let me know.
Something up?
Nah. Nothing.
Gotta pee! Gotta pee!
I can't believe I actually got questioned by the police!
That lady detective was mammoth!
They said all the victims have been high school girls.
Like, scary!
Why the long face?
I'm just not so sure keeping quiet was the best thing to do.
You shouldn't worry about it like this.
Like Muroto said, there's no way we could explain your psychic ability to them.
I know, but...
And anyway, you just passed by the criminal.
You didn't even see a face, right?
How could that help the police?
Still...
Wait, did you say "criminal?" You mean that psycho assaulting people?
Did you see him? What'd he look like?
She doesn't know anything about it!
Keep your stupid questions to yourself!
What's your problem? We were only asking.
Come on, Kotoura, did you see him?
I, well...
That's enough! Lay off her, damnit!
Ahh, sweet relief.
So I heard some girl in the school knows who's assaulting people.
So why can't they catch the criminal?
I heard she won't talk to the police.
Apparently she's afraid the criminal will come after her.
That's really low.
She's just gonna let someone else get attacked?
You mean that girl? Look, she's smiling!
Doesn't that bitch feel any guilt at all?
What's wrong, Kotoura?
Oh, it's nothing.
Stare.
Sorry. The truth is...
So it looks like those inconsiderate jerks are spreading rumors!
Indeed. It's going around my grade too.
I was at least able to get my friends to stop talking about it, but still.
That won't help much.
You can't stop people from spreading rumors.
Damn them! Damn those assholes!
What if we simply removed the grounds for the rumor?
How would we do that?
Well... we could find the criminal ourselves.
With Kotoura's power, I'm sure it's possible.
I-I can't do that!
And anyway, I'm still pretty scared.
That's right! Isn't that what the police are for?
I was just kidding. I know she's no Nancy Drew.
Right, Muroto?
Right.
I'm so sorry. This is all my fault.
I just had to open my big mouth and get you in this mess.
Moritani.
I'm really sorry!
Are you a total moron?
What? I'm trying to apologize!
But you didn't spread that rumor, right?
Apologizing will only make Kotoura feel worse.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
He's right. You were only trying to protect me.
I guess so.
It's my grandfather.
Hello, Haruka speaking.
What? You're here?
That's kind of sudden.
Have dinner together?
Oh, with Manabe and the others?
We'd love to!
Is this really the best time?
It's fine! It'll be a nice change of pace! Right?
Yeah.
Okay. See you later, then.
Score! Free food! Free food!
Moritani, do you want to come—
Thanks for the offer, but I'm busy tonight.
Sorry, Kotoura. See you.
Moritani.
It's all my fault. I have to make it right.
It hasn't been that long since we last met, and yet
Courtesy of
Manabe's brother
you all look so grown-up!
Coordinated by
Muroto's mother
Y-You...
You just had to say it.
It'll be a real dinner!
Everyone be sure to dress your best!
Roger!
Well, he's stupidly rich! I thought we'd go someplace fancy!
You must feel pretty silly, wearing those clothes in a joint like this.
Let's go somewhere else.
Go on and get yourself changed, Haruka.
Don't worry, I'll make it up to you later.
Whatever you say, Mr. Zenzou.
A ho-ho-hotel!
Exclusive! Luxurious!
At last I have found my rightful domain!
Hey Muroto, if we don't finish our meal,
y'think they'll give us a doggie bag for it?
Who is this strange woman?
Don't try to ignore me!
Honestly, I can't believe her.
Now, don't say that. She's the one who called me.
She wanted me to help cheer you up.
She did that?
Come to think of it,
I also got a call from that super-teasable girl.
She couldn't make it?
Oh, I get it. Moritani.
I wish she could've come.
Well, if it isn't my father.
Kumiko! What are you doing here?
I told you I never wanted to see you again!
Then don't look at me.
I can eat anywhere I like.
Hey, what's wrong, Kotoura?
M-My... my... m-mother...
Oh, you're here too?
What's going on here?
She's being so cold to her own daughter.
It must be complicated.
President Kotoura, I presume?
I've heard so much about you.
And you are?
My name is Tsuyama.
Pathetic. You can't even manage a "hello"?
This is weird. My voice won't work.
There was so much I wanted to tell my mother when I saw her again.
That I'm doing OK.
That I'm always thinking of her.
And that I so dearly want her forgiveness.
Hi there.
So you're Kumiko's daughter?
Your mother is my very special friend.
What's the matter? You're going all white.
Stop it, Haruka!
You're doing it again?!
I-I'm not! Mother!
I... I...
Oh, that's it.
That's what I really wanted to tell her.
Mother, I have friends now.
My friends are right here.
Everyone is around me.
Is that so?
Well, you'd better watch yourself.
You just might lose everything all over again.
Um, pardon!
What do you want?
My name is Manabe Yoshihisa!
I will absolutely never abandon Kotoura!
Manabe.
So you're after Haruka?
Do as you want.
Everything is permitted! As promised, I'll never leave you, Kotoura.
That's right! Never ever!
Have you no sense of decorum at all, you lecher?!
It's okay! We have your mother's approval!
And we just happen to be standing in a hotel!
How about it?
We could spend the night together for real this time!
Stop it, Manabe!
Hey, kid!
Knock it off!
Please stop hurting me...
You're quite the vulgar boy, aren't you?
You should know better, Haruka!
M-Mother.
Let's go somewhere else, Tsuyama.
Huh? O-Okay.
I felt it. Just a little, but it's there.
My mother's heart is still there.
Hey, you okay?
Guess I've gotta respect your balls.
Hey! Manabe?!
Looks like this isn't really the best time for a leisurely dinner.
Should we call it off?
We're okay!
That was nothing compared to Moritani's beatdowns!
Thank you, everyone.
When something trips you up,
how do you stand again?
Can truth be found by thinking
about the days to come?
When we are born, we all come into this world alone,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
No.
This can't be happening. It can't.
I...
Kotoura, you are hereby placed under arrest
for constantly peeping into a boy's dirty mind!
That's not fair! It's your own fault for letting your lust run wild!
Our great nation has wisely given its pubescent boys the freedom to fantasize!
Episode 10
But You're Not Here
And that is why our degenerate nation shall fall.