In retrospect, it was pretty strange.
But...
for some reason,
I don't feel that it was strange.
Either way, it was a turning point in my life.
Then again, it doesn't feel like anything changed at all.
It really was an awkward experience.
However, you might stumble upon it anywhere.
Here, in Ikebukuro.
S-So s-sorr... y.
I want to go back.
Please don't laugh at me.
In both elementary and middle school, I skipped all the field trips.
Kakamura
See ya.
I've never been outside my hometown.
Nara
This is the story of a confused fifteen-year-old boy who came to Tokyo.
The protagonist is me, Ryuugamine Mikado.
So why is a shut-in like me standing on a platform of the Tobu Tojo line, looking around cluelessly?
Because I'll start attending Raira Private Academy in East Ikebukuro this April.
You could say the school is pretty reputable.
They take great care of the buildings, and the classrooms are well equipped...
but the real clincher was an invitation from my best friend in elementary school.
My parents hated the idea and wanted me to attend a nearby school,
but my fascination with Tokyo made me ignore them.
Mikado!
Huh?
Kida-kun?
What? You're not sure?
All right, I'll give you three options.
One: Kida Masaomi.
Two: Kida Masaomi.
Three: Kida Masaomi!
Whoa! Is it really you, Kida-kun?!
Come on, don't ruin the hilarious joke I worked on for three years.
Glad to see you again, dude!
I really didn't recognize you. You've changed so much.
I never imagined that you'd dye your hair!
Oh, and that was a lame joke.
Well, no wonder. It's been four years since we last met.
But hey, you haven't changed one bit since elementary school.
Oh yeah, don't be a party-pooper.
This is my best friend, Kida Masaomi.
He transferred when we were in elementary school.
But he hasn't changed at all, except for his appearance.
Right, let's go.
Let's get out of here.
I'm in the mood to make a Journey to the West.
I'm a crooked tour guide who'll send you to the Seibu exit instead of the West exit.
His jokes suck, but he's a great friend.
I chat with him online every day,
so I hadn't realized how far apart we'd drifted.
So, do you know the difference between the West and Seibu exits?
But now that we've met after four years,
The Tobu department store is on the west side,
I finally realize that we've been living far apart.
and the Seibu department store is on the east side.
Shit, why am I explaining my failed jokes to you anyway?
Even though his jokes suck even worse now,
Whatever.
he's still the same old friend.
Any place you want to go?
Let's see...
Sunshine 60?
Right now?
If you're going there, you'd better take a girl with you.
U-Uh... Then how about Ikebukuro West Gate Park?
Dude, just say WGP.
But do all the Ikebukuronians call it that?
Hah, Ikebukuronians?
What? You really wanna go there?
Well... Uh...
H-Hey!
F-Forget about it. It's pretty late already.
We'll be killed by a Color Gang.
I can't believe you just said that.
Besides, it's only six o'clock.
Sheesh, you're still a chicken.
Good evening.
'Sup.
Ah, Setton-san,
you know, starting tomorrow I'll be living in Ikebukuro.
Yeah?
Maybe I'll end up living close to you.
Who knows?
I'm still at my old place right now,
but tomorrow I'm moving to an apartment
near the Sunshine Building.
Welcome to Ikebukuro.
Wow.
The realm I've only seen in comics and on the Net is right in front of me.
This is even cooler than Ginza Kami-Sakura.
All right, I'll take you to Shibuya next time.
If you're that fascinated by crowds, maybe I should take you to a horse race.
There aren't as many Color Gang members as before.
Until last year, quite a few conspicuous people were still on the streets,
but most of them got arrested for starting a gang war in Saitama.
So, if a crowd of people dressed in the same colors gathers,
the cops rush over.
In other words, this place is pretty safe now?
Well, that's all I know. I really have no idea.
And there are a dozen other dangerous folks around here,
so you'd better watch out.
I see.
By the way, this is 60 Floor Street.
There's also a Sunshine Street.
I wonder if Sunshine Street came first.
S-Sorry!
Oh, hey, Kida-kun.
Oh, if it isn't Karisawa-san and Yumasaki-san.
'Sup?
Hey, fancy seeing you here.
'Sup.
How you doing, Kida?
Oh, hello.
Who's he?
Your friend?
Yeah, he's my childhood friend.
He just moved here today.
Oh, yeah?
This is Karisawa-san.
And this is Yumasaki-san.
Uh, and over there we have Kadota-san and Togusa-san.
U-Um...
I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
Did I say something wrong?
Is that his pen name?
Why would a high schooler use a pen name?
Oh, maybe he's on the radio, or a writer for a magazine.
N-No... It's my real name.
You gotta be kiddin' me! Are you serious?
Whoa dude, that's pretty awesome!
He's like the lead guy straight out of a comic!
Geez, you're gonna make him blush!
What should I do?
I can't keep up with the conversation.
You guys are on your way back from shopping?
Yep.
The new publication of Dengeki Bunko came out today,
so we bought thirty of 'em.
Do they publish that many in a month?
No, no, you've got it wrong.
Ten for me, ten for him,
and ten... for other things.
Yep, for other things.
I wonder what they mean by "other things."
For themselves? To sell? Or to display on their shelves?
Anyway, we gotta go.
See ya later.
Yeah. Bye.
Should we carry this by the head?
Bye.
Don't hit the car, you morons!
Er, yeah, they're a little weird,
but they're great people if you're friends with them.
I didn't expect you to hang out with people like that.
I've got my dick in many holes, ya know?
I know the places where you can get clothes cheaply,
I wonder what he's done for the past four years...
or how to bargain with the vendors on the street.
while I stayed inside my house in the country.
Well, if you're knowledgeable about lots of things,
you can strike up a conversation with almost any girl.
Yeah, "dick in many holes."
I found her.
You sure?
The description matches completely. There's no mistake.
Got it.
Let's go.
Aye.
Don't fuck up the dose, 'kay?
They'll pay less if she doesn't wake up.
Who cares?
They pay a fifty percent bonus for a teen.
Twenty percent, dude.
We haven't had such a sweet deal for a while now.
And it's fucking jailbait.
Yeah.
Props to the informant.
Good evening.
Oh, you were here, Kanra-san?
I was actually on the phone.
Ah, I just read the scrollback.
You're coming to Tokyo?
Congrats.
Want to meet?
Sure, sounds great.
Yeah.
Ah, speaking of meetings...
You know, there are suicide meetings.
Yeah, they were Topic A for a while.
People meet on the Internet and commit suicide.
Ugly subject, eh?
But I haven't heard about them on the news recently.
Perhaps they failed at it.
There might be quite a lot of them,
but perhaps no one's noticed.
Like the bodies haven't been found... yet.
Dude, don't joke about that.
Oh yeah, lately a lot of people have disappeared.
Really?
Uh...
It's usually an illegal immigrant,
or a kid who ran away from home.
There seem to be many cases between Shibuya and Ikebukuro.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes.
Are you Nakura-san?
All right. I knew it was you.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Should we go then?
Okay.
It's right around the corner.
There are two more coming.
I see.
That's it.
Hey.
Hello.
Anyone around?
Not a single soul.
Well...
Sorry for tricking you!
Someone is around.
Kida-kun kept talking without stopping for breath.
I was actually getting a bit tired,
either from walking around so much,
or from pointing out his lame jokes.
Well, we always chat, but now that you're actually here,
Probably both.
I realize that I've still got a lot to talk about.
Y-Yeah.
I feel like I haven't told you even 5/400th of what I wanted to say.
By the way, Karisawa-san and Yumasaki-san took up 4/400.
Just when I was thinking of a comeback, a guy caught my eye.
It's been a while, Miss.
A man dressed as a chef trying to get customers...
Let me correct myself: a tall, black man dressed as a chef...
No, someone dressed like a chef who's supposed to get customers and who is, for some reason, black...
Hey, Mister, long time no see.
Hey, Simon!
It's been a long time, man!
Oh, Kida, you want some sushi?
It's yummy.
I'll make it cheap for ya.
Sushi is good, good.
Cut me some slack, man. I'm broke today.
I'll drop by when I get paid.
Make sure to gimme a handsome price then.
Oh, no!
They're gonna throw me off the bay onto Russian land.
Onto land? How you gonna drown there?
See ya.
Hey, Mister, long time no see.
You know him?
Yeah, he's Simon.
He's a black Russian.
He's supposed to get customers for that Russkie sushi shop.
Uh... What part don't I get?
I'm not kidding you.
His real name is Semyon.
But everyone calls him by the English equivalent, Simon.
I don't know the details,
but apparently his parents were deported from the US or something.
So, he ended up working here because his friend started a sushi bar.
You better not fuck with him, okay?
I saw him stop a fight once.
He grabbed some fucking giant as big as he is with just one arm.
And the other guy you shouldn't piss off is...
Huh? What the hell?
Speak of the devil.
Anyway, don't go near Heiwajima Shizuo.
If you live a normal life, you won't meet him, so do that.
Wh-What kind of monster is he?
Eh? They're still not here?
That's strange.
The higher-ups can't get their asses in gear, eh?
They'd better put some effort into this deal.
Who cares?
We don't have anything better to do anyway.
Yeah.
You gotta cherish your free time.
A short break from our chaotic life...
Oh yeah, I saw that black bike today.
Black bike?
You haven't heard of it before?
Everyone in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro is talking about it.
It used to be an urban legend,
but now people have pics of it and stuff.
Ah, yeah. I've heard about it.
Isn't it just some guy from a biker gang?
Uh, he doesn't ride with a group though.
He's got to be a retard for driving around without lights.
If he's even human, of course...
What do you mean?
Uh, how should I say it?
Simply put... he's something like a monster.
Hey.
Uh, are you one of the higher-ups?
Of course not.
Then who is that?
Are you fucking with us?
Can't you see that we're busy?
I'll beat your brains out if you get in our way!
Wh-What the fuck?!
Shit!
H-H-H-Hey!
Shit! Stop it!
Stop it!
I told you to stop it.
Shit.
Shit! Shit!
What the...
What the fuck?
What the fuck?!
What do you mean by "a monster"?
Dotachin says he's a Grim Reaper.
Dotachin?
Who's that?
You know, the guy who rides that black bike doesn't...
Hey, you switching topics?
Fuck you!
Suck it down!
Son of a bitch!
...have a head.
He moves just fine despite being decapitated.
H-Hey... What the fuck are you?
Y-You bastard!
Hey, are there other people I should avoid?
Well, leaving aside the gangs and the Yakuza...
There's Orihara Izaya.
Orihara Izaya?
That's a strange name.
You're one to talk.
Anyway, he's trouble, so don't get involved with him.
Well, he hangs around Shinjuku,
so I don't think you'll meet him any time soon.
Oh, and don't get involved with the Dollars.
Dollars?
Aye. Like the Dollars in "Wanderers."
"Wanderers"? What the...
I don't know much about them either,
but they have lots of crazy members. A shit load of 'em.
Apparently, they're part of a Color Gang,
but no one knows which color.
Maybe they've disbanded by now,
because there are so many cops around and they can't meet.
Yeah?
Hey! Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Um, I'm sorry.
Uh...
Get away!
H-Hey!
What the hell?
She didn't even bother to thank me.
I wonder what happened to her?
Who knows?
Anything can happen in this bizarre city.
But hey, you're lucky.
You met Simon and Kadota-san and company.
You even saw Shizuo throwing a vending machine and people around.
And you bumped into that babe.
I wonder if that makes me lucky, though.
I'm really happy...
that I can go to school and hang out here with you.
Me too.
You're really lucky, dude!
The frickin' urban legend is right in front of you!
Kida-kun!
Oh, you saw that black bike, Tanaka Tarou-san?
Was it around nine?
Oh, you heard about that, Setton-san?
Uh, yeah. I was there too.
What's this urban legend?!
The black bike, dude!
The rider without a head!
At that moment I noticed that I was trembling.
Not from fear.
I think I was just... mesmerized.
I'd seen something amazing.
Here, in this town, I'd experienced something I'd never experienced at home.
I felt the reality that seemed out of my reach unfold in front of me.
It might sound like I'm contradicting myself,
but at least that's what I thought.
I was thrilled by the premonition that a new reality was starting.
Really?
Then we just missed each other.
Yeah.
By the way...
who's Dotachin?
The girl with an enigmatic past
takes a peek at a reality she has never seen.
A reality that anyone could encounter, but never does.
What did the girl who was supposed to be dead see?
Next time: Highly Unpredictable.