I'm serious, okay?
Minami, you really do love...
I-I'm serious, okay?
I'm really gonna kill you!
Minami, you really do love...
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
through a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Question 9
Me, Romance, and the Art of Negotiation
It's been a week since the school trip,
and the second-year boys are back from their suspension.
Yuuji.
What do you—
Shit!
Don't dodge it.
Of course I'd dodge if you tried to headbutt me!
I was going to kiss you, not headbutt you.
All right. Hold it right there.
Put your hands above your head and explain.
Kiss, contact with lips.
It's what a couple like us, sworn to one another, does.
Stop. I know what a kiss is.
But why are you—
Who did you kiss? When? Where?
No, I just know the meaning of the word. I haven't actually experienced it.
Oh. That's fine then.
I thought I was gonna die.
What possessed you to say that?
That.
They just kissed.
Really?!
Akihisa really is an idiot.
He should've known that'd happen if he kissed a girl.
I'm sorry.
While you were asleep, I—
All right. There's another heretic here!
Good. Take him away.
W-Wait! Stop! I didn't do any— No! Don't!
I could only kiss you on the cheeks though, because you kept tossing and turning.
My fellow men, do you know what this is?
The Court of Final Justice!
And what do we do to heretics?
We strike them with the iron hammer of death!
Splendid. We will now begin interrogating these two.
Huh? Yuuji, what did you do?
I got caught up with your stupidity!
Read the charges.
The parties in this case are Yoshii Akihisa, hereafter referred to as the accused,
Yoshii
Akihisa
Accused
Minami
Shimada
and Shimada Minami, hereafter referred to as the ironing board.
The ironing board
Accused
The accused is in violation of our group's doctrines.
We've confirmed that he coerced the ironing board into an act of obscenity earlier this morning.
Accused
Ironing
board
I recommend the court to investigate the relationship of the accused with the ironing board in great detail
Investigate
to make sure that the accused receives adequate punishment
and to keep the ironing board under strict surveillance.
In conclusion...
Conclusion
I am so jealous of that kiss-crazy womanizer!
He is sentenced to death.
Death
Akihisa! What's going on?!
That's what I wanna know!
Wouldn't you know if you did something?
When was the last time you talked to Shimada?
The last night of the school trip, I think.
Oh, that night.
Minami came to my bed after everyone already went to sleep.
And you didn't wonder why she did that?
I thought she came to finish me off.
Well, what did you talk to her about before that?
Umm...
Shimada Minami
I have something to talk about.
Can you come to my room?
Yoshii Akihisa
I don't mind, but what do you
want to talk about so late?
Shimada Minami
Because my heart tells me to.
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Oh, it's nothing.
So what did you talk about?
It was a confession, kinda.
Shimada confessed to you?
No, I confessed to Minami.
How the fuck could you not remember that?
Heretic, Yoshii Akihisa, are you ready to repent for your sins and receive judgment?
What judgment?
You're condemned to do the special bungee jump.
Just to be clear, what's special about it?
I'll just give you a hint, so you don't worry too much.
It's just like skydiving without the parachute!
That's fucking obvious!
You want me to... You want me to bungee jump without a rope?!
Himeji's here! Help me, Himeji!
Minami, you really do love...
What? You're still saying that?
Yoshii and Shimada are talking with their eyes!
I knew he had the hots for the ironing board all along!
If he takes Himeji, Kinoshita, and Shimada for himself, then we're just left with Aki!
Aki
Morning, Aki.
Y-Yeah, morning.
Hey, can I sit at your desk too?
Mine's broken.
All right. Sure.
Thanks!
What did you clam up for?
Don't you think you're too close?
Well, the desk is so small.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, Aki, if you don't mind,
wanna have lunch with me?
I made a lunchbox for you—
What are you doing, Sissy?!
Sh-Shimizu?
You shouldn't sit so close to this pig!
I-I don't have a choice! My desk is broken.
You don't have to sit with this pig then!
Minami, you really do love...
But Mizuki studies very intently, so I don't want to bother her.
Aki doesn't mind. He's gonna flunk either way.
I have a vague feeling I was just insulted.
How dare this hog force my darling to make him lunch with her own two hands?
She woke up at 4 AM to make that fried chicken.
She searched everywhere for that quality steak.
She even chose only the finest potatoes for that salad, ever so carefully!
Why do you know all that?!
She even drew a heart on the rice, you know?!
Miharu!
Miharu, I've been putting up with it so far, but I want you to stop now, okay?
I'm going out with Aki after all.
Straw barrier!
That's how it is, Miharu. Please understand.
I want to marry you, have a daughter, take one character of your name, and name her Mirai!
Wait, Shimizu! What if it's a boy?
Then I'll just name him Namihei.
Miharu and I can't have a baby in the first place!
It's time for class!
What are you doing, Shimizu? Go back to your class.
This is very important! Please let me stay here today!
What's so important?
I must exterminate all the pigs in this classroom!
I prohibit you from stepping foot in this classroom ever again.
That disgusting swine!
Thou hast it tough indeed.
We could talk forever about that.
Oh, come on. It's not my fault.
Nope, we're in big trouble, and it's all your fault.
Class D seems to be preparing for an ESB.
How does it concern us whom Class D wants to fight?
Not even if it's Class F?
We have the worst facilities already!
There's no reason for them to attack—
No way!
Exactly. Shimizu stirred them up.
She wants us to go back to cardboard mandarin boxes for desks,
so you and Shimada can't sit together.
But why would everyone else in Class D want to help her?
We organized that peeping parade, remember?
All the girls consider us their sworn enemy.
Delicious flat chest
Class D's rep, Hiraga Genji, is a strong leader,
but even he cannot betray those women united by wrath.
No!
Our boys haven't been able to recover their marks because of the suspension.
We don't have a fighting chance, not even with Himeji's help.
There's only one option. We must prevent the battle.
How do we do that?
I have one thing to ask
about you and Shimada.
What is it?
Are you really going out with her?
I'm not supposed to be going out with her...
but because of that e-mail I accidentally sent...
Mistake?
I see now.
Akihisa can be forgiven for being his usual self, but thou madest it a real pickle, Yuuji.
Is that so? Sorry, Akihisa.
In that case, if you clear that up with Shimada,
and you two go back to being just friends again,
Shimizu should calm down too.
You mean...
Voyeur, does Shimizu have any listening bugs here?
Here. I kept it to use in negotiations.
What did you wanna tell us?
It's about that e-mail I sent you during the school trip.
It's... It's all a misunderstanding!
Huh?
I mean, I didn't mean to send it to you.
Then who?
Sugawa, actually.
You were going to confess to Sugawa?
Goodness! I thought you were straight, despite everything!
No, it's like this.
Yoshii, why are you so desperate
to peep on the girls, anyway?
Because my heart tells me to.
You're horrible, in so many unique ways.
I'm really sorry! But yeah, I didn't mean to send you that message.
Oh, I see! I see!
It did surprise me when I read it, but I understand now!
You shouldn't jump to conclusions like that, Minami.
Come on. You sent it to the wrong person, so you're not any better.
What are you gonna do about my first kiss?!
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean any ill will!
"Sorry" ain't gonna cut it!
Then let's...
What?
It was my... first kiss too, so can we call it even and let it go?
Of course you can't.
Oh, really? In that case... it was good.
You're okay with it?!
Listen, Minami. I want you to answer me without getting mad.
What are you talking about?
You told Shimizu we're going out, didn't you?
Is it because you really do love—
That was just...
You know, Miharu annoys me a lot, so I thought she'd stop if I told her I had a boyfriend.
It pains my heart to hear her excuses.
She just isn't honest.
Well, why didn't you say that?
I thought you really did love me!
O-Of course I don't!
I knew something was wrong! You were being so sweet, and
you're dislocating my shoulder!
At least he cleared up that misunderstanding.
Now we just have to wait for Shimizu to hear this, and it'll all be over.
Just like that, the situation with Class D was de-fused.
However!
Question 9:
Translate the following
into correct English:
"Heartful love story"
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
"Heart-warming love story"
Teacher's comment:
That's correct.
This is a very common phrase
in promos for books and movies,
but sometimes, another word,
which sounds similar to "heart,"
is used by mistake. It's such
a small word, but it's still hard
to remember.
By the way,
the equivalent phrase
in Japanese is
"ai ni michita monogatari".
I wish you all a youth just like that.
Shimada Minami's answer
"Hurtful rough story"
Teacher's comment:
hurt
ful
rough
story
I don't think you did this on purpose,
but that is a very cute mistake.
I believe you're the only one who could
put out a love story like that.
Kirishima Shouko's answer:
"Hurtful rough story"
Teacher's comment:
Oh, here's another one.
Listen to this.
The situation worsened this morning.
Umm, do you really have pictures of Akihisa in a girl's uniform?!
One for 100 yen.
Don't sell copies of it.
I'll take all the copies you have—
Oops.
What was that? What was that?
That really sounded like a bad situation!
Shut up, Akihisa. Stop making such a fuss over it.
I am gonna make a fuss!
Why is he secretly selling photos of me like he does with Hideyoshi?!
Halt, Akihisa! That sounds like a bad situation for me as well!
This is the one I meant.
Has Class F started preparing yet?
No, none of them have caught on to our scheme.
Good. Use this time to raise our marks.
If they find out, declare an ESB on them immediately.
But... I thought Class D wouldn't attack us now.
No, you're mistaken. That wasn't Class D.
This was from Class B.
That Nemoto, sneaking around like the rat he is.
Why does Class B want to battle us?
Nemoto lost to us and lost his standing, remember?
Thereafter he brought his class for the peeping parade and lost there too.
He probably has no more influence over his classmates.
I guess he's doing this to quickly resolve the dissatisfaction in his class.
Cross-dresser!
Enemy
o
He wants to make us the enemy and direct Class B's anger at us instead of himself.
So if they defeat us, his leadership shall be restored, aye.
We haven't taken any tests recently. If they attack us now, we're doomed!
We don't have a choice. We'll have to create a situation where they can't attack us.
How can we do that?
We just need to get another class to challenge us to an ESB before Class B can.
You mean...
We'll get Class D to challenge us.
Come on! We just cleared up Shimizu's misunderstanding so she wouldn't attack us!
Declare ESB
After the ESB, we'll get to take the recovery test and raise our scores.
+TIME
+RECOVERY
If we win against Class D, we'll have plenty of time to recover.
+TIME
+RECOVERY
I get it. If we recover to our usual level,
Class B won't attack us so carelessly either.
But Yuuji, we don't have enough marks to win against Class D either!
I have another plan for that.
Anyway, first, we have to provoke Class D into declaring an ESB on us.
How?
We'll repeat what you did this morning.
You and Shimada will stick to each other and make Shimizu mad.
No way in Hell!
Pretty please?
No, and you can't convince me otherwise.
I don't even want to pretend to be this moron's girlfriend.
Shimada! Only you can do this!
If Class B invades us now, we'll go back to using mandarin boxes for desks.
Then Himeji's parents will get worried again and get her transferred to another school.
Himeji
Parents
Worried
Transferred
I need you to help us too, Himeji.
Me too?
Aye, Shimada alone will not be enough to fool our enemy.
Thou shalt play the part of being the jealous third wheel.
Won't you do it, please?
Umm, Minami! Akihisa!
I know it's not very pleasant, but let's do this!
Mizuki!
I don't want to make excuses, but I really don't want to transfer out of this school.
That's why...
A-All right! We're just gonna be acting, after all.
Thank you very much!
Now that we've decided that, here.
A script? Let's see.
I'm sorry for calling you here like this, Aki. You know, I love you.
I've always loved you too, Minami.
W-What's with these lines?!
There's no way I'm gonna say this!
I know we're acting, but this is too embarrassing!
I see how it is. Allow me to demonstrate.
I'm sorry for calling you here like this, Aki.
You know, I love you.
I've loved you since we first met.
It's been so hard being just friends.
I really, really couldn't stand it!
Aki, I know it's too late to say it after what we've done already,
but I'll say it again. I love you.
Please go out with me.
Like that.
A-Amazing!
I was enthralled!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Could you all leave me alone, just for a little while?
I don't want to wake up just yet.
Voyeur, put that bug back on the roof.
Roger.
You three, go to the roof and start your performance.
Shimizu will then overhear you through the bug and fall in our trap.
'Tis the scene of a lover's date.
Both of you must hold hands.
Hold hands?
But...
'Tis the least you can do to fix that last screw up.
Well then...
Touch me anywhere odd, and I'll pulverize you.
It's hard to walk if you grip it so hard.
We're going out! This is normal for us!
But Minami, my elbow is touching them.
Y-You perv.
Your ribs—
Damn! I have to keep up the act!
Say, Minami!
What, Aki?
What do you love about me?
Isn't it obvious?
From the top of your head...
From the top of my head?
...to your eyebrows.
Oh, my forehead.
What are you two doing?
Mizuki!
You're so close together and even holding hands.
It's just like you're... like you're...
a couple.
Huh? Was that in the script?
I get it. She's ad-libbing!
That's right, Mizuki. We're going out.
Is that the truth?
Yes. I'm sorry I never told you, Mizuki.
Minami!
You really do love Akihisa!
I never told you that either. Sorry.
I know you feel the same way.
I'm sorry. I know I mustn't ask for forgiveness.
It's okay. I knew how you felt all along... sort of.
In fact, my mind is at ease now that you've told me up front.
Does that mean... you'll forgive me?
I don't need to forgive you. You're free to fall in love with whomever you want to.
I can't get mad at you for that.
Mizuki. Thank you!
But...
I can't forgive you for kissing him this morning!
That wasn't fair! It was Akihisa's first kiss!
That was just... All because of that message... I just...
Don't you "just" me! I won't forgive you for that, even if the gods do!
That's a listening bug!
Minami, you idiot!
Damn! If Himeji mentions the plan, we're done for!
Himeji!
What are you doing, Aki? Are you choosing Mizuki over me?!
Forgive me, Minami, but I have to go!
Aki! Stay here with me! I...
I...
love you, Aki.
That's the truth.
Calm thyself, Shimada. Be careful about what thou say—
It's all right. We're done acting.
Aki likes girls like Mizuki, after all.
Himeji!
Akihisa...
Thank you. I never noticed it.
Is something wrong, Himeji? You seem down.
Do I?
Yeah, you seem really lonely.
Lonely, huh?
I must look like that because the one I love was snatched away from me...
even if it was just make-believe.
It's all right. That really was just an act.
It was, wasn't it? It was just an act.
I'd be jealous, though.
I'd be jealous of a guy who was in love with both you and Minami, even if it was just an act.
If you were the guy in that scene, what would you do, Akihisa?
Let's see.
I'd think about it really, really hard.
What?
I'd think really hard and tell you both as soon as I'm done.
I was hoping you'd tell me who you'd choose.
No, it's nothing!
I was really surprised, though.
About what?
It didn't look like you were acting back there.
Don't tell me you...
have done this sort of thing before?
Himeji?
Idiot.
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem.
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby.
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you.
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N.
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go.
I've fallen in love.
I don't want any doubts in my heart.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Sparkling, glittering.
The right answer is pop!
Question 10:
Answer the following
question:
What is the name of the
nutrient lacking in miso?
What can be added
to miso soup
to compensate?
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
Spring onions.
Teacher's comment:
That's correct.
Other vegetables like onions and chrysanthemums are also
a good source of Vitamin C. Miso is abundant in B vitamins
and, along with soybean protein from the soup base, makes for
a very healthy meal. However, it also has a lot of salt,
so one must be careful about having too much.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
Vitamin C. Oranges or
hydrochloric acid.
Teacher's comment:
Is that really cooking?
Question 10.
What is the name of the nutrient lacking in miso? What can be added to miso soup to compensate?
Vitamin C. Oranges or hydrochloric acid.
Is that really cooking?
Next time: Me, romance, and the art of love.
Next time:
Me, Romance, and the Art of Love
This will be on the test.