Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
I want you to keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
You've all had times
when you've done bad things
even though you knew
they were wrong, haven't you?
But if you're sorry later and you
apologize, everyone will understand.
Mr. Yuri said a proper apology
for his mistakes in the past,
and now he's one of our important comrades.
But you know, it looks like there was also
something that happened way before that.
Mr. Leon, Miss Sophie,
and the Angel's Maneuver...
What exactly happened
three years ago? What? What?
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
That was so much fun!
The time just kind of flew by, didn't it?
It's kind of sad to think it's over, huh?
Yeah.
Yay! Bravo!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Um...
Up-ho! Up-ho! Up-ho! Up-ho!
Please, I'm begging you, can we stop now?
Great, they like us!
Ken, it's your time to shine!
Go!
Viva la France!
Isn't it great to see the
audience enjoying themselves?
I hear the Kaleido Stage will
start preparing to reopen soon.
Huh.
Don't give me that "huh"!
I see you're as happy-go-lucky as ever.
If you want to return to
the stage, then do something!
"Something"?
Like blackmailing the Boss, for instance.
That method is...
Hey.
Mr. Yuri!
I watched your Noir Circus show.
Looks like you've bounced back, Sora.
Yes. I'm sorry I caused
you so much trouble, Mr. Yuri.
Well, shall we go?
Go where?
Kaleido Stage.
What does this mean, Yuri?
Are you going to Kaleido Stage too, Mr. Yuri?
Yeah, Kalos asked me to return to work.
As a producer and a performer.
My my!
Really?
Well congratulations!
I'm not the only one who's returning to work.
"The Amazing Fated Duel."
Can it be true?!
I sure hope so!
Mr. Yuri said it, it has to be!
Yeah, it's totally okay!
Right!
Boss Boss Boss Boss Boss...
Be quiet! Come in.
Boss! Um, I heard from
Mr. Yuri that you're let going me
going me to let going
to let me back on stage!
Yes, I'm extending you a new contract.
Thank you, sir!
I'll play any role with all I've got!
Your role's already been decided, Sora.
You come in too, May.
All right.
I'm going to be producing our next new show.
The program will be Swan Lake.
Princess Odette, the lead, will be Sora.
The lead?
Yay!
But, um...
Whoa, she's accepting it meekly...
Isn't she going to start making a fuss?
I spent my whole time in
France researching "true stars."
You met a man named Alain, right Sora?
Yes, he said he taught Sophie,
Mr. Leon's sister, the Angel's Maneuver.
Right.
Did he also say he'd tried to bring a true star
into the world by perfecting
the Angel's Maneuver?
Yes, he did.
I heard the story from someone
who knew Alain a long time ago.
I too felt there was truth in the
thought that the Angel's Maneuver
is connected to the path to being a true star.
That's why I taught it to Sora for the Festival.
I thought that if it were true,
the hearts of the people who saw Sora's
Angel's Maneuver should come together as one.
But that didn't happen.
It did occur to me that perhaps
it wasn't the true star's maneuver,
but when I met Alain in person,
I was finally able to hear my answer.
What we did wasn't the full Angel's Maneuver.
You're talking about the
"perfect Angel's Maneuver"?
Yes. There's another part
to the Angel's Maneuver.
Sora, I'd like you to bring off a
perfect Angel's Maneuver on this stage.
We'll display the Angel's Maneuver
during the climax of Swan Lake.
And Sora, you get on that stage
and aim to be a true Kaleido Star!
A true Kaleido Star...
That's right.
I came back to be your partner in doing that.
I see.
So the reason you called me here was to
tell me you no longer had any use for me?
Are you saying you can
teach the Angel's Maneuver?
Are you saying you can do it?
I'll put it bluntly: that's impossible for you.
I had high hopes for you,
the man called the "God of Death,"
but from what I've seen,
you're running from facing Sora.
I have no choice but to
say you're a disappointment.
Running, you say?
You've been doing nothing
but running, have you?!
I hear you even walked away from the
Angel's Maneuver training halfway through.
Go ahead and do it, if you think you can.
You did run. You really are a hopeless coward.
That's why you can't even
get your revenge against me.
Revenge?
What's with these trapezes?
I've never seen ones like that before.
They're just the temporary
set for our rehearsals.
We're going to do the
Angel's Maneuver on these?
That's right.
I wonder how they'll move... I can't even guess.
I want to try performing on these trapezes!
Be right there!
Yo!
Miss Cathy!
What is it all of a sudden?
What do you mean, "what is it"? Do I look
like I've come to sleep over or something?
You... kind of do--
Your guess is correct!
Did you hear about the plan for Swan Lake?
I did, and I just couldn't sit still!
I thought, "Boy, I want to work
out this whole script with Mia!"
Um, right...
So, how about it? Got an image?
Um, I just now heard about it,
so I sort of haven't thought about it yet...
You're kidding! You say "just now,"
but it's been almost an hour, right?!
I'm amazed you could go this long
without thinking about it!
Um...
Nothing's come to mind yet? Seriously?!
I'm sorry!
I mean, honestly...
At any rate, would you like some tea?
Is anything coming to--
Not yet!
For this show Ken's got his own job to do,
so we can't rely on Ken's
airhead character anymore.
Hanna.
Yes.
Barbara.
Yes!
We have to think up some material, don't we?
That'll totally go over!
I believed those words before,
and the reception was lukewarm.
Let's think about this more deeply.
Yes, Miss Anna!
I had a lot of trouble
investigating the Angel's Maneuver,
because there are very few
records of people who've attempted it.
Well, that's only natural, though.
It requires extraordinarily harsh
training, but it's not even flashy.
Everyone came to think that anyone
who attempted such a thing was a fool.
Now there's hardly anybody
who even knows what it is.
Sora.
Yes?
If you attempt the Angel's Maneuver and fail,
all that will be waiting
for you is scornful laughter.
Will you really walk this path?
Yes.
You're convinced this is the
path to being a true star, aren't you?
Actually, it's more like right now
I just want to try my hand at this maneuver.
Even if I think about what's going to happen
afterwards, it's not like I'll somehow know,
and I don't want to not
do it and then have regrets.
My parents died when
I was small, leaving me behind.
I'm sure they had all kinds
of things they wanted to do,
so I think maybe dying really stung.
So I live life trying everything.
I see.
And I understand how much it stung Sophie that
she couldn't bring off the Angel's Maneuver...
Sora. Do you know why Sophie died?
No...
I killed her.
Just before the Festival three years ago,
I happened to see Leon and Sophie
practicing the Angel's Maneuver.
It was something I could tell
with one look wasn't perfected.
It wasn't something that
could possibly have jeopardized
Layla's victory with the Golden Phoenix.
But what I was afraid of then
was Leon's presence in my world.
I thought that if Kalos called Leon to
Kaleido Stage, my position would be in danger.
But at the time I had ambitions.
I had ambitions to rout out Kalos,
the cause of my father's death,
and seize control of the Kaleido Stage.
On the day of the Festival,
I called her to a park
a ways off from the arena.
I lied, telling her I had
something to say to her.
She kept waiting for me when
there was no way I'd show up,
and then at the last possible
moment she tried to return to the arena.
On her way back, she was in an accident.
Leon called me countless
times from the hospital.
He asked me again and again to
meet with her before she passed on,
crying as he spoke the words.
Sophie is smitten with you.
Please!
Tell her you weren't trying to trick her!
Please don't let her die with a wounded heart!
I'm begging you! Please!
It was almost my turn to perform; he must
have known there was no way I'd come.
You... did something like that...
I can become a demon at any time.
Only a true demon can raise an angel.
If you're going to try to become an angel,
you'll have to accept a demon for a partner.
I intend to settle things with Leon.
Whichever one of us can become
a true demon will be your partner.
Yuri's Pisces and Leon's Scorpio...
The curtain is about to rise on a battle
more fierce than any that has come before.
It's been a long time since
Sora's had a leading part, huh?
I know, I'm looking forward to it!
Now if only May weren't here...
Tell me about it.
Oh, Sora, good luck!
Show May how much better you are than her!
All finished already?
I don't have that much stuff.
There we go...
It's great that you got to
have your old room back, huh?
Yeah. Thanks for everything!
It looks like everybody's
excited about your lead role.
Yeah, I'm happy about that,
but I wish they'd get along with May too...
With May?
Yeah. After all, she is one of us,
performing on the same stage...
Maybe that's Mia and the others?
Yes, I'm coming!
May...
Is there someone here?
Yeah, Rosetta...
I thought that might happen.
It's a good thing I came prepared.
I'm coming in.
Er, okay. Come on in. Come all the way in...
You come too, Rosetta.
Huh? Come where?
May, you don't have to come that far in...
Um, what are you doing?
You'll drink cola, right?
What's this about?
I'm sure you'll do a comeback
party and stuff with your friends,
but I don't go to things like that.
I see you're as dense as ever.
I'm saying let's make a toast!
Huh?
I intend to have you show me
your best Odette in this show.
I'm going to give the part of Odile my all,
so that people will say she
shines more than Odette does.
May!
But if you ever look like you're flagging,
I'm standing by ready
to steal your role anytime.
Right.
Receiving Sagittarius' light,
Taurus grows brighter as well.
Okay then, let's make a toast!
Cheers!
That's not really a toast, it's more like...
This is the way we do it in my family!
Come on, shake shake shake shake shake!
Boy, for a second there I was
worried about whether I...
Cheers!
Just so you know,
I totally don't believe in this "stage with
no battles" thing you keep talking about.
The reality is, you won
against me and got the lead role.
I intend to win against you someday.
Right.
That's the way things work, isn't it?
Yeah... But I don't feel like this is fighting.
Maybe that's because I've been
able to make friends with you.
Well, you don't piss me off as
much as you did before, either.
Why don't you make friends
with everyone else in the cast too?
You've got to be joking.
Make friends with riffraff who
are all talk but don't do anything?
They're not like that.
They're all doing their best.
Sora.
What?
Let's go back to the stage again.
Huh?
Show me what your stage is like.
Right now?
Of course, practice starts tomorrow!
Okay...
I'm impressed, you came
instead of running away.
What's the meaning of this?
I thought I'd give you a
chance to take your revenge.
You hate me, don't you?
I'm the man who caused Sophie's death.
Then take that sword and face me.
What's the matter? Can't you do it?
Why don't I reveal who
the God of Death really is?
You're no God of Death.
And you're not searching for a partner, either.
For the past three years, you've
just been relieving your own mind,
confirming over and over that
no one could take Sophie's place.
But then Sora came along.
You must have noticed right away that
she had abilities that rivaled Sophie's.
You gave Sora special
training out of the blue like that
because you thought if you gave her the
test for the Angel's Maneuver she'd pass it.
You were hoping Sora
would be the one to run away.
But Sora never gave up.
You were afraid of her.
If things went on like that, the
Angel's Maneuver training would continue.
If that happened,
you'd have to acknowledge that you're a
coward who can't completely turn into a demon.
You're wrong!
The reason Sophie couldn't become an angel
was because you couldn't
completely become a demon.
For you, those days while
Sophie's lukewarm training continued
were more important than
her turning into an angel.
Because that was the only way your
cowardice would remain undiscovered.
You're the one who's most
relieved that Sophie's dead, am I right?
What did you say?!
Because you got by without
your deceit being found out.
Shut up!
Be grateful to me, Leon!
Because I freed you from your suffering.
Sophie's dream was a millstone
around your neck, wasn't it?
Admit it.
Don't you say another word!
What's that sound?
Is someone in there?
At this time of night?
I intend to settle things with Leon.
Whichever one of us can become
a true demon will be your partner.
Sophie might have realized your
true colors long before she died!
Shut up!
Sora!
That's right.
This is fine.
I'm satisfied with this...
Stop it.
Sora!
Both of you, stop it!
This is a stage!
I can't believe you'd
hurt each other on a stage!
No matter which one of
you becomes my partner,
an Angel's Maneuver that can't be
created without doing things like this...
A maneuver like that is meaningless!
The stage is grieving. Can't you tell?!
When fighting and hatred
hang over the stage, it grieves.
You say the same things as Sophie...
I promised her.
I promised I'd perfect the Angel's Maneuver
and make the "true star" a reality.
A true star will wreathe the stage in smiles.
Everyone's hearts will come together as one...
The performers and the audience...
will be like a family...
Promise me, Leon...
Yes.
Sophie? Sophie!
Sophie!
But the truth is, I wasn't confident
that a true star could really exist.
And that "stage without battles"
that Sophie dreamed of...
I still couldn't understand it.
She left behind the promise alone.
Sora is the only one who
can make good on that promise.
And the only one who can raise
her to be an angel is you, Leon.
Time stopped for you three years ago
when Sophie died, and it hasn't moved since.
I thought if you could start moving by
getting revenge on me, I'd gladly help, but...
You did this on purpose?!
I was doing it to atone.
For what I did to Sophie,
and for what I did to Layla.
You're an idiot.
Miss Layla!
You called me all the way over here for that?
You haven't done anything to
me that you need to atone for.
The value of the victory doesn't change.
You know about Miss Sophie...
I heard from Yuri, just a little while ago.
A stage without battles...
It sounds like Sophie was aiming to
become a true star without fighting anyone too.
I can't believe that that's possible,
but there is one thing I've figured out.
Miss Layla?
There's something very important that
I forgot to take care of before I left the stage.
It's all right, Yuri.
Leon will become Sora's partner.
If you mean to make good on
your promise, this is your last chance.
Yes.
You're right.
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
Perhaps what I'm feeling right now is jealousy.
And so, I've chosen a
different path than Miss Layla's.
And I meet that person our
destinies are entwined with again.
That's right, both Miss Layla and I began there.
The impression that day made on
us wasn't a lie! It wasn't! It wasn't!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Flight of the Amazing Angel."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...