Fortunes
Restore your divining powers in the spring!
A wide variety of medicinal baths and a big outdoor bath!
A big feast full of delicious foods waiting for you!
This is an Urara's paradise,
the Super Divining Baths!
SUPER
DIVINING
BATHS
Alright, everyone, do you want a bath? Dinner?
Or maybe...
Dinner!
Too bad, we're going to the baths first!
Why?!
She just wanted to give that line a whirl.
The greuling Rank 9 Urara exam is finally over,
and we're all gonna celebrate passing today!
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
BATHS
They're so fluttery!
Hey, Chiya!
You flipped our skirts!
You're under arrest for lewdness!
Just kidding.
We're fine even if you flip our skirts.
We've got our uniforms on underneath.
What?
Don't pull up your skirts like that!
They're hard to move around in.
Honestly, we could just take these off.
They are pretty hot to wear.
What? You can't!
What?
If you don't have anything to flip up,
you'll be a boring grown-up like Captain Saku!
B-boring grown-up?
Calm down, Saku.
Being boring is one of your strong points!
That's right, the Captain truly is boring,
but there's more!
She has wonderful qualities that nobody can imitate!
Like the absolutely perfect proportion
of skin showing on her legs!
Wh-what was that just now?
I got the worst chills...
That won't do, Captain!
Let's get a move on and warm you up in the bath!
We'll go check it out!
Let's go!
No, no, no, wait!
It's a little late to ask, but why are they here?
I invited them.
Huh?
We were having a celebration after all,
and I figured the more the merrier, so...
Did I do something wrong?
No, it's good to relax sometimes.
They're giving it their all every day, too.
Captain Saku is so kind!
We're gonna feel that kindness skin to skin today!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Heart!
Nono, hey, could you help me real quick?
I can't get the ribbon on the back undone.
Here?
Yeah, if you could.
I tied it a little too tight.
Koume, what's that weird top?
It's not weird! It's a corset.
A corset?
Yup.
It's a magic item that slims your waist
just by putting it on!
It makes your waist slim...
Every Western lady has one!
Doesn't it hurt?
Of course it hurts, but beauty before comfort, right?
That philosophy's just not right...
That's not right at all!
You're not really Koume if you don't have a squishy belly!
Are you trying to pick a fight?
I didn't know there were Western clothes like this.
I kinda want one, too.
You like it, Nono?
Huh?
M-my body's like a little kid's, so maybe wearing it
will make me look a little older.
Nina-sensei's got a really pretty figure, too.
She's so mature!
Speaking of which, Chiya-chan and Kon-chan
have nice bodies, too!
Yes. I'm so jealous of them, Matsuko-san.
You're scaring me, Nono!
Okay, you wanna try it on?
Can I?!
Yeah!
I mean, we're gonna get buck naked after this anyway,
so let's have some fun switching outfits!
But it'd be boring if it was just Nono...
BATHS
No, no, no, I couldn't!
Wh-why do I have to change into Chiya's clothes?!
'Cause it's more fun
if everyone switches with one another!
Doesn't it feel good to be wearing something
other than what you usually wear, Kon?
NO IT DOESN'T!
There's too much of a breeze!
There's a breeze where there shouldn't be a breeze!
This is the worst outfit I've been put in yet!
How're you doing, Chiya?
Oh, you actually look pretty ladylike now!
It looks great!
How nice...
I-it's so tight!
SHE
LIKES
BEING
NAKED
BEST
OF
ALL
A kimono on top of a shirt!
What kind of training is this?!
Looks like this is the worst for her, too.
Umm...
Wh-what do you think?
Do I look enough like a witch, like Koume-chan?
I'm a witch, too!
You look great, Nono!
Do I look mature?
Yeah, yeah!
You look more mature than Nina-sensei!
Right, Koume?
Huh?! Y-yeah, she's cute, but...
Why're you upset?
I'm not upset!
I-I'm not jealous that she got to look
more like a real witch than me...
Huh?
I wish I were blonde...
What?!
Nothing.
Didn't expect that.
You're the cute one, Koume-chan.
You're the last one I wanna hear that from, Nono!
You damn cute thing!
What?!
What're they having so much fun with over there?
Saku!
Wha-?!
What do you think? Does it look good?
Maybe I'll become a city guard, too!
Don't play around in our uniforms!
It's a little big for me!
Seriously... hurry up and get ready!
Oh, that's right, Saku. There was one thing
I wanted you to help me with before we get in.
This feels so good!
I wish Tokie-san could've come, too.
No way, my mother's the head of Tatsumiya.
But I did talk to her a little after the exam.
Kon, congratulations on passing.
Mother...
But you're not going to tell me
you're happy where you are, right?
Rank
If you're upset about it,
then hurry your butt up and get up here.
...she said!
Why does your relationship make it sound like
you two are fated rivals?
We're not rivals!
I'm still much too far from my mother's rank.
But one day, I'd like to get there...
to be a better Urara than she is.
TATSUMIYA
That's why I split off from her Tatsumiya and came here.
But that's how I met all of you.
I have friends who all want to become
Rank 1 Urara together.
I feel like I've found true happiness!
Kon-chan!
That face right now makes you look so mature!
Hey, everyone, what do you wanna eat when we get out?
Meat and anmitsu!
We're celebrating today, so it's totally fine
to have the Koume Deluxe!
You're gonna get too fat to pull you out of a hole again.
Okay, Chiya, give her the fury of a hundred pokes!
Okay!
Stop!
Come on now, don't make such a fuss in the baths.
DIVINING
BATHS
That's bad manners.
You're drinking in the bath!
You're the one with bad manners!
No fair, no fair, how come Nina-sensei
and Captain Saku get to break the rules?!
We're not!
Sake is a special drink that cleanses
the soul of an adult, just like a bath.
Right, Saku?
Mm-hmm.
What an excuse.
UNDONE
Still, I can't believe you're all Rank 9 Urara.
Chiya, do you remember...?
The night you tried to sneak into Bloque 9?
Uh... I do...
Good girl.
You remembered our promise
and worked hard towards it.
Good work, Chiya.
Captain Saku!
Why are you all lined up?
Don't fret about it!
We're waiting our turn to get petted!
I won't pet you!
But you know somethin'?
My amazing shtudentsh actually passhed,
I'm sho proud of them!
She's completely gone.
Big Sis...
No, she's only just begun.
Huh?
Note: In Japan, at a party it's considered bad manners
to pour one's own drinks
POURING
HER
OWN
SAKE
Nina's happy when she first starts getting drunk,
POURING
HER
OWN
SAKE
then she gets really weepy.
After that, she starts singing and dancing
and telling fortunes for everyone.
How annoying.
She finally comes to her senses the day after
and tries to commit seppuku. It's a real pain.
But that's what makes Nina really cute.
Huh? Is Captain Saku drunk, too?
Okay, everyone, listen up!
I'm going to perform a song that's been
passed down in Natsumeya for generations,
a song filled with all the Urara knowledge!
The Onsen Ondo!
And a one, and a two... Go!
Onsen, onsen, go! Onsen, onsen! Go!
If you go to the onsen,
you'll get buck naked!
Wow, wow!
All your exhaustion melts away!
Nice, Nina!
Your whole body under, getting so smooth!
S..Saku-chan, what should we do?
Man, Nina's the best!
Take in her performance, m'kay?
Then you gotta give her one right back.
A good little trick 'r somethin'!
She's hopeless...
A trick, huh? I got one!
It's show time!
Chiya Censoring!
What do you think?
No matter how much it seems like it'll show,
you can't see a thing!
It's a close battle!
Umm...
Y-yeah...
We can see everything from behind.
Huh?
Buck naked!
Here we go!
BALANCING
IN
THE
BATH
The weird onsen variety show continued...
IMPRESSIONS
CELEBRATION
DANCE
I healed everyone's hearts with an impressive dance.
Healed?
The hopeless adults turned into
an even more hopeless situation,
but we all had a wonderfully fun time.
But not a single one of us had realized...
...that a terrifying disaster was creeping up on us.
Jeez, you scared me back there.
I can't believe everyone got dizzy from being in the bath.
They were moving around too much!
I mean, I was too, but...
S-sorry,
I just wanted to celebrate us becoming Rank 9 Urara...
Kon-chan...
Well, then, once Nina-sensei's up,
have her do some divining for you.
Ask her to show you how we've grown.
My Rank 9 card is gone!
Mine's gone, too!
Did someone...
Cadence is gone, too!
My kokkuri paper's missing!
Ma-Ma-Ma-Ma-Ma-Ma-...
Matsuko-san's gone!
Nono!
The incident must have taken place
during the 40 minutes we were in the bath...
Who did this, and why?
I don't know...
But we'll find them for sure!
Yeah! Those Rank 9 cards are important to us!
Oh!
What?! Did you find it?!
This is Matsuko-san's hair!
Huh?!
How do you know?
There's some here, too!
...over there, and here,
and here, and there!
I see, Matsuko-san's shedding right now.
WHAT?!
If we follow this trail, we can find Matsuko-san!
Hold it, hold it, hold it! This is creepy!
I get it!
Some animals grow in new fur
when the seasons change!
A-animals?!
Let's just go!
Hey, w-wait! What IS Matsuko-san...?!
Umm, uh...
There are no more hairs to follow!
S-so that means...
What's up, Chiya?
There's a sweet smell coming from over here!
A sweet smell?
Like what?
Hmmm, like sugar and soy sauce boiled together...
That's what goes on soy-glazed dango.
Wow! You know that just from the ingredients?
Ahem. I don't go for Arinsu just for show, you know!
But soy-glazed dango have nothing to do
with our divining tools.
They do so!
I just remembered that yesterday some of the glaze
from the dango I was eating fell onto Cadence!
O-oh...
I wiped her off, of course!
Chiya's keen nose picked up on it.
But I don't know where the smell is coming from.
Over here!
What?
Wait, Kon-chan!
H-here?
Yes, probably.
How did you know, Kon?
This!
Ants!
I get it, ants go after the smell of sweet things!
This ant line leads...
Over there!
Okay!
Found it!
FRIENDS!
I found it in an opening behind the waterfall!
Let's go!
RANK
We did it!
Matsuko-san's hair is so shiny!
She must've grown out new hair!
Eek!
C'mon now.
I'm really sorry!
I would've never thought it was you, Nina-sensei.
I went to imbue your instruments and cards with power
by purifying them in the Watcher's Waterfall...
We were supposed to tell you before
we got in the bath, but we got drunk and forgot.
We're sorry.
Nina-sensei, what kind of power
does that waterfall have?
It has the power to protect Urara.
I wanted it to protect you in my stead.
Huh?
In your stead?
Wait, no, that makes it sound like you're going away!
The truth is, now that you're Rank 9 Urara,
you'll be staying at a school in Bloque 9.
What?!
You'll leave my side to further your studies
with other girls who have passed the exam.
What?! That sounds super fun!
Y-you're not sad?!
Of course we're sad!
We love you, Nina-sensei!
I-I'm nervous to be living without you too, Sis,
but I'm gonna try hard with everyone!
We know how much you care about us, Nina-sensei!
So don't worry about us anymore!
We'll use all of our strength together as one!
Thank you, Nina-sensei!
G-girls...
We've gotta cheer 'em on.
We'll always be in Bloque 10, Ma'am!
Yes, Ma'am!
Stop calling me "Ma'am"!
How about "Mom"!
And you're "Dad"!
Why am I the dad?!
I see a new family here now!
We'll happily become your children!
What the heck are you two going on about?!
Whatever you do,
we want to be in your life, Captain Saku!
We'll go crazy for your love!
D-don't shout ridiculous things like that so loud!
This...
This is...
This is Hea...
This is Heaven!
What's wrong, Chiya?
Just thinking...
RANK
We moved forward 'cause a lot of people
were cheering us on, helping us, and supporting us.
That's right.
That's why I want to get closer to our dream
by my own accord.
Hey, Kon, can I ask you something?
I got closer to my mom, too.
In that maze.
Huh?
I was really happy, but I was kinda scared.
Why?
I found out my mom's name.
Yami.
The Urara steeped in sin, Yami.
And the black ghosts in the maze...
They all seemed to really hate my mom and me.
I wonder where your mom really is.
Why don't you call for that Dark creature
and ask it to show you where your mom is?
I tried, but I couldn't call it to me.
I see.
I don't know why I can't.
Just more mysteries for us.
Well, maybe that's good!
Chiya said something like that once.
It's more fun if we don't know something.
Kon...
I think I understand how you feel now.
I'm feeling excited for some reason!
Yeah!
There's a whole lot of new things we don't know,
but there is something we do know!
If we keep smiling and moving forward,
I'm sure I'll meet my mom!
I'm so glad I came to Meirocho!
That's right! You'll meet her someday!
Y-you think so?
I do. You don't believe the prophecy
that you'll be a Rank 1 Urara someday?
No, I believe it. Thanks, Kon!
Okay!
Miss Plum here will divine
who will be the future Rank 1 Urara!
That's creepy! It's not gonna work!
I see it!
Every day will be fun, even in the future.
If the four of us stick together, it's sure to be fun!
Yeah!
Every day will be fun...
What kind of place is Bloque 9?
I wonder what the schools are like?
Maybe there are witches there!
Maybe we'll make new friends there.
Then we can all do kokkuri divination together...
I can't wait!
Okay, let's go there right now!
Chiya!
You can't!
It's fine, we have our Rank 9 cards!
That's not what I meant!
Hold up!
Hey, you four!
Don't go outside in that state!
Oshima, Shiozawa, after them!
Yes, Ma'am!
My goodness...
I guess I'm a little worried about them.
Perhaps I should join their school, too!
Nina?!
This is Meirocho.
A city of divination that is still full of mysteries.
Hey!
Hold it right there, Chiya!
Chiya-chan!
How will these girls' dreams play out?
I said wait, Chiya!
Chiya!
Do not wander astray, but follow the arrow's guide.
Chiya-chan!
Hup!
No matter what lies beyond tomorrow.
The end!
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?