[(3:32)sign: [bright purple]Up[/bright purple]roar]
A lot more people around town have
been wearing yellow recently, haven’t they?
The Yellow Scarves?
Did you hear?
There's a rumor that the Slasher is part of the Dollars.
We really do need you...
How's your boyfriend been?
He comes to visit sometimes.
At least until recently.
Don't you think the air in Tokyo is dirty?
Parasite! Parasite! Parasite!
Did you hear?
Some Raira Academy students just got assaulted by the Slasher!
Eh? Really?
How dangerous...
As serious as the stare of Daimajin!
I heard they were first year girls!
Excuse me,
I've got to make a call, so I'm going to lurk for a while.
Don't worry.
Apparently it wasn't your girlfriend.
Thanks.
But I'm still kind of worried about her...
Hmmm.
Do you know where it happened?
Umm...
It's not far from the Eastern Ikebukuro subway station that borders the Shuto Expressway.
But there are a lot of police cruisers
there, so it should be easy to find.
Is that so?
Sorry, I'm leaving for a minute.
Setton, you going rubbernecking?
Setton has left the chat room.
Aw, c'mon!
Excuse me,
I'm leaving, too.
Eh?
Did you get through to her?
Right now she's with the police or something...
She apparently witnessed the incident...
I'm going to see her.
Tanaka Taro has left the chat room.
Ah...
Then I'll leave, too.
Tanaka Taro has left the chat room.
Kanra has left the chat room.
Today.
I cut.
I cutted.
Today.
I cut.
I cutted.
Wrong.
I cut.
I cutted.
Wrong.
More,
I cutted.
Wrong.
More,
Strong,
Wrong.
More,
Strong,
Love,
More,
Strong,
Love,
Desire,
The Slasher...
Strong,
Love,
Desire,
I,
Want,
Desire,
I,
Want,
People strong
I,
Want,
People strong
Who hear?
Want,
People strong
Who hear?
Want, to hear
People strong
Who hear?
Want, to hear
The culprit behind this bloody incident...
...changed the fate of one girl...
At that point, I was completely unaware...
That all this was mysteriously tied to my past.
Mother
[Mother]
I'm home!
It's time for...
A welcome-home greeting!
I'm home, Celty!
Welcome back.
What's wrong?
I just saw something horrifying.
Something horrifying?
Don't make me say it! I want to forget!
I feel much better.
Why don't you at least take that white thing off when you shower?
Nope. The air here in Tokyo is dirty,
so I can't just take it off whenever.
Oh, That's right.
Good job last night, Celty.
And just who were those brutes wearing all that yellow?
They're the Yellow Scarves.
They appeared around the time you left for America.
They got in a brawl with the Blue Squares a
while ago and were supposed to have calmed down.
Hmph. They should just destroy each other and go die in some sewer.
Don't be ridiculous.
Anyway, Celty brought you here safely, so pay the fee.
Put it on my tab.
Absolutely not.
Then I'll just bilk you out of it like I always do.
I was just testing you, Celty.
If you just let me go now—
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's cutting into me! It's cutting into me!
These shadow thorns are cutting into me!
Shinra! My life is in real danger here.
What should you do in this kind of situation?
You'd know if you were my son!
Of course I do.
What?
Thanks.
I'm not giving you an inheritance, so that can be it.
I don't need any.
I've been had by a monster...
If you'd truly been had, she would've taken your soul.
Oh?
Well, well, well, Celty.
Are you...in love with Shinra?
I knew my son would be weird enough to get
attached to you, but do you actually like him too?!
Yes, I do.
Celty!
It's great that you're being so honest about our relationship!
The fact that our connection, which I
thought was no more than unrequited love,
has developed into a solid relationship
that we can boldly express in front of others...
Fills me with thoughts of jumping for joy—
Stop it; you're embarrassing me!
Did you think I'd approve of this relationship?
What was that?
You're an uninvited guest in human society.
You're aware of the fact that you're
commonly referred to as a monster, aren't you?!
Of course I am.
"Of course," she says...
So what? Do you have a problem with that?
It seems my plan to point out that she
won't fit into society has failed miserably.
That's not in the least bit convincing, coming from you.
Moreover...
Shinra says he likes me the way I am.
Hmph. There's nothing I can do.
I approve of you two dating.
In return, you shall call me...
...my beloved father!
Shove it!
Even so, Celty...
Your memories will never return as long as you remain headless.
Your memories of when you were a dullahan in your native country of Ireland, that is.
That's...
Something I'll have to live with.
Let's create a lot of memories
together to make up for the ones you've lost.
Shinra...
For starters, let's hold a wedding!
I'll measure your for your wedding dress,
so take off those shadow clothes—
Come to think of it, you were a perverted
child who'd laugh merrily at an autopsy...
He definitely gets that from you!
It's not "you," it's "my beloved father!"
Honestly...I just said it a moment ago.
You're as thoughtless as ever, Celty.
That's why you had no idea I stole your head—
Huh?
Ah, crap!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What did you just say?!
What should I do? I just spilled the beans about an important secret.
It's still okay.
Celty's an airhead, so she won't notice.
Huh?
Celty the airhead, Celty the airhead...
Shut up! Why'd you say that twice?!
Because the attacks of a frenzied airhead are easy to rea—
I won't let you make fun of Celty, even if you are my dad.
I get it, I get it! I'll explain everything.
Well, there's no point in hiding it now.
The person who stole your head and sold it to a
pharmaceutical company was none other than me!
Don't be such a jerk!
Whatever.
Come with me.
There's something I want to show you.
Huh? He ran away?
That perverted freak...
I won't let you get away!
Is she gone?
It seems my "just push the elevator button" plan was a success.
I'm going to get my bags.
Well now...
Beep.
Damn, where'd he go?
Oh, Celty...
Is something wrong?
You're just spacing out in a place like this...
Well, I'm thinking about some stuff...
Talk to me.
About that "stuff." You look pretty depressed.
It's about the Slasher...
There are some weird rumors on the Net and message boards...
Weird rumors?
Yeah, like the Slasher is part of the Dollars.
That's absurd.
Do you believe that?
Of course I don't, but...
But something dangerous will probably happen if the rumor gets around.
Especially since relations between the Dollars and
the Yellow Scarves are strained enough as they are.
The balance of this city certainly is hanging over a precipice...
Mikado...
I'll look into the Slasher incidents as well.
Celty...
So get out of here.
You're bound to get caught up in
something just zoning out in this type of place.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
The Slasher, huh?
Sorry, but it doesn't ring a bell.
I see...
There's no reason for you to do all this for the Dollars, is there?
It's not just for the Dollars...
I have a history with him.
If I weren't headless, I'd be dead now.
You idiot...
People who call others idiots are usually more idiotic, but I'm an idiot, so I'll say it anyway:
Idiot! You should've said something!
Alright, I'm gonna kill him!
I'll definitely kill him!
Without a doubt, I'll kill him!
I'll hunt him down and kill him!
Wait, I'm the headless rider!
I'm fine!
No, no, no...
It's no longer just about that.
Drawing your sword usually means certain death, right?
I'll kill him...
What about your work?
You're only on break now, right?
It's fine.
Hey now, I'm not going to let you get fired over me.
Moreover, I need a lot more information before I search for the Slasher.
Can you at least wait until I'm done with all my preparations?
Fine.
But make it as fast as possible.
I'll kill him...
There's a reason I parted with Shizuo.
Wow, I'm so happy you came to see me.
By the way, how are you?
Did you find your head?
I don't care about my head.
I'll get right to the point:
I want to know about the Slasher.
Three bills should do it.
Although, your clothes and your wallet are made of shadows, aren't they?
I wonder if it's possible to shine a light on
them that's bright enough to leave you naked.
Do you want to see me naked?
Not really.
Unlike a certain perverted,
black-market medical scholar,
I don't lust after headless or bodiless girl—
That's fine with me.
But I won't let you off so easily the next time you insult Shinra.
You two sure do love each other.
But hey...
What would happen if another dullahan came along, seduced him, and stole his heart...?
I'd like to think that wouldn't happen...
But if it does, it does...
Would you kill Shinra yourself then?
No...
I just wouldn't let him go near...
Another headless woman.
I love him, too, so...
That's surprising!
You've become even more human!
Still, be careful.
The closer you get to becoming human...
The bigger the gap will be when you get your head back.
I'll think about that after I actually get my head back.
Well, to be honest, I've been thinking that I might not even need my head.
More importantly, give me that information about the Slasher.
Don't tell me you don't know anything after you've taken my money.
Don't worry.
I have some special information that I've yet to leak to the police, the media, or the Net.
Actually, I've been waiting for you to come.
What do you mean?
This incident belongs in the realm of the fantastical.
Do you know of a katana called Saika?
The Saika...?!
It may be hard to believe, but Saika is an
ethereal sword that used to reside in Shinjuku.
An ethereal sword...?
Like the Muramasa Blade?
Right.
It's a katana with dubious magical powers.
What's wrong?
I heard about some ethereal sword called Saika from Izaya.
There's a legend that it has a mind of its own and takes control of humans.
Plus, every single one of the Slasher's victims says that it has red eyes.
You're saying that's because of the Saika?
Yes.
The night the Slasher first appeared, someone with the handle "Saika" logged onto the network I use.
But when I was attacked, I didn't notice it approaching.
I should be able to sense something if Saika isn't human.
That would be because the Saika can only control one's mind, while the person's body is the thing that's actually moving.
Then it's understandable why you couldn't sense any type of presence.
Shinra, you seem pretty knowledgeable about Saika...
I mean, you told me to look into it before, didn't you?
Now, come to bed quickly.
I thought, "Shinra's hiding something."
Hey, welcome back.
When I conducted my own search for Miss Namie after Nebula merged with Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, I found out that she frequents your place.
So I threatened her with this model gun and she let me come in with her.
A model gun?!
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Shouldn't we report this guy to the police?!
Oh, won't you be the ones in trouble if you do that?
Once the police conduct a search of this room based on
my testimony, they'll find the head of some young woman!
I see.
This might become a first-rate scandal to take the place of the Slasher.
So...Shinra does get his twisted personality from you after all.
You won't get anything for complimenting me.
Well, to be honest, I'm in no rush to get the head back.
Oh?
The executives at my company are quite
surprised at what they saw of Celty on TV.
They've decided that her body should be studied before her head.
That's why I've unilaterally decided that the
location of her head is "currently under investigation."
After all, it seems that you've taken quite
an interesting approach concerning her head.
Based on the theory that a valkyrie is a dullahan, you try to awaken it by causing a power struggle.
What a unique idea.
Well, I'm testing it in various ways.
If worse comes to worst, I might just have to bring it to a war zone.
Anyway, I'd be happy to cooperate with you.
Great.
I'm also interested in you.
There aren't many people around who'd conduct
research from a mythological point of view, including myself.
Thanks.
Well now, why don't I give you a piece of advice?
If you do cause some manufactured conflict in order to stimulate either Celty's head or spirit,
don't involve her in some clash of wills between other people...
But make her body the center of it all...
And throw those around her into the fire.
That's what I plan on doing.
Things are being set in motion faster than I'd anticipated.
Anri...
You're already making preparations for the sports festival?
Are you sure you're okay?
Y-Yes...
I was worried about you.
Why were you with those students who got slashed?
You weren't being bullied again, were you?
I'm worried.
I really am.
The Slasher might come after you again.
It's dangerous to go out alone.
Are you sexually harassing her again?
We can't have that now, can we?
I'm just worried about Anri.
Whoa, using only her first name?
How dangerous!
If you worry too much, Anri might transfer out like Niekawa did.
You were Niekawa Haruna's homeroom teacher last year, weren't you?
What?
You know about Niekawa?
Yes, in name only.
On that note, us students have to go home!
Who in the world is Niekawa Haruna...?
Hey, Anri...
Mikado hasn't confessed to you yet, has he?
Eh?
I knew it.
But you have noticed he's totally fallen for you, right?
Ryugamine's a good friend, so...
My best friend seems like he truly does
love you, so I'm going to look after you two.
Plus, I should get along well with beautiful girls from all over the world.
Masaomi!
Sonohara!
Enter the coward.
Sorry again!
I thought I'd turn into a fossil waiting for you!
Eh?
Square root of three points.
A square root? What's a square root?
At least make your criticism easy to understand with something like "minus twenty points."
See you!
See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
You finally came.
Celty...
About Saika...
It was in my father's possession for a while.
He apparently sold it to an antique shop a few years ago, though.
Shingen had it?
What for?
It's said... that the Saika can cut people's souls.
It couldn't be...
Yes.
He used the Saika to steal your head.
He used it to cut the soul that bound your head and body together.
And you knew about that, Shinra...?
Yeah.
Of course, I realized he used it to steal your head only
after I'd conducted my own investigation after the fact.
I thought I'd best not say anything, since you were trying to forget about your head.
But...
Just...
Let me think about this on my own.
I knew it...
Love breeds confusion.
That same night, the ethereal sword Saika was trying to find a certain girl.
A girl who couldn't find her own place in this reality...
Sonohara Anri.
Ikebukuro:
All I wanted was to learn about it.
About the source of this refuse-packed city's energy,
and the truth behind this city that bulges with desire.
Next Time: Even Fools Can Give Good Counsel.