How do you do, Ein?
Or should I say ex-Phantom?
But that was in the past.
I am... Phantom now.
Rage
Scythe calls me Drei.
Ein, Zwei, Drei...
I don't have to explain, right?
Greeting people with "How do you do"? How lovable Phantom has become.
If I just wanted to kill you, I could have done it any time.
But that wouldn't be fun, right?
Locating you and driving you into a corner, then killing you...
I've lived the past two years looking forward to just doing that...
while being the property of that damn Inferno.
So, I'll have fun as much as possible...
watching you run in fear.
Will that satisfy you?
It will.
Reiji looked so shocked when he saw me.
He became pale, like he saw a ghost.
What shall I do next? I know...
Why don't I kill you in front of him?
How do you think he'll react?
That won't happen.
Huh?
Unfortunately, you ran into me first.
You'll be... killed here...
by me.
Oh? You're prepared.
You risk your life to protect Reiji?
How commendable.
It's you who is commendable.
Huh?
You couldn't forget the fact that Reiji abandoned you all this time, could you?
You wish he'd regret it more.
You wish he'd feel sadder.
But he's no longer the Reiji you knew.
He put the past behind him and lives in the present.
So what?
You're only a ghost from the past.
If you stand in his way,
he will... shoot you.
You talk like you know everything.
You just don't know...
his real strength.
Here comes the hero.
Elen... Cal...
There's no reason for you two to kill each other.
Did you hear what he said?
Ein... sounds like you had the wrong idea.
Not yet. All the actors aren't assembled yet.
Drive.
Yes sir.
Go ahead and shoot... Reiji.
Please stop it, Cal.
You abandoned me once.
Once... twice... it makes no difference, right?
Cal...
Shoot! But... I'll take her down with me.
I'll take her to hell with me.
Stop it, you idiot!
Geez... this is just what I was afraid of.
Why are you acting so impulsively?
This has nothing to do with you.
We're in Japan, you dummy.
Don't think that you can get away with firing a gun in the middle of the day.
Who cares.
I see. Then shoot... Phantom.
But when you do
I'll shoot everyone down
including you.
Now, you first, Phantom.
Put down your gun and beat it already.
I've got my gun pointed at those two.
Bang!
Geez, what a boring ending.
Cal...
That's your successor, Zwei.
And I'm assigned to support her.
Thanks to that, I feel more dead than alive these days.
Thanks for looking after her.
Yeah, seriously.
In any case, you're done playing students.
The organization has found out your whereabouts.
Hurry up and get out of town.
Also, sorry to say this, but I'm not sure if I can continue to stop that mad dog.
Okay. We'll hurry.
Lizzie.
I really... uhm...
Live in the present, Zwei...
Live the life Clo couldn't.
Were you going to shoot?
How about you?
I...
She and I... If you had to choose one of us...
If that happens...
We don't have time now.
I'll secure an escape route.
During that time, we'll have Inferno restrain Drei.
The time to use our trump card has finally come.
Hurry up.
We'll go without you!
Ah, sorry!
Come in.
Excuse me.
You've got a phone call, bro.
Who is it?
Well... he said he's Claudia's right hand man.
Shiga speaking.
It's been two years, Toru Shiga.
Who is it?
I'm just who I said I was.
Hm?
Claudia McCunnen's right hand man?
The Asian brat who was always by her side...
If I remember correctly, he was an assassin called...
Phantom!
That's right.
I heard that you're under pursuit by the organization.
What do you want now?
You know Shinokura Academy, right?
Shinokura...
That's right. Kaiten Godo's... the Godo Family's head's daughter,
Mio Fujieda, goes to that school.
Hey, you do understand, right?!
What you're talking about is off-limits!
Don't worry. As long as nothing happens to us, we won't harm Mio.
As long as nothing happens.
What do you mean?!
Inferno's assassin is after me right now.
Stop her, Toru Shiga.
Put a collar on Inferno in Japan using your power.
Don't be ridiculous!
Whether you do it or not is up to you.
It has nothing to do with her!
Do everything possible, anyway.
You've become a good actor, too.
Not as good as you are.
If things go well, we can buy some time.
Shiga is smart. It'll be fine.
I'm sure he'll do as we hope.
What if it doesn't work?
If that happens, we'll come up with another way.
I don't intend to put Mio in danger.
Drei...
Are you happy that she's alive?
Yeah.
I thought she died on that day.
I thought because of me...
because I dragged her, a bystander, into my business, she died.
But... she was alive.
I'll head north at dawn tomorrow.
There's a smuggler cargo boat. I'll go negotiate in person.
Going by yourself?
Yes. You stay by Mio's side.
Now, let's go home.
It's gotten late. I'll make dinner quickly.
Hey, Phantom!
I heard from the senior members earlier and...
Dammit!
Looks like she has heard already.
The daughter of Kaiten Godo, the Godfather of the Godo Family,
whose existence has been kept secret from the public...
Seems like Zwei and Ein didn't disguise themselves as students just for fun.
Who gives a damn about the Japanese mafia!
Cool down, Phantom.
The Godo Family is also a respectable member of Inferno.
She's right. Your hands are tied until the safety of Godo's princess is secured.
Zwei outwitted you.
This is it for this time. Wait for the next opportunity.
Dammit!
Guarding a high school girl?
That's right.
Who is she?
You don't have to know.
But she's an important person to me as well as to our Family.
So you need us for that?
Yeah.
Do all you can to protect her, even at the cost of your lives!
Got that?!
Yes sir.
Do you detest him that much?
Of course.
Why do you think I've been doing as I'm told by this damn organization?!
It was so that I could hunt down and kill that man.
Just for that.
To be honest, I'm relieved.
Huh?
I can't bear to see you and Zwei kill each other, Cal.
Boy, you don't have confidence in me, do you. You think I'd lose?
That's not it.
It's true that he deceived many people and made a fool of them two years ago.
I was deceived, too.
He's quite the con artist.
But, when it comes to your case, Zwei was protecting you.
He deceived me all that time.
He didn't tell me anything and lied repeatedly.
He was afraid of... the moment that he couldn't fool me any more.
The reason why he lied... was to protect you.
Protect?
There was only one thing that he wanted to protect...
Himself.
He abandoned me after all.
He ran off with a woman.
But that was no reason for you to become an assassin.
It's not like you wanted to become one, right?
I wanted to.
Now I'm Phantom, who can scare even a crying child into silence.
Even those gangsters who used to do whatever they wanted in town
get terrified just by hearing my name.
It's great, isn't it?
Kicking those guys around, making fun of them and killing them...
Is there any other life that's this fun?
He was afraid of me.
He knew...
that I was going to be too strong.
He deceived and used me.
I'll make him pay for that dearly.
Cal... You're like a firework that burns itself out.
Is it true that Elen is absent today?
Yeah, she came down with a bit of a fever last night.
I think it's just a cold, though.
You should have told me sooner.
I would've gone to your place and took that cold from her.
...Hey! Hm?
I see you idiots are having a dumb conversation as usual.
Shut up.
By the way, we're all going to see a movie, so I'll let you guys come too.
Is that what you call an invitation?
Humph! Mio is coming, too.
Ahh... Sorry, I'll pass today. I've got something to do today.
Could it be a date?
Whoa, a good guess.
So, we were both tricked.
Looks like it.
That darn Sanae. "All going to see a movie"?
What a roundabout way of doing things.
Indeed.
I hope Elen feels better soon.
Let's go see a movie!
Even if I go home, I'll just interrupt Elen's sleep.
Okay!
This is convenient.
If I'm doing things with Mio Fujieda like this,
it'll put pressure on Shiga.
I got carried away like a kid. I'm embarrassed.
The movie was quite interesting, wasn't it?
I have to admit, I appreciate Sanae.
I think...
you are a little mysterious.
What?
How should I say...
I feel that how you see things is different from ordinary people.
What do you mean?
Everyday life is just natural and trivial to us.
But I feel like you really cherish it.
So when I look at you I come to like where I am right now.
Even if things are boring and you get tired of them,
they all mean something.
I feel that everyone might just be forgetting that.
Am I interrupting?
Reiji...
I see... so that girl is Mio Fujieda, huh?
Ein, me and Godo's daughter...
You sure do use all the women who get close to you.
I know you don't really intend to do anything to her.
Cal...
Now, let's resume the game.
Let's settle who the real Phantom is.
You are Phantom, Cal.
I'm just a student now.
Don't make me laugh, Zwei. You aren't like that.
If you want my head, I'll give it to you.
What... have you continued to run up until today?
You didn't want to die.
You just wanted to live.
Am I not right?
If I'm killed by your hands, that's just what I deserve.
I've been doing things that I deserve to die for.
But I have a condition.
In return for my life, I want you to let Elen... let Ein go.
So you want to sacrifice yourself for that woman?
She'll no longer be a problem for Scythe or Inferno.
So...
You want to protect her even if it kills you.
You abandoned me and ran off by yourself.
And yet you have someone that you have such feelings for, huh?
That's not true, Cal. At the time, I thought...
I'll kill you as you wish.
But first I'll hurt you more... and make you suffer more...
I'll kill you after that.
Reiji...
Next episode
Determination
If you can't shoot in this situation, you're a real softy...
so you dying here would be just natural.