Yoshii.
Yes!
Summon.
As he is the Punishment Bearer, Akihisa
Yoshii's Being is used for special purposes.
It possesses prodigious strength in addition to being corporeal.
Bring me the world map.
Fine.
Thus, he is treated as the teachers' gofers.
Yoshii, take the tables to the auditorium.
What?
Yoshii, take down the soccer goal.
Why do I always have to do it?
You're the Punishment Bearer, remember?
Dammit, this pisses me off!
The pain that the Bearer's Being feels will be transmitted back to its owner.
There's a quiz coming up. Make sure you review the material.
I'll review you!
Stupid.
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Fourth Period
Love and Spice and Boxed Lunches
Today is Sunday, but...
That's it for today.
Be sure to study at home.
Supplementary Lessons
Okay.
It may be the weekend, but class F is
required to take supplementary lessons.
By the way, Yoshii... What happened to your clothes?
Well... I went to review...
And you got your ass kicked, right?
Man, I'm hungry.
I'm particularly hungry today, since I was forcibly enslaved and all...
Your Being seems like it would be pretty convenient to have, but I guess not, huh?
Yuuji, lunch.
Shouko? Why are you here?
You guys don't have lessons today, right?
I came to do a little self-studying.
I don't care if it's Sunday as long as you're here.
You don't need to come.
I won't come if you won't come, even if it's a school day.
That's a problem.
You brought your own lunch today, right, Akihisa?
The hell's that?
1/67th of a cup ramen.
1/67th?
Half of half of half of half of half of half.
That's 1/64th, dude.
Man, you suck at fractions.
Stuff's not bad.
Man, I feel sorry for you.
I'd be bawling if that were my lunch.
V-very well! I'll just have to share my lunch with you.
Really!?
I made too much and forgot to take it out.
I guess it'd be a waste to trash it, so you want it?
Hell yeah!
One sec.
Where is it?
Sorry, I left it at home.
Gimme a break...
God, and I spent all that time on it...
Don't worry.
It's my bad. I almost believed that you had
done something feminine for a second there!
...and my neck is going to break!
I told you! I forgot to bring it!
A-almost...
Double Eye Poke!
Don't look.
These guys never quit.
Excuse me... is this class F, the one full of idiots?
What are you doing here, Hazuki?
Sis!
Hazuki...
Oh, Mr. Stupid!
Nice work, Akihisa. I had no idea the entire country knew you were such a dumbass.
Couldn't it just be the neighborhood!?
Awesome! You really are Mr. Stupid!
Hold on... Why do you know Aki, Hazuki?
He's my husband.
I'm going out with him because we're going to get married!
Akihisa had indeed met Hazuki before.
We'll explore the details later.
What the hell, Aki? What have you done to my sister!?
Time for an inquisition.
What are you doing!?
Defendant Yoshii Akihisa is charged with breaking the FFF's blood pact.
He perpetrated a felony by going out with a girl.
No objections, correct?
Correct.
Defendant, any last words?
Shouldn't my defense come before my last words!?
Verdict is guilty. Death penalty.
What grade are you in?
Fifth.
You're way more mature than Akihisa.
Oh, Miss Pretty over there!
Hello, Hazuki.
So why did you come here today?
Oh yeah!
Here you go! You left this at home.
My lunches! Thanks a ton, Hazuki.
Good thing you brought both of them...
See? I wasn't lying.
I know how to cook.
Oh, I see what's going on.
I was wondering why you were acting so serious
first thing in the morning. You even woke up early.
You wanted to make-
What are you talking about?
She's a little strange...
Oh, so you made a lunch especially for Akihisa.
No way! I'd die before I did that!
Then what exactly where you acting so serious over?
Well, not lunch, that's for sure!
It's that thing! A model!
A model?
The 1:35 King Tiger!
A German heavy tank...
You're in luck, bro.
It's bigger than your 1/64th of a cup ramen.
Does that matter?
Yeah, looks like this will work.
It's inorganic! It's inedible!
Anyway, Akihisa, I just made too much.
I definitely didn't go out of my way for you!
What's the matter, Himeji?
Nothing.
That's a boxed lunch.
Oh, Himeji brought one too.
Yeah, but I don't think it's any good...
Actually... I made this for you!
Yoshii, I'd be really happy if you ate it!
Time for an inquisition.
Dude, wait!
Verdict is guilty. Death penalty.
You're not even giving me a chance to speak this time!?
Wait! This isn't what you think!
Well...
Umm...
It's not like that.
This lunch is, umm...
Torture him first, then kill him.
It's hot! Hot! Hot!
Sis?
Jerk.
Are you okay?
Right as rain. I can endure any
hardship in order to eat your cooking.
Aww, shucks...
No one can interrupt us here.
I guess.
Whoa, this looks awesome!
I wouldn't say that...
Oops, I forgot the drinks. Hold on.
Himeji is cute, smart, and great at cooking.
You don't deserve this.
What the hell, Yuuji!?
Let me have some too.
You too!?
Hey, man, we're just having a few bites-
Yuuji!?
Hideyoshi!
What happened?
This ain't good, Voyeur!
We've gotta get these guys to the nurse's-
Voyeur!?
The food can't be...
No way. It looks so good.
That was close.
I almost got taken through the gate.
There's no mistaking it.
The food is the reason why everyone fainted.
Smelling it was bad enough...
A-Akihisa...
Hideyoshi!
Can you... Can you bring me a plate?
Plate?
They say you might as well swallow
the plate if you're eating the poison...
So I'll be fine if I swallow a plate...
Damn it, his cognitive ability is leaving him!
I brought some drinks.
Himeji...
What happened to them?
Well, they got a little tired after eating, so they took a nap.
If you take a nap right after you eat you'll turn into a cow.
I'd rather be a living cow than a dead human.
Here you go.
Thanks...
Crap. What should I do?
You'll hurt her feelings if you don't eat it. Tough it out.
Stop. You're gonna fuck yourself up something good if you eat that.
You'll be fucked.
You'll hurt her feelings if you tell her the truth.
What, are you suicidal?
You're not going to eat?
Well, uh... it's just so beautiful, I can't bear to eat it!
I'm asking you if you're suicidal, man.
Am I imposing on you?
No way! I'm so glad you went to all this trouble for me!
It's the thought that counts.
So don't go any further than the thought.
Thank goodness.
Do you try your own cooking when you cook?
They say you'll get fat if you do that.
Besides...
Besides?
I wanted you to be the first person to try it.
My fate is sealed.
You have no choice but to eat it.
You have no choice but to die.
Why are my super-ego and id agreeing with each other!?
Akihisa...
Yuuji!
Sakamoto?
I'm sorry, Himeji. Could you get me a drink?
I want some oolong tea.
Sure.
Yuuji!
Akihisa, I want you to listen to what I have to say.
Spices have been used to cure poison since the olden days.
Before the refrigerator was invented,
they were used as disinfectants in order to aid food preservation.
And they say that a girl's love is the strongest spice in her cooking.
Wait... That means...
Yes, that's right.
Use the spice named love to cure the poison.
I see.
Thanks, Yuuji.
This is a test!
Don't worry.
I'm prepared to cast my life away for the sake of love.
As long as I have the spice called love, no matter what the poison...!
Love can't cure poison.
You're my hero, Akihisa.
RIP.
What happened to Yoshii?
He got sleepy after eating.
You'll turn into a cow if you
take a nap right after you eat.
By the way, where's Shimada?
After all the time I spent on this...
I should have just been honest.
Man, I wasn't expecting that at all.
I never thought Himeji could
actually be bad at something.
I'm even more hungry now...
Aki...
Mr. Stupid!
Hazuki.
Have you seen my sister?
Actually, I haven't...
What happened to lunch?
Some stuff happened that prevented me from retaining the calories.
You must be hungry, then!
I should've asked Minami for her lunch...
My sister's?
Yeah.
I wonder what she made. Man, I really want to try it.
All right.
Aki, the boxed-
Let's have lunch together, Sissy!
Miharu!?
I've been looking all over for you!
I want you to try the special lunch I made just for you!
Why the hell are you here!?
Class D doesn't have lessons today!
I don't care if it's Sunday as long as you're here!
I won't come if you won't come, even if it's a school day!
Why does our school have so many retarded kids who can't think normally!?
Enjoy this fabulous moment with me!
Let's go look over there.
Stop following me!
Let's find an empty place to sit down and have lunch.
Buzz off!
Gosh, she's just too shy.
Sissy! Sissy!
Jesus Christ...
Whatever, I need to go find Aki...
Charge, Haiseiko!
Faster!
No running in the halls.
Aki... Thank god.
I'll make sure he takes it this time!
Just as we thought.
That bastard!
He had two chicks make him lunch!
This is inexcusable!
Traitors must be lynched.
Traitors must be lynched!
No! You're getting the wrong idea!
You're getting the wrong idea...
Well... Umm...
Uhh...
Dude, wait! Hang on! Stop!
You guys are out of your fucking minds!
What the hell is wrong with me?
Charge, Haru Urara!
Full speed ahead!
No running in the halls.
We're outside right now.
I've had just about enough for one day...
I'll make sure...
Aki.
Minami?
Sis!
Mr. Stupid was playing with me!
That's nice.
Just don't harass him too much, okay?
Hey, Aki.
Have you had lunch yet?
Well... I guess it could go either way...
Really?
Well, umm...
If you're hungry, umm...
I...
I?
I... I...
What's Oshamanbe's specialty?
Huh?
Shit!
Oshamanbe's specialty is hair crabs.
Kubo!
Are you here for some self-studying? It's Sunday, you know...
Class F has supplementary lessons...
You haven't eaten lunch yet?
Not really...
Why don't we eat lunch together?
I'm kinda broke...
Dearie me. Guess I'll have to pay for you.
Hell yeah! Let's do this!
Catch you later, Shimada.
While we eat, let's come up with
some strategies for the midterms.
Midterms?
Hazuki, have you eaten lunch yet?
Oh, I forgot to since I was busy playing...
Hey, you need to get your vitamins.
Don't you wanna get big and tall?
I thought this was for Mr. Stupid...?
Yeah right. Like I'd cook something for that loser.
I made it for you.
Let's eat it together then!
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot that I still have lessons.
Why don't you go home first?
All right!
I guess I'll take the A set.
Or should I get the B set since it's cheaper?
Oh, Yoshii.
Mr. Fukuhara.
Great timing.
I can't open this.
Could you summon your Being to help me open it?
Sure thing.
Summoning Being...
Summon!
Open up!
Those who were KIA are assigned supplementary lessons!
What!?
Wait a second! I still haven't had anything to eat!
Because you're a dumbass.
He's such a cutiepie.
What am I saying?
Allow me to dig in.
That jerk! That dumbass!
He's the biggest greatest hugest jerk in the world!
Who the hell would make lunch for him!?
Jeez!
Jerk.
Other
Glass, Cans, Plastic Bottles
Hold your horses!
Aki?
Are you going to throw that away?
Why?
Well, uhh...
Let's see...
There are starving people in Haiti, you know?
Huh?
If you waste food, global warming will kill us all.
And karma will come for you.
And, uh, I guess you can consider this recycling in an environmental sense...
I feel that we need to take great care with how we use nonrenewable resources.
Here.
Want it?
You don't?
I'll take it then.
Remember to cherish your resources-
Minami...
Stupid.
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Question five:
What's the name of the sport that requires a map and compass to reach a checkpoint?
RPG!
I knew that would be your answer.
Next episode: Maps and
Treasures and Striker Sigma V.
This will be on your test.