Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
I'll dispense you with the face of mask
kamen no kao de tebanasu no da
We meet only to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume nomama tabitatou
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru utakanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
Take them both to the treatment room.
Prepare them for dissection by the time I get there.
Chaika!
And toss that one in the dungeon.
He can at least be Fayla food.
Toru...
Get in there!
Izhmash-sama.
It appears the intruders escaped because of Ursula's poor handling.
I-I'm sorry!
This is a good opportunity.
After we're finished with the Chaikas, we'll get rid of her.
Please wait! Ursula didn't do anything wrong!
All the escaped prisoners were caught!
There's no need to punish—
Same goes for you, Cyril.
Once you've contributed cells for the mass-produced models,
there's no reason to keep you here.
All you demi-humans need to do is shut up and obey me.
The Emperor's Fortune
Rude! Stop!
Rude!
Not allow restraint! Not allow touch!
Pervert!
Rude man! Rude! Rude!
Release now!
Order! Release!
No touch!
Bullseye...
No debt.
R-Right.
No close follow! Separate!
One exit. No choice.
Cooperate, only now. Escape.
Rescue David, Selma... and other.
Other... Toru?
Cooperate, only now!
Accept?
Accept.
Not disturbed?
Chaika truth...
Memories fake...
Shocking truth.
Lies.
Decide truth, self.
Chaika.
Name?
My name is Niva Lada.
Niva...
Confined, restrained?
I have waited for Chaika.
Want come with?
Chance now.
Leave quickly.
Can't abandon! Rescue!
You stupid?!
Emergency now! Save others, no time!
Can't... abandon!
Release, success!
Startup factor verified.
Startup factor?
Urgent! Move now!
Right!
What is this?!
They escaped? They waste their time.
Lock down all the exits.
Release the demi-human troops and Orthros within the facility!
An alarm?
I wonder if something happened.
Their stronghold must be down here.
I'm worried about Brother. I'm going in.
Uh-huh.
You just need it opened?
Damn... They found out already?
Is Toru being held in here?
I don't know.
Did you guys see my brother and Chaika?
Nope, haven't seen them.
Have you two seen our Chaika?
No.
Hey...
Could you break down this door for us?
No time. Can't do it.
H-Hey! Hang on!
If you help us, we'll pay you back double someday!
Hey!
Chaika's...
So she has been here.
Hey, what about this one?
You said you'd pay me back double, right?
Yeah.
I'll remember those words.
Thank you.
Climb fast! Hurry!
Not only Fayla...
Demi-humans...
Duplicate... Mass produce?
Research, what purpose?
Understood? There are two girls!
They shouldn't be able to get far.
Find them and bring them here at any cost!
So the Chaikas got away?
I've gotta hurry...
Demi-humans...
Wait!
Are you friends of Chaika's?
Please, get us out of here!
You two? Why should we?
You could use someone to show you the way, right?
If you guys cause a commotion,
it increases our chance of surviving!
Please!
I will stay here.
Inform me the moment you find them.
Niva Lada is...
No way...
Where has she gone?
It couldn't be...
Did the Chaikas take her?
Toru!
We've gotta run!
You okay?
Yes.
And the other Chaika?
Of course.
And, this is...
You tried to play the hero again?
Girl, confined! Could never abandon!
I swear, you always do this...
Still no report?
No, sir. We're currently searching one area at a time.
We'll find the Chaikas soon.
I don't care about the Chaikas! Just get Niva Lada back!
All the exits are sealed.
If we search every last corner...
Izhmash-sama!
The exit in corridor #6 has been destroyed!
What?!
Assume level 1 alert status.
Mobilize all demi-human soldiers and Fayla over the entire island
and recover Niva Lada!
Kill anyone who interferes, no matter who they are!
Yes, sir!
I will go to the tower and mobilize the Fayla myself.
I'll leave things here to you.
Damn rats... There's nowhere for you to run.
Unicorns?
And so many of them...
Looks like this is no simple island.
Hey, you've gotta be kidding!
If all the Fayla are released, we're done for!
Our only choice is to destroy their control source!
Control source?
Little punks!
This way!
Hey, they're escaping outside!
Dammit! What are the unicorns doing?!
Sorry about that.
They looked dangerous, so we sealed the exit.
I don't think they'll be getting out of there for a while.
There she is! The princess!
Izhmash-sama?
Move. I'm taking over.
I never thought they'd take Niva Lada.
I finally completed her after extracting elements from all Fayla.
She is what the emperor entrusted me with!
I will find her at any cost!
Get down!
Now's our chance! Run!
Damn! With that many Fayla bearing down on us,
we'll never outrun them!
Are you all right, Chaika?
Akari!
Fredrica!
Here you go.
Grateful!
That's...
Brother, they are our guides.
What?
Does this mean
another young girl's purity has been tainted this night by my brother's wiles?
I'm disappointed in you, Brother!
I didn't bring her out here!
Come forth, The Slugger!
Your defense is weak, Sticky!
Chaika Bohdan!
Chaika!
Catch!
Grateful!
Don't stab me in the back the first chance you get.
Same to you.
Damn it! There's no end to them!
It's dangerous in the forest!
There's a place up ahead with a better view!
All right! Let's run!
An observation tower?
Yes.
It perpetually releases psychic waves across the entire island through controlling magic.
There's a magic receptacle in the brains of all the mass-produced beings,
through which they receive orders from the tower and act upon them.
So they use that tower to control the Fayla?
Not just Fayla. Demi-humans, too.
We were brought here from our homeland to
contribute cells to the mass-produced models.
But Izhmash disposed of the others of our kind, one by one.
We're the only two left.
Living weapons that act according to his will?
And this island is the factory where they're produced...
Pretty messed up.
Entire tower, most likely, Gundo.
Amplify magic, high output.
Yes... I think the magic that conceals the island comes from there, too.
So we just have to destroy that tower, right?
Questions later!
Battle, prepare!
Niva Lada... I've found you.
Those damned thieves won't get away with this!
Chaika! Can you climb up this rock?
Uh-huh?
We'll take on the Fayla.
You climb up and take out that tower with long-range magic!
Right!
Akari, back up Chaika!
Got it.
N-Niva!
Dangerous here!
Beside me, stay close!
Abt... Abt...
Kala... Silnicoba...
Come forth, take aim and destroy!
The Sniper!
Defense magic...
She fired!
A waste of time.
I'll feed her to the Fayla!
There are too many...
This is bad!
No luck, Chaika?
Try again.
Combat situation acknowledged.
Startup conditions met.
Initiating operations test.
Three of six seal spell layers removed.
Switching to functional mode.
Niva?
I am the Gundo Niva Lada.
I am currently in magic fuel consumption mode.
Niva... true form, Gundo?
Yes.
Possible. Can understand.
Niva Lada has... activated!
I see...
This is what the emperor wanted her to be!
Chaika! Are you all right?
No problem! No problem with me!
Final check complete.
Grant permission to begin spell?
Yes! Accept!
Activating offensive magic.
Come forth, to ruin and eliminate!
The Annihilator!
Niva...
I see...
So Chaika was the key to activating Niva...
The Chaikas coming to this island was part of the emperor's plan...
Are you guys staying here?
Yes. Izhmash is gone, anyway.
What about the Fayla and demi-humans?
Let them be and they'll die.
They can't even feed if they don't receive orders to.
So, we came to this island and found no remains.
I don't think either of us can leave empty-handed!
Why did we come here?
Huh?
Why did Guy send us here?
What if it was someone's plan to have us kill each other?
Well, no reason to go out of our way to fight here.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
We found a boat back there.
We'll be taking that home.
Next, we'll discuss the martial arts tournament in the Principality of Hartgen.
Is it true that the remains of Emperor Gaz are offered as a prize
to coerce participants into killing one another?
Kill one another?!
It's said that hundreds of the strongest fighters from across the continent
have taken up arms and begun to assemble.
There is suspicion that a military expansion is planned.
He wouldn't...
No, we have the precedent of Duke Gavarni.
We mustn't be negligent.
If we wish to act, it may indeed be wise to do so quickly.
We'll request that the tournament be called off immediately,
and deploy the allied army if they don't comply...
Wait.
What is it, General Fyodor?
It seems a bit hasty to use military force before confirming their true intentions.
Then...
If remains are involved,
there may be some connection to the Chaika issue.
Why don't we have the Kliemann Organization investigate
what's going on within the Principality of Hartgen first?
I'll take care of it.
Is Chaika all right?
Mind, confused.
I'm sure.
Memories...
Fortune...
Truth, fake...
Confused.
Why don't you take some time to think about it?
It's okay to stay here until you find the answer.
Whether we continue to gather remains after that...
You can take time to think before you decide.
Yes. Grateful.
You will gather the remains.
That is why Chaika exists.
I have waited for you.
The sky is overcast
The bell rings to signal the beginning
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
noroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
The time has come to break a curse
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
kono inochi kono ai mo
This life and this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
Captain Gillette was always pursuing Chaika.
I will continue where he left off and capture her myself.
But what is the emperor's fortune?
The Castle of Madness
Next time: "The Castle of Madness."