Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Perfect Weather
for Athletic Festivals
On this day...
...the sunniest day in autumn...
...athletic festivals are being held all over the country.
Fathers and Brothers
Enjoying Athletic Festivals
Man...
I came to cheer for my daughter...
...but I didn't expect such a turnout.
This was worth the trip.
Fathers and Brothers
Enjoying Athletic Festivals
I got some great pictures.
Look.
Dad.
Isn't this a great shot?
If you put it like this...
Which daughter are you talking about?
Don't Need Me
to Have a Blast
Maybe I should cut my hair for the athletic festival.
Go for a really short look.
You're going to cut your hair?
But it took forever to grow it so long.
I wasn't that serious about it...
That profound response...
...must have something to do with a guy!
Stop connecting everything to that subject!
And you stop talking so much!
But if Kagami cut her hair...
That's what I heard...
...but it's not unusual, right?
Ya can't!
Bipolar girls hafta have twin pigtails!
Sorry I have a boring face!
Oh, yeah.
The athletic festival's coming up.
Sounds like a pain.
Wouldn't expect to hear that from a young person.
Kona-chan's good at sports so she's okay...
...but someone like me...
...just drags everyone down.
Don't worry.
What event are you doing, Sis?
Well, it's Kagami, so you know...
A bread eating contest.
I've been wondering...
Are you trying to pick a fight or something?
So what are you going to do, Kagami?
I guessed right?
Did I guess right?
She pisses me off!
So I plan on doing some
independent training for the athletic festival.
Since fall is for sports.
But are you really training for the athletic festival?
Aren't you actually training
for the main event afterwards?
What do you mean?
You want me to say it?
She really pisses me off!
So Miyuki's participating in the inter-class relay.
Well, I can understand that one.
She was originally supposed
to be in the obstacle course.
Ball Roll
5m Dash
50m Dash
100m Dash
Obstacle Course
Matsuo
Shiraishi
Yamata
Izumi
Takara
Ball Roll
5m Dash
50m Dash
100m Dash
Obstacle Course
Matsuo
Shiraishi
Yamata
Izumi
Takara
Okay.
No more candidates, right?
I've never tried it so I can't wait.
That's no good, Miyuki-san!
Your body sticks out too much for an obstacle course.
Like Here
And Here
You'd have to go through stuff.
Like Here
And Here
After I said that, she was switched to the relay.
Isn't that something a middle-aged guy would say?
Oh, yeah.
Did you guys ever have a
scavenger race in middle school?
Sure did.
I was called up once...
Me?
For what?
...but he never told me what the criteria were.
Too many unspeakable things come to mind.
Well, just ask Miyuki-san
when you don't know the answer.
Don't ask her something like that.
It's impossible to answer.
And she really went and asked...
A character trait that would
come up in a scavenger race...
...that people wouldn't want to tell you about?
Perhaps he needed a person with a mole on her face.
Some people are sensitive about that.
I guess it was expected...
...but that was one masterful dodge.
But I'm pretty sure she's wrong.
I enjoy athletic festivals...
...but we have tests right after.
Once the festival's over...
...there aren't any more events which is kind of sad.
Midterms.
Practical exams.
Finals.
All we have are tests.
The second semester is a drain on your energy
with events like the cultural
festival and the athletic festival.
Right?
Midterms are particularly rough.
They also say that fall is for reading...
...so maybe I should read something.
It's also a good season to study for tests.
And there's a whirlwind of
new game releases before Christmas!
But finals come first.
Oh, yeah!
You two.
Could you stop trying to avoid reality?
I see.
The athletic festival's coming up, huh?
You know about the starter's pistol?
I thought it was a real gun until middle school.
No way...
That was when I knew I wanted to be a cop.
That misunderstanding led
to something totally unrelated.
That's right, Konata.
When's the athletic festival at your school?
This Sunday.
Th-This Sunday?!
Why didn't you tell me
such an important thing earlier?
But we just got the notice today.
There's no time to waste!
Why's he in such a hurry?
Okay!
Today's the big day!
Show me the fruits of your training!
Teacher!
I'm the type who does well without ever training!
Don't say that out loud!
Anyway, you better show some
backbone in the team chicken fight!
The fundamental strategy is to rush
in from all sides and whack 'em good!
So attack from their weak side, right?
But we only need to take their hat...
Hitting people's kinda...
Don't sweat the little stuff.
That's one of those mistakes of youth.
So we're just boys.
Sis!
Do your best!
Good luck!
Hey.
How is that anpan attached to the string?
It's probably attached to a clip or something.
So you can't take it off very easily.
Bring us victory!
Girls must be elegant!
Like an eating contest could ever be elegant!
Ready!
She did it!
That's Kagamin for you.
That person has an incredible camera.
Man, he's so easy to understand.
Hey.
Aren't you in the 100 meter dash next?
Technically.
How can I learn to run fast like you?
It's important to visualize.
Visualize.
Ready!
Set!
That's one ancient visualization.
Goal!
Like that?
Are you serious?
3 meters and 25 centimeters.
So they measure from where your hands reached.
This is it!
That's Kagami.
Dived straight into the sand, huh?
One, two, three.
I've heard that timing your
steps is important for hurdles.
Steps?
One.
Two.
Three.
I get it!
One, two, three.
Set!
One...
Um...
Three, two, three!
One, three, huh?
Um...
I started with my right foot so...
I don't get it!
That was my left foot so...
Three, three, three.
Three, two, three...
She's knocking every single one down.
You could say she's got talent.
Geez Louise.
I totally sucked.
Man...
I told you.
I thought my daughter was in this.
A common occurrence.
It's finally time for the last relay.
Yuki-chan!
Do your best!
No...
I told you that my daughter's...
I'll do my best!
Hold on a second!
I haven't even done anything yet!
Okay!
Go for it!
Pedal to the metal!
Awesome!
We're in second!
Not bad.
Sachi, over here!
Okay!
We've fallen to third.
This is what you call a race.
Keep at it!
Okay!
They're working pretty hard.
This is getting interesting.
Will Yuki-chan be okay?
Okay.
Okay!
Go, Miyuki!
Yay!
Yuki-chan's so cool!
That's our Miyuki-san.
Didn't forget to give the spectators some eye candy.
It's Tsukasa.
Oh, well.
Happy Henry Likes Beer But Could Not Obtain Food.
Hey!
Can you do something about that?
Sorry.
I chose to play the alto part
in a quartet for music class...
...but my fingers are getting numb.
Why did you choose the alto part?
I-I thought the lower part might be easier.
Why don't you condition your
fingers on an easy song for now?
You missed most of the notes.
So try to match me.
Ready and...
H-Hold on!
Play by yourself.
Somehow seems wrong...
Try blowing a little softer.
If you relax, it might go a lot better.
I see.
Softer...
That's it.
I'll give it a try.
Isn't she doing more breathing than playing?
I was thinking we should
try the cafeteria occasionally...
...but it sure is crowded.
It's pretty overwhelming.
And waiting in line is annoying and exhausting.
Sure sucks.
Haven't you gotten used to
this kind of thing from those events?
When I'm not eagerly anticipating what
awaits me at the end of the line, it sucks.
True to your desires, huh?
That's right.
I went to a theme park once...
...and thought that I had lined up for an attraction...
...but the line was for the restroom.
It's a fundamental rule to
check what the line is for first.
And I waited two whole hours...
I've also gotten in line a few times...
...and when it was finally my turn...
Cream Puffs
Sold    Out
...the person before me had bought the last one.
Terrible...
Don't even wanna picture it.
You're just unlucky.
Look, everyone.
What shall we have today?
Deep-fried Tempura
Soba/Udon
Fox
Miso
Ramen
Soy Sauce
Curry
S M L
Daily Special
A Meal
B Meal
Eggs
Special
Miso
Ramen
Soy Sauce
Curry
S M L
Daily Special
A Meal
B Meal
Eggs
Special
Well, I guess I'll go with curry.
They can't screw it up...
I'll go with ramen.
Me too.
I was planning on having miso ramen today.
With lots of corn...
...and seaweed, too!
Kagami's probably having ramen,
pudding, and an éclair.
If I have enough room to eat more.
You always have more room.
What about you, Yuki-chan?
I'll have a sandwich.
With strawberries.
Sounds like something you would have.
Right?
By the way...
Isn't a strawberry sandwich considered dessert?
Would it count as lunch?
Th-That's true...
You pick some odd issues to be concerned about.
What about those chocolate cornets you always have?
Wouldn't sweet pastries be considered dessert?
Stupid Tsukasa has the gall to give me lip...
Anyway, moving on...
Unfortunately, Miyuki-san...
The line for sandwiches is over there.
Typical behavior.
Walking is healthy.
Look.
It's your turn, Kona-chan.
Curry please.
With extra sauce.
Okay.
You're pretty shrewd.
I'll take what I can get.
Okay.
Next person?
Soy sauce ramen please.
With hard noodles.
Okay, please wait one moment.
Okay.
Here's your curry.
I'll go get a table.
Countin' on you.
Thanks!
Let's see...
Next person?
Yes.
Can I please have miso ramen?
Sorry.
The last person ordered the last of our noodles.
We're out of ramen.
Say.
If you're okay with soy sauce, do you want mine?
I'm okay with fox udon.
Thank you, Sis.
Hey, Sis.
You're the older sister because
you came out first, right?
Yeah.
I was thinking that it's a good
thing I'm the younger sister.
Why?
Because an older sister shouldn't be asking a
younger sister for help with homework and stuff.
I'm pretty sure that copying homework
has nothing to do with that.
Besides, we're twins.
Neither of us is really older or younger.
Stop worrying...
...and do your homework.
But if I were the older sister...
...and all dependable and responsible...
Sis!
Show me your homework!
Again?
You're so hopeless, Kagami.
Hey.
That was wack!
You okay there?
Get a grip.
I did it!
Newtype...
...published my...
...very own...
...postcard!
In the May issue...
Saitama province.
The one that has Akira-chan standing on Shiraishi.
Konata Izumi.
Good for you.
Look at it!
Kinda amazed they published this.
A-Amazing!
What a surprise!
This is pretty rare, yeah?
Like, seriously, huh?
Now I have one more thing to look forward to buying!
You don't need to praise me so much!
1,260 yen...
...and 567 yen, huh?
I'll have enough points after one more book.
Then I should just get something...
No.
Then I'd be falling into their trap.
I'm not so easy to fool.
That would be an unplanned
purchase for the sake of points.
That's their strategy.
I'm not dumb enough to fall for that trick.
Oh!
I forgot that the fifth volume was out.
Okay!
This works!
Genius
Oh, well.
Extra, yeah...
I can't get it loose.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to let go.
Yes...
I thought that only ever happened in manga or games...
...but it actually happens in real life.
Guess so.
Which means...
Those two definitely triggered a flag.
Konata...
Fantasy refers to the world of illusion.
Can't tell the difference between dreams and reality?
Good lucky!
I come with a dreamer's heart to spread love again!
I'm Lucky Channel's navigator, Akira Kogami!
And I'm the assistant.
Minoru Shiraishi.
We've already reached the
eighth episode of this program.
That's true.
If we don't come up with some fresh material...
...we'll be accused of abusing mannerisms.
What was that?
What am I doing?!
No.
I just wanted to try some new things...
You said it.
You know...
Do it.
That's right!
I was walking around town the other day...
...and someone came up to talk to me.
Was it some salon doing a survey?
Geez, Shiraishi-san.
Do you actually mean that?
Of course, it was a fan.
This would never happen to you...
Right?!
I-I-I-I-It wouldn't!
That's true...
Right?!
You're the assistant...
Well, keep workin' hard.
B-But...
I've already received this many...
A oopsie-daisy.
...fan letters!
H-How?!
Hey, Itou!
Haven't I gotten any?!
Incredible.
I feel like a real voice actor.
So I did get some.
Only one?
Your membership has almost expired...
Hey!
This is that stupid online service!
Everybody who's watching!
Please send me fan letters, too!
Big, big, big recruitment drive!
Akira-sama.
Shouldn't we get to today's topic...
Don't get too cocky.
You're easily replaceable.
I'm so sorry.
Ta-da!
I have an announcement to make!
Wow!
We'll be creating figures on this program!
Akira-sama!
The clipboard!
The clipboards upside-down!
Oh, you're doing it on purpose!
You're a genius, Akira-sama!
Actually...
...this project is...
Peel.
P-Peel. Peel.
Don't touch me.
Peel. Peel. Peel.
Huh?
That's weird.
This project is...
Don't touch me.
This is...
Peel.
What's wrong with this thing?!
H-H-Hey, Seishi!
A-Akira-sama, calm down!
I got it, okay!
That's the name of your manager in real life!
This is my prop!
Could you have...
Of course not!
Okay!
Then we'll decide which figure
to make based on your votes!
Have fun waiting for us to
turn the character into a figure!
Everyone, please vote!
Okay.
That's all for today.
Look forward to next week's Lucky Channel!
Bye-bee!
A character from the actual show's
obviously gonna win the poll.
What's with this?
Like I have a chance in hell.
No, you can't be sure yet.
I see.
They're finally going to make a figure of me.
What are you talking about?
This is...
That was great, Yuki-chan!
Thank you for listening.
I never expected this side of you.
Please...
It's embarrassing.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
Let's sing a song together.
Let's do that.
Sing! Sing!
A duet, huh?
Which song do you know?
Let's see...
Then I'll sing a song while we're waiting.
There's never gonna be a break, huh?!
You should also sing!
What is this?
Journey to the West.
Machaaki's Son Goku was great.
Huh?
Wasn't it Shingo-chan?
That was the third remake.
This one ran from 1978 to 1980.
The original series!
How old are you?!
This is a long intro.
This was when the actors delivered the main narration.
Like I would know!
Here it comes!
You're shouting again?!
Born from an egg on a mountain top.
It's in English. Forget that.
That's it after all this build-up?
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Miyuki.
When describing an enormously large object...
...it is described as being super-dreadnought.
The word dreadnought in this expression...
...was derived from a British
ship commissioned in 1906...
...the HMS Dreadnought.
In other words...
...something super-dreadnought...
...would be larger than a dreadnought-class battleship.
Well, that was the original meaning...
...but now...
...it's being used in the former context.
Next time:
「Just a Feeling」
Just a Feeling.
Look forward to next time!