Ah, Cherry...
Good morning.
Good morning...
Everyone's coming over today...
So be a good girl, okay?
Hello.
Coming...
Hello, Miyuki-san.
I baked some cookies yesterday.
I thought I'd bring some over for you to try, Minami-san.
Hello, Cherry-chan.
Would you like to try some too?
H-Hey, Cherry!
What are you doing?
Well, dogs sometimes tend to do that.
Ah...
Would it be alright if I gave her a cookie?
Ah, yes.
I'm sure she would be happy to have one.
Here.
She went to bury it.
She didn't eat it, did she?
Ah, it's Cherry-chan!
Her nose is all black!
Huh, that's strange...
Where did it go?
My cell phone...
Cherry-chan...
You didn't bury it, did you?
C'mon...
Keep on looking around.
R-Right!
You sure have a dirty face...
You always seem to have it easy...
Meanwhile, Tsukasa loses her phone...
Konata is way late...
She didn't even bother to call us, as usual.
Ah, geez!
No, because I am.
A Scorpio woman.
I'll laugh heartily.
Until I'm satisfied.
Hello!
Hello, Cherry!
Your paws are so hard...
Not comforting at all!
These paws aren't squishy like they are in manga...
I am in despair!
No reaction whatsoever.
Cherry, stupid dog.
There are times when even if call her, she won't wake up.
Also, she's not stupid.
Cherry, you stupid dog.
Cherry, you lazy bum.
L-Lazy bum?
Cherry...
You fat dog.
Drooling dog.
Stupid dog.
Lazy bum.
Oh!
At least she's aware.
A stupid dog like yourself that sleeps all day...
...deserves to be called a lazy bum!
Whenever I try, no matter what I do...
...she never wakes up.
Ah, she's sleeping right here.
Hello.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You're such a cute and quiet dog, aren't you?
Thank you, thank you.
Cherry-chan, you're so cute!
What are you doing?
C-Cherry-chan was being so quiet...
...so, I couldn't resist...
But to have a huge dog like this lying in the hallway...
This house sure is laid-back.
Well, she's so quiet.
Just looking at her makes me feel at ease.
I have a dog at home too, so I totally know what you mean.
Anyway, didn't you need to use the restroom?
Oh, right!
Excuse me for a bit.
So relaxing.
What-!?
You're so quiet around the others...
Why are you suddenly reacting to me?
Slowly...
Oh...
You're a good girl today, aren't you?
Okay, shake.
Not gonna do it, huh?
You're Minami-chan's dog, so I thought you would be a bit smarter...
Oh, I know!
Wait, wait!
Sit, girl!
Sit!!
What an honest dog...
Well, then...
Shake!
H-Hey!
Lay off!
Please stop...
Here.
I don't understand big dogs at all...
What the-!?
D-Don't spit it out!
Minami, dinner time!
Mom, Cherry's not eating her dinner.
Seems like it...
I even put in some of the canned food you got for her.
But she still won't eat it...
I thought she liked that stuff.
Cherry...
Cheer up.
We're all worried about you.
What happened to your face?
What were you digging up?
Oh, I get it...
You were eating the stuff you buried?
That's fine...
As long as you're happy, Cherry...
That's all I need.
Still, that was pretty sudden.
Why did you start playing online games, Hiiragi?
Eh?
Sensei, believe it or not...
Kagami is a big fan of the artist who worked on the anime adaptation for this game.
Seriously?
So you've finally given into the dark side, huh?
Konata!
Don't say unnecessary things!
Huh?
But if you want to copy the anime, then aren't the Hiiragi sisters a mis-casting?
It should be the reverse.
Ouch!
Konata!
Kagami, thx!
Nothing to it.
Sensei...
For the sake of our own survival...
...swapping them would be a fatal mistake.
I see what you mean...
I feel a lot safer this way.
Hey, Konata...
I have a feeling the jobs we have in the game...
...and the ones that are in the anime are different...
Oh, those are higher level jobs.
We have to transfer professions from our current jobs to get those done.
How do you switch jobs?
Coming soon.
Huh?
Well, it happens all the time.
They claim that the anime and game will progress concurrently...
...but once the anime finishes airing, it's all "coming soon."
But when you're in a game world like this, you start getting immersed.
And you really do get reminded of those game-based anime.
Oh yeah, like the one they set up to look like an online game but was actually offline.
I wonder why they didn't release that online.
I honestly believed that it was an online game, and I went looking for it all over the place.
That does seem to happen often.
Tsukasa, just hit ENTER.
Ah.
Aah, aah...
Yay, I can finally talk!
I was wondering why you weren't talking...
If you don't hit ENTER, you won't talk.
Man, it's so nice forming parties with people you know.
You're so right.
Pick-up groups are hit or miss, so it's a gamble every time.
What do you guys usually do, Kona-chan?
Just start spamming for groups or form one myself.
Then again, there are lots of times when no one picks me up.
If you miss the prime time for groups, then you end up playing solo the whole night.
'Cause no one ever wants to be the party leader.
And everyone just looks for groups.
Not to mention there are lots of times where you get too many of the same class.
And if you form a group in a rush, you could end up wasting even more time wiping.
I have absolutely no idea what you're talking about!
Tsukasa, your spells never do much damage, do they?
That's weird...
Mages are supposed to be strong enough to solo-farm.
Where are you putting your stats?
Stats?
Eh!?
B-But normally in games...
...when you level up, you just automatically learn spells.
So, I thought this was just like that...
Indeed...
Here it is!
Now that I'm level 10, I can attack twice!
If I keep leveling up, I wonder if I can pull off three attacks...
Hmm...
What is this feeling of déjà vu...?
It feels very much like I'm playing a Lodoss tabletalk RPG...
More nonsense...
This game's got a lot of emotes.
Sensei, we should make a victory pose for our party!
Was that really necessary?
Yes, yes it was, Kagami. Especially since we're online.
This floor has 3 enemies and a hidden treasure.
For this boss, I'll pull him away and kite him, so you guys DPS him from behind.
He's weak to fire, so make sure you take advantage of that.
If you talk to that guy over there, he'll give you a quest.
Next, you just talk to the old man by the exit and you'll get some cash.
Kona-chan, you know so much.
Lately, all that information is floating around the net.
There are some amazing sites that'll have a complete walkthrough uploaded the same day.
It's almost as though they're getting paid for it.
If only they could redirect all that energy into fueling society...
...and make themselves useful.
This is invincible Pizza-La Shield, there's nothing to fear!
P-Pizza-La?
It's an in-game promotional item.
If you order a pizza, you can get such special items.
Why do I feel like you're falling into their trap?
Man...
Even though I'm aware of it, I still do it for some reason.
You too!?
Eh?
A trip?
We're going to the hot springs as a family.
So I don't think we'll be on during Golden Week.
Oh, I'm going somewhere with Yu-chan, too.
I hope it won't be too crowded...
After Golden Week
Sensei...
Don't tell me...
And so, what did this kid do after that?
This is the right answer.
Eh?
Yes, Mayumi-chan.
Then we're off to go see the ball.
Watch over the house, okay?
Okay.
Kagami, you're really not going to go?
Yeah, it's too much trouble anyway.
Are you sure?
You're going to miss out on this chance.
I'm starting to get a bit nervous.
Tsukasa, why don't you try participating?
Eh?
T-That's impossible!
We're off.
Make sure to lock up, okay?
Okay, okay.
Take care.
Still, this wife is pretty scary.
Do you think so?
Something like this is normal, right?
She didn't think so at all!
I shall make that wish of yours come true!
Where did you come from?
And what's with that getup?
Now, now...
By the way, my current designation is a mage.
What do you mean, "designation?"
Oh, is that so...?
Your evil stepmother and sisters are picking on you, huh?
Huh?
What's this?
You want to go to the ball too?
No, I said nothing of the sort.
In other words...
You're the fairy godmother, and I'm Cinderella...
...and now I must get on a carriage and go attend the ball?
That's correct.
Which is why....
That's not even a carriage!
Don't worry about the details, Kagami.
Okay, let's head out!
Kagami, you get on as well.
No.
Geez...
Do you really want to have a carriage that much?
No!
I don't even know what the hell you're talking about!
And I never intended to go to the ball in the first place.
Now, now...
Don't talk like you know it all.
Anyway...
I'm not going, got it?
For sure?
For sure!
No matter what?
Enough!
Geez...
What was she thinking?
Ah!
I forgot to have her turn that back to normal.
Whoa!
A-An earthquake?
W-What the hell is this?!
Oh, Kagami...
I wouldn't go outside right now if I were you.
Is this your doing?
Yup.
Stop it already!
But you refused to leave the house...
I told you that I don't want to go, didn't I?
Then I'll just go to the dance hall like this.
Okay, fine!
I'll go, now stop all of this!
Aren't you looking forward to the ball, Kagami?
Not at all.
I bet the truth is that you're really happy.
You tsundere, you.
Stop calling me a tsundere!
Besides, why is a fairy godmother such as yourself coming along too?
Oh, yeah...
We should take this opportunity to get you all dressed up.
Hey, are you even listening to me?
Here.
I guess this is the default selection.
Hey, this isn't something you'd wear to a ball!
No, no...
I think you're more than qualified for that type of niche, Kagami.
What are you talking about?
Anyways, change my clothes back!
Huh, after I went through all that trouble?
I never asked you to!
Change it back right now!
Okay...
Hey, you didn't fix anything!
I guess you could call this another type of "default".
Besides, this is your usual cosplay.
Don't call it cosplay!
Somebody's gonna get hurt real soon...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
I'll do it right this time.
Ah.
It fell off...
Huh?
Sorry, but it looks like I can't change your clothes back to normal.
We're here!
Fighters' ball in Saitama: Love is touch and endless.
How 'bout this?
Winner, Kuroi Nanako!
All right!
Today, I will escape from my life as a bachelorette!
You just wait for me, Prince Misao!
Okay!
Win, win, and keep on winning!
Whoever wins this competition...
Will be my bride!
They're really getting into it...
Whatever, I don't care.
Oh, Hiiragi-chan!
I knew you would come after all!
Love.
Be quiet.
Don't touch me.
Did you dress up like this just for me?
No.
Hiiragi, you're participating too, right?
Not a chance.
C'mon, just participate.
I'll fix all your matches.
Then why even have a competition?
First of all, I don't want to participate...
...and second, I don't want to become your bride!
What is this, Hiiragi...?
You're being pretty cold...
Don't worry, prince, this is just her "tsun" side.
Oh, which means deep down...
No!!
Geez...
I know this was going to happen, which is why I didn't want to go!
Anyways, I'm going home now.
Eh?
You're leaving already?
When the clock strikes midnight, all the magic will be undone anyways, right?
If I don't leave now, the car will disappear.
How did she know?
Who cares, who cares?!
Let's play!
It's time for the fight predictions!
Are you a little kid?
Hey, Konata.
The house is still displaced!
Can't you move it back to its original location?
I fixed the Starring Inferno, so everything should be okay!
Why do I not feel reassured?
Is it really okay?
Eh?
I guess time's up.
No way!
It's already past midnight?
What about the house?
I guess it'll have to stay like this.
Stay like this?
Can't you do something with your magic?
Actually, I was also on the receiving side of a magic spell...
Which is why I can't do anything past 12AM.
What do you mean you can't...
Oh, right...
I just remembered a spell to reset everything.
Really!?
Then why didn't you say that earlier?
Well you  have to say this one, not me.
Then tell me already!
It's...
Do I really have to say that?
Yup.
Really loud, too.
Really loud!?
Yep.
Ugh...
Things won't return to normal if you don't.
Fine, then.
I want to ***** with Konata.
Don't worry, Sis.
I won't say a word.
No!
It's not what you think!
Oh yeah, I should go mail Kona-chan.
T-Tsukasa, listen!
You've got it totally wrong!
It was against my will...
What I meant is that she totally...
Here!
You did it!
That was amazing, Hiiragi-chan.
It was just luck, I swear.
There's no way I could hit that...
Hiiragi's little sis.
Don't give up.
Kusakabe-san.
Do you want to live in Hiiragi's shadow forever?
But...
No buts!
Today's your big chance to show your sister up!
Muster up some courage and prove to your sister that you can do it too!
O-Okay.
We'll show 'em the true power of a support character!
I-I'll do my best!
Oh, what a nostalgic scene...
There!
Alright!
Here!
And that's how it's done!
I was so close...
Not bad, Kusakabe!
Here it goes...
Super Ultra Miraculous Eccentric Special...
Serve!
An underhand serve?!
Leave it to me!
Nice receive!
Here!
Not bad...
Not bad at all...
Misakichi, Tsukasa.
We're gonna do a Jet Stream Attack on the attacker!
Roger!
Okay!
By the way, what's a Jet Stream Attack?
Ahh, you're not supposed to say that!
Now the plan won't work!
What are you guys doing?
Take this!
Take that!
Yes!
Eh?
Little Sis!
Tsukasa!
Something like that is impossible...
However...
Even when it's tough
The tears had fallen.
What's that?
Eh!?
You don't know it?
It's cutural literacy for the Japanese!
You're the only one that feels that way.
Little Sis...
There's no point in sulking there.
You're gonna beat down Hiiragi today, right?
I...
I've always been relying on Sis...
Yeah...
I'm sorry.
I'll do everything I can!
I got it!
Good job, Little Sis!
Guu~
One more point...
...and our team will...
...win!
Let's do this!
We won't lose, Hiiragi!
I won't let it...
...end like this!
Here!
Spin.
Stop.
Just call me the Witch of Kasukabe.
There!
Go for it, Little Sis!
Hit it with everything you got!
Alright!
Ow, it hurts as if I just smacked into something.
We did it!
You really shined today, Hiiragi-san.
Eh, really?
Nothing less from Hiiragi-san.
Thanks.
That was amazing!
It was.
Damn it...
I suppose the supporting characters...
...are never meant to win...
I guess I still can't match Sis.
But...
Someday, surely...
Heaven has forsaken us!
Hey, let's go.
Yeah...
I was just trying to get into the mood.
Stop messing around.
Come on.
This is a story that happened during a summer camping trip for our school.
We had decided to take a hike and were in the midst of our orienteering course.
That's when our group...
...somehow ended up lost.
How did this happen?
It's because you  forgot the map and compass on the bus!
Besides, why did we have to go this way?
Well, I suddenly had the urge to climb a mountain.
And why is that?
"Why?" you ask...
Because it's there.
Now now, Sis.
How about we start by checking our cell phones?
As expected, out of range.
Me too.
I got nothing.
Same.
I guess we're doomed.
Ah, geez...
We should've been at the camping grounds by now.
That's true.
According to the schedule, we were supposed to start making dinner at 5PM.
Reacted to the word "dinner", huh?
What about you, aren't you hungry?
Just a bit...
But I ate a ton of these on the bus.
Oh, again!
That one was me.
Anyways, how about we escape absolute starvation with these...
S-Starvation seems a bit exaggerated.
But these...
One, two, three...
We're one short!
Um, may I?
This way, there will be six total.
If we give everyone one piece...
..we can then break the last two into halves again.
How about that?
Yuki-chan, you're incredible!
Nothing less from our Miwiki-san!
Oh it's nothing, really...
Now we won't have to starve to death.
Like I said, you're exaggerating.
However...
Izumi-san's words began to seem like less and less of a joke...
...and more of a reality.
I have a feeling we're completely and utterly lost.
Yes.
We've been walking the same area over and over.
Ah, if only we had a magnet.
I guess I need to smack you across the face with this.
Or perhaps I should shove it down your throat?
How scary!
Kagami, you're serious!
Um...
That looks like the Summer Triangle.
Therefore, I'm pretty sure this direction is East.
Wow Tsukasa, that's pretty amazing.
Tsukasa, do you like stars that much?
Um, this is the only one I know.
One of the big stars of the Summer Triangle is called Vega...
...but it's also the Orihime Boshi.
Since we were born on Tanabata.
The Big Dipper also looks really beautiful.
Listen up, Kagami!
Until the day the Death Omen Star has fallen...
...you must live your life to the fullest!
Although, even if we do know the cardinal directions...
...we still don't know how to get to the camp.
And such is our problem.
Heaven has forsaken us!
Enough of that.
After screaming like that, I'm seriously starting to get hungry.
And whose fault is that?!
I never spoke of the idea openly...
...but I was seriously...
...starting to consider the possibility that we wouldn't make it back.
We're not descending...
Yes.
We've walked quite a bit, huh?
That's right.
I wonder if we lost our sense of direction inside the forest.
You may be right.
Story number ten.
In the silent forest...
...you could hear the *pant* *pant* of their breathing...
What are you doing?
The Gathering of One Hundred Supernatural Tales.
If you tell a hundred ghost stores in a single night...
...a real ghost will descend upon you!
Eh?!
When that happens...
...you can feel a cold sensation on your cheek...
Stop messing around.
But...
...a campout at night means ghost stories!
And after, love stories!
Huh?
D-Did I say something weird?
Story number eighteen.
I tried calling out, "Hey!"
But there was only silence...
...then all of a sudden-
Is that supposed to be the sound of you blowing out a candle?
Yeah.
In The Gathering of One Hundred Supernatural Tales...
...you're supposed to blow out a candle...
...each time you finish a story, right?
That's our Miwiki-san!
And then...
Huh?
What story was I on again?
Story number sixteen, probably.
You're going backwards!
Yes, this is Sazae-
Don't you mean Izumi!?
Where the hell are you guys right now?
Do you guys have any  idea how worried we all were?!
What awaited our return to the camping grounds...
...were Kuroi-sensei's harsh words.
Which is why...
...you must be extra  careful from now on!
We're sorry...
You're hungry, right?
It's delicious.
Yeah, it really is.
Yep, yep.
Indeed...
...the curry we had that day was truly delicious.
Perhaps, it was even the most delicious curry I had ever had.
And so something outrageous like that happened.
It was a really troublesome day.
Oh?
But you seemed to be enjoying yourself while you were telling the story.
Is that so?
Yes.
Very much so.
I suppose so.
Hey Kagami.
There's a place I want to stop by on the way back...
We're going straight  home with no detours.
Don't say that...
It won't take long at all.
No way!
But why?
You're getting annoying!
Don't say such harsh words...
Gah, get off of me!
Okay, fine!
But just for a little bit, okay?
Thank you, Kagami!
You're such a nice person, Kagami!
We're going straight home afterwards, okay?
Sure, sure.
By the way, Kona-chan...
Where are we stopping at?
Oh yeah, well...
Some pet show that just recently opened up.
Pet Shop
Oh, a pet shop?
How nostalgic!
Minoru~pa~
Are you going to buy a dog or something?
I want to look at the bunnies.
I want to see the cute puppies.
Not at all.
This  is what I wanted to look at.
Ah, this cat has really nice fur.
Konata, I'll remind you right now...
This cat isn't a witch
or anything, so don't
bother it, okay?
...this cat isn't a witch or anything.
I know that.
I know that. I won't go as far as collecting its soul.
I won't go as far as collecting its soul.
Everything you've said up until now...
I am Zero!
I have returned!
I will use you up like a ragged cloth!
Ah, this cat must have really nice lineage.
Yuki-chan, you come from a really nice lineage as well.
Hey, hey...
I don't think you're using that in the right context.
Well...
Right now, Miyuki-san is the Galactic Fairy.
The Galactic Fairy
Although her appearance is slightly different...
These are the most famous frogs in Pekopon.
Ge~ro Gero Gero
Ta~ma Tama Tama
Ge~ro Gero Gero!
Ta~ma Tama Tama!
Ge-ro Gero Gero
Ta-ma Tama Tama
Ge~ro Gero Gero!
Ta~ma Tama Tama!
Oh!
I'm a dark-spotted frog.
I look like a Japanese tree frog.
I seem to be a bullfrog.
I'm a common toad...
Hey, wait a second!
Hmm...
Now then...
What happened here?
Alrighty then!
For-For-For-Forgot my something...
Oh!
That's...
Legendary Girl A!
This means...
...I must have her buy something!
Behold! The best armament I have collected!
With these slick deals...
Not even Legendary Girl A can resist!
Dammit! She's AFK?!
Good lucky!
It's this era's super...
...super idol, Akira Kogami here!
Long time no see, everyone!
And...
And...!
Her assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
Moving on!
Wait!
Everyone, if he hears you call out for him, I think he'll show up.
But if you're really quiet, he might now hear you...
So please, say it as quietly as you can.
Hey!
Now then, one , two...
Minoru-senpai...
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa!
So, you've appeared after all...
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa...
Wa~
Wa-wa-wa-wa-waa...
You didn't have to show up...
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-waaaa...
Wa-waah...
Hello! I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
You're not gonna do a little skit for us?
A skit?
Usually...
...you would stop in front of the camera...
Yes.
And then you would say, "And now I'll put on a little performance..."
Right?
Now, let's try it!
Start!
How's that?
That's 10 years worth of experience for you.
Not bad at all.
Thank you very much.
And so, nice to meet you, everyone.
Speaking of...
Yes.
What's this?
Oh, this?
It's something that's pretty popular around these parts.
Nezumi-senpai.
Hmm...
Right now, it's totally in style.
I hear it's the best.
Okay, whatever.
What?
Anyways!
You don't even care?
Okay, what is it then?
What I'm referring to is this entire situation.
What's up with this?
Eh?
What's up with what?
Well, it's a live-action filming.
A live...
A live Lucky Channel.
Something like that...
It's so loud!!
Now, now, now, now...
Let's calm down, okay?
I mean, c'mon...
Isn't this lovely?
It's lovely.
What is this?
What's up with that teary-eyed face?
I'm telling you, this is an animation!
Oh, but there was an animation.
Just before this.
What about me?
W-Well...
What about Akira Kogami?
Yes.
Let me repeat myself...
Okay.
I'm this era's...
Right.
This era's...
Super idol!
Right, right.
That's correct.
Which is why...
...we had you do this live performance that one one else could pull off.
I mean...
...it's a visual animation.
So we need to have some animations...
...and also some visuals...
Which is why...
Ah.
By having both parts separate and then together...
...it'll be twice as good.
I just realized.
What?
It's a bit like...
And Original...
Yes.
...Visual...
...and Animation?
Animation?
Yes.
So, Minoru Shiraishi is an original...
...in the visual...
...as well as the animation?
That means the entire program is about you!
Wait...
That's not true!
Geez!!
You have it wrong!
Even though Akira is supposed to be the super idol!
You're absolutely correct.
Why are all the staff...
...on Minoru-kun's...
Geez!!
Okay, okay...
Please calm down.
There's not enough love!
Calm down.
I am shocked.
Shocked?
YOU are SHOCK!
The skies have fallen from love.
Um..
Yeah...
YOU are SHOCK!
Look...
My heart has fallen.
It's playing...
Look.
Um, the theme song...
See?
Even bound by chains, the heart burns.
What's this?
Oh this... this is nothing!
It's useless now.
It'll disappear over here, so don't worry about it!
The staff, everyone, loves you...
Those who interfere will be taken down by a single finger.
Don't worry, Akira-sama.
It's hot.
It's too hot?
Oh, excuse me?
Could we get some water or something?
Thank you very much.
YOU are SHOCK!
Staff, may I have some water?
The pulse quickens from love.
Yes, please.
Some water, please... ah.
Here, here it comes.
Thank you very much.
Now, please rest a little, okay?
YOU are SHOCK!
My pulse quickens.
Okay?
Yeah...
Anyways...
Searching for you,
This is fine too.
Yeah...
My wandering heart is now burning up.
Like I was saying...
Now that I think about it, I'm a little thirsty, too.
Everything must dissolve and scatter apart tragically.
Excuse me, um...
Um...
Staff!
Um, could I also...
To protect our love,
...get some water here?
Staff!
You departed on a journey.
Ah, yes.
I would like some water...
Had lost sight of tomorrow.
Wait...
Why are you taking the mic?
H-Huh, that's a bit strange...
Umm...
I don't want to see,
Hey, where's my water?
My water...
Staff~
Such a face that has forgotten how to smile.
Reclaim the love!
I see...
So that's how it is...
You are already dead!
Huh?
But...
You know...
This is all wrong.
While this certainly is water...
It's not quite what I was expecting...
Hey...
It's...
...wrong...
Oh.
Welcome back.
You know...
I mean... seriously.
Yes.
Something like that...
Yeah, yeah...
Well...
You know...
And so...
Yes.
I've been thinking...
They kept on telling me, "You'll be in the main series."
Yes.
But those were all empty promises.
So then I tried being a pop star...
...but that didn't last long, either.
Right.
And so...
...I even told them that I was willing to play some side parts and the like in the main series, you know?
Right.
But here I am...
It'll be fine, Akira-sama!
You'll see!
Good things will happen!
But they haven't...
Not matter what I do...
It's like there's just not enough love in here...
Akira...
Akira-sama, the ending...
Ehh?!
It's the end already?
Akira's so lonely!
That's it for today.
And then this!
Oh, this is new.
Certainly...
Right around here.
Around here.
Somewhere...
Please send all your love to Akira!
Yes.
Please!
And thus...
Yes.
I await the next time we can see each other again!
But for now, bye-bee!
Bye-bee!!
I'm seriously going to do my best.
I'm already at the top.
As high as the heavens.
Thank you very much.
What?
What is it?
You know...
Reproduction, modification, public
exhibition (broadcasting, streaming,
Internet downloading, etc.), screening,
enacting, distribution (retail or rental),
translation, or adaptation of this product
is illegal under law without permission
from the copyright holder.
Yes.
I've decided.
About what?
Well...
Yes.
I'm going to aim for the top.
Somewhere so high you can't touch me.
That's a good idea!
Something like that...
You're approaching it then.
Slowly but surely...
Like...
Inching your way to the top.
You know,
Right, it makes me think I should climb to the top.
Right, right.
Something like...
The both of us climbing to the top...
Zoom!
Let's do it. Just like that.
And we'll figure it out just like that.
Right?
And we'll be at the top just like that.
Seems unreliable, but I'll give it a shot.
Alright!