Damn it all...
Why?
This doesn't make sense!
It's over after one fight?
I won't let it end like this!
Why?
Why did this happen?
The old me wasn't like this...
Back in elementary school,
I was one of the popular kids in class.
We would bully any classmates who
were awkward and had no friends.
Now!
Sorry, Kiyoi-chan!
We didn't see you down there!
So when I ran into Kiyoi-chan
again in middle school,
I was so surprised.
Hello, Selector-san.
You've been chosen.
Kiyoi-chan didn't seem to realize it,
but she and I made a good team.
I did a great job of manipulating her,
and we won our battles.
It was so fun to watch the way she
believed me and did what I told her.
And when she became an Eternal Girl,
she and I switched places,
and I kept my promise with her.
When I was chosen again
for the Selector battles,
I was sick of Kiyoi-chan's body,
so my goal was to get my old body back.
And then I ran into her again.
That idiot Kiyoi-chan gave up
her chance to be human again.
I became an Eternal Girl and,
in the final step toward my goal,
I became the LRIG of the girl
who owned my original body.
Well?
If you do this, you'll be able to
get your old body back for sure!
This time, I'm the LRIG,
and you're the Selector.
It must be fate!
"If I just act polite and do
what the fortune-telling says,
a happy future will come." Was that it?
That's right! I'm so glad you remember!
Are you stupid?
I never liked that about you.
You know, I really like your body.
Hey, wait...
Wait... Stop! No! This is a joke, right?!
I'm taking your life all for myself.
But... You can't... No! No!
I was trapped for what felt like an eternity.
And then, that suddenly ended.
But something had gone wrong...
I'll get tired easily today,
and my lucky color is green, huh?
What's she doing?
You didn't know?
She uses fortune-telling to
decide everything in her life.
I heard the reason she skipped school the
other day was because of a bad fortune.
What? That's scary!
That's getting way too into it.
They say she's a little crazy.
You should stay away from her.
This isn't right... Why?
I wasn't like this.
I... I...
6/24
Cleaning today was so much fun!
Me, Mio-chan, Azusa-chan, and the others
all said that Kiyoi-chan was gross,
so we decided to clean her up by throwing
a bucket of water on her.
Her shocked face was just PERFECT.
6/24
Cleaning today was so much fun!
Me, Mio-chan, Azusa-chan, and the others
all said that Kiyoi-chan was gross,
so we decided to clean her up by throwing
a bucket of water on her.
Her shocked face was just PERFECT.
That's it.
It's because I don't have Kiyoi-chan!
When she was around,
everything went perfectly.
So that's it.
I need Kiyoi-chan in my life.
I want to see Kiyoi-chan again...
I want to see her!
I want to see her! I want to see her!
Do you want to see her?
Is this... the room of white windows?
Why?
Do you want to play?
With her.
Again.
Do you want to be friends?
To see her suffer?
To be with her?
To fight her?
To see her?
I guess I shouldn't have come here on a whim.
I didn't expect to be ambushed.
Book me a battle with Mizushima Kiyoi.
Sorry.
I'm not Satomi Kou or
the bookmaker anymore.
What do you mean?
You should be able to guess.
I'm Carnival, his LRIG.
And anyway, Mizushima Kiyoi beat you,
so you don't have any LRIGs anymore, right?
You're out of the battle.
All you can do now is wait
for your coins to disappear.
I want to beat the shit out of her.
I want to warp that stupid
smirk of hers with despair.
Well, I can't help.
Wait!
Give me an LRIG, then!
I'll give it back when I crush Kiyoi!
I don't care if I lose
my memories after that.
I don't care if I lose all my
memories of this stupid life!
I'm impressed by your obsession with her,
but you can't just lend someone a LRIG.
I've never heard of that...
An LRIG?
I'm Remember.
I'm dying to see Mizushima Kiyoi-chan again!
You know her?
I sure do!
And I'm absolutely dying to see her!
I can make that happen.
Let's play with Kiyoi-chan together!
A new pawn that I don't know...
Interesting.
Naturally, we're not here to do karaoke.
I know that!
Main topic.
Let us begin.
I invited Morikawa-san, too, I thought.
I guess Chi-chan had other plans...
She said she'd give it a pass.
I see.
Putting together the information
we've all gathered,
it feels like someone is controlling
this round of Selector battles
for their own purposes.
Controlling?
Doubt.
I think it could be said that Satomi
was controlling the previous battles.
Satomi simply prepared the stage
and watched Selectors suffer on it.
But this time, it feels like
they're trying to interfere
with the flow of the
Selector battles themselves.
Confirmation.
Is Carnival behind it, then?
At first, I thought so.
But after talking to Donor,
I changed my mind.
I just suddenly found myself there.
"There"?
You've been there, too.
The place where you first met your LRIGs.
It's the room of white windows.
The room where Mayu, the girl who
created the first Selector battles, was.
Surprise...
I see.
I heard a voice there,
and when I answered it,
I was right next to Kiyoi.
In other words, the "someone"
who's controlling this is Mayu?
But Mayu was released in the previous
Selector battles, and she disappeared.
Confusion.
Whose voice was it, then?
I just heard a voice.
I didn't see anyone.
Hanna-chan?
Acquaintance.
I'm going to talk to someone.
I'll tell you what I learn later.
I'm not going to sing.
Hey, Chi-chan.
How'd the discussion go?
Good! We made some progress.
Sorry...
You kept me away because I don't have
my memories of the Selector battles.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
It really is frustrating.
Do you really want your memories back?
Huh?
Uh, I mean...
The memories you want back
might not be all good ones.
Do you still want them back?
Of course.
I see.
Question.
Is Kurebayashi-san coming today?
Sorry.
She's taking some time off work.
Doubt.
Did something happen?
Her family called and said
it was for personal reasons.
That's all I know.
Imagination.
If Nanashi-chan were here, she'd say,
"Something happened, huh?"
This park...
This is where Yuzuki fought
a girl named Layla
and was taken away, right?
Yeah.
Thanks, Ruuko.
With Yuzuki, Hanayo-san, and Midoriko...
I couldn't handle it all myself.
Don't get down, Hitoe!
That's right.
Let's get all of them back.
Wow... You're pretty bold.
Give back Yuzuki!
Yuzuki? Oh, you mean this?
Hitoe... Ruuko...
I'm sorry.
This happened because I was careless.
Don't worry.
I'll get back you back.
Battle me.
So you beat Uemura Hitoe,
and then Kurebayashi Yuzuki?
I didn't do it for you.
I know that.
But now Kominato Ruuko will be forced to act.
Who's that?
Is she strong?
She's strong.
How strong?
Well...
Depending on how things went,
even I might have trouble with her.
I heard you're strong.
She is!
Ruu and I are super strong!
I see...
Then let's do it.
Use Yuzuki as your LRIG.
Huh?
I won't fight under any other conditions.
I'm here to save my friend.
You're strange.
Oh, well.
I guess that could be fun every now and then.
I'll play your little game.
Open!
I'm sorry, Yuzuki.
Just hang in there for a bit!
I'm paying for my own mistake.
But, Tama, I'm sorry.
An LRIG can't hold back even if they want to.
Don't worry!
I'm strong!
Stop talking and let's just do this!
Ruuko, Yuzuki...
Tama, grow!
Summon Playground Equipment: Snow Sled.
Control top and turn end!
Grow.
It's no fun at all if I can't fight.
Summon Dinos.
Show hand and banish Snow Sled.
Tama, I'm sorry!
Tama!
I'm fine!
Turn end.
That's right...
This is a Selector battle.
Grow!
Summon SIGNI Sanpoku,
attack phase effect,
activate combo,
put snow tracks into play!
She guarded?
When she fought me and Yuzuki,
she was ultra-aggressive
and didn't even use a Servant.
What's wrong? An attack
like that won't hurt me.
Attack me harder!
Grow!
Play Double Crush on Yuzuki and attack!
Tama!
I'm fine!
She's calmly testing Ruuko and Tama-chan.
This isn't like Hitoe said.
She doesn't just want to fight!
Now, show me
the power that he said even
he might have trouble with...
I need to end this battle fast!
Tama, please!
ARTS: Queen Boundary!
That's it!
That's the power I wanted to see!
But this is only the beginning, right?
Grow!
Coin bet.
Tama, hang in there!
Burning!
Tama!
I'm just... fine!
You have more power than that, don't you?
You'll never get to them that way!
ARTS: Overheat.
She enhanced her defenses?
Is she going to drag this out longer?
I can't break that with a direct attack.
But I will end this.
Yuzuki, this is the end!
Yeah...
That's right! Come on! Bring it!
Coin bet!
Innocence!
Tama!
Ark Gain!
That's incredible power!
This is what I wanted!
It's incredible!
Yuzuki!
Welcome back, Yuzuki!
I'm sorry I caused trouble for you.
Thanks.
Don't be.
Yuzuki, did it hurt?
Yeah, it really hurt.
I'm sorry!
Just kidding.
Thanks, Tama.
Not bad.
Now use Midoriko-san and Hanayo-san.
No.
Battling this way is boring.
I'm done with that!
Next time, your LRIG and I
are going to fight a battle
that makes blood and flesh
and bones all scream!
Wow, really?
Where do we go next?
Hey, isn't that Aoi Akira?
Who's that?
The amateur model!
I don't know her.
Akira-chan, are you an amateur model?
Please don't ignore me!
If I know more about you,
I can give you more accurate fortunes.
My fortune-telling is really good.
Shut up.
I just wanted an LRIG.
I don't want to be your friend.
When's your birthday?
What's your blood type?
Your favorite color?
Dog person or cat person?
Give it a rest!
If you don't shut up, I'll rip you in half!
Your fortune says you'll
have trouble with water.
See?
Let's be friends, Akira-chan.
Hell no.
Once I'm done with Kiyoi,
I'm throwing you in the trash.
You're stopping after one fight?
Let's keep playing with Kiyoi-chan forever!
Then I can be happy!
You're screwed up.
So are you, aren't you, Akira-chan?
I happen to know her weakness.
Yeah? What weakness is that?
Kiyoi,
which do you like?
I don't know about that stuff.
Just tell me which you prefer.
This one, I guess.
Okay, here.
I'll get this one.
We can be twins!
No.
Let's do it!
This stuff's on sale, and it's cheap.
No way.
You're no fun.
Eat up. We've got three more places to go.
You wanted me to come here
just to go shopping with you?
That's right.
You're always so busy with
your Selector battles
that you never hang out with me.
This is so good!
That was fun.
Well, I'll invite you again sometime.
Amika...
Thanks for always worrying about me.
Of course I do.
We're friends!
Bye!
Where am I going to wear something like this?
Amika
What? Did you forget something?
Yeah, I did!
I forgot to kick your ass.
Akira!
That's right!
That's my little Piruluk-tan!
If you want to see her, come to the
address I'm about to give you.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Don't do it, Kiyoi!
Amika!
Shut up, you stupid bitch!
Attachment / Trick and Trap
For your friend.
I'll take some embarrassing photos and stuff.
Do what I tell you.
I'll make her pay!
My wish came true!
I can finally beat the shit out of you!
Bond / Crime and Punishment
Bond / Crime and Punishment.