Rabou.
Reiki.
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
What's going on?!
Sounds like Yato-chan
and the others are back.
When exactly did they become
part of this household?
What the heck is happening?!
You should just calm down, Yato.
But what happened to Hiyori?!
Hey Yukine-kun,
if you don't mind me asking...
Who's this guy?
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh, man, Hiyori! Kicking off
the new year with a joke, huh?
It's me, duh!
Itsumida-san?
That's right! Itsumida!
Man, what nationality
was that supposed to be?
Is he a friend of yours, Yukine-kun?
Is he a comedian or something?
Huh?
It must be amnesia.
You think so?!
For some reason, she's forgotten about you and only you.
What are we gonna do?!
Oh, relax, will you?
I'm sure it's a temporary thing.
She'll remember you soon enough.
No.
Yato?
I will turn Hiyori back to normal.
Abandoned God
Chapter
That's it! Right this way!
I actually only came to give you some more of my old books.
Just play along for a bit.
If you look to your left,
you'll see the legendary street
where the famous god named Yato
and a girl rescued Milord!
Huh?!
A lord used to pass through here?!
I had no idea this was
such a historical location!
I don't think she remembers.
Which lord was it, Yato-san?
"-san"?!
It's "Yato"! You used to call me
just "Yato," without any honorific!
But it would be rude to
call you that since we just met.
Look, Hiyori!
Wha... Not my notebook again!
MILORD
This is Milord! This!
Oh!
You're really good at drawing, Yato-san!
That isn't what I'm trying
to show you, Hiyori-san!
Oh, that's right!
Milord was the cat's name!
It's coming back to you?
Do you remember who I am, too?!
Let me see...
A manga artist?
I need to get going now.
Could we have your lesson
another time, Yukine-kun?
All your homework
until then is in here.
Yeah, sure.
See you later!
Hiyori!
Hiyori...
Have you really forgotten me?
You really can't remember me?
In that case...
Get in bed with me.
It might remind you of when
we met at the hospital—
Pervert!
Pi
ping
Hot
Oden
Soba-Dango
Shiruko
Sweet Sake
Yato-chan and Yukki said
they'd have dinner later.
So they're still gonna eat here, huh?
A memory picture show?
Will that really bring back her memory?
It will! You saw how she
reacted to my drawing!
It definitely sparked something
inside Hiyori's mind!
Now quit slacking off and help me!
No way. This is so childish.
I wonder...
I wonder why that guy
seemed so desperate.
All right!
Now I can make the
perfect picture show!
It won't be long now!
I can't believe you spent all your 5-yen coins to buy art supplies.
Just you wait, Hiyori!
Still, why can't Hiyori remember?
Yato?
What's wrong?
I should've known you
were behind this, Nora.
I stole her memories of you.
It was very easy, actually.
She has no need for memories of Far Shore denizens like us.
People are quick to forget you, anyway.
Wouldn't you agree?
In spite of how much
you grant humans' wishes,
their feelings will always
be fickle and erratic.
Poor Yato. You've been hurt so many times.
Remember your true self.
Yato!
Don't listen to her!
Yukine...
Nora, what are you plotting this time?!
I was just hoping that you might visit us.
Reiki.
Y-You...
Rabou!
You're alive?
It's been a while, Yato.
Wh-Who is he?
What's with that sun visor you're wearing?
Have at you.
Come, Sekki!
Whoa! Are you trying to kill him, Yato?!
If I hold back at all against this guy...
he'll kill me!
He's as fast as ever!
Yato...
What has happened to you?
This is not the extent of your power.
Remember...
Remember.
Remember. Remember.
Remember. Remember. Remember.
Remember. Remember!
Yato!
You okay, Yato? Yato?!
As for the next report...
What is this?
What's happening?!
Y-Yato!
Yukine!
You were right.
This isn't the Yato I knew, Furuhime.
So now you understand?
Listen, Yato.
If you can beat Rabou,
I'll give Iki Hiyori her memory back.
I promise.
NORAGAMI
Then, concerning this unusual storm...
Nope.
My lady has nothing to do with it.
I came to ask if a Vent
had opened unexpectedly.
I never would have thought
it had to do with Yato.
We were no match for
that Rabou guy at all.
Rabou?
Never heard of him.
Rabou is a god of calamity.
No one really talks about him these days,
but he used to be really
well known a long time ago.
You know him?
Rabou was originally human, you see.
As I recall, in life he served as a Herald.
Herald?
A spy who sneaks into enemy territory to conduct dirty work.
Once a Herald finishes their job,
their master kills them to ensure silence.
That's awful!
They say that after his death,
people who feared being cursed
deified him and made him
a god of calamity.
A god of calamity?
People don't always wish for good things.
There are evil wishes, too.
Evil wishes?
Wanting to eliminate someone
you hate, for example.
A god of calamity is one that
answers such wicked wishes.
In particular, Rabou granted
people's wishes through killing.
They say he has killed people, Phantoms...
and even other gods, if requested.
Wh-What does someone
like that want with Hiyori?
Is he an old pal of Yato's?
I have heard rumors...
that a god of calamity
once fought alongside Yato.
Rabou hasn't changed at all.
He's still powerful.
If I'm not careful,
he could end up killing Yukine.
But shouldn't it be difficult for a god of calamity like him to continue existing?
H-Hold on a minute!
Yato and Rabou were partners?
Does that mean Yato's
a god of calamity, too?!
I-I never knew—
Hiyorin knows.
I was the one who told her.
It didn't seem to bother her one bit, though.
Hiyori-chan's one tough girl, all right.
Yato-chan's different now.
That's why she stuck with him.
Hiyorin must really
love you and Yato-chan!
I...
want to bring Hiyori's memory back!
At this rate, Hiyori will
never remember me.
Perhaps it's for the best.
As I said before,
you should cut your ties with her.
Your connection gets her
too involved in our world.
Maintaining that connection would keep her from living on her own.
If she forgets about you, she'll likely stop changing into a half-Phantom.
That will give her happiness.
It appears he's made up his mind.
Yato-san...
Yato!
Where have you been?
I've been thinking
about Hiyori's memory—
Forget it.
Just forget about Hiyori.
Huh?!
Hey, Yato! Yato!
There is no time to waste.
Even now while I wait,
time endlessly slips through my fingers.
Don't worry.
Yato will return.
I'm sure of it.
And then...
Yukki! Did you see Yato-chan?
Man...
What's Yato's deal?!
He's not making any sense!
Why is he suddenly...
The Tale of Hiyori
and the Yato God
Looks like I really did know him.
If only I could remember...
Yukine-kun?
Hiyori!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, don't worry.
So, what's up?
Here.
Wow! A picture play!
Did you make it?
Yeah.
Will you watch it?
Okay.
This is the story of Yato—
the sweats-wearing god—and Hiyori.
Let the story begin!
Yukine is with Hiyori again?
And so the gifted Regalia drew
a Borderline on his very first try!
Yes, yes! You're amazing, Yukine-kun!
Even Yato was surprised when I did it!
Oh... He was?
Um, and then...
Yato.
Know what this is?
The ablution was a success,
and thanks to Yato and Hiyori...
Thanks to Yato and Hiyori
being there for me,
I managed to become normal again.
And that's how...
Yato
Me
Hiyori
A-And that's how Hiyori, Yato, and I...
all became good friends.
I'm sorry. I still can't
remember Yato-san.
But it sounds like
we're good friends.
Hiyori
Me
Yato
Yeah... Yeah!
Say, Yukine-kun.
Could I have that notebook?
Huh?! Oh, but...
I feel like it might somehow help me remember what I've forgotten.
In that case...
It's really waning now.
Tell me, Yato.
Where do you suppose the
waning part of the moon falls?
Falls?
Hiyori?
Hiyo—
Is this yours?
Yukine...
What have you done, Nora?!
Iki Hiyori's memory is
waning bit by bit, falling away.
If you don't pay us a visit soon...
there'll be nothing left.
Hiyori's forgotten about me too.
She's forgotten!
Yukine...
We're going to go
bring her memory back.
But a fight against them
could end up destroying you.
Yato...
And I might just be giving them exactly what they want.
"Believe in yourself!"
Those were your own words.
This... is me?
A tail?
Hiyori! It's time!
Hiyori!
Um...
I'm sorry for losing my cool back there.
You're probably the one most
troubled by forgetting all this.
We've dragged you
into something terrible.
Although, technically,
his twisted past is entirely to blame.
But he is my master,
and what's my master's is also mine, so...
Say something too, Yato!
We will bring your memory back.
So just rest easy and wait, Hiyori.
Hiyori? What's wrong?!
I'm not sure.
I'm not really sure.
Stop crying.
Let's go.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
Ding-ding! It's time for
a Regalia midterm test!
List ten good things about your master!
Ten?!
What's the matter, Yukine?
Five would be okay, I suppose.
Five...
On the next Noragami:
"A Scrap of a Memory."
Fine! Just three, then!
Sorry, can't think of any.
Next Episode
A Scrap of a Memory
Whoa, whoa! Does nothing come to mind?!