Everything okay?
I heard you moaning.
Yeah, I had another nightmare.
What manner of monster is this Saitama?
You kept repeating "Saitama, Saitama" in your sleep.
The Overly-Complicated Ninja
This is the first time I've experienced this.
Losing a fight is one thing,
but for some reason, I no longer "feel the wind".
This is unprecedented.
It was just one fight.
And it was just bad luck that caused me to lose.
There should be no difference in ability between us.
So... Why?
No matter what strategy I use...
I can't picture myself winning!
Why—
Well, that's how it is.
That's how psychological trauma works.
You've been so good to me, Hunter.
Don't mention it.
We're birds of a feather.
My work puts my life at risk, too.
Up in the mountains,
I occasionally come across
horrible monsters on my hunts.
Just like you...
I've got my own enemy to defeat.
Is he tough?
Yeah, he's the master of this mountain.
He's the one who gave me these scars.
A bear?
Fortunately my life was spared
when I ran straight towards a cliff,
but only because I fell off.
It really hurt like hell.
Ever since,
the hand I hold my gun with trembles...
...from fear.
What if my gun fails me again like last time?
The thought makes my hand shake
and I can't make a good shot.
But if I can defeat him,
I'm sure my hand will tremble no more.
If you want to overcome your own fear,
the only way to do it is to defeat your enemy.
Eh? He's gone...
Who says I'm afraid of him?
Ridiculous! There's no way...
Sure, why not?
It'll be good training.
Damn it!
Wind Blade Kick!
I see. So that's how it is.
I'll admit it, Saitama...
You make me feel afraid!
I owe you one, little boar.
Thanks to you, I might get my strength back.
What a treat tonight!
Snake meat isn't all that bad, you know.
Looks like this uribo
has taken a liking to you.
Uribo?
Yeah, boars found in the wild
rarely take to humans—
Why'd you call him "uribo"?
Huh?
No reason.
That's the word for wild boar piglets.
Isn't that normal?
He'll have a name, and I'll decide it.
O-Okay.
"Ino".
From Inoshishi, or wild boar.
How's that?
"How's that?" Well...
Sounds pretty normal,
but then again...
From then on, I devoted my days
to training for Saitama's defeat.
And, by the time I finished,
I'd come to a conclusion.
I decided I would not run away from fear,
but would face my fears head-on.
By doing so, it becomes possible to
prevail over and control fear.
And if I can do that...
Wind Blade Kick!
Moving on?
Yeah, thanks for everything, Hunter.
Call me Frank.
Frank Hunter, huh?
Good name.
Huh?
It's a fine name for a man who hunts.
I won't forget it.
No, I'm no hunter...
You're not a hunter?
Well yeah, I am a hunter,
but that's not my name...
It's, you know, my job. Let's see...
maybe you'd understand it better
if I say it's more like "Hunter Frank".
Ah, I get it.
So "Hunter" is the same as
"Speed-o'-Sound" in my name.
Anyway,
you plan to stay here?
Yeah.
I see.
Listen, Hunter.
Yeah?
If you're defeated even before you fight,
the results will be the same
no matter how often you try.
Any idea what he meant, Ino?
Ino? What's wrong? You miss him?
I'm sure he'll be back when he loses... again.
Just as I thought...
It is you.
Allow me to repay you for my scars.
Listen, Hunter.
If you're defeated even before you fight,
the results will be the same
no matter how often you try.
I get it. That's what he meant.
Sonic, what you were saying is...
I win!
Run, Ino...
Oh. A bear.
Well, bear's not bad but...
I could go for wild boar too...
Oh—
Whatever. Bear will do.
So this is a bear hot pot, Sensei?
Yeah.
You heard those rumors about
the giant bear causing all that damage, right?
You can eat bear?
Yeah, you can eat most animals.
I see!
Oh, and I hear wild boar's pretty good, too.
I have so much to learn from you, Sensei!
Just you wait, Saitama.
Next time we meet will be your demise.
Oh...
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ore wa ansatsu kara yojinbo made
No matter if it's assassination or bodyguard
Nani demo ukeou saikyo no ninja,
I accept any commission for I'm the strongest Ninja
Onsoku no sonikku
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic
Ninja no sato ni nama o ukete
I was born in a Ninja village
Osanai koro kara mi ni tsuketa
I trained myself from when I was little
Supido ninjutsu tekunikku
Speed, skills, techniques
Mukau toko teki nashi
I know not defeat
Zenaku nanka do demo ii
I care not about good or evil
Onore o tameshitai
All that matters is my potential
A motto motto motto
Ah more more more
Kansetsu panikku shite nai zo
My joints won't fail
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
Saitama! tsugini atta toki ga omae no saigo da!
Saitama! Our next encounter will be your demise!
kyukyoku no ninjutsu de kakujitsu ni shitomeru!
I shall kill you with ultimate Ninja technique!
kono onsoku no sonikku ga na!
For I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
Wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch ah March