The Overly-Complicated Ninja
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ore wa ansatsu kara yojinbo made
No matter if it's assassination or bodyguard
Nani demo ukeou saikyo no ninja,
I accept any commission for I'm the strongest Ninja
Onsoku no sonikku
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic
Ninja no sato ni nama o ukete
I was born in a Ninja village
Osanai koro kara mi ni tsuketa
I trained myself from when I was little
Supido ninjutsu tekunikku
Speed, skills, techniques
Mukau toko teki nashi
I know not defeat
Zenaku nanka do demo ii
I care not about good or evil
Onore o tameshitai
All that matters is my potential
A motto motto motto
Ah more more more
Kansetsu panikku shite nai zo
My joints won't fail
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
Saitama! tsugini atta toki ga omae no saigo da!
Saitama! Our next encounter will be your demise!
kyukyoku no ninjutsu de kakujitsu ni shitomeru!
I shall kill you with ultimate Ninja technique!
kono onsoku no sonikku ga na!
For I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
Wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch ah March