Oh, my!
I'm terribly sorry, but my master is out at the moment.
Well, since you're here...
Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I've always wanted to say that.
Now then, I see you've helped your new bonds blossom.
The Moon and Strength...
I wonder how these two Arcana will influence your future.
Please come back again when my master has returned.
Or do you prefer it when he's away?
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
Hey, did you hear about the new first-year student?
I sure did! But is it for real?
Like how he beat up an entire biker gang?
Supposedly, it's true.
It was 1 versus 100, and he just about beat 'em to death!
Bastard!
He took over the biker gang and became their boss.
Some TV station is even sending someone to interview him.
Take that!
What's a degenerate like him doing in our school?
I wish he'd just get out of here.
Here.
Next, we'll cover the case on everyone's mind, Ms. Yamano's murder.
Isn't this fried chicken good?
Although singer Hiiragi Misuzu is a suspect,
It might be Dad!
her alibi has been confirmed. She was on tour abroad on the day of the murder.
Hello. Yep, we're okay.
The man she had the affair with, Namatame Taro, also has a solid alibi.
Okay.
Huh?
I understand.
Ms. Yamano had only recently returned to her hometown of Inaba.
Dad wants to talk to you.
And Namatame had witnesses confirm that he was doing office work all day.
Hello?
Hey.
Sorry, but I have to work late.
Feel free to lock the door and hit the hay.
Okay.
Also...
About me taking off the 4th and the 5th...
One of the younger guys got sick.
His case doesn't look like it can be put on hold,
so I'm stuck filling in.
I'll get to take a hard-earned break during Golden Week.
Really?!
Sorry for the sudden change in plans.
I'd appreciate it if you could look after Nanako.
The police are currently investigating the connection between the high school student and Ms. Yamano.
Sure thing.
Later.
Hiya!
Satonaka?
Are you free today?
Huh?
If you're free today, wanna go somewhere?
Yukiko's coming too, and we can invite Hanamura if we really have to.
Sorry, but not today.
Are you Nanako?
Yeah.
Nanako, wanna come too?
U-Um...
Let's go together.
I-Is it okay?
You bet! Of course it is!
Should we get going?
Okay!
Ta-da! Here's one steak!
Wow!
It looks yummy.
Here.
Geez, you're slow!
Here, Nanako. Eat up and enjoy yourself!
Okay, thanks!
Prepare to chew a lot. This isn't quality steak or anything.
Seriously?! How could you say that right in front of me?!
Are you done now?
I'm just on break.
But geez, what are you doing wasting Golden Week here?
There's nowhere else to go!
Still, don't you feel sorry for Nanako, since you brought her here?
At Junes, every day is Customer Appreciation Day!
Yes, I feel sorry for her.
Come see for yourself, and get in touch with our products!
You didn't have to rub it in.
Every day's great at your Junes!
I love Junes!
Oh, Nanako!
But we were supposed to bring our own lunches.
Really? You know how to cook?
Nuh-uh.
Huh?
So what, are you a great cook?
I just do it for fun.
Oh, so you're the family cook? Pretty impressive, "Big Bro"!
Big Bro?
But really, that's pretty cool.
You've got Satonaka beat hands down.
Hold it!
What makes you think I can't cook?!
Huh? You can?
Seriously?
Then I challenge you to a cook-off!
Okay, you're on.
Here, Nanako can be our judge.
Huh?
Am I competing too?
I bet we'll make something that ranks up there with your mom's cooking!
I don't have a mom.
She died in an accident.
R-Really? I'm so sorry.
It's okay!
Even if I don't have a mom, I have Dad with me.
And now a big brother too.
And I'm having a lot of fun today! I love Junes!
Nanako, we'll play with you anytime you want!
Yeah, let's hang out!
Oh, thank you.
Thanks for tuning in, all you curious kiddies!
I'm back.
Dad!
Hey, Nanako.
I'm sorry I broke my promise again.
It's okay. My big bro played with me!
He did?
Thanks.
Nah, it was fun.
Hey, what's that?
Well, today's Children's Day, so I bought you a present.
Oh, yay!
It's a shirt!
There's a weird thing on the front!
That's so funny!
And this is for you.
Not that you're still a child or anything, but fair's fair.
This swimsuit is...
very fashionable.
Really? So you like it?
Dad, Big Bro, let's eat together.
Yeah, let's eat.
It's been a while since we last ate together.
Yep! It sure has.
We need to eat before the steak gets cold.
Okay, okay.
Hanamura insisted on forming a study group,
and now he's sleeping!
Come to think of it, there weren't any incidents during Golden Week.
What now? You wanna talk about that?
Yikes, he came back from the dead.
He looks fine.
Don't I?
I've actually put some thought into this.
The first victim was Ms. Yamano, followed by Konishi.
And Amagi was the third.
They weren't picked out at random.
I'm sure there's some sort of motive.
A motive? But there's no connection between them.
That's not true. All three victims were connected in some way.
First, Konishi was the one who found Ms. Yamano's body.
And didn't Ms. Yamano stay at the Amagi Inn?
Yes, that's right.
So wouldn't this be a fair assumption?
Women associated with Ms. Yamano are being targeted one after another.
You're right!
But why?
I haven't figured that out yet,
but we'll never get anywhere if we don't piece together the few clues we do have.
I recall the doorbell ringing and someone calling for me, but not who.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Don't apologize.
Not to mention, there's the Midnight Channel.
Yep.
If you think about it, it might be warning us who's next.
Warning us?
In that case, we have to check the Midnight Channel every night it rains.
Right. Then we can prevent anything from happening.
Okay, now that we're all on the same page, let's call it a day!
I didn't get even a minute of studying done.
Yosuke's seat
Man, free at last!
Yeah, it's all over.
Where have you been?
I figured I'd get the same grade whether or not I came.
I wish I could be that carefree.
So, how'd you do?
Not bad.
A biker gang composed of young men terrorize this quiet town.
That's ambitious enough.
Whadduya want?
Their alleged boss suddenly attacked the cameraman!
That voice...
This ain't a freak show, dammit!
He's still pulling this crap?
Do you know him, Dad?
Yeah, through work.
He's Tatsumi Kanji, a troubled teen who loves getting into fights.
Courage
Reliable
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Kindly
Expression
Decent
Knowledge
Average
A
Courage
Reliable
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Kindly
Expression
Decent
Knowledge
Average
A
We hereby commence the Special Investigation Team meeting
for the Inaba serial murders and kidnappings.
Too long.
So this is our secret headquarters?
You got it! Amagi, you're on the ball.
Anyway, about the guy on the Midnight Channel...
You mean Tatsumi Kanji?
We just saw him on the news!
Man, we missed the mark.
So much for the victims only being women.
I doubt there's any connection between Ms. Yamano and him.
Kanji, huh? He wasn't like this when he was little.
Yukiko, you actually know that creep?
Yes. His family runs a textile shop.
The inn has sold their wares for ages,
but I haven't spoken with Kanji for a long time now.
That simplifies things!
Let's go check out that textile shop.
Good idea. If the people on the Midnight Channel are being thrown into the TV...
Yeah.
Tatsumi Kanji will be next.
Excuse me!
Oh! Come on in, Yuki.
I'll be taking my leave.
Oh, I'm sorry I wasn't much help.
Not at all. You gave me something to think about.
I'll see you later.
Goodbye.
What gives?
Yuki, you're as beautiful as ever.
You're too kind.
Um, where's Kanji?
He's still not back yet.
Is that so?
I've seen this scarf somewhere before.
Which one?
Oh, I know!
It was there, in the TV.
It was in the room with the faceless posters.
So it was Ms. Yamano's?
Were you friends with Ms. Yamano?
I wouldn't say friends.
It was a special order she placed.
Excuse me! Package delivery.
Coming!
I'm sorry, but I have to step out for a moment.
It's okay. We were just leaving, anyway.
Huh?
It's Tatsumi Kanji.
Oh, shit! Hide!
Y-You want to talk?
Yes, I'm quite interested in you.
I guess that's cool.
I'll be waiting for you after school tomorrow.
H-He's "interested"?
He's a guy, and I'm a guy, but he's interested in me?
What the hell are you pricks looking at?!
Split!
What's their problem?
That was scary.
I couldn't hear a word they said.
I know! Let's keep watch over Tatsumi Kanji and the textile shop.
Good idea. If the killer really is after Tatsumi Kanji,
he'll either approach him directly or drop by his house.
So it's settled!
That said, Amagi, can I have your number?
So that's what you were after!
Of course not! But I'll be needing it for stuff.
Speaking of which, could you stop calling me at night to tell me dirty jokes?
You're such a perv.
Don't interrupt!
C'mon, Amagi. You don't mind, right?
I just remembered that I have to get some tofu.
That's it?
What's gotten into me?
He's here!
Sorry. Did I make you wait?
No, I just got here too.
Something about them seems weird.
Weird? How so?
Dunno. Maybe it's just my imagination.
Whatever. Satonaka and I will trail Tatsumi.
What?!
Narukami and Amagi, keep an eye on Tatsumi Textiles.
You got it.
Let's go!
Y-Yeah!
Tatsumi Textiles
Do you think the killer will come?
Are you scared?
A little, but my desire to see this through outweighs it.
I'm sure there's something I can do to help.
Don't stress about it.
I-Isn't that obvious?
I guess I'm a little nervous.
You should ease up.
There's still a chance the killer won't show up.
That's not it. I'm nervous about something else.
I've never been alone with a boy my age before or anything.
Chie, of course, has no problem with guys because of her personality.
But I think she's had more fun hanging out with you and Hanamura lately.
Is that right?
The same is true for me.
I'm sorry. I made things even more awkward.
Nah.
I wonder how Chie's doing.
I'll give her a call.
Oh, the line's busy.
And I don't know Hanamura's number.
I need it too.
Hanamura's number?
Yours.
Huh?
Well, I might need it for the investigation.
Yeah, you're right. We need to keep in contact with each other.
Hey...
May I cut to the chase and ask you a few questions?
Satonaka, Satonaka, do you copy? Over.
I hear ya.
The target is conversing 200 meters in front of me. Over.
Say...
Why are we positioned like this?
We'd both get busted if he found us together. Over, geez.
You put "over" in the wrong spot.
So I was thinking we should split up a little. Over.
Then this is pointless.
It's 100% guaranteed he'd get us both.
That aside, I'm getting hungry. Over.
Like I care! Why don't you just order delivery?
Delivery? But we're outside.
Didn't you know?
Aiya's known to deliver anywhere and everywhere.
For real?!
In that case...
Excuse me, but I'd like a delivery for two beef bowls.
I don't want anything!
Who said one's for you?
They're both for me!
Oh, you don't say?
I'm at...
Hey, you!
Whadduya think you're doing?
W-We're just a loving couple passing by!
In your dreams!
Don't argue with me, stupid!
But I'm not going along with that story!
Huh? Didn't I see you yesterday?
We weren't trying to get in your way.
And we don't think it's strange or anything.
S-Strange?
Satonaka, you moron! Keep your mouth shut!
Run for it.
Hey, Hanamura!
Don't leave me behind!
Hey! Stop right there!
It's not like that! I swear it isn't!
Sorry, but we brought trouble!
Yukiko, I'm sorry!
He's chasing them!
Let's run.
Wait, dammit!
I said, wait up!
You're dead! You're so friggin' dead!
Dammit! He's gonna get all of us at this rate.
Time to become our decoy, Satonaka!
Why me?!
You know the line, "I'll handle him. You keep going!"
This is your chance to say it!
You have a point.
Chie, don’t let him trick you!
I said to stop running from me!
The hell?!
Thanks for the order.
What?!
Here's your delivery.
How'd you find us when we've been on the move?
The total is 1,600 yen.
Don't blow me off!
Sorry. Do you have change?
And you're paying?!
Chie, here's a hundred yen.
Save it for later!
Just leave the bowls.
Where?!
We managed to lose him.
Yeah...
Chie...
Is it good?
Ah, it's so nice and warm!
Man, this sucks! We can't keep this up!
Let's disband already!
But what about Kanji?
He'll be fine on his own.
He won't get kidnapped without a fight.
Let's keep an eye on him a bit longer.
Well, we're done for today.
Where should I leave the bowls?
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
Good evening, dear viewers.
Today, I'll introduce a superb site for those searching for a sublime love
that surpasses the separation of the sexes.
I will be your host.
I'm Tatsumi Kanji, my darlings!
No way.
H-Hold it! It's too gay in there!
That pisses me off!
Calm down, Yukiko!
If you don't stop this shit...
Time for one last hustle!
Ch-Change!