When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Thank you for your hospitality.
You're very welcome.
Come visit us again.
Isumi, do you feel like getting lost for another night?
But...
I need you!
If we part now, there's a chance that we'll never meet again in this life!
We can meet again if you come to school, too.
She even has a friend that would ask her to come.
I need to do something so Milady can commute to school joyfully.
Hayate!
Y-Yes?!
What do you think the meaning of life is?
M-Must I answer that now?
No, but I feel that one's proof of life shouldn't given by someone else.
Once you're born a human, there has to be a path of life reserved for each person.
Um, is this going to take long?
That's all I had to say.
Phew.
Well now, the problem's not going to get solved as long as she makes excuses for herself.
To listen to what Milady has to say even in a state of emergency.
Another job as a butler.
Why are you coming in here, too?!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Please do not watch this episode alone.
Good morning, Milady! It's Hayate!
What do you want so early in the morning?
Milady!
Idiot! What are you doing all of a sudden?
I'll be helping you get dressed.
Walking you to the school isn't enough!
Don't be ridiculous!
How could I get changed in front of you! It's so embarrassing!
Walk me to school?
Yes.
Starting today, I'll be taking you to and from school.
Do you actually think that would make me go back to school?
Actually, not going to school but somewhere else sounds good.
What are you saying? A student's job is to study.
You have to attend every day and study hard.
Have a good day, Milady.
Why?
You and I will be apart during the time I'm at school,
so why do you want to make me go to school so much?
Because there are those who can't attend even if they want to.
I-I'm sorry.
I'll come pick you up once the school lets out.
When our Lady's off to school, the mansion's nice and quiet.
I think it'd be quieter if the tiger didn't talk.
Man, the debt-ridden butler is unsociable.
And speaking of school, don't you have to go?
You were going to a high school
before coming here, weren't you?
I was, but...
...having to serve Milady as her butler for the next forty years, I can't go back to school now.
So I have to listen to classes that resemble shitty old games again...
Nagi, hold on.
Why doesn't the blackboard come with a skip function?
Because Japan uses such an old system, their education never-
Wh-What are you-
You mustn't go.
You're not headed towards the academic building.
O-Oh, right.
And it sure is rare that you knew we were headed the wrong way.
Looks like coming to school daily does help.
That's not exactly why, but I can tell.
I won!
Note: あたり (Atari) means "Win"; たたり (Tatari) means "Curse"
I-It's off by a letter.
Hey, I'm home.
What, this is strange.
What's wrong?
Looks like she left a notebook at school.
What?
Look! This is what happens when I go to school.
It happens only because you go to school ever so rarely.
I'll go get it.
I can't let the proof of Milady's day of hard work
lay in an empty classroom.
It's not that important of a thing...
It's getting late, too.
I'm off!
How do I enter the school at night?
An intruder!
Um, hey!
You're the former intruder,
the Sanzenin butler who saved my life, umm...
It's Ayasaki Hayate.
And you were a teacher here...
Katsura Yukiji.
Wait, what are you doing here?
I was dodging an attack from behind.
And what are you doing here?
Ah, me?
I'm the POD.
Note: POD stands for "Person on Duty"
Ah, I see, that's perfect. Lady Nagi left a notebook here.
May I borrow the key to the classroom?
The key to the classroom?!
You're going to follow me to the POD room?
Yes, since I don't want to bother you too much.
I'll get it for you, so wait here.
No, I'll get it myself.
Don't open it without a warning!
This POD room is stuffed with the life of a woman in her mid-twenties.
Not at all! I've taken lots of personal stuff out.
Do you perhaps live here?
D-Don't blame me!
I don't have enough money to pay for rent,
and the bath tub here is bigger and cleaner.
Besides, I don't need you, an outsider, to be asking me about that!
Hey, hey.
Katsura-chan's taking a guy into the POD room.
And he's younger than her, too.
Indecency revealed; getting sacked for sure.
Nothing but that!
My salary!
You're misunderstanding us!
And that poor man's face, I recall seeing it somewhere...
I'm the Sanzenin butler, Ayasaki Hayate.
The one who broke into school and...
...flirted with the student council president, but got dumped and kicked in the face...
...and thus tried to lock her up in the student council room, but the plan failed due to Yukiji's brave actions.
The Sanzenin butler!
I think a really incorrect story's being told here.
It's your imagination.
I'm the student council chairman, Segawa Izumi.
Nice to meet you!
The vice-chairman, Hanabishi Miki.
Disciplinary committee, Asakaze Risa.
Student Council? Then they're Katsura-san's friends?
What are you doing here?
Err, err, Hayata-kun?
It's Hayate.
I'm here to pick up a notebook Lady Nagi forgot.
I see.
By the way, Hayata-kun,
we're here for a study group for midterms.
Just as she said, Hayata-kun.
Hayata's fine...
But to have a study group so late at night; you must all be hard workers.
If we truly were hard workers,
we wouldn't be studying here, Hayata-kun.
But isn't Hakuou a prestigious school?
Only some students are wicked smart ones.
That's what the transfer and the grade skipping system we have is for.
The backbone is an escalator system where you don't drop out unless something major happens.
All the way from elementary school to high school.
People like us that have been here since elementary school are...
...genuine idiots!
So much so that we could drop out from the something major happening.
Do you get it?
And I'm teaching them.
Katsura-chan's teaching is so easy to understand.
Oh, stop it.
It's a great proof that good teachers are good PODs.
Exactly.
Wait, is that a compliment?
Don't worry, I'm ridiculing you.
Don't make fun of teachers!
They look like they're having fun.
Here.
The key to the classroom.
Make sure you come return it, Hayata-kun.
You do know my name, right?
But you're definitely a boy to have the courage to go to the west wing at this hour.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, does that mean...
Well, it is an old school.
So a lot of them will appear.
Don't bring a curse back with you!
Make sure to defeat Sada** or Kaya** or Jaso* or Fre*** if they were to appear.
They're playing with me since it's not their business.
Besides, it's the building they always go to, so such things can't possibly come out.
Wait, wait! It looks way different from last time I was here!
Well, since I've come all this way, might as well as go in.
Through the red door.
Ika ha ikaga? = Would you like squid?
Ika ha ikaga?
Gattsuri itadakimasu = I'll take a whole lot
Gattsuri itadakimasu
Cell phone?
Oh yeah, Maria-san gave it to me.
Hello?
Hey Hayate. How's it going?
I just made it to inside the building.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But the school at night is dangerous, so...
...I was worried for you.
Thank you very much.
I was relieved to hear your voice, too.
I thought you were alone, but I hear lots of voices in the background, so there must a group with you.
People's voices you say?
Yeah, I hear a lot in the background.
But it's not a haunted house,
so they don't have to yell so loudly.
Well, good luck.
Milady!
Milady!!!
I've got to hurry to the classroom.
He's not coming back, is he?
Well, school at night tends to have
the lustrous flutes and gym shorts that seduce men.
He may be a butler, but he's a guy before that.
He must be rustling through Hina-chan's desk and working on the flute right now.
Aren't you all having fun!
What's the topic of discussion?
President.
Hina, when did you come?
I came all the way to bring a care package. Are you guys taking this seriously?
Don't worry, we were having a serious discussion about the perverted nature of boys who've hit puberty.
Huh?
As a result, Hina's flute must belong to Hayata-kun now!
That's right!
Get back to studying!
Or maybe Hayata-kun made a mistake and got lost in the old building.
The old building?
That's entirely possible!
That's a problem. That building is-
What?
Hakuou Academy has ghosts?
Yes. They apparently appear in the old building.
But that school would probably hire Ghostsweepers.
What are we going to do if Hayate goes in there by mistake?
Hayate! Answer me, Hayate!
What? Hayate-kun from Sanzenin went to that old building?
It's only a possibility, and we're not sure if he got lost or not.
I'll go search for him.
It's dangerous, Hina-chan.
A person unrelated to the school might be in danger on campus.
I can't leave the matter alone.
Ghosts might appear, though.
Don't worry. I'm not scared of ghosts and such.
That sure is Hina.
My sister is a waste to keep as a girl.
That said...
Anyway, I must find Hayate-kun fast.
Come to think of it, why is it so bright here?
That scream was...
The cell phone's...
Weren't you not scared of ghosts?
Where would you find a girl that can stand up to that?!
I'm told that the floating fires are
balls of plasma that can be scientifically explained.
You can't explain fear!
Then here's the last question.
Who's been asking you questions for the past few seconds?
S-Someone...
Someone!!!
Are you all right?
You're the student council president, Katsura-san.
K-Katsura-san?
Thank you for saving me.
But...
...don't get lost in such a scary place!!!
Oh, this is the old building?
No wonder something was strange.
Keep that a secret, okay, Hayate-kun?
Eh?
If you tell anyone that I was seriously scared,
I'll hit you with all my might.
I think you had lots of might in the first one.
Anyways, let's hurry up and get out of here.
What are you saying, Hayate-kun?
You think I can leave here defeated?
But I have to go get Milady's notebook.
No!
We're going to find out who's doing this.
Katsura-san!
Call me Hinagiku!
Please wait, Katsura-san!
Something has to be done.
Katsura-san's just like Milady after all. So stubborn.
It's so hot.
Oh, so you're actually conscious of the fact you're alone with a girl at school at night?
I-I'm not particularly conscious of you.
Not particularly?
Besides, you're too forward.
You need to have a little more modesty in front of boys.
With an aggressive attitude, no matter what boys do, you can't-
Fine.
If it's you, I don't mind what you do.
K-Katsura-san?
Would boys take it seriously when I make jokes like that?
Thank you for the warning.
I'll be sure to watch out for boys like you from now on.
I thought she was as stubborn as Milady, but I was wrong.
She's more stubborn than her.
That's the doll I broke a few minutes ago!
You're joking!
Tada.
Go home, you humans.
If you don't, I-I'll eat you all.
Don't take the Hakuou Academy's student council president, Katsura Hinagiku, so lightly.
It's not fair to attack so suddenly.
Anyways, Hayate-sama.
Please leave here... I mean get out!
The humiliation I received earlier, I'll return it to you a hundredfold.
Take that!
"Hayate-sama"?
I don't understand why, but maybe this is a simple threat just because she wants us out of here?
Katsura-san, let's forget about
that fearsome monster and get out of here!
Call me Hinagiku.
Anyway, I'm going to defeat this.
What? Don't say you need to defeat that thing "oh so wonderfully", and let's get out of here!
Don't worry, Hayate-kun.
If you don't get scared, this isn't that strong.
I am strong!
I am strong, so I'll kill you all, humans!
Even if you transform, you're still no match for me.
You got me.
But I haven't done anything yet.
Yikes.
Th-That was amazing, Katsura-san.
To defeat the sprit with only your mind.
That must have been what people refer to as chi.
Like the sort of thing that masters use.
You must have used it unconsciously.
You're so amazing, Katsura-san.
It's hard to accept the theory.
Now, since we were able to defeat the ghost, let's hurry out of-
You're going to go get Nagi's notebook, right?
Let's hurry on.
Yes, Katsura-san.
Call me Hinagiku.
Yes, Hinagiku-san.
They're finally off.
Yes.
Now, let's do away with the real ghosts.
Yes, ma'am!
Hayate!
I was worried about you! Did you get possessed by any spirits?
I'm fine.
School's a nice place.
School life is so far away now.
What does the indebted butler think?
And next time, an accident that nobody has imagined will happen.
We'll be fighting against an emergency.
Or rather, we'll have no choice but to fight it.
Get back to studying!
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Nice to meet you, I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
Today, we have Maria-san as our guest.
Nice to meet you. I'm Maria.
This song is so soothing.
As expected from Maria-san.
Thank you very much, Hayate-kun.
Stop flirting again, Hayate.
Oh?
All right then! I'll get working
on becoming a soothing type of girl!
Milady, you're best as you are now.
Really? If you say so.
Bye bye.
Maria, I remember seeing this scene before...
Next time is the same as episode eight.
Then we can see the cat-ear Hayate from another angle?
Not only that, but it is an anime original story.
That's filled with expectations and anxiety.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
The World's Bizarre High Deflation.
Don't Stack Up Games and Play Them.
Sir Hero! Please come fast!
I'm on fire!