A barbecue?
That's a great idea! But...
Wouldn't that distract Ryuunosuke from his work?
Don't worry about that!
The barbecue was his idea in the first place.
The woods at Kibougamori are really pretty, you know!
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Well, in that case, I guess I'll have to take you up on that offer.
Excuse me...
Welcome!
Sorry to run like this, Sakura, but we have a customer.
What timing, so do we.
Well, I'll call you to confirm the details, all right?
Toshioka, what flowers are you looking for today?
Well, um...
Is he a regular customer?
Yup. He buys a lot of bouquets from us.
As presents for his girlfriend, he says!
Welcome!
What kind of clothes may I interest you in today?
I want something that'll make him love me more than anyone in the world!
I want flowers that'll bloom for all eternity!
Huh?!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
When you say you want flowers that'll bloom for all eternity...
you mean preserved flowers, right?
That's right. That's what I meant!
Preserved flowers?
They're flowers that've been plucked at full bloom,
then are processed in such a way that they don't wilt and will always stay beautiful.
Well, they won't last for all eternity, but they will last for a really long time.
However, I'm afraid we don't sell them here...
But I've been wanting to get into them for a while now!
So if you like, Toshioka, I can get the tools and make them for you.
You can?! That's great...
I want to give her a bouquet of preserved flowers...
"More than anyone in the world" is a little...
I thought if I went to Fairy Drop...
If I went to Kurumi Sakura, the super charismatic ex-model...
I thought you might be able to help me.
Well, wearing my designs does tend to enrapture people.
So I'm certain it'd work!
Mom...
Oops, my bad.
Young lady...
It might be a bit brazen of me to say this, but...
Being loved by someone...
is about more than just appearances, right?
You're probably right.
But I want to make myself look prettier!
I want to win back his heart!
I want to win back her heart!
Win her back with preserved flowers?
That's right. I'm...
I'm going to propose to her!
Propose?!
Hearts Aflutter!
The Great Proposal!
Proposing, huh?
What flowers do you think we should use, Tsubomi?
Well, roses are pretty much
essential for this sort of thing!
We have a lot of designs to choose from.
Or you can make an original design if you like, Toshioka.
R-Right...
Toshioka?
You're nervous, aren't you?
I know the feeling.
When I proposed to my dear wife here,
my throat felt so dry from nervousness that all the water in the world wouldn't put it right!
Dear...
Um, did something happen between you two?
The thing is, as of late, she just seems so distant!
I see.
So your boyfriend seems to be distant as of late.
Cut that out.
Are you sure you're not imagining it?
We've been so busy with work lately that we just haven't had time to see each other.
And when we do get to meet, it seems like he's hiding something from me.
I don't think that's worth worrying yourself over!
When my husband and I were dating,
he once went overseas for a whole year!
Well, some people are just like that.
You can't think so pessimistically about these things.
You're wrong!
I always thought this time might come.
He's... Yuuto's brilliant, very kind, and really dashing.
I don't deserve someone like him!
I'm certain that Yuuto's fallen for someone else!
She's fallen for someone else?! I'm sure that can't be right!
But even if I did buy her an engagement
ring, I've neglected Lisa so much lately...
I wouldn't blame her if she didn't love me anymore!
You can't think like that, Toshioka! You need to have more faith in yourself!
That's right!
Whenever you were going on a date, you always came here to buy flowers for her!
There aren't many guys as kind as you out there!
Being kind isn't all it's cracked up to be.
So is that why you want the preserved flowers?
Yeah.
When I heard that there were flowers that never wilt, I just thought...
"This is it!"
...to myself.
So when I give her the engagement ring,
I want to give her those preserved
flowers as a sign of my eternal love.
If I do, I might be able to win Lisa's heart back.
Oh, I get it! So that's why you want us to find you something nice!
I can't bring myself to give up on him, no matter what.
So if I show him just how pretty I can be...
I might be able to win back Yuuto's heart.
Erika!
Roger!
When a lady's in love, fashion will always be on her side!
We understand your feelings perfectly, Lisa!
So just leave it to us!
Th-Thank you very much!
But...
Just the thought of meeting her...
scares me so much!
I'm pathetic, aren't I?
When I think that Lisa's heart might've slipped from my grasp, I just...
completely lose my courage to propose to her!
No way...
Toshioka.
Lisa always loves the flowers you buy for her, right?
Yes, very much.
That's not just because of how pretty they are, you know?
It's because they're from you that they're so special to her.
I wonder if that's really true.
Excuse me, Toshioka!
Would you like to bring Lisa to our barbecue?!
A barbecue?
Yeah!
You might not be able to handle it when you're alone,
but if you're having fun with everyone, you might loosen up a bit!
That's a good point.
So why not just pluck up that little bit of courage and invite him to come along with you?
That's right! If he sees you wearing this, he'll be putty in your hands!
All right!
Well then, I'll leave it all to you!
Lights!
You damn annoying Precures!
Aaaaargh! Ever since I went to the human plane, my skin's been so moist that I can't do anything with it!
The dryness of the desert is
meant to enhance my beauty.
All this moistness is preventing my hair from setting!
Kobraja.
If it plagues you so, you should reduce their dank and sodden world to sand.
As you wish, my liege.
Then go forth, Kobraja.
Yes, sir.
Good morning.
That customer of yours said he was
bringing his girlfriend, didn't he, Mizuki?
And didn't the girl from your place say
she was bringing her boyfriend, Sakura?
Then are you two...
I'm Toshioka Yuuto.
And I'm Shibata Lisa.
Which means...
...that they're dating!
I guess coincidences do happen, huh?
Yeah, it really shocked me!
But...
After we have our fun with the barbecue, we're going to go unwind down at the river, right?
Toshioka, try to keep up!
Ah, right!
They're just falling further apart, and all because of some misunderstanding!
I'm gonna go sort this out!
Erika, please stop!
What is it?!
He's going to propose to her, you know!
It's mature and romantic love!
They say "Love is without reason."
That's right. Love is a scoundrel which has rid itself of the shackles of logic and wisdom!
Though they love each other, they drift so tragically apart.
Don't you see, Erika?!
Our role is merely to observe and guide them!
All right, all right, I get it...
But it'd be nice if we could do
something to help them make up.
I suppose you're right.
If only we had some way of getting them past that misunderstanding.
You done with that, you two?
Dad!
I was just on my way to the
suspension bridge over there.
Would you two like to join me?
Are you going to take some photos?
Yeah. I really enjoy admiring the scenery from a bridge like that.
A suspension bridge?
That's it! A suspension bridge!
We can use the Suspension Bridge Effect!
What?
Allow me to explain! The Suspension Bridge Effect works thusly!
Lay it on me!
When you're in a high place like a suspension bridge, you feel scared and your heart starts pounding, right?
Does it?
Well, it can...
That's right, it can! And then...
"Oh no, the bridge is shaking!"
"Oh no, I'm scared! Thump, thump!"
"Are you all right?"
"Could it be that this pounding in my chest... is love?!"
And then the two of them fall in love once more!
You really are an interesting girl, Tsubomi!
You really give off a "This is Tsubomi!" aura!
Doesn't she?
Anyway...
When their hearts are pounding from the fright, their minds will confuse it for the pangs of love!
Then we can use that confusion to help them make up?
That's right!
In that case, we'll have to tag along after all!
Dad, go invite Toshioka and Lisa to join us, all right?
Roger that.
Wow!
What do you think? It's a nice spot, isn't it?
Y-Yeah... It may be a little frightening...
but it's very pretty!
Isn't it? This view is the best!
And the air's nice too! But there's more important things to worry about!
Th-Those clothes sure are pretty!
Huh?
Th-Thank you...
Damn it, this is pissing me off!
Erika, please don't rock it like that!
Hey, cut it out! Rocking the
bridge like that is dangerous!
Well, your dad's gonna head down and take some photos by the river.
Oh, that's it!
Wait up, Dad! I'm coming too!
Huh? Hey, wait, I'm coming too!
Now they're all on their own!
Let's hope Operation: Suspension
Bridge Effect goes according to plan.
S-Sure is nice weather we're having, huh?
Yeah, it is nice out.
R-Really is perfect conditions for a barbecue.
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
This is working out well!
All right! Keep it up, suspension bridge!
Hey! I'm heading back soon!
We're at the good part right now!
Head back without us, Dad.
All right then, I'll see you back there.
The food's almost ready, so hurry back soon!
All right!
I-I'm all right now, so...
Oh, I'm sorry!
My Fairy Drop dress...
Please lend me courage!
Yuuto, please listen!
Wh-What is it?
Well, well, what have we here...
Such reserved yet loving hearts.
They're so very beautiful.
That's...
Kobraja?!
Yet the Flowers of your Hearts seem far less sturdy.
Especially yours, mademoiselle.
The Flower of your Heart is so close to wilting.
I shall steal it away!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Li-Lisa...
Today's Desertrian will have an aquatic flavor, I think.
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Erika!
Let's do it!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
We'll make you return the Flower of Lisa's Heart!
Lisa!
Waaaaaaaateeeeer!
Well this isn't beautiful at all!
It's no wonder things are over between you two when you act like this!
Now go!
Waaaaaaaaaateeeeeeeer!
Marine, leave this to me!
Marine Impact!
Great as ever, Marine!
Huh?
I can't get my hand out!
Waaaaaateeeeeeeeeer!
Marine!
Chypre, Coffret!
Thank goodness...
Yuuto...
I don't have any confidence in myself.
That's why even though I know you love me, I still feel so anxious!
I feel so scared, but I don't want to!
What? What's it saying?!
Those are Lisa's true feelings for you!
Lisa's true feelings?
Waaaaaaaaaateeeeeeeeeer!
Desertrian!
Don't be distracted by this pointless talk of love and romance!
It's not pointless!
Our love is genuine!
Look at these!
They're the tulips you love so much!
In the language of flowers, they symbolize eternal love!
I swear my eternal love for you with these immortal tulips!
Lisa! Please marry me!
What?!
Lisa!
You've really moved me, Toshioka!
So I'll use the Pink Forte Wave...
and bring the two of you back together!
Hey, what about me?!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Marine, are you all right?!
Love is kinda addictive...
Tch! Next time, you shan't be so lucky!
Adieu!
This flower belongs to you.
Now hurry and return her to normal!
Right!
Your words can't have been a dream.
They weren't.
This is no dream.
Lisa, let's get married.
Loving someone can be so troubling at times, but it's still so beautiful.
Lisa seems so happy!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born!
With this, the Great Heart Tree will recover a little more!
All we need is love, huh?
Yeah, you're right!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
I've been dreaming about Cure Moonlight again recently...
Cure Moonlight?!
Could it be some kind of sign?!
Where could she be?
She might be closer than you think!
What if she's really Momoka?!
No way!
Ms. Tsurusaki?!
It could be.
How about that cute guy that keeps saving us?!
Don't be ridiculous!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Truth is Revealed!
Cure Moonlight's True Identity!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!