Hurry up, Yui!
Your ribbon's crooked, Haruka.
Thanks!
We have plenty of time, so take it easy.
I know, but my excitement's in full bloom and I can't sit still!
After all, tonight is my dearly awaited Noble Party!
Haruno Haruka's taking her first step into high society!
Um, it's a school event...
Line those chairs up by the wall.
Got it!
President!
We can handle this, so go get changed.
Everyone's dying to see your dress!
Thank you.
Oh, place those plates on the table over there.
Okay!
Next is...
Close.
Y-Yes...
I will give you one more chance to redeem yourself.
Y-You will?
However...
This is your final one.
The consequences for failure...
go without saying.
Right!
I swear I'll defeat the Princess Precures and steal their Dress Up Keys!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
The Curtain Rises!
The Noble Party of My Dreams!
Miss Haruno!
Y-Yes?
No running in the halls!
I'm sorry...
Pets aren't allowed inside the buildings...
but I'll allow her for today.
You both match.
Splendid, splendid!
Oh, it's simply splendid!
Haruharu, calm down.
Kirara!
Whatcha think? I put a star on one of Mom's old dresses.
It's cute!
Yours is cute, too!
Same to you.
Thank you...
Bonjour, everyone.
Oh, it's Minami!
She's splendid...
Like a real princess!
Minami's so pretty!
Tonight's party is a tradition hailing back to Noble Academy's foundation.
Let us all enjoy this event without letting our grades separate us.
Now raise your glasses...
and have a toast to your dreams!
Cheers!
So this is a party!
It's like we're in a fairy tale!
Yeah!
Like a fantasy in full bloom!
What's over there?
What's happening?
Wow!
Huh?!
Shirogane. Dorm mother.
Shirogane?
Have a Shirogane Mixed Juice.
How pretty...
You're amazing, Shirogane!
Don't mind if we do!
It's delicious!
The buffet is to your right.
Oh!
Let's go, Haruharu!
It's huge!
They went all out!
This feast is the fruit of the Culinary Club's labor!
Help yourselves!
Don't mind if I do!
So, can I serve myself?
Sure, just get a plate.
Oh, I see!
If you'll excuse me...
I'll have some of this, some of that, and that looks good too...
There we go!
Can you eat all that?
Of course!
Oh, fried chicken!
Oh, pardon me!
Oh no, pardon me!
Go for it.
Oh, I couldn't!
Wait, Yuuki?
Haruno?!
That dress...
It...
It looks nice in spite of you!
What, was that an insult?
Aihara, let's go talk over there!
Yeah, over there!
Hey, I haven't eaten anything!
He sure keeps busy.
Phew, I'm full!
I'm in full bloom happiness!
You really ate it all.
Hey, where's Minami?
Now that you mention it...
Minami has business to attend to.
Oh, Vice President, uh...
It's Azuma.
Having fun?
Yeah!
So, that business...
The Student Council organizes the Noble Party...
But the President oversees all of the preparations herself.
The Pres always puts too much pressure on herself.
Indeed. We're here to help her,
yet she always handles matters alone.
She actually can handle everything, though, so we can't even talk back.
Is that true?
Pardon the late introduction.
I'm the other vice president, Imagawa Shuu.
I also represent the men's dorm.
I'm a secretary, Koshiba Naoto.
Oh, nice to meet you!
The Pres has told me all about you, Haruno Haruka.
About the knack you've got for ballet, or about how hard you study.
I feel a bit embarrassed...
We didn't mean it like that!
Sorry, really!
The next song will begin the waltz.
Finally!
The waltz is the centerpiece of a party!
Oh, I want to dance!
Do you even know how to ballroom dance?
I took a lesson the other day!
Like this, right?
One, two, three!
One, two, thr—uwaagh!
Haruka!
Minami!
Glad you're all right.
Sorry, I know you're really busy...
There was a lull in my duties.
Being the Student Council President must be such a burden.
You have so much work,
but I was just enjoying the party without a care in the world...
It's nothing you need to worry about.
Besides, I've never thought of my position as a burden.
Huh?
My father and brother are far more capable than I am and do splendid work for their companies.
I want to grow up to be just like them.
That's why I can't let such a trivial
amount of work get the best of me.
So, is that... your dream?
My dream?
Perhaps...
But you've done so much for me already...
so I'd like to help you and return the favor!
Thank you.
Now, the waltz has begun!
Why does the Film Club have to record this stinkin' party?
I couldn't care less about filming these things!
Then what do ya wanna film?
Lemme see that dream of yours!
I'm directing a horror film!
I'll toss that dream into the cage of despair!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Princess Precures...
I swear that today,
I'll send you into des—
What're ya tryin' to film me for?!
What?
What happened?
Haruka...
Yui...
Everyone, stay calm.
This way! The corridors are still lit.
It seems that only the party hall's lights are out.
The light switches aren't working.
We'll have to check the breaker panel in the storage room.
The storage room?
It's one of the school's seven mysteries.
Seven mysteries?
I hear it's haunted by ghosts!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll head to the storage room.
Seira, Ayaka, you stay here.
Imagawa and Koshiba, can you come with me?
Sure.
I'm humbled to act as our Noble Princess's knight.
Minami...
I'll be right back.
Be careful!
It's probably just a prank.
Yeah. That's just a rumor, anyway.
Who still believes in—
Please stop talking!
People have had high hopes for this party.
Let's get it back on track.
Right...
Pineapple Ponytail!
It seems the hall's breaker really was switched off.
Switching it on should solve our problem.
Thank goodness...
Boo?
Boooooo!
What's that?
We found our prankster. Catch him!
Get back here!
Are you okay?
Gotcha!
Dyspairvil!
Hey, what're you makin' ghosts for?!
You'd gotta be barmy to think that'd scare a Pre—
Dyspairvil.
Booooo!
A ghost!
Bollocks!
Kaidou's been gone for a while.
Maybe I should have gone with her.
Why's that?
Well, Minami tries to do everything,
but there's one thing she can't stand.
And that's...
Back when Minami was in elementary school with us,
she accepted a dare, and then Seira...
scared her a bit too much.
Ever since then...
Just hearing about ghosts gives her the shivers.
What?
Not bad!
Dyspairvil!
So it was you who turned out the lights!
Huh?
I won't let you ruin our party!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
You're the one who oughta be prepared!
Scare her stiff, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Boooooo!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Boo!
You're shakin' in your boots!
This is no time to be afraid!
Boo!
Now I can show Lady Dyspear just how strong I am!
Keep it up!
Dyspairvil!
Boo!
Noooo!
Finish her!
Dyspairvil!
Mermaid!
Huh?!
Are you all right?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Blimey!
Just beat 'em all!
Dyspair... vil!
Mermaid!
Are you all right?
It's kinda cute that you're afraid of these guys.
Well, I'm not afraid of ghosts!
Good for you.
Wait, that's not the point!
Those ghosts came from a Dyspairvil!
Yeah, I can tell.
Leave the Dyspairvil to me!
Dyspairvil!
Can you stand?
This isn't quite my proudest moment...
I know I have to fight for everyone.
But I can't help it.
I can't control what I'm afraid of.
Dyspairvil!
Boo!
Flora...
When I was young, my mom would always do this for me on scary or lonely nights.
I'll be your knight and protect the academy's princess!
Flora...
Let's go!
Right!
Dyspairvil.
Dys!
Hey!
Dyspair!
Boo!
Mermaid!
Flora!
Vil!
Boooo...
Mermaid!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rage, O seas!
Precure!
Mermaid Ripple!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Noooo!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
I can't show my face to Lady Dyspear again...
This is your fault, Cure Flora!
Open!
The door to your dream!
I'm certain your dream will come true.
You gave me quite the scare, after all.
Our apologies for the delay.
We shall resume with the waltz!
May I have this dance?
Sorry, but I've already chosen
who I'll have my first dance with.
Huh?
Let us dance, my knight.
Huh?!
Follow my lead.
You're dancing well. Thank you, Haruka.
Perhaps I ought to ask for your help more often.
Sure!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
We'll get the Dress Up Keys
and become Grand Princesses!
Go! Princess Precure!:
Where Is It?
The New Dress Up Key!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hyougo Prefecture - Honoka (Age 5)
Chiba Prefecture - Ayaka (Age 12)