Ryuu-chan...
Ryuu-chan!
Y-Yo.
W-Why?
Ryuu-chan, you're all right?
A-Aren't you...
I-In... Help...
Yasuko...
You've raised Ryuuji-kun well.
Yeah, I-I have...
The reason why my life was in "danger"...
L-Listen, Ya-chan!
Ryuuji is...
After falling for the fake voicemail that Taiga left,
Yasuko cried a lot and Grandpa scolded her.
Somehow...
Somehow, it's like Ya-chan is a child right now.
Families are amazing.
Even though they haven't seen each other in about ten years,
they're still...
Mum, thanks!
It's all because of you spoiling Yasuko-
Come on, there's nothing wrong with it.
No, but you...
Yasuko must be tired.
We're a family, right?
Family...
Ryuuji-kun, hurry up and take your bath before the water gets cold.
Okay.
So you weren't married...
You found out?
Yeah.
Your dad ran away with another woman while I was pregnant.
Even though everyone told me to get an abortion,
I really wanted to protect you.
In the end, I couldn't protect you, and things broke.
Nothing broke.
Didn't Grandma say you raised me well?
See, I'm a lot taller than you.
Be proud.
Yeah, you've grown.
Your back was really big when you were running...
So big that I didn't recognise you.
I was really scared,
but I was also a little happy.
But I was so afraid that you'd leave and never come back...
So you left by yourself?
Idiot.
I'm the last person who should say this,
but running away won't get you anywhere.
Ryuu-chan...
I will become an adult.
I'll do it right in front of you, not in some place far away.
That's why you have to look at me... always.
Come on, stop crying!
But...
W-What is this?
Grandma said there's nothing wrong with sleeping in the same room, since we're going to get married.
Now I understand how Yasuko became the way she is now...
Ya-chan is laughing!
Yeah, she is.
Hey, turn off the lights.
Huh? Why?
Just do it.
What are you doing?
The stars are amazing.
To be honest, I'm kind of worried.
I don't think running away and getting married will work out,
but I still want to have this dream.
I feel like if I don't do something here, things will break again.
Sheesh, you and Yasuko...
Nothing broke, right?
Also, it's okay for us to start here.
We don't need to run away to get married. Let's do it with everyone's approval.
Wouldn't it be best to receive everyone's blessing?
Who do you mean by "everyone"?
Grandpa, Grandma, and your parents.
That will take a long time...
It doesn't matter.
Since we'll be happy anyway,
why not share our happiness with everyone else?
Okay,
but before that, let's have a little rehearsal.
Look,
a veil.
Taiga...
Um... I, Takasu Ryuuji, will...
Uh, what should I say?
It doesn't matter, just say something.
H-How can it not matter?
Uh... will marry Aisaka Taiga-
As I thought, I don't want a vow yet.
What?!
Wasn't this your idea in the first-
Do you remember what you said before?
Huh?
"Since ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast to equal the tiger."
That's why, even without a vow, we'll always be together, right?
Yeah.
Tai-
Your eyes are red.
Your breathing is all weird.
Shut up!
Your lips are cracked.
It'll hurt if we kiss.
It's not like...
If we kiss, it'll definitely hurt... a lot.
How was it?
Just as I expected...
It was like a rough, dry wilderness.
Also, it was really, really warm...
Hey, it's cold, so let's do it once more-
Once more...
Takasu
Somehow, it feels weird.
Just us two left,
but now three people and a pet are coming back.
Ryuuji, you believed it, right?
Huh?
That Ya-chan would come if you lied,
then get back on good terms with Grandma and Grandpa.
I didn't think she would,
but I didn't think she wouldn't either...
I wonder why.
Perhaps it's like that.
Perhaps families are like that...
Oh, I'm so hungry!
Taiga-chan, you're coming over for dinner, right?
I...
It's all right.
We're a family of three, right?
Yeah...
Oh, I forgot about you, Inko-chan...
Taiga?
You guys go ahead, I'm going to go change my clothes.
But won't your parents be-
I'm coming with you.
Fine.
Be quick, since I'm making your favorite tonight; pork cutlets.
Huh?
Mum?
Taiga, what are you think-
You seriously don't think about the consequen-
Cut it ou-
Taiga...
Taiga, do you really hate me that mu-
Fine!
I don't give a damn anymore!
I'm leaving, so do whatever you want! Bye!
She's just like a kid...
Ryuuji, you know,
I always thought that I would never be loved...
It smells great!
I'm not just making pork cutlets.
Grandma taught me how to make some delicious taro rice.
Yay!
Thank you, Ryuu-chan.
...but perhaps that was just an excuse for running away.
I can't see the stars...
It's so small...
It's hidden and lonely, just like me.
I blamed my lack of confidence on my parents and my surroundings,
but Ryuuji still loves me.
That's why...
...I won't run away anymore.
I have to change.
I have to accept everything.
I will be proud of myself and love Ryuuji.
That day, Taiga didn't come over for dinner.
Takasu, we can't understand if you don't tell us anything.
What actually happened?
Why did Taiga-
Come on, everyone, back to your seats.
I have some bad news for everyone.
Due to family reasons, Aisaka-san is withdrawing from this school.
I've just received that message from her mother.
Aisaka-san will be going back to her mother's-
Wai-
This is a lie, right? It's a joke, right? She was forced, right?!
She didn't tell us or...
In your lives, you will all come to different crossroads.
Regardless of whether you decide to stay where you are, or turn back,
you still have to make a decision.
Aisaka-san's decision may mean leaving you all,
but it's a decision she tried her best to make.
Let's support her, okay?
Kids these days are so scary!
Are you all calling Aisaka-san?
Texting her?
Unbelievable!
You should all take a good, hard look at your lives!
Takasu?
It won't go through if we all call at the same time!
Everyone, back to your seats!
Takasu-kun!
Kushie-
Can you clench your teeth for a second?
Why did you come back by yourself?!
Why is Taiga transferring?!
I don't get it!
Hey, Takas-
Wait, Kushieda!
Kitamura-kun.
I... I didn't want her to go.
I'd bring her back right now if I could.
I'd ask her why she decided everything by herself.
But...
...she believes in me.
That's why the only thing I can do right now is accept it.
Takasu...
Wow, she learns how to be tidy at the last minute.
What's this?
Oh! A single sock!
Unforgivable!
Where's your buddy?
I'll definitely find him for you!
That klutz...
How could she forget these?
You're really stupid, aren't you?
1 NEW
MESSAGE
Taiga
You never
told me that you
love me.
I didn't?
I remember when I fell into the river-
Oh, yeah! Crap!
I was interrupted...
Gosh, I even said it a few times to Kawashima...
Stupid.
Yeah, I can be really stupid sometimes too...
Tomiya-kun, are you free today?
Yeah.
There's somewhere I want to go, can you come with me?
Hey, this is...
Ami-chan!
Taiga...
"I'm sorry for yesterday."
That won't happen.
Then, why are you telling me?
I think I kind of understand what you said now...
Hey, hey! Taiga's text message!
I got it!
I got it too!
This is it, right?
Yeah, that!
It seems like Taiga replied to everyone who texted her.
Why is it just a picture?
I really don't get it.
Yeah, what does it mean?
Seaweed?
It's the night sky.
Kushieda?
Oh, she's right.
Is that small dot a star?
Really? You're imagining things, right?
No, it's definitely a star.
But why did she take a picture of it?
"I will protect you all from the faraway sky."
Shut up! She's not dead yet!
I think she means, "I'll try my best."
Huh?
"Even if the sky is pitch black, with nothing to see,
there will be stars shining somewhere out there.
If I keep shining brighter and brighter,
I'll definitely look better to people."
I think Taiga is kind of selfish.
But even if that's the case, the sky will connect us.
As long as we all shine,
no matter how far apart we are,
we will definitely be able to see each other doing our best.
You overdid that...
It sent chills down my spine...
W-What?!
I think she's right.
Yeah.
This is the feeling of being young, right?
Me too! I'll be happy if she's right!
Yeah.
Speaking of stars, someone caused a lot of trouble back then.
Oh, that!
After taking the time to send us this, I think she'd be happy if we replied.
Be careful!
I can't find it...
Where is it?
I remember putting it away with Ami-chan's tree...
Thanks.
You think of these things to make others happy...
How should I put it... You're amazing at it.
I guess.
Ami-chan's existence itself should be surprising.
You know, before she became who she is,
people loved her even though she caused trouble for everyone.
I was jealous of her.
But that's not true at all.
Even though she seems amazing,
her body and heart are both so small and timid.
All she does is take whatever people throw at her.
She won't let anyone see her true self.
She's the same as someone.
Yeah, she was seen through from the very beginning.
Didn't you say I was a kid?
You know, I hate myself when I pretend to be an adult.
That's why I'm desperate to have others accept me for who I am.
But I finally understood after meeting Taiga...
As long as there's at least one person who understands me, I'll be okay.
Even if it isn't love...
Kawashima-
I found the treasure!
Uh...
So I just have to press here?
Sensei, please hurry up before my godlike power runs out!
Come on, Takasu-kun, smile.
Smile already.
I am!
Amin.
Okay.
Here I go!
I'm a dragon.
You're a tiger.
Since ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast to equal the tiger.
Even if you're not by my side right now,
I will leap through space and time, and always be by your side.
These feelings will never change.
nitete mo chigau yo
似てても違うよ
They're similar, yet different
mandarin orenji
マンダリン オレンジ
- mandarins, oranges;
tomodachi koibito
友達 恋人
friends, lovers -
futari no kokoro mo
２人のココロも
as are the hearts of two people.
kizutsukitakunai
傷つきたくない
I didn't want to be hurt,
watashi wa nigeteta
私は逃げてた
so I ran away.
soshitara hikari mo
そしたら光も
But then, even the light
sashite wa kurenai
射してはくれない
didn't shine for me.
Hey Inko-chan,
isn't this makeup a bit much?
kiseki na no ni ne
奇跡なのにね
They're are miracles, aren't they?
I'm a mother, after all.
deai mo koi mo
出逢いも恋も
And meetings and love,
I should just use some softer colors,
but I don't have things like that...
tane mo tsubomi mo
種もつぼみも
and seeds and buds,
Inko-chan!
mada aoi mi de sae mo
まだ青い　実でさえも
and even the fruits
that are yet unripe?
I-Inko-chan finally said his own name!
Oohashi
High School
78th Graduation
Ceremony
orenji iro wa ano hi
オレンジ色は　 あの日
The orange colour
mita yuuyake wo
見た夕焼けを
reminds me of a sunset
I saw that day.
omoidasasete kureru
思い出させてくれる
It'll be lonely once the seniors leave.
futatsu no kage ga
２つの影が
Our two shadows
They're all so cool and interesting...
te wo tsunaideru mitai datta
手を繋いでるみたいだった
seemed like they were
holding hands.
Did you know that our student council president, Kitamura-senpai,
will be studying abroad in America after graduating?
orenji itsuka
オレンジ　いつか
I wonder if someday the orange
amaku naru kana
甘くなるかな
will become sweet?
The president and the seniors made the cultural festival and the sports festival amazing!
sore tomo shibonjau no
それともしぼんじゃうの？
Or will it wither away?
watashi no mirai shiritakunakute
私の未来知りたくなくて
I don't want to know
about my future,
Yeah!
But I heard that the previous cultural festival was even more amazing.
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
suppai
すっぱい…
Sour...
Oh, I heard about that!
It was the legendary one where 2-C won everything, right?
Yeah! It was all because of the Palmtop something...
suki da kedo nakeru yo
好きだけど泣けるよ
I love it, but I feel like crying.
Palmtop something?
You mean the Palmtop Tiger?
The one who brings you good luck?
That person really existed?
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish would
turn orange soon
Yeah, the Palmtop Tiger!
She went to this school last year.
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
Moreover, she's Takasu-senpai's girlfriend!
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams
just swell-
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
Today, I tried eating an orange
orenji kyou mo
オレンジ　今日も
There's something in this world that nobody has seen yet.
tabete mita kedo
食べてみたけど
but it was so sour I cried.
mada suppakute naita
まだすっぱくて　 泣いた
It's something gentle, and very sweet.
I couldn't leave it behind
like I have been,
watashi mitai de nokosenai kara
私みたいで残せないから
And if you ever laid eyes on it,
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
you would yearn for it.
suki da yo
好き だ よ
I love it.
That's why no one has ever seen it.
suppai
すっぱい
It's Sour.
The world hid it so that no one could get their hands on it easily.
nakeru yo
泣けるよ
I feel like crying.
suki da yo suki da yo
好き だ よ 好き だ よ
I love it... I love it.
However, someday, someone will find it.
The one person who is destined to find it will be able to find it.
What?
I was planning to surprise you...
It seems like you grew.
Not even a millimetre.
I'm sorry.
Listen...
I love you.
Tai-
W-Why would you say something embarrassing like that?!
You should've waited for a better mood or something...
That's just how it is.