Street No. 10
"Old Men and Holes"
And Yet the Town Moves
People sometimes pray to a being they cannot see
or depend on something unclear.
A god. Buddha. The mysterious powers of the cosmos.
And, if their prayers come true,
they believe in the unknown power.
If not, they think they are not praying hard enough.
Still, they believe the unknown power.
THE PROPER WAY TO WORSHIP
(TWO BOWS TWO CLAPS ONE BOW)
FIRST, BOW (BEND AT THE WAIST TO ABOUT 90 DEGREES WITH HEAD DOWN) TWICE.
NEXT, PUT TOGETHER BOTH HANDS AT YOUR CHEST, CLAP TWICE THEN PRAY.
LASTLY, BOW ONE MORE TIME.
Please... this summer, let me be in a good
relationship with Arashiyama... I mean...
DEDI-                                                             CATION
I say good relationship... but I don't mean
I'm wanting anything impure...
I mean, if you ask if I want it or not,
it's not that I don't like it or I'm rejecting it...
If it comes naturally or it just so happens
to go that way, then that's fine...
I mean, not such a loose relationship
that it just so happens to go that way...
I'm not asking for that, because I'm serious,
I mean, my feelings toward her are serious...
If I was seriously thinking impure thoughts
that would make me a pervert and...
What I want to say is, not something like that,
but um... I don't know anymore, but...
A god would probably know, and so,
in any case, I ask of you these things.
DEDI-                                                             CATION
Even before an unknown power can grant wishes,
it must first understand them.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Kurai kimochi sae
Suguni harete
Minna uki uki
Uki uki
Downtown e kuridasou
We are all targeted.
For the next 9 minutes, 16 seconds, 15 frames...
your eyes will leave your body and enter
a strange world far beyond your comprehension.
Neither real nor imaginary, but an unknown place.
Welcome to Maruko Shopping District.
Tokyo
Live Breaking News
In a plot of land within Tokyo
A MYSTERIOUS HOLE!?
Ah, are you able to see it?
As you can see, in various spots on this open plot,
round holes were found late last night.
Tokyo
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
Live Breaking News
In a plot of land within Tokyo
A MYSTERIOUS HOLE!?
This plot of land is actually planned for the
building of a new high-rise apartment,
and so it is said that there was conflict between
locals opposed to the construction and the workers.
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
There are also reports that last night,
people heard something like the screams of a woman.
Chiba
Who, with what purpose,
and how did this person create these holes?
The mystery keeps getting deeper.
That's all from the scene.
Sun Sun
Wide
From the scene was Reporter Suekane.
In the studio we have an expert
in hole-digging, Professor Majima.
Hole-Digging Expert
Professor
Taichi Majima
Professor, please share your expertise.
Yes, I've dug many holes until now,
but in order to create such a hole
so close to being a perfect sphere so cleanly,
Mom! I spilled it!
but in order to create such a hole
so close to being a perfect sphere so cleanly,
you would need extensive machinery...
What's wrong, Sis?
So that means a person who owns such special
equipment would be the one who created these holes.
I-it's nothing.
So that means a person who owns such special
equipment would be the one who created these holes.
If you don't hurry up and eat, you'll be late again.
Yes! It came! It finally came!
Did you watch the TV this morning?!
Hey! I'm asking if you've seen it!
Senpai, you're very orange for a change.
Orange?
It means opposite of blue...
Speaking of which, you've been blue all day.
Are you on your period?
No I'm not, but...
If you know I'm not feeling well,
why can't you be even a little considerate?
But there's no time for that, you know?!
The plot of land with the mysterious holes!
That's in your neighborhood, right?
Where is it? Take me there.
No way!
What's up with you? You like things like that, don't you?
Hmph!
I love it! I knew something like this
would happen one day.
Like waking up one morning to find horns
on my head or something...
That finally happened this morning!
And the TV show proved it to me!
The one that has to go to that plot of land is me!
So, come on, take me there!
Do you hate normal life that much?!
I do.
Stupid!
You...
I don't know what you're pouting about,
but why don't you talk to me about it?
You've got nothing to lose.
Aren't we friends?
Senpai!
Hotori?
I can't take you to that plot of land!
I'm the one who made those holes!
Huh?!
You see, last night I went to the convenience
store to buy some Koala ice cream.
Oh yeah.
They don't sell those at the Green Marts
around here, do they?
Koala Ice
Strawberry
Ice Cream
What flavor did you get?
Strawberry.
So stupid! I told you vanilla is the best!
That's beside the point! Listen to me!
So I was walking home—
With your stupid face...
Shut up and listen!
So, just as I got to the plot of land in question...
What is this?
A laser gun?
For a child's toy, it's pretty heavy.
There's no trigger nor barrel...
Maybe it's a replica from a movie or something.
Bang!
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
Model Room
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
Oh... Th-this, right?
You're telling me to give it back, I'm sure, most likely...
Of course I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
If you'd like you can have my ice cream, too.
It's praised as the best tasting on this Earth, yes.
I'm not sure where your mouth is, but, yes...
Please eat before it melts—
It's here! Another one!
It's here! This time, a black one is here!
Wh-wh-wh-who should I return it to...?
Won't one of you settle for ice cream?
You won't settle, right? I'm sure, most likely...
A weapon?!
Oh... I did it again.
And so on that plot of land, me, the holes,
and my ice cream were the only ones left...
So that's what happened...
You're going to believe this sheer nonsense?
Yeah, typically I would kick you and that
would be the end of it.
Will I be punished for my sin of digging round holes?
What is that? Are you giving it to me?
No I won't! I found it yesterday.
This... is similar to the laser gun from yesterday.
This isn't as dangerous.
Give me the chopsticks you were using to eat your lunch.
This?
Watch.
What are you doing, idiot!
I'm going to get yelled at by my mom!
There, there, there. It's fine, it's fine.
No it's not fine!
Don't give me any more things to worry about!
Here!
Oh.
You're kidding! It's fixed! It's back!
This is the reason why I believed your nonsense.
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
MAST
MEN'S APPAREL                                  LIQUOR
NAKAJIMAYA                                   STORE
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
The day after I picked this up, that stuff on TV came on.
So you'd think that there is something starting to happen.
Finally, something out of the ordinary...
This strange incident...
And it all centers around me!
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
But the one who was actually in the midst of all
this and experiencing the fun stuff was you,
and I was just there to follow up behind you.
Well, that's fine too.
The fact that I had a role to play in this is plenty.
Whoa! The holes are filling up!
If you see a little grave marker
in the plot of land in Maruko City,
that may be a grave that Hotori had set up for the alien.
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
Model Room
Now everything is back to its original shape.
Thank you, Kon-senpai!
Man, thank goodness.
Units for Sale
Residence Maruko
Model Room
This is an incident that happened close to you.
Whether or not you believe it is up to you.
Bookkeeping, huh?
Can't say you're making much at all.
You were never very bright since long ago.
Before the dollar store was a liquor store,
and before that was a futon shop?
You don't have any hair!
Ignored.
Rightfully so.
I take it you're the type that can "see" me.
It seems that is the case.
What happened to your tail?
I don't know where or how you lost it,
but you must've gone through a lot...
Yoshiharu!
Hang in there!                  Yoshiharu!
Please take over my dream...
Yoshiharu!
Whenever it is, everyone can get together and com...
What is it?
Comuni...
(Komugi?!)
Flour?!
Comunu..
Konbu?
Conumu...
Do you mean,
"communication"?!
Ah... that...
Dead...
I messed up.
I couldn't say "communication,"
and so I couldn't let her know in the end...
To the end of the end...
Shame for me to be so affected.
Well, I mostly have no other regrets.
You're here to pick me up?
Oh?
It's someone else...
Ota City Fire Dept.
I get no one to pick me up?!
I don't know what kind of mistake
caused me to be this way,
but ever since then, for over 10 years,
I've been floating around.
Isn't that impressive?
I've had a lot of things going on with me too.
There you are, Koban!
Why do you always go here
and there without any permission?
Really, you're so fickle!
Why are you facing in a weird direction?
Well then, you hang in there too...
You're following something with your eyes?
Hey, hey, that's creepy!
Don't tell me you see an evil spirit or something.
Sorry I'm an evil spirit!
Come to think of it,
with animals I can see eye-to-eye, but...
No human has ever noticed me.
Even the priest at the Shinto temple is like this...
Josephine, dash!
She has no intention of running whatsoever...
If you don't exercise, I won't take you for a walk.
Yo.
There are animals that don't notice at all, huh...
So, what about that kid?
Oh yeah, that girl is really something.
How do I say it...? She's like...
"Like"?
She's like a lobster!
What kind of example is that?!
Wow... we were in sync.
You should strengthen your vocabulary...
Takeru, do you like that girl?
Th-that's not the case! You always take
the story in that direction.
Today, I thought I was going to make agedashi tofu.
But yesterday, the moment I looked away,
Hotori put it away somewhere... That tofu...
Heh... I don't know what to do with her, really...
That's fine, it's just tofu.
The guys in the shopping district were fighting again.
They're so noisy.
They should do it at their own stores.
That can't be helped. Men never stop being children.
If you were around, you would've been
raising a ruckus right along with them.
It seems... it's getting lively again.
Just like when you were around...
It's been over ten years...
If you pray to me that hard,
I may actually go to heaven, you know?
Well, good night.
Um... Oh, heave ho.
This should be good for today. You liked bananas, right?
If I remember correctly... Say... Probably...
I-it may have not been that hard...
Well, that must mean so much time has passed
that you forgot what your husband liked...
I never forgot...
You never even appear in my dreams!
You're such a heartless husband.
I came! I am here!
Well... I'm sure you're doing
what you like to do on that side.
Yeah...
Ever since I made that snarky comment
to the heavens on the day I died,
I've been doing what I please...
Well, well... It's one-sided comunucation.
Note: Yoshiharu still can't say it correctly.
Maid
Cafe
SEASIDE
Why you, stop while you still have a chance!
Kobuhei is my little brother!
You're not one to understand, are you?!
He's my little brother!
Besides, the one who named him Kobuhei is me!
Whichever way it falls, it's not going to be rewarding.
I was the one who gave you the hint!
You came in late today, too, didn't you?
Despite being tardy, you came in yawning blatantly,
so that's why the teacher got mad.
Well, you know...
I thought since it was a Monday right after
a weekend he'd go easy on me.
Of course, he wouldn't!
Yes.
No, he wouldn't.
Yes...
No, he wouldn't!
...yes.
You're really going to get held back.
Hello!
You never run out of people to talk to here.
Hey, you're going to get yelled at
by that blonde girl again.
Toshiko-chan...
Yes, ma'am.
Could you leave a cup of coffee at the table in the back?
Would this table be all right?
Yeah, thanks.
Uki...
You...! Can you see me...?
It's your own?!
Ah, so good.
The King Crab is not a crab, poko.
People sometimes pray to a being they cannot see
or depend on something unclear
And, if their prayers come true,
they believe in the unknown power.
If not, they think they are not praying hard enough.
And still they believe the unknown power.
THE PROPER WAY TO WORSHIP
(TWO BOWS TWO CLAPS ONE BOW)
FIRST, BOW (BEND AT THE WAIST TO ABOUT 90 DEGREES WITH HEAD DOWN) TWICE.
NEXT, PUT TOGETHER BOTH HANDS AT YOUR CHEST, CLAP TWICE THEN PRAY.
LASTLY, BOW ONE MORE TIME.
Please... this summer, let me be in a good
relationship with Arashiyama... I mean...
DEDI-                                                             CATION
I say good relationship...but I don't mean
I'm wanting anything impure...
I mean, if you ask if I want it or not,
it's not that I don't like it or I'm rejecting it
If it comes naturally or it just so happens
to go that way, then that's fine...
I mean, not such a loose relationship
that it just so happens to go that way...
I'm not asking for that, because I'm serious...
I mean, my feelings toward her are serious...
If I was seriously thinking impure thoughts
that would make me a pervert and...
What I want to say is, not something like that,
but um... I don't know anymore, but...
A god would probably know, and so,
in any case, I ask of you these things.
DEDI-                                                             CATION
The gods have a hard time, too.
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
Konna member rock ja ne
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Kancho kancho!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
The novel I read yesterday,
I cried because the ending was so sad.
Senpai, has that ever happened to you?
I dunno.
Have you ever cried while watching a drama?
Movie?
I'm not sure.
You're cool and collected.
Maybe.
Even someone as dauntless as you cries sometimes
because you miss your parents, right Senpai?
Right.
Wait, what are you talking about?
It's a secret.
Cafe Seaside
Street No. 11 "KON-SENPAI'S SUMMER OF BITTER TEARS"
Next, Street Number Eleven,
"Kon-senpai's Summer of Bitter Tears."
Everyone turn around and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside